I'M, UH, JERRY LUNDEGAARD.
YOU'RE JERRY LUNDEGAARD ?
YAH.
SHEP PROUDFOOT SAID--
SHEP SAID YOU'D BE HERE  AT 7:30.
WHAT GIVES, MAN ?
SHEP SAID 8:30.
WE'VE BEEN SITTING HERE AN HOUR.
HE'S PEED THREE TIMES ALREADY.
OH, I'M SURE SORRY.
SHEP TOLD ME 8:30.
IT WAS A MIX-UP, I GUESS.
YOU GOT THE CAR ?
YAH, YOU BET. IT'S OUT IN THE LOT
THERE. BRAND-NEW BURNT UMBER CIERA.
YEAH, OKAY.
WELL, SIT DOWN, THEN.
I'M CARL SHOWALTER.
THIS IS MY ASSOCIATE GAEAR GRIMSRUD.
YEAH, HOW YOU DOIN' ?  SO--
WE ALL SET
ON THIS THING, THEN ?
SURE, JERRY.  WE'RE ALL SET.
WHY WOULDN'T WE BE ?
YEAH--  NO, I'M SURE YOU ARE.
SHEP VOUCHED FOR YOU AND ALL.
I GOT EVERY CONFIDENCE
HERE IN YOU FELLAS.
I GUESS THAT'S IT, THEN.
HERE ARE THE KEYS.
NO, THAT'S NOT IT,  JERRY.
HAH ?
THE NEW VEHICLE
PLUS $40,000.
YEAH, BUT THE DEAL WAS
THE CAR FIRST,
THEN THE 40,000,
LIKE AS IF IT WAS THE RANSOM.
I THOUGHT SHEP TOLD YA.
SHEP DIDN'T TELL US MUCH, JERRY.
WELL, OKAY.
EXCEPT THAT YOU WERE
GONNA BE HERE AT 7:30.
YEAH, WELL, THAT WAS A MIX-UP, THEN.
YEAH, YOU ALREADY SAID THAT.
YEAH, BUT IT'S NOT A WHOLE
PAY-IN-ADVANCE DEAL.
SEE, I GIVE YOU
A BRAND-NEW VEHICLE IN ADVANCE,
AND THEN--
I'M NOT GONNA DEBATE YOU, JERRY.
- OKAY.
- I'M NOT GONNA SIT HERE   AND DEBATE.
I WILL SAY THIS, THOUGH. WHAT SHEP TOLD
US DIDN'T MAKE A WHOLE LOTTA SENSE.
OH, NO.  IT'S REAL SOUND.
IT'S ALL WORKED OUT.
YOU WANT YOUR OWN WIFE
KIDNAPPED.
YEAH.
YOU--
MY POINT IS,
YOU PAY THE RANSOM-- WHAT, 80,000 BUCKS ?
I MEAN, YOU GIVE US
HALF THE RANSOM, 40,000. YOU KEEP HALF.
IT'S LIKE ROBBIN' PETER
TO PAY PAUL. IT DOESN'T MAKE ANY SENSE.
OKAY.  SEE, IT'S NOT ME
PAYIN' THE RANSOM.
THE THING IS,
MY WIFE, SHE'S WEALTHY.
HER DAD, HE'S REAL WELL-OFF.
NOW, I'M IN A BIT OF TROUBLE.
WHAT KIND OF TROUBLE
YOU IN, JERRY ?
WELL, THAT'S-- THAT'S--
I'M NOT GONNA GET INTO, INTO--
SEE, I JUST NEED THE MONEY.
NOW, HER DAD, HE'S REAL WELL-OFF.
SO ?  WHY DON'T YOU JUST
ASK HIM FOR THE MONEY ?
OR YOUR FUCKIN' WIFE, YOU KNOW.
OR YOUR FUCKING WIFE, JERRY.
WELL, IT'S ALL PART OF THIS--
THEY DON'T KNOW
I NEED IT, SEE.
OKAY, SO THERE'S THAT.
AND EVEN IF THEY DID, I WOULDN'T GET IT.
SO THERE'S THAT ON TOP, THEN.
SEE, THESE ARE PERSONAL MATTERS.
- PERSONAL MATTERS ?
- YAH, PERSONAL MATTERS   THAT NEEDN'T, UH--
OKAY, JERRY.
YOU'RE TASKING US
TO PERFORM THIS MISSION, BUT YOU WON'T, UH--
YOU WON'T--
AW, FUCK IT.
LET'S TAKE A LOOK AT THAT CIERA.
[ TV: Hockey Game ]
HON ?
HI, HON.   WELCOME BACK.
HOW WAS FARGO ?
YAH.  REAL GOOD.
DAD'S HERE.
[ Game Announcer ]
...NUMBER 25  LEADS THE BADGERS...
IN GOAL PRODUCTION
WITH FIVE THIS YEAR.
HOW YOU DOIN', WADE ?
YAH, PRETTY GOOD.
WHAT YOU WATCHIN' THERE ?
GOPHERS.
WHO THEY PLAYIN' ?
OOH ! [ Grumbles ]
IS HE STAYIN' FOR SUPPER, THEN ?
YEAH, I THINK SO.
DAD, ARE YOU STAYIN' FOR SUPPER ?
[ Wade ]  WHAT ?
YEAH.
MAY I BE EXCUSED ?
HUH ?
YOU DONE THERE ?
UH-HUH.  I'M GOIN' OUT.
WHERE YOU GOING ?
JUST McDONALD'S.
BACK AT 9:30.
OKAY.
HE JUST ATE.
HE DIDN'T FINISH.
GOIN' TO McDONALD'S
INSTEAD OF FINISHIN' HERE.
HE SEE HIS FRIENDS THERE. IT'S OKAY.
IT'S OKAY, McDONALD'S ?
WHAT DO YOU THINK
THEY DO THERE ?
THEY DON'T DRINK
MILK SHAKES, I ASSURE YA.
IT'S OKAY, DAD.
WADE, HAVE YOU HAD A CHANCE
TO THINK ABOUT THAT DEAL I WAS TALKIN' ABOUT ?
THOSE 40 ACRES THERE
IN WAYZATA ?
YOU TOLD ME ABOUT IT.
YAH.  YOU SAID YOU'D
HAVE TO THINK ABOUT IT.
I UNDERSTAND IT'S A LOT OF MONEY.
IT'S A HECK OF A LOT.
WHAT'D YOU SAY YOU WERE
GONNA PUT THERE ?
A LOT. IT'S A LIMITED--
I KNOW IT'S A LOT.
I MEAN A PARKING LOT.
AH, WELL, 750,000 IS A LOT. [ Laughs ]
YEAH, WELL, IT'S A CHUNK, BUT, I THINK--
I HAD A COUPLE LOTS, LATE '50S.
LOST A LOT OF MONEY.
A LOT OF MONEY.
BUT THE DIFFERENCE-- I THOUGHT YOU
WERE GONNA SHOW IT TO STAN GROSSMAN.
HE PASSES ON THIS STUFF
BEFORE IT GETS KICKED UP TO ME.
WELL, STAN'LL SAY NO DICE.
THAT'S WHY YOU PAY HIM.
I'M ASKIN' YOU HERE, WADE.
THIS COULD WORK OUT
REAL GOOD FOR ME AND JEAN AND SCOTTY.
JEAN AND SCOTTY
NEVER HAVE TO WORRY.
- WHERE IS PANCAKES HOUSE ?
- WHAT ?
WE STOP AT PANCAKES HOUSE.
WHAT, ARE YOU NUTS ?
WE HAD PANCAKES FOR BREAKFAST.
GOTTA GO TO A PLACE WHERE I CAN GET
A SHOT AND A BEER  AND STEAK, MAYBE.
NOT MORE FUCKIN' PANCAKES.
COME ON.
OH, COME ON, MAN !
OKAY, HERE'S AN IDEA.
WE COULD STOP OUTSIDE OF BRAINERD.
I KNOW A PLACE THERE
WE CAN GET LAID. WHAT DO YOU THINK ?
I'M FUCKIN' HUNGRY NOW, YOU KNOW.
YEAH, YEAH.  JESUS !
I'M SAYIN' WE CAN STOP,
GET PANCAKES AND THEN
WE'LL GET LAID, ALL RIGHT ?
[ Muzak ]
[ Woman On P.A. ]
LOU KNIGHT, LINE ONE.
[ Man ]
WE SAT RIGHT HERE IN THIS ROOM...
AND WENT OVER THIS  AND OVER THIS.
YEAH, BUT THAT TRUE COAT--
I SAT RIGHT HERE AND SAID
I DIDN'T WANT ANY TRUE COAT.
YEAH, BUT I'M SAYIN'
THAT TRUE COAT,
YOU DON'T GET IT,
YOU GET OXIDATION PROBLEMS.
IT'LL COST YOU
A HECK OF A LOT MORE  THAN $500.
YOU'RE SITTIN' THERE,
YOU'RE TALKIN' IN CIRCLES.
YOU'RE TALKIN' LIKE WE
DIDN'T GO OVER THIS ALREADY.
- YEAH, BUT THIS TRUE COAT--
- WE HAD A DEAL HERE   FOR 19,500.
YOU SAT THERE AND
DARNED IF YOU DIDN'T TELL ME YOU'D GET ME THIS CAR,
THESE OPTIONS
WITHOUT THE SEALANT FOR 19,500.
ALL RIGHT, I'M NOT SAYIN'
I DIDN'T.
YOU CALLED ME 20 MINUTES AGO
AND SAID YOU HAD IT, READY TO MAKE DELIVERY !
HE SAYS, "COME ON DOWN,
GET IT. "
AND HERE YOU ARE,
AND YOU'RE WASTIN' MY TIME AND MY WIFE'S TIME AND--
AND I'M PAYIN' 19,500
FOR THIS VEHICLE HERE.
ALL RIGHT.
I'LL TALK TO MY BOSS.
SEE, THEY INSTALL THAT
TRUE COAT AT THE FACTORY. THERE'S NOTHIN' WE CAN DO.
BUT I'LL--
I'LL TALK TO MY BOSS.
THESE GUYS HERE,
THESE GUYS--
IT'S ALWAYS THE SAME.
IT'S ALWAYS MORE.
[ TV: Hockey Game ]
YOU GOIN' TO THE GOPHERS ON SUNDAY ?
OH, YOU BETCHA.
YOU WOULDN'T HAVE
AN EXTRA TICKET ?
YOU KIDDIN' ?
WELL--
HE NEVER DONE THIS BEFORE,
BUT SEEIN' AS IT'S SPECIAL
CIRCUMSTANCES AND ALL,
HE SAYS I CAN KNOCK
$100 OFF THAT TRUE COAT.
ONE HUNDRED ?
YOU LIED TO ME,
MR. LUNDEGAARD.
YOU'RE A BALD-FACED LIAR.
[ Woman Whispering ]  BUCKY, PLEASE.
A... FUCKING LIAR !
BUCKY, PLEASE.
WHERE'S MY GODDAMN CHECKBOOK ?
LET'S GET THIS OVER WITH.
WHERE IS IT ?
[ Laughing, Moaning ]
[ The Tonight Show Theme ]
[ Ed McMahon ]
FROM HOLLYWOOD,
THE TONIGHT SHOW
STARR--
I AM TALKING ABOUT
YOUR POTENTIAL.
MM-HMM.
YOU'RE NOT A "C" STUDENT.
YEAH.
YET YOU'RE GETTIN' "C" GRADES.
IT'S THAT DISPARITY THERE
THAT CONCERNS YOUR DAD AND ME.
UH-HUH.
YOU KNOW WHAT A DISPARITY IS ?
YEAH !
OKAY, WELL,
THAT'S WHY WE--
WE DON'T WANT YOU GOIN' OUT
FOR HOCKEY.
OH, MAN !  COME ON,
WHAT'S THE BIG DEAL ? IT'S JUST AN HOUR--
[ Phone Ringing ]
HOLD ON.
WHAT'S THE BIG DEAL ?
HELLO.
[ Wade ] HIYA, HON.
OH, HI, DAD.
IS JERRY AROUND ?
YAH.  HON ?  YAH, HE'S HERE, YAH.
I'LL CATCH HIM FOR YA. HON ?
YAH ?
- IT'S DAD.
- LOOK, DAD, THERE'S   NO FUCKIN' WAY THAT--
SCOTTY !
HEY, LET'S WATCH THAT LANGUAGE THERE.
HOW YOU DOIN' THERE, WADE ?
WHAT'S GOIN' ON THERE ?
UH, NOTHIN', WADE.
HOW YOU DOIN' THERE ?
STAN GROSSMAN LOOKED AT
YOUR PROPOSAL.
HE SAYS IT'S PRETTY SWEET.
NO KIDDIN'.
MIGHT BE INTERESTED.
NO KIDDIN' !
I-- I NEED THE CASH
PRETTY QUICK THERE  IN ORDER TO CLOSE THE DEAL.
COME BY 2:30.
WE'LL TALK ABOUT IT.
IF YOUR NUMBERS ARE RIGHT,
STAN SAYS IT'S PRETTY SWEET.
STAN, YOU KNOW, GROSSMAN.
YEAH.
2:30.
YAH.  OKAY.
[ Radio ]
SAY, SHEP,
HOW YOU DOIN' THERE ?
SAY, UH, YOU KNOW
THOSE TWO FELLAS...
YOU PUT ME IN TOUCH WITH
UP THERE IN FARGO ?
PUT YOU IN TOUCH
WITH GRIMSRUD.
YEAH, WELL,
HE HAD A BUDDY THERE. HE, UH--
WELL, I DON'T VOUCH FOR HIM.
WELL, THAT'S OKAY.
I VOUCH FOR GRIMSRUD.
WHO'S HIS BUDDY ?
UH, CARL SOMETHING.
NEVER HEARD OF HIM. DON'T VOUCH FOR HIM.
WELL, THAT'S OKAY.
HE'S A BUDDY OF THE GUY YOU VOUCH FOR.
SO I'M NOT WORRYIN'.
I JUST--
I WAS WONDERIN', SEE,
I GOTTA GET IN TOUCH WITH 'EM.
SEE, THIS DEAL
I NEEDED 'EM FOR, I MAY NOT NEED IT ANYMORE.
SOMETHING'S HAPPENIN', SEE.
CALL 'EM UP.
WELL, SEE, I DID THAT,
AND I HAVEN'T BEEN ABLE TO GET 'EM,
SO I THOUGHT
MAYBE YOU'D KNOW AN ALTERNATE NUMBER...
OR WHAT HAVE YOU.
NOPE.
OKAY.  WELL,
REAL GOOD, THEN.
[ Radio: Rock ]
[ Coughs ]
CAN YOU CRACK A FUCKIN'
WINDOW OPEN, MAN ?
YOU KNOW, IT'S PROVEN
THAT SECONDHAND SMOKE IS CARCINOG--
UH, YOU KNOW,
A CANCER AGENT.
HEY, LOOK AT THAT:
TWIN CITIES.
THAT'S THE I.D.S. BUILDING,
THE BIG GLASS ONE.
TALLEST SKYSCRAPER
IN THE MIDWEST AFTER THE, UH,
SEARS AND, UH, CHICAGO,
OR JOHN HANCOCK BUILDING,
WHATEVER.
YOU EVER BEEN
TO MINNEAPOLIS ?
NOPE.
WOULD IT KILL YOU
TO SAY SOMETHIN' ?
I DID.
NO.  THAT'S
THE FIRST THING YOU'VE SAID IN THE LAST FOUR HOURS.
THAT'S A--
THAT'S A FOUNTAIN
OF CONVERSATION, MAN. THAT'S A GEYSER.
I MEAN, WHOA, DADDY,
STAND BACK, MAN.
SHIT.
I'M SITTIN' HERE DRIVIN'.
I'M DOING ALL THE DRIVIN', MAN.
WHOLE FUCKIN' WAY
FROM BRAINERD DRIVIN',
JUST TRYIN' TO... CHAT.
YOU KNOW, KEEP OUR SPIRITS UP,
FIGHT THE BOREDOM OF THE ROAD,
AND YOU CAN'T SAY
ONE FUCKIN' THING JUST IN THE WAY OF CONVERSATION ?
OH, FUCK IT.
I DON'T HAVE TO TALK,  EITHER, MAN.
SEE HOW YOU LIKE IT.
JUST TOTAL FUCKIN' SILENCE.
TWO COULD PLAY AT THAT GAME,
SMART GUY.
WE'LL JUST SEE
HOW YOU LIKE IT.
TOTAL SILENCE.
MR. LUNDEGAARD,
THIS IS REILLY DIEFENBACH FROM G.M.A.C.
HOW ARE YOU THIS MORNING ?
REAL GOOD. HOW YOU DOIN' ?
PRETTY GOOD, MR. LUNDEGAARD.
YOU'RE DAMN HARD TO GET ON THE PHONE.
YAH.  IT'S PRETTY DARN
BUSY HERE, BUT THAT'S THE WAY WE LIKE IT.
WELL, THAT'S FOR SURE.
NOW, I JUST NEED ON THESE LAST,
THESE FINANCING DOCUMENTS
THAT YOU SENT US,
I CAN'T READ
THE SERIAL NUMBERS OF THE VEHICLES--
YEAH, BUT I ALREADY GOT THE--
IT'S OKAY.
THE LOANS ARE IN PLACE.
I ALREADY GOT THE-- THE WHAT ?  THE--
THE 320,000.
YOU GOT THE MONEY LAST MONTH.
YEAH.  SO WE'RE ALL SET THEN.
YEAH, BUT THE VEHICLES THAT YOU'RE BORROWING ON,
I JUST CAN'T READ
THE SERIAL NUMBERS ON YOUR APPLICATION.
MAYBE IF YOU CAN JUST
READ THEM TO ME.
YEAH, BUT THE DEAL'S
ALREADY DONE. I ALREADY GOT THE MONEY.
WE HAVE AN AUDIT HERE.
I JUST HAVE TO KNOW THAT THESE VEHICLES...
YOU'RE FINANCING
WITH THIS MONEY, THAT THEY REALLY EXIST.
[ Laughs ]
YEAH, WELL, THEY EXIST, ALL RIGHT.
I'M SURE THEY DO,
BUT I CAN'T READ
THE SERIAL NUMBERS HERE.
SO IF YOU COULD READ ME SOME--
YAH, BUT, UH--
SEE, UM--
I DON'T HAVE THEM IN FRONT OF ME.
WHY DON'T I JUST
FAX YOU OVER A COPY ?
NO.  FAX IS NO GOOD.
THAT'S WHAT I HAVE,
AND I-- I CAN'T READ THE DARN THING.
YAH, OKAY.
I'LL HAVE MY GIRL
SEND YOU A COPY, THEN.
OKAY, BECAUSE IF I CAN'T
CORRELATE THIS NOTE WITH THE SPECIFIC VEHICLES,
THEN I GOTTA CALL BACK
THAT MONEY.
YAH.  HOW MUCH MONEY WAS THAT ?
320,000.
I GOTTA CORRELATE THAT MONEY
WITH THE CARS IT'S BEING LENT ON.
YAH, OKAY.  NO PROBLEM.
I'LL JUST FAX THAT RIGHT OVER.
NO, NO, NO.  FAX IS--
I MEAN SEND IT RIGHT OVER.
I'LL SHOOT IT RIGHT OVER TO YOU.
OKAY.  OKAY, FINE.
OKAY.  REAL GOOD, THEN.
WE'RE BACK WITH KATIE CARLSON.
HI.
NOW, BEFORE WE GET GOING HERE,
WE JUST WANNA REMIND ALL OF OUR VIEWERS AT HOME...
THAT THIS MARCH,
FOR THE SECOND YEAR IN A ROW,
KATIE AND I, ALONG WITH
TWIN CITY TRAVEL,
WILL BE LEADING
A TWO-WEEK RIVERBOAT TRIP  DOWN THE NILE.
IT'S A TERRIFIC TIME.
I KNOW YOU'VE HEARD ABOUT IT.
WE WANT ALL OF YOU
TO COME WITH.
AND THAT'S THE TRUTH.
[ Raspberry ]
[ Laughing ]
OKAY, NOW, THOSE OF YOU  THAT JUST JOINED US,
KATIE HERE THIS MORNING IS GONNA SHOW US HOW TO MAKE...
[ Thumping ]
HOLIDAZZLE EGGS
OURSELVES AT HOME.
NOW, KATIE,  I GOTTA ADMIT.
WHAT ?
I WAS A LITTLE BIT SURPRISED
WHEN I FIRST PICKED THIS UP.
THIS IS AN EMPTY EGG.
THAT'S RIGHT, DALE.
WELL, HOW DO YOU GET THE--  THERE WAS AN EGG IN HERE.
YEAH.
WELL, I DON'T--
HOW DO YOU--
I MEAN, YOU DON'T HAVE
AN EMPTY CHICKEN SOMEWHERE  THAT LAYS EMPTY EGGS.
NO, NO.  I GUARANTEE THIS WAS
AN HONEST TO GOODNESS, GREAT--
[ Screaming ]
[ Straining ]
[ Screams ]
[ Jean Whimpering ]
UNGUENT.
WHAT ?
I NEED UNGUENT.
[ Screaming ]
NO.
[ Sobbing ]
[ Banging On Door ]
[ Carl ] YOU WANNA DO IT ?
[ Gaear ]  OKAY.
SHIT.
[ Clang ]
[ Screaming ]
NO !  OH, NO !
HOW ARE YOU, STAN ?
HOW YOU DOIN', WADE ?
GOOD TO SEE YOU AGAIN,
JERRY.
IF THESE NUMBERS ARE RIGHT,
THIS LOOKS PRETTY SWEET.
OH, THOSE NUMBERS ARE RIGHT,
ALL RIGHT.  BELIEVE ME.
THIS IS DOABLE.
CONGRATULATIONS, JER.
YAH, THANKS, STAN.
IT'S A PRETTY, UH--
WHAT KIND OF FINDER'S FEE
WERE YOU LOOKIN' FOR ?
- HUH ?
- THE FINANCIALS ARE    PRETTY THOROUGH, SO...
THE ONLY THING WE DON'T KNOW
IS YOUR FEE.
MY FEE ?
WADE, WHAT THE HECK
ARE YOU TALKIN' ABOUT ?
STAN AND I ARE OKAY.
YAH ?
WE'RE GOOD TO LOAD IN.
YAH.
BUT WE NEVER TALKED ABOUT
YOUR FEE FOR BRINGING IT TO US.
NO !  BUT, WADE, SEE,
I WAS BRINGING YOU THIS DEAL...
FOR YOU TO LOAN ME
THE MONEY TO PUT IN.
IT'S MY DEAL HERE, SEE.
JERRY, WE THOUGHT YOU WERE
BRINGING US AN INVESTMENT.
- YAH, RIGHT.
- YOU'RE SAYIN'--
WHAT ARE YOU SAYIN' ?
YOU'RE SAYIN' WE PUT IN
ALL THE MONEY, AND YOU COLLECT WHEN IT PAYS OFF.
[ Laughing ]
NO, NO.  BUT I-- I'D--
I'D PAY YOU BACK
THE PRINCIPAL AND INTEREST.
HECK, I'D-- I'D GO...
ONE OVER PRIME ?
WE'RE NOT A BANK, JERRY.
IF I WANTED BANK INTEREST ON 750,000,
I'D GO TO MIDWEST FEDERAL,
TALK TO OLD BILL DIEHL.
HE'S AT NORSTAR.
HE'S AT--
NO, NO !  BUT, SEE, I--
[ Nervous Laughter ]
I DON'T NEED A FINDER'S FEE.
I NEED--
A FINDER'S FEE'S,
WHAT, TEN PERCENT ?
HECK, THAT'S NOT
GONNA DO IT FOR ME. I NEED THE PRINCIPAL.
WELL, JERRY, WE'RE NOT JUST
GONNA GIVE YA $750,000.
WHAT THE HECK
WERE YOU THINKIN' ?
IF I'M ONLY GETTIN'
BANK INTEREST, I WANT COMPLETE SECURITY.
HECK, F.D.I.C.
I DON'T SEE NOTHIN' LIKE THAT HERE.
YEAH, BUT I--
OKAY, I--
I GUARANTEE YOU YOUR MONEY BACK.
I'M NOT TALKIN' ABOUT
YOUR DAMN WORD, JERRY. JEEZ !  WHAT THE HECK--
WE'RE NOT A BANK, JERRY.
WELL, LOOK, I DON'T WANNA
CUT YOU OUT OF THE LOOP,
BUT THIS HERE'S A GOOD DEAL.
I ASSUME, IF YOU'RE
NOT INTERESTED,
YOU WON'T MIND
IF WE MOVE IN ON IT... INDEPENDENTLY.
[ Sighs ]
[ Door Alarm Beeping ]
DAMN IT !
[ Shrieks ]
HON !
GOT THE GROCERIES !
YEAH, WADE, HI.
IT'S JERRY.  I--
[ Frantic ]
WADE, IT'S JERRY. I DON'T KNOW WHAT TO DO.
IT'S JEAN.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT TO DO.
IT'S MY WIFE.
[ Sobbing ]
YEAH, WADE, I--
IT'S JERRY.  I--
[ Firm ]
WADE, IT'S JERRY.  I--
WE GOTTA TALK.
IT'S SOMETHING--  OH, JEEZ.
IT'S TERRIBLE.
[ Woman ]
HELLO.
UH, UH--
WADE GUSTAFSON, PLEASE.
[ Jean Whimpering ]
[ Sobbing ]
SHUT THE FUCK UP,
OR I'LL THROW YOU
BACK INTO THE TRUNK, YOU KNOW.
JESUS.  MORE THAN I'VE
HEARD YOU SAY ALL WEEK.
[ Siren Wailing ]
AH, SHIT.
OH, THE TAGS.
ALL RIGHT,
IT'S JUST THE TAGS.
I NEVER PUT MY TAGS
ON THE CAR.
ALL RIGHT, DON'T WORRY.
I'LL TAKE CARE OF THIS.
ALL RIGHT,
JUST KEEP IT STILL BACK THERE, LADY,
OR ELSE WE'RE GONNA HAVE TO,
YOU KNOW, TO SHOOT YOU.
HEY, I'LL TAKE CARE OF THIS.
[ Door Closes ]
HOW CAN I HELP YOU,
OFFICER ?
THIS A NEW CAR,
THEN, SIR ?
OH, IT CERTAINLY IS, OFFICER.
STILL GOT THAT SMELL.
YOU'RE REQUIRED TO DISPLAY
TEMPORARY TAGS...
EITHER IN THE PLATE AREA
OR TAPED TO THE INSIDE OF THE BACK WINDOW.
CERTAINLY.
CAN I SEE YOUR LICENSE AND REGISTRATION ?
YEAH, I WAS GONNA TAPE UP
THOSE-- THE TAG.
YOU KNOW, TO BE
IN FULL COMPLIANCE, BUT, UH--
IT MUST'VE, UH--
MUST'VE SLIPPED MY MIND.
SO MAYBE THE BEST THING
TO DO...
WOULD BE TO TAKE CARE OF THAT
RIGHT HERE IN BRAINERD.
WHAT'S THIS, SIR ?
MY LICENSE AND REGISTRATION.
YEAH, I WANNA BE
IN COMPLIANCE.
I WAS JUST THINKING WE COULD
TAKE CARE OF IT RIGHT HERE...
IN BRAINERD.
PUT THAT BACK
IN YOUR POCKET, PLEASE,
AND STEP OUT OF THE CAR,
PLEASE, SIR.
[ Jean Whimpering ]
[ Jean Screaming ]
SHUT THE FUCK UP !
WHOA.
WHOA, DADDY.
YOU'LL TAKE CARE OF IT.
YOU ARE A SMOOTH-SMOOTH,
YOU KNOW.
OH, DADDY.
JUST CLEAR HIM OFF THE ROAD.
YEAH.
[ Door Opens ]
[ Straining ]
- [ Car Accelerating ]
- [ Engine Starting ]
[ Tires Screeching ]
[ Straining ]
[ Whimpering ]
[ Distant Tires Squeal ]
- [ Tires Screech ]
- [ Jean Yelps ]
[ Panting ]
[ Running Footsteps ]
[ Motor Running ]
[ Warning Bell Dinging ]
[ Snoring ]
[ Phone Ringing ]
OH, JEEZ.
HI.  IT'S MARGE.
[ Moans ]
OH, MY.  WHERE ?
YEAH ?
OH, JEEZ.
OKAY.  THERE IN A JIFF.
REAL GOOD, THEN.
OKAY.
YOU CAN SLEEP.
IT'S EARLY YET.
GOTTA GO ?
YEAH.
I'LL FIX YA SOME EGGS.
THAT'S OKAY, HON.
I GOTTA RUN.
YA GOTTA EAT A BREAKFAST,
MARGE.
I'LL FIX YA
SOME EGGS.
AW, HON, YOU CAN SLEEP.
GOTTA EAT
A BREAKFAST.
[ Clears Throat ]
I'LL FIX YA
SOME EGGS.
AW, NORM.
THANKS, HON.
TIME TO SHOVE OFF.
LOVE YA, MARGIE.
LOVE YA, HON.
HON ?
YAH ?
PROWLER NEEDS A JUMP.
[ Warning Bell Dinging ]
[ Police Radio Chatter ]
HIYA, LOU.
WHOO !  WHATCHA GOT THERE ?
MARGIE, THOUGHT YOU MIGHT
NEED A LITTLE WARM-UP.
THANKS A BUNCH.
SO WHAT'S THE DEAL NOW ?
GARY SAYS TRIPLE HOMICIDE ?
YEAH.  LOOKS PRETTY BAD.
TWO OF 'EM ARE OVER HERE.
WHERE IS EVERYBODY ?
WELL--
IT'S COLD, MARGIE.
WATCH YOUR STEP, MARGIE.
AH, JEEZ.  SO--
AH, JEEZ !
HERE'S THE SECOND ONE !
IT'S IN THE HEAD
AND THE HAND THERE.
I GUESS THAT'S A DEFENSIVE WOUND.
OH, YAH ?
WHERE'S
THE STATE TROOPER ?
BACK THERE A GOOD PIECE
IN THE DITCH NEXT TO HIS PROWLER.
OKAY.  SO WE GOT A TROOPER
PULL SOMEONE OVER,
WE GOT A SHOOTING,
THESE FOLKS DRIVE BY,
THERE'S A HIGH-SPEED
PURSUIT, ENDS HERE,
AND THEN THIS
EXECUTION-TYPE DEAL.
YAH.
I'D BE VERY SURPRISED
IF OUR SUSPECT WAS FROM BRAINERD.
YAH.
AND I'LL TELL YA WHAT.
FROM HIS FOOTPRINT,
HE LOOKS LIKE A BIG FELLA.
YOU SEE SOMETHIN' DOWN THERE,
CHIEF ?
NO.  I JUST THINK
I'M GONNA BARF.
JEEZ.
YOU OKAY, MARGIE ?
YEAH, I'M FINE.
IT'S JUST MORNING SICKNESS.
WELL, THAT PASSED.
YAH ?
YEAH.   NOW I'M HUNGRY AGAIN.
YOU HAVE BREAKFAST YET,
MARGIE ?
OH, YAH.
NORM MADE SOME EGGS.
YAH ?
WELL--
WHAT NOW DO YOU THINK ?
LET'S GO TAKE A LOOK
AT THAT TROOPER.
THERE'S DIFFERENT FOOTPRINTS HERE, LOU.
YAH ?
YAH.  THIS GUY'S SMALLER
THAN HIS BUDDY.
OH, YAH ?
FOR PETE'S SAKE.
HOW'S IT LOOK, MARGE ?
WELL, HE'S GOT HIS GUN
ON HIS HIP THERE,
AND... HE LOOKS LIKE
A NICE ENOUGH GUY.
TSK.  IT'S A REAL SHAME.
YAH.
- DIDN'T MONKEY WITH
HIS CAR THERE, DID YA ? - NO WAY.
WELL, SOMEBODY
SHUT HIS LIGHTS.
I GUESS THE LITTLE GUY
SAT IN THERE, WAITING  FOR HIS BUDDY TO COME BACK.
YEAH, IT WOULD'VE BEEN
COLD OUT HERE.
HECK, YEAH.
YOU THINK IS DAVE OPEN YET ?
DAVE ?
OH, YOU DON'T THINK
HE'S MIXED UP IN--
OH, NO, NO.
I JUST WANNA GET NORM SOME NIGHT CRAWLERS.
DID YOU LOOK
IN HIS CITATION BOOK ?
YEAH.  LAST VEHICLE
HE WROTE IN...
WAS A TAN CIERA
AT 2:18 A.M.
[ Sniffing ]
UNDER PLATE NUMBER, HE PUT "D.L.R."
I FIGURE
THEY STOPPED HIM OR...
SHOT HIM BEFORE HE COULD FINISH FILLING OUT THE TAG NUMBER.
UH-HUH.
SO I GOT THE STATE
LOOKING FOR A CIERA WITH A TAG STARTIN' D.L.R.
THEY DON'T GOT NO MATCH YET.
I'M NOT SURE THAT I
AGREE WITH YOU 100%...
ON YOUR POLICE WORK THERE,
LOU.
YAH ?
YAH.
I THINK THAT VEHICLE THERE
PROBABLY HAD DEALER PLATES.
D.L.R. ?
OH.
JEEZ.
SAY, LOU.
D'YOU HEAR THE ONE ABOUT
THE GUY COULDN'T AFFORD PERSONALIZED PLATES...
SO HE WENT AND
CHANGED HIS NAME TO "J3L 2404" ?
YAH.  THAT'S A GOOD ONE.
[ Wade ]
LOOK, ALLS I KNOW IS,
YOU GOT A PROBLEM,
YOU CALL A PROFESSIONAL !
NO !  THEY SAID NO COPS.
THEY WERE DARN CLEAR ON THAT, WADE.
THEY SAID, "YOU CALL YOUR COPS,
AND WE'RE GONNA SHOOT-- "
OF COURSE THEY'RE
GONNA SAY THAT !
WHERE'S MY PROTECTION ?
THEY GOT JEAN HERE.
I GIVE THESE
SONS OF BITCHES $1 MILLION,
WHERE'S MY GUARANTEE
THEY'RE GONNA LET HER GO ?
WELL, THEY--
$1 MILLION IS A LOT OF DAMN MONEY.
YEAH, BUT THINK THIS--
THERE THEY ARE. THEY GOT MY DAUGHTER.
THINK THIS THING THROUGH
HERE, WADE. YOU GIVE 'EM WHAT THEY WANT,
WHY WON'T THEY LET HER GO ?
YOU GOTTA LISTEN TO ME
ON THIS ONE, WADE.
AH, HECK.
YOU DON'T KNOW.
YOU'RE JUST
WHISTLING DIXIE HERE.
I'M SAYIN' THE COPS,
THEY CAN ADVISE US ON THIS.
I'M SAYIN' CALL A PROFESSIONAL.
NO !  NO COPS !
[ Grumbles ]
THAT'S FINAL.
THIS IS MY DEAL HERE, WADE.
[ Grumbles ]
JEAN IS MY WIFE HERE.
I GOTTA TELL YOU, WADE.
I'M LEANING TO JERRY'S  VIEWPOINT HERE.
WELL--
WE GOTTA PROTECT JEAN. THESE--
WE'RE NOT HOLDING
ANY CARDS HERE, WADE.
THEY GOT 'EM ALL,
SO THEY CALL THE SHOTS.
YOU'RE DARN TOOTIN'.
AH, DAMN IT !
I'M TELLIN' YA.
WELL, WHY-- WHY DON'T WE--
STAN, I'M THINKIN'
WE SHOULD OFFER 'EM A HALF-MILLION, OKAY ?
NOW, COME ON HERE !
NO WAY, WADE !  NO WAY !
WE'RE NOT HORSE TRADIN' HERE, WADE.
YEAH.
WE GOTTA JUST BITE THE BULLET ON THIS THING.
SO, UH, WHAT'S THE NEXT STEP
HERE, JERRY ?
THEY'RE GONNA CALL ME UP
AND GIVE ME INSTRUCTIONS FOR A DROP.
I'M SUPPOSED TO HAVE THE MONEY READY TOMORROW.
DAMN IT !
[ Punching Keys, Beeping ]
HOW WAS EVERYTHING TODAY ?
YAH.  REAL GOOD, NOW.
[ Grumbles ]
HOW YOU DOIN' ?
OKAY.  NOW, WE'LL
GET THE MONEY TOGETHER.
DON'T WORRY ABOUT IT,
JERRY.
NOW, DO YOU WANT ANYONE
AT HOME WITH YA TILL THEY CALL ?
NO.  I--  THEY DON'T WANT--
THEY WERE JUST SUPPOSED
TO BE DEALING WITH ME. THEY WERE REAL CLEAR.
YEAH.
YOU KNOW, THEY SAID NO ONE LISTENIN' IN.
THEY'LL BE WATCHIN',
YOU KNOW.
MAYBE IT'S ALL BULL,
BUT LIKE YOU SAID, STAN, THEY'RE CALLIN' THE SHOTS.
OKAY.  NOW, IS, UH,
IS SCOTTY GONNA BE ALL RIGHT ?
YEAH, JEEZ, SCOTTY.
YEAH.  I'LL GO TALK TO HIM.
[ Horn Honking ]
[ Knocking, Door Opens ]
HOW YOU DOIN' THERE,
SCOTTY ?
[ Sobs ]
DAD, WHAT ARE THEY DOIN' ?
WHAT DO YOU THINK THEY'RE DOIN' WITH MOM ?
IT'S OKAY, SCOTTY.
THEY'RE NOT GONNA
WANNA HURT HER ANY.
THESE MEN, THEY--
THEY JUST WANT MONEY.
YEAH, WHAT IF SOMETHIN' GOES WRONG, DAD, AND THEN--
NO, NO.
NOTHING'S GOIN' WRONG HERE.
GRANDDAD AND I, WE'RE, UM--
WE'RE MAKIN' SURE
THIS GETS HANDLED RIGHT.
I REALLY THINK WE SHOULD
CALL THE COPS HERE.
NO, NO.  NO ONE CAN KNOW
ABOUT THIS THING.
WE GOTTA PLAY BALL
WITH THESE GUYS.
YOU ASK STAN GROSSMAN,
HE'LL TELL YOU THE SAME THING.
YEAH, BUT, DAD--
WE'RE GONNA  GET MOM BACK FOR YA,
BUT WE GOTTA PLAY BALL,
YOU KNOW ?
THAT'S THE DEAL HERE.
SO IF--
IF LORRAINE CALLS OR SYLVIA,
YOU JUST SAY
MOM'S DOWN IN FLORIDA WITH PEARL AND MARTY.
THAT'S THE BEST
WE CAN DO HERE.
[ Screaming ]
- WHOA.
- [ Panting ]
[ Carl Laughing ]
OOPS !
[ Laughing ]
[ Jean Crying ]
[ Carl Laughing ]
LUNCHTIME !
THIS CAME IN FOR YOU, MARGE.
RON, HI.
WARD, CAROL.
OH, JANIE, TWO MORE OF THOSE SKIN SO SOFT, PLEASE.
SURE THING.
HIYA, HON.
I BROUGHT YOU SOME LUNCH, MARGIE.
WHAT ARE THOSE, NIGHT CRAWLERS ?
YAH.
AW, THANKS, HON.
YOU BET. THANKS FOR LUNCH.
OH, YAH.
LOOKS PRETTY GOOD.
WHAT DO WE GOT HERE, ARBY'S ?
UH-HUH.
HOW'S THE PAINTIN' GOIN' ?
PRETTY GOOD.
FOUND OUT THE HAUPTMANNS
ARE ENTERING A PAINTING THIS YEAR.
AW, HON,
YOU'RE BETTER THAN THEM.
THEY'RE REAL GOOD.
THEY'RE GOOD, NORM,
BUT YOU'RE BETTER THAN THEM.
NAH.  YOU THINK SO ?
[ Kiss ]
YOU GOT ARBY'S ALL OVER ME.
[ Knock On Door ]
HEY YA, NORM. HOW'S THE PAINTIN' GOIN' ?
NOT TOO BAD, YOU KNOW.
HOW WE DOIN'
ON THAT VEHICLE ?
WELL, NO MOTELS REGISTERED
ANY TAN CIERA LAST NIGHT,
BUT THE NIGHT BEFORE,
TWO MEN CHECKED INTO THE BLUE OX,
REGISTERING A CIERA
AND LEAVING THE TAG SPACE BLANK.
JEEZ, THAT'S A GOOD LEAD.
YAH.
BLUE OX.
THAT'S THAT TRUCKERS' JOINT OUT THERE ON I-35 ?
YAH.  OWNER WAS ON
THE DESK THEN.
SAID THESE TWO
HAD COMPANY.
- OH, YEAH ?
- YAH.
[ Girl ]
YEAH, WE BOTH DID. SHE WENT TO COLLEGE TOO.
[ Second Girl ]
I WENT TO NORMANDALE FOR ABOUT A YEAR AND A HALF.
- YAH.  THAT'S WHERE WE MET.
- BUT I DROPPED OUT, THOUGH.
YAH, SHE DROPPED.
SO WHERE YOU GIRLS FROM ?
CHASKA.
LE SUEUR.
BUT I WENT TO HIGH SCHOOL
IN WHITE BEAR LAKE. GO BEARS.
OKAY.  I WANT YOU TO TELL ME
WHAT THESE FELLAS LOOKED LIKE.
WELL, THE LITTLE GUY, HE WAS KINDA FUNNY-LOOKIN'.
IN WHAT WAY ?
I DON'T KNOW.
JUST FUNNY-LOOKIN'.
CAN YOU BE
ANY MORE SPECIFIC ?
I COULDN'T REALLY SAY.
HE WASN'T CIRCUMCISED.
WAS HE FUNNY-LOOKIN'
APART FROM THAT ?
YAH.
SO, YOU WERE HAVIN' SEX
WITH THE LITTLE FELLA, THEN.
UH-HUH.
IS THERE ANYTHING ELSE YOU CAN TELL ME ABOUT HIM ?
NO.
LIKE I SAY,
HE WAS FUNNY-LOOKIN'.
MORE THAN MOST PEOPLE, EVEN.
WHAT ABOUT  THE OTHER FELLA ?
HE WAS A LITTLE OLDER.
YOU KNOW, HE LOOKED LIKE THE MARLBORO MAN.
OH, YAH ?
YAH, BUT MAYBE I'M SAYIN' THAT, YOU KNOW,
'CAUSE HE SMOKED A LOT OF MARLBOROS.
UH-HUH.
LIKE A SUBCONSCIOUS TYPE OF THING.
OH, YAH, THAT CAN HAPPEN.
YAH.
HEY, THEY SAID THEY WERE GOING TO THE TWIN CITIES.
OH, YAH ?
YAH.  IS THAT USEFUL TO YOU ?
OH, YOU BETCHA, YAH.
YAH.
[ Carl ] COME ON !  GODDAMN IT !
[ Thumping ]
[ Banging On TV ]
JESUS CHRIST.
COME ON,
YOU FUCKIN' SHIT BOX.
BE HERE FOR DAYS.
GODDAMN IT ! NOTHIN' TO DO !
[ Hitting Continues ]
FUCKIN' TV DOESN'T EVEN--
DAMN IT !  COME ON !
PLUG ME IN, MAN ! GIMME A FUCKIN' SIGNAL !
GODDAMN IT !
[ Scoffs ]
UNBELIEVABLE !
COME ON !
GOD !
[ Smack ]
FUCK !  COME ON !
PLUG ME INTO THE OZONE, BABY !
COME ON !  COME ON !
[ Hitting ]
FUCK !  FUCK !
[ Narrator ]
THE BARK BEETLE CARRIES THE WORM TO ITS NEST,
WHERE IT WILL
FEED ITS YOUNG FOR UP TO SIX MONTHS.
IN THE SPRING,
THE LARVAE HATCH,  AND THE CYCLE BEGINS AGAIN.
WELL--
I'M TURNIN' IN, NORM.
OH, YAH ?
HERE IT IS THROWING OFF
THE LARVAL ENVELOPE.