Is to love rendering aen
The World has changed...
Han mathon ne nen
I feel it in the water...
Han mathon ne chae
I feel it in the Earth...
A han nostron ned wilith
I smell it in the air...
Much that once was is lost,
for none now live
It began with the forging
of the great Rings...
Three were given to the Elves
inmortal, wisest and fairest of all beings.
Seven to the Dwarf Lords...
Great miners and craftsmen
of the mountain halls
And nine...
Nine rings were gifted
to the race of Men...
who above all else desire power
For within these Rings was bound
the strength and will to govern each race.
But they were all of them deceived...
for another ring was made
in the Land of Mordor
in the fires of Mount Doom
The Dark Lord Sauron...
forged in secret a Master Ring
to control all others
and into this ring he cored his cruelty, his malice,
and his will to dominate all life...
One Ring to rule them all.
One by one,
free lands of Middle Earth
fell to the Power of the Ring.
But there were some
who resisted...
A last Alliance of Men and Elves
marched against the armys of Mordor...
and on the slopes of Mount Doom
they fought for the freedom of Middle Earth.
Victory was near
but the power of the ring
could not be undone...
It was in this moment...
when all hope had faded...
that Isildur, son of the King
took up his father's sword.
"Sauron"
the enemy of the free peoples
of Middle Earth
was defeated
The ring passed to Isildur,
who has this one chance
to destroy Evil forever
but the hearts of the men
are easily corrupted
And the ring of the power...
has a will of its own
It betrayed Isildur,
to his death
And some things
that should not have been forgotten
were lost
History became legend...
Legend became myth...
and for 2,500 years
the ring passed out of all knowledge.
Until
when chance came
it ensnared a new bearer
My precious... my own...
The ring came to the creature Gollum,
who took it deep into the tunnels
of The Misty Mountains,
and there it consumed him
It came to me, my own!
My love, my precious!
The ring brought Gollum
unnatural long life
For 500 years
it poisoned his mind,
and in the gloom of Gollum's cave it waited.
Darkness crept back into the forests of the world.
Rumor grew of a shadow in the East,
whispers of a nameless fear,
and the Ring of Power perceived that its time had come
It abbandoned Gollum
but something happenned then
the ring did not intend.
It was picked up by the most unlikely creature imaginable
A Hobbit... Bilbo Baggins,
of the Shire
Lost!
I lost my precious!
For the time will soon come
when Hobbits will shape the fortunes of all
You're late!
A wizard is never late,
Frodo Baggins,
nor is he early. He arrives precisely when he means to.
It's wonderful to see you, Gandalf
You didn't think I'd miss
your Uncle Bilbo's birthday.
What news of the outside world?
Tell me everything
Everything?
You're far too eager and curious for a hobbit
First and natural...
Well, what can I tell you?
Life in the wide world goes on,
much as it has this past age,
full of its own comings and goings, scarcely aware
of the existence of the Hobbits
For which I am very grateful
Ah... the long expected party...
How is the old rascal?
I hear it's going to be a party
of special magnificence
You know Bilbo
He has the whole place in an uproar
- That's a pleasant
- Half the Shire has been invited
- Goodness
-He's up to something.
All right, then keep your secrets
Before you came a long way,
Bagginses were very well thought of
- Indeed
- Never had any adventures or did anything unexpected
If you're referring to the incident with the dragon,
I was barely evolved
All I did was give your uncle
a little nudge out of the door
Whatever you did
You've been officially labeled a disturber of the peace
Gandalf, Gandalf!
Fireworks!
Gandalf! Gandalf!
Fireworks! Gandalf!
Gandalf, I'm glad you're back
So am I, dear boy
So am I...
No, thank you!
We don't want any more visitors,
well-wishers or distant relations!
And what about very old friends?
Gandalf?
Bilbo Baggins
My dear Gandalf!
Good to see you...
One hundred eleven years old
Could you believe it?
You haven't aged a day
Come on, come in!
Welcome, welcome!
Tea? or maybe something a little stronger?
I've got couple of bottles of the Old Winyards left
1926. Very good year!
Almost as old as I am!
It was laid down by my father
What say we open one?
Just tea, thank you!
I was expecting you last week,
but you come and go as you please
thus to be always
I am afraid that badly I am prepared
single we have chicken fried and cucumbers
is a little cheese and
is not sufficient
we have frambuesa jelly, apple pie
but I am afraid that
are no great desserts we do not have sufficient
I found a little spongy pie
I can make you some eggs if you like... Gandalf?
Just tea, thanks!
Ah, right!
You don't... if...
No... not at all!
I'm not at home!
I've got to get away from
these confounded relatives!
Hanging on the bell all day
never giving me a moment's peace!
I want to see mountains again, mountains! Gandalf
And then find somewhere quite
where I can finish my book.
Oh! Tea!
So you mean to go through with your plans?
Yes, Yes!
All the arrangements are made.
Open it
- Frodo suspects something!
- Of course he does! He's a Baggins!
Not some blockheaded Bracegirdle from Hardbottle!
You will tell him, won't you?
Yes, yes!
He's very fond of you
I know
He'd probably come with me
if I asked him
I think in his heart
Frodo's still in love with the Shire
The woods... and fields... little rivers
I'm old Gandalf!
I know I don't look it,
but I'm beginning to feel it in my heart
I feel thin!
Sort of stretched like...
butter stretched over too much bread!
I need a holiday!
A very long holiday...
And I don't expect I shall return
In fact I mean not to.
The old toby,
the finest weed in the south farthing
Gandalf my old friend
this will be a night to remember
Fat Golberg, glad to see you
welcome, welcome!
Go on, Sam, ask Rosie for a dance
Uhmm... I think I'll just have another ale!
No, you don't
Go home
So there I was...
at the mercy of 3 monstrous Trolls
And they were all arguing amongst themselves
about how they were going to cook us
Whether they would mince us, or sit on us,
and squash us to jelly
they spent so much time arguing that
how and because
And they spent so much time arguing,
that sunlight crept over the top of the trees...
And turned them all to stone!
Quick!
Oh! Off we go!
No, no! The big one, big one!
- Done!
- Ypu're supposed to stick it in the ground!
- It is in the ground!
- Outside
- That was your idea!
Bilbo, watch out for the dragon!
Dragon?
Nonsense, there hasn't been a dragon
in these parts for a thousand years!
- That was good
- Let's get another one!
Meriadoc Brandybuck and Peregrin Took
I might have known
Speech, Bilbo! Speech!
Speech!
My dear Bagginses, and Boffins...
Tooks and Brandybucks
Grubbs! Chubbs!
Hornblowers! Bolgers!
Bracegirdles! Proudfoots!
Proudfeet!
Today is my 111 birthday!
Happy Birthday!
Alas. Eleventy-one years
is far too short a time
to live among such excellent,
admirable Hobbits!
I don't like
half of you half as well as I should like,
and I like
less than half of you half as well as you deserve.
I have things to do...
I've put this off far too long
I regret to announce this is the end!
I'm going now
I bid you all a very fond farewell
Good bye!
- I suppose you think that was terribly clever
- Come on, Gandalf!
Did you see their faces?
There are many magic rings in this world, Bilbo Baggins
and none of them should be used like that!
It was just a bit of fun!
Oh, you're probably right, as usual.
You will keep an eye on Frodo, won't you?
Two eyes, as often as I can spare them
I'm leaving everything to him
And what about this ring of yours?
Is that staying too?
Yes, Yes!
Take an envelope over there, on the mantlepiece
No... wait it's...
here in my pocket...
Why... isn't that... isn't that odd, now
Yes, after all, why not
Why shouldn't I keep it?
I think you should leave the ring behind, Bilbo
Is that so hard?
Well, no...
and yes!
Now it comes to it
I don't feel like parting with it, it's mine!
I found it! It came to me!
- There's no need to get angry
- Well if I'm angry, it's your fault!
It's mine!
My own
My precious
Precious? It's been call that before
But not by you
Oh, what business is it of yours
what I do with my own things!
I think that you have that ring quite long enough!
You want it for yourself!
BILBO BAGGINS!! Do not take me for
some conjuror of cheap tricks!
I'm not trying to rob you!
I'm trying to help you
All your long years, we've been friends
Trust me, as you once did
Let it go!
You're right, Gandalf
The ring must go to Frodo.
It's late
The road is long
Yes, it is time
Bilbo,
the ring is still in your pocket
I've thought of an ending for my book:
And he lived happily ever after,
to the end of his days.
And I am sure you will, my dear friend
Good bye, Gandalf
Good bye, dear Bilbo
Until our next meeting...
It's mine... my own...
my precious...
Riddles in the dark.
He's gone, hasn't he?
He talked for so long about leaving
I didn't think he'd really do it.
Bilbo's ring
He's gone to stay with the Elves
He's left you Bag End
Along with all his possessions
The ring is yours now
Put it somewhere out of sight
- Where are you going?
- There are some things that I must see to
- What things?
- Questions...
Questions that need answering
But if you've only just arrived!
I don't understand
Neither do I
Keep it secret
Keep it safe
Shire!
Baggins!
Year 3434 of the Second Age...
here follows the account of Isildur...
high King of Gondor
and the finding of the Ring of Power
It has come to me, the One Ring
which shall be an heirloom of my kingdom
All that will follow in my bloodline
shall be bound to its fate
for I shall risk no hurt to the ring!
It is precious to me...
though I abide with a great pain
Markings upon the band begin to fade
The writing wich at first was as clear
as red flame, has all but disappeared
a secret now that only fire can tell
Shire!
Baggins!
It's no Baggins around here!
They're up in Hobbiton
That way!
Is it secret?
Is it safe?
What are you doing?
Hold out your hand, Frodo!
It's quite cool
What can you see?
Can you see anything?
Nothing!
There's nothing!
Wait...
There are markings
It's some form of elvish, I can't read it
There are few who can
The language is that of Mordor,
wich I will not utter here!
Mordor...
In the common tongue it says:
"One ring to rule them all
One ring to find them
One ring to bring them all
and in the darkness, bind them!"
This is the One Ring,
forged by the Dark Lord, Sauron...
in the fires of Mount Doom...
taken by Isildur, from the hand of Sauron himself!
Bilbo found it... in Gollum's cave
Yes... for 60 years the ring layed quite...
in Bilbo's keeping...
prolonging his life...
delaying old age...
but no longer Frodo
Evil is stirring in Mordor
the ring has woken,
it's heard its Master's call
But he was destroyed!
Sauron was destroyed!
No, Frodo
The spirit of Sauron endured
His life force is bounded to the ring,
and the ring survived
Sauron has returned,
his orcs have multiplied...
His fortress of Barad-Dur is rebuilt
in the land of Mordor
Sauron needs only this ring
to cover all the lands on a second darkness!
He is seeking it,
all his thought is bent on it
The ring yearns above all else
to return to the hand of its master
They are one,
the ring and the dark lord
Frodo!
He must never find it!
All right! we put it away
We keep it hidden, we never speak of it again
No one knows it's here... do they?
Do they, Gandalf?
There is one other who knew
that Bilbo had the ring!
I've looked everywhere for the creature Gollum,
but the enemy found him first!
I don't know how long they tortured him for
But amidst the endless screams and the babble,
they discerned two words:
Shire!
Baggins!
That will lead them here!
Who goes there!
Take it, Gandalf!
Take it!
- No, Frodo!
- You must take it!
- You can not offer me this ring!
I'm giving it to you!
DON'T... tempt me, Frodo!
I dare not take it,
not even to keep it safe!
Understand Frodo...
I would use this ring from a desire to do good
But through me, it would wield a power
too great and terrible to imagine
But it cannot stay in the Shire!
No!
No, it can't!
What must I do?
You must leave. And leave quickly
Where? Where do I go?
Get out of the Shire. Head for the village of Bree
- Bree... What about you?
- I'll be waiting for you
at the Inn of the Prancing Pony
And the ring will be safe there?
I don't know Frodo
I don't have any answers
I must see the head of my order
He's both wise and powerful
Trust me Frodo, he'll know what to do!
You'll have to leave the name of Baggins
behind you, for the name is not safe outside the Shire
Travel only by day, and stay off the road!
I can cut across countries easily enough
My dear Frodo...
Hobbits really aren't basic creatures!
You can learn all there is to know
about their ways in a month,
and yet after a hundred years,
they can still surprise you
Get down!
Confounded old, Samwise Gamgee!
Have you been eavesdropping?
I haven't dropped no eaves, sir, honest
I was just cutting the grass under
the window there, if you follow me
A little late for trimming the verge, don't you think?
I heard raised voices!
What did you hear? SPEAK!!
N-n-n-nothing important!
That is I heard a great deal about a ring,
dark lord, and something about the
end of the world, but, please Mr. Gandalf,
sir, please don't hurt me
Don't turn me into anything... unnatural
No?
Perhaps not
I've thought of a better use for you
Come along, Samwise, keep up
Be careful, both of you
The enemy has many spies in his service
Birds, beasts...
Is it safe?
Never put it on. For the agent of
the Dark lord will be drawn to its power
Always remember, Frodo.
The ring is trying to get back to its master
It wants to be found
This is it
This is that?
If I take one more step,
it'll be the farthest away from home
I've ever been
Come on, Sam
You remember what Bilbo used to say?
It's a dangerous business,
Frodo, going out your door. You step out onto the road,
and if you don't keep your feet, there's
no knowing where you might be swept off to
Smoke rises from the mountain of Doom,
and the hour grows late,
and Gandalf the Grey rides to Isengard seeking my council
seeking my council
For that is why you have come, is it not?
- My old friend...
- Saruman!
You are sure of this?
Beyond any doubt
So the ring of power has been found
All these long years, it was in the Shire,
under my very nose
Yet you did not have the wits to see it
Your love of the Halflings' leaf
has clearly slowed your mind
... enough time. Time to counter Sauron if we act quickly.
Time?
What time you think that we have?
Sauron has regained much of his former strength
He cannot yet take physical form,
but his spirit has lost none of its potency
Concealed within his fortress,
the Lord of Mordor sees all
His gaze pierces cloud, shadow, earth and flesh
You know of what I speak, Gandalf
A great eye, lidless, wreathed in flame
- The eye of Sauron
He is gathering all evil to him
Very soon he will summon an army great enough
to launch an assault upon Middle Earth
You know all this?
How?
- I have seen it
A palantir is a dangerous tool, Saruman
Why?
Why should we fear to use it?
They are not all accounted for, the lost seeing stones
You do not know who else may be watching
The hour is later than you think
Sauron's forces are already moving
The nine have left Mordor
The nine?
They crossed the river Isen on Midsummer's
eve, disguised as riders in black
They've reached the Shire
They will find the ring, and kill the one that carries it
Frodo!
You do not seriously think that a hobbit
could contend with the will of Sauron?
There are none who can
Against the power of Mordor, there can be no victory
We must join with him, Gandalf
We must join with Sauron
It would be wise, my friend
Tell me, friend...
When did Saruman the wise
abandon reason for madness?
I gave you the chance of aiding me willingly,
but you have elected a way of paying!
Mr. Frodo! Frodo!
- I thought I'd lost you
- What are you talking about?
- It's just something Gandalf said
what did he say?
"Don't you lose him, Samwise Gamgee"
And I don't mean to
Sam, we're still in the Shire.
What could possibly happen?
Frodo! Merry... It's Frodo Baggins!
- Hello Frodo!
- Get of him!
What's the meaning of this?
Hold these
You've been into Farmer Maggot's crop
Hey! You get back here!...
You get out of my fields
I don't know why he's so upset
It's only a couple of carrots
And some cabbages
And then those empty bags of potatoes we left in last week
And then, the mushrooms, the week before!
Yes, Pippin, my point is,
he's clearly over reacting
Run!
Ahhh. Ohhh
I think I've broken something
Trust a Brandybuck and a Took
What? It was just a detour. A shortcut
A shortcut to what?
Mushrooms!!
that is mine!
that is precious!
is one good Sam here!
I think we should get off the road
Get off the road!
QUICK!
Silence!
What was that?
See anything?
Nothing!
What's going on?
That black rider was looking for something.
Or someone... Frodo?
Get down!
I have to leave the Shire
Sam and I must get to Bree
Right!
Right... Buckleberry Ferry. Follow me.
Hurry!
Follow me!
Run!
Get the boats out!
Frodo!
Go!
Hurry!
Run!
Jump Frodo!
... We go!
How far to the nearest crossing?
The brandywine bridge. Twenty miles
What do you want?
We're heading for the prancing pony
Hobbits. Four hobbits!
What business brings you to Bree?
We wish to stay at the inn.
Our business is our own
Alright, young sir, I meant no offence
It's my job to ask questions after nightfall.
There's talk of strange folk abroad
Can't be too careful
Excuse me
Good evening, little masters!
If you're seeking accommodation,
we've got some nice cosy,
hobbit sized rooms available... Mr...
Underhill. My name's Underhill
- Underhill...
- We're friends of Gandalf the Grey.
Can you tell him we've arrived?
Gandalf?
Oh, yes!
... I remember
Elderly chap. Big grey beard, and pointy hat
Not seen him for 6 months
What do we do now?
Sam, he'll be here. He'll come
What's that?
This, my friend, is a pint!
It comes in pints?
I'm getting one
You... already?
That fellow's done nothing but stare at you since we arrived
Excuse me.
That man in the corner. Who is he?
He's one of them rangers.
Dangerous folk, they are, wandering in the wilds
What his right name is, I've never heard,
but around here, he's known as Strider
Strider
Baggins?
Sure I know a Baggins
He's over there, Frodo Baggins!
He's my second cousin once
removed on his mother's side and...
and my cousin third quite distant...
Steady!
You cannot hide
I see you
You draw far too much attention to yourself
Mr. Underhill
What do you want?
- There is sort of trinket you carry
- I carry nothing!
Indeed. I can avoid
being seen if I wish
But to dissapear entirely.
That is a rare gift
Who are you?
Are you frightened?
Yes
Not nearly frightened enough.
I know what hunts you
Let him or I it will hurt, Strider!
You have a stout heart for a hobbit
But that will not save you
You can no longer wait for the wizard, Frodo
They're coming
What are they?
They were once men.
Great kings of men
Then Sauron the deceiver gave to them 9 rings of power
Blinded by their greed, they took them without questioning,
one by one, falling to darkness
Now they are slaves to his will
They are the Nazgul. Ring wraiths.
Neither living nor dead
At all times they feel the presence of the ring
Drawn to the power of the One
They will never stop hunting you
Where are you taking us?
Into the wild
How do we know this Strider is a friend of Gandalf?
We have no choice but to trust him
But where is he leading us?
To Rivendell, Master Gamgee, to the House of Elrond
Did you hear that? Rivendell
We're going to see the elves
Gentlemen
We do not stop 'til nightfall
- What about breakfast?
- You've already had it
We've had one, yes
What about second breakfast?
Don't think he knows about
second breakfast, Pippin
What about elevensies? Luncheon
Afternoon tea
Dinner? Supper.
He knows about them. Doesn't he?
Pippin!
The power of Isengard is at your command,
Sauron, Lord of the Earth
What orders from Mordor, my lord?
- What does the eye command?
- We have work to do!
The trees are strong, my lord
The roots go deep
Rip them all down!
This was the great watchtower of Amon Hen
We will rest here tonight
These are for you, keep them close!
I'm going to take a look!
Wait here
You want a tomato?
What is doing?
Tomatos, Sausages, golden bacon,
We kept a little to you
- Stifle this, stupids!
- Look at that, ash-gray in my tomatos!
Go!
Back you devils!
Frodo!
Strider!
Help him Strider!
He has been stabbed by a Morgul blade
This is beyond my skill
He needs elvish medicine
Hurry! We're 6 days from Rivendel
He'll never make it!
Frodo, Frodo!
Gandalf!
Mr. Frodo!?
He's going cold!
Is he going to die?
He's passing into the shadow
He'll soon become a wraith like them
They're close!
- Sam, do you know the athalus plant?
- Athalus?
- Kingsfoil
- Kingsfoil, that's a weed
- It may help to slow the poison. Hurry
What's this, a ranger, caught off his guard?
Frodo!
I am Arwen
I've come to help you
Hear my voice
Come back into the light
Who is she?
She is an elf!
He's fading
He's not going to last
We must get him to my father
- I've been looking for you for 2 days
- Where are you taking him?
There are 5 wraiths behind you
Where the other four are I do not know.
Stay with the hobbits
I'll send horses for you.
I'm the faster rider
I'll take him
What are they saying?
If I can get him across the river
the power of my people will protect him
I do not fear them
Ride hard, don't look back
What are you doing!
Those riders are still out there!