Subtitles by Insidious
I don't wanna be a product
of my environment.
I want my environment
to be a product of me.
Years ago, we had the Church.
That was only a way of
saying we had each other.
But now, I don't know.
It's a funny thing.
It put hate in your heart.
The Knights of Columbus
were real head-breakers.
True guineas.
They took over their
piece of the city.
Twenty years after an Irishman
couldn't get a fucking job...
we had the presidency.
May he rest in peace.
That's what the niggers
don't realise.
If I got one thing against the
black chappies, it's this:
No one gives it to you.
You have to take it.
Vin, don't make me have to
come down here again for this.
Won't happen again, Mr C.
Carmen's developing
into a fine young lady.
You should be proud.
You get your period yet, Carmen?
You Johnny Sullivan's kid?
-You live with your grandmother?
-Yeah.
Vin, get him a couple loaves of
bread, couple
half-gallons of milk.
Do you like Bologna and cheese?
Give him some cold cuts.
Throw some mayo in.
You like comic books?
You do good in school?
-Yeah.
-That's good. I did too.
They call that a paradox.
Just keep it. Buy
yourself some make-up.
You ever wanna earn a little extra
money, you come by L Street.
You know where I am on L Street?
Good.
-Good boy.
-Thanks.
To you, O Lord, we commend the
soul of Alphonsus, your servant.
In the sight of this
world, he is now dead.
Forgive whatever sins he committed
through human weakness.
Amen.
The Church wants
you in your place.
Kneel, stand, kneel, stand.
If you go for that sort of thing,
I don't know what to do for you.
A man makes his own way.
No one gives it to you.
You have to take it. Non seveium.
-James Joyce.
-Smart, Colin.
Guineas from the North
End, down Providence...
tried to tell me what to do.
And, uh...something maybe
happened to them.
Maybe...uh like that.
Jeez. She fell funny.
Francis, you really
should see somebody.
When you decide to be
something, you can be it.
That's what they don't
tell you in Church.
When I was your
age, they would say
we could become cops or criminals.
Today what I'm saying
to you is this:
When you're facing a loaded gun...
what's the difference?
Hmm? That's my boy.
Terminal ballistics is the
study of a projectile...
as it hits a target and the
destruction that it causes.
Take, for instance, what
you carry, 9 hollow-point.
When the hollow-point hits the
skull, what happens
is it mushrooms.
When it mushrooms it peels back.
So you may have six, eight...
ten little particles of the bullet
that are like razor blades...
Sir, yes, sir! Sir, yes sir!
Tearing their internal
organs, their
liver, their lungs, their heart...
bringing tissue,
bone, blood, brain
matter, and that's
called a blowback.
Fuck you. Fucking queers.
Firemen getting
pussy for the first
time in the history
of fire or pussy.
Hey, go save a kitten in a
tree, you fucking homos.
Pencils.
Begin.
What are you looking at?
Forget it.
Your father was a janitor,
his son's only a cop.
Those fucking firefighters
are a bunch of homos.
They are.
So she tells me, You never finish
anything. You finish
the police course...
you get taken care
of again, baby. So
after graduation, I
get a blowjob again.
That's great, your mother
must be a wonderful woman.
Go fuck yourself.
Put it this way. You're
a black guy in Boston.
You don't need any help from
me to be completely fucked.
The Massachusetts State Police has
a long tradition of excellence.
Your graduation today
solidifies your acceptance...
into one of the finest law
enforcement agencies
in our nation.
As the governor of
the Commonwealth
of Massachusetts,
I am confident...
each and every one
of you will serve
with distinction,
honour and integrity.
Congratulations to all
our new troopers.
Thank you. You are dismissed.
Sullivan! Assigned to
plain-clothes right
out of the gate, congratulations.
We're gonna go out for a
beer. You wanna come?
No, no, I'll catch up with you guys.
School's out.
Thank you, Frank.
You earned it.
No more pencils, no more books.
Alright.
This is not the regular police...
-this is the state police.
-And fire.
Your training will
illustrate the difference.
State police, search warrant.
State police, open the door.
What's the difference?
-Go, go, go!
-Sir, yes, sir!
-Is that understood?!
Move it, get the fuck down right
now! Get down, right now!
Congratulations on passing the
detective's exam, and welcome...
to the Special Investigation Unit.
Whoop-de-fucking-do.
We won't be working together,
that is, directly.
You'll be working for Captain
Ellerby, but I like
to see everybody.
You're a worker. You rise fast.
Like a 12-year-old's dick.
-Thank you, sergeant.
-My pleasure.
-Thank you, sir.
-Good luck.
-Congratulations.
-Thanks, hon.
You can go in there now.
You can sit.
So...
Do you know what we
do here? My section?
-Sir, yes, sir, I have an idea...
-Whoa, whoa, whoa. Let's say you have no idea...
and leave it at that, okay?
No idea. Zip. None.
If you had an idea
what we do, we would
not be good at what
we do, would we?
We would be cunts.
Are you calling us cunts?
Staff Sergeant Dignam
has a style of his own.
I'm afraid we all have
to get used to it.
So you have family
connections down in
Southie, right?
Through your father?
Why don't you tell us
about your Uncle Jackie?
He was a carpet layer
for Jordan Marsh.
Uncle Jackie was a
small-time bookie who
tended bar at the
Vets in Somerville.
He got popped by
Nicastro in '95. We
found his body out by the airport.
That's right.
-I remember his funeral.
-Oh, good.
Closed casket?
That's right.
So tell anybody up at Deerfield...
That is, before you got kicked
out for whaling
on a gym teacher with a folding chair.
You had an uncle met
his demise like that?
I got a question.
How fucked up are you?
Hi, Darlene.
What you got, staff sergeant?
In no time you made sergeant.
-SIU. What a country.
-Ha. Perfect.
Hey, I don't mind going it alone.
You know, if you
went alone every once in
a while you might get somewhere.
We're cops, alright?
This isn't somewhere.
Alright, lookit, I
know you're a worker.
Maybe I can do something for you.
You got any suits,
or do you like...
coming to work dressed like
you're gonna invade Poland?
You got quite the family tree here,
kid. That maggot uncle of yours...
Tommy Costigan, is another goof.
He gets busted selling guns...
to federal officers, among many,
many, many other departures...
from our normative behaviour.
And what's this got to do with me huh?
Why are you pretending
to be a cop?
This unit is new, and you are
the newest members of it.
You have been selected
for it on the
basis of intelligence
and aptitude.
This is an elite unit.
Our job is to smash or
marginally disrupt...
organised crime in this city...
by enhanced cooperation
with the FBI...
represented here today
by Agent Frank Lazio.
And we will do it.
And by organised crime in this
city, you know who we mean.
That's Jackie Costigan.
That's an old picture.
Jackie met his demise.
Last known photograph.
Costello uses three key guys.
That's Fitzy. Off-the-boat psycho,
lives in Brockton with his mother.
She's straight out
of Going My Way.
Delahunt, muscle.
French, the number one. But of
course, the rock
star, you know who.
We've done a briefing book, so
read up. I want any and all ideas...
so I can pass them off as my own.
Work hard and you'll
rise fast. You're
in the best possible position...
in the department.
Let's go to work.
Your old man was a fucking
hump from Southie.
Baggage handler at
the airport, right?
Family's all criminals
except for the old man, huh?
And one priest, since you
seem to know everything.
Well, last I heard he was happily
married to a 12-year-old
boy, living on a
beach in Thailand.
Fucking family's dug into the
Southie projects like ticks.
Three-decker men at best.
You, however, grew up...
on the North Shore, huh?
Well, la-di-fucking-da.
You were kind of a double
kid, I bet, right?
One kid with your old man,
one kid with your mother.
You're upper-middle class during
the weeks, then you're dropping your eyes and you're hanging...
in the big, bad Southie projects with your
daddy, the fucking donkey...
on the weekends. I got that right?
Yup. You have different accents?
You did didn't you, you
little fucking snake?
-You were like different people.
-You a psychiatrist?
Well if I was, I'd ask you why you're
a statie making 30 grand a year.
And I think if I was
Sigmund fucking
Freud I wouldn't get an answer.
So tell me, what's a
lace-curtain motherfucker
like you doing in the staties?
Well, families are always rising
or falling in America, am I right?
-Who said that?
-Hawthorne.
What's the matter, smart-ass, you
don't know any
fucking Shakespeare?
We have a question.
Do you wanna be a cop, or do
you wanna appear to be a cop?
It's an honest question.
Lot of guys want to
appear to be cops.
Gun, badge, pretend they're on TV.
A lot of them just wanna slam
a nigger's head through a plate-glass window...
I'm set without your own personal
job application, alright sergeant?
-What the fuck did you say to me, trainee?
-With all due respect sir, what do you want from me?
Hey, asshole, he can't help you.
I know what you are, okay?
I know what you are...
and I know what you're not.
I'm the best friend
you have on the face of this Earth and I'm
gonna help you understand
something you punk.
You're no fucking cop.
He's right. We deal
in deception here.
What we do not deal
with is self-deception.
Five years from now you could
be anything else in the world.
But you will not be a
Massachusetts state trooper.
-Are you sure of that?
-I'm sure of that.
Guaran-fucking-teed.
You had 1400 on your SATs, kid.
You're an astronaut, not a statie.
You don't have much family.
I don't have any family.
What's this I hear from Stephanie
about you becoming a policeman?
You mean Stephanie, who was the only one
who came to my father's funeral?
-That Stephanie?
-Yeah, that Stephanie.
Nothing much to it, Uncle Edward.
You trying to prove something
to the family?
When you say the family, who
do you mean exactly? You?
You always have to question
everything, don't you?
Maybe it would've
done you some good to
have some questions
from time to time you know?
Am I an asshole? Are
my kids a mess?
Is my wife a
money-grubbing whore? I
mean, those are questions, right?
Have I ever been good
to my dying sister,
or am I just now pretending to be?
Do you need some money
for the funeral?
When my mother dies, we don't
have any more connection.
It's very lovely. You get
the high ceilings,
the parquet floors.
Uhhh...bathroom is massive.
The fridge has got an alarm
in it in case you have uh...
you know, eating issues, which is a
joke. Not a very funny one.
Well, there's a great
view of the State
House. Beacon Hill,
if you can see it.
I mean, you move in, you're
upper-class by about Tuesday.
-So you're a cop.
-A state-police detective.
A state-police detective.
And are you a married
state-police detective?
No.
Because this is kind of a...
Sort of a big place and...
I have a co-signer.
Oh, cool. Yeah, you intend to have
a house guest. That's cool. Good.
-Yeah, it's got...
-Just give me the papers.
Sure.
Eternal rest grant
unto her, O Lord, and
let perpetual light
shine upon her.
-Amen.
-May she rest in peace. Amen.
May her soul and the souls of
all the faithful departed...
through the mercy of
God rest in peace.
Amen.
So what do I do?
There's money behind
this operation.
You won't be paid
as a regular cop...
but there's a bonus involved.
Tax-free.
We can't conceal that you were a
trainee. You'll be
convicted of a crime.
We're thinking a guilty plea to
assault and battery
would make sense.
Given your nature.
You'll do enough jail time to
convince anyone this is no setup.
You'll be on probation, see
a court-ordered shrink...
the whole nine yards.
You wanna serve the Commonwealth,
this is your chance.
We need you, pal.
You've already pretended to be
a Costigan from South Boston.
-Every weekend, Sergeant.
-Perfect.
Do it again.
For me.
-Hey, you Billy Costigan?
-Yeah, who wants to know?
Well, nothing. I know a Sean
Costigan down on L Street.
-Yeah, that's my cousin.
-Connected. Not too bright.
-Yeah, I know.
-I mean, no offence.
-Billy?
-Yeah, it's me.
-Oh, my God! Good to see you.
-Aunt Kathy, how are you?
Oh, good to see you. Come on in.
They said you was in the
staties. I couldn't believe it.
I got kicked out, like,
four months ago.
Yeah, it was in the papers.
So you know.
And why are we graced
with your presence?
I brought your mother some
pictures of my father.
-Look at the smile.
-My mother had them. My uh...
My mother's dead.
I'm sorry. Sorry
for your troubles.
I was at a funeral myself, man.
Myles Kennefick.
Knew him in school.
He was a young guy, you know?
It's terrible. It's a shame.
-You remember that. What a night.
-Listen. Listen, listen.
I got, like...
Like 30,000 bucks,
right? Insurance money.
Yeah.
You know, after my mother
passed and everything.
In your line of work,
if I gave you...
like, what, say, 10,000,
what could I get back?
You know what you...
You know what you usually
say at these moments.
-What? What?
-Come on, man.
Oh, come on, you fucking
moron. Come on.
What, you want me to say it?
I'm not a cop, alright?
-I'm your fucking cousin.
-You're, you're bad.
You corrupt fuck, man.
You must be my cousin.
Fucking Ricans think
they know everything.
If they knew shit, they
wouldn't be Puerto Ricans.
R is for Ricans P is for pigs.
Would you shut the fuck
up for five seconds, huh?
That's right. You
used to be a cop.
When we're working together just
limit it to two
eight-balls an hour.
We're not even
supposed to be doing
this shit this close to Worcester.
This side of Worcester.
-Says who?
-Says him. Says Costello.
God says, as far as you're...
concerned.
No, no, he's no cop. He got out
of the joint three weeks ago.
-Cunt cop.
-No, no, no.
He talks like his shit don't
stink, but he's good people.
Well, I knew his father.
-I liked his Uncle Jackie better.
-Jackie was alright.
Uncle Jackie was excellent.
Fucking guineas.
-To Jackie.
-Uncle Jackie.
Cranberry juice.
It's a natural diuretic.
My girlfriend drinks it
when she's got her period.
What, do you got your period?
-Fucking...
-Get off.
-Get your fucking hands off me.
-Hey. Hey, hey.
Do you know me?
No. No.
Well, I'm the guy that tells you
there are guys you can hit...
and there's guys you can't.
Now, that's not quite a
guy you can't hit...
but it's almost a
guy you can't hit.
So I'm gonna make a fucking
ruling on this right now.
You don't fucking hit
him. You understand?
Yeah, excellent. Fine fine, fine.
I fucking know you.
I know your family.
You make one more drug deal...
with that idiot fucking cop-magnet
of a cousin of yours...
and I'll forget your
grandmother was so nice to me.
I'll cut your fucking nuts
off. You understand that?
Yeah. Yeah, I do.
What are you drinking?
A cranberry juice.
What is it, your period?
Get him a cranberry juice.
Hey, fuckhead, that's
Jackie's nephew.
What? Oh, fucking what?
Get the fuck out of here.
Sorry I'm late.
Staff Sergeant Dignam is our
liaison to the undercover section.
His undercover work is extensive.
He's here to give us his
report. Sergeant Dignam.
Okay, my people are out there.
They're like fucking Indians.
You're not gonna see them.
You're not gonna hear about them except through
me or Captain Queenan.
You will not ever know the
identity of undercover people.
Unfortunately, this shithole has
more fucking leaks than the Iraqi navy.
Fuck yourself.
I'm tired from fucking your wife.
-How's your mother?
-Good, she's tired from fucking my father.
Good. Today, girls...
what I have for you is microprocessors.
Somebody, as you may already know,
stole 20 microprocessors...
from the Mass Processor
Company out on Route 128.
These are the kind of processors they
put into computers...
that could put a cruise missile
up the ass of a camel...
from a couple hundred miles away.
These little pieces of plastic are
worth about 100 grand apiece.
Now get this, we got a guy working for
the company two months...
walks out the door with a box
of processors on Tuesday...
has a ticket for Florida
on Wednesday...
but on Thursday, he gets
found in a dumpster.
You know where that
dirtball started his life?
Southie projects.
-What was his name, the departed?
-Myles Kennefick.
Got the job with a forged UMass
transcript. UMass, Boston...
-which happens to...
-South Boston?
Oh, you're a fucking genius. Who
forged your transcript, dickhead?
Hey, this guy, his old man runs the Hibernian
Liquor Mart. Kennefick's.
We're not here to solve the
case of the missing scumbag.
We're here to nail Costello.
Alright, look. We got a guy...
says Costello's moving
the processors to China.
He set up the whole fucking
job and popped Kennefick.
You do not want to miss it
if Costello takes a dump.
We'd miss a lot less if you
made your informants
available to us and of course, to the Bureau.
Without asking for
too many details, do
you have anyone in
with Costello now?
Maybe. Maybe not.
Maybe fuck yourself.
My theory on Feds is
they're like mushrooms.
Feed them shit and
keep them in the dark.
You girls have a good day.
Normally he's a very, uh, nice guy.
Don't judge him from
this meeting alone.
Now, Mrs Kennefick,
I knew your son.
I knew Myles.
Now he was little younger than me, but
he was behind me in school.
I wanna get these people
who did this to him.
Would you like to help us? You
wanna help us catch the people...
who forced your son to do a
robbery and then killed him?
Allegedly.
If he was killed, he probably
did something wrong.
But not the robbery.
That's not wrong.
He did something else wrong?
Wave to your girlfriend, honey.
I mean, fuck yourself.
-Did you get that?
-Allegedly or fuck yourself?
Welcome to the neighbourhood.
Different breed down here, Sarge.
I need a cup of coffee.
You making a house call?
Have I seen you professionally?
No, no. No, I know who
you are, though. I know.
Guys gotta use their service
revolver in the course of duty...
and then they get
to come to talk to
you about their
feelings and whatnot.
No, no, I know how it goes. You're
a mental health professional.
I have an appointment
on this floor.
Oh, well, you'll have fun. They're
all frigging crazy on that floor.
-I'm one more up.
-Oh, fancy policeman.
-Yeah, that's right, fancy.
-Are you a statie?
Yeah, I am. I'm actually
going to law school also.
Suffolk, nights?
Yeah, they don't run Harvard
at night, last time I checked.
When's the last time you checked?
Before I went to fucking Suffolk.
Okay, listen, I went to UMass.
I wasn't insulting you.
Well, I thought you were. So
now you gotta buy me dinner.
Maybe you can shoot someone and
then see me professionally.
I'll stab someone in the
heart with a fucking
ice pick if it gets
me dinner with you.
Wait. No, no, that's alright. I'm a
detective. I'll find you.
No, sorry. I'm just joking. I
need the card. Card helps.
Nice to meet you, Madolyn.
Hi, Dad. I had no idea about
the tail until I saw it.
No, I couldn't. I had the other
guy with me, I couldn't...
Alright, it's a blue sedan
and then a white van.
It's fucked up with graffiti on the side. And
the van is the audio surveillance.
Alright, have a nice day.
Cut him here.
Bye-bye.
Jerk-ass!
Come on, Babu. I can't do
any more. I cannot hold off.
Please don't let me go back empty-handed.
Don't do this. I wanna help you.
Come to my store next Friday.
I'll give you the money.
This is Friday, Babu. How
many times I gotta tell you?
You keep on calling me Babu.
It's Singh, motherfucker.
I'm trying to help you.
You keep telling me
I'm your friend.
You don't even know
my fucking name.
You want me to catch a beating? I'm gonna catch
a beating if I go back again like last week.
See this guy? You
see this guy? This
guy don't want you
to have the money.
Because he wants to come back
there and squash your head.
-And I don't want to see that happen.
-I have one customer sitting here. What I'm gonna do?
Business is bad? You opened a
store in an Irish neighbourhood.
These are dirty, dirty people.
Don't you know that?
Sell potatoes, I don't
know what you're gonna do.
Excuse me, gentlemen.
Excuse me. Sorry.
Know what I'm saying?
Hey, you fellas come from Providence?
It isn't any of your business
where we come from, is it, now?
What, are you fucking delivering
cannolis or something?
Hey. You are killing
my business, man.
Fuck.
What's wrong with this fucking
country? Everybody
hates everybody.
Get out of here. Get out of here.
Now, you also do
probation work, right?
That's right, I see
violent offenders.
-Oh, bad guys.
-Not necessarily.
You know, they got this but they
don't got duck L'orange.
Was your meal okay?
Yeah, no, no, the lobster was good.
I was just, you know, because it was a
French restaurant I was surprised.
I'm waiting for you
to make your move.
Look, I don't know, if that thing
moves, I'm gonna shoot it.
I don't even know what it is.
So what's it like having
people find themselves...
in your office all day long?
Does it get messy with all
those feelings flying around?
Why, does that make
you uncomfortable?
-No, no, no.
-No?
No, no, no. No, I'm
not on your couch.
Well, you know what Freud
said about the Irish?
Yeah, I do.
Yeah, if you actually
do, I'll see you again.
Who says I wanna see you again?
Don't you?
-You should see your face.
-Don't you?
Of course I wanna see you again!
What Freud said about
the Irish is...
we're the only people who are
impervious to psychoanalysis.
-Yeah, he said that.
-I know he did.
So you're up shit's creek with a
client list full of Mick cops.
I mean, opening up?
Good luck to you.
Why do you do it, then?
Some people do get better.
Fair enough.
Sometimes I want
people to forget about their
personal bullshit
and do their jobs.
Including the criminals?
Well, if they don't do their
jobs, you don't have one.
I'll always have a job. I'll
just arrest innocent people.
-Wait. You are trouble.
-You don't know the half of it.
I'll arrest you right now.
My word against yours.
...then I see her dancing at the
wedding with you-know-who.
Oh and the other one I says to him, why don't
you go up to Parents Without Partners?
And he goes, 'Ma, they're all losers at
the Parents Without
Partners,' so...
So I say to him, Princess
Carolina of Monaco...
Schuyler.
Do you know who I am?
No.
You met my friend Mr.
French the other night.
His real name Mr. French?
No.
Come with me.
I'm not the cops.
I'm not asking you.
You know something,
they just do not
stop having the Mafia
in Providence.
And this can cause me
a lot of problems.
Those guys you tuned up...
they're connected down Providence.
What they're gonna do...
is come back with some
guys and kill you.
Which, sure as you're
born, they will do.
Unless I stop them.
Do you want me to stop them?
Is this something I
can't do personally?
I'm gonna have my
associate search you.
No, No one's fucking searching me.
Search me for what?
Contra-fucking-band.
Take your shoes off.
Shoes.
I knew your father.
Yeah? Do you know he's dead?
Oh, sorry. How'd he go?
-Stand.
-He didn't complain.
Yeah, that was his problem.
Who said he had a problem?
I just said he had
a fucking problem.
There's a man could've
been anything.
Are you trying to say
that he was nothing?
Fuck.
I'm saying he worked
at the airport.
-He's clean.
-Arm.
Yeah, come on.
What arm? What fucking arm?
Show me your arm. Flip it.
Makes me curious to see you
in this neighbourhood.
He's clean.
And if I can slander
my own environment...
it makes me sad, this regression.
Plus, I don't know
if it's beyond some
fucking cop prick like Queenan...
to pull you out of the staties
and send you after me.
I just can't know.
I don't know what they do in that
particular department, anyway.
-Are you still a cop?!
-No. No.
Swear on your mother's grave
you're still not a cop?
I am not a fucking cop!
Are you gonna stop
doing coke deals
with your jerkoff fucking cousin?!
Yes, yes, yes. I am.
Alright, alright, alright.
You're okay. You'll be alright.
Get your hand taken care of.
I'm sorry, but it was necessary.
As for our problem
with Providence...
let's not cry over
spilled guineas.
Who let this IRA
motherfucker in my bar?
Just kidding. How's your mother?
She's on her way out.
We all are. Act accordingly.
Here it is, Your
Highness, as ordered.
Get in the car. I wanna
show you something.
What's got you all
hot and bothered?
Get in the car. You'll see.
Do you trust him?
Well, these days um...
who's reliable?
His Uncle Jackie was.
Yeah, but you can't trust a guy
acts like he's got
nothing to lose.
I'm reliable.
Arnold, you're one in a million.
Ten. Ten million.
What about your wife, Arnold?
Well, I thought she was.
She wasn't.
Well, she got reliable.
Don't you people ever
shut the fuck up?
Oh, another county heard from.
One too many. She got a big mouth.
Answer this for me, will you?
Ah. The principles of
detection tell me these
two gentlemen came
from Providence.
Lieutenant Risteen,
Lynn PD. I'd appreciate
it you get out of my crime scene.
Yeah, actually, it's my crime
scene, but knock yourself out.
Thanks.
I saw a dead guy. I think I'm
having post-traumatic stress.
Can I meet you for lunch?
Alright, see you then.
Who's the lead detective?
Good. He's a lox.
Get the cops to look
at Jimmy Pappas for
the hit. Of course, he had nothing
to do with it...
and he'll say so.
You look in his car, you'll
find the gun that
did it, registered,
official. Providence.
In the trunk or the
glove compartment?
Hey, you wanna see some dead guys?
Hey, this will get Captain
Ellerby on the 6 o'clock news.
No wonder you get ahead.
Have a seat, Bill.
Do you know John Lennon?
Yeah, sure, he was the
president before Lincoln.
Lennon said:
I''m an artist.
You give me a fucking tuba, I'll
get you something out of it.'
I tell you, Mr. Costello...
I'd like to squeeze some
fucking money out of it.
Smart-mouth.
Too bad.
If you'll indulge me...
Now what?
Choir practice.
Choir practice...
The point I'm making
with John Lennon is...
a man could look at anything...
and make something out of it.
For instance...
I look at you and I think
'What could I use you for?'
Get rid of this.
French.
Put it downstairs. Here.
Go ahead, thank you.
Maybe we could work something out.
-Good.
-And send this to his wife.
I thought was nice the way
you asked the guy...
which hand he jerked off with.
I hope this don't shake Rita up.
As I remember, she ain't
that sentimental.
That was quick. You think
he's dead already?
We have to do it by
phone. I won't do it...
if I have to wear a wire.
No wires ever. Understand?
You don't know what this is like.
Microprocessors.
-Micro-what?
-Microprocessors.
We'll probably be at war with
the Chinese in 20-odd years...
and Costello is selling
them military technology.
Microprocessors,
chips, computer parts.
Anybody says anything about
anything like that...
you let us know.
So who did the two
guys from Providence?
Jimmy Pappas.
What happened to Jimmy Pappas?
Jimmy had a rough month.
Jimmy had a heart
attack in jail...
and uh, then he got himself knifed
at Boston City Hospital.
I believe it's been in the papers.
You seem quite happy
with that result.
It's a fucking result.
Yeah, but cui bono? Who benefits?
Cui gives a shit? It's got
a friggin' bow on it.
I think you are a cop, my son.
-Where's your fucking licence?
-What licence?
I don't see no fucking license. There's no such
thing as a licence, of course.
But you, you definitely
need to have fucking one.
In fact, if you're not being run by us,
you're being run by someone else.
That means you're bringing some
undesirable elements...
into Mr. Costello's area.
I was going for my
fucking cigarettes.
Hey.
That's Jimmy Bags.
-He was rea... I don't know.
-What the fuck you doing?
I'm in the hole, I
pay him two grand a week.
There's no profit, I
Then make more fucking money.
This is America.
You don't make money, you're a fucking
douche bag. Now what you gonna do?
-Make more money.
-That's the spirit.
-Oh, fuck.
-Don't worry about it.
The guy don't need any
fucking teeth anyway.
It's a small surveillance
subunit, but it's mine.
I didn't take this job to fuck
up or let anyone else fuck up.
I hand-picked this group. You're
my A-team. Now, our prim...
Hi, Captain.
This crazy fuck...
-knocked Jimmy Bags' teeth out.
-So?
Look, he was reaching for
his fucking...
Guy was reaching for
his cigarettes.
You're gonna give me shit huh? Look, it
wasn't for no reason, alright Frank?
The man reached into his coat.
I don't know if he's a
bookie or what the fuck he's doing.
Well, you do know what a
bookie does, don't you?
Yeah. Yeah, he pays you.
Queenan's compartmentalising
everything in SIU...
which is the right thing to do.
Personally, I don't trust half the
fucking troopers out there any more.
Bottom line...
we think we might have a problem.
We think Costello's got a
rat in the state police.
-Really?
-Yeah, really.
Do we have direct access
to Queenan's undercovers?
No, no, not presently.
But I'm working on that.
Here, Bill, this is for you.
From now on, call the bar,
ask for Mikey. Just Mikey.
You ask for Mikey because
there is no Mikey.
You wait. We'll call you.
-You got that?
-Yeah, I got that.
-Sorry, I didn't hear you.
-I got that.
Good.
Hi, Dad.
I got promoted. Alright.
Excuse me for one second.
You know...
if your father were alive...
and saw you here
sitting with me...
let's say he'd have a
word with me about this.
In fact, he'd kill seven
guys just to cut my throat.
And he could do it...
which is maybe something you don't
know about William Costigan Sr.
-So he never? I mean, never?
-No. No, no.
He kept his own counsel.
He never wanted money.
You can't do anything
with a man like that.
Your Uncle Jackie...
he also would kill
my entire fucking
family if he saw me here with you.
And I think about this.
So what the fuck are
we talking about here?
Did you ever think about
going back to school?
School?
With all due respect,
Mr. Costello...
school is out.
Maybe someday you'll
wake the fuck up.
Good day, Fathers.
Mr. Costello.
Good morning, Francis,
good morning.
You recall our chat?
Little boys...
sucking on their peckers,
et cetera and so forth...
I am as God made me. Was
that your rationale?
May I remind you, in this
archdiocese, God
don't run the bingo.
May I remind you that pride
comes before the fall.
How's Sister Mary Theresa doing?
We had a tasty relationship
before she took her vows.
Enjoy your clams, cocksuckers.
Pay them.
Get the old bombardier
a drink on the house.
What do you got for me, trooper?
Uniform clipped him for
suspended licence.
However, he's a subject of
an open investigation...
More than one, yeah. He's
one of Costello's crew.
Yeah, we're getting a warrant. We can't
get an address off of him.
He paged his lawyer but the
lawyer hasn't called back yet.
Who's the lawyer?
He didn't know the name.
Just had a number on a card.
Beeper number.
SULLIVAN: And the guy didn't show up?
BROWN: No.
-And he beeped him?
-Twice.
Give me your phone. Turn that off.
BARRIGAN: What?
SULLIVAN: Turn the fucking camera off.
Give it to me. He
doesn't know what
the fucking lawyer looks like.
Whose briefcase is
this? Alright.
-It's off?
-You're good.
Afternoon, Mr. Fitzgibbons.
-He can't do that.
-He just did.
-You my attorney?
-What do you think?
Now, have you made any statements
or phone calls...
I need to be made aware of?
I beeped you.
The card they gave me. That's it.
-That's it?
-That's it.
I think you need to call your mother...
tell her you're not gonna
be home for supper.
Camera's off. It's
off. Call your mother.
Lookit, they're suiting
up for a raid right now.
I don't know where they're going,
but they do. And so do you.
So make the call.
Lookit fuckstick, you
don't gotta trust me...
just listen to what
I'm saying to you.
Mum, I'm not gonna make
it home for supper.
Sorry, yeah, I got held up.
Yeah, no, you carry on without me.
I'll talk to you later. Okay.
Bye.
Everybody out. Move.
Thank you.
So who are you?
I think you need a
different attorney after all,
Mr. Fitzgibbons. Have a great day.
So when the fuck am
I gonna get out?
Alright, run the last number
he called. That's his house.
Now whatever the address is, I'll swear to
the judge I surveilled him there...
and abra-fucking-cadabra,
we got a warrant.
-Why did you use my phone?
-Because you didn't go in there.
The light's nice
here in the morning.
So do you wanna talk
about last night?
You know, it's alright.
Guys tend
to make too big a deal out of it.
It's actually quite common.
I gotta go to work.
Do you lie?
Why? Do you?
No, I'm asking if you lie.
Honesty is not
synonymous with truth.
Yeah, you lie.
You lie.
Is it to do some good, to
get somewhere personally...
or, what, just for the fuck of it?
Well, I expect that some people do
it to keep things on an even keel.
Wow. So you had a parent
who was a drunk.
Did you?
No.
Let's keep it with you.
Talk about how you feel.
How I feel.
-Fuck!
-Brian, stop it.
No. Please. No.
Ain't gonna hurt you.
You sit there...
with a mass murderer.
A mass murderer.
Your heart rate is jacked.
And your hand...
steady.
That's one thing I figured out
about myself in prison. My hand...
does not shake.
Ever.
Wake the fuck up.
There was a cop leaving
when I came in.
How did you know he was a cop?
Bad haircut, no dress
sense and a slight,
you know, air of
scumbag entitlement.
-Do you see cops?
-That's part of what I do.
I mean, I normally don't see cadets who've
been kicked out of the academy.
Oh, boy. You should get
a better job, huh?
Should I?
So, do they all come in here...
and cry, your cops?
-Sometimes they do.
-Yeah?
-Yeah, sure. Sometimes they cry, yeah.
If they've had trouble at home, if
they've had to use
their weapons...
Use their weapons?
Let me tell you something.
They signed up to
use their weapons.
Most of them, alright? But
they watch enough TV...
so they know they have to weep
after they use their weapons.
There is no one more
full of shit than a cop.
Except for a cop on TV.
I looked at your file.
I see that you have a
record of assault.
Yeah.
So what was it like
for you in jail?
What, you wanna hear
about the showers?
Is that what you wanna hear about?
Did something happen to you?
No.
Okay kid, let's do this.
Come on, spread them.
Hey, you think you
can pop somebody...
and there's a special
card to play?
That guy, Jimmy Bags, whose jaw you broke...
happens to work undercover for
the Boston Police Department.
I'm going fucking nuts man. I can't be
someone else every fucking day.
It's been a year of this, I've had enough of this shit.
Calm down alright? Most people in the world
do it every day. What's the big deal?
Well, I'm not them.
I'm not fucking them, okay?
Exactly.
You're nobody. You signed
the papers, remember?
Now we're the only two people on the face of this
Earth that even know you're a cop.
How about we just
erase your file, huh?
How about that, how about we erase your file...
and then bang, you're just another
soldier for Costello...
open to arrest for
I don't know how
many felonies, huh? What do you say we do that Cap'n?
How about I fucking kill you, huh?!
How about I fucking kill you?!
-That was a joke. Come on.
-That wasn't a joke.
Just 'cause you play a tough guy,
doesn't mean you are one...
you lace-curtain,
Irish fucking pussy.
Hey, hey! Stop it!
Break it up! Stop it!
Fuck you, motherfucker!
Goddamn it, stop it!
That's an order!
For Christ sake, be smart.
If anybody's watching us now, how
are we not supposed to arrest you?
Come on, get in the car.
Both of you, get in the car!
When are you gonna take Costello huh?
I mean, what's wrong with taking
him on any one...
of the million fucking
felonies that you've
seen him do or I've seen him do?
I mean, I mean, he murdered
somebody, right?
The guy fucking murders somebody
and you don't fucking take him.
What are you waiting
for honestly? Do you want him
to chop me up and
feed me to the poor?
-Is that what you guys want?
-Yeah, that might stick.
Will you shut up?
We are building a case
and it takes time.
You know that.
Something's wrong.
I'm telling you,
something's wrong.
Yeah, maybe.
Look, we need you to keep
your ears open, alright?
No bullshit.
I think Costello's
got a spy inside
the Special Investigation Unit.
You...you serious?
I'm afraid so.
Have you heard anything like that?
Aw, Jesus Christ.
Hang tight for me, kid.
Just a little while longer.
We are this close.
Alright?
What do you expect coming in here?
-I have to come here.
-I know you have to come here.
But now that you're here...
what do you want?
You want the truth?
Valium.
Ugh, you know, if you lied, you would have an
easier time getting
what you wanted.
What's that say about what you do for a living?
We should have a few
more meetings...
before we even talk
about prescriptions.
Look, look. I'm having panic attacks alright?
The other night, I thought
I was having a fucking heart
attack. I puked in a trash
barrel on the way over here.
I haven't slept for fucking weeks.
-Is that true?
-Yeah, that's true, alright?
I said something fucking true.
I want some fucking pills...
and you're gonna, what? You're gonna close my file?
I didn't say I'd close
your file. I...no, I...
I thought I was
supposed to tell...
the truth here, if
only fucking here.
You are. Yes. Okay.
When a guy comes in here
against every, every instinct
of privacy, of self-reliance
that he has...
and what do you do?
What do you do, huh? You
send him off on the
street to score smack?
Is that what you do?
You're fucking ridiculous.
Two pills? Great.
Why don't you just give
me a bottle of Scotch...
and a handgun to blow
my fucking head off?
Are we done with this
psychiatry bullshit?
You know what? You can leave!
What did fuck did I just put myself
through? I'm fucking out of here.
And what if that was
a legitimate threat?
Think about it, fucking hotshot.
Fuck.
Why is the last patient of the
day always the hardest one?
It's 'cause you're tired and you
don't give a shit.
-It's not supernatural.
-Listen.
Listen. You know, I'm
not just somebody that
you have to see or
they put you in jail.
Okay? I mean, if you're in
distress, I will help you.
What's this?
It's my card. And a
prescription for 20 lorazepam.
Yeah?
Is it enough to commit suicide?
Maybe it is. Alright? Okay?
Have I done my job up to
your goddamn standards?
Because according to
my standards, you
fit the model of
drug-seeking behaviour.
You know, and too
damn bad if you don't
like my initial clinical reaction.
Thank you.
I'm transferring you
to another counsellor.
-Good.
-Okay.
So you wanna get a cup of coffee?
Bring it in here, please.
Would somebody bring it in?
Come on in.
Our target is a major
transaction of microprocessors.
Yes, those.
I don't know what they
are, you don't know
what they are. Who
gives a fuck? Cash.
Lots of cash is gonna change
hands inside a building...
that we have under AV
surveillance close-by.
I know this off-site location
is not the best,
but we had very little
time to set up.
You guys know anything about this?
No.
Sullivan's team will ID the bad
guys and listen in on the phones.
Our unit will not take action.
I repeat, not take
action, until a man
that Captain Queenan has inside their operation
verifies the transaction.
Are we clear?
Anybody? Any questions? No?
This is who we're after.
We've been after this cocksucker
for a long time, and tonight...
we are going to get
him. Let's go to work.
Alright, you guys find out
what we're doing and get on it.
-Hey.
-Sorry to get you at the last minute, but things leak.
This lead came from
Queenan's undercover guy.
I'm gonna smoke. You
don't smoke do you? What, you one of
those fitness freaks,
huh? Go fuck yourself.
-Hi, Dad?
-Yes.
Yeah, something big
came up at work.
I'm not gonna be home for supper.
Too bad.
Your mother worked
all goddamn day.
We'll just have to sit down
without you and your friends.
Oh, no, my friends
are still coming.
So we'll just... I'll just see
you for lunch instead tomorrow.
Your mother will be proud.
Alright, thanks, Pop. Bye.
The readiness is all.
You know the players.
Call the game.
Thank you.
-You ready?
-Is your highness...
gonna drop me off at confession
before work, or fuck me, or what?
What have you got to confess
to that anointed paederast?
A confessional seal, these days...
I'm not so sure.
Piece of cake. He'll operate the cameras. You
ID the guys and log them.
All cell-phone signals are
under surveillance...
through the courtesy of our
federal friends over there.
Patriot Act, Patriot Act. I
love it, I love it, I love it.
Keep an eye on this one.
Alright, here we go.
There's Costello. Mr. French.
There's Fitzy, Delahunt...
and the new guy, Billy Costigan.
Time is 10:46.
Alright, turn off
your cell phones.
Fitzy's got the chicken.
Check your weapons.
-We have a blind spot.
-Why do we have a blind spot?
We had two hours'
notice. Fuckin' two hours.
-Fuck you think this is, NASA?
-It never crossed my mind.
Have you got a camera in the back?
What back?
-How you going, Robert?
-Good, Mr. Costello.
I wanna tell you, at least two of
these gents have machine guns.
He's from the Chinese government.
He's just scared shitless.
Government man. Scared.
I'm concerned about a Chinaman
who thinks it's wise...
to come to a business
transaction...
with automatic weapons.
For his own good, tell Bruce
Lee and the Karate Kids...
none of us are carrying
automatic weapons.
Because here, in this country...
it don't add inches to your dick.
You get a life sentence for it.
Yeah maybe if we had some of that
Homeland Security money
like some fuckin' douchebags
I could mention...
Any calls?
They turned off their cell phones.
Search randomly for calls
made from the area.
Eight hundred and seven
phones are live in this area.
Then narrow the area.
What you see there for service
is what you're gonna get.
Why the fuck did they turn
their phones off?
Wait. There's still one phone up.
Where?
The buyers are there.
You know, direct contact with your
guys would have its advantages.
Not to my guy.
This is unbelievable. Who put
the fucking cameras in this place?
Oh, who the fuck are you?
I'm the guy who does his job.
You must be the other guy.
If these Chinks wanna nuke Taiwan
any time in this century...
they'd better shape up and
show me 1 million dollars.
What we generally do,
in this country...
is one guy...
brings the items...
and the other guy...
pays him.
No tickee...
no laundry.
Go ahead, Fitz.
Cars are moving, but did
you see anybody come out?
Please tell me those
cars aren't empty.
I mean, Jesus fucking
Christ, please tell
me that those Chinamen's
cars aren't empty.
They didn't figure we had a navy.
Did you put a camera in the back?
Can I talk to you for
a second, please?
You stupid fucking hard-on.
You fucked this whole thing up.
What the fuck did you do, you
cocksucker? Let go of me.
I'm gonna rip your fucking arm off
and shove it up your fucking ass you hear me?!
Why don't we just meet up sweetheart?
Let me buy you an ice cream.
I'm getting on a plane
unless you put Queenan on the phone.
Queenan had a funeral to go to, okay?
This is my shift. Just calm down.
Why shouldn't I get on
a fucking plane, huh?
Meet up? Meet...?! You actually
want me dead?
Look, there is a rat in your
unit. That is a fact, alright?
-Where's Queenan?
-He's not here.
They knew you had cameras in the
building. They knew everything.
There is a leak from the inside.
It's real. Man, smoke him out.
Yeah, how do we do
that, Mr. fucking "Genius Who
Didn't Even Graduate
From the Academy?"
Disinform alright? Let it slip to SIU that
you have a sealed
wiretap warrant...
for Costello's
apartment. Don't tell
anyone in our division,
but tell SIU.
Flush it down the pipe, and see
if it comes out on my end alright?
That's what we do
first. We narrow it down.
-Where the fuck is Queenan, huh?
-He's not here alright?
You wanna meet up or you got
something real, call me back.
Changing your life radically.
Change anything. Right?
Change everything.
-Right?
-Yeah.
How long you been with this guy?
-My boyfriend?
-Yeah.
-Four months. Almost four months.
-Four months.
Do you love him?
It's a pretty serious
relationship, yeah.
It's very serious.
Is he a headcase like
me or? I'm just curious.
No more than I am.
I know that it's a
serious relationship.
I know there are ups
and downs. Right?
People have doubts and problems.
Well, not problems, but doubts.
What would you do if he was
standing right there
and he saw us huh?
I would lie. Yeah, I would lie.
You know, to keep things
on an even keel, right?
Right? We talked about that.
-Morning.
-Good morning.
Want a French doughnut?
Yeah.
-Hey, can I lookit?
-Yeah.
Sure.
Alright, we're not
having this out.
What?
You don't see any pictures
of where I came from.
Look, I respect who you are...
just, you know, not
in the living room.
We might have company.
-Company?
-Yeah, company.
Hey, now, why do you
work for the state?
Why not? You do.
No, what you do. The
degrees and all,
everything you got.
You're hot shit.
Yeah?
So why do you make as much
as a guidance counsellor?
Because I believe
in public service.
So now you're gonna
fuck with me? So
now you're gonna be
ridiculous, huh?
No, don't start with me. Don't...
Hey.
Ah, fuck with the
fucking phone. Stop it!
-The phone.
-Forget the phone.
Get it. Answer it. Answer it.
This is your first phone
call in the new house.
You live here now.
You're a resident.
Mayor Sullivan's office.
Put Colin on the phone right now.
Oh, my God. I'm sorry.
What?
I think it's a guy with...
-It's like a cancer guy.
-Hello.
What the fuck is it with
you and your phone, huh?
Something for work.
Hey. Uh, nothing, nothing, nothing. It
went dead. I don't know, I get...
Was that that shrink cunt
that answered the phone?
Remember I told you that we
were... She was gonna move in?
-Yeah.
-She moved in.
You better get organized, quick.
Hey, last time I checked,
I tipped you off...
and you're not in jail.
-Are you listening to me?
-Yeah.
Do you like Little Miss
Thing sucking on your cock?
Yes. Yes, I do.
So earn it.
I'm getting the feeling...
we got a cop in my crew.
Yeah, I know, I'm kind of
getting that feeling too.
He's one of yours. Inside.
Have you seen anything?
Frank, I got no access to
Queenan's undercover
files. He and Dignam
run the snitches.
-I'm doing my best.
-Your best?!
What do you think we're in, the
fucking haberdashery business?
Alright, look, Frank, if you don't relax...
If you don't relax,
I can't relax.
Alright? Now, what I
need you to do...
you get me information on the people who were
with you last night. Your crew.
Get me social security
numbers, get me...
-...full names
-Get you? Give you? Who the
fuck do you work for?
Alright, alright, alright. Frank, Frank.
Frank! Alright. I'm sorry.
I didn't...If you could, please. What I
need are SS numbers, DOBs...
just all the pedigree
information so I can
run it on my end and
we can ID the prick.
If you could just get me
that information...
what I can do is... I can just ra.....
We're, we're, we're gonna handle it. I can handle it.
Calm down, or you'll
shoot in your pants.
I'll get you the
records and whatnot.
But listen to me, son. Don't
disappoint me on this...
or some other guy will be
putting their fat cock...
up Little Miss Freud's ass.
How are you, Francis?
-My mother called me Francis.
-I know she did.
And your father called
you the tumour.
And what did your father
call you, Charlie?
Oh, yeah, I forgot.
He wasn't around.
You have a boss that
has a laryngectomy?
No, no, no. That was a
guy who works for me.
You're lying to me.
Not exactly.
What did you do with the
real microprocessors, Frank?
Microprocessors.
Oh, yeah.
I heard the story. You arrested
some Chinese government guys...
at the border carrying some
light sockets or something.
I can't wait to wipe that
fucking smirk right off of your face.
Wouldn't you rather
wipe my ass for me?
Look, there are certain parts
of my job that I'm
not gonna be able to
talk to you about.
And I cannot allow
you to jeopardize
an ongoing investigation...
or your life.
No, really, there are things you
don't even wanna know about.
Okay, then just say that.
Alright, I will.
Oh, that's the movers.
Yeah, you still wanna stay?
-Yes.
-Yeah?
Come on, I'm coming.
It's the worst timing.
I'm gonna get you.
If you coulda, you woulda.
But I guess you like to
go at your own pace.
Excuse me. Got a date
with some angels.
Frankie.
Frankie. Frankie
Your mother forgives me.
You take off an armoured
car at the Deda Mall.
What the fuck you do, you pay
guineas in Providence?!
-Fucking now I do.
-What the fuck you do?!
What?! I gotta pay Costello, wait
for him to trade me
to the FBI? Because
that's what he does.
FBI? What the fuck you
talking about, FBI?
Oh my God, is that French out there?
What the fuck did you
just say about the FBI?
Forget what I said.
I'm fucking high.
Whatever may be going on in
that very fucking poor...
very limited brain of yours, I am
not gonna hurt you, alright?
Just tell me what
you just fucking said.
Forget it.
I'm high. I'm fucking
high. I must be high.
I would never say what
you thought I said.
Oh! Fuck!
Now, what the fuck did
you just fucking say?
Why do you think he
never gets busted?
Costello's a protected
FBI informant.
He'll trade you out.
I thought I was supposed
to go into shock.
I'm not in shock.
It fucking hurts.
Hey. It's me.
-What are you doing here?
-Come here.
Costello's giving
people up to the FBI.
The FBI?
He is giving information
to the FBI.
He's a protected
fucking informant.
I mean, aren't they
always trying to make
it a federal case and
it never gets made?
Go around the back. I'll
open the door. Go on.
-Here's some ice water.
-Oh, thanks. Thanks.
That's my son, Patrick.
-Goes to Notre Dame.
-Oh, yeah?
My wife's asleep but she left some
supper out. You want
something to eat?
No. No, thanks.
Yeah, come on, man. You have some
supper. We'll talk in the kitchen.
Come on.
You want some coke?
There it is.
Don't move 'til you're numb.
Come on. Get inside.
Boss wants your real name...
your social and licence number,
your bank account numbers.
I don't have a bank account.
I'm a cash business myself.
What's he doing, setting up IRAs?
Just fill the fucking
paper in. Your
real name and all
your account numbers.
Then we wait here.
-You're shitting me.
-No, I ain't.
Put the forms in there.
I don't know if this is
how you spell citizens.
But fuck it, you know?
No, no, no, no, no. Come here.
What, are you fucking
retarded or something?
That ain't fucking right.
Are you kidding me?
Look at this. Look.
Citizens. Look.
Billy, he said to stay here.
Yeah. I'm not sitting here
without getting a tetanus shot.
Where the fuck are you going?
I'm not staying, alright?
You can tell him I said that.
-Hey.
-Hi.
-It's pouring out there.
-Yeah.
Look...if...
-if this is inappropriate, I...
-No.
No, it's not inappropriate.
You're not a patient.
So you moving out
or you moving in?
I've still got three
weeks left on the lease.
That's me.
Yeah, I know.
-Hedging your bets?
-No. No.
You have to choose.
-You have to make a...
-A decision.
A decision. And, and, you know, you
have to stick by what you choose.
-You have to...
-Move in with your boyfriend?
Yes. Otherwise it's...
Oh, I know, I know. I know.
I have to say your
vulnerability is
really freaking me out right now.
Is it real?
I think so.
You don't have any cats.
No.
I like that.
I don't get it.
Well...we are all convinced that
Costello has at least...
one mole inside the Special
Investigations Unit.
You will investigate
everybody and anybody.
Well, that's not exactly
a dream job for a cop.
We looked at all
possible candidates.
You have an immaculate record.
Some people don't trust a guy
with an immaculate record. I do.
I have an immaculate record.
How is your wedding coming along?
Great. Great. She's a doctor.
-Ooo. That's outstanding.
-Yeah.
Marriage is an important
part of getting ahead.
Lets people know you're not a
homo. Married guy is more stable.
People see the ring, they think at
least someone can stand the son of a bitch.
Ladies see the ring,
they know immediately you must
have some cash and
your cock must work.
Yeah, it's working. Overtime.
-I'm glad to hear that.
-Yeah. Thank you.
Be dirty, be dirty.
Yeah...
Frank. The fuck is wrong with you?
-See anything you like, Col?
-I almost fucking shot you.
I mean, you're not indulging in
self-abuse, are you?
Sit down.
I hope you're not
turning into one of
them sob sisters who
wants to get caught.
You're not cracking up, are you?
-I don't crack up.
-Pick a place like this...
where any cop could
see you. Jesus.
If this is such a fucking
bad idea why'd you show up?
I own the place.
Why am I not fucking surprised?
Alright, lookit, I
gotta tell you...
You're getting reassigned. I know.
How the fuck do you know that?
-Where'd they put you?
-Hey, Frank.
I gotta find myself.
You're telling me, sonny boy.
I gotta find the guy you
got in the department.
With everybody
looking up their own
ass and you looking
for yourself...
I put my money on
nobody finds nothing.
I know, but, Frank, lookit.
For me, you gotta lay low.
-Right now.
-Collie...
laying low is not what I do.
Alright, fucking Big Daddy
Frank. Fucking perfect.
What good am I to you if
you don't listen to me?
What good am I if
you don't listen?
Queenan is compartmentalising.
He's splitting everything up.
Alright? He's fucking smart. You know this.
I can get the rat. You just gotta
let me do it my way, Frank.
Okay.
But Colin, I hope I won't
have to remind you...
that if you don't find
that cheese-eating
rat bastard in your department...
most likely, it won't be
me who suffers for it.
Now, why would you have
to remind me of that?
Would I be any good
at what I do if
I didn't fucking
already know that?
Frank, you gotta trust me.
Alright? Just, just trust me, Frank.
Hey, it fucking
involves lying and I'm
pretty fucking good
at that. Right?
Right?
Maybe because it's
always been so easy...
for me to get cunt that I never
understood jerking
off in a theatre.
Christ.
Who knows what's easy?
Colin, I know you'll
take care of business.
Shit!
Fuck.
Hey, how you doing?
Hi, Darlene, hi.
-That's it for me.
-Yeah, see you.
Have a good one.
I smell a rat.
Jesus Christ.
You got a girlfriend?
No.
No, no. Why, why, what
does that matter?
It depends.
I'm sure by now you know...
I got an informer in my outfit.
Cop.
Staties, Boston Police
Department, I'm not, uh, sure.
Jesus Christ.
You, you sure it's not the FBI?
It ain't the FBI.
Ex-wife.
Old girlfriend.
Or stupid.
That is what brings you
down in this business.
Stupid, huh?
Well, I guess that leaves me out.
You know, past days, situation
like this, I kill everybody.
Everybody who works for me.
Right. You know, Frank...
I, uh, I look around at
your other guys...
I mean, they're all
murderers, right? Right?
And I think, Could I do murder?
And all I can answer myself is:
'What's the difference?'
Give them up to the Almighty.
You see, that's my
point, you know?
You accuse me once,
I put up with it.
You accuse me twice...
I quit.
You pressure me to
fear for my life and I
will put a fucking
bullet in your head...
as if you were anybody else. Okay?
You got something
you wanna ask me?
Look, you're 70 years old,
Frank. I'm just saying, okay?
One of your guys is gonna pop you.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
As for running drugs, what the fuck
are you doing? What are you doing?
You don't need the
money or the pain
in the ass. And they
will catch you.
I haven't needed the money...
since I took Archie's milk
money in the third grade.
Tell you the truth, I don't
need pussy any more, either.
But I like it.
Point I'm making here is, Bill...
I got this rat...
this gnawing, cheese-eating,
fucking rat...
and it brings up questions.
You know. See, Bill, like,
you're the new guy.
Girlfriend...
Why don't you stay in the bar
that night I got your numbers?
Social-security numbers.
-Yeah.
-Everybody's fucking numbers.
Is there something that you
just wanna go ahead and ask me?
'Cause I'll give you the
fucking answer, alright?
Frank, look at me. Look at me.
I'm not the fucking rat. Okay?
I'm not the fucking rat.
Start with you agree
there is a rat.
You said there is one, alright?
I base most of what
I do on the idea
that you're pretty fucking
good at what you do.
Sure. Sure, Will.
You, William. What would you do?
Frank, how many of these guys...
have been with you long
enough to be disgruntled huh?
Think about it. You don't
pay much, you know.
It's almost a fucking
feudal enterprise.
The question is, and this
is the only question...
who thinks that they can do
what you do better than you?
The only one who could
do what I do is me.
Lot of people had to
die for me to be me.
You wanna be me?
I probably could be you. Yeah.
Yeah, I know that much.
But I don't wanna be you, Frank.
I don't wanna be you.
Heavy lies the crown...
sort of thing.
Yeah.
Francis.
I'm out of here. You'll have to
set the alarm...
Yeah, alright. I'll
see you at Christmas.
Alright. Good night.
You know what I like
about restaurants?
The fucking food? I
don't know. What?
You learn a lot
watching things eat.
There's a boat coming
up Gloucester.
French will give you all
the details. Don't forget.
Eat something, for Christ's sake.
In the future, I tell you to do a
thing, you fucking
do it. You got that?
I got it. Okay?
Excuse me...
-French, I forgot my...
-Okay, Francis.
Cigarette.
Eat something.
Problem?
Yeah, I got a problem.
I run rat fucks
like you, okay? I don't like them.
The day you wouldn't take
a promotion, let me know.
If you'd taken care of
this I wouldn't even be here.
Fuck yourself, you piece of shit.
And Imma need the identity
of your undercovers.
Blow me, alright? Not literally though.
Unfortunately,
there's no promotion
involved for you.
Fucking prick.
-Hi, Captain.
-Look who's here. The prom queen.
-They are not happy with me.
-What do you expect?
Everybody knows
you've been assigned
here to find Costello's rat.
They want to find the
leak as much as you do.
Like I said, two days
ago, my guy damn
near found out who
Costello's rat is.
-But he lost him in the streets.
-Really?
Well, did he get a
look at the guy?
No.
I mean, nothing? Like, I mean,
anything that could help us.
No.
So you got any advice for me?
Just, I mean, generally.
Costello can't do
much business without
coordinating with his source...
who is here in SIU.
Follow Costello.
You'll find his rat.
You're gonna be looking
at my people...
going through their
bank statements,
their phone calls and
medical records.
Don't be surprised if
they don't buy you
a beer or invite you
into their homes.
Let me get you a coffee.
If I wasn't with the
Massachusetts State Police...
if I did it full-time,
law school...
I'd be through it in a year.
If I wasn't a trooper.
But another city. I
was thinking that.
Another city.
Another city, huh?
Yeah, well, that would
be a clean slate.
I want you to know, you
don't got to stay.
If we're not gonna make it...
it's gotta be you that gets
out, because I'm not capable.
I'm fucking Irish. I'll
deal with something
being wrong for the
rest of my life.
It might not be a bad idea,
you know, another city.
Of course I know
how to spot a cop.
How's that?
If he's not paying attention
to us, he's a cop.
Lookit. You see that guy over
there? Right over there.
Yeah.
Not paying attention
to us. He's a cop.
-Okay.
-You get it now, do you?
-What about this guy?
-Cop.
Hey, how you doing? What
kind of dog is that?
She ignored us so
she must be a cop.
-She's probably the fucking
police commissioner.
-Ha, stop it with your fucking...
You can get out of here. I'm using
a new crew tonight. New guys.
I thought I was on for this.
I changed my mind.
Take the night off.
Francis, we're ready
for the sushi bar.
-Out the back.
-Jimmy, bring a mop.
There's guys who answer
the questions right...
-and there's guys that don't.
-And a pail.
You're a cop.
What?
You ignored us, you're a cop.
We're guessing who
cops are. You know,
most good-looking women are cops.
Well, I'm going home, alright?
He's playing with his new guys.
-See you later, alright?
-(Fitzy) See you later.
-(Delahunt) See you later.
-He's moving something with all
new guys. A whole new crew.
-Where?
No, no, I can't tell you what or
where. It's probably
disinformation.
Just keep following
him, alright?
Listen, I need to see you today.
-Tomorrow.
-No, no, no. Today.
-You heard nothing about drugs?
-No.
Nothing about new guys?
Nothing about Gloucester?
Not a thing. And I
would have. That
information would have come to me.
It ain't Bill.
No way, he says.
Follow Costello.
You'll find his rat.
Yeah, this is Sergeant Sullivan.
I want constant surveillance on
Captain Queenan,
starting right now.
Good. Thank you.
Can I ask a question,
Sarge? Why the
fuck are we following
Captain Queenan?
To find out about the
good Catholic life?
I have to follow every
lead, however unlikely...
however fucking painful
it might be to
your delicate fucking
sensibilities.
Who told you I had
delicate sensibilities?
I just don't like it,
Sarge. It don't feel right.
I have reason to believe...
that Captain Queenan
is Costello's rat.
So just follow him
and don't get made.
Sarge, we got the
target coming out.
Hey. Where are you?
Look down the car.
-You got me?
-Yeah, I gotcha.
Is there any reason you
would have a tail?
No.
-Because I think there's...
-Billy, I don't have a tail.
Get off at the next
stop, alright? South
Station. You wait
there 10 minutes okay?
South Station. Wait 10 minutes.
He just went into a building
down the waterfront. 344 Wash.
You got that? 344 Wash.
Yeah, he went up to the top floor.
Building's empty. No tenants here.
He's got dope coming in. I
don't know where. He...
He's getting spooky, Captain.
-What do you mean?
-I just saw him.
He had blood all over his hands.
He's lost his fucking mind.
I don't know what we're
doing here, boys.
He's not including his regular
guys. But I'mma tell you something.
Sooner or later he's
gonna find out who
I am and he's gonna
fucking kill me.
-I know it. He's gonna fucking kill me.
-Alright.
Alright, alright!
I think we got him.
I think Queenan's
meeting with him right now.
Alright, alright. Listen to me.
I'm really sorry for your
trouble. I swear to God I am.
I'll get you out of
this. I cannot do
it overnight but I will get you out.
Yeah?
Hey, get the van. We're
moving. Heavy work.
-What about the FBI?
-They're compromised.
-They're what?
-They're fucked.
-Yeah.
-Billy, where the fuck are you?
We've been trying to reach
you. We found the rat.
Listen, we're gonna
take him out. Lookit:
The address is 314 Washington
Street. You got it?
Alright, we'll see you there.
-What?
-You were followed.
-By who?
-By Costello's people.
-Impossible.
-One of the cops...
he's got on the inside tipped
him. Come on. Come on.
Come on.
What the fuck is going on?
Fucking shit. Looks like Queenan's
meeting with all of them.
Yeah, he must be our guy.
Sarge, we gotta get
him out of here.
Those guys aren't fucking around.
Ah, Christ, it's too
late. Let's go back up.
-Shit.
-You got to get out of here.
-Take the fire escape.
-What about you?
I'll be fine. But if you get made
I can't protect you. Now, go. Go!
-One of you mugs got a light?
-Where's your boy?
-He's studying law at Notre Dame.
-Where's your fucking boy?
-Hey. Hey.
-Goddamn motherfucker.
-Fucking kill you.
-Where's your fucking boy?
-Whoa!
-What the fuck was that?
-Did you fucking see that?
Sarge, something just
came off the building.
What the fuck?
Fuck.
What do you mean, something came
off the building? Go again with that information.
Something came off
the fucking roof.
It's a fucking body.
Sarge, we can't get a visual.
Do you want us to get out of the car?
We gotta get on foot if you want
me to get up on this thing.
-Where the fuck were you?
-What the fuck happened?
You're fucking late!
Get in the van!
What do you mean, something came off the roof?
Fuck's what's going on?! I
came to meet you.
-Where the fuck could you be?
-Get in the van! Get in the van!
I don't know, Sarge, but I got four armed men right out
front. You want us to pursue?
No, do not pursue.
Stay in the car.
-Fuck. No fucking pursuit.
-I need information.
What came off the roof?
-No pursuit.
-That's bullshit.
Fuck this.
Fitzy! Get in the van!
Get in the fucking
van! Let's go! Move!
Alright. I got him.
32X to CP. We're being fired upon.
An officer is down. I
repeat, an officer
is down. A trooper's been shot.
Send some back...
So do you know why Queenan
went into that building?
-No.
-Well, a better question...
is why the fuck were
your guys following him?
I told Internal Investigations
to follow Captain Queenan.
Why?
That's Internal
Investigations' business.
Fucking piece of shit!
-Whoa, whoa, whoa!
-Hey, hey, hey!
-Fucking bitch.
-Let him go.
Cocksucker. I don't
have to fucking
explain anything to anybody!
I can fucking investigate
anybody I fucking want to!
Let him go. Come on.
I don't give a fuck
what you think!
Captain, I got reason to
believe that Queenan
got killed by his own
fucking undercover.
That's a fucking lie.
He has fucking information in a
locked file, as did
Captain Queenan.
I need access to those files.
Hey, I forgot the password but if you wanna come down
to the garage with me I'll be happy give it to you.
-That's a fucking lie.
-Nobody calls me a liar!
Shut up! Work with the tech
guys to unlock those files.
-Dignam, take a leave of absence.
-Take a leave of what?
Queenan is dead.
I'm your boss now.
I don't give a fuck. I'd rather
hand in my papers first.
World needs plenty of
bartenders. Two weeks with pay!
Good.
-Piece of shit.
-Fuck off.
-I need those codes.
-No.
You want those codes.
So where the fuck were you?
Well, boss told me to go home.
Whatever. Maybe he
did, maybe he didn't.
But you weren't at fucking home.
So where the fuck were you?
I was at the grocery store
with no signal, alright?
When I got the signal,
I got the call.
What the fuck do you want from me?
Was I there or was I not there?
Billy. Billy.
Yeah?
You know what I thought today?
What's that?
Who didn't show up
today is the rat.
Yeah?
So?
And you never been
late in your life.
When I called you...
I made a mistake.
I gave you the wrong address...
but you showed up
at the right one...
didn't you?
Tell me why I didn't
tell nobody, huh?
Tell me why.
That cop was tough. We were
excessive with the cop.
He's dead.
I'm going home.
Your guys should not
have done that.
One of us had to die.
With me it tends to
be the other guy.
Yeah. But Queenan. Now I got no access.
You killed the guy
who had all the the information.
Now Dignam's gone. Forget about him.
He resigned.
I don't give a fuck about Dignam.
Yeah, he put in his papers, Frank.
He left. I don't know where he is.
Don't get your balls
in an uproar, Collie.
That Irish pissant...
he's so hot for me,
we give him a whiff
of my ass, he'll
crawl right in it.
Let's give him a whiff.
I will.
Don't worry. I'll take care of it.
Sweetheart.
You're giving me a hard-on.
Are you sure it's me?
Not all that talk about
whiffing and crawling up asses?
Watch your fucking mouth.
No. You watch it.
Let me straighten you out.
I tried to call you a few times.
I know.
Listen, I...I can't be
a friend to you.
I'm sorry.
Yeah...
I know.
Yeah.
You called this number
on a dead guy's phone.
Who are you?
So it is you.
Well, thank God you're all
right. We were very worried.
Who are you?
This is Sergeant Sullivan.
I'm taking over Queenan's unit.
Let me talk to Dignam
to confirm it.
Staff Sergeant Dignam...
is on a leave of absence.
He's very upset.
We're all very upset.
I think the best thing would
be for you to come in.
We need you to come
in. Can you come in?
We'll meet...
Police confirm the body
of the man found dead...
in the Fenway marshes yesterday afternoon...
is that of Timothy Delahunt,
an undercover policeman for...
the city of Boston. This
was the scene yesterday...
when Delahunt's body was found
in the marshes near the Fenway.
As for who did this or why...
that's something police
are working on right now.
-I don't believe it.
-What can't you believe?
I spent all fucking night dragging
the poor bastard in there.
Tell me how they
found him so fast.
Somebody walking a fucking
dog in three feet of mud?
What kind of fucking
size of dog is that?
Must have been a big
fucking dog, man.
I spent all fucking
night doing it, man.
I'm embarrassed.
I still don't believe he was
a cop. I don't believe it.
The cops are saying he's a cop...
so I won't look for the cop.
Are you soft, Fitz?
When I tell you to dump
a body in the marsh...
you dump him in the marsh!
Not where some guy from John
Hancock goes every Thursday...
to get a fucking blowjob!
Don't laugh!
This ain't reality TV!
Proceed.
-What?
-Yeah.
You got a tail. Two
cars. Not very subtle.
They're not gonna be
subtle from now on.
That's what I've
been trying to say.
So get rid of them.
There's no need for you
to go yourself, Frank.
Get rid of the fucking tail!
Alright.
Fucking rats. It's
wearing me thin.
Francis, it's a nation
of fucking rats.
Stop, stop. Pull
them off Costello.
There's no need to surveil him.
-What the fuck are you talking about?
-I got it from an undercover.
He knows he's being followed.
So let's just let the UC take him in.
-What undercover?
-Queenan's guy.
He called me when he found out
Queenan was dead. I'm running him.
You're running him? You give him to me.
No, no. I can give you
Costello's destination.
-You know where he's going?
-Yes. And what he's doing.
So get rid of the tail, get
Special Ops on standby.
-We'll take this prick tonight.
-Alright, let's go. Now.
All units fall back.
Alright, it's the warehouse he
owns over on Sheffield.
He's gotta have a container or a
truck or something there. Go, go, go, go.
Load it.
Frank, how do you know you
don't have a tail, huh?
Were you not in the fucking car?
Yeah, what if they took one off
and they put another one on?
Load.
Go, go.
Come on, what are you waiting for?!
Frank wants me to check
the back, alright? You go ahead.
-Watch your fucking back.
-Move out. Go on.
Cocksuckers.
Motherfucking shit.
Motherfucking.
Back the fuck up.
They fucking shot me.
Get down.
Come on, fucking bastards.
Fuck it.
How the fuck did this happen?
You're an FBI informant?
Are you fucking kidding me?
Grow up.
Of course I talk to the FBI.
Do they know who I am?
I never gave up anybody who
wasn't going down anyway.
Nobody knows nothing.
Frank.
Frank. Frank.
Do they know about me?
I know about you, Collie.
You know I'd never give you up.
-You're like a...
-What? Like a son?
To you? Is that
what this is about?
All that murdering and
fucking, and no sons.
Fucking rat prick.
Frank?
Yeah?
Who's this?
Gwen?
Where the hell's Frank?
Frank got shot.
Gwen, we lost Frank.
I got him!
I got Costello here!
Hey, good job, Sarge.
No, it's...
For you.
-Thank you.
-No. Thank you.
He's been waiting here
a long time for you.
How'd you get him
without the files?
-Caller ID on Queenan's phone.
-Hmm.
You know that guy?
Yeah. We were classmates
in the academy together.
Good to see you, trooper.
Yeah.
Colin Sullivan. We
spoke on the phone.
-Yeah.
-So.
Now, how long were you undercover?
Long time.
-Long fucking time.
-Yeah. Yeah.
Well, I can't even
tell you the debt...
I just want you to know I'll be
recommending you for
the Medal of Merit.
-Oh, yeah?
-Yeah.
That's kind of like a gold
star around here, huh?
It's the highest honour we got.
Look, I just want my
identity back, alright?
-That's all.
-Alright.
I understand. You
wanna be a cop again.
No, no.
Being a cop's not an identity.
I want my identity back.
Check your computer. Go on. You'll
have to excuse my behaviour.
My only contact in the last six
months has been a police shrink.
How's that working for you?
Is it helpful?
What are you gonna do about
Costello's rat in this building?
-I'm gonna find the prick.
-Yeah.
I'm gonna find him,
I'm gonna arrest him.
Good.
If there's anything you can do to help me...
You know, I mean, did Frank ever
mention a name? You
know, anything.
Someone he was in contact with.
Anything you can give me.
I'm all done being
a cop, alright?
I just want my money
and I wanna go home.
Alright. That'll be the
best thing I think for everybody.
Fair enough.
I just, I can't, can't get into your
file unless I have your password.
It's my name.
William Costigan Jr.
They gave it to me
in case I had to
explain myself to
someone like you.
It's your name.
Alright.
Uh...fucking unreal, that's...
Well, makes a lot of sense.
Listen, Bill, I gotta run
this in the other room.
This computer's getting all
frigging blooey on me.
Give me two minutes. I'll have
you out of here in no time.
Alright, everything checks
out, so let's get you paid.
I know.
I know. I'm not... I'm
not here for that, okay?
I'm not.
Listen. I've gotta
give you something.
Something I need you to keep.
For me.
Okay?
What is it?
This is for you to hold. Only you.
You open this if something
happens to me or
if I call you and I
tell you to open it.
You're the only person I
can trust, alright?
Please.
-Alright.
-Look, I'm sorry to even...
I'm sorry to even show up
here like this, you know?
I... There's just no one
else I could give it to.
There's no one else.
-I'm really sorry.
-I...um.
You know, I have...um.
-I...
-Whatever you have to say...
think about it real
hard, alright?
If you still wanna tell me, you
tell me in two weeks, okay?
I was dreaming I was dead.
Death is hard. Life
is much easier.
-What's this?
-Open it.
-Really?
-Yeah.
Really?
Yeah.
And they, they say that
this little speck...
is a penis.
Wow. It's a boy.
Yeah, well, one usually
follows the other.
Can you still uh...
I hope I won't have
to remind you...
that if you don't find
this cheese-eating
rat bastard in your department...
you can assume it won't
be me who pays for it.
Now, why would you have
to remind me of that?
Would I? Would I be
any good at what I do
if I didn't fucking
already know that?
Frank, you gotta trust
me. I can get the rat.
You just gotta let me
do it my way, Frank.
Just let me do it.
Let me do what I do.
Hey, it fucking
involves lying and I'm
pretty fucking good
at that. Right?
What?
-We got a cop in my crew.
-Yeah, I know.
I'm kind of getting
that feeling too.
He's one of yours. Inside.
-You seen anything?
-Frank.
I got no access to
Queenan's undercover
files. He and Dignam
run the snitches.
I'm doing my...
You know what, I thought
I was the liar.
Hey, I can explain that.
Costello recorded everything.
He put all the tapes
in a little box and kept them
with his lawyer. That
was his insurance.
His lawyer came to me.
Imagine that, you rat fuck.
Costello trusted me
more than anyone.
Sound quality good enough?
Because I was a little worried.
What do you want?
I told you I want
my identity back...
you two-faced faggot.
Alright, where are you?
Three o'clock. Where Queenan died.
You keep your cell on.
Open the door.
Open... Didn't we already
talk about this?
This is my job.
Freeze! Get your fucking hands up!
Hey! Hey! Hey!
Put the fucking gun down!
Put the gun, put the gun down,
alright? I came
here to talk some sense into you.
-Hands!
-Alright, just act professional.
-I can get you your money.
-What did you say?
I can get you your money.
You didn't come here
to talk, alright?
-You came here to get arrested.
-You got fucking tapes? Of what?
Costello was my informant. I
was a rat? Fuck you. Prove it.
He was working for me.
He was my informant.
Shut your fucking
mouth. Come on, get up.
What is this, a citizen's
arrest? Blow me, alright?
Only one of us is a cop here,
Bill. You understand that, Bill?
-No one knows who you fucking are!
-Will you shut the fuck up?!
I'm a sergeant in
the Massachusetts
State Police. Who
the fuck are you?
-I erased you.
-You erased me, huh?
Yeah, go ahead, shoot a cop,
Einstein. Watch what happens.
What would happen is this bullet
would go right through your fucking head!
Watch what happens!
What, so you can get
the parade, huh?
The bagpipes and
bullshit? Fuck you!
Fuck you, I'm fucking
arresting you!
That's the stupidest
thing you could do.
Shut the fuck up.
I could give a fuck if
the charges don't stick.
I'm still fucking arresting you.
Get up.
Drop your weapon and step
away from Sergeant Sullivan.
I called you. You
specifically. Look,
You know who I am.
I'm not gonna shoot.
-I told you to meet me downstairs.
-Help me, help, help, help!
Put your weapon on the deck and
step away from Sergeant Sullivan.
Where's Dignam? I told
you to bring Dignam.
Shoot this motherfucker!
Would you fucking shoot?
Drop your weapon to the floor
and we'll discuss it.
Look, he's Costello's
rat, alright?
I got boxes of tapes. Evidence.
Other documents proving it.
Maybe you do.
But right now I need you
to drop the weapon.
I told you, I have evidence cold-linking
this prick to Costello, alright?
Would you shoot
this fucking prick?
You know who I am.
-You know who I am.
-Shoot this fucking prick.
I'm taking him downstairs now.
You know who I am.
Shut up.
I can't wait to see you explain
this to a fucking Suffolk County jury...
you fucking cocksucker.
This is gonna be fucking fun.
Just fucking kill me.
I am killing you.
Did you think you were the
only one he had on the inside?
Costello was gonna
sell us to the FBI.
It's you and me now,
you understand?
We gotta take care of each
other, you understand?
Give me that.
Right. Slow. March.
I attempted to subdue
Trooper Barrigan...
at which time he
drew down on me, and
I was able to squeeze
off one shot...
and strike him in the head.
At that time I immediately
checked the vitals...
on both Troopers Brown
and Costigan...
and discovered that
they had expired.
I just wanna go on record.
I'm recommending William
Costigan for the Medal of Merit.
Eternal rest grant
unto him, O Lord.
Ready?
And let perpetual
light shine upon him.
Fold.
May he rest in peace. Amen.
May his soul and the souls...
of all the faithful
departed, through
the mercy of God, rest in peace.
Amen.
Detail. Half left. Face.
Prepare to fire.
Fire.
Prepare to fire. Fire.
Detail. Half right. Face.
I'll catch up with you guys.
What about the baby?
Hi, pup.
Okay.