My poor baby.
Who has stolen the child's dream?
The mad genius Krank
in his evil scheme.
To what vicious depths
will he not descend?
Will the tale turn to tragedy...
or have a happy end?
Step up, ladies and gentlemen!
Step right up! Come closer.
Don't be afraid.
See the strongest man in the world.
Look at those chains,
made of the same steel...
as that used to lift...
Yes, my friends...
The true light is invisible.
Penetrate the corridor of shadows...
and you will enter
the world of the chosen ones.
Renounce the gift of sight.
I know there are skeptics among you...
afraid to share with us
the dead of night.
Be brave.
Renounce your gift of sight.
Pluck out your eyes.
Come and join us.
Help us build a better world.
The crusher Bones is going to try
once more to shatter steel...
only using the power
of his mighty arms.
Please, ladies and gentlemen,
I want absolute silence...
during the demonstration.
I must beg of you,
for your own safety...
not to look him in the eye...
because his power of concentration
is so great...
that he might provoke
a cerebral hemorrhage...
in the weaker ones among you.
Mr. One, ready?
And now, attention!
Little thief!
Stealing money from orphans.
I'll teach you!
Let go of that!
What's going on?
What's the matter?
The poor man's not well.
Don't move!
Don't move or I'll waste you!
Denree!
Kill him!
- Who's that?
- He's the strong man at the fun fair.
I don't know him.
What do you want?
I have lost little brother.
He didn't come all by himself.
Well, well, kiddies, hard at work?
It looks like you're doing
really well.
Thanks for waiting for us.
Thank you.
Just remember,
my ears are so sharp...
that I can hear you think.
Go buy yourself some sweets.
Don't overdo it.
Come on. Move your bum.
Go on. Here.
Move it!
Get the tools and let's beat it.
Those rotten Cyclops.
Don't worry.
We know where to find them.
And him?
What about him?
You helped us out.
Here. Now we're even.
Hey, girl. Cyclops.
You know where to find Cyclops?
Will you get lost?
Beat it!
Happy birthday, Uncle dear
Our wish is most sincere
We hope this cake of ours
will bring you happiness
Good fortune and success
Wait till the candles are blown out!
In fair or foul weather
We'll always be together
Happy birthday, Uncle Irvin.
A cake for me?
You're really too kind.
Are you ready, children?
Not you.
You've got a cold.
One, two.
What is all this bellowing about?
But, sweetheart,
it's Irvin's birthday.
Irvin's birthday?
Why, of course.
How could I have forgotten?
Let us celebrate.
Let us all make merry.
Everyone, let's shout!
Scream out!
Krank, come back.
I had a thought last night.
If these children
only have nightmares...
it's perhaps
because the evil is in you.
Why not seek the cause
of your torment...
in the molecular study
of your own tears?
Who could make me cry?
Well, boss...
we could make you cry
with laughter.
I am a gnome
a bag of bones
A man of means
and full of beans
The girls in Spain
sing my refrains
I've such a pain
that it's insane
You mustn't be angry.
Your brothers are doing their best.
My brothers?
May I give it a try?
Go ahead, mollusk.
Once upon a time,
there was an inventor so gifted...
that he could create life.
- Truly remarkable man.
- Ah, a fairy tale.
I can already feel tears
in my eyes.
Since he had no wife or children...
he decided to make them
in his laboratory.
He started with his wife
and fashioned her...
into the most beautiful princess
in the world.
Alas, a wicked genetic fairy
cast a spell on the inventor...
so much so that the princess
was only knee-high to a grasshopper.
He then cloned six children
in his own image.
Faithful, hardworking,
they were so alike...
no one could tell them apart.
But fate tricked him again,
giving them all sleeping sickness.
Craving someone to talk to,
he grew in a fish tank...
a poor migraine-ridden brain.
And then, at last,
he created his masterpiece...
more intelligent than
the most intelligent man on Earth.
But, alas, the inventor
made a serious mistake.
While his creation was intelligent,
he, too, had a defect.
He never, ever had a dream.
You can't imagine
how quickly he grew old...
because he was so unhappy.
Boss.
There!
An eye dropper, quick!
An eye dropper!
Then the poor masterpiece
became so crazed...
that he believed
a single teardrop could save him.
And, after committing
many cruel deeds...
he died a horrible death...
never knowing
what it is to dream.
Get out!
All of you, get out!
Good-bye, Uncle. Happy birthday.
See you tonight.
Silence...
you glub!
What do you expect us
to do with that?
I wouldn't waste a nail
to hang it up.
But it's pretty, isn't it?
Don't get smart with us.
The picklock won't always
be there to save your behind.
All right, get lost.
- That's all?
- Afraid so.
If you keep being sassy...
You'll be sorry.
There's no shortage
of orphans, Miette.
Listen carefully, Tadpole.
You don't want to go
to the hole, do you?
- It's very cold there.
- And pitch black.
And full of spiders.
So give us all the rest.
The rest.
There's a fine lad.
See? When you want to.
Now, the second shift.
The neighborhood's calm, isolated.
But be careful.
You never know.
There's a backyard.
You'll go that way
with all the stuff.
On the landing,
there are three doors.
One is locked from inside.
That's the one that must be forced.
Behind is what interests us.
Here's the prize.
It's identical to the one
where he hides his loot.
The problem with this safe:
It takes two hours to crack it.
Two hours?
We're going to get caught.
We have no choice, unless you know
someone capable of carrying it.
Somebody got in.
- You big idiot!
- He's right here now.
Do I pay you to sleepwalk?
Who is this guy?
- Don't ask me.
- I know who he is.
The strong man at the fair,
the one who breaks his chains.
Are you thinking what I'm thinking?
Nice going, Mr. One.
One don't like whistles.
One not thief.
A thief? Who's a thief?
We're not stealing, just borrowing.
What he said?
He said you can take it back.
It just won't be as heavy.
- The true light.
- Little brother.
Renounce the gift of sight
and penetrate the corridor of shadows...
the world of the blind.
That guy is crazy.
The Octopus will kill us.
Tell her I'll bring him back.
I won't be long.
Help us build a better world...
or we shall witness
a reign of terror.
One! Where do you think you're going?
Cyclops truck.
Denree, little brother.
What about the truck?
Cyclops truck.
Kidnap Denree.
Kidnap little brother.
You know something?
You won't find Cyclops truck like that.
When you get there,
someone will have eaten Denree.
The wolf will have eaten him.
Take a break.
No use wearing out your shoes.
I know where the truck's going.
Miette and One together?
And then what?
And anyway, how old
was this brother of yours?
Little, little brother.
Found him...
one night...
on his rubbish bin, crying.
One comes close.
Discover...
Okay, I can guess the rest.
He's just like I thought.
He's too little to bother.
Let's go.
We have to get out of here.
Stupid!
Lmbecile! Idiot!
Have you finished?
My crystal glasses are broken!
You'll crack my chandelier!
Are you calmer now?
One look for Denree.
See you.
Oh, come on, fat head.
- Where did those brats go?
- I don't know.
It's the big guy's fault.
Miette's different since he came.
Does he have all the jewels?
That's all he's interested in?
You had big ideas?
Poor little Tadpole.
You haven't fallen in love, too,
like the others? Get to bed!
- Filthy brats.
- All the same.
We really can't count on them.
- Raise crows, they'll rip out...
- Your eyes.
- It's the best ones who want to go.
- It's not the first time it's happened.
It's always the same old story.
- Remember little Lucas six years ago?
- And Marcus before.
Yes, Marcus.
I'd almost forgotten him.
- When we think...
- Of everything we've done for them.
And if she had an accident?
You never know.
At that moment, the winkles
suddenly break into a dance...
then cast off their shells
and begin to use them as megaphones...
to announce the concert.
Winkles, winkles.
Shells, shells.
And then, at that moment...
all the winkles
cast off their shells...
and use them as megaphones
to announce the concert.
The winkles?
The winkles cast off their shells?
Please continue.
Continue, and with colors as well.
Yes, yes, yes.
Then the hammerhead shark plays
xylophone with the catfish bones.
The walrus plays
the Jew's harp with the...
the sperm whale's suspenders.
The sea is blue like the sky...
and the sky is blue
like the South Seas.
And I don't know
if I'm swimming in the sky or...
or flying at the bottom
of the sea.
I swear it gives me the shivers.
Shivers? Shivers all over.
And igloos?
Oh, yes, tell me about the igloos.
Igloos that turn into mushrooms.
Ah, it's you, my boy.
I was expecting you.
Not so loud. Turn it down.
The boss might hear you.
The boss? He's out of a test tube,
like all of us.
Lay the boy in the sarcophagus
and come here.
But before...
Well, you promised me...
What's tormenting you, my son?
Well, this story that among us
there's an original clone...
different from the others.
Is that true?
Of course it's true. The others
are nothing but cheap copies...
while the original one is unique.
- Unique?
- Yes.
And do you know who it is?
Do you really want to know?
Connect yourself to the child.
- To the child?
- Yes.
Connect myself to the child?
But I can't.
It's forbidden.
Exactly.
The others wouldn't dare,
but you, you can do it...
because you're the original.
Me?
I'm the original?
But it's not lonely
being the original?
All the penguins, the centipedes,
everyone applauds.
Except, even if you climb
to the treetops...
it's impossible to catch
the candy floss.
And so, everybody climbs
to the top of the mountain...
except the giraffes who, of course,
stay in one spot...
munching the clouds.
Sleep.
Sleep, my little one.
I am the sandman...
and you can't resist me.
Your eyelids are so heavy.
Sleep, my little one.
The snowflakes evaporate...
and then turn into hailstones.
In the farmyards...
the turkeys scramble towards...
the hailstones.
The better to peck them?
And then when the children's voices
cry for help...
the chickens are merciless.
There.
Now he's going to come around
very nicely.
- Who, the boss?
- No, the child.
He's a real nightmare factory.
- What's that? A fuse blew!
- Perfect.
Be careful.
Someone will hear you.
It's hard to be original.
Now, throw this message...
uh, bottle into the sea.
- Yes.
- Go on!
May someone find my plea
to get it over with.
I...
Gabriel Marie...
I came into this world
with open eyes...
but I saw a world...
that was a world of dogs.
Litter of dogs!
And so, the creator...
sent me down here to Earth...
to recover the power...
that men have illegally seized.
My brothers...
you who have joined me
in this struggle...
understand that together
we must fight...
human beings...
from their own grounds.
The world...
of appearances.
I thought we had agreed
on half a dozen.
But you know it's becoming
more and more difficult.
People are suspicious.
They've put up posters.
In any case, this batch
is as fresh as they come.
Not one of them
is over five years old.
Listen. Let us have
maybe a couple of hours...
and we'll sort this thing out.
Only the third eye...
will enable you to enter...
the world of appearances.
But beware...
because this sordid world
of temptation and perversion...
is also the world of desire.
Try, Brother Angel Joseph...
to discover it...
without your losing sight...
of the only true light.
Be strong.
My brothers...
our grace...
our great superior race...
shall reign once more...
on Earth!
From that day on...
our faithful third eye...
will become useless...
as the world of appearances...
will be abolished.
It's Denree.
I see!
What's that?
That, Brother Angel Joseph...
is a female.
- A female.
- Do you have a problem?
What's that?
That is a condemned man.
Take them. Go on!
Come back when those idiots
have had enough.
Search her!
What is it?
Kill her!
She's clean.
Then tomorrow night at Pier 24.
100,000.
We'll never get half that.
One more scrap of information.
A girl in a red dress...
with a big moron.
We found these on them.
But there was much more in the...
What'll you do with them?
A midnight snack for the fishes,
tonight, Pier 24.
A midnight snack for the fishes.
- Irvin?
- Such a migraine.
You know all about feelings.
Won't you try to help me?
Won't you explain why all those children
only have nightmares?
'Cause you were their nightmare.
You can persecute
all the children in the world...
but there's one thing
you'll never have.
- What?
- A soul.
Because you believe you have one?
You don't even have a body.
He who created us
made us all monsters.
No, Krank, you're wrong.
You are the only monster here.
Be quiet!
He's the only one responsible.
For that, I say I'm innocent.
I'm innocent!
Anyway...
I thank you for your help.
Hurry up! And don't break
any of the baubles.
Well done.
And don't cut yourself.
Are you sure that we're doing
the right thing?
Of course, my pet.
All children love it.
Lift your elbow.
Why worry, Krank?
If you're sincere,
you have nothing to lose.
How are you, Marcello?
What's it to you?
We need you, Marcello,
and your creepy-crawlies.
Have you still got the knack?
No, please, not again.
I paid enough already.
- Nice place...
- You've got here, Marcello.
I'm glad to see
it hasn't changed much.
You know, I never liked
that blue cage.
You were always so kind
to us, Marcello.
- It's only fair...
- That we look after you...
Today.
- A little girl in a red dress...
- With a big moron.
We want him.
And what do I do with her?
A midnight snack for the fishes.
Come on, my little flea.
There, there.
Easy does it.
Midnight snack for the fishes.
Will you shut up, you idiots?
- It wasn't me.
- I don't care.
Work this out among yourselves.
How dare you hit the original.
You, the original?
Have you looked in the mirror lately?
Miette...
One will die?
You're born in the gutter.
You end up in the port.
Miette too little.
Not as little as all that.
Five thousand on the kid.
Ten thousand on the monster.
There are pebbles in the meat pie.
There are pebbles, bits of...
- Did you hear anything?
- Just them crazy birds.
- There's something over there.
- I don't see anything.
- Who is that guy there?
- What's all that monkey business?
Well, Brutus.
- I can't see anything now.
- Don't you like the music?
What you doing?
I can't see.
I don't want to be dead.
Jump! Go on! Jump!
Save Miette!
Hurry! Jump!
Found, West Pier,
eve of St. John.
Oh, it's a miracle!
She's come to.
Spit!
Feel better? Look at me.
Are you all right?
You're very lucky that I came by.
Haven't I seen you somewhere?
I doubt it.
No one ever sees me.
I'm always underwater.
Why?
It's dangerous up there.
- He wants to kill me.
- Who?
I can't remember anything.
Some people lose their marbles.
And me, I've lost my memory.
I'm glad you're here.
I bring in more than enough stuff
for two.
Look.
You see, I'm a treasure hunter.
The city's history is here.
Cast into the sea
and forgotten forever.
- I see.
- I'm here, cataloging, dating.
Wait. That's the land shark's safe.
Oh, yes.
Yes, I brought it in yesterday.
And this is Vito Nine Fingers.
Everyone thought he ran away
with his money.
They're wrong.
What are you doing?
I stole them.
I'm taking back what's mine.
Don't go back up there.
It's dangerous!
You're a kid.
Stay with me.
Well, thanks for everything,
but I've got to go.
Not that way.
- The children.
- What about them? What do you know?
He takes them.
The devil takes them away...
in his boat.
He takes them to hell.
- What hell?
- The Tattooed Man, he knows where.
The map.
The map of the minefield
is tattooed on his body.
It's all my fault.
This man's a proper nutcase.
Holy cow, it's little brother again.
Miette.
Take care of him.
He's hopeless.
Sure.
What's the trouble, handsome?
There's no reason to be depressed.