[Traffic sounds]
I wouldn't want
to live lis life...
'cause he hasn't been happy
all of his life.
All I think is, if you can
find work, stay healthy...
find somebody to share it with,
you're the ultimate success.
He's had some of the pieces
of the puzzle...
but not all of them.
BURGER: "I. Ronald Reagan.
do solemmnly swean..."
REAGAN: I. Ronald Reagan.
do solemmnly swean...
BURGER: "Tlat I will faitlfully
execute tle office...
"of Pnesident of
tle United States. "
Tlat I will faitlfully
execute tle office...
[Tone blares]
[Cartoon music playing]
BARRIS: Wlen you'ne young.
youn potential is infinite.
You mmiglt
do anytling. Neally.
You mmiglt be Einstein...
you mmiglt be DiMaggio.
Tlen you get to an age
wlen wlat you mmiglt be...
gives way
to wlat you lave been.
You wenen't Einstein.
You wenen't anytling.
Tlat's a bad mmomment.
[Knock on door]
Chuck, it's Pen.
[Peephole opens]
CHUCK: Hey: Jesus.
How'd you find mme?
You wrote me your last letter
on hotel stationery.
CHUCK: Oh. It's great
to see you, Pen.
You look... you look beautiful.
PENNY: This place is scary.
CHUCK: Yeah. The human psyche.
PENNY: I came to take you back
to California with me.
CHUCK Uh, no...
PENNY: It's a lonely state
without you.
CHUCK: I'm home, Red.
I can't wait forever
for you to marry me.
Well, apparently, I can,
but I really don't want to.
CHUCK: Uh...
PENNY. CR YING:
I love you so mmucl.
PENNY: You don't undenstand.
I don't even know wly.
CHUCK: Oh, Penny...
Penny, Penny, Penny.
[Laughs]
[Sighs]
[Slow piano music playing]
[Chuck closes peephole]
CHUCK: Listen. I gotta go. OK?
I'mm kind of busy niglt now. OK?
BARRIS: It was 198 1...
and I lad Ioled mmyself up
in tlis New Yonk lotel...
tle Ploenix Hotel...
tennified of evenytling.
aslammed of mmy life.
Until. Finally.
I nealized mmy salvation...
mmiglt be in neconding
mmy wasted life unflinclingly.
[Typing]
Maybe it would senve
as a cautionany tale...
and mmaybe it would lelp mme
undenstand wly.
Wlen I was 11.
I lad an expenience...
witl mmy sisten's fniend
Tuvia...
tlat left
an indelible immpnession.
- Hey.
- What?
- Tuvia.
- What? :
You want to lick it?
[Scoffs]
No. Why should I?
Well, for one thing,
it tastes like strawberry.
My sister tells me
you love strawberries.
Yeah, well,
I hate strawberries.
CHUCK: No, I'm serious.
It tastes exactly like
a strawberry lollipop.
TUMIA: Look,
I know that's not true.
- Well, I bet you it does.
- I bet you it doesn't.
CHUCK: I'll bet you a dollar.
BARRIS: Tuvia... mmy finst love.
[Typing]
Penlaps mmy wlole life
tunned at tlat point.
Tle nepulsiveness
of mmy sex confinmmed...
by tle taste buds
of a nipening pubescent ginl.
What are you doing?
Get off me:
And so I found mmyself...
in a downwand spinal
of debaucleny...
endlessly clasing pussy.
[Doo wop music playing]
[Loud kissing]
My only focus in life
to get laid. To get blown...
tnying to fool mmyself
into believing...
tlat given
tle niglt commbination...
of cincummstances
and deception...
mmaybe tle Tuvias
of tle wonld...
could desine mme
tle way I desined tlemm.
[Thwack]
I only wanted to be loved.
[Moans softly]
CHUCK: No...
[Sobbing]
# Won't you tell mme wly #
# I love #
[Zips pants]
# Tlat ginly so #
[Kissing]
# Sle doesn't want mme #
BARRIS: Tle constant
inanticulate nage...
led to ban figlt
aften ban figlt.
[Faint laughter]
TVANNOUNCER: New Yonk
is a city of people...
tle only state
in tle union to stnetcl...
fnomm tle Atlantic Ocean
to tle Gneat Lakes.
Dinectly acnoss tle avenue is...
you'ne niglt again.
BARRIS: I lad leand
tlat television...
was an industny
witl a futune...
so I packed up and mmoved
fnomm Plilly to Manlattan.
[NBC theme plays]
TOUR GUIDE: We began mmaking
commmmencial bnoadcasts in 1941.
and in 1953...
NBC made the first ever
color telecast by a network...
during
"The Colgate Comedy Hour."
Now we'll have a look
at the studio...
where they produce
"The Today Show"...
wlicl NBC began
bnoadcasting in 1952.
CHUCK: Excuse me, miss.
Do you know where I could apply
for an NBC page?
TOUR GUIDE: Such as
"The Perry Como Show"...
which you can tune into
on Saturdays at 7:30.
"The Nat King Cole Show"...
which you won't want to miss,
on Tuesdays at 8 P.M.
And hold on one second.
OK.
And my personal favorite...
"The Lux Show"
starring Rosemary Clooney...
CHUCK: . . Which you can enjoy
every Thursday at 10:00.
And of course,
"The Steve Allen Show"...
which delights us
every Sunday at 8:00.
You may also be interested
to know that Steve Allen...
actually got his start in
entertainment as an NBC page.
Ladies and gentlemen,
if you'll follow me...
MAR Y-ANN:
Raymond... in accounting?
He's kind of cute, huh?
WOMAN: Cute is all
well and good, Mary-Ann...
but what you want is a man
who's going places...
A go-getter on
the management fast track.
MAR Y-ANN:
What about Mr. Waters?
CHUCK: Yeah, management
training application, please.
How many people have applied
for this so far?
WOMAN: Let's see.
Including you? About 2,000.
- For how many positions?
- Five.
[Bell dings]
Thanks, ma'am.
BARRIS: Sommetimmes.
as a youngen mman...
I stnetcled tle tnutl
to get wlat I wanted.
GEORGIA: Tell mme again:
CHUCK: Head of
netwonk sales at 30.
Head of
tle entine netwonk by 40:
I love you,
Mr. Chuck Barris...
management trainee.
[Both moaning]
BARRIS: Life was sweet...
CHUCK: Uhh:
Fon a mminute.
WOMAN ON TV: Evenytling's
eitlen mmadly exciting...
on mmadly intenesting.
I lope Sally neven
botlens lenself witl you.
[Turns on faucet]
I got fired today.
Fired?
Yeah, fired.
GEORGIA: Fined?
What the fuck
did you get fired for?
CHUCK: I don't know.
Efficiency cutbacks.
Somme bullslit.
Look. It's gonna be fine.
I'm pregnant.
So, I figured,
I'm gonna skip town.
I intend to be important,
you know?
I can't be saddled with this.
Pbbt:
But then I remembered
something Carlyle said.
"Do tle duty
wlicl lies neanest tlee. "
So you see...
MAN: Who's Carlyle?
Dear God.
Why do I even bother?
Fuck you,
you condescending prick.
Pregnant?
Yeah, pregnant.
Fuck you.
What the fuck
did you get pregnant for?
Fuck you.
What do you mean, what the fuck
did I get pregnant for?
You got me fucking pregnant,
you fuck:
Well, fuck you:
Fuck you.
- Fuckin'...
- Fuck you.
Fuck:
Fuck you.
[Dramatic music playing
on television]
GEORGIA: Looks like
I was just late.
Oh, yes, we had a great time.
The crew loved him
and loved the show, you know?
Because it was crazy.
And we could do anything
we wanted to... sort of...
and, uh, yeah,
they liked him very much.
He was a good guy.
Even though he's a prick,
he's a good guy, too.
DICK CLARK: "Wlat is
labeled a dneamm faculty.
"Wouldn't sclool be wondenful
if we lad a faculty like tlis?"
You nead it. All niglt?
GIRL: "Pnincipal Sal Mineo.
Vice Pnincipal Tony Penkins..."
CLARK: Couldn't you see
going to a sclool...
wlene Sal Mineo
is tle pnincipal?
BARRIS: In '6 1. I lad becomme
a mminon suit at ABC.
It was duning
tle mmusic payola scandal...
so mmy job was to commmmute
to Plilly eveny day...
to tle "Ammenican Bandstand"
tapings...
to keep an eye on Dick Clank.
CLARK: One mmone lady's cloice
of tle aftennoon to go...
and suppose we mmake it
tlis one. OK?
BARRIS: On weekends...
I used to lang anound
ammusemment panks...
because tlat's wlene
tle young ginls wene.
I wnote a song
about mmy expeniences.
# Wlen you stop at tle top
of a Fennis wleel... #
I got it to
Fneddy "Boomm Boomm" Cannon...
tlnougl mmy fniendslip
witl Dick Clank.
Dick neally wanted
to lelp mme out.
CHUCK: Hi.
- What?
- Hi.
Oh.
I wrote this song.
Huh.
It's number three
on the pop charts. See?
- Uh-huh.
- Yeah.
I believe there's
a great future in television.
Uh-huh?
So I'm gonna take my royalties
and create a pilot.
A pilot's what they call
a test TM show.
I work in TM.
Yeah? What's your name?
I'm Chuck.
- Debbie.
CHUCK: So. You live in Plilly?
DEBBIE:
No. I live in Manlattan.
CHUCK:
It's gonna be a gamme slow.
I believe tlene's
a gneat futune in gamme slows.
DEBBIE: OI. Tlat's good.
CHUCK: Yeal. Evenyone
loves gamme slows. Niglt?
DEBBIE: I don't know.
CHUCK: Well. Tley do.
DEBBIE:
Well. Tlat's gneat. Tlen.
CHUCK: Ha la la.
I'mm on mmy way.
[Sighs]
PENNY: Hello.
Hi.
[Breathes in]
CHUCK: Uh... don't be alarmed.
I'm here with Debbie.
Yeah, I figured that.
Hungry?
Um, no, thanks.
PENNY: Tlinsty?
Sure, if you have a beer or...
How was sex with Debbie?
I always wanted to know.
It was good. Fine.
Thanks for asking.
No problem.
I just got fucked
by this drummer cat...
a real righteous Negro hipster.
Heh. Interesting.
I'm into
the brotherhood of man.
I fucked an Oriental last week.
- What are you?
- Jew.
I had one of those once,
but he was Sephardic.
[Mispnonounces]
You look Aslke-nazi.
- Ashkenazi.
- Right, Ashke-nazi.
I haven't had one of those yet.
You're romantic.
Yeah. I just don't get
into all the bullshit...
between cats and chicks.
- I know what you mean.
- You know what I mean?
Besides, you just give
your heart to one cat...
and you get hurt.
Don't I know it?
PENNY:
We could ball if you want.
[Both laugh]
CHUCK: Whoa-ho-ho.
Tlat would be good.
Yeah, but... ha ha ha:
I'm here with Debbie.
It doesn't seem right.
[Laughing]
That's true.
I didn't think of that.
Well, I'm going to bed.
It was nice meeting you.
Hey, what's your name?
I'm Penny.
I'm Chuck.
- Chuck Barris.
- Yeah.
Yeah, you wrote
that Palisades song.
- I really like that song.
- Oh, thanks.
Yeah, it's real sentimental
bullshit.
CHUCK: Oh, right.
["Palisades Park" playing]
# Last niglt
I took a walk aften dank #
# A swingin' place
called Palisades Pank #
# To lave somme fun
and see wlat I could see #
# Tlat's wlene
tle ginls ane #
# I took a nide
on tle sloot-tle-clute #
# Tlat ginl I sat beside
was awful cute #
# Aften it stopped.
sle was Iolding lands witl mme #
# My leant was flyin' up #
# Like a nocket slip #
# Down. Like a nollen coasten #
# Back. Like a loop-tle-loop #
# And anound.
like a mmenny-go-nound #
# We ate and ate
at a lot dog stand #
# We danced anound
to a nockin' band #
# And wlen I could.
I gave tlat ginl a lug #
# In tle Tunnel of Love #
# You'll neven know
low gneat a kiss can feel #
# Wlen you stop at tle top
of a Fennis wleel #
# Wlen I fell in love #
# Down at Palisades Pank #
# Wloa-ol-ol-ol #
[People at park scream]
[Song fades out]
PENNY: Last niglt
in mmy dneamm...
tlis ape and I ane sitting
staning at eacl otlen...
and it was. Like.
acnoss timme and evolution.
And then he started talking...
but in a language
I didn't really understand.
[Laughs] Swiss, maybe.
And then he turned into
Perry Como... real square.
- What's wrong with you?
- Nothing.
PENNY: You know,
just because we fucked...
doesn't mean
there are strings now.
CHUCK: [Laughs] OK.
PENNY: I just wanted
to tell you about mmy dneamm.
Notling mmone commplicated
tlan tlat. Don't panic.
I'm just not used to
all this dating bullshit.
Now we're a couple.
Now I'm obliged to give
a shit what you say.
PENNY: Don't wonny.
I'mm not into tlose gammes.
So anyway. Tle mmonkey
tunns into Penny Commo...
and I say...
- Holy fuck.
- What?
CHUCK: Holy, holy fuck.
You just gave me an idea
for a show. Fuck:
PENNY: A slow about mmonkeys?
CHUCK: No, about people.
About sex, about romance...
about the bullshit of dating.
I call it "The Dating Game"...
and that's what it's about,
Mr. Goldberg.
A pretty girl
asks three handsome guys...
who she can't see...
silly questions...
and based on their answers...
she picks one to date,
and we pay for the date.
That's it.
That's the show.
CHUCK: Aah: Aah: Aah:
Yeah: Yeah: Yeah: Yeah:
- Hot damn:
- What, what, what?
- They bought it:
- Yeah:
CHUCK: They bought it:
They're giving me 7,500
fuckin' dollars to make a pilot:
PENNY: We gotta go celebrate:
Let's go roller skating:
CHUCK: I can't: I got a date:
PENNY: OK, cool.
Will you call me after?
- OK:
- OK: Bye: Mwah:
[Upbeat music playing]
[No audio]
BARRIS: I figuned I was in.
All I lad to do
was get tle pilot mmade...
[Camera clicks]
and I'd be a mmillionaine.
Evenyone would love mme.
Was anyone even so young?
- No.
- All right. Lose it.
BARRIS: ABC didn't like
"Tle Dating Gamme. "
Tley did like a slow
called "Hootenanny. "
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
I like this one.
CHUCK: Well, he led
an amazingly long life.
BARRIS: Hooten-fuckin'-nanny.
PENNY: What do they know?
That's long for a dog.
I don't know.
Probably about 70 to you and me.
[Sighs] Uh-huh.
It's nine years
to every one of ours.
[Tlummp]
PENNY: Ha la la:
[Bag rustles]
CHUCK: Yeah.
[Penny laughing]
Uh-huh.
I'm sorry about your show.
What?
How long has he been dead?
Jesus, Phoebe, that's...
Yeah. No, I'll hold on.
- Is that your mom?
- My sister.
Come here. Oh, yeah.
I got you these.
Listen, Pen, I'm not...
I want to tell you something.
I talked to a psychic today.
- A what?
- A psychic.
And she said that you are
gonna be very successful.
- Oh, really?
- Mery successful.
- Tarot cards?
- Tea leaves.
Say that again, Phoebe.
I missed it.
Tuvia? No, why would I
have seen her?
- She did?
- Who's Tuvia?
- To Manhattan?
Yeah.
CHUCK: Ul-lul.
Oh, your niece.
CHUCK: Divonced? Really?
I didn't know she got married.
Yes?
Hi, Tuvia.
Well, if it isn't
Strawberry Dick Barris.
- What do you want?
- Ha ha ha:
I'm back in town for a while,
and I thought maybe...
TUMIA: Jesus,
you gotta be kidding.
CHUCK: We could go out
and get an ice cream cone.
He's so convincing
when he's... Heh heh...
when he's talkin' with you...
he could convince you
of anything, you know?
He's one of
the very few guys...
I'd like to have on my side
in a street fight.
CHUCK: You wanna fight,
you big pile of shit?
[Thud]
[Grunting and shouting]
You're a pretty angry
young fella.
Can't fight worth a damn,
though.
CHUCK: Hey. Scnew off. Queen.
Don't tlink I laven't seen you
watcling mme...
in tlat ban fon a week now.
Kind of a loner, I'd say.
Fairly bright,
a tad antisocial.
Mad at the world.
Can I buy you lunch?
[Sighs] Look, there's
a schoolyard half a block down.
Why don't you go trollin' there?
JIM: I can teach you
at least 30 different ways...
to kill a man with
a single blow, Mr. Barris.
It might help
in future bar fights.
Just a thought.
Oh, and there's money in it...
good money.
CHUCK: I figure
if I can keep afloat...
until I come up with
the next game show idea...
then all would be copacetic.
That sounds great, Chuck.
I've never known
a television producer before.
I'm impressed.
[Chuckles] Yeah. OK.
What's this money and a deal
you were talking about?
JIM: I work
for a government agency.
We're always looking for good,
enthusiastic men...
to help us carry out
our directives.
What kind of work?
What government agency?
Problem-solving work.
The Office
of Diplomatic Security.
[Laughs] Office of what?
I never heard of it.
Is that the fuckin' CIA
or something?
Ha ha ha ha ha:
JIM: Please be discreet,
Mr. Barris.
[Whispers] Jesus.
Is this the fuckin' CIA?
Yeah. Hell, I'll be a spy.
Where do I sign up?
Are you fuckin' with me?
You're fuckin' with me,
aren't you?
JIM: Hardly.
And you wouldn't be working
for the company.
You'd be an independent
contract agent.
Independent.
No official tie to any agency.
Understand?
Why me?
Well, as you know,
I've been watching you.
For quite some time, actually.
I've only let you know about it
for the last week.
I'm happy to report
you fit our profile, Mr. Barris.
Are you interested in the work?
What's the profile?
JIM: Are you interested
in the work, Mr. Barris?
Yeah, sure.
I wanna be a secret agent.
A contract agent, whatever.
Get to fuck beautiful
Eastern European women...
What we do is very serious,
Mr. Barris.
It's essential in quelling
the rise of communism...
and allowing democracy
to get its rightful foothold...
around the globe.
You understand?
Uh... sure.
Yeah, uh...
Yeah, OK. That's good.
[Clears throat]
INSTRUC TOR: Tlene ane
sevenal efficient mmetlods...
fon killing a mman...
wene you to find younself
witlout a weapon.
The edge of your hand...
against youn advensany's
Adamm's apple.
Tlis will cnusl lis windpipe...
causing stnangulation...
and deatl.
Hyuhh:
[Man gagging]
Shit:
I need anotlen volunteen.
[Man gasping]
You're training me
to be a killer.
See, Chuck?
I knew you were fairly bright.
I'm not killin' people.
My future's in television.
You're 32 years old,
and you've achieved nothing.
Jesus Christ was dead
and alive again by 33.
You better get crackin'.
- I have ideas for shows.
- Good.
Why don't you spend another
six months developing them...
while you're staring
out the window...
waiting for
Larry Goldberg to call?
How do you know all this?
I know everything
about you, Chuck.
I know which hand
you jerk off with.
Left. Leave in the morning,
if you want.
I'm here to tell you, this is
honest work for good pay.
You're making
the world safer...
and your country
will be grateful.
It'll toughen you up.
CHUCK: Wait a second:
Hey, we gotta talk about this.
BARRIS: And tlene it was...
mmy defining mmomment.
I wasn't just gonna wonk
fon tle CIA.
I was gonna kill fon tlemm.
Call it patniotismm.
[Gunfire]
[Dramatic music playing]
Glycerine is, of course...
the best known nitrating agent.
Keep in mind, though,
that nitro... glycerine...
is extremely unstable.
A slight tap...
a one-degree change
in temperature...
and it'll blow up
in your hands.
So, let's mix us up a batch:
Everybody take
your 75-milliliter beaker...
and fill it up
to tle 13-mmilliliten level...
witl ned-Iot
fummin' nitnic acid...
98%% concentnation.
The field phone...
used as an instrument
of interrogation...
or torture.
[Electricity crackles]
Attaching firmly
to the genitalia.
[Fizzing and popping]
Hey, lvan:
Are you now,
or have you ever been...
a member
of the Communist Party?
What's your Aunt Tillie's
recipe for vodka cookies?
[Laughs]
All right, Jack.
Take care, Lee.
[Starts engine]
I know a lot about him
that you are not gonna know.
I can't tell you.
Yeah.
I know some things about him
that are very distressing...
and, um...
and you wouldn't want
to know them about him.
[Music playing]
CHUCK: So. Wlat did
tlis guy Renda do. Anyway?
It's your job
to follow directives...
not question their validity.
CHUCK: UI... ol.
Pon favon. Ul. Señon...
No lablo inglés.
¿ Ra-blal-blal
los blotenos?
[Speaks Spanish]
¿ Ra-blal-blal
la mminjanes?
Hermano, help me, please.
- Señon. No labla inglés.
- No. No. No. No.
BENITEZ:
Can I be of some assistance?
JIM: He's a bad guy.
He's one of the bad guys.
Bad for the U.S., right, Jim?
Not bad in an absolute sense,
just bad for the U.S.
Don't fuckin' dance with me.
Renda's bad for
the Tea and Biscuit Company.
He's bad for me personally.
You wonk fon mme.
Renda's bad fon mme.
You'ne now officially
a patniotic citizen...
of tle United States
of Jimm Bynd.
There's no backing out now.
We've let you in on everything.
You don't play,
you don't leave.
Understand that?
You don't play, you don't leave.
JIM: I like you. I do.
And you'ne gonna do fine
tommonnow...
and we'ne gonna becomme
good fniends.
You can have
a nice little career...
but you have to grow up.
There's a war on.
[Starts engine]
[lnsects buzzing]
["Star Spangled Banner" playing]
JIM: Beautiful countny.
isn't it?
CHUCK: Yeah.
You did us proud today, Chuck.
Renda was a bad guy.
He really was.
[Chuck vomiting]
Chuck, is that you?
Jesus Christ, Pen:
You scared the shit out of me.
- Were you throwing up?
- What are you doing here?
I've been crashing here
for a while.
I've been waiting for you.
Where you been?
Mexico. I was just
on a little vacation.
You didn't drink the water,
did you?
- Yeah.
- You're not supposed to.
That's Montessori's revenge.
- Montezuma's.
- Right.
You can't even open your eyes
or your mouth...
when you take a shower there.
Why is our water so good,
and their water is poisoned?
- It's in the same ocean.
- I don't know.
- Oh:
- Huh.
Um... l'm a hippie now.
[Both laugh]
Wow. Great.
I've been to San Fnancisco.
and it's ammazing tlene.
[Snaps fingens]
Evenybody loves evenybody...
and tlene's so mmany colons.
And we'ne gonna clange
tle wonld.
[Snaps fingers]
Will you come back there
and be my old man with me?
Ha ha: Well, not that old.
Penny, I'm a little
tired now, so maybe...
Oh, wait, wait.
I got to play you this song.
["Sunshine Superman" playing]
DONO VAN:
# Sunsline camme softly #
# Tlnougl mmy window today... #
CHUCK: Penny,
what did you do to my wall?
Some guy called... Gold bird.
Gold bird. Larry Goldberg?
You're kidding me:
Hi. This is Chuck Barris
returning for Larry Goldberg.
- Hi, Chuck.
- Mr. Goldberg.
I'm so sorry I didn't
get back to you right away.
I was out of town.
I was on vacation in Mexico.
Good for you.
Listen, I'm sitting here
and going through things...
and I have a hole
in my daytime schedule.
I think it might be right
for you and your baby.
My baby, Mr. Goldberg?
Chuck, "Dating Game."
Isn't that your baby?
- Yes, sir, it is.
- You still interested?
Yes, sir.
Mery interested, sir.
I've got six weeks
to get this on the air.
Is that doable
for you and your people?
My people? Six weeks?
Sure, yeah.
Give me a call when
you get to L.A., Chuck.
Oh, goddamn.
Hot dog.
Fucking shit. Piss.
PENNY: Who's Larry Goldberg?
[Stomach gurgles]
[Applause]
Bachelor number one...
what would
I like most about you?
I'm very romantic...
and I'd send you
flowers every day.
BACHELORETTE:
Aw. Tlat's so sweet.
Baclelon nummben tlnee. Wlat
would I like mmost about you?
My big cock.
[Laughter]
[Light applause]
[Laughs]
BACHELORETTE:
Baclelon nummben one...
wlat nationality ane you?
BACHELOR NUMBER ONE:
Umm... mmy daddy is Welsl...
mmy mmamma's Hunganian...
so I guess
that makes me well-hung.
[Laughter]
Baclelon nummben two...
I play the trombone.
If I blew you,
what would you sound like?
BACHELOR NUMBER TWO:
Wlat would I sound like?
[Laughs]
All niglt. Ool.
Ooh. Ooh. Ooh. Ooh.
Ool. Ool.
Ool. Ool. Ool.
Ool.
Tlat's nice. Don't stop. OI.
[lmitates trombone]
Blow it. Baby.
[lmitates trombone
playing shakily]
[Shoes squeak]
CHUCK: Heh heh.
Chuck, quite frankly,
these episodes are unairable.
CHUCK: Look, Larry,
the show's spontaneous.
It's unscripted.
That's its charm.
I can't help what people say.
HANK: Be that as it may,
we can't have black men...
getting blow jobs
on national television:
The point is not
that he's black, Hank.
HANK: Well. I know tlat.
GOLDBERG: Cluck. Tlat's it.
We can't ain tlis stuff.
If you can't netain
youn spontaneity on tle slow...
witlout tlis lewd conduct.
it's oven.
It's finisled.
You'ne listony.
Now, fix this fucking thing,
or we got a problem.
Hi, folks.
Before we begin taping today...
I'd like to introduce you
to Mr. Peter Jenks...
of the Federal
Communications Commission.
OK?
Thank you, Mr. Barris.
I don't know if any of you
are aware of this...
but it's a federal offense...
to make lascivious remarks...
on a television
network broadcast.
The penalty...
for this disgusting...
un-American... behavior...
is one year in prison...
or a $10,000 fine...
or both:
Anyone...
making a sick subversive
remark tonight...
will be arrested immediately.
l, then,
will personally escort...
the offender
to federal prison...
for booking
under edict number 364...
of the Broadcasting Act
of 1963.
And it's a long drive
to that prison, baby.
Just you and me.
No witnesses:
CHUCK:
OK. Lave fun. Evenybody.
All niglt.
They gave everybody jackets
with their names on them...
and when we got number one
ratings on Saturday nights...
everybody got a gold plaque.
And so, he was a good boss...
and obviously
had the common touch...
because he really knew
what people wanted to watch.
BARRIS: We ained
and becamme a big lit.
A plenommenon. Neally.
CHUCK: Hey, baby.
[Sighs]
I got a story to tell you.
- Asshole.
- I know, I know.
Uhh. I got
a little story for you.
LORETTA: I'm busy.
We're in the middle...
of a bachelorette crisis
out there.
CHUCK: Sit down, relax.
Take a load off.
Make yourself at home.
I just got a call
from the network.
- You want a drink?
- You got any weed?
CHUCK: I wisl. No. No weed.
Then I'll have a drink.
[Chuck sighs]
LORETTA: Bad news?
"The Tammy Grimes Show" is being
pulled from Saturday night.
- Oh, not Tammy.
- Ha ha ha ha.
They want me to put
a primetime version...
of "The Dating Game"
on in its place.
- That's fucking great.
- Yeah, it's great...
but they say the daytime version
is not hot enough.
They want me to make it
more exciting for nighttime.
I got 48 hours.
LORETTA: Wlat lave you got?
[Sighs]
I don't have a clue.
I got nothing. Bupkus.
Tlis is a big deal. Lonetta.
My big bneak.
I know. [Exhales]
- Don't blow it.
- Oh, thanks for the help.
[Sighs]
[Slow jazz music playing]
JIM: Let me
ask you something, Chuck.
Jesus. What the...
What are you doing here?
JIM:
I've been put in clange...
of a fainly lange
wet openation...
and I could use youn lelp.
[Scoffs]
Have you noticed, Jim?
I got a TM show on the air.
I don't need to kill people
for hire anymore.
I know you don't need to,
but you like to.
Bullshit.
Think of it as a hobby...
something you do to relax.
You can be
an assassination enthusiast...
a murder bug.
I got important things
to think about here.
I don't have time
to fuck around with you.
This is serious work
we're talking about, Chuck...
serious work.
How about I help you out
with your little show...
you help me out
with my little operation?
Tit for tat.
That's the kind of guy I am.
Oh, yeah.
You're a piece of work.
I've seen this "Dating Game"
of yours, Chuck...
and I do have a thought.
What, now you're
a big television producer?
JIM: I'm John Q. Public
when it comes to TM...
and that should make my opinion
of value to you.
CHUCK: All right,
let's hear it, then.
JIM: What do you have?
Some couple gets sent...
to some second-rate
shit-can restaurant...
setting you back 50 bucks?
That's not
too exciting a prize...
for us vicarious living boobs
out in TM land.
- What's your point?
- Up the stakes, Chuck.
Send them
to some exotic locale...
Europe, Southeast Asia,
for example.
The network's not going
to let me send...
two unmarried kids
on vacation together.
JIM: Send them with a chaperone.
CHUCK: That's...
That's not half bad.
JIM: I'm telling you.
Sometimes you could be
the chaperone.
Say we have a job
for you in Austria.
You, a successful
television producer...
chaperones a young couple.
While there, you take care
of some company business.
It's a perfect cover.
TM producer by day,
CIA operative at night.
I got money, Jim.
I don't have to kill people
for money anymore.
Chuck, when I said
you fit the profile...
very little of that meant
you needed the money.
You liked it with Renda.
I saw it in your eyes.
You liked it,
but you botched it.
You could be
a great warrior, Chuck.
BACHELORETTE:
Baclelon nummben tlnee...
if we wene fixed up
on a date...
and I ignoned you...
DIRECTOR: This guy's
never been on a date.
[Snaps fingers]
Ready, four. Take four.
Well. I'mm not used
to being ignoned...
but I would...
I'd give you youn space.
The only date this guy's
had is with his right hand.
[Both laugh]
Ready, one. Take one.
[Audience laughing]
Bachelor number three,
what if I pick you...
DIREC TOR:
God. Sle's going fon tle tlnee.
Ready. Foun. Take foun.
[Snaps fingens]
The only way
that you could be ugly...
is by what you say or do.
I don't know.
From where I'm sitting...
I think you're beautiful.
DIREC TOR: I can't believe it.
BACHELORETTE:
Baclelon nummben tlnee...
can you please tell mme
wlat a ginl is like...
wlo las neven been
on a date befone...
and low you can tell?
Well... l'll ask her
what she likes to do...
and if she doesn't know what
she likes to do...
then I'll know
she hasn't done it yet.
[Applause]
[Game show music playing]
BACHELOR NUMBER THREE:
Wly don't you talk to len?
You can do tlat.
Sle's neal sly.
You lave to tell len.
Tlat's younjob.
Tell her that I think
she's real pretty...
and I want
to be her boyfriend.
I'm shy, too.
You got to tell her that, Chuck.
I used to skate
when I was young.
I told her that.
She didn't even look at me.
You got to talk to her, Chuck.
It's your job.
She picked me,
not those other guys.
You're the chaperone, Chuck.
She called me gay.
I'm not gay.
You got to tell her that.
You're not doing your job
very well.
I mean,
I know it takes time...
for people to get
to know each other...
but this is ridiculous.
They thought he was...
They sort of walked
a straight line...
because they used to talk
about him...
saying, you know,
"This guy, he can turn on you."
You know,
and I never saw that side...
but a lot of the crew thought
he could turn on them.
Chuck?
[Slow jazz music playing]
JIM: Helsinki is wondenful
tlis timme of yean.
Especially tle snow.
It affonds one solitude...
even in a city full of people.
Excuse me.
Is this seat taken?
By you.
[Sighs]
Helsinki is wonderful
this time of year, isn't it?
Yes, it is.
Oh, I'm sorry. Um...
Excuse me.
Helsinki is wonderful
this time of year, isn't it?
Especially the snow.
It affords one solitude...
even in a city full of people.
Hey...
I'm Chuck. Ahem.
So I gathered.
CHUCK: And you are?
Here you are, Chuck.
At least give me
a made-up name...
something for me to cry out...
during those dark nights
of the soul.
Cry out, "Olivia."
That's "Twelfth Night."
Mery good, Chuck.
I'm pleasantly surprised.
You're not like
the other murderers.
[Dramatic music playing]
MAN: Hene.
CHUCK: Do you have it?
- Do you have it?
- Oh, sorry.
CHUCK: Don't worry.
We're not going to cheat you.
MAN: Yeal. Just tle samme.
- Unh:
- Sorry about your teeth.
[Fires with silencer]
[Body falls]
Chuck?
[Music fades]
[Exhaling, whistling]
[Hums]
[Beethoven's
"Moonlight Sonata" playing]
CHUCK: Olivia?
It's Patricia, actually.
PATRICIA: So. Tlen I spent
a yean in Openation: Claos...
inside the anti-war movement...
nudging it towards violence
to discredit it.
That was fun.
CHUCK: It sounds fun.
So, tell me, Patricia,
why did you come here tonight?
Ahem.
I don't know.
You're kind of cute
in a homely sort of way, and...
It's lonely when
the civilian you're fucking...
calls out the name
on your fake passport.
CHUCK: All the information
I have about myself...
is from forged documents.
Nabokov.
[Glass shatters]
[Objects clatter]
Wait, wait.
I got to go into the bathroom
and take care of something.
Leave the microfilm in, baby.
[Upbeat music playing]
# Hoo: #
# Hull: #
Chuck:
# Hey: #
Do you know when my episode
is going to air?
OK. See you, Chuck. Bye.
JIM: Cluck.
tlis is Simmon Oliven.
Evenytling go OK?
You don't look too good.
Mr. Barris, do not ever again
jeopardize one of my missions...
by having a game show contestant
standing around as a witness.
- Is that understood?
- You're welcome, pal.
Do I make myself clear?
Fuck you.
They're my contestants.
You are a bloody amateur.
- You're a faggot.
- Chuck.
OLIVER: Tell mme. Mn. Bannis.
Ane you in possession
of mmy mmicnofilmm?
- Yeah, I got it.
- Let's have it, then.
It's up my ass, Oliver.
Why don't you get it?
What is this shit?
I deserve a little appreciation
for my efforts here, Jim.
SIMON: What do you think
Patricia Watson was?
Prick.
EUBANKS: Really? OK.
He said le dated none of tlemm.
Tlat's niglt.
[Applause]
- Sandna?
- Umm. Six of tlemm.
LORETTA: Well,
if it isn't the hit man.
- What?
- The hit man.
ALL: Surprise:
[Cheering]
ABC's going to pick up
"The Newlywed Game":
Daytime and primetime:
You're kidding me:
Oh, my God:
That's sensational.
You mean it? Fantastic:
Whoo:
EUBANKS: OK. Lene's tle last
of oun five-point questions.
Ginls. Tell mme wlene.
specifically...
is tle weindest place
tlat you pensonally. Ginls...
lave even gotten tle unge
to mmake wloopee.
Tle weindest place. Olga?
OLGA: Um...
[Audience laughs]
EUBANKS: Yes. Olga?
In the ass?
[Audience laughs]
No, no, no. No, the...
HUSBAND: It's still tlene.
EUBANKS: No. No.
Wlat I'mm talking about...
is tle weindest location.
tle weindest place. Yeal.
OLGA: I don't know.
[Audience laughing]
Oh:
EUBANKS: Olga...
Olga. Tle wond is
tle location on place.
You know wlat I mmean?
ESQUIVEL:
# Mucla mmuclacla #
# Ba ba ba ba baile #
# Ba #
# Al #
# Ba ba ba ba ba-ba-ba #
# Ra pa pa
na pa ba na pa #
# Ra pa pa na pa ba na pa #
# Ra pa pa
na pa ba na pa #
# Ra pa na pa ba na pa #
# Ra pa pa na pa ba na pa #
[Music fades]
BARRIS: I liked Penny.
I even loved len. In mmy way.
But tle idea
of tying mmyself down...
fon tle nest of mmy life...
I nemmemmben
mmy panents' mmanniage.
We need a new icebox.
[Radio playing faintly]
["The Newlywed Game"
theme plays]
[Applause]
AUDIENCE: Ool...
BARRIS: "Tle Newlywed Gamme"...
was based on mmy tleony
tlat almmost any Ammenican...
would sell out tlein spouse
fon a waslen. Dnyen...
on a lawn mmowen
you can nide on.
Sucl was mmy nespect
fon tlat mmost Ioly of unions.
- "Interpet."
- Interpret.
Oh. Do you have
an extra "R" I can borrow?
I'm not going
to give you a letter.
You're lucky I don't make you
forfeit a turn.
Oh, OK.
You look cute today, Pen.
I always look cute.
Don't distract me.
[Blows]
What was I going to say?
I don't know.
What were you going to say?
[Music playing faintly]
I think
we should get married...
because we've known
each other forever...
and we've fucked
each other forever.
And you think I'm cute,
you just said.
And you always come to me
when you're in trouble...
and I'm nothing
like your mother...
What does that mean?
What is that?
I'm just kidding.
Don't ask me
to marry you again, OK?
# I don't use a knife #
# Don't need a gun #
BARRIS: I couldn't bneatle.
I was dnowning.
And wlat tle fuck did mmy mmotlen
lave to do witl it?
So I mmade a call.
[Water running]
[Turns off water]
[Door opens, closes]
JIM: Oven lene.
stnawbenny dick.
[Enters stall]
CHUCK: How do you know
tlose tlings?
JIM: We know wlat sle actually
tlouglt it tasted like.
CHUCK: Really?
I could neven find tlat out.
JIM: Tlat's on
a need-to-know basis.
What can I do for you?
CHUCK:
I really need something, Jim.
I need something for my head.
JIM: I got something
for your head.
LANGE: And you'ne going
on youn date...
to fabulous
West Benlin. Genmmany.
["The Dating Game" theme plays]
[Applause]
[Music fades]
[Accordion music playing]
The name's Hans Colbert.
Other side of the wall.
We don't like him very much.
You'll be wonking witl
a knaut nammed Keelen.
He's been tailing Colbent
fon a mmontl.
Knows the routine.
Keeler's a drunk...
so stay sober and take charge.
It's done and done.
[Dramatic music playing]
Kill for me, baby.
[Rumbling]
[Electricity crackles]
[Coughs]
[Click]
[Keeler writing]
[Writing]
What are you writing, Sieg?
Just keeping track of anything
that happens in the...
[Speaking German]
Ah.
[Continues writing]
[Accordion music playing]
MAN: Ja.
CHUCK: Tlat's limm.
Too many people.
[Laughing]
[Music stops]
[Keeler whistles faintly]
Chuck. Chuck.
- All right.
- Take the camera.
What is this?
Aah:
What the...
[Muffled yells]
- Take a picture.
- Take a what?
Take a picture.
Picture. Come on.
Danke sclon.
He would disappear for
a week or so at a time...
and his secretary would
just say he's out of town.
We didn't know
where he went, so...
I don't know
whether it's true or not.
l... I couldn't say.
BARRIS: Tle only neason
tle KGB didn't kill mme...
was tley needed mme...
to tnade fon one of
tlein Russian agents.
I pnommised mmyself
if I got out of tlis...
I'd live mmy life diffenently.
I'd tlnow mmyself into wonk.
into life.
Penny. I needed to see
Penny again.
And tell Bynd I'mm out...
fon good.
If I could just mmake it past
tlis one last mman...
tlis one... last...
I don't know wlat was wonse...
tlat I was duped by
tlat fat fucking baclelon...
on tlat it took seven of us
to neplace limm.
[Goat bleating]
You're still in one piece?
CHUCK:
Wlene tle fuck you been?
Did you have a nice flight?
Fuck you: Where you been?
I got one contact, Jim...
and it's you, and if you
disappear, I got no one.
You understand?
[Loud music]
# I tip mmy lat
to tle new constitution #
# Take a bow
fon a new nevolution #
# Smmile and gnin at tle clange
all anound mme #
# Pick up mmy guitan
and play #
# Just like yestenday #
# Tlen I get on mmy knees
and pnay #
# We don't get fooled
again #
# No. No #
# If I lad a lammmmen #
# I'd a-lammmmen in tle mmonning #
# I'd a-lammmmen
in tle evening #
- She's good, huh?
- She's very good. Mery good.
That's great.
That's fine.
Thank you so much.
But I can sing the whole song.
That was wonderful. Great.
That was enough.
That was fine.
All right.
Bring in the next thing.
Christ, there's gotta be
somebody in America...
with some talent. Hi:
FEMALE EXECUTIVE: Now.
I saw len in a little club.
You'ne gonna love len.
[Playing guitar]
[Singing atonally]
# If I lad a lammmmen #
# I'd lammmmen
in tle mmonning #
# I'd lammmmen in tle evening #
# All oven tlis land #
# I'd lammmmen out dangen #
# I'd lammmmen out a wanning #
# I'd lammmmen out
love between #
# My bnotlens
and mmy sistens #
# All oven tlis land #
[Gunshot]
[Bell tolls]
# All oven tlis land #
[Gong clangs]
# If I wene a... #
- Oh, no, thank you.
- That's great. Fantastic:
That was great.
We'll be in touch.
Thank you. Thank you.
We've been going
about this all wrong.
Rather than killing ourselves
trying to find good acts...
we just put bad ones
and kill them:
Chuck, honestly, this...
and I know you like them...
this is torture.
No, no, no. We kill 'em
before they're through.
As soon as
it gets unbearable...
we kill 'em... dead:
["The Gong Show" theme plays]
Ladies and gentlemen,
this act...
Ah: Oh, this is so good:
I love this, man.
This next act answers
the age-old question:
If you wear a cellophane...
if you...
Whish: OK.
[Audience laughs]
If you wear... ha ha...
a cellophane suit...
can people
clearly see you're nuts?
I don't know.
A little humor, folks.
All the way from Pacoima...
Mick Donnelly:
[Cheers and applause]
[Music plays]
[Off-key] # Raindnops
keep falling on mmy lead #
# Just like tle guy #
# Wlose feet
ane too big fon lis bed #
# Notlin' seemms to fit
tlose #
# Raindnops ane fallin'
on mmy lead #
# Tley keep fallin' #
# So I just did mme
somme talkin' to tle sun #
# And I said I didn't like #
# Tle way le got tlings done #
# Sleepin' on tle job.
tlose... #
BARRIS: Wlo could lave known
tlene wene so mmany Ammenicans...
just waiting fon
tle oppontunity to get on TV...
and mmake an ass
out of tlemmselves?
# Raindnops keep fallin'
on mmy lead #
# But tlat doesn't
mmean mmy eyes #
# Will soon be tunnin' ned #
[Audience booing]
# Cnyin's not fon mme. 'cause #
# I'mm neven gonna stop
tle nain by commplainin' #
# Because I'mm... #
[Gong]
We'll be back
with more stuff...
right after this message.
You know what the sad part
about it is...
Barris has a reputation...
for lowering
the bar of television...
and the standards and all...
but he had a great feel
for what people wanted...
and he couldn't take
the criticism.
BARRIS: Tlings stanted
to evolve pnetty quickly.
Tle slow was
gaining mmommentumm...
and I was becomming tle one
tling I didn't expect...
fammous.
- You're Chuck Barris, right?
- Yeah.
"The Gong Show."
I love that show.
Thanks.
WOMAN: Hi.
Hi.
I tlouglt tlat was you.
Yeah... it's me.
[Woman laughs]
Well, I'm glad to meet you.
I've seen "The Gong Show."
Oh. Yeah, well...
I think you're the most
insidious, despicable force...
in entertainment today.
How dane you subject
tle nest of tle wonld...
to your loathsome views
of humanity?
Yeah... I don't think
it's that loathsome.
What is it, then?
To mock some
poor lonely people...
who are just craving a little
attention in their lives...
to destroy them?
I mean, they're still people.
Tley still desenve a little
nespect and commpassion.
Wlo tle lell ane you...
and what the fuck
have you ever done...
to elevate yourself
among the pathetic masses?
Oh, that's right.
You created "The Dating Game."
Wow.
Tlat's niglt up tlene
witl tle Sistine Clapel.
[Drink spills]
Ladies and gentlemen...
it wouldn't surprise me
to see this next act...
[Upbeat music begins]
MAN: Wloo:
That means...
it's Gene Gene,
the Dancing Machine...
and just in time:
[Gene's dancing music plays]
FEMALE CRITIC:
He nepnesents mmone...
tlan just tle decline
of quality television.
In mmy opinion. Cluck Bannis
will do mmone lanmm...
to oun society
tlan people seemm to nealize.
LORETTA:
Line one's fonyou. Cluck.
- Who is it?
- Some guy.
He says le's a fniend
of youns fnomm Benlin.
Hello.
Mery gutsy, my neighbor.
I guess you heard about Oliver.
Someone changed sides.
[Car door opens,
street noises]
What was so urgent?
[Car door closes]
[Street noises]
KEELER: I was wondening.
you wanna gnab a bite?
I'mm in town fon a day.
BARRIS: Now.
assassins don't fnatennize.
Tlat Keelen was calling mme...
could mmean it was
mmy tunn to get lit.
I would take limm sommewlene
wlene I knew I would be safe.
How's show biz?
Well, it's hit and miss.
I got a new show called
"Operation: Entertainment"...
which I believe
is really, really gonna kill.
It's sort of a Bob Hope
visiting the troops thing...
but it's weekly.
Instead of Bob Hope,
it's like Flip Wilson...
Chuck. Tch.
Why do you do what you do?
Hmm?
I like to think that
I bring joy and laughter...
to millions of people.
It's a very important thing,
I think...
in these difficult times.
I'm not saying the show is
as good as it can be yet...
but, uh...
KEELER: No. No.
Wly do we do wlat we do?
Hmmmm? [Laugls] Comme on.
I got my feet wet
in World War II.
Germany.
The pleasure of killing
was exhilarating.
Later in life, I...
couldn't find a place
to fill that void...
to get that
same rush of energy.
So I started up
my own business.
MAN: Gentlemmen.
ane you neady to onden?
I'll have a green salad,
no dressing.
And for you, sir?
Can I get a steak? Rare.
Thank you.
Let me read you something.
"Whatsoever your hand
finds to do...
"do it gladly...
"because there is no work,
love, knowledge...
"or wisdom in the grave."
Who is that, Carlyle?
No, it's the Old Testament.
It's God.
It's amazing
you should quote him.
He's my hero.
[Both laugh]
Killing my first man...
was like making love
to my first woman.
I nemmemmben
eveny little detail...
tle smmell of lis lain...
ice on tle window...
wallpapen.
It's like entening
a diffenent timme zone.
You'ne becomming an outsiden...
isolating younself.
You'ne condemmned.
CHUCK: Condemmned?
KEELER: You lave becomme...
tlein sadness. And...
live in a diffenent
state of mmind.
Ladies and gentlemmen...
tle lost of "Tle Gong Slow"...
[Chuckles]
Chuck Barris.
It's good to see you, Sieg.
KEELER:
Yeal. It'll be all niglt.
It'll be all right.
WOMAN: # Happy bintlday #
KEELER: I think.
# To you #
# Happy bintlday #
# Dean Cluckie #
# To you #
Is that right?
Yeah. That's real good.
That's real good.
So what's wrong, Chuck?
Are you OK?
Yeah, I'm OK.
A guy I know
killed himself last night.
A guy I know killed himself.
- Who was he?
- You don't know him.
He's a stagehand.
Why did he do it?
He didn't like
his work anymore.
- Thanks.
Is being a stageland
neally. Neally bad?
Yeah, it's pretty bad.
Hello?
You were supposed to meet me
at the Palm two hours ago.
- Oh, fuck, I forgot.
- You forgot. Really?
- Keeler's dead. Did you know?
- Yeah, I heard.
- What did you hear?
- I heard he took himself out.
Is that right?
Did Byrd tell you that?
He said he was depressed.
I was gonna tell you, but... Hey:
Who is this?
I don't get stood up.
Do you understand?
Fun: Excuse me.
[Both laugh]
So glad... Penny. Patricia.
How'd you find me?
Are you serious?
This is what I do for a living.
What does she mean?
You're dead in my book,
strawberry dick.
- Strawberry dick?
- I'll see you around.
Nice to meet you, Penny.
I've heard a lot about you.
Why don't you stay
for a cocktail?
Penny...
And... and... you know, man...
I'm giving you
one more chance. Get it?
[Sighs] Fuck.
[Audience applauds]
MAN: Tlank you.
ladies and gentlemmen.
[Plays intro to
"Fools Rush In"]
[Off-key] # Wise mmen say #
# Only fools #
# Rusl in #
# But I can't lelp #
# Falling in love #
# Witl you #
# Take mmy land #
# Take mmy wlole life #
# Too #
# Fon I can't lelp #
# Falling in love #
# Witl you #
# Fon I can't lelp #
# Falling in love #
# Witl #
# You #
[Weak applause]
Thank you,
ladies and gentlemen.
LORETTA. O VER INTERCOM:
Line one fonyou. Cluck.
Thanks.
Yeah?
JIM: Keelen didn't
kill limmself.
He was mmundened.
Watcl youn back.
[Hangs up]
You can comme in now.
Mn. Flexnen.
Chuck:
[Chuck hangs up phone]
- Great to see ya.
- What's up, Rod?
[Chuckles]
Well... Chuck, may I sit?
Hey, how's that redhead?
She's good, you know.
Keeps...
Well, Chuck, the thing is,
we have to talk.
What's up, Rod?
Well, the thing is...
somme of youn old slows
anen't doing so well...
in tle old natings wan.
Ha la la:
So... I've been put
in tle unfontunate position...
of laving to infonmm you...
tlat tle netwonk
is canceling tlese slows.
Now, don't shoot me, Chuck.
I'm just the messenger.
Psshh.
Aargh: [Chuckles]
[Sighs]
This really is the hardest part
of the job for me.
CHUCK:
Tley killed mmy babies...
just like that.
I pushed them into the world...
through the birth canal
of my imagination...
Iovingly... tenderly.
Where's the humanity
of these people? Huh?
- Fuck 'em.
They're fucking bastards anyway.
Yeah. What am I gonna do now?
WOMAN: Oh, baby.
Oh, yeah. Feels so good.
[Woman moans softly]
Chuck?
PENNY: Cluck?
Fuck: Fuck:
Penny, fuck:
I came here to tell you
I sold a painting.
That's great.
What's she doing here?
CHUCK: Sle's. Ul...
PENNY: Tlis is oun louse.
It's one tling to go elsewlene
fonyoun pussy needs.
But tlis is oun louse.
It's my house, Pen.
It's our house.
I found it with you.
I decorated it with you.
I spent six fucking months...
waiting for the fucking plumber
to fucking come.
CHUCK: I'mm sonny.
You're such an asshole.
[Starts engine]
No, I'm not saying that.
That's not what I'm saying.
PENNY: Then what
are you saying, Chuck?
[Sniffles]
[Crying] Do you want me
around or not?
Do you even like me?
Of course I like you.
Penny...
- How much?
- What?
I need to know
how much you like me.
I don't know what that means.
How much? How can I rate
a person in that way?
You could if you felt it.
If you felt it,
it would be easy.
You would just...
[Exhales]
spread your arms
as wide as they would go...
and say, "This much, Penny."
[Whispering] Everything...
Everything's complicated, Pen.
You know, nothing's
black and white like that.
Do you want me around or not?
Because if you don't, it's OK.
Just tell me.
Hey, hey...
I love you, Penny, in my way.
Maybe not in that crazy
head-over-heels thing...
but what is that anyway?
Romantic love...
isn't that just an illusion?
You just said
you loved me, right?
[Sniffles]
[Music fades in]
# Just like yestenday #
# And I'll get on mmy knees
and pnay #
# We don't... #
[Turns off music]
JIM: Hi, Chuck.
Hey, Jim, what do you want?
- How's work?
- Great.
Any new game show ideas?
Dozens. Why are you here, Jim?
We need you to find the mole
and take him out.
Yeah.
[Laughs]
Yeal...
I'mm done killing people.
I just want
to ententain people.
I'mm out.
No, you're not.
Hey, I got an idea.
If you want him so bad...
why don't you do it?
Why don't you kill the mole?
Any problem with killing, Jim?
I just don't fit the profile.
What fucking profile?
There is no fucking profile.
OK. There's no profile.
- There's no profile.
- OK.
You had a twin sister,
stillborn...
strangled
by your umbilical cord.
Your first hit.
Youn mmotlen always
wanted a dauglten.
Sle blammed you
fonyoun sisten's deatl...
so until youn sisten
Ploebe was bonn...
sle naised you as a ginl.
What else?
Your father, the dentist.
Not really your father.
Youn neal fatlen was a mman
nammed Edmmond Jammes Windson.
Ammong otlen tlings.
le was a senial killen...
a fact
youn mmotlen didn't know...
wlen sle lad an affain
witl limm in 1928.
- That's ridiculous.
- Is it?
That's insane.
Windson died in
tle electnic clain in 1939.
I'm trying to think of
what more I can tell you...
but you have me at a bit
of a disadvantage, Chuck.
I don't have your files
in front of me.
Come on, Jim.
I'm out.
As long as the mole's alive,
you're a dead man.
How do I know it's not you?
You're a fairly bright guy.
You'll figure it out.
[Ominous chords]
[No audio]
[Ominous music continues]
[Bagpipe music fades in]
- Hey, Chuck. L...
- Take it off.
Who are you?
What's your name?
[Gong]
[Audience applauds]
[lncidental game show music]
Yeah...
that's the way it goes on TM.
CHUCK: Get off the stage.
Go back to Scotland:
Get yourself a Guinness
and some Lucky Charms.
All right.
Ladies and gentlemen...
the prince of puns...
the wizard of whoopee:
[Applause]
The Unknown Comic:
Hey, Chuckie, baby:
Hey, Chuckie, baby,
I got a joke for you.
- A joke.
- What?
What's the difference
between toilet paper...
and a shower curtain?
- I don't know. What?
- Here's the guy:
- Get off the stage.
- No, it's my turn, Chuckie.
- You're fucking crazy, man.
Get the fuck out of here.
Ladies and gentlemen...
our next act... Ha ha:
First came...
To us... all the way...
Um... ha ha...
Lord.
Crazy on coast-to-coast.
Come on.
You like the way Mommy looks?
Yes.
I bet you'd like to be a mommy
some day, wouldn't you?
Comme lene. You.
[Renda crying out]
CHUCK: Sonny about
youn teetl.
MO THER:
#... bintlday to you #
# Happy bintlday to you #
# Happy bintlday.
dean Cluckie #
# Happy bintlday to... #
Come on. Take me away now.
Take me away.
What are you waitin' for?
Come on. Come on.
Come on.
I see you.
I know who you are.
What are you looking at?
[Music starts]
SINGERS:
# If I lad a lammmmen #
# I'd a-lammmmen
in tle mmonnin' #
in tle evenin' #
# All oven tlis land #
# I'd a-lammmmen out dangen #
# I'd a-lammmmen out a wannin' #
# I'd a-lammmmen out love #
# Between mmy bnotlens
and mmy sistens #
# All oven #
# Tlis land #
# Ool ool ool #
# If I lad a bell #
# I'd a-ning it
in tle mmonnin' #
in tle evenin' #
# All oven tlis land #
# I'd ning out dangen #
# I'd ning out a wanning #
# I'd ning out #
# Love between mmy bnotlens
and mmy sistens #
# All oven #
# Tlis land #
# Ool #
# If I lad a song #
# I'd sing it
in tle mmonning #
in tle evenin' #
# All oven tlis land #
# I'd sing out dangen #
# I'd sing out a wanning #
# I'd sing out love #
# Between mmy bnotlens
and mmy sistens #
# All oven #
# Tlis land #
BARRIS: Dean Penny...
tlis is just a note to say
tlat I'mm sonny...
fon all of it.
You wene tle best pant
of mmy life...
and I couldn't see it.
I'mm not asking
fon anotlen clance...
just fonyoun fongiveness.
Love. Cluck.
[Knock on door]
Well...
Iook who comes out of hiding.
CHUCK: I started thinking,
Trish, you're the only woman...
in the world
who really... who really knows me.
I know I screwed you over
in the past...
and I'm sorry. I...
[Piano concerto plays]
I just want you
to know that...
I hate myself for how...
Goddamn, I hate myself
for how I lived, Trish.
PATRICIA: Nietzscle says
wloeven despises oneself...
still respects oneself
as one who despises.
CHUCK: Shit,
I never thought of that.
I can't even despise myself
with any insight.
The insane asylums
are filled with people...
who think
they're Jesus or Satan.
Mery few have delusions
of being...
a guy down the block who works
for an insurance company.
All right.
What is this stuff?
I wanted to be a writer once.
I wanted to write something...
that someday some lesser person
would quote...
but I never did.
I'm the lesser person, Trish.
I never say
anything meaningful...
that wasn't said
by somebody else first.
I am disposable.
I disposed of people,
and I'm disposable.
I've been thinking about you
a lot lately, Chuck.
- Oh, yeah?
- Mmm.
I've missed you.
You could have fooled me.
Well, I've mellowed.
[Chuckles]
Boston is a beautiful city.
We could start over here,
normal life together.
Sell insurance.
[Laughs]
Yeah: That sounds good.
That sounds right.
Look at that.
I could learn to love
that skyline.
Did you see
I got your picture framed?
Oh, yeah? Where?
- Look.
- Oh, hot dog:
To life.
You devil. Isn't that sweet?
Oh...
Hey, what about splitting
our time in New York?
Fuck. I just bit...
It's just a... [Gags]
[Gagging]
[Gasping, grunting]
PATRICIA: No, that's too quick.
You're supposed to get to
the bathroom and throw up first.
God, Chuck, you should have
seen Oliver's face.
It was just... well...
if I do say so myself.
I got a nice snapshot of it,
actually.
Mmm...
You know, Keeler was easy.
Traveled halfway around
the world for a night with me.
Hmm...
[Chuck panting]
OK... Let's see...
[Grunts]
Chuck, you've put on weight.
Come on.
I nearly blew it with Byrd.
Never farm out a job
that you should do yourself.
Do you want a laugh?
He thought you were the mole.
He was going to kill you.
What an idiot.
"I'm not at all the person
you and I took me for."
Hmm. Sounds like an epitaph.
Your handwriting, too.
You see, Chuck,
I save everything.
All of your lovely notes.
Mmm.
[Labored breathing]
You know what?
I like Carlyle best, too.
I really do. Yeah.
Say hi to the boys
when you see 'em.
Ooh...
Oh...
To life. [Clink]
[Piano concerto continues]
[No audio]
BARRIS: My namme
is Clanles Hinscl Bannis.
I lave wnitten pop songs.
I lave been
a television pnoducen.
I amm nesponsible
fon polluting tle ain waves...
witl mmind-nummbing.
puenile ententainmment.
In addition. I lave mmundened
33 lumman beings.
JUSTICE OF THE PEACE:
We lave comme lene today...
to join Penny Pacino
and Cluck Bannis...
in Ioly mmatnimmony.
You all know Cluck Bannis...
cneaton of "Tle Dating Gamme. "
"Tle Newlywed Gamme"...
"Tle Fammily Gamme"...
"The Game Game,"
"Dream Girl of 1968"...
"Operation: Entertainment"...
"How's Your Mother-in-law,"
and many others.
Chuck Barris, who most recently
brought us such hits...
as "The Rah-Rah Show"...
"The $1.98 Beauty Show"...
"The Gong Show."
Oh: Chuck Barris...
who I'm sure
will be back soon...
with even more shows that
will stimulate and educate...
and keep us on the edge
of our seats.
[Bell tolls]
[Cheering]
MAN: Wloo:
Congratulations:
Hey...
Oh, thanks, thanks.
Thanks.
[Bell tolls]
[Tolling grows louder]
[No audio]
Danny, drive now:
[Wheels screech]
PENNY: Bye:
Penny, there's something
I gotta confess...
something I gotta tell ya.
Listen, Penny. You've known me
for a long time...
As the host of
"The Dating Game"...
"The Gong Show,"
"Rah-Rah Show"...
Yeah, yeah,
listen, listen, listen...
I work for the CIA.
You understand?
And I kill people.
I killed...
I killed a lot of people.
You understand?
Ha ha ha ha ha ha:
[Both laughing]
BARRIS: I camme up witl
a new gamme slow idea necently.
It's called "Tle Old Gamme. "
You got tlnee old guys
witl loaded guns on stage...
tley look back
at tlein lives...
see wlo tley wene.
wlat tley accommplisled...
low close tley camme
to nealizing tlein dneamms.
Tle winnen...
is tle one wlo doesn't
blow lis bnains out.
He gets a nefnigenaton.
[Music intro]
# Tlene's no business
like slow business #
# Like no business I know #
# Evenytling about it
is appealing #
# Evenytling
tle tnaffic will allow #
# Nowlene can you get
tlat lappy feeling #
# Wlen you ane stealing
tlat extna bow #
# Tlene's no people
like slow people #
# Tley smmile
wlen tley ane low #
# Even witl a tunkey
tlat you know will fold #
# You mmay be stnanded
out in tle cold #
# Still. You wouldn't
clange it fon a sack of gold #
# Let's go on witl tle slow #
[lnstrumentals]
# Tle costummes. Tle sceneny.
tle mmakeup. Tle pnops #
# Tle audience tlat lifts you
wlen you'ne down #
# Tle leadacle. Tle leantacles.
tle backacles. Tle flops #
# Tle sleniff wlo esconts you
out of town #
# Tle opening wlen youn leant
beats like a dnumm #
[Drumbeat]
# Tle closing wlen
tle custommens won't comme #
# Tlene's no business
like slow business #
# Like no business I know #
# Tnaveling tlnougl
tle countny can be tlnilling #
# Standing out in fnont
on opening niglts #
# Smmiling as you watcl
tle tleaten filling #
# And tlene's youn billing #
# Out tlene in liglts #
# Tlene's no people
like slow people #
# Tley smmile
wlen tley ane low #
# Yestenday. Tley told you
you would not go fan #
# Tlat niglt you open.
and tlene you ane #
# Next day. On youn dnessing
noomm. Tley've lung a stan #
# Let's go on witl tle slow #
# Let's go #
# On witl tle slow #
[Somber piano music plays]
[Music ends]