Please.
If he makes it to the river,
he's won.
We cannot allow that
to happen, Mr. Lopaki.
Brandy?
It's like a drug,
isn't it?
To bring a man down.
Was it worth it?
- Every nickel.
- Good.
Yes?
Hi, I'm... I'm looking
for Douglas Binder?
- You a friend of Mr. Binder's?
- No, l...
I'm... I'm his daughter.
Doug was a nice man.
He had manners.
He didn't tell you where
he was moving, did he?
He owed some rent,
honey.
I told him he could
wait to pay me...
- 'til he got back on his feet.
- He wasn't in an accident, was he?
Oh, no. He lost his job
with the oil tool company.
When Doug moved out,
he left this box.
He told me I could
hold it...
'til he could make up
his back rent.
Do you have any idea
where he might be now?
You might try checking down
at Our Lady of Charity.
Marine, huh?
Ah, Recon.
- I was in the service
for a while myself.
- Really?
- Yeah.
- Do you know him?
Well, he comes here
sometimes.
Nice guy too.
Uh, if I see him,
I'll... I'll tell him
you're looking.
Do you happen to know
where he lives?
I-I'm afraid your...
Your daddy, uh, well...
Well, he was like the rest of us:
Out of doors.
You know?
How is that gumbo, Chance?
A tragedy.
The coffee
was tolerable, though.
- It ain't free neither.
- Yeah, I know.
Leave your wallet
in your tuxedo?
I play that one
on you before?
- Yeah. For the gumbo.
- That's right.
- If you don't want me, baby
- Hi. Do you have any change?
Baby
please tell me so
- If you don't want me, honey
- Thank you.
Honey
please let me know
But if you don't
want me that bad
Darlin'
please let me know#
Hi, Murray.
Yes, I was wondering if my father
came to pick up his mail yet.
He hasn't? No, that's fine.
Thank you. Bye-bye.
- Hello, pretty lady.
- Leave me the hell alone.
We'll take the wallet.
How about a little
extra, honey?
You having fun?
Why don't you do yourself
a favor, boy?
I think the favor
gonna be done for you.
It's okay.
I said get lost.
Now, take your big stick
and your boyfriend...
and find a bus to catch.
Oh, this guy's funny.
Come on, let's go!
Let's go! Come on!
You know, it's a shame. This
used to be such a nice part of town.
Next time be more careful
when you show your wallet.
Without cops, the city stops!
Without cops,
the city stops!
Without cops, the city stops!
- Come on, let's hurry now!
- Without cops, the city stops!
- Will the strike end soon?
- Here you go.
Without cops,
the city stops!
Happy birthday to me.
Excuse me.
- Can I help you?
- Yeah. I need to fill out
a missing person report.
Look, I just pulled a double shift.
Why don't you catch me tomorrow.
Okay.
Why don't you catch me now.
- What is the name
of the missing individual?
- Douglas Charles Binder.
Relationship
of reporting party?
Daughter.
- Okay. You got a picture?
- Mm-hmm.
- Got something a little more recent?
- Oh, no, I don't.
See, my parents
were divorced 20 years ago.
- You got an address?
- I think my father was homeless.
I didn't even know myself...
u-until I just
came down here.
Look, um, I'm not sure
what you want me to do here.
I want you
to take my report.
Well, generally, in order
to be considered missing,
you need somewhere
to be missing from.
Fine.
If you're too busy
to do your job, Detective,
then I'll find somebody
who isn't so busy.
Look.
You wanna find your father,
take my advice: Canvas the missions,
ask at the shelters,
but, um,
get somebody who knows the city
to show you around...
or I'll be filling out
one of these on you.
Hey, you're welcome.
All right,
pipe down and listen up.
We got 12 positions this morning,
Able Seaman or better.
When I call your name, come into
the office, show your papers,
and you'll get your ship.
Here we go. First man,
Gombas, Luigi. Able Seaman.
- Right here.
- Walker, Steven. Second Engineer.
- Hi.
- Leslie, Francis R.
- They told me at the cafe
that you might be down here.
- Seeler, D. Master.
I need to talk to you
about something.
- I don't think this is a good time now.
- Walters, Nichols D.
- Yeah.
- Able Seaman.
How'd you, um,
like to work for me?
- I'll pay you $100 a day.
- Third Mate. Stevens, Frank G.
- For doing what?
- For $100, does it really matter?
Actually, it does.
Yeah. It does.
Look, I really need you
to help me find someone.
Jales, Bill. Cook.
You know this city, you obviously
can take care of yourself.
Boudreaux, C. Able Seaman.
I would like to
help you, darling.
- Looks like I'm gonna be out of town.
- Bakelman, Fats.
- Way out of town.
- Able Seaman.
Sorry.
Chance.
Thought you got blackballed...
about that thing with,
uh, Captain McDonald.
- That was a big misunderstanding.
- Right.
Broke his damn jaw
is what I heard.
You make sure I said
a big "hello."
Whoa. Wait a minute.
Johnson says
I was reinstated.
With the company.
Not with the union.
You owe some dues here,
boy.
- 217 bucks.
- I'll pay that off on this cruise.
No. Nobody ships out if they're
in arrears, you know that.
- How am I gonna pay my dues
if I can't get the job?
- I don't make the rules, mate.
Look, your ride doesn't sail
'til the end of the week.
If I can get the money,
then what?
Then I'll let you
ship out.
I'll get the money.
Keep goin'.
Take it back. Yeah.
Bring it, bring it,
bring it, bring it.
Okay, down.
So, this guy you're looking for,
he owes you money or something?
- He's my father.
- Okay, I change my mind.
I'll help you for two days,
you'll pay me $217.
It's a deal.
- You can drive.
- I...
don't have
a driver's license, ma'am.
So, what's your name?
Chance Boudreaux.
What's your name?
It's Nat.
Nat?
Your parents name you
for a... bug?
No, actually,
it's short for Natasha.
Natasha.
What kind of a name
is Chance?
Well, my mama took one.
So how did you lose
your papa?
My parents, um, they got divorced
when I was seven and my father...
Well, he moved away.
We started to write and
he even called me a couple of times.
Three weeks ago
the letters just stopped.
I've got a friend here
who can help us.
You check the line,
I'll look around inside.
Hey, you don't have
a bottle of hot sauce on ya, do ya?
- Elijah. What's happening?
- Hi.
Wednesday meat loaf.
I mean, they said
it was meat loaf.
- I thought you were gonna get a ship.
- I lost my boarding pass.
I've got something
to show you.
You two know each other?
- We met yesterday.
Have you seen my father?
- I saw the next best thing.
I was over at
Plaza D'ltalia yesterday...
and I saw this sleeping bag
in a cart.
It was a tiger stripe, like the kind
they used to issue to Recon guys.
Your daddy had one
just like it.
- Thanks, Charlie.
- You bet.
Don't be offended.
He passed them out for money.
Uh, yeah, I've had to
do it myself.
Here. Barracks Street.
Both sides this time, Grandpa.
Next! Get!
Here. Decatur. Lower half.
Well, if it ain't
my good friend Boudreaux.
I thought you was gonna
catch a ship.
Maybe I'll stick around
to run for mayor.
We're looking for someone
who worked for you.
The man's name
is Douglas Binder.
- I never heard of him.
- I think he know you.
- Did he work for you, sir?
- Maybe he did, maybe he didn't.
I'm not too good with names.
I have a photograph.
What Mr. Poe trying to say,
he's not too good with faces.
Right?
Hello, Randal.
I didn't know you had company.
We were just leaving.
- You know, we should go back up there.
- Not now. Not together.
Poe knows something
about my father, obviously.
If you don't want to go back
up there, I'll go myself.
If you want to find your daddy,
you're gonna have to work smarter,
not harder.
Yeah.
- Natasha Binder?
- What's the problem?
I'm afraid I have
some bad news.
They found
your father's body.
I'm sorry.
- They made a positive I.D.
- How did it happen?
There was a fire last night in
an abandoned building in the Ninth Ward.
The fire department discovered
your father's body in one of the rooms.
I need to see him.
Your daddy was burned
pretty badly.
The identification had to
be made from dental charts...
in your father's
service record.
What's your
involvement here?
I was helping her
find her daddy.
Wakey, wakey, you fat fuck!
Oh, God!
Mr. Fouchon,
what are you doing here?
- Aah! Oww!
- Don't talk, Randal. Listen.
Oh, don't worry
about Randal.
- Aah!
- He's all ears.
When Mr. Van Cleaf came upon
your visitors yesterday,
you neglected to tell him
that they were inquiring...
- about one of our volunteers.
- That was nothin', Mr. Fouchon.
Oh, it was something,
Randal.
This man we hunted last night.
Why don't you tell us his real name?
- You fuck.
- Binder. Binder. Douglas Binder.
That's not the one
we selected, is it?
I-I couldn't get the guy
you asked for.
Look, y-you said you wanted
a combat veteran, so I sent you Binder.
- He has more medals.
- He had a family.
Now they're asking questions.
Please. Please.
I said I was sorry. I sai...
- Aah! I said I was sorry.
- Careless is what you are, Randal.
Careless and stupid...
and now you're sorry, too.
He said he...
He said he was alone.
- I didn't know he had
any relatives. Honest.
- You made a mistake?
- Is that what you're saying?
- Yeah. Yeah.
Uh-huh. And I see you're anxious
to make up for it, aren't you?
Yeah. Yeah, right.
Yes. Yes, sir.
We've got another client
and he's about to select a new playmate.
Next time send us
the one we ask for.
I will, Mr. Fouchon,
I swear. L...
I think
we understand each other.
- Yes? No?
- Yes. Yeah.
Randal.
I come back here,
I cut me a steak.
You did your best.
No, l...
I came too late.
I mean, Jesus, he was living
out of a shopping cart.
Goddamn it.
Why didn't he just...
tell me?
Why didn't he ask
for my help?
I've been there myself
on the street.
It's hard.
It's hard to...
put your hand out.
I just kept thinking
if I could...
just tell him
that I loved him.
And because
he loved you so much,
he didn't want to
pull you into it.
- Our friend, Mr. Boudreaux.
- Mm-hmm.
Silver Star.
Marine Force Recon.
He joined
the Merchant Service after he got out.
His captain
was smuggling opium.
When Boudreaux found out,
he threw the man overboard.
He's been looking
for work ever since.
He's obviously not someone
we should underestimate.
He was raised
in the bayous by his uncle.
I think Mr. Boudreaux...
would make
a very interesting quarry.
Maybe I should, uh,
pay him a visit.
No, no, no, no, no.
Send a couple of lads down there
to have a chat with him.
Yeah.
Bingo.
Some friendly advice, Boudreaux:
Get the fuck outta Dodge!
Do it today! And tell
that bitch girlfriend of yours...
to point her titties north
and step on the gas!
It's always
nice to see you.
You seem to have a real talent,
Mr. Boudreaux,
for attracting violence.
Does that make me
a bad person?
Why did you arrest me for,
getting beat up
without a license?
Thank you for calling me.
Oh, my God, you look awful.
Darling,
you hurt my feelings.
What we have here is a charge sheet.
Willfully crossing a police barrier;
that's considered Criminal Trespass.
Yes, that officer was nice enough
to mention that to me.
- What were you doing at the house?
- The dog tag...
you find in that fire?
They always come in twos.
So I went back to that place
to look for the other one.
Your daddy,
he didn't die in the fire.
- He was murdered.
- There's no evidence of that.
There is now.
That hole in that tag was made
by something sharp and hard.
And I'll bet my rent money
it was made...
when Binder
was still wearing it.
Why would somebody go through all
this trouble to kill a homeless man?
- Do you believe us now?
- The wheels turn slow around here.
- Real slow.
- But they do turn.
I'll order a new autopsy.
This'll help.
- You should see a doctor.
- I hate them doctors.
Yeah... Aah! Shit!
Goddamn it.
What? Not now.
So... So, you in 'Nam?
Yeah,
a long time ago.
It seems to me a man with
your obvious experience...
should be pullin' down
a lot more money.
You're gonna pay me 100 bucks
to fill out a form?
I'll pay you a lot more than that
if you got the experience.
What kind of experience?
Well, maybe you ain't interested.
Uh, no.
I'll fill out
the application.
You got any family?
Anybody to worry about you?
Friends?
Anything like that?
I got nobody.
You'll deposit
$500,000 in our account...
in a bank
in the Cayman Islands.
Do not refer to
our agreement by telex...
or in conversations
on the phone.
You'll be provided
with a guide, trackers...
and the weapon
of your choice.
Naturally, we will
dispose of the body...
and provide you with
an out-of-town, airtight alibi.
Don't worry, Mr. Zenan, all you
have to do is point and shoot.
Mr. Zenan has made his selection.
A black man named Roper.
Used to be in Special Forces.
Excellent.
I don't see any problem
with your choice.
It has always been
the privilege of the few...
to hunt the many.
Soldiers, policemen,
fighter pilots.
Men who kill for the government
do so with impunity.
All we do is offer
the same opportunity...
for private citizens
such as yourself.
- These opponents, they're volunteers?
- More or less.
The same government that has
made murder their sole preserve,
they train our targets.
We pride ourselves
on only hunting combat veterans,
men who have
the necessary skills...
- to make our hunts more interesting.
- What about the police?
I'm sure that they would be interested
if they were to find out.
Dr. Morton here
assists us...
with the formality
of police autopsies.
It's no accident
that we're in New Orleans.
Last year we conducted hunts
in Rio de Janeiro at Carnival,
Yugoslavia during
the late unpleasantness.
Oh, yeah.
You see, there's always some unhappy
little corner of the planet...
where we can ply our trade.
All right, Mr. Fouchon.
- You have a client.
- Well,
thank you for visiting,
Mr. Zenan.
Dr. Morton will
show you to the car.
My bank will arrange
the transfer of funds within the hour.
- Excellent.
- When do we go out?
We'll contact you when the
necessary arrangements have been made.
Chance. What you doing here?
- Secret mission.
- Mmmm.
Rub me, baby.
Oh, yeah, baby.
Hello, Poe.
What the fuck?
- You miss me?
- Aw, Christ, not again.
Looks like you're short
an ear,
so you better listen
very carefully.
- Now, are you paying attention?
- Uh-huh.
Who sent those apes
after me?
I don't know
what you're talking about.
Two million people
in this city.
- Who's gonna miss a fat
slob like you, Poe, huh?
- Van Cleaf!
H-His name was Van Cleaf.
Good boy.
Where is he?
I don't know where he lives!
He ain't even American!
Look, he'll... He'll kill me
if I don't do what he says!
You gotta believe that!
Aaah!
Tell your boyfriend
Van Cleaf...
I'm gonna find out who
killed Douglas Binder.
If you understand me,
just grunt.
Again.
Did you get my memo?
Binder, Douglas C.
I want you to take another look
at the post-mortem.
That memo contains evidence...
that might make
Binder's death a homicide.
Now, you can act on it, Doctor,
or you can file it,
but if I have to get a court order
for a formal inquest,
I will.
You should do something
about that cough.
Don't you ever knock?
We have a problem.
A big problem.
They want me to redo
the autopsy on Binder.
- Who is it that's asking?
- A detective named Mitchell.
Binder's family's
breathing down her neck.
- Can we buy her?
- No.
I guess we've overstayed
our welcome.
Tonight is our last hunt
in New Orleans.
Open it.
What a funny
little man, eh?
A change of scenery's what we need.
Something less tropical.
Rolling hills, castles.
Eastern Europe.
We can work there for years.
- Where's Poe?
- Mr. Poe couldn't make it.
He's got an ear infection.
Look, he, uh, he said
he'd have some work for me.
That may still be
a possibility.
We got a little game
we'd like you to play with us.
This money belt...
has $10,000 in it.
It's all yours if you want it,
every penny.
What do I have to do?
The rules of the game
are very simple.
All you have to do is get to the river.
Ten miles through the city.
You and the money belt make it
to the river, you're $10,000 richer.
Bullshit.
Maybe you like being
the object of pity,
begging for quarters,
sleeping in the rain,
listening to a half an hour
of fire and brimstone...
- for a bowl of soup.
- Man, fuck you.
You could change everything
tonight.
Think of what $10,000
could buy you.
You could get new clothes,
clean yourself up,
look men in the eyes when
you pass them on the street.
This money could
make you a man again,
instead of the shadow
of your former self.
- I get to the river, I get the cash.
- Every nickel.
- If I don't make it?
- Oh, you're a sports fan, Roper.
Figure it out.
You've got a five minute head start.
Don't waste it.
This is New Orleans,
Mr. Zenan,
not Beirut.
After you, sir.
- Mr. Zenan, take it off "safe."
- Oh.
Finish him.
I don't want him. H-He's wounded.
- Finish him.
- I can't do that. I hit him.
- I shot him. Let's go, okay?
- Listen, don't make me look bad
in front of my dogs.
You know why you're here?
You paid us a
half a million dollars...
to find out
if you're alive or dead.
Now finish him.
Finish him!
God, why didn't he
go fishing?
Now you understand why we
insist on payment up front.
Here.
Set the dogs on him,
won't you, Pick?
I don't wanna be out here
all night.
Help me!
Please! Please!
H... Please!
Help me! Help me!
- Go on, get a job!
- Please!
- Watch it! Damn! Watch yourself!
Help me. Help me!
Help me! Please!
Hey, look!
Come on, man!
- Walk on by, now, man.
- Call the police here or somethin'!
Help me!
- Hey! Hey! Let me in! Come on, man!
- No, we're closed!
Let me in!
Hey, buddy!
Hey! Hey! Come on!
- Brother, get out of here, man.
Come on, get out of here.
- Hey, come on, man!
- Help me!
- Hey! I ain't got no change, man!
He was passin' out flyers
for Randal Poe.
Let's pay him a visit.
Randal, Randal, Randal.
You were gonna leave
without saying good-bye?
My mama got sick in Biloxi.
L...
I was gonna call you,
Mr. Van Cleaf.
Of course you were,
Randal.
Of course you were.
I know you didn't mean to
hurt my feelings.
Hmm?
Looks like we missed
the party.
- Get down!
- Ooh!
Stay down!
Go! Go! Go!
- Let's go.
- We can't just leave her here!
Keep him in the Quarter.
Stay on his ass.
She's dead. Come on.
Grab the bar!
Yeah!
Ladies first.
What?
It appears we'll have
one last hunt after all, Pick.
The train went by
maybe two,
two and a half hours ago.
This could be dangerous.
We're on his turf now.
Thank you, gentlemen, for making
yourselves available on short notice.
We are stalking
an exceptional opponent.
Truly a world-class trophy.
The price for participating
in this little excursion...
is $750,000 each.
Should one of you be lucky
enough to bring him down,
I'll consider that hunter's
account paid in full.
Shouldn't we be worried
about alligators or something?
If it make you
feel better,
yeah.
Come on, keep going.
It's still a long way...
- to Uncle Douvee's place.
- At least they won't
be able to find us out here.
Yes, they will, if they have
a tracker as good as Uncle Douvee.
All they have to do
is to check along the railroad.
I'm just guessing
we have a couple of hours.
- Okay.
- Maybe less. Come on. Let's go.
Isn't there
a trail or something?
This is the trail.
You're really enjoying yourself,
aren't you, Chance?
If it's tough for us,
it's tough for them.
You trust me?
Of course I trust you.
Close your eyes.
Why do you want me to trust you
with my eyes closed?
Close your eyes.
- Is it dead?
- Not hardly.
What are you doing?
I'm leaving a surprise
for my friends.
Son of a bitch!
If you would die quieter
and pick up the pace,
Boudreaux would have less time
for these little surprises.
Jerome!
Would you be so kind?
And do watch your step,
won't you? Let's go.
Sometime I amaze myself, me!
Is good whiskey!
Make jack rabbit slap the bear!
- Chance? Chance.
- Yeah!
You come to see your Uncle Douvee.
Natasha,
my Uncle Douvee.
Enchanté, mademoiselle.
We'll fix him up good.
Put bandage on, it no hurt.
- Be strong, my boy.
- Douvee, I've got some people after me.
I know.
I can smell them.
You've still got a.30-06,
the one I gave you for your birthday?
No. A gator ate it.
But, uh,
I've still got
your shotgun.
So tell me, this mans
what chase after you,
he mad at you
for business or pleasure?
- Both.
- Uh-huh.
I'm going to take Elvira south,
then to Bayou La Fouche,
Mardi Gras graveyard.
If you can talk her
into it, go ahead.
You be careful.
Don't worry about me.
I love the company.
Be careful.
Without you, I'm hunting them.
He's gonna be all right.
Oui. Come.
We go.
Here, drink. But do not spill.
It kill the grass.
The place is clean.
He just left.
Get the fuck down!
Hey!
Hold it!
Boudreaux is the target
we're after.
You are a fucking buffalo!
Move!
Boudreaux went this way, maybe ten,
15 minutes ago. He's on a horse.
He's trying to lead us
away from his friends.
Get in
the fucking trucks.
Move! Fucking move!
Will you move? Move!
They're fucking brain-dead.
Get the helicopter.
Find Boudreaux.
- We'll set up an ambush
this side of Bayou La Fouche.
- I can take him from the air.
Any pinhead can take him from the air.
I want to take him from the ground!
I can take him
from the air.
- Be a professional, Pick.
- Hey, you're making a mistake here.
Make sure
he gets there, Pick.
That's him.
Hey, pigeon.
Avril Pybus has a store
two miles this way.
You go to a telephone,
call the sheriff.
You know,
chére, I think you should
call the sheriff.
It appears your trophy's
ripping us a new orifice.
Let me review the tactical situation
for you, gentlemen.
Boudreaux is wounded.
He's been pursued and harried...
across miles of open country.
Now he's cornered
and outnumbered 20 to 1.
He's an annoying little
fucking insect...
and I want him
stepped on, hard.
You're not angry with me,
are you, Pick?
I don't get angry.
I'm a professional.
Let's move!
This is not good.
If we walk away now,
we can be in Mexico in five hours.
What the fuck is the matter
with you, Pick?
Hunting drunks in alleys
made you soft?
God, that son-of-a-bitch
is good!
Goddamn it, I'm gonna blow
his goddamn head off!
What are you lookin' at,
you sons-of-bitches?
This is what you paid for!
Get him!
Seal off this place.
The son-of-a-bitch
is mine.
Sorry about the shirt.
Give it a rest, pal.
- Now what do you want to do?
- Now...
Now we put arrow into everyone
what's not Chance, huh?
Come.
You fuckin' bitch!
Now...
Now look what you do.
Give me this gun.
I take care all this bad guy.
Give me this gun!
Chance!
- I told you to go for help.
- But we help.
All these men try to kill you.
We're here to help.
Boudreaux,
Boudreaux, Boudreaux.
I've been looking
all over for you.
- You've been looking
in the wrong places.
- That's good,
'cause I know you wouldn't
want to... hurt my feelings.
Can you get up?
I cannot dance,
but I can get up.
Hey!
You lucky son-of-a-bitch!
- You want some more of that?
- Yeah!
How does it feel
to be hunted?
You tell me!
You should know better.
There isn't a country in the world
I haven't fired a bullet in!
You can't kill me!
I'm on every battlefield!
There's no winner here!
I don't see one.
You're looking at him!
Come on, you son-of-a-bitch!
Take your best shot!
Chance!
My boy!
Just shoot him!
You won't do that, will you,
Mr. Boudreaux?
- Chance, please!
- If he shoots me, he'll kill you.
He's picked the wrong tool
for the job.
Put the weapon down...
or I'll run her through!
No!
You see, Miss Binder,
you I can understand;
it was a matter of family.
You had nothing in common
with those people.
What made you want to
complicate my life like this?
Poor people get bored too.
- Come here.
- Please.
Load me.
Hunting season... is over.
Douvee!
What is this noise?
I was dreaming.
Chére, I think about you.
I tell this turkey,
he no kill this eagle.
Some headache I got here!
Oh, my God.
- What?
- I think I hurt pretty bad.
Now this,
this real catastrophe!
- This real bad.
- Yeah, real bad.
Ah, when I was just
a little boy
A-standin'
to my daddy's knee
My papa said, Son
don't let the man get ya
And do
what he done to me
Born on the bayou
Lord, lord
Wish I was back
on the bayou
Rollin'
with some cajun queen
A-wishin' I were
a fast freight train
A-just a-chooglin'
on down to New Orleans
Born on the bayou
Mmm, mmm, mmm
Doin' it, doin' it
doin' it, doin' it
Lord
Oh, get back now
Well, I can remember
the fourth of July
A-runnin' through
the backwood bare
And I can still hear
my ol' hound dog barkin'
Chasin' down
a hoodoo there
Born on the bayou
Ohh, ohh
All right
Do it, do it, do it
do it
Mmm, ohh