The Indian knew
that deer moved in circles...
that if the hunter calculated
his moves with skill...
he could run the swift deer
into submission.
Its hooves would bleed,
and the animal stumbled.
The Indian was to kneel
above his dying prey...
putting his mouth
to that of the deer...
stealing its last breath.
While he had earned
the swiftness of the beast...
in its death he was struck by
its peace and stillness...
and by his own.
I tried telling myself
I'd done my job...
defended my life.
But I didn't believe me.
You killed my boy, Joe Roberts.
You killed my baby boy.
This is how houses catch fire.
Murderers' houses! Murderer!
Mrs. Baker, come on.
This isn't helping anything.
He killed my baby!
Robert, you and Jim
want to get Mr. Baker there?
I'm real sorry.
Captain said, John Henry
I'm gonna bring
my steam drill round
Bring my steam drill
out on the job
I'm gonna whup
that steel on down
Lord, Lord, I'm gonna
whup that steel on down
Henry said to Captain
Whoa, man ain't nothin'
but a man...
My brother Frank was due back
from Vietnam within the week.
We hadn't seen each other
since I'd lost the farm in '65.
I took the uniform job
to make ends meet.
In one of his letters,
he complained...
that his fellow soldiers
were disturbed...
by the killing they'd seen.
He wrote...
"Guys over here expect their
hair to stay dry in the rain."
Good.
Your mom called.
Yeah? What's happening?
First the plane was going to be
delayed in Hawaii or somewhere.
Then it was going to be
on time again.
Now she says
9:30 Tuesday for sure.
He's got to go through Fort Dix.
Raffael asleep?
Yes, babe.
You worried about today...
or about Franky coming home?
No. This kid today...
His parents came into
the station making threats.
What threats?
Threats.
When they pulled the father
outside, he started singing.
Joe.
- Don't move!
- Hey! It's me.
Shit.
You scared the hell out of me.
Come here.
I almost kill you!
He's got you trained, ain't he?
You are early.
I didn't want
to hang around Fort Dix...
so I took a Greyhound.
Joey's going to be
so happy to see you.
Joe is so happy to see you.
Come on, baby, come on.
Come on, a little bit.
Hey.
Share with
your Uncle Franky, shorty.
I'm going to take Frank
over to the folks.
I'll be back in a bit.
You'll be here?
Yeah. I've got two lessons
this afternoon.
See you.
Welcome home, Franky.
Bye-bye.
Bye-bye, say...
Your uncle is a barnyard dog.
Town looks same-same.
So you're a dad, man.
How's that?
Undescribable.
It's great.
He's amazing.
What?
Just looking at you.
Got to admit,
it feels kind of strange...
riding up front
in the man's car...
no handcuffs,
my own brother driving.
Shit.
Remember we used
to plug cop cars with snowballs?
Pull over.
Hey! Don't you do that.
You did it.
Hey, get the cop!
Come on.
All right!
Fire!
King of the mountain!
Need an army to fight me?
What are you doing?
Listen, I just wanted
to see you guys...
meet the baby and all.
I ain't going over
to see Mom and Pop.
What are you talking about?
Franky.
You caught me off balance here.
What are you saying?
Good-bye?
Let's just call it
see you later.
Hey, I came to see you,
brother man.
What about Mom and Dad?
What about them?
You're going
to break their hearts.
You're the one who always
takes shit personal.
Wait.
If anything,
they'll be relieved.
You'll see.
Where are you going?
You got a place to stay?
You got money?
I already took forty bucks
from your wallet.
It's in the glove box.
I don't want you to go.
Hey, Joe, this whole town's
talking about you.
Good shot, boy.
Thanks, sir.
You know, if I could
figure out the difference...
between what gets you a kiss
on the ass and me locked up...
I used to know my brother...
like I used to know
I'd always be a farmer...
but drifting off on the train
that day was a stranger.
He looked like a hero.
The closeness
I felt with my brother...
was with that
rough-and-tumble kid...
I knew before
high school distractions...
and then later my wife and farm
occupied our time together.
In the last few years
before going overseas...
Frank had become branded
the hell-raiser of town...
that he'd come to no good.
Maybe leaving so suddenly
was the only mercy he knew...
for the grief
he'd caused before.
As for my parents,
Franky was right.
They would not
take it personally.
They say some of
the boys coming back...
are coming back real confused.
Frank left confused.
Well, maybe
it'll straighten him out.
That's what Randall said.
Oh, my God, now my boy's
comparing his mama to a moron.
It wasn't a comparison, Mom.
He's a very restless boy,
that Franky.
That's what got him
into trouble, you know.
That's why he left.
I thought maybe
he just hated cops.
Don't say that.
Listen to your mama.
You are a good man, you hear me?
You are a good man.
That don't exempt you
from having the time come...
when you have to kill a man.
You can't regret it.
If it hadn't have been him,
it might have been my son.
No, sir. Don't you regret it.
You just keep saying
the Serenity Prayer...
and you get on with it.
We didn't see or hear from Frank
for a good six months...
when our lives took a turn.
There was a crack
of thunder outside.
Mrs. Roberts must have
jumped a foot off...
Do you want anything?
No. I know where it is.
Thank you.
She sure could make
good apple pie.
Do you need anything?
No. Thanks, Maria.
Thanks.
You know, Joe,
it didn't sit right with me...
when you married
a Mexican woman.
But I look at her today...
she's beautiful.
She's a beautiful
and good woman.
Boy, was I wrong.
I was dead wrong.
I'm going to check
the teletype at the station.
It wouldn't surprise me if he
were somewhere in the system.
He is. Yeah.
He sent out a card
about a month ago...
but I didn't want her to know.
He's got twenty-four more days.
Twenty-three and a wake-up.
Oh, yeah.
I've been counting.
Where is he?
Columbus.
Now, he didn't send a card,
but a girl named Dorothy.
"Dear Mr. And Mrs. Roberts...
"Frank hit me.
"My daddy said
he had to go to jail.
"But don't worry, because
I'm here to take care of him."
He's a likable son of a bitch.
Where does he get it, Joe?
I don't know.
Frank, he took his clothes off
to take a shit!
He took his clothes off
to take a shit.
Look.
That's a great-Iooking kid, Joe.
Thanks.
He has a great-Iooking mama.
What'd she say?
She asked would you mind
playing with the kid...
while we chatted a bit?
Sure thing. Kids love me.
Come here, Raffael.
How you doing, boy?
Incest product?
That ain't really
what she said, is it?
I knew that.
I got a real bad idea
I want to follow through on...
and I need your OK.
It's about Franky, huh?
I want to offer him a room
in our place for a while.
I got to try
and get close to him again.
I got to try... something.
Why do you think he'll want to?
I thought he had that little
masochist waiting for him.
Maybe the little masochist
will come, too.
Now, wait a minute.
No, Maria,
you're probably right.
He probably won't want to come.
Joe, we have a child
in the house.
I've thought about that.
I'd talk to him first.
If he wants to come,
if he wants to bring the girl...
I'd meet her
and decide from there.
I'm not going to say no.
Doggone it!
Raffael,
what did you do that for?
Put sand down my pants for?
I'd spoken
to Franky's jailers...
who told me that releases
didn't start till 10 a.m.
I'd only driven through
three states...
but, man, this country
looks smaller on a map.
Franky seemed to have few enough
moments of tenderness in him.
I didn't need
to interrupt this one.
I thought it better
to wait my turn.
Collect from Joe.
Hiya, baby.
Yeah, I'm still here.
No, I haven't yet.
Well, soon, I figure.
Kid's got me smoking again.
I will.
I know. I will.
I love you.
Bye-bye.
Little sister, that you?
Will big brother do?
How about Winnie the Pooh?
He's in the zoo.
This I knew.
He don't like the view.
'Cause he sniffs glue.
Open your damn door.
Are you sore?
How the hell
did you find me here?
Nice guy.
Are you going to invite me in?
I owe you forty bills.
So... pay me.
Repeat... how the hell
did you find me here today?
Well, I followed you
from the jail...
and I've been sitting
out there across the street...
smoking, which I had quit, but...
You followed me?
What you got there?
You got some squares for me?
Mommy's gone.
Bye, Mommy.
Where the hell is she?
The funeral
was almost a month ago.
I was in fucking jail, Joe.
I know where you were.
What difference does that make?
You wouldn't have known anyway.
What are you doing here?
Did you come here
to fucking guilt me to death?
Meet my old lady
Dorothy or Dotty...
or Doe or Dute or whatever.
Not whatever.
Hi, Dorothy. I'm Joe.
I'm Franky's brother.
Nice to meet you.
Joe followed us.
Like a common criminal.
Well, here's your beer
and stuff.
Joe come here to tell me...
that my mother died.
What do you say
we all go for some chow?
- Piñatas are from Spain.
- From Mexico.
Catch you smoking again in
the motor home, I'll shave you.
That woman has a beard.
Are you saying that twice...
because you think we can't
hear or see or what, girl?
I'm going to go say hello.
You do that.
How do you do?
My name's Dorothy.
Is it real?
A way-out lady I got, huh?
She used to be
one of them flower children...
before I set her course.
All right, come on.
The bigger they come,
the harder they fall.
Frank, I want you
to come back with me.
What?
I knew you were
going to say that.
So, come back with me,
live at the house a while.
Oh, yeah, Maria'd love that.
I got Dorothy. I'm cool.
You're cool?
You're living in a motel.
No. Just for now,
till I find another place.
She's staying
at her folks till then.
Why don't you come back
and spend time with me...
Raffael?
Spend time with the family?
- How's he doing?
- He's OK.
She let me touch it.
She's just a little squirrel,
ain't she?
Bring her with you.
What would I do there, man?
Have a few laughs with Pop?
You stay out of trouble.
Get yourself a damn job.
I don't want a damn job.
Besides, I got a deal where
I'm scamming G.I. Bill checks.
Far as Mr. Trouble goes...
he ain't no less
in one place than another.
Why is that, Frank?
I always figured
it was Trouble had a car.
You know what I mean?
The law is here.
Never smoke this stuff
in front of the law.
The law gets upset.
I'm home!
Dispose of the evidence!
Woman.
Man.
- Hey there.
He didn't come?
I'm sorry, Joe.
No surprise.
Where's the boy?
In there shooting heroin?
Thank you, Lord, for the gift
of this woman's cooking...
for the food to cook...
and the family
we have to share it.
Amen.
You want some?
Going to sell the house,
I think.
Are you?
Think so.
Where are you
thinking of living?
There's a trailer park
over on Bright's.
They got
a pretty good deal there.
That's nice there.
They have a vegetable garden
in the back...
where you can rent a plot,
grow your own vegetables.
That's right... vegebulls.
Vegetables.
Vegebulls, that's right.
Did you know your daddy
grew vegebulls, Raffael?
Your daddy was a farmer
before he was a po-lice-man.
Very good, Raffael.
You miss the farm, Joe?
Sometimes.
It's a bitch, ain't it?
The same thieves
that took your farm...
now have you work for them.
We get by fine.
Oh, sure. Of course you do.
Joe Roberts.
Hey, boy, did I wake you?
Who is it?
It's my father.
No, it's all right.
I'll tell you why I called.
You know
that strip of molding...
that you have between
the kitchen linoleum...
and the carpet
in your living room?
Well, I noticed this evening
that it was loose.
You might get yourself
a screwdriver...
and tighten up on it before
somebody trips and falls.
OK, Dad. Thanks.
I'll take care of it.
Good night, son.
Good night, Pop.
Who is it?
It's me, Joe.
How you doing?
Well, it's pretty early,
Randall.
What's going on?
Got your paper.
Joe, your daddy
shot hisself last night.
Is he dead?
Can I use your john?
Mr. Roberts?
I just took a telephone call...
from somebody claiming
to be your kin.
I think there's been
some kind of family emergency.
Mr. Roberts?
Did you have
a nice walk up here?
I don't understand.
What are you doing here?
I just told you.
Your family needs you
to get ahold of them...
because apparently
there's been some kind of...
Family emergency.
Right.
OK, thank you.
Did you like that?
Joe, Franky's girl just called.
He didn't want
to get on the line.
Did you tell her?
I told her.
I don't know how
much got through, man.
At least he knows.
Have you been
on my property lately?
Have you seen those hippies
down there with their tents?
They have fires down there
at night, you know.
Well, I sent Randall
down to talk to them.
Why don't you come over
to talk to them?
I'll do that, honey.
- Pardon?
- I'll do that.
Well, if you need
moral support about your dad...
you could just stop by.
I appreciate that.
You just can't carry
that stuff alone.
It's pretty emotional, you know.
I got a family helping me out.
I appreciate it.
Well, sometimes you can
talk to another person...
a lot more openly than
you can your own family.
You know, let it out?
So, if you could just
come over on the property...
and I could even have
something to eat there.
Thank you.
You're a lovely lady.
You afraid of me?
- Am I what?
- Afraid of me?
What do you mean
am I afraid of you?
Can't you open up
and talk to me a little bit?
What do you mean open up
and talk to you?
I'm offering to share
some time with you...
while you're there
checking out these people.
I don't like them there.
I do own the land.
I don't really
want to prefer charges.
They're just kids.
Well, I don't want
to cause them problems...
but with fires and stuff,
and then at night...
the pop cans and everything,
for crying out loud.
How's your pig doing?
- Pardon?
- How's your pig?
He's fine.
He still living in
that old pickup truck?
Yes, he is.
He's a good guy, that pig.
Want to come to play with him?
That's an awfully
nice color on you.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
Did you, uh...
You missed a spot.
That's just...
Well, you missed a whole spot.
The whole fender.
I'll take care of them hippies.
Don't you worry about that.
You need a lift anywhere?
To my house.
To your house. Just get in.
In front or back?
Can you squeeze in there?
Adios, Mrs. Roberts.
What do you say?
I don't speak no Mexican.
Good-bye, and please give
for me prayers to Mr. Roberts.
Thank you, Lucy, I will.
Work on your past tense.
Lucy, George Washington.
Glow in the dark.
Are you Joe Roberts' wife?
Yes. Who are you?
Me?
I'm Dorothy.
You in there, Frank?
It's me... Joe.
You in there, kid?
That you, Joe?
It's me, kid.
What are you doing in there?
Working on my draw.
All right if I come in?
Sure, Joe, come on in.
Bang. Gotcha.
So I had a bit to drink.
Somebody was boring me.
Think it was me.
You want to get dressed, Frank?
Take you to see your lady.
Pass me my drawers, would you?
I just hope he's OK.
Sometimes he hurts himself.
No, he'll be fine.
Joe'll bring him home.
So where did you and Frank meet?
Shoot.
Everywhere, I guess.
Excuse me.
Do you have a six?
Go fish.
I got what I asked for.
Do you have a nine?
Go fish.
Welcome back.
I'm sorry.
Feel sort of funny
showing up like that.
I don't know.
I'm glad you're here.
And Dorothy, too.
Finally got lucky, huh?
I sure hope so, because...
she's got my little monkey
in her belly.
You're going to be a pop?
Joe, Dorothy's pregnant.
I know. So I just heard.
Come here, Slappy.
I knew that Frank had come back
as a result of Dad's suicide.
It was an unsettling thought...
but that he'd come back
at all...
Help me with this shit!
And that he was going to
have a baby with his girl...
was enough for me to feel that
he'd not gone completely numb.
What am I, black?
Messy.
What are you doing?
This is where you
used to be a little boy.
It's where I grew up.
We're going to be
in the big room, girl.
I know.
I just want to smell it.
Sorry.
I love you more than anybody
ever loved anybody before...
in the whole wide world.
Come on, Franky.
It's our first night
alone together in a big house.
I love you back, OK?
Honey, I got to go.
I told Joe
I'd meet him at 11:00.
I'm late.
You're a beauty.
What?
If you see a shooting star...
or if you see
anything else...
will you think of me?
Little sister, you really
asking me those questions...
or are you just
stalling me here?
Both.
I'll be back soon.
Used to be bears out here.
Not so damn long ago.
This place wasn't even
timbered when we were kids.
New ground.
New ground, shit.
Not new ground.
What do you mean,
not new ground?
Old ground!
Old ground, shit.
Old ground. Dad said.
Said what?
What did Dad say?
You had a Sioux village
twenty-five miles north.
You had another
ten miles southwest.
He said,
when this was all woods...
you had Indian runners traveling
messages right through here.
Getting chewed by wolves.
Safe from wolves!
Shredded by grizzlies.
Safe from grizzlies.
Safe, shit.
Safe, Dad said.
Said what?
"Independent of time and space,
the Runner becomes his message."
Ain't no wolf, no bear
going to eat a message, Joe.
Never fucking happen.
Since when do you...
Wait a minute.
I get it.
I know you think that way.
What way?
I still love you.
Dad finally did something
you respect.
Hey, Pop should have been
an Indian Runner.
This place looked better
when I had it.
I'll bet it did.
You know why?
Because you had the fire in you.
People got it now don't live
on the land they're working.
Ain't got no fire.
Never had it.
This fire?
The fire's out now.
So what?
Between the cradle and now,
you happened.
You burned, brother.
What do I have to show for it?
What you got, Farmer Joe,
is knowing you once was.
On fire.
Shit.
Man...
I burned.
The land was churned.
- I burned.
- The soil was turned.
- They took what you earned.
A lesson learned.
Meeting adjourned.
I've missed this, Franky.
I've missed having
a laugh with you.
Me, too.
Oh, man...
what'd you do that for?
Come on.
OK, Big Bear.
I'm an Indian Runner.
I'm a message.
And the message is...
bet you can't find me.
I'll get you.
Ready to give up?
God damn it.
All right!
All right, you win!
You're a message.
You win.
Oh, Joseph.
Oh, Joey.
The message is...
never trust a bear.
I thought you're a tough guy.
Frank worked hard,
every shift he could get on.
And Dorothy
tended to the house...
got the old place
looking remarkably new.
Me...
I wanted to burn again.
How much longer
do I have to do this, Franky?
Forty seconds.
I don't think
this is good for the baby.
Thirty-five seconds.
Why do I have to do this?
Because I got to know.
Twenty-five seconds.
Got to know what?
Twenty.
Ten, nine, eight, seven, six...
five, four, three, two, one.
Good.
I'll marry you... if you want.
Did you say you'd marry me?
If you want.
Oh, my God!
I'm going to be your wife!
Go!
Go, Franky, go!
Good, little sister.
It's kicking!
Franky, it's kicking.
Let me see.
There?
That ain't a kick,
that's a punch.
That's the last wild son
you're baking, baby.
Is that right,
what your papa said?
You going to be
a big, strong, handsome dude?
What about me?
I got some skeeter bites
that need scratching.
How about you and me
go fiddle with the hydraulics?
Frank, don't talk like that!
Why are you looking
at me like that?
Come on, Franky,
you're scaring me.
Frank, you're scaring me.
Did I say the wrong thing?
Is it that you don't know me...
you don't know when
I say something nice?
Don't.
You don't know how to see
good things from bad things?
That it?
Is it that we're strangers?
We're not strangers.
I don't know what
you're talking about.
Let's eat.
You eat.
Stop it.
Wait. Where are you going?
It's OK, baby.
He's just restless, that's all.
Put your hands on him...
and you can't bring
any charges against him.
You weren't here.
You didn't see what he did.
He blind-sided me, man!
Listen to me.
Get in there!
No, you're not going
to get in there!
I'll run you in, man.
Damn it, he blind-sided me!
We tried to get you at home.
Maria said she didn't know
where you were.
Inside. It's Frank.
He busted this guy up
pretty good.
The guy's talking
about pressing charges.
Settle down. Take it easy.
Keep him there, Jim.
Where is he?
He's in there, boss.
I had to handcuff him
to the bar rail.
Looks like he ran up
a tab tonight, huh, Caesar?
He did that.
He tells me
he can sell some furniture.
Can you give us a minute,
Caesar?
Is that right, Frank?
You can sell some furniture?
That's good.
You blow off some steam,
Dorothy's got nothing to sit on.
What are you going to sell off
to keep this fella...
with the big eye from
pressing charges against you?
With your record,
you could do a year on this.
What can I say?
I fucked up.
I get in a violent way,
look around a room...
I want to bust it all to hell.
I see a guy like that...
I don't want him
to look at me cross-eyed.
I want that excuse
to fucking do him.
So you spend your life in jail?
That's a bear, man.
I'm a message!
Jail can't touch me.
Give me a cigarette.
I thought you were done
with this shit.
Well...
What about Dorothy? The baby?
Can it touch them?
- Outside parties.
- What?
Outside parties.
Give me a light.
I'm tired.
I just want to sit here, OK?
I'll sit here. I'll relax.
- You got something...
- Wait a minute, Clyde!
- Let me get in there!
- Listen to me.
Boy, I've had some
western times in this joint.
Frank, you got a job.
Oh, yeah.
You got a great girl.
You have a baby coming.
Give me your free hand.
Frank, give me your hand.
What are you doing?
I'm going to cut you a break.
Yeah, boss?
Bring that fella in here.
He's just going to jump
all over Frank.
I know.
You're bleeding.
Goddamn rocket scientist,
I tell you.
I'm going to go, Frank.
Be sure he comes by
to see me tomorrow.
I'll hold on to
the car keys till then.
All right.
Good night.
Good night, Joe.
What happened?
Ask Joe.
Joe, you've done
everything you can.
I know.
I look at him...
and I see this little boy...
with his little toy gunbelt on.
My little brother.
He's not
a little boy anymore.
He's got a problem.
He has to deal with it.
Dotty?
Dotty!
Yeah, Franky?
Come here.
I guess I got
a little off course last night.
I know.
I love you, little sister.
Look who I caught in
the parking lot doing wheelies.
I came to get the car...
but if you got a minute,
I'd like to talk to you.
Sure.
Can you follow?
- Drop Frank's car at his place?
- Sure, boss.
You ride with me.
- Randall?
- Yeah, boss?
Where's your gun?
There it is.
Damn it!
That ain't funny, Frank.
I know you're worried about...
will I take care of business...
with the old lady...
when the baby comes.
I appreciate it.
But I don't want you
to worry about me no more.
I'm good, Joe.
I'm good.
I want you to have
a good life, Frank.
I know.
I guess...
I guess what I'm here
to say is that...
I'm sorry about all the shit.
I'm sorry about Mom...
and Pop.
And, you know,
I ain't said it, so...
I'm saying it.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry, Joe.
- Have.
- I have.
Have.
My pen.
She.
- Had?
- Has.
Has. Telephone!
Her.
She has...
Joe Roberts.
What is it, Frank?
We'll be right there.
The baby's coming.
The baby was come.
Present.
I'm checking
the baby's head now...
and the back of the baby
is right over here.
The baby's coming.
We'll see if there's a horsy.
It's all right.
I'll be right back.
Would you ask the doctor
where Frank went?
I just saw him drive off.
He said he left the room
just to let us in.
I'm going to go find him.
Did you ever
want to kill someone...
just out of rage...
and you don't do it
because you're afraid?
And it's all about fear.
Fear of the law
coming down, sure...
but mostly...
fear like in sin...
sin with God.
Yeah, Almighty God.
What if he ain't almighty?
What if he ain't sacred?
You might just as well
have done the fella, right?
Goodness...
maybe ain't nothing but fear.
You know?
What you doing here?
Looking for you.
You found me.
What are you doing here?
I'm having a drink.
Buy you one?
Don't you think you ought to be
by your lady's side?
Leastways, over at the house?
The house.
Why not?
Why?
Come on, Frank,
don't give me that horseshit!
How are you, Joe?
Afternoon, Caesar.
You boys watch the place
for a minute?
I got to go pay a visit
to the captain's chair.
Chickenshit.
I'm trying to understand
why you are...
such a selfish son of a bitch.
I want to know how
to help you, Frank.
You're my brother.
You're the angriest man I know.
I want to know
why you hurt people...
why you're not with Dorothy
when your baby's being born.
Let me ask you something.
How'd it feel
when you killed that fella...
that kid out on the highway?
Not good, Frank.
No? I would have thought
that felt real fucking good.
It was clean. It was legal.
You saved your own life.
I mean, that's common sense.
It's common fucking sense,
right?
It's how these people think.
What people?
Man, you're on
a fucking tangent.
I ain't on a fucking tangent!
These fuckers don't give you
time to figure out the problem.
It's a math class.
The whole deal.
Just like every math class,
there's a clown in the front...
and everybody hates this clown
because he raises his hand.
He's answering
all the questions.
What do we do? Move on.
Just fucking move on,
ready or not.
He's deciding
we got to move on.
He knows his math.
I hadn't even figured out
about Santa Claus yet, dragons.
Gasoline was my favorite smell.
It's like your farm.
Who grew better crops,
you or the math man...
who bought it
out from under you? You!
What's a farm for?
It's for crops.
That's the world, Joe...
and it's a beauty.
Am I right?
You're right.
Am I wrong?
There is no common sense.
Right? I'm right.
All right.
So you're angry.
All your problems
are the world's fault.
That's right.
It's the world's fault.
Your fault. My fault.
The fault of every
motherfucking human being...
every fucking one
of them out there.
Life lacks tenderness, does it?
Go on back there.
Go see my angel get born.
Life must be great
if you laugh it up.
No, mister...
I'll just stay here
and drink it down...
because there's only
two kinds of men in this hell.
There's heroes and outlaws.
Which one are you?
Men come strong or weak,
and you ain't strong.
You're in a bar when
Dorothy needs you the most...
so you go ahead, Frank.
You go ahead. Drink it down.
You got it right.
There ain't nothing.
Ain't nothing worthwhile left,
not even our own children.
Your eyes are closed.
Keep them that way.
My eyes are open, Frank...
and I love looking at
my little boy and my wife...
and my house
and my little garden.
And I love you, Frank.
That all there is?
Why does that scare you so much?
Why doesn't it scare you?
Why?
I'm fixing a bridge
for fat retired men...
and their fat wives
and fat fucking little kids...
to drive over it
in their motor homes.
I'm making an impact.
That's what I'm doing.
That's all there is, Frank.
Out there it's family.
In here it's hell.
I'll be right back.
I'm here.
- What happened?
- It's nothing.
She all right?
She's tough.
Where's Frank?
- Not here.
- Where?
God! No!
Breathe!
You're doing beautifully.
- You're doing great.
- Almost there.
Oh, God! Help me!
Where's Franky?
What?
Take a deep breath
and blow it away.
Keep pushing.
It's just about here.
This is Unit Three.
I got him.
The baby's coming.
He's coming.
The head is being delivered.
Stop!
Can you see it?
Oh, God.
Here we come out,
and it's a boy.
A healthy boy,
it looks like.
I knew I'd never see or hear
from Franky again.
He turned his back...
on himself...
and on his family.
I went home that night...
watered my garden...
kissed my baby...
and I held my wife
until morning.
Life is good...
my brother Frank.