# Deep in the
Hundred Acre Wood
# Where Christopher Robin plays
# You'll find
the enchanted neighborhood
# Of Christopher's
childhood days #
This is one of my
favorite once-upon-a-times,
although I'm not quite sure
which time it was once upon.
But it had been so nice and summery
in the Hundred Acre Wood,
and the sunshine
was as warm as a blanket.
And the streams
were gurgling happily.
As happily as a tumbly
full of honey...
... which is very happy.
But all that changed when...
... the stranger came.
Honey.
Oh! Oh!
Oh, bother.
Oh, d-d-dear!
Oh, my!
It's got me!
Ah!
Huh?
Dear Roo. All excited
to go out already?
You're not
even dressed yet.
Mama, did you
hear that sound?
What sort of sound, dear?
I don't know.
It was sort of strange.
And kind of neat.
- Oh, the bother...
- Did it sound something like that?
No, Mama.
That's a Pooh Bear.
Good morning, Pooh.
What? Oh, well, uh,
good morning, Roo.
I wish it was.
A good morning, that is.
- Why? What happened?
- Many things.
- Many strange things.
- Oh, dear.
I'm sorry, Roo.
I must be going.
Where was I? Oh, bother.
- Oh, d-d-d-dear. Oh!
- Good morning, Piglet.
What happened?
Where's everybody going?
To Rabbit's house.
He'll know what to do.
I hope.
Whatever do you
suppose is going on?
I'm gonna go see.
Have fun, dear.
Come home when I call.
Yes, Mama.
Pooh! Piglet! Wait for me!
Hold tight, Piglet.
Pooh! Piglet! Tigger!
- It's a Hundred Acre "catastrophide"!
- Help!
Open up
in the name of us!
Quick, Rabbit! Help!
All right.
Uh, what?
- Thank goodness you're all right.
- It came at me!
- I heard this neat sound.
- Terrible.
- What's this all about?
- It chilled me to the bone.
- I was asleep.
- Something like...
...this.
- One at a time!
Thank you.
Now, what is going...
Me! Pick me! Me, me, me!
- Tigger?
- There I was,
sleeping,
dreaming Tiggerish dreams.
And suddenly
everything starts shaking.
And there's stuff
falling everywhere.
And then it stops.
And I look around.
And there it wasn't, my most
"favoritest" family portrait.
It was clean gone.
Did it look something
like this, Tigger?
Yeah, it was...
Actually, it had
a little less Pooh in it.
I see.
And, uh, Pooh Bear,
what about you?
Well, whatever it was,
it ate my honey. Oh...
And... Aw!
Well, actually, I ate my honey.
- But it made me do it.
- Humph.
I was asleep in bed, and I heard
this neat trumpety sound, and...
Thank you, Roo. Very good.
Now, Piglet, tell us
what happened to you.
Actually, l-l-I'd like
very much to forget.
Well, what we have here
is a mystery...
- Wow!
...of the most mysterious kind.
Hey, everybody.
Look what I found.
It's a swimming pool.
The sky has finally fallen.
Always knew it would.
Oh, m-m-m-my!
It looks like a footprint.
That's "impossibibble."
A footprint, indeed. Anyone
can see it's only a... a... a...
Rabbit, what sort of creature
do you suppose
would be attached
to a foot that...
...big?
There's only one thing
it could be.
A Heffalump.
Excuse me.
What's a Heffalump?
# Everyone knows
what a Heffalump's like
# It's got fiery eyes
and a tail with a spike
# Claws on its paws
are sharp as a tack
# And wing-a-ma-things
coming out of its back
- Out of its back?
- Of course, Roo. Precisely.
"Exact-tickally."
# Its bottom is up
and its top's really down
# So its nose is its tail
or the other way 'round
# Yeah, and it's wide as a river
and tall as a tree
- # Imagine gigantic
- # And times it by three
- # It clomps here and there
- # It stomps to and fro
- # Got three horns above
- # And eleven below
- # Those are its good points
- # There's much more to know
# About the
dreadfully dreaded
# Thoroughly three-headed
Horribly hazardous Heffalumps
Wow. Neat.
Neat? It's most
certainly not neat.
# Everyone knows
they lurk and they creep
# The best time to see one
is when it's asleep
# If you sneak up
behind it and get it to jump
# You can tell which part's
Heffa-hee-hee
# And which part is lump
# They'll steal all your
honey and eat your last crust
# Stomp on your house
till it's nothing but dust
# The worst part of all is
They're different
from us?
# They're the
dreadfully dreaded
# Thoroughly three-headed
Fiercely ferociously
# Mostly atrociously
Horribly hazardous
# Heffalumps #
Yeah!
And they live
right over there.
Heffalump Hollow.
Oh, oh, d-d-d-d-dear!
I know. I know.
Let's go get them.
Capture a Heffalump?
Ha-ha. Impossible.
Besides, it's never been done.
Then we'd be
the first to do it.
It'd be fun.
It'd be an adventure.
It'd be...
...an "expotition."
- Hmm.
Yes. Well, now that I think
of it, it would be a first.
- Mm-hmm.
- Oh, yes.
The first Heffalump expedition
in history.
Oh, splendid idea.
Glad I thought of it.
Of course, capturing a Heffalump
is a perilous affair.
Meticulous planning
is called for.
But how does one capture
a Heffalump?
How, you ask?
It's quite simple, really.
Come back with your equipment
and I'll show you how it's done.
Humph.
Woo-hoo!
Ohhh!
All right. Let's see
what everyone's brought.
Hoo-hoo-hoo!
Has anyone brought
anything useful?
I brought some rope.
Rope, yes. My thought exactly.
Thank you, Roo.
You see, a simple piece of rope
if the most effective device
for capturing Heffalumps.
Now, everyone together.
Aim at the barrel
and say in a firm voice,
"In the name
of the Hundred Acre Wood,
I capture you."
In the name
of the Hundred Acre Wood,
I capture you!
And toss.
Brilliant.
In the name
of the Hundred Acre Wood,
I capture you!
Whoa! I did it! I did it!
I'm gonna capture
a whole bunch of Heffalumps.
Come on, everybody.
Let's go get them.
Just a moment, Roo.
A Heffalump expedition
is fraught with danger.
But we gotta go
catch the Heffalump.
Roo, you just can't argue
with a word like "fraught."
- But I really want to go.
- It's too dangerous, Roo.
You're simply too young.
You could get hurt.
But I...
Roo!
Time to come home!
Roo, dear!
You mean I can't go?
- I'm... I'm sorry, Roo.
- Roo!
Coming, Mom.
Oh, don't be sad, Roo.
L-l-I think you're
very, very lucky.
All right, everyone,
we'll meet here tomorrow morning
for the grand expedition.
And Rabbit and Tigger are
quite sure Heffalumps are so awful?
And everybody's
gonna catch one but me.
It isn't fair.
Oh, I'm sorry, Roo,
but there will certainly be
other adventures you can go on.
I'm grown up enough to catch
a Heffalump. Aren't I, Mom?
You're growing up
very fast, indeed, dear.
Faster than you think.
Do you think I could grow up
by tomorrow morning?
So soon? Why?
Then I could go
on the "expotition."
You know, dear, growing up
doesn't happen all at once.
It takes its own time.
But I need to grow up now.
Well, then, how about starting
with a good night's sleep,
little Mister Roo?
# Little Mister Roo
# Reaching for the moon
# So many things
you've got to do
# And no time for dreaming
# Little Mister Roo
# Let the stars
shine over you
# Don't grow up too fast
too soon
# Save some time for dreaming
# Settle in, settle down
# Let me see that sleepy yawn
on your face
# Close your eyes
# I will love you completely
# And always
# Little Mister Roo
# The moon shines silver
over you
# No one knows you like I do
# And little Mister Roo
# Reaching for the moon
# Don't grow up too fast
# Too soon #
Do you want your nighty light?
No, thanks.
I don't need it anymore.
- Good night, sweetheart.
- Good night, Mama.
I just know I could catch one.
Ahhh!
Hoo-hoo-hoo!
Ah!
Ah, yes.
A perfect morning
for catching Heffalumps.
It's very brave of you
to join us, Piglet.
Especially since it's
so very dangerous.
Well, I thought of hiding
under my bed, Pooh Bear,
but I'd rather be hiding
out here with all of you...
...than under my bed,
with all of me!
Now, now. We've gathered
the best minds to the task.
Namely my own.
We simply can't fail.
Right you are, Rabber-rific.
With Tigger's
Heffalump-tracking skills,
it's a fate-a-complicated.
With courage, cunning,
and superior tactics,
we'll be home by teatime.
Oh, I hope so.
Behold. Heffalump Hollow.
Home of the dreaded Heffalump.
Oh, my. I believe
that what's over there
doesn't look quite as friendly
as what's over here.
Fiddlesticks and nonsense.
There's nothing to be afraid of.
Hmm.
There you go. See?
Rabbit didn't
get gobbled up.
Yet.
Hmm!
Okay.
Hoo-hoo-hoo!
Well, would you look at that.
I didn't get gobbled up either.
Hoo-hoo-hoo!
Yet.
There you are, Piglet.
It seems that both sides
of the fence
are about the same.
So far.
Ha! Now to teach those
Heffalumps a thing or two.
Ready!
Forward, march!
# No time to lose
Chin up, tallyho
# We'll never stop
till those Heffalumps go
# The best Heffa-quest
you'll ever know
# They're the
dreadfully dreaded
# Thoroughly three-headed
Horribly hazardous Heffalumps
# The dreadfully dreaded
Thoroughly three-headed
- # Massively monstrously
- # Unbearably scare-ably
# Horribly hazardous Heffalumps #
- Thank you, Pooh Bear.
- You're welcome.
Now,
remember, everyone,
the important thing is
that we stick together.
- Oh! Uh, coming.
- Safety in numbers, you know.
You know, if we didn't
stick together,
we would be very lost indeed.
Don't let me hold you up.
Got it.
Who's there?
Ah!
Hello?
Is anyone there?
Who's there?
Ah!
You're it.
Now you gotta catch me.
- I really need to go, 'cause...
- Aw. How come?
Because...
- I've got to catch a Heffalump.
- Oh, really?
You can catch me.
I'm a Heffalump.
A Heffalump?
Heffalump. Heffalump.
That's what I am, all right.
A Heffalump.
But you can't be.
Actually, I am.
If you're a Heffalump...
...then where's your horns
and spiky tail?
I don't know.
Wow, a spiky tail.
I wish I had one.
Are you sure you're a Heffalump?
My mummy says I am.
Well, if you are a Heffalump,
then in the name
of the Hundred Acre Wood,
I capture you.
Okay.
Jump.
I did it.
I did it!
You did it!
Yay!
Wait. I captured you. Whoa!
I capture you!
Whoa!
Wait! Whoa!
You're supposed to come with me!
Um...
...Piglet?
- Yes, Pooh?
Why are you setting out
little pink jelly beans?
I've been leaving a trail
so we can find our way back
from the Heffalump "expotition."
Oh, bother.
Oh, no.
We're lost!
Whoa!
- Stop!
- Okay.
What game should
we play now?
Rumblejump? Leaplog?
Or Hogswallow?
We can't play any games.
- Why?
- You've gotta come with me.
Yow!
Why?
Because I captured you.
Because...
Because I'm a grownup.
Wow. You're a grownup?
- Hey!
- A grownup.
You must have
your own call, then.
My call?
Yeah, like this.
Like that. But only better.
Haven't found mine yet.
My mum said I'll find it
when I grow up.
I can't wait till I grow up.
Well, growing up
takes a long time.
It took me just about forever.
That's it.
That's the sound I heard.
Gotta go now. Bye.
Wait. Wait a minute.
You can't leave.
But my mummy's calling.
That's your mom?
Don't you have to go
when your mum calls?
Well, yeah, but...
Don't go yet.
Let's go see my friends first.
Then you can go.
Well, I don't know.
Please?
Mmm...
Okay, I guess.
Thanks.
But soon as we're done,
I've got to go.
Okay.
Forward, bounce!
I know another game.
It's called The Name Game.
Heffalumps have names?
Of course.
My name is Heffridge
Trumpeter Bumpet.
Heffridge Trumpler Brompet
Heffalump the Fourth.
Whoa.
How do you remember all that?
I can't, so everybody
calls me Lumpy.
Lumpy.
Lumpy-bumpy-dumpity-bump!
That's The Name Game.
# Lumpy lumpity lee
# Lumpy bumpity bee
# Lumpy dumpity dee
# Heffa-Lumpy like me
# You make a game
of your name
# So it's never the same
Never the same
# Add a sound
Add a doodle
# Now you've got a name
that's brand new-dle
- Huh?
- Go on, then. What's your name?
Roo.
# Rooty tootle-y-doo
- Hey!
- # Rooty tootle-y-doo
# Rooty bootalee-boo
# Rooty tootie, that's you! #
No, just Roo.
#... Heffalumps like... #
Okay,
so why are we hiding again?
We're not hiding.
We're planning an ambush.
So, um...
You see any Heffalumps yet?
I know.
I'll use my famous Heffalump
call to lure one over.
You have an infamous
Heffalump call?
Well, of course.
All great Heffalump catchers do.
Scree!
Yooo!
Ah!
M-M-My, what a dreadful sound.
Do you suppose
it might b-b-b-b-be a...
Oh, yes, Piglet.
It does sound rather Heffalumpish.
Oh, m-m-my!
Do you see it?
That one was good.
I see a tail.
Are there horns too?
Two of them.
Oh, d-d-d-dear.
Be brave, Piglet.
This is our chance
to save our woods.
And our honey.
Yes, Pooh.
In the name
of the Hundred Acre Wood,
I capture you!
I caught a Heffalump, Piglet.
And so did you.
Rabbit would be proud of us.
Pooh, have you noticed
that Heffalumps
look a lot like rabbits?
And why do you think that is,
Piglet?
Oh, d-d-dear.
The Heffalump knows my name.
Well, hello there, Tigger.
Did you happen to see
the Heffalump I just captured?
Hmm.
You got me there.
# Kerplunk went the little
green frog last night
# Kerplunk went
the little green frog
# Kerplunk went the little
green frog last night
# And his bump went
bloomp-bloomp-bloomp
# We all know frogs go... #
Hey. Come on. Let's go.
I think I better go home now.
Why?
'Cause I'm not supposed to go
in that part of the woods.
- Scary things live there.
- Huh?
That's where I live. There
aren't any scary things there.
Are too.
There's a stripy thing
that bounces, and it goes...
Whoo!
Then it pounces.
Whoa!
No, that's Tigger.
You're wrong about him.
He's great.
And there's this
little pig monster
that squeals and shakes
all the time.
And it will get you
if you don't watch out.
Oh, no.
You're wrong about Piglet too.
He wouldn't hurt a fly.
And then there's
this loud thing,
and it's got long ears.
And he yells at everybody.
Yeah, you're kind of right
about Rabbit.
But he's okay
once you get to know him.
I don't want to get to know him.
Do I have to?
Hey, you really are scared,
aren't you?
- But my friends aren't scary.
- Uh-huh.
Who told you all this stuff?
I don't know.
Everybody knows.
Hmm. That's just what Rabbit
and Tigger said about Heffalumps.
There's nothing scary here.
Promise?
Promise.
Hmm.
Whoa!
- Roo.
- Sorry. My fault.
Why, thank you, Tigger.
All right, no more fun and games.
The Heffalump is all
but in our grasp.
- Go away!
- Excuse me.
Are we planning
another ambush?
Of course not. We're hiding.
H-H-How will we know
w-when it's s-safe?
Oh, m-m-my.
Well, Piglet?
Do you see it?
It's coming! It's coming!
I suggest a retreat
to another part of the wood.
I'm right behind you.
This way.
No, that way.
Oh, hello, Eeyore.
Ah! Goodbye, Eeyore.
I'm afraid to ask.
Hello?
Pooh Bear?
Hello!
Anybody? Rabbit?
I caught the Heffalump.
I mean, uh, Lumpy.
Pooh Bear?
Hmm. It looks
like nobody's home.
Excuse me. Sorry.
Is that you?
Yeah. My mum usually
makes me a snack about now.
Do you have any Rumpledoodles?
- What are those?
- They're like biscuits.
They go rather well with honey.
Wait. That's Pooh's honey.
Mmm.
Oh, well. I guess he won't mind.
Um, we better go
before we break something.
Uh-oh.
This is where Rabbit lives.
Is he the one
with the pointy ears?
Don't worry.
He won't hurt you.
They must still be out
on the "expotition."
Lumpy?
Mmm.
Ha! Hmm.
Oh, yeah?
Whoo-hoo-hoo!
Whoa.
Huh? Wh...?
Ah!
Missed me.
Oh!
Whoa!
Gotcha.
Oh-oh!
My mum's not going to like this,
Rooty-toot.
Yeah. My mom neither...
...Lumpster.
We'd better get cleaned up.
- Hey, wanna play a game?
- What kind of game?
Cannonball!
# We stand shoulder to shoulder
# We see eye to eye
# We dive deep under water
# We jump high in the sky
# High
# We stand shoulder to shoulder
# We stand side to side
# When one of us
gets a tiny bit tired
# One gives the other a ride
# Ride
# I've never had
a best friend before
# So I can't be sure
# What it feels like
# But I think it feels
more like this, I do
# I think I feel
more like myself
# When I'm with you
- Can you teach me that?
- Of course.
Suck it in...
...and then spray it down.
See?
Tell you what, you stick to squirting
and I'll stick to bouncing.
Yup.
Are you thinking
what I'm thinking?
- Yeah!
- Cloud racing!
Lumpster?
Yeah?
You're not captured anymore.
Yay!
# Finding, finding
Losing and finding
# Making, making
a bond that is strong
# Building, building
a house for a friendship
# Breathing a breath for our song
# Song
# For our song #
Run! Hurry! Come on!
You're behind!
Quiet!
Well, what do you know?
We're home.
Well, well.
All in all, a successful
Heffalump expedition.
- Are you sure, Rabbit?
- Well, certainly. Just look around.
You don't see any Heffalumps,
do you?
Oh, bother.
Rabbit, I don't think
it's successful anymore.
Rabbit! Rabbit! Rabbit!
The Heffalumps
are among us!
- What'll we do?
- We're surrounded.
- Run for your life!
- Where?
- Look for an exit!
- They got us surrounded!
- Did you hear that?
- We're trapped!
That's it. Traps.
We need traps!
Everywhere!
Whoo-hoo-hoo!
Ah!
I'll get some bait.
- Oh!
- Ah!
Ahhh!
Ooh!
What?
- Hoo-hoo-hoo!
- Ah!
Behold.
A super-duper, extra-looper,
hunka hunka Heffatrap.
Oh, m-m-m-my.
Well, what do you know?
It catches Piglets too.
I'd like to see a Heffalump
try and breach these defenses.
- It's impressive, Rabbit.
- Now,
to await the attack.
# Lumpy lumpity lee
# Lumpy bumpity bee
# Lumpy dumpity dee
- # Heffa-Lumpy like me
- That's it.
# You make a game of the name
# So it's never the same
Never the same
# Add a sound
Add a doodle
# Now you've got a name
that's brand new-dle
# Lumpy lumpity lee
# Lumpy bumpity bee
# Lumpy bumpity dee #
Oh, no! We forgot your mom.
I really have to go.
She sounds worried.
Come on.
I'll help you find her.
Thank you, Roo.
Roo!
Mrs. Heffalump!
Mrs. Heffalump?
Gosh.
She's not here, either.
Don't worry, Lumpy.
We'll find her.
Um, uh...
Let's try that way.
Lumpster?
Are you okay?
We haven't heard my mom
in a really long time.
Um... Do you wanna
play a game?
No, thanks.
Don't feel like games.
When I don't feel good,
my mom sings to me.
My mum sings to me too.
# Little Lumpy Loo
# Reaching for the moon
# So many things
we've got to do #
I want my mum.
Me too.
Wait.
My mom.
She'll know what to do.
Come on.
Come on, Lumpy.
Let's go back and find her.
Come on, Lumpy. My mom
will make everything okay.
Roo?
Roo!
Oh!
Oh, my goodness.
False alarm!
As in, "Never mind!"
We almost casually captivated
ourselves a captive Kanga.
And that's kind of hard to say.
What's all this for?
We built traps
to catch the Heffalump.
Clever, huh?
Please, have any
of you seen Roo?
He should have
been home by now.
Come on, Lumpy.
Just a little further.
Hey, look.
There she is, Lumpy.
Mom!
Roo!
This is Lumpy!
He's a Heffalump!
A real Heffalump!
- And it's got Roo too!
- Stop him!
- Unhand him!
- We'll save you, Roo!
Wait!
- Never mind.
- Retreat!
- Retreat! Retreat!
- Bounce for your life!
- Charge!
- No, wait!
- Lumpy!
- Roo!
Lumpy!
Wait! Don't go!
Roo!
Huh?
Lumpy?
You said they
wouldn't be scary.
You promised.
Oh, Lumpy. I'm so sorry.
This is all my fault.
I want my mummy.
- Roo!
Come on, Lumpy.
We gotta get you out of here.
Roo.
Come on.
Let's get you back home.
- There they are!
- The Heffalump's got him.
Drop my bouncing buddy,
you Heffally-rascalump!
After it!
In the name
of the Hundred Acre Wood,
- I capture you!
- No! Lumpy!
- We did it!
- We did.
- Leave him alone!
- Wait!
You're scaring him.
Rabbit, what on earth
are you all doing?
Well, we're rescuing Roo
from the Heffalump!
Wait. No, stop.
You don't understand.
What? Now, see here, Roo...
Rabbit, let him finish, please.
We were wrong about Heffalumps.
They're not scary creatures.
Lumpy's my friend.
He's just like us.
- He gets afraid.
- Oh!
- He likes honey.
And he even learned
how to bounce.
Oh, look at that.
So... So you've
got to un-capture him.
But...
- Oh!
- Lumpy!
Lumpy!
Oh!
We're coming, dear!
- Oh, dear. Roo?
- Roo!
- Hold on, Roo!
Mom... Mama?
Tigger.
We'll help you!
Just hang on!
Roo, I've got an idea!
One, two, three...
Hold on, Roo!
Pull!
Lumpy?
There, there, Piglet.
I think he's trying to help.
- Mummy!
- Mummy?
My mummy's coming!
Heffridge Trumpler Brompet
Heffalump the Fourth,
where have you been?
Oh, my little darling.
I've been worried sick.
I'm okay, Mummy,
but my friend Roo's in trouble.
Can't you save him?
- Mummy, this way. Hurry.
- Oh, my.
Roo, can you hear me, love?
Now, don't be frightened.
I'm Lumpy's mummy.
Here I am! Right here!
- Don't you worry, love.
- Oh!
Just leave it to me.
- Ohhh!
- Oh!
Now, now, try not to move, love.
Here I come.
Hold very still, love.
Easy does it.
Yeah!
Oh, thank goodness.
- Mama! Mama!
- Roo! Oh, Roo.
I was so worried.
Thanks, Mrs. Heffalump.
Mummy!
You did it! You did it!
My little Roo.
Oh, Lumpy.
You've found your call.
Oh, Rabbit.
That's why the Heffalump
was in our wood.
She was looking for her baby.
Young...
...Heffalump.
I...
That is to say, we...
Can you ever forgive us?
We've acted very badly.
That's okay, Long Ears.
I like this kid already.
You're right, Rooty-toot. He is
nice, once you get to know him.
Lumpy, darling.
We really should be going.
I have to go home now.
Goodbye, Lumpster.
Goodbye, Rooty-toot.
- Just a bit longer?
- Please?
Well...
I don't see why not.
I suppose a few more minutes
wouldn't hurt.
- Forward, bounce!
- Wow!
Here I come!
Roo, Roo, Rooty-toot-toot.
Woo-hoo!
Yippee!
And so,
things were quite different
in the Hundred
Acre Wood after that.
You know, we never really did
capture a Heffalump that day.
It was more like...
... like Lumpy
captured all of us.
# We stand shoulder to shoulder
# We see eye to eye
# We dive deep under water
# We jump high in the sky
# High
# We stand shoulder to shoulder
# We stand side to side
# When one of us
gets a tiny bit tired
# One gives the other a ride
# Ride
# I've never had
a best friend before
# So I can't be sure
# What it feels like
# But I think it feels
more like this, I do
# I think I feel
more like myself
# When I'm with you
# Finding, finding
Losing and finding
# Making, making
A bond that is strong
# Building, building
A house for a friendship
# Breathing a breath for our song
# Song
# For our song #
# In the name
of the Hundred Acre Wood
# We claim thee
# In the name
of the Hundred Acre Wood
# We claim thee
# In the name
of the Hundred Acre Wood
# What do you do
when something new
# Crosses your path
out of the blue?
# What do you do?
What do you do?
# I think once upon a time
# The Heffalumps
ruled the forest
# They romped and stomped
and blew their horns
# To their near and dearest
# They scared
all the rest of us
# A Heffalump is
as a Heffalump does
# Is a Heffalump now
as a Heffalump was
# What do you do
when something new
# Crosses your path
out of the blue?
# What do you do?
What do you do?
# In the name
of the Hundred Acre Wood
# We claim thee
# In the name
of the Hundred Acre Wood
# We claim thee
# In the name
of the Hundred Acre Wood
# What do you do?
What do you do?
# In the name
of the Hundred Acre Wood
# What do you do?
What do you do?
# What do you do? #