If anyone finds this letter..
it means that my plan didn't work..
and that I'm already dead.
But if I can somehow go back to the beginning of all this
I might be able to save her.
Evan!
We're going to be late again.
Since when do you care about going to school on time?
Don't worry, we've plenty of time.
Is dad going to come?
You know the answer to that.
Can he just come out for one day?
We've been over this a hundred times.
It's too dangerous for him.
But Lenny said his dad is coming..
and Tommy's and Kelly's Dad.
Ok I get the point!
I'm not so bad, am I?
No.
Ok! Have a good day.
I will pick you up later. Got to go.
Bye!!
bye!!
Mrs. Treborn, I need to speak to you.
Can we just wait till tonight?
I'm already late for work and I...
I think you really need to see this.
Tommy! Leave Lenny alone!
Don't let me send you to Mr Voyteck office!
I was going to show this to the principal..
but I thought I'll talk to you first.
What is it?
Yesterday, I had the child to draw whatever they wanted
to be when they grow up.
Most of them made drawings of their parents.
But this..
I don't understand?
Evan did this?
Can I keep this drawing?
Of course.
Umh..there is one more thing Mrs Treborn
I feel bad even mentioning.
What?
When I asked Evan about the drawing..
well.. he couldn't remember doing it.
I don't wanna go.
I don't like this place Mom,
it's creepy.
I promises I won't make any bad pictures.
We'll be fine OK.
He just want to do a couple to tests. That's all.
You'll like him.
You're doing great.
Just tell me he has not
inherited his father's illness.
I'm sure the results will come back negative.
But there is something else
you can do to monitor his memory.
Anything.
A journal.
Just get him to write down everything that he does.
And what would that do?
It could help to jock his memory.
..See if he could remember anything new the next day.
This test result will come back in a few days
..and then we’ll take it from there.
OK
Today, mommy is taking me to play with Kelly and Tommy.
I’ll meet their father and see what a real dad is like.
Great! See you soon.
Evan!
Evan.
What are you doing with that knife?
What happened?
Honey..
..what were you doing with that knife?
I don’t remember.
Hey Andre.
George!
Hello little man.
Watch your steps.
Thanks George.
Not a problem.
Here’s my number at the hospital
..if there is any problem.
You know.
You’re kidding! We’re gonna have a
great time today. Right sport?
OK! Be good kiddo.
I love you.
Bye bye.
Bye George.
Go..go on.
Right at the back yard.
Here it comes.
Evan, Evan guess what? Dad got a new video camera
..and we’re all gonna be in the movie.
That’s right Evan
..and you
..got to be the star.
I thought I was the star!
Hey! What did I tell you?
Now Evan.
..you have to promise
..you’re the bestest super-doper promise
..that this will be our little secret.
Huh huh.
My boy…
Where am I?
Where did we all go?
Calm down kid and stand still.
I was just somewhere else.
How did I get here?
Stop acting like some retard
or I’ll call your mother
..to tell her how a naughty
little shit you have been.
Kelly?
Kelly>
What happened?
The good news is, the result is negative.
I found no evidence of legends,
hemorrhages, tumors..
There must be sometime you can work on?
If I were to guess
..I’ll say the blackouts are stress related.
But he’s seven years old.
What kind of stress a seven year old can have?
Plenty.
Maybe he has severe coping problem
of not having a father.
You said the last time the blackout occurred
he was visiting his friend’s dad.
Well..
he has been pushing me
to meet his father
..and I’ve been putting it off.
It’s worth a short Andrea.
We can arrange controlled meeting.
..some security,
Evan comes for a quick visit,
and with a little luck,
..no more missing father complex.
April fifteen.
Today I got to meet my father.
His name is Jason and he’s crazy.
I hope he’ll let me call him Dad.
Dad lives here?
Not in this wind. Actually no.
If you seems a little sleepy
it’s because of the medicine, OK?
OK.
It’ll just be a moment.
It’s OK I’ll won’t bite.
You’ve seen pictures of me, right?
Uh huh. Mom says I have your smile
..and your hair.
I’ll kill you!
He’ll have to die!
It’s the only way!
Jason! No!
No!
It’s gonna be alright
it’s gonna be alright.
Come on. Let’s get him outta here.
I'm sorry Evan.
..in certain hope the resurrection to eternal life
we command our mighty God, our brother Jason.
May Lord bless him and keep him
The Lord make light to shine upon him,
..and be gracious onto him
..and give him peace.
Amen.
Come on, where is it?
I know it’s down here somewhere.
Tell me what shit, it’s so boring.
Ya, what are you looking for anyway?
Shutup loud ass.
You hold your fucking horses.
It’s here somewhere.
We should go though.
If Dad catch us smoking down here,
we’re dead.
Lets go.
I knew Dad has a blockbuster down here.
Lets blow the shit out of something.
Here you go buddy.
What dreaming man,
I’m not touching this thing.
Anyone else would piss out, and nuts for sure.
It can’t work this time buddy,
Look how small this fuse is. I’ll get killed.
Not necessary.
Here you go.
That’ll buy you two minutes, at least
Gee, thanks friend.
Oh for Chris sake Lenny you moron
just do it.
You have balls man.
Shouldn't took you long enough.
What the hell, come on!
Evan, you want to help me get him up?
Evan, get your ass back here
and help me get him up!
What happened?
Where are we?
Oh my God.
What are we going to do?
Evan, come on! Help me!
Oh my God. How could we?
Come on, lets go.
Lenny, what happened to you?
Fine, he’s going to be OK.
Everything is going to be fine.
What’s wrong with him?
Why is he not speaking?
Shock mdm.
What is it? What happened?
We were just in the wood
building a fire when Lenny freak out.
One minute he was OK and
then he just froze up. Right guys?
What happened Evan?
The truth.
I dunno, I..I don’t remember.
Something must have happened.
Something set him up.
I blanked out.
Don’t try to get your
blackout to get out of this one.
You’re not making it up?
Breath in
..and breath out
..and relax.
You are completely asleep.
Relaxed.
I want you to take me to the time when
you are in the woods with Lenny.
Think of it like a movie.
You can pause,
..rewind
..or slow down any details you wish.
Yes.
Where are you now?
I’m standing next to Kelly,
my hands are over her ears.
Are you hurting her?
No, I’m protecting her.
OK. Lets move forward in time.
What do you see?
I see a car.
Yes Evan..tell me about the car.
Go on
..nothing can hurt you
Remember, it’s only a movie.
You’re completely safe.
I can’t.
The car vanishes, all of a sudden
I’m on the ground in the woods.
The car isn’t varnished Evan.
The movie in your head is broken, that’s all.
Tell me about the car.
I can’t.
It’s coming...
Hurry Evan, hurry!
It’s coming!
Oh my God!
On the count of ten, you’re going to wake up,
..feeling your flesh,
..and everything you talked about.
Make it stop!
One..you’re feeling awake.
Two..you’re eyes are not feeling as heavy.
Five..six..come on Evan wake up! Nine..ten..
God!
What happened?
Did it work?
Thanks mom, see you later.
Wake that sad eyes off your face
before you get busted.
Did you see how Lenny’s mom
is looking at you?
Sorry.
(Sign)…alright.
Does someone tell me what happened at the mailbox?
Don’t you ever bring that shit up again
..not ever!
Let’s go.
Are you OK?
Holly shit! Look at that fat fuck!
...
Shut up baggard.
Who’s talking to you?
I’m sorry Kelly this is a really bad idea.
You don’t really remember anything that happened?
You’re so lucky.
Look, everything is going to be OK.
Lenny will be fine..you’re see.
Sorry.
It’s not your fault.
It’s Kagan called Dad and blamed
us for what happened to Lenny.
Your Dad did that?
I deserve a lot worst.
What are you talking about?
What you deserve is a better father and brother.
What they do is make you feel like shit.
You have no clue as to how beautiful you are,
do you?
What the fuck are you doing?
Buying popcop, what the fuck are you doing?
Ops.....
Stop it!
Stop hitting him!
What’s wrong with you?
Will somebody please help us?
Now OK kid..you’re outta here.
Now another story. The peaceful town of BrayerVille
was rocked this afternoon
in the wake of an horrible act of vandalism.
While the police of upstate New York believes
this could be a simple case of
act of mischief gone array
..the tragedy has definitely devastated the community.
Now this is the grisly aftermath of an powerful explosion
believed to have been caused by an unknown quantity of dynamite.
Police has no leaks, no suspects,
and no motive for the...
Good night.
We’re moving.
Even Tommy is so pissed at me.
He knows I’m moving right?
He’s acting real strange lately.
He don’t even look me at the eyes anymore.
Dart, here he comes.
Did you mom says that Lenny is OK?
It must be..I mean,
they let him out right?
Welcome home.
Though you might to have some fresh air for a change.
Tommy with you guys?
No..it’s cool.
So what did you do in there?
It’s awful! Can’t sleep cause
everybody screaming all night long.
I don’t want to go back.
Did you see that?
Ya...what’s with the smoke?
Croquette!!
What are you doing with my dog?
Look at what you make me do!?
What the hell’s wrong with you?
Kelly! Come on, please wake up!
Wake up please!
Wake up!
What don’t you fucking kiss her
you Price Charming.
How long was I out?
Kelly, what’s wrong?
ooh Croquette!!!
I’m sorry.
And time..put your pencils down and place
your blue books on my desk before you leave.
You too Mr. Nelson,
we’re all on the same time-zone here.
So how did do Evan?
I don’t know,
may get some names sorted out.
Was it Pavlov that conditioned his dog to lick his nuts?
You’re a major, wise-ass.
And how’s you project been coming?
You still planning to change
..the way we humble scientists view memory differently?
Don’t really have a choice.
Jesus, must be truly an ass.
Arlette, this is my well-mannered roommate, Evan.
Ya..
You’re the man that fuck up the grade
of a man at the anthropology final.
See you later Tombeur.
Bye.
Ah...sweet girl.
Here’s you shirt bro.
Sick fuck.
Alright man, get dressed.
You’re taking me out.
Why, you just make another mid-term?
No. Better than that!
Seven years no blackouts.
Fuck you bro, let do this.
Be gentle with me, be gentle.
Nice.
Look at that fucking guy.
Fuck out of my bar.
So which one of you have the pet worm?
Worms..pural.
Ah...that’s so gross.
Talk to him about it.
He got the fetish.
Watch it. That psychoon project
actually study how memory lost.
That’s explain for all the excitement that I had.
Ten bucks says he’ll eat it out of the floor.
Well, like to figure out how the
memory in the simple worm functions
to help me understand the complexity
of the human brain.
Let me take a shot.
What the fuck weirdo?
Well, this not your game.
Smell like a sex in here.
Yeah..Tomber has a busy day today.
You kidding. This is so big.
Yeah? Well I guess charisma and I let it go all the way.
You want a beer?
Ya.
You got any incest or scent candles or anything?
Wo..no..
Most guys just put porn books under their bed
all you got are comp books?
Yeah..they’re my journals.
Something I begin since I was seven.
Read me something.
Maybe I’ll get some fun out of this.
Here we go…
Looks like my mind refuses to believe what I’m seeing.
..hearing Croquette make those awful screams.
Just writing about it gives me the shivers.
Come on. Go on.
It was kinda like Tommy was possessed
or something.
There was a hate in his eyes and…
Are you OK?
Where am I?
What’s the hell is going on?
I can’t get it opened.
Drop it!
Or I’ll slick your mother’s throat
while she’s asleep.
I get hold of Tommy...save Croquette!
Listen to me Evan
..you listen to me good.
There is a million other sisters in the world
why do you have to fuck with mine?
It’s OK, it’s just a dream.
Didn’t feel like a dream.
Maybe because it never do.
So Gift Juan, you pass out on all your dates?
Lenny?
I got a surprise for you.
Never guess who’s here.
Hey, it’s me.
Evan
You’re working on
..a model?
Look ur..see that you’re busy so
I’ll try to make this quick.
Remember that day at the junkyard
when we were kids?
All I was hoping was you
can help me remember it.
Just some details on how
I couldn’t cut the robe.
Ya.
..that’s good.
Anything else?
Drop it or I’ll cut your mother’s throat when she’s asleep!
Jesus Christ.
It really happened.
Wow..er
Make one peek,
..and I’ll swear you be last one fucker.
The last thing I remember before the blackout
I cup my hands over Kelly’s ears.
I think I was more focused on her hands on mine
than on the mailbox
..across the street.
Maybe it went out.
Someone check it?
Yeah, you do that Lenny.
Be cool peek to be the last one fucker.
How is my sweet girl?
How is my sweet girl? You got the hic don’t you?
You want to open it?
You want to...
Oh my God!
Shit! Come on!
Fuck, Lenny come on!
Lenny come on!
Come on Lenny lets go!
Please man..fucking brutal.
Whata?
Hello?
Hello, who’s this?
Ms Kagan, it’s Evan..Trebon
I hope you know how much you upset Lenny.
Yeah..I’m..look I’m really sorry about that..
It took me over an hour to
clean up the mess you made.
Can..can I just talk to Lenny?
Don’t call here.
Mom.
I can’t help it,
I’m just so proud of you.
Dad er..
Did Jason get good grades?
He got straight As without touching the books.
It’s one area where memory never fails him.
Did he ever say like he figured out
a way to recall his lost memories?
Years after the blackout happened?
Why you asked?
No, I just figured being just a brain and all.
Looks like I would think that he would figure out
a way to remember stuff that he forgot.
Well, he was at your age,
almost exactly at your age..come to think of it.
..he said he figured out a way
he could remember his past.
I could tell if they were real memories
or just his imagination.
Then, just before he got so bad,
he..um..has to be institutionised.
He said he could...
What?
Look
What did he do?
Forget it. It’s nothing.
He was far to sick by then.
I didn’t want to be in the movie anyway.
I was cold so I want to wear my clothes.
But Mr. Miller took my shirt off..
What the fuck are you doing?
Shh..I need quiet for this.
Are you stupid or what man?
Maybe there is a reason why you repressed some pervert
who had you in his tidy-widy.
I think twice about what you are doing.
You could wake up a lot more fuck up than you are now.
I’m fuck up than I already am.
You think you know me? I don't know me!
No, it's my fault.
Can you get through one damn day
without breaking something?
Hey!
Evan!
Oh my God, it's been a long time.
How've you been?
Same know, you know..
No, I don't know.
Fill me in.
Well..go on the state now.. all's good
..my mom's good.
You want some?
No, now since I was kid.
I quit like a hundred times.
Are you walking home?
Can I walk you?
Sure.
My God.
So
..how's Tommy?
Well they kept him in the Juville for a few years, but
..now he is working over at Dell's Autobody.
That's cool.
Still live in with your Dad?
No
I pay for myself at fifteen.
Must have taken alot of courage.
Not if you remember my Dad.
Can't you just move in with your Mom?
No, she had a new family,
wasn't enough room.
...whatever.
Look, the reason why I came back is to talk to you.
To me?
Why?
Well,
..remember we were kids and
I used to have those blackouts?
Ya, of course.
Some of those memories-
they're coming back to me.
..and I just want to talk to you about just one particular.
I try to remember.
When we were kids, your Dad was making a movie
..about Robin Hood, or something...
What do you want to know Evan?
Did he...what happened at the basement?
Look, it was a long time ago.
I know.
Is that why you came all the way back here?
To ask about lots of
stupid questions about Robin Hood?
No.
I just think that something really bad might happen.
Was there a point in any of this?
Look, whatever that happened wasn't your fault.
We were kids, and there is nothing we can do
to deserve what he has done.
Shut up Evan!!
You're wasting your breath.
You can't hate yourself because
your Dad is a twisted freak.
Who are you trying to convince Evan?
You came all the way back here
to stir my shit just
..because you have a bad memory?
What? You want me to just
..cry on your shoulder and
everything is all better now?
Well fuck you Evan!
Nothing is all better OK.
Nothing ever gets better.
You know? If I were so wonderful Evan,
..why don't you call me?
Why did you leave me
here to rot?
Well, he was at your age,
almost exactly at your age..come to think of it.
..he said he figured out a way
he could remember his past.
Some dude left a message for you.
You can smoke all you want at the bathroom.
Hi Evan this is Professor Carter.
Just wondered why you didn't hand in your essay
this afternoon I was concerned.
Call me to schedule a makeup.
What did you say to my sister
you mother fucker?
Last night she cried on the phone for over an hour.
She said you came and saw her last night.
She...
She fucking kill herself last night.
She's dead.
..and so are you.
If the scar on my stomach
did'nt come out of nowhere
..maybe my father wasn't
as crazy as I thought.
If I can make scars,
do I have the power to heal them?
What about Kelly's scars?
I wan't wanting to be in the movies anyway
It was cold.
So I wanted to wear my clothes.
..but Mr Miller
..took my shirt off.
I got an idea.
Lets go down to the basement.
Looked more like a dungeon down there.
A little light here.
Hey, what did I tell you about keeping the door shut?
But I wanted to see.
See the back of my fist in two seconds
if you don't do as I tell you.
Now, and this part of the story
Robin Hood had just married Maid Mariane.
..and they have to kiss
and stuff like growups do.
So, take off you clothes Kelly.
Come on, like we take a bath.
Don't make a big deal out of it.
You too Evan.
Come on lets go, lets go!
We're making a movie here.
Puts your hands on your ears Kelly.
Which time is it?
It's time for you
to do what I tell you to do.
Wrong answer fuckbag!
This is the very moment of your reconing.
In the next thirty seconds
you're gonna open up one of two doors.
The first door,
you forever traumatise your own fresh and blood.
What's happending?
How are you doing this?
It will change your daughter
from a beautiful child into an empty shell.
..was her only trust was being
betrayed by her own sick pedophil father.
Ultimately
it will lead to her suicide.
Nice work Daddy.
Who are you?
Lets say you are being closely watched George.
Your other option is to treat Kelly like...
..say a loving father treats her daughter.
So is that OK with you Papa?
Yes.
Listen close you fuckbag.
You screw this up again,
I swear I'll castrate you.
What you need to do, is to discipline your son Tommy
cause the kid is one sadistic pop.
A last thing.
Do'nt ever touch me again.
No, I won't.
Faster, faster..
Croquette!!
I will return to look for you
Kelly I can't believe you came!
..you got that one..
Check out our new house..
Honey, are you alright?
Oh my god Evan, your bleeding!
Kelly! it's..you.
Incredible!
Thanks, go get clean up
..and come back to bed.
Where are my clothes?
These are your clothes silly.
Bathroom?
Hurry up, I want to get a picky before school starts.
What?
Unbelievable!
I did'nt know you can get
so fascinated over a nose bled?
Sorry, eh...I didn't see you.
Wait.. you're the girl
..with those guys that throw popcorn at Tumeour.
What?
..and your name is Gwen!
I know you.
Seriously Evan, we have a go.
Hi.
Don't freak out if I ask you this but
..did you remember the day your father
got that video camera?
Ya..em..
I think he had it like the first day,
and then he gave it away.
Why would that freak me out?
I don't know.
It's being weird.
You are such a goofese.
So I see you tonight.
OK.
Come on mom.
Andrea, Evan and Chuck aren't home right now.
You know what to do.
Hey mom, it's me...n Chuck.
I just called to say hi
I may call back.
Hey Tumeour you know what time is now?
What's the matter, you lost your Rolex?
Fuck you frag boy!
Remember everyone, there is only two more weeks
until your psy project is due.
About the essay that I missed last week
..you're still OK with the extension right?
And you are?
Evan...Treborn
The answer is no Mr Treborn, please take your seat,
the exam is about to begin.
Settle down everyone.
The exam will begin in 1 minute.
Stop it asshole,
you got started on that shit.
Evan you're hesterical.
Did you study for this?
We'll find out.
Me neither.
Holy shit. Are these the answers?
Damn Evan, keep it on the down!
I want to do something special
for Kelly tomorrow night.
So if I said I need some help from you,
we're brothers.
that didn't bother me.
..it's a pleasure to do it!
Ya...
You may begin now!
That was so good.
Oh my God.
Where did you learn that new trick?
Why? It wasn't weird, was it?
Ya if you call multiple orgasm is weird.
Hello?
Fuck em.
What do you think it is about us
I mean
..why did you sneak out
to visit me after I moved away.
Because I missed you.
Why? You think my Dad
might stop me from seeing you?
What you're going to do?
Oh my god, my toes are numb.
Do you think that
we'll be together forever?
That is the plan, isn't it?
Hell over high water?
Ya.
Ya. I was just making sure.
Ya..that's the plan!
Alright.
All you rushes know what you need to do for me.
Pleaches,
..we're pleaches, sir.
..brother Evan
..er..sir.
Are you kidding me?
What? What did you say me?
Give me the Greek alphabet.
Give it to me!
Alpha, silly, gamma, delta,.....
........sir!!
..maybe that's what it is!
Do'nt fucking look at me.
Look down!
Alright..em..
you pleaches guys know what to do for me and
you guys go take a shower,
and if anyone gives you any trouble
..you tell em I said it was OK.
What?
Shower up bitch!
I do'nt understand
where are you taking me?
I am not telling you.
Oh my God!
Wow.. it's beautiful.
Go on, sit down.
Thank you.
Why are you doing this for me?
When I woke up this morning
..I saw your smile.
..that smile.
And I knew
..that I want to spend the rest of my life
..with you.
I've been looking all over for you man.
Someone trashed your car!