I've been born-again
my whole life.
Accepting Jesus into your heart
and getting saved is a big decision...
... especially for a three-year-old.
My faith taught me that everything
was a part of God's plan.
Mom said that he even had a reason
for taking my father to heaven.
She explained
that Daddy was with the angels.
Well, I wanted
to be with the angels, too.
But God had other plans.
Jesus became
the center of my life.
I still don't think
he's supposed to be white.
- I was watching this thing on television--
- Of course, he's white.
Gosh. Sometimes I think
my brother's retarded, too.
No, your brother's not retarded.
I was a member in good standing
of the Christian Jewels.
It's sort of like
a girl gang for Jesus.
Don't kill your baby!
Lillian Cummings.
My mom was finally named
the number one
Christian interior decorator
for the entire region.
And in spite of living
in what the Bible calls "the end times,"
my future was looking bright.
I had the perfect Christian boyfriend.
And I was about to be a senior
at a really good Christian school.
Two weeks before
summer vacation ended,
everything changed.
My boyfriend and I
played this game
of telling each other
secrets underwater.
It's lame, I know.
But this wasn 't exactly
the MTV Beach House.
Okay, now my turn.
Okay, ready?
Mary!
Maybe it was
because I was drowning,
or the shock
of Dean's confession...
... but at that moment,
I had a vision.
Dean needs you now.
You must do all you can
to help him.
It's just a little bump, Mom.
I'm totally fine.
Okay, all right.
Mom was away at the Christian
Community Leader's Convention
in Orlando with Pastor Skip--
the principal of my school.
- Honey?
- Mom.
You didn't tell me
Pastor Skip was so nice.
Yeah, everybody loves him.
We've been talking about setting up
our own fellowship programs
when I get back to Cherry Hill.
- I have to go.
- Come and get it.
Come and get it.
Love you.
- I love you, too.
- Bye.
What's shaking, Skip?
How could my boyfriend be gay?
He's, like,
the best Christian I know.
He's an athlete who's
constantly strengthening himself--
physically, creatively,
and spiritually for the Lord.
Thank you, Jesus.
Why had he been stricken
with such a spiritually toxic affliction?
I figured I needed to take
the most direct approach to saving him.
I mean,
it was Christ's will and all.
Jesus spoke to you?
In person?
He trusts me.
Okay? You're just gonna
have to trust me, too.
- Just kiss me, okay?
- Okay.
Dean and I worked diligently
on his problem
for the rest of the summer.
Anything yet?
Now?
Are you sure this isn't a sin?
I was pretty sure
what we were doing wasn't a sin,
but not sure enough
to give Dean what he really needed.
I needed spiritual guidance
or a sign or something, and quick.
Hilary Faye seemed to have
a spiritual solution for every problem.
Christian girls have got to know
how to protect themselves.
I mean, sure, Jesus could restore
my physical and spiritual virginity,
especially if I lost it
to some rapist, but...
who wants that?
I'm saving myself until marriage,
and I'll use force if necessary.
What's all that about
restoring your virginity?
I mean, physically,
you're a virgin once.
Yeah, and it's not about reversing
the violation of your blessed womb.
It's about Jesus
granting you a virginal heart.
That way, you're pure again.
Do it.
My next move was clear.
Nice.
You're getting the hang of it.
How are you doing?
What's going on?
Sure, it was a radical step,
but why else had Jesus
directed me to the gun range?
Thank you, Jesus.
Having asked Jesus to restore
my emotional and spiritual virginity
in exchange for curing Dean,
I started my senior year
with all of that behind me.
This new van is amazing.
Thanks.
It's official.
The Christian Jewels--
I bought one for everybody.
Pin it on.
I wanna see it.
It's terrific, Hilary Faye.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Hi, Roland.
How was your summer?
- What?
- Your summer, how was it?
Well, I went rollerblading,
water-skiing, learned to kickbox.
You know, the usual.
Why do you have to make people feel so
awkward about your differently-abledness?
I'm sorry, I really don't know
what's gotten into him.
Here's the latest from Godflight.
I love these guys.
They are totally
Jesus-centric and gorgeous.
Veronica was
adopted by her parents
when they were
missionaries in Vietnam.
Hilary Faye sees her
as an example of God's will
triumphing over
a savage, godless nation.
So what do you think
of the new ride?
You're so lucky, Hilary Faye.
Yeah, I could've had
a Lexus gold edition, you know.
Roland is blessed
with such a thoughtful sister.
In countries like China, Hilary Faye
probably would've been killed at birth.
And then where
would you be, Roland?
China.
Welcome.
You're one of us now.
- What?!
- Come on, pin it on.
You guys, I'm not gonna have
any time to warm up now.
- You will.
- Where's Dean?
He knows I have to sing
at assembly this morning.
He's coming.
Can you go check?
Move him along a little bit?
- Yeah.
- Thank you.
Not a problem.
Is Dean ready?
I...
I found this
under Dean's bed last night.
He's on his way
to Mercy House this morning.
He could be gone a long time.
We thought you should know.
But...
I'm so sorry, Mary.
Let's go.
Is he coming out, or not?
Not.
Mercy House
is a Christian treatment facility
where they deal with
everything from drug abuse,
to alcoholism, to de-gayification,
and unwed mothers.
I need to tell you guys something.
What? It wasn't like it was
some kind of secret.
The guy was like
a one-man gay pride parade.
You know, we've never
had a gay at American Eagle.
We're not gonna
tell anyone, okay?
Sure.
Hilary Faye.
- You promised me.
- Yeah, that's fine.
What if you had married him?
The gayness would be
passed on to your children.
Cassandra Edelstein was the only
Jewish to ever attend American Eagles.
She transferred in last year
amid rumors that she was a stripper.
Everyone wanted to get her saved,
especially Hilary Faye.
Hi, Cass.
Welcome back.
Smoking isn't just bad for you,
it's bad for all of us.
Secondhand smoke kills.
I'm counting on it.
Oh, my gosh!
Hilary Faye, are you okay?!
I bet she doesn't even have
a handicap permit for her car.
And I'm right!
Oh, my God.
Come on. We don't want to be late
for homeroom, okay?
Let's get to class.
- Hi, Matt.
- Hey.
- I'm a Jewel.
- Oh, it's awesome!
Hey, guys, guess what?
I think Jesus appeared to me
in my fish tank, and he--
It's okay, it didn't move.
The tank's kinda dirty
and most of the fish are dead,
but my mom said if you guys--
Okay, Tia, thanks.
- I'll see you after class.
- I'll talk to you guys after class.
I hope you all
let God use you as a vessel
for his divine plan this summer.
I'm sure by now most of you
have noticed the beautiful billboard
designed and painted
by our own Hilary Faye
and donated by her father.
Thank you.
Mary helped.
And speaking of new additions, class.
I'd like you to welcome Patrick Wheeler.
Most of the boys in school looked
like NASA employees, not Patrick.
There had to be a catch.
Patrick is Pastor Skip's son.
He's been in South America
doing missionary work with his mother,
and this summer
he just completed a world tour
with the Christian
skateboard association.
Nice.
Out there hitting the board
for the Lord?
Is nothing sacred to you people?
Before this morning's assembly,
why don't we catch up
on what everyone did this summer?
Mary, let's start with you.
All right, everyone.
put your hands together
for the Christian Jewels!
Some of the words to myself
would make the clouds disappear
If you were gone,
what would I become?
You're so good to me
I mean that.
Oh, clarity
Dear God
A little piece of Heaven
in my world
So, I figured they would've
sent you to a special school by now.
This is a special school.
No.
I fell out of a tree
when I was nine.
Hilary Faye found me.
She calls it
the miracle that saved my life.
The miracle
you could've used
would've been not falling out
of the tree in the first place.
Sorry.
Is that why
you're behind a year?
Yeah.
We should get back inside.
Nice.
- You want a push?
- Thanks.
If you stare at my ass again.
I will push you off a cliff.
Thank you, Jesus.
Amen.
All right!
Welcome to
the first assembly of the year!
Give it up.
The Lord Jesus is in the house!
Let's get our Christ on.
Let's kick it Jesus style.
Y'all wanna walk
with the ultimate rebel, right?
The ultimate CEO.
The biggest celebrity of them all.
Who's down with G.O.D?
I'm down with the G.O.D!
That's right!
Jesus Rules!
Let's pray.
Lord, we're gonna have
an awesome school year
here at American Eagles
Christian High...
I know I'm not supposed
to ask for specifics, Lord,
like when I prayed for an expensive car
and got the handicapper van instead,
but I want this to be
the best year ever.
And between you and me...
... I think you'll agree
I totally deserve it.
Thank you for sparing me from
the eternal hellfires of damnation.
I'm sorry I let that Promise Maker guy
touch me in the rectory.
Daddy still hasn 't stopped drinking,
but I know you're working on it.
And I really want to be a Jewel.
I wonder if rollerboy's paralyzed
everywhere below the waist.
Oh, yeah, she digs me.
Please, Jesus,
don 't let Dad humiliate me.
Those Jesus freaks
are on to something.
Especially in front of her.
About Dean and I,
I thought we had a deal.
Why is he at Mercy House?
You did restore me, right?
And keep our president safe.
Amen.
Now, who wants to come down here
and give their heart to the Lord?
Who wants to start the year
off right and get saved?
A lot of temptations
over the summer.
I bet some of you folks
backslid just a little.
Who wants to recommit
themselves to the Lord?
There we go!
All right.
Praise Jesus.
Fantastic.
Come on down.
- There you go.
- Awesome.
Welcome home.
Welcome home to Jesus.
Welcome to his home.
Jesus loves you.
Praise Jesus.
Accept him into your heart.
Hallelujah!
Bear witness.
She's speaking
God's love language, folks!
Oh, my God.
The Jew girl's speaking in tongues!
She's gonna show her boobs.
Thank you, Jesus.
She is!
She's gonna show her boobs!
Mahh possie is a hot pooosie!
Mahh hotta pooosie!
She's saying
she's got a hot--
After that, Cassandra's status
went from a cautionary tale to legend.
It seemed like there was no act
too vulgar to get her expelled.
The more she acted out...
... the more Hilary Faye
wanted to get her saved.
I am totally glad she wasn't expelled.
Her actions are such a cry for help.
She may not know this now,
but she is like--
she's like that much closer
to accepting Jesus in her heart, right?
Seriously, she could be some poor savage
in some remote jungle somewhere
who will never know the Lord
and who will never go to Heaven, ever.
I think that's why God has missionaries
like Patrick to spread his word.
Yeah.
What's up, guys?
- You're Mary, right?
- Here's your board.
- Thanks, bro.
- Yeah.
You played the keyboard
during assembly. That was really cool.
- Thanks.
- Isn't she great?
She knows just how to compliment my
vocal stylings without overpowering them.
We were just talking about
all your missionary work, it's so great.
So, like, what part of the world
has the worst heathens?
'Cause I'm so interested in that.
Honestly, I couldn't say.
Mostly, I just stuck to skating.
No, but how many of them
did you actually save, do you think?
Guys, I totally scored
some free stuff for you.
Thank you, Tia.
Piss off, asshole!
And another thing--
no more muffin for you.
The muffin shop is closed!
- Come on.
- Oh, my gosh.
She is in worse shape
than I ever could have imagined, right?
We need to show her
just how cool we Christians can be.
- Totally.
- Let's start the laughing.
Now!
Cass, come join us.
We're just--
Do you wanna go wait in the van again?
Do you know these are new pants!
You're handicapped,
but get it together.
Hey, Roland,
how about we get outta here.
and you can give me
a little spin in that thing?
Release his parking brake,
Hilary "Fake."
You smell like Tia's dad.
Have you been drinking?
Come on. Careful.
I'm having a vision
of the Virgin Mary.
Cassandra, are you all right?
What she needs to do
is accept Jesus into her heart.
I think what she needs
is a ride home.
- I'll take her.
- I'll help you, then.
Come on, Cassandra.
No, no, let go of the pizza.
Get off of me!
Helping Patrick
haul Cassandra out of the mall
was like the most perfect
God-centered moment.
You really learn a lot about a boy
when you're servicing the Lord.
Hilary Faye, I can see your pad.
- I can see a little bit of it right--
- Quit it!
Slowly raise up through the knees,
still bent at the waist, and roll to standing.
Good.
And twist and hold.
Come on.
Keep holding.
I know what you're looking at, Mary.
And Jesus does, too,
After a threatening letter
from the State Board of Education,
they finally broke down
and created a Sex-Ed class.
A little too late, I might add.
So, it's all about
populating the planet.
And good Christians don't
get jiggy with it until they're married.
Lights.
Yes, Mary.
Is it possible Jesus might need us
to do his will by, you know, not waiting?
Of course,
he wants us to wait.
I don't think I get
what you mean, Mary.
I don't know.
Which variety of bass
is not indigenous to North America?
- B--small mouth.
- Peacock.
- Large mouth?
- I'm sorry. That's incorrect.
This religious figure
was best known
for offering to God
a sacrifice of one of his sons.
- Moses!
- Brenda.
I--I'm guessing Abraham?
- That's correct.
- Oh, really?
- Congratulations. Well done.
- I hate this show.
Coming up on Lifetime,
Valerie Bertinelli
stars in "Bitter Harvest"--
a sensitive portrayal
of one woman's struggle with cancer.
This looks good.
There was a feeling
of twilight in the air...
... all honeydew and lilac.
God wasn't just
smiling down on me...
... he was jumping up and cheering.
And then, well...
... I thought I was pregnant.
I'd been throwing up every morning
and hadn't had my period
in two months.
So I took a home pregnancy test.
What happened?
I found out I wasn't pregnant.
It was the cancer.
She found all that out
from a home pregnancy test?
Valerie's struggles made me realize
that my problems weren't so bad.
Dean was getting help,
and I still had the Jewels.
I was gonna be okay.
- You work here, too?
- Yeah, I'm saving up for a car.
When I get one I can
come pick you up and stuff.
You okay?
Yeah, it's just really hot in here.
- I'll see you later.
- Promise?
Please let it be cancer.
The test mentions something
about a possible false positive.
Do you have anything
later on Monday?
3:00?
No, no, I can make that.
I have my leadership meeting
tonight after work.
- You're not wearing that, are you?
- Why not?
You just can't, Mom.
You're right,
it's too hot for a sweater.
- I'll see you later.
- Bye, hon.
Hey, Mary.
Sorry to hear about Dean's faggotry.
- What?!
- See you at P, circle?
Can I talk to you?
What's going on?
You promised me.
It's hard.
But I think this is the only way
we can actually help Dean.
Don't you think?
Come on.
You're not born a gay.
You're born-again.
I don't know
what I think anymore.
I've gotta go.
Wait. Don't you need me
to give you a ride home?
Not today, Hil.
Okay. Well, tonight
at the prayer circle meeting then, okay?
Prayer circle meeting
at my house at 7:00.
I'm conducting it
for Mary's gay boyfriend Dean.
What?
You know where a guy
can get some smokes?
What's the matter?
Scared to be seen
in public with a stripper?
No. Scared of being seen
with a cripple?
I've been seen with worse.
Hilary Faye's gonna freak out
when I'm not there waiting for her.
Who cares?
It's just that I don't
get out much on my own.
- I'm not really a stripper.
- I'm not really a Christian.
So, how did you
end up at American Eagle?
I mean, you're Jewish, right?
Well, after I got expelled
from my last school,
it was either here
or home schooling.
I figured I could handle
these freaks better than my parents.
Lucky me.
- Are you playing footsies with me?
- Wheelies.
Hey, isn't that...
What is she doing downtown?
There's only one reason Christian girls
come down to the Planned Parenthood.
- She's planting a pipe bomb?!
- Okay, two reasons.
With Dean?!
I think there's a better chance
of that pipe bomb.
I... I should get home.
Yeah, you should.
Shit.
Fuck.
Goddamn.
And we pray for all the perverts, Lord,
but especially for Dean,
whom at this time,
just hasn't found the right girl.
We join together and beg you
to rid him of his unnatural perversions.
May you lead him
out of the darkness, Lord,
and into your divine light.
Amen.
That was good.
That felt really nice.
Thank you so much
for that good prayer.
- Hi, Mary.
- Hi.
How are you? So good to see you.
We've been waiting for you.
We were just finishing up, so if you
have anything else you wanna add.
Jesus is still listening.
Jesus isn't listening, Hilary Faye.
I did everything I could to save Dean,
and he still ended up at Mercy House.
Let's take a breath--
What can they say and do
that I haven't already done!
Don't embarrass me!
We have to pray about this.
Prayer works!
- It's been medically proven.
- Just lay off of me, Hilary!
Wait a second.
Give me that.
You could pollute the Jewels
and everything we stand for.
And I can't have that.
Good-bye.
I hope you know
that this is all a waste of time.
I just got off the phone
with Hilary Faye.
Wow! Can she be
an uppity whootie-who.
What's the matter?
Nothing.
Come on.
Why do you think Dean's parents
sent him away so fast?
They probably thought
they couldn't handle it by themselves.
Having a child
is like owning a car--
I can change the oil,
fill the gas tank,
take it to a carwash,
but if the carburetor broke.
I wouldn't have a clue
as to how to fix it.
What are you saying--you'd actually
send me to a place like Mercy House?
Mary, please don't tell me
you're a lesbian.
Should I be worried about you?
I don't need to
worry about you... do I?
No.
My mom just compared me to a car,
so me having a baby
definitely falls into the category
of things she couldn't handle.
A week after prom
and two days after I turned eighteen,
I was going to join
the unwed mothers club.
Dean, I'm really sorry
about what we did.
I mean, we should've
at least used protection.
But you're the only person
I've been with.
- No, I know that.
- I don't have anything.
It's just--
Dean, I really...
I need to tell you something.
- Hey, governor.
- Hi, Mitch.
- Mitch?
- He's my roommate.
He's here for
the same reason as me.
He even ran away from home
to San Francisco.
He's like the worst one here.
- You better be careful.
- I'm gonna beat this.
According to the brochure,
hundreds of others have.
What were you gonna say?
Nothing. Just...
I wanted to know
if you'd be out by prom.
- Wild horses couldn't stop me.
- Mercy House residents--
I gotta go. We're doing
a Christian haunted house.
Happy Halloween.
Let's go, let's go.
Let's pick it up.
Nice costume.
Thanks.
'Cause we have the same...
If you don't let go, I'll tell everybody
you touch me inappropriately
while helping me in the bathroom.
- Is that supposed to embarrass me?
- I'm tired of you pushing me around.
Well, maybe I'm tired
of pushing you around.
He's all yours!
Thanks.
Call me later, okay?
He doesn't appreciate
one thing you do for him.
Without the strength and love
that Jesus provides me,
do you really think Cassandra's
gonna be able to take care of him?
No way.
She's just gonna
end up hurting him.
By the look of the bruises
on his neck, she already has.
Tia, please.
What are you supposed to be?
A roller skate.
I've got something to show you.
You do?
You didn't just do this
for the parking permit, did you?
Pretty much.
In the meantime,
I was trying to find a new religion
or a new God or whatever,
but to tell you the truth,
they were all kind of freaking me out.
I mean, sure, they can't all be right,
but they can 't all be wrong, right?
You know, the whole
crystal thing is so felt up.
Don't you have a church
to desecrate or something?
Roland and I saw you
sneaking out of the clinic.
Kudos on the Bono shades,
by the way.
I was distributing pamphlets.
I was trying to prevent
girls like you from making a mistake.
Thank you.
After we win
the costume contest,
we'll distribute religious tracts
to the kids instead of candy.
- Good one.
- That's awesome.
Hey, ladies.
- Sorry. You got a second?
- Yeah.
Listen, I'm concerned about Mary.
Something's going on.
Yeah, me too.
Well, she's part of your posse,
and I think that you could help her.
I'm gonna need you to be a warrior
out on the front lines for Jesus.
You mean like shoot her?
No, no, I was thinking
of something a little less gangsta.
I need someone who's spiritually armed
to help guide her back to her faith,
to love and care
that only Jesus can supply.
- You down with that?
- Yeah, I'm down with that.
She's pretty vulnerable right now,
so I'm gonna need you to be extra gentle.
- Hurry! Hurry! Come on!
- I'm going! I'm going!
- Get her!
- Come on, Tia!
Stuff her in here!
Hurry up! Hurry Up!
In the name of Jesus Christ.
I command you,
leave the body of this servant of God.
You're performing
an exorcism on me?! Get off me!
Where are you going?
Get back here!
We've gotta
get rid of the evil in you.
- It's God's will!
- God's will?
- Christ died for your sins!
- Okay, wait a second.
Are you not gonna accept
our intervention?
You mean kidnapping? No!
You are backsliding
into the flames of hell.
You've become a magnet for sin.
We've all witnessed it.
Sure.
Veronica acting all pure.
What about last spring break
at the Promise Maker's rally?
You are making accusations
as we're trying to save your soul?
Mary, turn away from Satan.
Jesus--he loves you.
You don't know
the first thing about love.
I am filled with Christ's love!
You are just jealous
of my success in the Lord.
This is not a weapon, you idiot.
What, did they send you to
strap me on the back of your scooter?
Scooter?
Mary, this is a Vespa.
And I don't know
what you're talking about. Hop on.
I'd rather walk.
Suit yourself.
She actually tried to exorcise you?
Yeah.
That was nice of her, I guess.
The way things have been going.
I probably should've let her.
Listen, Mary...
I want you to know that I don't think
Dean's sick or anything.
- Yeah, right.
- No, really.
Mercy House doesn't really exist
for the people who get sent there.
It exists more for the people
who do the sending.
So why were you at Hilary Faye's
when she was praying for Dean?
Honestly...
I thought you'd be there.
Well, thank you
for the ride, Patrick.
Any time.
Do you wanna go out sometime?
What--are you gonna
take me out on your scooter?
Come on.
I'm, like, totally adorable.
Besides,
it would drive Hilary Faye crazy.
I can't.
I'm not dating right now.
What about tomorrow night?
Will you be dating then?
Good night, Patrick.
Thank you so much.
You guys are so sweet.
You know what?
We need to...
We need to take a moment
and think about those people
who aren't as fortunate
to have the body of Christ
in their life right now.
So, let's...
let's pray for Mary.
Lucky for me, at our school,
teen pregnancy was about as common
as the flesh-eating virus.
No one really
seemed to catch on.
All right, students...
Except Cassandra.
... and we're going to continue
with the Beatitudes.
- Let's--Mary?
- Could I have a bathroom pass?
- Sure.
- Thanks.
Blessed are those who are persecuted
because of righteousness,
for theirs is the kingdom of Heaven.
Blessed are you when people
insult you, persecute you,
and falsely say all kinds of evil
against you because of me.
Excuse me.
It doesn't bother you to have
people smoking around you?
It's so bad for the baby.
I'm not pregnant, okay?
So, what's your plan?
It's too late for the big A.
You look like a smuggler.
I know somewhere you could sell it.
I'm not gonna sell my...
It's Dean's, isn't it?
You can't do this on your own.
Yes, I can.
No, you can't.
I thought I was helping him.
I thought it was...
... what Jesus wanted me to do.
That's pretty stupid, right?
It's not stupid.
- Yes, it is.
- It's not stupid.
If you're interested.
I know some people
who would pay a lot of money
to take naked pictures of you
in a family way.
Oh, yeah?
How much money?
You need to get out of here.
Are we cutting?
- Should you be driving?
- What is it with you people?
You don't think
we can do anything, do you?
No, I mean, you don't have
your license, do you?
No.
Here. Years of shoplifting
have taught me how to hide a bundle.
Did I ever tell you about the time
that I shoplifted a frozen turkey
out of a Piggly Wiggly wearing only
a tube top and some daisy dukes?
I can't pay for all of this.
Compliments of Hilary Faye.
So, Patrick asked you out,
and you turned him down?
The boy is a tomcat,
even if he is a big J.C. freak.
And, double-plus bonus.
I'm pretty sure he's not a mo.
He's Pastor Skip's son,
and I'm about to pop a baby out.
I should tell Patrick to act gay.
Maybe then he'd get a little action.
Nice, very nice.
Does it ever bother you
that he can't walk?
He can't walk?!
No, I mean
it must be tricky, that's all.
I don't care.
- He gets me, and I get him.
- Cool.
- Hello, ladies.
- Hello.
Check this out.
I got a candy bar
and a whole nickel.
Oh, Jesus.
Don't look now, but bitch face
is here with your boyfriend.
Hey, guys.
Merry Christmas.
What's wrong with her?
It's nothing.
I just get this really left-out feeling
around Christmas time, you know?
Jewish.
Well, if you decided
to accept Christ into your heart,
then you and your people
could join in on the fun, too.
We should go.
Bye, guys.
- Wait!
- What?
- You're right.
- I am?
I wanna join in on the fun.
I don't want
a Hanukkah bush this year.
I want a Christmas tree.
- You're kidding me again, right?
- I wanna get saved.
I want a relationship
with Jesus Christ, for real.
- Are you serious?
- Yes.
Okay. This is gonna
be pretty intense, Patrick.
I don't have all of
my equipment with me, but...
Okay, sit down.
First of all. we need to have you
confess all of your sins out loud.
Well, there's all the swears.
I mean, I have
a pretty goddamn dirty mouth.
And then there's the sex.
I mean, are we counting oral?
So, Christmas shopping
with Hilary Faye?
No, no, I just
ran into her here, honestly.
She's helping me pick out
some last-minute gifts.
- Come here. Sorry.
- What are you doing, Patrick?
I just wanna see what's in here.
- But--
- No, no, come on.
- We're not allowed...
- Just for a second.
- I don't think we should be in here.
- Yes, we should definitely be in here.
It's incredible.
I like you, Mary.
I really do.
Why?
You're beautiful.
And you speak for yourself.
God gave us all free will,
and that day
at Hilary Faye's prayer circle,
you weren't afraid to use it.
You inspired me.
You amaze me, Mary.
This is a bad idea.
I knew it.
- Wait a minute.
- You're not my type, Patrick.
Why?
Why not?
I'm sorry.
Mary, wait.
Thanks.
So, I duct taped a piece of rotten bacon
inside Hilary Faye's locker.
That's disgusting.
She made me listen to
the entire Elms CD on her iPOD.
I didn't ask you to get saved.
Anyway, it's not a big deal.
Last year I got saved
so I could go on a ski trip.
Oh, my God!
How do you feel?
I'm a whole new girl, Hay Faye.
I told you!
How great is Jesus?
About that, I've decided
to devote my life to Satan instead.
Thanks, though!
What?
Who beefed?
She was found to be pregnant
through the Holy Spirit.
When he had contemplated this,
an angel of the Lord
appeared to him in a dream
and said, "Joseph, son of David,
"do not be afraid
to take Mary as your wife
"because the child conceived in her
is from the Holy Spirit.
Behold, a virgin shall conceive
and bear a son."
I know this is,
like, totally wrong,
but don't you ever wonder
if she made the whole thing up?
I mean, you have to admit
it's a good one.
It's not like anyone could use
virgin birth as an excuse again.
I don't really think she made it up,
but I could understand
why a girl would.
Quit being so stingy.
What? They're my
Valentine's Day chocolates.
Hilary Faye, you bought them
for yourself, so it doesn't count.
You still have that?
I haven't decided
if I wanna give it to him yet.
Well, you better decide fast.
Happy Valentine's Day.
- Thank you.
- I made it myself.
It's a dumb idea anyway.
Mary's been going through
a lot of changes this year, and...
a relationship is the last thing
she needs right now.
Yeah, you're
the relationship expert.
You and Mom
don't even talk any more.
That's because your mom
has her missionary position,
and I have my responsibilities
running the school, and--
Mom told me
everything this summer.
Why didn't you just get divorced
when she wanted to?
Because divorce
is not part of God's plan.
Dad, you need to think of a new plan.
I thought you were
at your meeting with Pastor Skip.
It got cancelled.
Again?
That's, like, three times this week?
Four.
Well, do you wanna
talk about it?
I think this one's
between me and Jesus.
But do you wanna talk?
No.
I keep trying to remind myself
that when Jesus shuts a door,
he opens a window.
Yeah, so we have something
we can jump out of.
- Hello.
- Hey, it's me.
I'm trying to get the board to okay
this new youth outreach program--
you get the kids into the church
via rock music concerts.
One of the board members says,
"Hey, I can't tell the difference
between Christian rock
and secular rock anymore."
And I said, "Dude, exactly."
You get their attention, and then
you hit them with the message,
and boom,
you've saved another soul.
- Skip.
- What?
I don't care.
- You don't care?
- I've missed you.
I've missed our meetings.
I feel good when I'm with you.
I think you feel good, too.
I've missed you, too, yeah.
I wonder why God would give us
these feelings of happiness,
if what we're doing is wrong.
What are we doing, Lillian?
We haven't done anything
to be ashamed of, Skip.
Is this how people
turn away from Christ's teachings?
I mean, I...
All the...
all the bible study I've done,
all the preaching
I've done to the kids, and...
... all the prayers
for forgiveness I've prayed, and...
All I can think about is...
... kissing you.
I want--
I want to kiss you.
Then kiss me.
By Easter, it seemed Jesus
had answered my mom's prayers,
and she was as happy as she was
when she first got back from Orlando.
I'm probably gonna be late tonight
'cause I have my meeting.
I know. What, are you
meeting twice a week now?
Or petrol, you could do petrol.
Pastor Skip suggested Patrick take
more interest in school activities.
He said that by focusing
his energies on the Lord,
he would have less time
to think about dating.
Or I should say, he would have
less time to think about dating me.
Now, that's what I call
being hung on a cross.
Patrick and I and everyone--
we're gonna go grab some food.
- If you guys wanna come, that'd be cool.
- We're going to DQ.
So we can watch Hilary Faye
try and get into your Easter basket?
No, thanks.
Cassandra, it's not too late to achieve
a personal relationship with Jesus Christ.
Eternal damnation's
not fit for anyone, not even you.
- Right?
- Good one.
I should kick your fat,
Christian ass right now.
Really? Do you know
that I could get you expelled
for that type of language, Edelstein?
- And I'm not even fat, okay?!
- Your head is fat!
And your ass is fat!
- Whatever!
- It's like she's retarded!
I'm two months away from getting
outta here without anyone knowing.
Just... it's hard,
but cool it, okay?
Next time,
the bitch is going down.
I'm sorry.
I wanna show you something.
It's a sonogram I took a while ago.
I'm having a little girl.
You sure you're not having
a sea monkey?
- Yeah.
- She's beautiful.
You think it's safe
to keep this in your locker?
- Safer than at home.
- Let's go.
I don't really get how someone
so pretty can be so... ugly.
She wasn't always pretty.
My parents didn't want two handicapped
kids, and she was the easy fix.
What do you mean
"handicapped?"
Before we moved to Cherry Hill,
before the fat camps
and Tetracycline,
her outside matched her inside.
Oh, my God.
- Just make sure you put this back.
- I'll take care of it tonight.
- What are you doing with that?
- Nothing.
Well, well, well.
If it isn't the heathens.
Burn in hell,
you narrow-minded, tacky-ass bitch.
you narrow-minded--
- She doesn't mean it.
- Yes, I do!
You're gonna be expelled for sure
for threatening me!
Pastor Skip put us on work detail
for Hilary Faye's prom committee.
You better be wearing
underpants this time.
A particularly cruel punishment.
No, seriously, move it higher.
- Higher!
- You're doing a great job.
It's looking really phat.
I'm so glad.
Hey, Mary,
you need some help?
- Sure, thanks.
- I'll come to you.
So, listen, I was wondering,
what are you doing the night of prom?
Why?
Are you asking me to prom?
Maybe.
- Okay.
- Okay?
Yeah, okay,
I'll go with you.
As friends.
Okay, as friends.
I thought you were gonna
ask Patrick to the prom.
Tia, would you just shut up?
Do you wanna go back to being
invisible girl with bad hair?
That could easily happen.
Just don't ask stupid questions!
Did you take care of business?
Now, where are you going?
You can tacky-up prom
on your own, because I quit.
Oh, my gosh.
You can't quit.
Watch me.
Watch me walking away.
Watch me
walking away from Jesus.
What?!
Yes, this is she.
Who is this?
Are you serious?
Thank you so much.
Godflight has agreed to perform
at our prom! Can you believe that?!
Prayer works for everything!
I told you.
- Oh, my gosh.
- I'm so excited.
Now she's never gonna shut up.
Give her about ten minutes.
Turn them off!
Turn them off now, please!
Turn them...
What?
It's not fair.
I am trying to be a good Christian
and a living example of Christ's love,
and I have done nothing
but bust my buns for those sinners.
And you know that Cassandra
and Mary are behind this.
Do you have proof?
I gave you proof before,
and you did not do one thing about it.
Those who did this will not escape
the eyes of God, Hilary Faye.
Please, Lord, don't leave me alone.
They need to know
that what they've done is wrong.
Please, Lord, please.
Just tell me what I need to do.
Listen, by the end of the week
we're out of here.
- She can't do anything.
- No, I know.
What's going on?
Oh, my God.
- Somebody call the police.
- Can you believe it?
No way.
This is screwed up.
Oh, my God.
Holy crap!
- That's sad.
- Turn away. Turn away.
All right. Everybody,
let's get to our classes, please.
- You two come in with me.
- What?
Unacceptable.
I can't even concentrate today.
Get to class, ladies. Go on.
What?!
That's not mine!
- Pastor Skip.
- Anything else?
No, nothing more.
What is that?
- Someone get the nurse!
- Just hang on.
I can't believe
we were friends with her.
You have everything,
Hilary Faye.
What are you afraid of?
So you offered up
your virginity to save Dean?
Because Jesus told you to?
- Anything else?
- No.
Can I have a word with you?
What's the matter, Skip?
You didn't know
that she was pregnant?
I thought she was stress eating,
I didn't want her to get a complex.
You are so blinded by this...
that you can't even see it.
Let me spell it out to you.
God is punishing us for our sin
by getting our attention through Mary.
That doesn't even make sense.
And the longer we lived in sin,
the worse things got for her.
And what's worse is we're not
spiritually right with the Lord,
and we are not fit to help her.
Dean has been here
for almost a year, okay?
They can help her.
I wanna think about it.
If you're not gonna send her
to get the help she needs.
I can't see you any more.
Cassandra, wait!
He expelled me!
Can you believe that?!
And the one time
I didn't do anything.
Well, I'll go with you.
I can't deal with this right now,
I have to go.
Wait!
I don't have a ride.
Please help me find him.
You know where a girl
can get some smokes?
You never fold things.
Well, I'm folding now.
I'm not going to Mercy House.
We agreed
that this is for the best.
We?!
Who's we?
Pastor Skip said this child needs
to be raised by a mother and a father.
So I don't even get a say in this?
You're not prepared
to raise this child by yourself!
Something like this could
ruin the rest of your life.
So, what,
did I ruin yours, Mom?
Don't talk like that.
It looks so perfect.
Just like the picture that I brought in.
Thank you.
Crap.
I'm sorry, but it's been declined.
Do you have another card?
I knew it.
Listen, I'm really sorry
I ditched you yesterday.
Look, this year has been great.
Before you, it was all about Hilary Faye
dragging my ass around all the time.
When you left yesterday,
I stuck on my own.
And it was okay.
So...
So I realized that I might
just be relying on you
the same way
I was relying on Hilary Faye.
I don't wanna be the guy who's
with the girl because he needs her.
I wanna be the guy who's
with the girl because he wants her.
And I want you.
I want you, too.
And I thought it was all about the sex.
Oh, well, that too.
Look, I have
this crazy idea about tonight.
Mary, Roland's on the phone.
I got it.
What's going on?
- Hello. Where you headed?
- Lombard and Kale, please.
You guys look incredible.
You're not really
going to prom, are you?
Don't get angry,
but I got you a really sexy dress.
Hilary Faye's gonna call the cops
if we show up at her prom.
No, she won't.
See, I've been snagging
all her credit card bills
so she wouldn't find out about
all the charges we made, right?
Look at this.
She charged a bunch
of spray paint at Home Depot
at 3 A.M. on the morning of the attack.
Now we have proof.
We have every right
to be at that prom.
Oh, yeah.
We've got another surprise for you.
So cute.
I got yellow and red
'cause I didn't know which one...
But, Patrick...
It really doesn't matter to me.
Are you sure?
Yeah.
Red. Right.
I can't believe that you guys
did all of this for me.
So, you in?
I'm in.
I knew Mary was hiding something.
To imagine her humping that pervert
makes me sick to my stomach.
- Gross.
- And Roland still hasn't shown up.
I can't believe your own brother
calls you the "C" word.
I can't believe we have to go
to the prom in this van.
Yeah, well, get over it, okay?
When I tried to pay for my hair, my
credit card was mysteriously maxed out,
and the limo guy wouldn't take
a personal check. Get off my back!
It's bad enough we don't have dates.
Hey, let me try that tiara on.
Lay off the tiara, Tia!
Your pimple hardly shows,
Hilary Faye.
Come on, Tia!
Let's get the lead out!
Let's go.
We're gonna be late.
Coming.
- Okay?
- You look beautiful.
You can hardly see that thing.
Can you stop bringing it up?
Thank you.
Let's go. Come on, Tia.
Walk fast.
Run.
Name the most recognizable
figure in the world.
Jesus Christ.
- Madonna?
- Jesus Christ.
Newborns bond with their mothers
during the first three what?
- Minutes.
- Months.
No! The correct answer is minutes.
In "The Wizard of Oz,"
Dorothy clicks her heels
three times and says what?
Charlene.
Are you ready?
- Sure.
Why are they here?
Praise Jesus, everybody!
Jesus loves you!
We're taking a short break.
We'll be back in ten.
We will inherit the earth.
Praise Jesus.
On behalf
of the prom committee.
I wanna thank
each and every one of you
for making our "Light of the World"
prom a huge success.
Give yourself a round of applause.
But on a sadder note--
I don't want to dampen the evening--
but the students
who were responsible
for the attacks on our school
have infiltrated our prom.
Pastor Skip?
Mary Cummings and Cassandra Edelstein
have crashed our prom.
- Could you please...
- Maybe we should get out of here.
We're not going anywhere.
Roland, where have you been?
I've been very worried about you.
You look like you survived.
- Excuse me.
- Finally.
All right. Chill out, everybody.
I don't think these students
are here to do us any harm.
- What? Are you kidding?
- No, I'm not kidding.
I think the Christian thing to do
would be to let them stay.
The Christian thing to do?
I've been doing
the Christian thing my entire life.
I did not have sex with a gay
and try and blame it on Jesus.
- Just cool it, Hil.
- Shut up, you fornicator.
And I did not hack into
the school's computer system
and cover our walls
with that blasphemous graffiti, either.
You planted that paint on Cassandra
and Mary to get them kicked out of school.
That's such a lie.
Oh, please.
And what does this prove,
except the fact that you stole
my credit card to charge the paint...
... and the clothes
from Maternity Girl.
Yeah, she's right, Roland.
Anybody could've made these charges.
Oh, yeah? You swear to God
you didn't frame us, Hilary Faye?
No, I will not.
You can't swear, can you?
Go ahead, swear it.
Come on, Hil. Swear before God
and everyone else.
All right, I swear.
I swear to God
I did not graffiti our school.
Are you guys happy?
Oh, yes, you did, Hilary Faye.
I found this crammed up
under her seat.
What?
It's got your signature,
Hilary Faye.
Come on, Veronica.
Let's go.
Let me go!
You are nothing but a big fake!
I think you should go, Hilary.
Step aside, please.
- Hil--
- Get away from me!
- You really should go now.
- You go!
I designed
these decorations here!
And my father
donated the refreshments!
And I got Godflight onstage, okay?!
And I was just doing this
because Jesus told me to. He did!
Now, you, get out of my way!
All of you, get out of my way!
Get out of my way, you freaks!
I'll go get Patrick and Mary.
What are you--
What are you doing here?
I'm going to my prom.
What, did Mercy House
let you just borrow the van?
Not exactly. We sort of led a rebellion
and swiped it. You're pregnant?
Look, I really...
I wanted to tell you, but--
On the first time?
Yeah.
That is so awesome.
Yeah?
There's something
I wanna tell you, too.
He's your life-partner, right?
Prom date.
It's really nice to see you.
- Dean, this is Patrick.
- Nice to meet you.
Excuse me, Mary.
Listen, son, I suggest you
and your friends get back in the van,
and back to Mercy House as quick
as you can before you're all arrested.
We've had enough
excitement here for tonight.
We're not leaving.
What you and your friends have done
is not cool in the eyes of God.
- Jesus, Dad, stop it.
- Patrick, this is not a gray area.
- Dad, it's all a gray area.
- The Bible is black and white!
Stop it!
Would you listen to yourself?
I don't need this from you now.
We've been kicked out
of our homes and schools,
and now we're gonna
be kicked out of Mercy House?
There's nowhere left for us to go.
I'm supposed to be here.
This is my prom.
I wanna spend it with my friends.
There's no room for moral ambiguity here.
The Bible is very clear about this.
So everything that doesn't fit
into some stupid idea
of what you think God wants
you just try to hide
or fix or get rid of?
It's just all too much to live up to.
No one fits in 100% of the time.
Not even you.
I know that, Mary.
I know in my heart
that Jesus still loves me.
Why would God
make us all so different...
... if he wanted us to be the same?
Nowwhat?
Save the heathens, Hilary Faye.
Be a warrior, Hilary Faye!
Sacrifice everything, Hilary Faye!
And here's your big,
fat, stupid reward!
Oh, my God.
- I think I'm feeling kind of woozy.
- What?
Somebody call an ambulance.
That was so awesome, Hilary Faye!
Jesus Christ!
- You okay?
- No, Roland.
I crashed my van into Jesus, okay?!
I have a pimple the size of Jupiter!
I am not okay!
This is...
... not how I wanted
to remember my prom.
This is not how I wanted
to remember my life.
Well, maybe we could fix it...
... with some glue or something.
I am so sorry, Roland.
I shouldn't have ratted you out
in front of everyone.
I would have probably
done the same thing.
Do you think
Jesus still loves me, Roland?
Probably not.
Yeah, sure.
Hey, she's over here!
- I'm okay.
- Come on.
- Don't worry. I won't bite.
- Thank you.
- It's gonna be okay.
I only got room for one of you.
- I'm the father.
- I'm the boyfriend.
I'm his boyfriend.
That's nice, but I still
only got room for one of you.
Starting the party without me?
Are you okay?
You didn't ruin my life, Mary.
Breathe, baby.
Good girl.
Just keep breathing.
You're gonna be fine.
Okay, I'm pretty sure
this isn't what Jesus had in mind
when he said, "Help Dean."
Look, don't be too harsh.
I'm not the first person
to ever get the message screwed up.
She's perfect.
Looking at her,
it's like life is too amazing
to be this random and meaningless
consequence of the universe.
There had to be a God...
or something out there.
Something inside.
You just have to feel it.
Do you want to hold her?
Do you want to hold her, Dean?
I mean, really,
when you think about it--
what wouId Jesus do?
I don't know...
... but in the meantime we'll be trying
to figure it out... together.