L.A. La La land?
Are you going to go all Hollywood on us?
C- ment ponds, movie stars.
Don't forget to write.
He already did forget to write.
The neighborhood's not going to
be the same without you guys.
Eesh.
Okay.
So, let's do it then, right?
Right.
Okay.
We made it.
So this is it.
Oh, Kevin.
Hello, home.
This place could use an open window or two.
Kevin...?
Oh, Christ.
Did Joe and Miranda vaporize or something?
We have our work cut out for us.
You ready to finally see
what we bought in the flesh?
Yeah. I'm curious to see
how much their photos lied.
Ta Da!
Wow.
Wow. Am I dreaming?
Instant house.
Their running out of time really worked out for us.
I'd say so.
Hi.
Hello. I'm Kevin.
Kevin, great to meet you.
Welcome to the neighborhood.
Rachel.
Nolan.
Oh yeah... Okay.
I've got your phone number. Miranda
gave it to me along with some others.
Rlght. So, let me help.
Thanks. We could use it.
No problem.
I'm going to clean the refrigerator.
You can thank me later.
Oh you can put that against the side wall.
There's still a bunch of Joe
and Miranda's stuff in here.
Right.
These are dishes. Just put them here for now?
That's fine.
Neighbors.
Yah.
Hey.
Hey. I'm Julian. This is Alex.
Hi
We're here to move you in.
Great.
Have a beer.
Thanks.
It's really nice to meet you guys.
Well, the neighborhood's just curious
to see who's taken over the house.
I'm going to put this out on the deck.
Do you have any ice?
No. The refrigerator wasn't even on.
Rachel's cleaning it right now.
Come on in.
Rachel...
Meet some more neighbors.
Oh... hi.
Hey. Don't worry.
Thanks.
No chemicals.
Excuse me?
It's not good for the ground.
Oh no. This is just warm water and soap.
Gotta get it working.
Who are you?
I'm Fred. I'm here to fix the hot tub.
Oh.
It should have been ready when you got here.
Thlngs happened too fast.
It'll all be working by the time you need it.
They were fun for a whlle.
Joe was always kind of Into the God thlng...
but... when they decided to become
missionaries - Yeah, that surprised us.
Didn't Joe say his parents were missionaries?
All I know Is that we'd been looking for a place
for - God-what...
six months?
And when I saw the ad for this
place, I figured it had to be a scam.
Yeah, we both thought it was a scam.
No scam, just Miranda and Joe deciding to move to the
Philippines, teach people modern farming techniques.
Well...
here's to Joe and Miranda and their noble ways.
May they never want their house or their stuff back.
Beause they ain't gonna get it.
Here, here.
So, Nolan, what do you teach?
Sound design and film history.
I also have a little post studio at the house.
So, all of you guys are in
the business in some way?
Pretty much. You know, it's an L.A. thing.
You'll be sick of it before you know it.
Who else in the neighborhood?
Well, let's see...
Lionel, Jeff and Marie on the
other side work for the studio.
Miranda also gave us our
neighbor Andrew's number.
Oh, yeah, Andrew.
Uh oh, that doesn't sound good.
No, Andrew is...
He's an actor, and he really screwed up on
a show that we had recommended him for.
It was embarrassing and it was a mess.
We don't invite him to parties anymore.
Julian, can you pass me another beer?
Guys, excuse me.
You okay?
Yeah. I just, believe it or
not, am getting a little chilly.
I'm going to go find a sweater.
Good luck.
I'll need it.
Where do I know her from?
That could be one of a couple places.
She used to be the Zoom girl...
Also plenty of makeup ads.
Oh right. We have a star in our midst.
Well, she's retired now. She's
going to give writing a shot.
What about you?
I wrote copy for a small newspaper back east.
We were both just really frustrated with the
way things were going so we figured, Hey...
Why not give the west coast a chance?
So here we are. Both ready write
the great American screenplay.
There's not too many people
like us in this town, are there?
No.
Somebody must have gotten
shanked in the bathroom.
I guess so.
El Paso...
You alright?
I...
Yeah, yeah.
You didn't find a sweater?
No.
Julian, can you hand me a beer?
Hello?
Hey, what's up?
Yeah, you're the first to call.
It's Rose.
Hl, Rose.
Yes, yes.
It is so beautiful. You would not believe it.
It's great.
I can't wait to get in it.
Rose...
I'm seeing them again.
No, I dld not tell Kevin. You know I can't.
I promised a fresh start
when we came to California.
Hey.
I'm Rachel, your new neighbor.
I'm Andrew.
Yeah, I kinda figured that.
Why?
Oh, cause I was told that I had a
neighbor named Andrew and...
I guessed you were Andrew-seeing
as you came out of the house.
My boyfriend's name is Kevin. He's inside.
Joe and Miranda...
gone?
Yeah, they're in the Philippines now.
We're your new neighbors.
Philippines?
Yeah... You know, the whole
religious missionary thing?
Didn't you ever hang out with them?
They never struck me as religious.
Is that your boyfriend I've seen around?
Yeah, Kevin. He's inside writing.
He's not a producer?
Kevin? Oh no.
He's a writer.
I have to get going.
If you have any partles, or if you hear
of any partles,
please let me know.
Okay.
Parties on the hill are cool.
Good to go to them. Important, you know?
I can meet your boyfriend, Kevin.
Oh, and if you need my headshot for
anythlng, let me know.
I just got new ones made.
Welcome to Sllver Lake.
Edendale.
Many of Hollywood's first studios
were built right in the area you live.
I'm busted.
I thought you were writing. I was jealous.
Nothing to be jealous about, I'm afraid.
So, I met our neighbor, Andrew.
Oh yeah?
What's he like?
Cuckoo, cuckoo.
Huh.
Hello?
Oh yeah, hold on...
Bill.
Hey, Blll.
We're great.
We're just starting to feel settled in.
Hold on just a second, okay,
I'm going to switch phones.
Hang up for me please?
Kevin?
Uh huh?
You need a shave?
Beats trying to write.
That was Bill.
I know who that was.
He wanted to know if I'm avallable for ajob.
What did you tell him?
I told him that I'd talk it over with you.
What is he thinking?
He asked how things were
going and I told him fine.
He's trying to do us a favor,
best way he knows how.
By driving you crazy. Nice guy.
It's five days and five thousand dollars.
The point of moving out here was to
get away from that, do you remember?
Do you remember saying new life when we
moved to California, do you remember that?
Kevin, I am fine now.
- And besides it's just a little tiny shoot.
No crazy locations, no strangers.
It'sjust a dumb catalog.
Where?
Boston.
Fine, if you want to take it, take it.
This will be the last one, okay. I promise.
It's your mental health remember, not mine.
You mad?
No. No, I'm not.
I was...
a teeny bit annoyed.
Then I got over it.
When I cut myself.
You know what they say, right?
Don't shave angry.
Is that what they say?
Yeah.
Well, how about after dinner,
we go and break in that hot tub?
Now that sounds like a really good idea.
To hot tubs.
Oh, yeah.
Rachel, come on. The water's perfect.
Wait. Let me get a picture of the big moment.
I'm blind. I'm blind.
Oh, yeah.
If the folks back east could see us now.
I love L.A.
Not much not to love, is there?
I'm not ever leaving.
I have got the life.
Yeah, you do.
Is the water hot enough for you?
It's fine.
Are you sure?
Cause I can make it hotter, if you llke.
No, it's fine.
No, I can...
It's fine!
Help, Help.
I'm drowning.
Hey... What's going on back there?
I have no idea what you're talking about.
I think this hot water is giving you ideas.
Yeah, what kind of ideas is that?
What the... What dld you see?
Careful.
Was it an animal maybe?
They wouldn't want to come in here.
The water, the bubbles. It would scare them.
It wasn't an animal.
What then?
A crazed killer?
Stop it.
It could be.
Don't worry. I'll protect you.
My hero.
Geez.
Julian?
Hl, Rachel.
Are you alright?
I heard crying. Is Andrew okay?
He has had some problems.
Well, Is he all right?
He'll be fine.
What happened to him?
Nothing. He was just very
upset about some things.
I'll tell him you were here.
Thanks.
Oh my god!
Quiet.
I thlnk the waterwas dralnlng slowly,
so keep an eye on it.
Aye, aye, Captaln.
Do you know where my purse is?
It's the living room.
Can you check to see if my ID's in
there? And my... flight... the tickets...
Rachel...
Put your clothes on.
Close your suitcase.
Everything is cool.
Okay.
Ready?
Ready.
Andrew?
Hello.
All by myself.
So, it was five o'clock In the mornlng...
and we were all waitlng In thls van
for everyone to show up...
and thls one model doesn't show
up for an hour.
- And then the photographer comes
in right behind her-two hours.
It was amazing.
God, you would think the traffic
wouldn't be so heavy right now.
So, by the time we got to the location,
we were four hours behind schedule.
and from there, it was downhill.
It was... horrible.
Glad to be back?
Yeah.
So, you experienced an earthquake?
So?
It was... exhilarating.
Frankly, I don't think I need to be
experiencing that kind of exhilaration.
Yeah, well if you'd been there
you wouldn't feel that way.
It was incredible.
Okay.
I like your hair like this.
Thank you.
I quit smoking.
Really?
Yeah, so if I get a little short tempered
with you, blame it on that. Okay?
I'm really glad that you quit.
Just, try not to be too mean to me, okay?
Home sweet home. Boy, it's good to be back.
Andrew's moving?
Yeah. Actually he's moved already.
Really?
Yup. Gone.
Kind of strange, isn't it?
Yeah. Did he say why?
Oh, I started working out.
Kevin? Where's the food?
I'm sorta watching what I eat.
Welcome home, baby. We missed you.
I can hear your chewing in my head.
Stop it.
I am going to take a shower before I drop.
A shower, shower-to get this day
old airplane-sweat and dirt off me.
I knew that would get you.
What are you doing?
Hey, Pardner. You a good guy or a bad guy?
Miss, Miss...
I'm looking for Mr. Garbutt, Frank Garbutt.
Frank Garbutt? I don't know him.
You don't know? That's the Edendale hill?
That's Edendale.
There's no need to make hills that steep.
The road doesn't need to be that steep.
The studlo's around here.
I know it's around here.
I'm sorry. Who are you looking for?
I was on that hill.
Garbutt, Eddie Habert, Sid Jordon, Selig.
None of these names mean anything to you?
Heads of the fuckin' studlo.
Tom. Tom was there.
You're "in" one day, and you're "out" the next.
It's a tough town, a tough town.
I gotta go.
You're beautiful. Beautiful people.
You tell Tom, the next tlme you see hlm,
that I got away.
Okay.
You bitch.
Bitch. You can't do this to me.
You can't just take my life
and my furniture, you bitch.
You see the same people on the
way up as on the way down.
It's who you know in this town. You
wanna be so fucking Hollywood!
Hello?
Hey, Nolan. How's it going?
Well it's good to be back...
A party?
When?
Hold on just a second.
Are we available for a party at Nolan's tonight?
Absolutely.
Yeah, that would be great.
Alright.
Okay.
Bye.
This should be fun.
Excellent.
We have been invited to our first hill party.
I hate you.
No one ever said it was going to be easy.
I really hate you.
Well I'm going to do some gardening.
If I can't be a decent writer, maybe I can
at a little Miss Beaver Cleever gardener.
Do you hate me because I can't write?
It'll come.
The writing or the hate?
Think you're so great.
You're just a stupid bimbo model.
You're not even a real actress.
So what do you know?
If you wrote about what you know
it'd be a god damn pamphlet.
Did he say who was going to be there?
No, but I'm guessing that
Alex and Julian will be there.
Why? You got any Ideas?
No.
Probably will be industry people though.
How long until you're ready?
Ah, just a mlnute.
Hey -
I found something that I think you might like.
I found it in the garden.
It looks like a...
are you okay?
You found this.
That is the nicest thing.
It's just an old hunk of metal.
God, Rachel,
You're the best.
Nice night.
Hey. Hi. Come in.
Nolan.
You made it.
Yeah, but traffic was a bitch.
They llve up the hlll...
In Joe and Mlranda's old place.
Hi.
The booze is in the kitchen.
Cheers.
To the hill.
I try to tell them that it's as important to get good sound on location
as it is to get a good picture, but people don't seem to listen.
I set it up with them, but they dldn't respond
the way I hoped they would.
That's Ed.
He's a producer.
He's a really good friend of
mine. You should meet him.
This is great.
How's the screenplay?
It's good. Very good, In fact.
Dld I tell you about it?
I don't know, did you?
I didn't think so, but-oh well.
We know pretty much everything
that happens on the hill.
Yeah, I guess so.
You have to take care of the hill.
Take care of the hill?
Yeah. All the roots from the trees,
the plants, the pipes, the plumbing.
It all combines, connects -
like a circulatory system.
A ha.
When something happens, you have
to take care of it fast. Call Dr. Fred.
Yeah, he fixed our hot tub.
Then you know. He keeps
everybody in good shape.
Do you want me to take this out for you?
Uh huh.
Hey.
Ed, I have someone I want you to meet.
Okay.
This is Kevin. He lives up the hill.
Edward Habert, good to meet you.
Nice to meet you.
He's written something I think
you really want to take a look at.
Really?
I don't know that it's quite ready yet.
I mean, I know it's not ready yet.
I'm only halfway through the first draft,
let alone any kind of rewrite.
Don't be modest. You said you're
were looking for a western, right?
I did, I did.
About time for our comeback, wouldn't you say?
A classic western like the old days.
How did you know that I'm writing a wes-
Anytime you're ready, Kevin.
How about Wednesday?
Jesus.
Yeah, I gota welcome to Sllver Lake pamphlet where
itactually boasted thatthls Is where Hollywood started.
Yeah. It's true, this entire hill
was part of Tom Mix's ranch.
Oh, I think I know who he is.
He was big.
At one point he was the highest
paid movie star around.
He made like fifteen thousand
dollars a week-in Nineteen fifteen.
Back when fifteen grand a week
meant somethlng.
Yeah, all of them in this square mile
or two. Mixville right on this hill.
What at tlme.
It was really llke the Wlld West then.
And the studio heads played right into it.
One story of how four of them tried to hang
some contract player...
...who had screwed up an entlre day's
shootlng with some less than deslrable actlng.
Wow, that's the good old days, huh?
I'm sure that the studio publicist
made up the entire story, but -
it gave them a reputation as bad asses
and the nickname, the four horsemen.
Tom Mix on the other hand -
He was your classic-squeaky
clean, cowboy image.
Kids' role model-don't drink, don't smoke,
eat your vegetables sort of thlng.
He signed autographs by the carloads.
There are still things on the hill
which hint to the Mixville era.
There's still some rubble on Lionel's
property that was part of the stables.
Honey, show Nolan what I found.
Wow.
Found it in the backyard-in the ground.
Pretty great, huh?
So, what happened to him?
Tom Mix?
Well, when sound came along, Westerns sortoffell
outoffavor, and he wentto dolng wild westshows.
Later, the studio four, the four
horsemen, got back together.
Tom Mix had written a Western, and they
were golng to make it.
A return to the glory days.
Well, on hls way back from Arizona,
he was driving a bit too fast.
Supposedly the accldent itselfwasn't so bad, but the
flylng suitcase that clocked hlm In the back of the neck...
End of Tom Mix, end of an era.
He's buried in Glendale.
The gully where he died is
named after him, and this hill...
Well, every so often this hill
coughs up a bit of his life.
It's an era that nobody remembers anymore -
except when I teach it in my film history
class or drink and talk about it at parties.
It's interesting.
So, what are you doing now?
Trying to write.
I just did a job back east,
but I'm really trying to write.
How's it going?
So far, not so good-whlch has really
got me worried.
Don't worry.
Things will work themselves out.
People who live on the hill do good work.
Geez, well I hope I'm worthy.
With Joe and Miranda, with the
whole kid thing... you know...
I thought they became missionaries?
Yeah, that and the kid.
He was never really part of anythlng
on the hlll.
But, we have big hopes for you though.
Guys, I'm leaving.
I just wanted to say good nlght.
You, call me.
I will. Nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you.
Hey, Edward?
Yeah?
I think there might be a vacancy.
Well I'll look into it. Good night.
Andrew's place?
Gotta move our people in, right?
That was cool.
God, thls hlll Is exhlllratlng.
I'm beat.
Wasn't that great?
All those cool people.
Kevin?
What?
How come that guy Edward
wants to talk to you so bad?
I mean, it's not llke anyone knows
or has read your stuff yet.
What are you talking about?
Julian recommended me.
Yeah, but if he's an important
producer, like they say he is,
why is he so hot to work with you
if he hasn't even read word one?
What? Are you jealous?
No, god no, I'm just curious.
I guess he really trusts Julian's opinion.
Yeah. But how does Julian
know if you're any good?
Don't get pissy.
I'm not being pissy. I'm just asking.
It's seems a little weird if you ask me.
Jesus Christl
Can't you ever not be susplclous?
That is how this town works.
It's about who you know.
You could be illiterate for all they know.
Yeah but I'm not. I am a fucking good writer.
Don't you try and bring me down, you bitch.
You were supposed to be on my side.
Kevin?
What?
You are scaring me.
Shut up.
There's nothing to be scared about.
Just don't say jealous, stupid things.
Good morning. How are you?
Okay, I guess.
You were a real asshole last night.
What? Oh. That was nothing.
What do you mean that was nothing? That
was not nothing. That was something.
Oh. Sorry.
Oh, come on.
Rachel...
Kevin?
Yeah?
What exactly happened to Andrew?
He moved.
I thought you said he lost it or had a
nervous breakdown or something?
I did?
Yeah.
No. He moved.
Are you sure?
Yes.
How do you know?
Hls car Is stlll there.
Hls stuff Is stlll In the house.
It just doesn't seem right.
You're imagining things.
He told me he was moving.
Said he didn't like living in L.A. anymore.
He told you he was moving?
Yes.
When?
When you were away.
Well then how come his stuff is still here?
Why are you asking so many questions?
It's really none of your business.
- And I don't have every single answer.
Maybe if you spent less time worrying about the
neighbors, and more time worrying about your writing -
- You might actually get something done.
What?
I'm going out. Do you need anything?
No.
Fuck you, Kevin. Maybe when you're nlcer,
I'll glve it back to you.
Oh great, Rachel. Why don't you just
bring the whole garden in with you?
Good thing you're not a cat burglar.
Right to the scene of the...
Get a hold of yourself. You are an adult.
You can handle your own imagination.
You'rejust a little stressed out.
Just breath. In and out.
Just relax.
There you go.
It's okay.
Just relax. You just need to relax.
You are a freak, Rachel. Stupid
freak, freaking yourself out.
Stupid freak.
You have got to relax.
Don't let it happen.
What is wrong with you?
Hello?
Who's here?
Nobody.
Who are you talking to?
Oh, but I heard you talking to someone.
What happened?
You dropped like a bag of flour
the minute I walked in the door.
Oh, God.
You had that hot tub way too hot.
How long were you in there?
God, I'm still in the buff.
Uh Huh.
You were pretty dehydrated, overheated.
You okay?
You want to see a doctor?
No. I'm fine.
I need to get dressed.
Oh God, Rachel.
That is so dangerous.
You can boil your brain that way.
You hungry?
How about I go get some takeout.
Okay.
I've got some news to tell you.
About what?
I'll tell you when I get back.
I also got a video you mlght get a kick out of.
What?
You'll see.
Okay. I'll be right back.
Who are you?
Dinner's here.
Okay.
What-are you talking about?
The cowboy...
Tom Mix.
What about him?
You need to eat.
Kevin...
Something happened to you.
It's this house, the hill.
I know I'm not crazy, I'm not imagining this.
Please, please leave with me and you'll see.
Back to the east coast?
To hell with that.
I told you, I'm not leaving.
I love it here.
I belong here.
I have found my place.
No, Kevin. It has found you.
Rose? It's me.
Everything. Everything is wrong.
The house is wrong.
Kevin is wrong.
This fucking hill is wrong.
Can you please come?
I have no friends here.
Don't you even want to know
what my news was?
What's your news?
I met with Edward today -
- And he loved the script.
Said it should have been made years ago.
He's golng to get it green-lit
as soon as posslble.
This all happened today?
It happens fast when it happens.
Good for you, Kevin.
I guess you're what this town likes.
Rose is helping me move.
She's coming the day after tomorrow.
Don't you have anything to say?
Good bye.
After I got back from thatjob,
he was different.
He quit smoking, he was writing non stop.
Those seem like good things.
But there are other things.
Hls mannerisms. The way he talks.
He's different.
He's mean.
It's the house.
It's the hill. Everybody on the hill is...
Rose, they're all in on it together.
I don't thlnk it was a mlstake that
we moved here.
And the thing is that if you
don't fit in, they exclude you.
They excluded Andrew, our nelghbor,
and now he's gone.
Gone?
And now they want me out. So, I'm leaving.
They have plans.
I know it sounds like I'm crazy, but
I'm not. You have to believe that.
I'm your sister.
It comes with the job description.
I'm here to do whatever you want me to do.
Thanks, Rose.
Yeah.
He's not home.
So now what?
I don't know.
Do you mlnd if I sit down? New York
tlme Is kinda catchlng up with me.
Oh yeah. Do you want to sit out on the deck?
Yeah.
You sure you want to give this all up?
All I want Is the stuffthat I came here with.
He can have everythlng we gotwhen we got here.
Is he going to pay you for it?
I don't care.
I just gotta get out.
Hello, Rose.
Kevin, hl.
How are you?
Okay. You?
Okay, I guess,
considering the circumstances.
Well, I'm going to be in the
office if you need anything.
Thanks.
Okay, your clothes, the computer,
whatever... You're going to need boxes.
I know. I gotta go get some.
Maybe you could start laying
my clothes out on the bed.
Sure. Yeah.
You need anything?
No, honey. I'm okay.
Rose, thanks again.
Sure.
Hey.
Kevin, what happened?
Why are you guys breaking
up? You're so good together.
I thought so too.
She really surprised me when she
just suddenly said she was leaving.
Nothing else?
She's been acting kind of
strange for the past few months,
but I just chalked that up to
moving, relocating to a new place.
God, it's killing me that she's leaving.
I don't know. To be perfectly honest with you...
I'm concerned about her.
I think she's got something deeper going on.
You might be right.
Oh, Kevin.
I'm so sorry that thls Is happenlng, but I'm not
supposed to be taking sldes, except her slde.
Don't-don't take sides.
I guess you're just going to have
to look at me as the bad guy.
Oh, honey, I'm so sorry about all thls.
Yeah, me too.
You poor thing.
Where's Rose?
She said something about going out for a walk.
I thought she'd be back by now.
She's not.
Huh.
Did you check outside?
She loves it out there.
She's not outside.
I guess she dldn't get back
from herwalk then.
Excuse me.
I'm going to a meeting with
Edward and somebody from Fox.
If everythlng goes the way he thlnks it will...
You could be readlng about me In
tomorrow's Variety.
I'm not going to be reading Variety
tomorrow or any other god damn day.
I am moving. You do realize that, don't you?
Sure.
I think you're basically
stupid, and I don't give a shit.
But yes... I am aware.
Fuck you, you self-absorbed
Hollywood wannabe.
Hello?
It's for you.
Edward... Great to hear from you.
Yes, yes.
I'm on my way out the door right now.
Uh huh. Okay. I will see you soon...
at Nolan's.
Ciao.
You're going to Nolan's?
Yeah. The big movie premiere.
What?
You are no longer part of this hill, as I recall.
Well, I'm off.
Don't wait up.
You Fuck!
You FUCK!
Shut up... Shut up!
I'm so sorry about all thls.
Rose?
911, what is your -
To the hill.
This entire hill was part of Tom Mix's ranch.
Abouttime forourcomeback, wouldn'tyou say?
I was on that hill.
Return to the glory days.
You need to move along.
I feel sorry for that woman.
Been around here for years, I hear.
It's a terrible thing.
Terrible, terrible thing.
Yeah.
Well you have to wonder how
they get that way, I mean...
It's a tough town.
Rachel...