People once believed
that when someone dies...
a crow carries their soul
to the land of the dead.
But sometimes,
something so bad happens...
that a terrible sadness is carried
with it and the soul can't rest.
Then sometimes,
just sometimes...
the crow can bring that soul back
to put the wrong things right.
Over here.
There's a piece of glass.
Hey, Sarge!
Yeah?
Shelly Webster and Eric Draven.
Wedding was tomorrow night.
Who the fuck gets married
on Halloween anyhow?
Nobody.
- Sir, we gotta move her.
- Do it.
All right, guys,
let's do it.
Devil's fucking Night.
What's the count so far?
143 fires.
- They're slacking off from last year.
- Three hours to go.
- Maybe they're just slow starters.
- Coming through!
You guys can't come in here
and take her away like this.
There are procedures. You should have
cleared this with me first.
- Is this the victim?
- No, it's Amelia Earhart.
- We found her, and you missed it.
- I don't care what her name is.
I didn't give the order to move her.
Jesus, Albrecht.
I can see why they took away
your gold shield.
Yeah, I wasn't a big enough asshole.
Come on. Let's go.
All right, clear out.
- Shelly?
- Stand back, kid.
- Where's Eric?
- Just don't worry about him.
Tell him to take care
of Sarah.
Look, I will.
You just, uh, lie back. Come on.
- You Sarah?
- Yeah.
Yeah, look. Your sister,
she's gonna be okay.
She's not my sister.
Shelly just takes care of me.
She's my friend.
Her and Eric.
You lied to her about Eric.
I had to.
And you're lying
to me about Shelly.
She's gonna die,
isn't she?
Hey, uh...
Now, come on.
Come on. It's okay.
She's gonna be fine.
A building gets torch ed.
All that is left is ashes.
I used to think that was true
about everything...
families, friends, feelings.
But now I know that sometimes,
if love proves real...
two people who are meant to be together,
nothing can keep them apart.
Later.
What are you,
like the night watchman?
You know, what this place
needs is a...
good natural catastrophe.
- Earthquake, tornado, you know.
- No, no, no, no.
Mickey, come on, man. You got to put
the mustard underneath first.
Maybe a flood like in the Bible.
Hey, hey, let me do it.
There we go. All right.
How about some onions?
Come on, man.
Don't cheap out on me.
- Lots of onions.
- All right, here you go.
Hey, all right.
Now we're talking.
Hey, it's the Sarah monster.
- How do you steer that on a wet street?
- Pure talent. Hi.
Now, Sarah, she's a genuine hot dogger.
You hungry?
- You buying?
- I'm buying.
- No onions though, okay?
- No onions?
They make you fart big time.
You know, Lake Erie
actually caught on fire once...
from all the crap
floating around in it.
I wish I could have seen that.
Fire it up! Yeah!
- All right, we busted their machines!
- Shit!
Oh, oh, shit, guys.
T- bird, cop car, cop car.
Bad people out
on the street tonight.
- Damn it!
- What was that?
- You wait right here.
- Be careful.
Mickey, call it in for me!
Gabriel!
- Eric?
- Department of Housing!
Code violations?
Safety hazards?
Place looks fine to me.
Let's redecorate.
"Abash, the devil stood...
and felt how awful
goodness is.
Saw virtue in her shape, how lovely."
It's pornography.
Virtue?
Shelly?
- No! Eric!
- See ya!
No, no, no, me first.
Please.
- Shelly.
- Eric!
- Hey, that's good.
- That's good.
See if you can top that, man.
Can you top that?
Look at that.
Here's to Devil's Night,
my new favorite holiday.
You go over there
and talk to your pals...
You sick fuck.
Are you out of
your motherfucking mind, man?
Look at that!
Pussies drink last, man.
- Fuck you, Tin Tin.
- Hey.
Shit ain't
even loaded, man.
This one is.
Which of you Motor City
motherfuckers...
wants to bet me
this one isn't?
Hey, fire it up!
Fire it up!
- Fire it up! - Fire
it up! - Fire it up!
Fire it up! Fire it up!
Here's your shooters.
- Put your guns away, huh, guys?
- How ya doing?
Pussycat.
Boo.
- I love you.
- Say that again.
I love you.
Oh, boy.
Restaurant.
- Wow, you look great.
- Ta-da!
Yeah!
- Come here!
- No, no, no!
Couple more rings.
That's 24k.
24k, huh? It's 18k.
It's crap. It's probably fake.
Leather purse. Leather.
Geez. Oh, what is this, Tin Tin?
A blood stain
that's on here?
I'll give you 50 bucks.
And I hate charities.
Now, you,
take it or leave it.
Right there for ya.
Decisions, decisions.
You cheap ass, chrome dome...
...child molesting,
saprophyte motherfucker.
Close the gate
when you go out!
Oh, I close this up
for you real good, massa.
Fuck you.
Yeah, sit on it and twirl,
you dirty scum.
Lucky I didn't stab
your fat ass.
What the fuck you all painted
up for, crackhead, huh?
Halloween ain't till manana.
Come on.
Fuck, you murderer!
I ain't murdered nobody, man!
I don't even fucking know you!
- Man, what the fuck you want, man?
- I want you to tell me a story.
A man and a woman
in a loft a year ago.
- You're out of your fucking mind...
- Listen!
I'm sure you'll remember.
You killed them... on Halloween.
Yeah, yeah, Halloween, yeah.
Some dude, some bitch, whatever, man.
Her name was Shelly.
You cut her.
You raped her.
Shelly, yeah, yeah. I shanked
her pink ass and she loved it!
Murderer? Murderer? Let me tell you
about murder. It's fun!
It's easy.
You gonna learn all about it.
I'd like you to meet
two buddies of mine.
We never miss.
Try harder.
- Try again!
- Aaah!
Victims.
Aren't we all?
- Look at this mess! What's the world coming to?
- It's a mess.
I got to go upstairs.
Report from the front.
Get out of my way,
you worms!
Give me some of that
over there!
Why don't you ladies come by later?
Check me out.
Hey, guess what?
Arcade Games fell down, went boom.
- Boom.
- Can you imagine that? It's tragic.
Gather your soldiers.
You're on for tomorrow night. No sweat.
- Is the man in?
- He's taking a meeting.
You're thinking
about the past.
Dad gave me this.
Fifth birthday.
He said childhood's over
the moment you know you're gonna die.
Is she asleep?
I think we broke her.
I love her eyes.
Pretty.
Hey, kid,
get the hell outta the road!
I told you to stay out of here.
So I guess you're not gonna be home
till a lot later, huh, Darla?
She's busy. Go play with your dolls
or something, okay?
I don't have any dolls.
Get some food, huh?
Somebody already bought me dinner.
The police.
- "Somebody already bought me dinner.
The police."
Thirty, forty dollars.
Who the fuck is this now?
Hey! Piss off!
We're closed!
Cerrado!
Sleep it off somewhere else, dusthead,
unless you want to get mutilated.
Goddamn creatures of the night,
they never learn.
Hey! Hey!
"Suddenly I heard
a tapping, as if someone...
gently rapping,
rapping at my chamber door."
What are you talking about?
You heard me rapping, right?
You're trespassing,
and you owe me a fucking new door!
I'm looking for something
in an engagement ring.
Gold.
You're looking for a coroner,
shit-for-brains.
Oh, shit.
Oh, shit on me!
Shit on me.
Shit on me!
- Aaah!
- Mr. Gideon.
You're not paying attention.
No!
I repeat, a gold
engagement ring, yes?
It was pawned here a year ago
by a customer of yours named Tin Tin.
He confided in me
before he ran out of breath.
Who's this sack of shit?
That's Tin Tin, one of
T- bird's little helpers.
I think you can rule out
accidental death.
Don't any of your street demons
have real grown-up names?
This could be a turf hit, but it doesn't
look like your usual gang crap.
Come on, Albrecht, spare me.
You're a beat cop now, so be a beat cop.
I'm suppose to thank you
for that, right?
Word to the wise:
Watch your fucking mouth.
What the hell
do you call that?
I call it blood, detective.
I suppose you'll write it up
as graffiti.
You can leave
my crime scene now, okay?
- Warmer?
- What are you doing?
- Don't you know this game?
- What game?
Okay, the rings!
I'll tell you about the rings!
They're in that metal box!
It's under the shelf there!
Take the fucking rings!
Choke on them, you son of a bitch!
- Look, it goes to the attic.
- Okay.
No, no.
No, no, no.
Oh, it's beautiful.
I don't believe it.
Shelly.
I love you.
- You have one chance to live.
- Take anything you want.
- Thank you.
- Take anything!
Now you're going to tell me
where to find...
the rest of Tin Tin's
little party pals.
The Pit. They all
hang out at The Pit.
T- birds's little potato-heads hang out
there. Funboy lives there upstairs.
- Funboy.
- Oh, baby, oh.
- A whole jolly club...
- Please!
- with jolly pirate nicknames!
- Stop! Please!
- Jesus Christ in a taxicab!
- Hold still!
Each one of these is a life...
a life you helped destroy.
I'm begging you.
Don't kill me.
I'm not gonna kill you.
Your job will be to tell the rest
of them that death is coming for them...
tonight.
Tell them Eric Draven
sends his regards.
You walk outta here,
they're gonna erase your sorry ass.
You're nothing but street grease,
you motherfucker!
Is that gasoline I smell?
No, man, no!
No!
It's on the house, kiddo,
you know that.
One root beer.
I can't do anything.
Your mom... technically,
she's off right now.
Yeah, way off.
Police! Don't move!
I said, "Don't move!"
I thought the police
always said, "Freeze!"
I am the police and I say don't move,
Snow White. You move, you're dead.
And I say I'm dead and I move.
Not one more step.
I'm serious.
Then shoot, if you will,
Officer Albrecht.
What are you, nuts?
Walking into a gun?
You high?
- You don't remember me?
- What are you talking about?
How about Shelly?
Do you remember Shelly Webster?
Shelly Webster's dead, my friend.
I want you to move over to the curb,
nice and easy. Move it!
Okay, we're gonna
wait here for backup.
- It's getting too weird for me.
- Oh, it gets better.
Do you know someone named T-bird?
He had a friend who shouldn't have
played with knives. Like the coat?
You're the guy
that murdered Tin Tin.
- Check it out.
- He was already dead.
- He died a year ago.
The moment he touched her.
They're all dead.
They just don't know it yet.
Get away from there!
Cops!
Get outta here!
Leave it, run!
Oh, great, great.
Guy shows up looking like
a mime from hell...
and you lose him
right out in the open.
Well, at least he didn't do that walking
against the wind shit. I hate that.
Little early
for Devil's Night.
You are very restless.
Just wish I was a little
hungry again, that's all.
- Be careful of what you ask for.
- Yeah, I may get it, I know.
There are energies
aligning against you.
Seeing is believing,
isn't it?
Mmm, yummy.
Gideon's pawnshop just burned down
to the foundation.
Nobody cleared
this little event with me.
I didn't have nothing
to do with that.
You must be
awfully disappointed.
I got trouble.
One of my crew got himself perished.
- Yeah, who might that be?
- Tin Tin.
Somebody stuck his blades in all his
major organs in alphabetical order.
Gentlemen, by all means,
I think we ought to have...
an introspective moment of silence
for poor, old Tin Tin.
You're working for me
tomorrow night, right?
- Whatever you say, I can do.
- Good.
That's very reassuring.
I still ain't heard
why Gideon's burned down.
Is that a natural catastrophe
or act of God or something?
Call it my need to know.
Let go, you creep!
Nah.
You didn't even slow down,
you dickhead!
He couldn't have stopped.
He was a buttface.
I could have made it.
What are you supposed to be,
a clown or something?
Sometimes.
It's more like surfing than skating.
I wish the rain would stop, just once.
- It can't rain all the time.
- Eric?
Don't thank me.
Are we fighting the good fight?
Double homicide a year ago.
No convictions.
Annie... look at that.
"We, the undersigned tenants of
1929 Caulderon Court Apartments... "
What is this, a petition?
Big "kick me" sign for a very nice girl
who found herself a cause.
- The cause got her killed.
- She was fighting tenant eviction in that neighborhood?
Shelly Webster and her nice
rock-and-roll boyfriend, Eric Draven.
The last time you snooped around a case
is when you got put back on the beat.
- I know. Torres keeps reminding me.
- I bet he does.
You're going to wind up
working a school crosswalk.
I'm cool.
You didn't get that file from me, okay?
And don't tell me you owe me one.
Ah, I owe you one!
Yeah, right.
Damn.
Tomorrow night
we can get high...
and watch this whole fucking city
burn from that window.
- There's a big fucking bird over there.
- * No more **
Huh?
It's a squab.
Come here, bird.
Hey, bird.
Bird. B-B-Birdie.
Here, birdie, birdie.
Come here, birdie,
birdie, birdie.
Birdie? Hey, birdie?
Here, Funboy.
What the fuck?
No, man! Don't do that! You nearly
gave me a fucking heart attack!
Look at him.
Don't sweat it.
It's time for you to take
your bird and leave, freako.
Take your shot, Funboy.
You got me dead bang.
You are seriously fucked up.
Did you look in the mirror?
You need professional help.
Bingo!
He shoots! He scores!
- Jesus Christ!
- Jesus Christ?
Stop me if you heard this one.
Jesus Christ
walks into a hotel.
Ow.
He hands the innkeeper
three nails and he asks...
Don't you ever fucking die?
"Can you put me up for the night?"
- Does that hurt?
- Fuck. Does it... Fuck, does it hurt?
Oh, God.
Look what you've done
to my sheets.
I've got a gun
in my pocket.
You're happy to see me,
aren't you?
Stay away!
Stay away from me!
Look.
Mother is the name for God
on the lips and hearts of all children.
Do you understand?
Morphine is bad for you.
Your daughter is out there
on the streets waiting for you.
If I wanted ice,
I would have asked for ice!
Now fill it up!
Fill it up yourself, macho man.
I really need this.
All right.
You burn yourself
playing with matches?
- Fuck off.
- You have an appointment.
- Well, shit on me.
- Drink up.
This is a first.
Do I bow or do I curtsy?
Get my friend here
a glass of blood.
Oh! Hey, hey, hon!
Hey, good night, Darla.
You stay put right there.
Get away, steamhead.
Shh.
As you can see, I'm
on the corner of 27th and Washington...
- the site of last year's biggest
Devil's Night conflagration.
It was exactly one year ago
that the building you see...
across the street from me
was totally demolished by fire.
The fire that was fought
by seven fire companies...
but lost the lives
of two fire fighters.
In fact, if it weren't for the constant
surveillance by the local police...
Freeze!
Jesus. Don't ever do that, man.
Fuck.
Good likeness.
I saw your body, man.
You died. You got buried.
You still have your hat on.
I gotta sit down.
Shi...
Holy Shit.
Say...
are you some kind of... ghost?
Boo!
I don't know what I am. I need you
to tell me what happened to us.
You took a six-story swan dive
out of a window.
She, ah, was beaten and raped.
Died at the hospital.
Hey, you asked, man.
Come on. Read the file.
Shelly Webster held on
for 30 hours in intensive care.
Her body finally just gave it up.
I saw it.
I couldn't do jack for her.
- Hey.
- Don't touch me!
Hey.
You okay?
I saw her.
I saw her
through your eyes.
You stayed with her
the whole time.
Yeah, well, you got to
understand something, all right?
I was hoping
she'd come out of it, you know.
Give me something
I could work with.
Yeah.
Look, I...
Why didn't you do
something about it?
You think any people in that building,
even the ones who signed the petition...
would talk after
what happened to you?
I kept asking
questions and...
finally got busted for sticking
my nose where it wasn't wanted.
This your wife?
Yeah, we, uh... Well, not anymore,
we're getting a divorce.
It's funny.
Little things used to mean
so much to Shelly.
I used to think
they were kind of trivial.
Believe me,
nothing is trivial.
You shouldn't smoke these.
They'll kill you.
You going to vanish
into thin air again?
I thought I'd use
your front door.
Look, man, I'm sorry as hell for what
happened to you and your girlfriend.
Yeah.
I got stabbed!
I shot the son of a bitch!
I watched the bullet hole
close by itself.
And then my business
gets blown up real good.
- Other than that, my day sucked.
- Yeah.
I saw him too.
He had a guitar.
He winked at me before he jumped out
a fourth-floor window like he had wings.
He winked at ya?
Musicians.
- What else did you see?
- So far I haven't heard...
shit about what you're going to do
about all this crap!
What do I get? My livelihood
got flushed and went swirling.
You ain't lost everything.
Yeah, and maybe you're not
such a big shot either! Ow! Jesus!
Fair enough. Catch.
Aah! Jesus.
Say hello to the last fellow
who wouldn't cooperate with me.
What're you telling me,
this thing is real?
All the power in the world
resides in the eyes, fella.
Sometimes they're more useful
than the people who bear them.
You're directly out of
your fucking mind! You know that!
Yeah.
Eyes see. It's one of the most important
things I learned from my sister.
Sister? She's supposed to be
your sister?