I am a prosecutor.
I'm a part of the business of accusing...
...judging...
...and punishing.
I explore the evidence of a crime...
...and determine who is charged...
...who is brought to this room...
...to be tried before his peers.
I present my evidence to thejury...
...and they deliberate upon it.
They must determine
what really happened.
If they cannot...
...we won't know if the accused deserves
to be freed or to be punished.
If they cannot find the truth...
...what is our hope ofjustice?
Where's Nat?
Burying a goldfish.
That he forgot to feed.
Kid's gotta learn responsibility.
He's nine.
When you were nine,
you fed the animals on the block...
...and made dinner,
did everyone's homework...
...and, in your spare time,
you practiced law.
I didn't practice law until I was ten.
Listen to this.
"In their first face-to-face debate,
Nico Della Guardia...
"...appeared to throw
Raymond Horgan off stride...
"...with an opening swipe
at the prosecuting attorney's...
"...twelve-year tenure as
'an uninterrupted retreat from reality...
"'... and slow-motion surrender to thugs,
punks and hand-wringing liberals."'
The guy's unbelievable.
I'm finally starting to get used to that rug
on Della Guardia's head.
Don't eat standing up. Sit down.
Food goes down easier.
It has the help of gravity.
Oh, God.
Yet another lawyer.
I won't be home till late.
I got a game after school.
Like his father, he doesn't come home
till he has to.
If Raymond loses this election,
I could be home a lot.
Rick, I looked this over last night.
Top count, max.
It's a first offense!
No plea to anything
but the A-1 felony. Period.
On all of them?
All of them.
And no promises on the sentence.
- Good morning.
This is for you.
Someone put it under the door last night.
I found it when I came in.
Mr. Big Cheese wants to see you now.
I'll be right along.
He said "now," now.
What's wrong?
Carolyn Polhemus was murdered last night.
Her cleaning lady found the body
this morning.
Some creep got into her place
and strangled her.
It looks like she was raped.
He tied her up...
...he beat her with some instrument
and strangled her.
No weapon. No sign of forced entry.
Unless you want me here,
I'm supposed to meet the coroner.
That's all right. Go on, get out of here.
I can hear Della Guardia now.
"If Raymond Horgan can't protect his own
attorneys, how can he protect citizens?"
Tommy Molto's secretary said
he wasn't coming in today.
Some fucking Acting Head of Homicide
he turned out to be, the little creep.
I should have fired him when we fired Nico.
If I had balls, I'd do it now.
I want you to handle this case personally.
I will assign it to somebody.
Who will you assign it to? Homicide?
Tommy Molto? For Christ's sake!
Della Guardia would love that.
Molto would tip him off on everything.
They're so close you can see Molto's nose
sticking out of Nico's bellybutton.
Listen to me.
What a waste.
Beautiful, sexy gal. Hell of a lawyer.
That's her ending. That's her au revoir.
The first thing we got to think about...
...is what the public thinks
in the middle of an election.
Take charge of this one for me, okay?
If you care about my health.
You're the only around here I can trust.
Greer's a good investigator, but I'd prefer
someone I'm used to working with.
Lipranzer.
Whatever you want.
Just catch me a bad guy.
So, I'm here.
What the hell was she doing with a B file?
Bribery of elected officials.
The case number is on her computer.
But the case itself isn't among
the papers in her files.
Why? Did she take it home? What?
Maybe it was taken?
Check the apartment.
What do you got here?
Bunch of pictures of a dead lady.
- No weapon found, yet?
- Nada.
It's a weird one.
She was strangled by the ropes
but by the way he tied her...
...it's like he put himself
between her legs and pumped...
...so they tightened up like he was trying
to let his weight strangle her.
Like he was trying to fuck her to death.
Look at the next one.
Check the computer for sex offenders
and cross match on Carolyn's name...
...or this business with the ropes.
Find out which of the creeps she put away
is out on parole.
I never did understand why you put her
in charge of rape and all that sicko shit.
She wanted it. And she was good.
Yeah, too good, maybe.
I'm not grabbing this, yet.
You worked with this broad.
She wouldn't leave her fucking door
and windows wide open.
She was drinking with him. She gave him
a glass of beer, like she was entertaining.
- Fingerprints on the glass?
- Yeah.
Greer sent it down to the lab.
You mean somebody she let in opened
the windows so it looked like a break-in?
She wasn't going to let some sex maniac
she sent to jail in for a beer.
On the other hand, we're talking Carolyn.
Mac...
...tell me what Carolyn Polhemus
was doing with a bribery file.
I had no idea Carolyn was interested
in crimes above the waist.
It's on her computer,
but not on mine or the department's.
That makes no sense.
Why don't you ask Raymond?
Ready for something else?
Molto's left.
His secretary came back from lunch
and found his desk cleaned out.
Exercise?
Masturbation.
The refuge of the lonely housewife.
Missed the 8:35. I tried to call,
but you weren't here.
Nat had dinner at Josh's,
and I was at the university.
I tried to get in a little extra time
on the mainframe.
Get anything done?
Who am I kidding?
Still working on my dissertation at my age.
It's ridiculous.
You were the best mathematician
in your class.
Second best just made
full professor at MIT.
All I've made are beds.
And now, the Channel Six local news.
Carolyn Polhemus, assistant prosecuting
attorney in Raymond Horgan's office...
...was found brutally murdered
in her Southside apartment.
Police are about to release a statement
about the circumstances of her death...
You hear?
Eugenia was thrilled to be messenger
of bad tidings.
Yeah, I'll bet.
From top to bottom
we are riddled with cruelty.
We must expose and punish it...
...especially when inflicted
upon the impotent and the ignored.
You sound like a woman with a mission.
I am.
The murder of Ms. Polhemus...
You have a suspect?
We have diddly-shit.
So Dan Lipranzer and Rusty Sabich
will work night and day for two weeks...
...to catch Raymond a killer.
That's the strategy.
You're in charge of this investigation?
Raymond insisted I take it on.
With 150 lawyers, they couldn't find one
who didn't fuck her to put in charge?
Did you tell Raymond?
This is a conflict of interest.
Is that professional?
Barbara, I'm Raymond's chief deputy.
You are so predictable.
It's your way of reliving the whole thing.
She's dead and you're still obsessing.
Rusty.
Nico.
She was just...
- Splendid.
- That's it. Very good.
Raymond's pressing hard
on that case, I imagine.
Raymond presses hard on every case, Nico.
You know who would've been hard
to beat? You.
You would've been tough. Very tough.
You are really something.
Where's Tommy Molto?
Molto?
I thought he'd come to the funeral
of his favorite colleague.
You must really have him scrambling.
Judge.
Who's that with Raymond?
I'm told that's her ex-husband.
I didn't know she had one.
Teaches college someplace.
Carolyn Polhemus worked for me.
I hired her...
...over the objections of...
...many of our prosecutors
who felt shejust didn't have the stuff.
I see those prosecutors here today...
...along with thejudges she defied...
...and the defense attorneys she defeated.
Why are they all here?
They're here because Carolyn Polhemus
stood for something.
She stood forjustice.
The Prosecutor's Office,
under my leadership...
...has a conviction rate of over 91 percent.
Mr. Della Guardia, or...
...as he is known to those of us
who have had to work with him, "Delay"...
There's food here for 100 people.
A lot of no-shows.
They smell a loser.
- Good speech.
- What the hell is happening with Carolyn?
Everything's in the works.
I reassigned her cases, and this afternoon
I gotta deal with Molto's stuff.
What's with this reassignment shit?
Goddamn it, Rusty!
I told you to give this investigation
top priority.
Nico is eating me alive with this thing.
The election is in ten days.
If you don't find Carolyn's killer,
we are both history.
Turn all of that administrative bullshit
to Mac.
Mac has more than she can handle.
And let me remind you,
we lost two key PA's in one day.
You only have time for the election.
I've got to run the office.
Fuck the office!
Don't you see what's happening?
If you don't find me a killer,
there is no fucking office!
I want you right on top
of Carolyn's case, understand?
Run out every ground ball and do it
in an orderly goddamned fashion!
Start acting like a fucking professional!
The campaign is a total disaster.
Haven't taken a poll in two weeks.
We don't know where the hell we are.
You're ten minutes late
for the bar meeting on criminal procedure.
Call them and tell them I'm on my way.
Did you assign a bribery case to Carolyn?
There's a file missing.
Loretta, find my driver.
Tell him to be ready to leave.
She had a case on her computer
we can't account for.
It was logged in as a B file.
Nobody knows where it came from.
Nobody knows where it went.
Where the hell is my speech?
It was right here on my desk.
Cody has it.
You're giving me a runaround.
Cody, pull the car around.
I'll meet you down in front.
Give me a straight answer, will you, Boss?
There's the B file, Tiger.
Read it, and we'll talk.
"Dear Mr. Horgan.
"This is about a deputy prosecuting
attorney who is taking bribes.
"Five years ago,
a person I'll call 'Noel' got arrested.
"I gave him $1,500 to pay somebody off.
"We went out to North Branch.
A secretary who seemed to know Noel...
"...took him into the PA's office, where
a man he could not see talked behind him.
"Ten days later, Noel went to court
and a lawyer from the PA's office...
"...told the judge that
the case was dismissed.
"I can't remember the lawyer's name.
I hope you get him.
"I hope you get Noel, too.
He has let me down."
- Unsigned.
Five years ago.
That guy must write real slow.
"Noel equals Leon."
This is Carolyn's handwriting.
Looks like she went to North Branch
to see Kenneally.
You'll love what I got from Painless.
There's this guy's semen
inside her vagina...
...but there's nothing outside.
Painless figures she didn't spend
much time on her feet after sex.
He says, normally,
he'd see the guy's little thingies...
...swimming upstream in the womb,
when he looked under the microscope.
Instead, this guy's was all dead.
Nothing went nowhere.
So Painless figures he's sterile.
He's got blood type A.
My very own.
I thought of that. But you got a kid.
Anything from hair or fiber?
No hair or skin fragments under her nails.
Carolyn would've fought back.
Maybe she was playing sex games
with the wrong guy.
The rope is K-Mart, Sears, Walgreen's.
You name it.
They found carpet fibers
from some other location. Zorak V.
It's only the biggest seller.
You call the Fingerprint Lab
on the bar glass?
Oh, I forgot.
You are a class-A fuck-up, you know?
They ain't going to expedite it for me.
I got the phone company printout
on her apartment.
I notice that one of the numbers
that comes up is yours a number of times.
At the office.
We were working cases together.
No, she's calling your home.
She never called me at home.
I made these calls...
...to Barbara from Carolyn's apartment.
"Late again, kid."
"This trial's a bitch.
I'll catch dinner in town."
I'd just as soon you'd let it go.
If Barbara sees a phone company
subpoena, now, she'll bust a gut.
Under the circumstances,
if you don't mind...
...l'd appreciate it.
I gave Barbara...
...enough pain.
Polhemus was bad news.
Know what they're calling you
and your partner downtown?
Spare me.
"Mission lmpossible."
Guerasch, bring that shit in my office.
So you're figuring what? The guy
she was having cocktails with did her?
I figure it was somebody who knew
what he wanted it to look like.
Cop. PA. A private dick.
Remember that lady PA
who was here four months ago?
Yeah, nice set of lungs.
This kid's gonna make a copper.
Never forgets a bra size.
He wants to know
what she was looking for.
She was looking for someone
by the name of Noel.
It took me a week to find this crap.
Five years back,
they booked 150 a day then.
Public indecency.
They were cleaning out the faggots.
Back when Raymond got some balls
for a day and a half.
- She find anything?
- I don't know.
When I gave these files to her,
they were in nice order.
The bitch just trashed them.
She never gave a shit
about anybody else's work.
One's completely missing. Look.
See right here? It skips a number.
Tommy Molto been looking at these?
What does Molto have to do with this?
Would there still be a court file
on this case?
That far back, it'd have to be in storage
on microfilm by now.
You don't want to say
what this is about, maybe?
Gee, Lionel, I can't.
She used to ask about you, you know.
Five, six years ago when she worked
out here as a probation officer.
- Five years ago I didn't know her.
- Sure you did.
The night you brought the Night Saints in.
You were hot stuff. A regular fucking hero.
Breaking the meanest guy
this side of Watts.
There was a lot of talk
you'd end up in Horgan's job.
She wanted to know what you were like.
I told her you didn't fuck around.
Dad, look who's here.
- How are you?
- Good. Mom's in a good mood.
How'd you know I'd be on this ferry?
Took a chance.
How was your day?
Well, I figured out today,
it's ten years this week...
...that I'm working on my dissertation.
I thought we'd celebrate.
Going to take us to dinner?
Why don't you just give up
on that dissertation?
It makes you miserable.
Your mom's not a giver-upper.
Maybe that's her problem.
I sure wouldn't do math unless I had to.
You got my genes in the math department.
If not for your mom,
I'd still be taking algebra.
I had to be good at something.
You were good at everything.
School.
Did you ever cheat?
Like borrow someone else's homework?
Copy it and pretend it was mine?
Why do I have the feeling that question
has some personal relevance?
I didn't say I did.
It's all right, kid.
It's good to see you guys happy.
Pretty.
It's new.
It's very pretty.
Mr. Polhemus? I'm Rusty Sabich.
Seems so strange to be talking about her
after all these years.
You hadn't had much contact
with her, then?
None since she left.
What about her family?
I have no idea where she came from.
She lied her way into the university.
Made up some kind of background.
She was very good at playing roles.
When she left me, I lost all pride.
I begged her not to leave.
The last time she looked at me,
it was with disgust.
Disgust that somebody she'd looked up to
could be so weak.
At that moment, I had the most
desperate wish that she were dead.
Maybe she made a man feel like that
who actually acted on his fantasy.
Would you like to see what she looked like
at that time?
Yes, I would.
They were taken at about the time
we were married.
This isn't just work?
No.
On the Polhemus thing, what the fuck
is happening to the fingerprints report?
Don't give me that computer crap!
You know I don't understand that shit.
They want to know how big a field
you want it run against?
We could do convicted felons...
...anybody ever fingerprinted,
county employees, etc.
Just do felons.
We'll do the rest if we need them.
Do them all. I may never get back on.
Do everybody. How soon?
What the fuck takes a week?
The man has the biggest murder case
in the city...
...and he has to kiss your ring?
I know. I know.
We don't have jurisdiction
over the computer.
- A week. Probably ten days.
- I need them yesterday.
I'll push, but I don't think
you'll see them any sooner.
Have your copper get the glass back
from Evidence and down to the lab...
...in case they need it for anything.
Ah, Mr. Sabich.
Real important stuff.
We got the chief deputy with us.
Lipranzer and I were wondering,
on your report...
...are you indicating the guy bashed her
after she was strangled by the ropes?
Read the fucking report.
This report?
No, not that report. My report.
The autopsy.
See anything with bruises on the wrists...
...bruises on the ankles,
bruises on the knees?
Are you saying she was raped
and then tied up?
Tied up last, yeah.
She already died
from multiple head injuries.
Rape? Now I'm thinking...
...no.
Why?
Read the fucking report.
- This report?
- No.
This report? The chemist's report?
Yeah, the chemist's report.
She had a two percent solution
of nonoxynol-9 in her vagina.
A spermicide used with a diaphragm.
That's why his sperms were dead.
Diaphragm? You missed a diaphragm
in the autopsy?
No. You've been to autopsies.
You slice her wide open.
No diaphragm in that lady.
What happened to it?
Somebody took it.
I think it's a setup.
This man...
...is her lover. He comes over.
They have drinks.
This lady has intercourse with him.
Real nice. Okay?
But he's an angry guy.
Picks up something, kills her.
Tries to make it look like rape.
Ties her up.
Pulls out the diaphragm.
That's what I think.
What does Tommy Molto think?
You got his phone number right there.
Want to jot it down in case you need it?
Next time you talk to him...
...tell him to call me so I can find out...
...what's going on
in my own fucking investigation.
Painless...
...you tell Molto, and you tell Nico, too...
...that this is cheap, cheap politics.
Cheap Police Department bullshit.
God better help them and help you, too.
I can't make a case for tampering.
Our poll shows Della Guardia's leading
Horgan by four percent. Eight days left.
At least it's made somebody happy.
I don't want to see you out of here.
Come on, pal. We're old news.
I'd miss you. Who else here can talk
morality and ethics and not break me up?
Voters smell an exhausted man who's lost
sight of all the important issues.
Issues? Bullshit.
The only issue is Raymond Horgan
has respect for the law...
...and Nico Della Guardia will fuck the law
for politics. That's the issue.
Rusty...
Have you ever been to an Irish wake?
Come on over and pull up a glass.
Know what Della Guardia
is going to find out?
You run for office because...
...you think you can make people do things,
make things better.
But you can't.
Nobody can.
You get a few potholes filled,
keep the lid on the best way you can.
But in the end...
...all you can do is try to hang on
to the fucking job.
I never used to drink when I started here.
Then, you still believed
you could make a difference.
Funny, part of me still does.
A guy as tough as you are...
...you're still hanging on
to the shreds of your ideals.
The shreds are all I got.
You're a good man, Rusty.
God bless you.
So, tell me, who's our bad guy?
It could be a boyfriend.
Some guy she picked up.
Whoever it is knew enough about her
to know what to make it look like.
Could be a law-enforcement type.
Jesus.
One of us.
You and Carolyn have a thing?
Don't beat around the bush.
Just come right out and ask the question.
I'll say that the decedent and I
were both single and both adults.
I had a thing with her.
She thought like everybody else thought...
...that I wasn't going to run again.
That I could just hand the mantle over
to anyone I chose...
...so why not a broad?
Why not her?
One more question?
I gave her the B file
because she asked me for it.
Because I was fucking her.
Stupid, huh?
She went over to Northside...
...shoveled through the records.
There wasn't anything there.
At least that's what she told me.
What are you going to do now?
Once the party's over?
I don't know.
I got an idea.
Suppose we try to get you on the bench.
I should still have enough clout
to pull that off. What do you say?
Why don't we just see
what the future holds.
Would that have satisfied her?
What's that?
A judgeship.
I wonder if a judgeship
would've satisfied Carolyn Polhemus.
Rusty!
Come say hello to Carolyn Polhemus.
Have you met?
I've seen Rusty.
I want to bring Carolyn on board
as a prosecuting attorney.
She's been working probation, Northside,
and she just passed her bar exam.
Congratulations.
Thank you.
She comes very highly recommended.
Why don't we see if we can find
a nice place for her.
I'd like the Index Division.
That's not a job, it's a jail sentence.
Rape, sex crimes, child molestation.
We can do better than that.
It's hard to get a conviction on a rape.
It's a dead-end for someone ambitious.
So you get the worst attorneys
trying the hardest cases?
Listen to this. We got another idealist
in the office.
He's five years old.
The doctors found 23 healed fractures
from old wounds.
Victim of his own beloved mother.
I need your help.
Your wife called.
Why don't you fire her?
Civil service. They're here forever.
Why don't you give this to Nancy.
You haven't had experience with kids.
Nancy's not available.
And, besides,
I'd like to try this case myself.
With your help.
Outline it for me.
About a month ago...
...the mother brought him
into the West End Pavilion Hospital.
The boy was unconscious
from severe head injuries.
She said he fell.
The doctor says...
...the head wounds were too symmetrical
to be the result of a fall.
He told me...
...he was treating a child whose mother
had crushed his head in a vise.
We have any proof it was the mother?
You got the vise?
Just the testimony of the child.
When he sees the mother in
the courtroom, he'll recant. An iffy case.
I've examined him several times and...
...I think he's begun to trust me.
Look, how many child abuse cases
does this office handle in a year?
Over a thousand.
Every one of them terrible.
Every one of them heartbreaking.
But I can't stop everything else
to take care of one case.
You're going to have to get somebody else
to help you.
You don't like me, do you?
I think you've turned out to be
a damn good prosecutor.
You're angry I didn't have to go
through the channels like everyone else.
Clearly, you're not like everyone else.
You think I got this job because
I fucked some fat-cat friend of Raymond's.
Look, it's late...
Come on, I'll drive you to your ferry.
This is not the way to the ferry.
I want you to meet somebody.
Wendell, this is Rusty Sabich.
He's a very important man in our office.
He's going to help me
when we go to court.
Remember what I told you about court?
Yeah.
Now, tell me.
There's a judge and some nice people.
They're called a jury.
And you're gonna ask me questions.
About what?
About what happened.
When?
When I got hurt.
What else did I tell you?
You said that if I told what Mommy did...
...the judge and the nice people
will protect me...
...and Mommy wouldn't hurt me anymore.
Do you think you can do that?
Answer my questions in court?
And tell what Mommy did to you?
I think you can.
Mommy will be there.
She can't hurt you.
She can't even talk to you.
You'll be completely safe.
You promise?
I promise.
His father got to him last night.
Told him God would put him in hell
if he testified against his mother.
He's terrified.
If you're not ready, we'll ask the judge
for a couple more days.
No.
We've got to do it now
or we'll lose him for good.
Your mommy took you to the hospital
because you were hurt.
What part of you was hurt?
My head.
How was it hurt?
Wendell, how did you hurt your head?
I don't remember.
Have you ever seen this?
Yes.
Where?
- In the cellar.
- At home?
Yes.
Did somebody put your head inside it?
Wendell?
What did you say when somebody
put your head in the vise?
You told me you screamed
when your head was put in the vise.
Remember?
You told me.
"I promise...
"...l'll be a good boy.
"I'll be a good boy."
Did somebody answer?
Mommy.
Mommy said I was a bad boy
and I deserved to die.
And then what did Mommy do?
She made it tighter and tighter.
On your head?
She hurt my head.
My mommy hurt my head.
No further questions, Your Honor.
The doctors have told us...
...that the wounds...
...that Wendell suffered
could not have come from a fall...
...as the defense would have you believe.
The police told us they found a vise
at the home of the defendant.
Medical experts have testified...
...that the size and the shape
of the jaws of that vise...
...exactly match the size and the shape
of the wounds to the little boy's head.
And this evidence is clear...
...and uncontested.
But the most compelling evidence
in this trial...
...comes not from doctors,
or police officers...
...or other expert witnesses.
The most damning testimony...
...comes from an abused
and frightened child...
...who overcame his fear and his pain...
...to tell you, in his own words...
...what really happened.
If you're to remember nothing else
as you begin your deliberations...
...remember Wendell's words:
"My mommy hurt my head."
Congratulations.
It's gonna be so good.
You're still in love with her.
It was never love.
What was it, then?
What did she have
to make you feel so much?
Ladies and gentlemen...
...Raymond Horgan.
Thank you. Thank you.
I wanted to come down
and say a few words...
...before I call Mr. Della Guardia
and congratulate him on his victory.
No, no, no. Come on.
Of all the wonderful things
that have happened to me in 12 years...
...the best has been...
...knowing and working with all ofyou.
Wait till you hear what's going down.
It's strange.
Someone's fucked up over at the Hall.
It's way wrong.
- Why?
- I get a message.
I'm supposed to be in the chief's office
8:00 tomorrow to be interviewed.
By Molto.
No discussion. Interview.
It's like they're after me, right?
Another thing. When I came back tonight...
...they took all the receipts
of the evidence I inventoried on Polhemus.
No questions asked.
Sounds like you're off the case.
Sure. Fine, but figure this in.
I'm at the North Branch before 5:00,
going through the microfilm.
All of this hits by 6:00, 6:30.
Look what I picked up
while I was out there.
The case number matches
the complaint number...
...that was missing
when you saw Kenneally.
Five years ago. Bingo.
And look who's listed
as Leon's probation officer.
"Carolyn Polhemus."
Wait. Here's the best.
Who do you think was the deputy
handling the case?
Tommy Molto.
You keep this because I don't know
what the fuck is happening with me.
Tommy Molto.
Tommy Molto once worked here,
but we think he might be dead.
Raymond's inside.
We've been waiting for you.
Rusty.
Molto and Delay...
...have questions about
the Polhemus investigation.
This should not be handled this way.
You should speak with Rusty alone.
What's this about?
You were at Carolyn's apartment
the night she was killed.
Bullshit.
What was it, a Tuesday night?
Barbara was at the university.
I was babysitting.
Keep your fucking mouth shut.
We got the fingerprint results...
...the ones that you could never remember
to ask for.
They're your prints all over the bar glass.
Yours, Rozat K. Sabich.
Five feet from where the woman
was found dead.
Or maybe you didn't remember
that all county employees get printed.
This is absurd.
The phone records
you told Lipranzer not to get?
We had the phone company
pull them this morning.
You were calling her all month.
There's a call from your house
to hers that night.
My God, you're serious.
Tommy, for Christ's sake!
Sabich.
I want you to know one thing. I know.
Sure you do.
Go ahead, play cool. I know.
You killed her. You're the guy.
Oh, yeah?
Yeah, you're right. You're always right.
They think I killed her.
They're going to charge me.
Don't be seen with me, man.
They'll fucking bury you.
I'm sorry. I didn't mean to scare you.
Are you sick?
Nico and Molto are charging me
with Carolyn's murder.
They found my fingerprints
on a glass of beer in her apartment.
What does this mean?
Grand jury investigation.
They will or they won't indict me.
If they do, there'll be a trial.
It's not going to go that far.
I'm going to need a lawyer.
A very, very good lawyer.
Expensive lawyer.
It could break us financially.
We can mortgage the house.
Or sell it if we have to.
What time does Nat get home?
Nat?
Oh, Rusty!
A lot ofpeople think Raymond
shouldn't run again.
If he agrees to step aside, the party
will let him decide who will take his place.
They know he won't hand it all to Nico.
That's for sure.
Who would he choose?
Somebody from the office.
Carry on his traditions.
You?
Mac, maybe.
She'd make a great candidate,
in that wheelchair.
That chair is not very telegenic.
I think he'd pick you.
You're the natural.
Rusty...
...if you let him know you want it,
it'll be you.
I should just tell Raymond his time is up?
- You could be tactful.
- No.
Why not?
I'm not going to bite that hand.
If Raymond wants out, that's up to him.
He's still the best candidate around,
against Della Guardia.
Without Raymond,
Nico doesn't have an issue.
Pull the party's people and Raymond's
people together behind somebody else...
...that person would walk
into the PA's office.
It wouldn't be close.
You've thought a lot about this.
He just needs a push.
Push him yourself. It's not in me.
What?
Were you all set on being chief deputy?
Carolyn...
...if I can get away tonight
shall I get some take-out?
I like you, Rusty, but I think it's over.
It's just not right for me now. It's over.
I don't accept that.
You don't accept it?
Do I have a say?
I don't want us to end up enemies.
Mac said it was all right.
Have it your way.
Someone's in my office.
What is it, Rusty?
I wanted to talk about this rapist
you habitualized.
There's some problems.
I'm late for an appointment.
I would appreciate it
if you could put it in a memo.
You keep avoiding me.
You communicate through memos.
You skip meetings I'm supposed to go to.
It's affecting work.
My work?
My work.
I tried to make it easier for you.
You make me feel uncomfortable.
I just want to be with you.
Can't we just talk about it?
I'm involved with someone else.
Since when?
What is it you want from me?
What do I have to do?
Grow up.
Rozat K. Sabich?
Rusty, I don't like to be here.
A search warrant for these premises.
Come on in.
They're taking swatches from your suits.
They'll try to match threads
from my clothing and the carpet...
...with fibers they might find
at her apartment.
They're not looking for a murder weapon?
I wouldn't be stupid enough
to bring it home.
If they look for it and don't find it,
they'll have to admit that in court.
I'll have to give a blood sample.
If you refuse?
They've got a warrant.
It's all routine.
I'm going to ask Sandy Stern
to take my case.
Hi, Sandy.
I realize you would like to avoid
public places at a time like this...
...but I don't think it is wise
for you to go into hiding.
I'm flattered that you want me
to represent you in this case.
You have been my toughest adversary.
Did you get my subpoena
from the grand jury?
This morning.
Clearly, we will not let you testify.
Sandy, you expect me
to take the Fifth Amendment?
Of course.
That I cannot do.
You don't want to prepare the prosecutor
by giving him pretrial statements.
Sandy, I don't think this case
is ever going to go to trial.
If I take the Fifth and refuse to testify
before the grand jury...
...it could destroy my reputation.
The results of the blood tests
have come back.
They have identified you as someone
who secretes A-type antibodies...
...just like the man who had last been
with Ms. Polhemus.
Chances of this being a coincidence
are one in ten.
So, I believe you will be charged
and that you will go to trial.
Have you anything to tell this grand jury
about the death of Carolyn Polhemus?
On the advice of counsel,
I decline to answer.
Wouldn't it be fair to say you were rather
well acquainted with Ms. Polhemus?
On the advice of counsel,
I decline to answer.
Weren't you, in fact,
intimate with the lady?
On the advice of counsel,
I decline to answer.
You are under arrest.
"You have the right to remain silent.
"Anything you say can and will
be used against you.
"You have the right to have a lawyer
present during questioning.
"If you cannot hire a lawyer,
one will be appointed to represent you.
"You may stop answering questions
at any time."
Do you understand the rights
I have explained to you?
Call Sandy Stern to make bail.
Sandy should be available in a few hours.
Let's see what they got.
Can't believe there could be
any more surprises.
That's when they come.
That's why they're called surprises.
Do we now understand
Della Guardia's case?
Yes, I think I do.
Let me hear it.
Sabich is obsessed with Polhemus.
She ditches him for another man.
Sabich becomes enraged.
He can't let go.
One night, knowing his wife is out...
...he calls her and begs her
to see him again.
Carolyn finally agrees.
She rolls around with him
for auld lang syne.
Then something goes wrong.
Sabich is jealous. He wants more
than she's willing to give.
He blows it.
Gives her what for
with some heavy instrument.
Decides to make it look like rape.
Sabich is a prosecutor,
knows there'll be dozens of suspects.
He ties her up.
Opens the latches to make it look
like someone slipped in.
And this is the diabolical part...
...pulls out her diaphragm
so it looks like rape.
But in his haste and confusion,
he makes mistakes.
He forgets the glass he drank from.
He doesn't think the forensic chemist
will be able to ID the spermicide.
But we know he did evil to this woman...
...because he lied about his presence
in her apartment the night she was killed.
His fingerprints on the glass...
...his blood type A identified from semen...
...fibers from the carpets in his home,
tell us he was there.
Very convincing.
But their evidence of motive is weak.
That's where we must attack.
Is there any proof of prior
amorous relationship between the two?
A few telephone calls.
They can be accounted for
by business needs.
- Any diary?
- No.
No note that came with flowers?
No lovers' correspondence?
- No.
- Good.
Gossip will not be admitted.
There are calls from my home to Carolyn's
in October of last year.
You were trying the case
of Wendell McGaffney then.
Reason enough for calling her.
Why did I tell Lipranzer not to get
my home phone records?
I take it for granted that a person
of an innocent state of mind...
...would rule himself out as a suspect...
...and save a busy detective
from wasting time.
Clearly, they hope to win the case
on the strength of their physical evidence.
I'd like to look at that glass.
It could help me.
List a motion for production
of physical evidence.
I want an inventory of everything
in that apartment.
Where's the contraceptive jelly...
...the chemist is saying he finds present?
In her medicine cabinet?
I don't know.
I'll hear worse in court.