Agent Junod? I got a call for you.
It's Wilson.
What's up Wilson?
On the corner of Sunnyside and
10th Avenue there's a diner.
Meet me there at 7 pm.
I'll tell you everything I know.
Get on the radio.
Tell him we're coming over.
Follow us.
Show me what you got.
He won't talk.
You know what?
I'm gonna use the drug.
No! Sullivan said no.
You're in a graveyard, Wilson.
And if you don't tell us
what we wanna know...
you are gonna be buried here.
So tell me, who was your contact?
Who were you going
to meet at the diner?
He won't talk.
Who were you meeting
at the diner?
What?
Wilson, we can't move the drug
unless we know what you said.
What did you tell
the FBI, Wilson?
He's coming out of it.
- What did you tell the FBI?
- We've got to keep him alive.
Stop moving.
If you talked
we can't move the drug...
and then nobody gets paid.
Hold him!
Shit!
That stuff really works, man!
- Do you want me to wait?
- No. No.
I'll be fine.
I'm gonna do this.
I'll do this.
There's no other
place left, Dean.
- I'm gonna do it.
- Ok.
Eventually.
I'm just kidding.
- I love you.
- I love you back.
All cars in the vicinity of
Sunnyside and 98th...
please respond to an 11-80.
That's Sunnyside and 98th, 11-80.
I still have those dreams.
But it's not as I was then.
It's as I am now. I'm 53.
I'm out in the bush,
out of shape, overweight...
a big, fat and immobile target.
A lot of guys had
a lot worse than me.
And they're fine.
Why can't I do that?
Why do I have to keep coming
here to feel any better?
What about you, Dean?
It's your first time.
You wanna share?
Yeah. My name is Dean Cage.
And... I was in Bosnia.
Guess it's a small war compared to what
some of you guys have been through.
There ain't no
small war, brother.
No. I guess there isn't.
My friend, Amy...
she's actually technically
more like my... brother's...
Well, she's my best friend's sister.
You know, she and I...
it's kinda complicated.
Anyway, she suggested
that I come.
Dean, they're pouring gasoline on me.
Because I'm...
The bastards are gonna burn me!
- I'm kinda stuck.
- They're gonna burn me, Dean.
They're gonna burn me.
If it's alright with you guys,
since it's my first time here...
I'd like to just sit
this one out...
and listen if it's okay
with you guys.
Of course it is, Dean.
What the hell happened?
The trucker says a gurney
came flying out of an ambulance,
that John Doe over there,
riding it like a bronco.
The bastard took an up close
tour of each tire.
- Is this the ambulance?
- No, another one.
Where is it?
That's the thing.
The ambulance kept going.
What?
- Does this make sense to anybody?
- Not yet.
Can you make out
these letters here?
What is that, an "M"?
"N", "V"? I don't know.
So, you wanna tell me about it?
Did you fuck up?
Who told you to interrogate him
after the injection?
Lietch, would you put
your piece to his head, please?
Do as I ask, please.
You think I like this?
Lietch doesn't like it,
I know you don't.
This is where we are,
because you...
despite all your training,
decided on actions...
that went outside the mission
parameters, do you understand?
- Yes.
- Wilson did say something.
The guy he was snitching to.
Supposed to have a meeting.
We know when and where.
Tonight...
diner, 7 o'clock.
You can lower your weapon now.
The point has been made.
Of course, Wilson can't tell us
what he told the Feds.
But the Federal agent he's been
snitching to can.
Well then, why don't we stick around
and see who should up for coffee and pie?
How did it go?
It's still going on.
Dean, you left?
You know, look.
These guys...
they're alright,
but they're kinda cuckoo.
I was thinking...
maybe we can meet up
at an out place.
There are some things
I wanna tell you.
I don't wanna tell them,
Meet me at the diner.
7 o'clock, ok?
I'll see you there, baby.
Alright. Bye.
MacNab...
Stay.
Peterson, I want you
out in the street
- Why?
Because MacNab
will be doing the id...
and I want Lietch to drive.
You got a problem with that?
Good. So take up
his position.
Come here.
So what's this stuff gonna do?
What's it gonna do?
It's gonna make us very rich.
This is about all you need
to worry right now.
Have you used one of these?
- No.
- Look and learn.
You load it exactly like
you load a gun.
Lock it up.
Hypodermics. Eight of them.
You stick it in his arm, his leg.
Doesn't matter where.  Bang.
You clear?
Let's do it.
We id him then we wait.
You take him down outside,
you understand?
Outside when you inject him.
You do not talk to him.
Not a word.
- You got it?
- I got it.
Let's rock and roll.
- Hi.
- One for dinner, please.
- Table 14 is open.
Thanks.
- Coffee?
- Great.
Thanks.
A new guest to the party,
coming in.
Right on time.
MacNab, hold tight.
It's him.
He's waiting for someone.
Let's make sure.
Right. OK.
Brilliant.
Alright. Here we go.
Look good.
- We're trying.
- The best as you can.
You look beautiful.
Ready?
One, two, three!
Dean!
Listen, MacNab, he's not
going anywhere. We wait.
Sullivan, I just got made.
Big time.
What do you mean 'made'? How can he
make you, you're on the street!
He's right. He's anxious and
scoping this place out like a pro.
- He's just made us too.
- We're not sure.
Fuck!
Damn it!
We're gonna have
to do this ugly.
MacNab, you're a go.
Compromised authority.
- Sorry pal, that seat is taken.
- I'm afraid not.
Wilson can't make it,
ever again.
Look buddy,
you got the wrong table.
This don't have to be messy.
I just got a few questions for you.
Sorry, left handed.
You see?
Now it's gonna get messy.
Get out of the way.
Hello?
How are you doing?
He's a runner, Lietch.
You're out of position.
Get in position.
Get out of the way!
Back it up.
We need to extract MacNab.
Are you ok, man?
Police officer!
Let me see your hands!
Get your hands in the air
and get on your knees!
Now!
Hands behind your head
and get on the ground.
I want you kissing the
pavement now.
Alright, down on the ground.
Take it easy.
Dean!
Move!
Come on!
What's with you, idiot?
You stupid moron!
Sullivan, we got him.
Turn him over.
Let's go.
Lift.
Apparently, Dean assaulted
another man outside...
before being picked up
by an ambulance.
We're calling hospitals.
This doesn't make sense.
You don't use a hypogun
as a weapon.
Look, I like Dean too.
He's a war hero.
He certainly got medals
to prove it.
But did you see
that guy's face?
So what? He just snapped,
is that it? Just went nuts?
You say like the possibility
has never occurred to you.
What is this?
Who are you guys?
I'm one of the guys that
Washington sent you to whack.
But we didn't like
that idea very much.
Peterson, do not talk to him.
Your instinct's right.
You should be scared.
Will you shut up?
Where is he?
Where's Scott?
Who the hell is Scott?
- Where does he think he is?
- What did you say to him?
Who's in charge here?
Detective Knight.
- Can I help you?
- Agent Junod. FBI.
You had a suspect here.
Where he's been booked?
Slow down. This is
my crime scene, alright?
- My town, my suspect.
- I'm sorry, my fault.
You're under the impression
I'm asking.
We're investigating the theft
of a prohibited narcotic...
from a government facility.
Our drugs, our facility,
our suspect.
No, you're gonna have
to do better than that.
If I get the right phone call
from the right person...
then we can talk.
I want the other one too.
The runner.
He's at a hospital, and he hasn't
been charged with anything.
You sure he's at a hospital?
Witnesses saw him being
picked up by an ambulance.
So yes, I'm sure.
Amy, why are you
messing with the Bureau?
Because they are here.
Why is the Bureau here?
You should not have brought
a body here.
How much time do we have, doctor?
- When did you inject him?
- About thirty minutes ago.
He's pretty beat up.
He weights what? 180, 190?
I'd say synapse failure and
death in six hours.
Let's get him inside.
And then he pulled that on me.
I know. He was the wrong guy
to ask.
No, I don't know what that is.
What is that?
What did you do to him?
Did you inject him?
With what?
I got news for you,
you cocky little prick.
You fucked with the wrong guy,
because when you fucked with him...
you fucked with me.
I'm gonna get what I need from you,
if I have to cut you open to find it.
- Still haven't got that phone call.
- I weighed you one better.
in writing.
Alright. Every 'i' dotted,
every 't' crossed.
I guess he's all yours then.
You'll have him as soon
as he's out of processing.
I want him now, Detective.
Well, that's a whole other
set of orders.
If you'd gotten here
a little quicker...
The runner from the diner,
Dean Cage, I checked him out.
- The guy is a Three Charlie.
- Jesus!
Pentagon trained spook...
Black Ops, Panama,
Iraq. Real bad ass.
This guy has toured the world
and left a wake of bodies behind.
- So what's going on now?
- He's a civilian now.
Discharged right after
his last Op.
A little wet job in Bosnia.
Complete failure.
Cage is the only member
of his team that came back.
The guy snapped.
He's a section 8.
- So who is he working for?
- Who cares?
We know where they are.
I say we move it on the hospital.
And if the package ain't there?
No, we stick to the plan.
This is the man who killed
your husband and children.
Would you like to know
where you can find him?
Hold up. What are you doing
with my suspect?
Stand down, detective. This is
no longer your concern.
What do you think? You think
you can walk in here...
flash your badge and I'm supposed
to give you a hand job, is that it?
Well, fuck you!
And fuck Hoover too,
I wanna talk to that man.
You ain't talking to no one.
You're a nuisance, an annoyance,
you're a mutt running around,
sniffing other dogs' butts.
- Go away.
- You're out of your league.
- These guys ain't FBI.
- What?
- You're talking?
- What did you say?
You have the balls
to open your mouth?
I'll talk to you.
I'll tell you whatever...
Fuck!
It's alright.
It's just the shoulder.
Somebody get me an ambulance.
Dean, can you hear me?
Can you hear me?
We've got someone who wants
to talk to you.
Someone you trust.
Your best friend.
Alright, shit, it's me man.
It's me. Fuck...
Scott?
They need to know what Wilson
told you about the shipment.
It's not a big deal.
They just need to know...
Did he tell you where they
were shipping it out from?
I don't know what
you're talking about.
Did Wilson tell you where
they were picking up the XE?
I don't understand.
If you don't tell them...
what Wilson told you,
they're going to kill me.
Scott...
you're already dead.
I'm right here. You can see me,
I'm talking to you.
What did Wilson tell you?
What did he tell you
about the shipment?
What do you know about
the goddamn shipment, Dean?
Dean Cage,
United States Army...
1-9-0-4-0-5-2-4-3.
Dean Cage,
U. S. Army...
- 1-9-0-4-0-5...
- Son of a bitch.
What the fuck is going on here?
What is this?
We told him you're
his best friend.
- His best friend is dead.
- Now he thinks we killed him.
Hold on.
Give me a sec.
- How are you feeling? Does it hurt?
- Fuck you!
Where did you get that?
You don't share with us,
we don't share with you.
You're not FBI,
who the hell are you?
- CIA.
- Spooks working domestic.
Now that's illegal.
- We're on the same side.
- No.
Somebody injected this shit
into my friend.
I'm on his side.
Your friend?
My friend, my family.
You're fucking with my family.
What is this shit?
It's called XE,
as in "experimental".
What does it do?
If I inject you with this...
can I make you shoot
somebody at the police station?
Yes.
You can control the subject
with a simple suggestion.
And it's fatal.
Total synapse failure from
6 to 8 hours of injection.
Is there an antidote?
- We don't have it.
- Who does?
Alright!
Sullivan has the antigen.
- Who's Sullivan?
- He's former Agency.
He used the XE for
hostile interrogations.
He was impressed.
He decided he could make
more by selling it.
He went after the whole
batch and he got it.
Where can I find him?
Where?
I don't know.
Let him go.
What did he say?
Cut him down.
Cut him down or I'll kill
every one of you motherfuckers.
- Cut who down, Dean?
- Don't say another word to him.
Is he talking about his buddy?
You said his buddy was dead.
You have to understand
something here.
This is the most powerful
hallucinogen the world's ever seen.
His susceptibility to suggestion
is almost total...
but his mind will still
take him places.
I don't understand.
Something was said to him before
you brought him to me.
It's total reality,
but in his mind...
- I'm gonna kill every one of you.
- Future tense, past tense...
OK. You mentioned Scott.
Now Scott is dead.
- Still he says...
- Cut him down.
He's reliving something now.
This is a memory.
- He's reliving a memory.
- What is it a memory of?
Dean Cage,
U. S. Army.
I say he was captured, him and
this man named Scott.
Out in the field
they were captured.
Something was said to him
before you brought him to me.
You didn't bring me
a clean subject.
Peterson.
What exactly did you say to him
before you brought him here?
I told him we were the guys
Washington has sent him to whack.
Great. Because that has
triggered something...
and now he thinks we're
about to kill his friend Scott.
He said he's already dead.
Not anymore, he doesn't.
At least not in his mind.
Why couldn't you keep your mouth
shut like I asked you to?
Let me raise his heart rate
a little bit...
just give it a little bump. These
floors are completely sound proof.
Doesn't matter how loud
it gets.
Whatever.
Just get me what I want.
I'll get you what you want.
I don't mind doing this
the hard way.
- We got more on that ambulance.
- What?
He used his chrome box to change the
traffic lights all the way to Catonsville.
Where did it go?
We lost it when it got off
the beltway, but we got its id.
St. Nevis Hospital. It's a private
facility. Psychiatric.
Psychiatric?
- Dean...
- Cut him down.
Listen, I wanna
get this straight.
Cut him down.
You want us to let
Scott go, is that it?
- Cut him down.
- We'll cut him down.
Cut Scott down.
He doesn't have to die again.
Just tell us what
we wanna know.
Is it safe to move the XE?
I don't know. I told you I don't
know anything about any XE.
Do the Feds know where
we're moving the XE?
Don't make me kill him.
I don't know what
you're talking about.
You don't know what I'm
talking about?
- Are you sure?
- Fuck it, I don't know.
You don't know?
OK. Have it your way.
Kill him. Kill him.
Go kill Scott.
Rip his fucking throat out. We're
gonna make this prick watch.
Mr. Sullivan?
I'm sorry to disturb you,
but we got a situation down here.
Mr. Sullivan?
We got a couple of cops
wanting to get in.
Wanna tell me what I should do?
Are you coming down or what?
Give me a couple of minutes.
I'm gonna have to let them in.
Here we go.
Detective Knight.
My partner, Detective Miller.
My supervisor will be
right down.
We didn't ask
to see a supervisor.
Make it hurt.
Fuck you.
This is all your fault.
Kill him.
Kill Scott.
You fucked up.
Sullivan...
we have a problem.
Whatever it is,
it can wait.
Open it.
Hi, I'm the hospital administrator.
How can I help you?
Clear.
Are you quite sure it was
one of our vehicles, right?
That's a little strange.
I didn't hear anything
about accidents tonight.
Would they concern you
with such information?
Absolutely.
I'm very hands on here.
Can we see that ambulance?
- Sure, if you think it's important.
- I do.
Shit! Did I do that?
I don't see any signs
of any accidents.
Where's the other ambulance?
The other one? It's been on
the shop for over a week now.
I've got a better idea.
The whole place is on fire.
The drug. The drug.
Right.
Alright. Let's try this.
You're on fire.
We'll put that fire
out for you.
There's lots of water down here.
Come on down.
We'll put it out for you.
What the fuck...
Goddamn it!
You're free!
What the hell is he doing?
He thinks the whole place
is on fire.
There's one in there.
He's saving the patients.
Have you seen my pony?
He's white.
If anything comes to mind,
anything at all.
- Sure.
- Thanks for your time.
Put your hands over your head
and surrender your weapon.
You won't be harmed.
Place your weapon on the ground
and put your hands over your head.
Put your weapon on the ground
and your hands over your head.
Amy?
Don't fire.
Do not fire.
Don't fire! Officer
needs assistance.
Hold your fire!