Helmwige! Here! Bring your horse
Tether your stallion
next to my mare to graze
- Who is hanging from your saddle?
- Sintolt the Hegeling
Ortlinde's mare carries Wittig
the lrming
Sintolt and Wittig were always foes
The stallion is kicking at my mare
The hostility alienates the horses
Quiet, Bruno!
Siegrune, where have you lingered?
There was work to do
Are the others here?
Grimgerde and Rossweisse!
They are riding abreast
Greetings, you riders!
lnto the wood with your steeds
Keep the mares far apart ...
... until the hatred has subsided
My grey has already paid
for the heroes' anger
Welcome!
Were you together?
We were separate and met only today
lf we are all assembled ...
... let us set out for Valhalla
to bring Wotan his warriors
One of us is still missing
Brunnhilde is still
with the Walsung
We must wait for her
We will receive a grim welcome
if we arrive without her
This way!
Brunnhilde is galloping here
She is heading towards the firs
How Grane is panting!
l never saw Valkyries galloping so
- What is on her saddle?
- That is no hero
She's carrying a woman
How did she find her?
She gives no greeting!
Brunnhilde, don't you hear us?
Help our sister from her horse!
Powerful Grane has sunk
to the ground
She lifts the woman from the saddle
Sister, what has happened?
Help me in my sorest need!
Whence come you?
Only fugitives fly thus
l am fleeing and being pursued
by the father of battles
Have you lost your senses?
Speak! Tell us!
Sisters, look from the mountain!
Look north whether Wotan is near
Can you see him yet?
A storm threatens
Heavy clouds are massing
Father is riding his sacred steed
The raging hunter is coming!
Shield me, sisters!
- Save this woman!
- But who is she?
This is Sieglinde,
Siegmund's sister and bride
Wotan is towering with rage
against the Walsungs
Brunnhilde was to have withheld
victory from her brother
But l sheltered Siegmund
in defiance of the god ...
... who smote him with his spear
Siegmund fell, but l fled
with his wife
To save her l have hurried to you
Protect me too, in my fear,
from punishment
Deluded sister,
what have you done?
Woe, Brunnhilde!
Have you deliberately disobeyed
the father of hosts?
- Darkness looms from the north
- A raging storm steers hither
Wildly neighs father's horse,
fearfully snorting as it comes!
Woe to this poor woman
if Wotan finds her
Lend me your swiftest steed
that would spirit the woman away
Are you urging open defiance?
Rossweisse, lend me your courser!
He has never fled from father
- Helmwige, hear me!
- l obey our father
Give me your horse!
See my distress!
Stand by me as l have stood by you
Save this wretched woman!
Do not concern yourself over me
Death is all l ask
Who bade you bear me from battle?
Had l been struck by the weapon
that slew Siegmund ...
... l should have met my end
united with him!
Far from Siegmund!
Death overwhelms me at the thought
lf l am not to curse you
for your care ...
... then hear my solemn entreaty
Thrust your sword into my heart
Live, woman, for love's sake!
Save the pledge from him
A Walsung is growing in your womb
Save me, fearless one!
Save my child!
Shelter me, you maidens!
- The storm is approaching
- Fly, all who fear it!
Away with the woman!
No Valkyrie dares protect her
Save me!
Save a mother!
Then flee at once, and flee alone
l will brave Wotan's vengeance
l will detain the angry god
while you escape his rage
Which way shall l turn?
Which of you, sisters,
ranged east?
To the east stretches a forest ...
... into which Fafner carried
the Nibelung treasure
He assumed the form of a dragon
ln a cave he keeps watch
over Alberich's ring
A forbidding place for a woman
The wood would shelter her
from Wotan's wrath
The mighty one shuns the place
- Wotan is galloping to the rock!
- Brunnhilde, hark to the thunder!
Hurry eastward!
Defiant, endure all dangers,
hunger, thirst, thorns and stones
Laugh if weakness wears you down
Know one thing, and guard it ever
ln your womb you carry the world's
most wondrous hero
For him preserve the fragments
of the sword
He who forges the sword anew
shall one day wield it
Let him take his name from me
Siegfried, joy in victory!
Marvellous miracle!
Most glorious maid!
Thank you for your comfort
For him whom we loved
l will save the child
May reward one day smile at you!
Farewell!
Sieglinde's woe blesses you!
Stay, Brunnhilde!
He has reached the rock!
Woe, Brunnhilde!
Vengeance blazes forth!
Sisters, help! My heart fails me!
His rage will shatter me
- Keep out of sight!
- Stay silent when he calls!
Woe! Wotan leaps from his horse
Hither he hastens,
breathing revenge!
Where is the guilty one?
Do you dare hide the miscreant?
Your wrath fills us with fear!
What have we done to provoke you?
Do you mock me? Take care!
l know you are hiding Brunnhilde
Recoil from her!
She is cast off for ever!
From pursuit she fled to us
ln fear she roused your wrath
For our anguished sister's sake
we beg you to curb your fury
Weak-willed womanish brood!
Did you inherit such spineless
spirits from me?
Did l make you bold in battle ...
... did l make your
hearts harsh ...
... so that you wild ones now whine
when my wrath punishes perfidy?
Then learn, you whimperers,
her offence
None but she knew my
inmost thoughts
None but she knew the source
of my resolve
She was my will's creative womb
Now she has broken the sacred bond
She has disloyally flouted
her father's command ...
... and turned against me
the weapon my will alone made her!
Do you hear, Brunnhilde ...
... you to whom l granted
helmet and spear ...
... affection, name and life?
Do you hear me make this charge,
and yet hide from your accuser ...
... whose punishment you evade?
Here l am, father
Pronounce my sentence!
The sentence does not stem from me.
You brought punishment on yourself
My will brought you into being ...
...but you have set your
will against it
You could carry out my orders only,
but you have given counter-orders
You were my wish's maid ...
... but your wishes thwarted mine
You were my shield-bearer ...
... but you raised it against me
You were my arbiter of fate ...
... but you chose to frustrate me
You were my rouser of heroes ...
... but you roused them against me
Wotan has told you what you were
Tell yourself what you are now
No longer are you my wish's agent
You have been a Valkyrie
Henceforth be what you are now!
Would you disown me?
Never again will l send you
from Valhalla ...
... never assign heroes to you
Never again will you bring
victors into my hall
At the god's banquets ...
... never again will you pass
me my drinking-horn
Never again will l kiss my child
From the gods you are cut off ...
... expelled from the race
of the immortals
Our bond is broken
You are banished from my sight
Woe, sister!
Do you take all you once gave?
He who masters you will
take it from you
To this mountain l banish you
l will lock you tight in
defenceless sleep
Let the man then capture the maid
who finds her and wakes her
Retract your curse!
Must the maid be wasted by a man?
Hear our plea!
Spare this dreadful disgrace!
We should share in her shame
Did you not hear what l decreed?
She is banished from your band
No longer shall she ride with you
Her beauty's flower will wither
A husband will win her favours
Henceforth she shall belong
to this masterful man ...
... sit and spin by the fire,
the butt and sport of all mockers
Does her fate appal you?
Then flee the lost one!
Keep away!
Should any of you dare to linger
and sustain her ...
... that fool shall share her fate
Of this l warn you!
Away with you! Shun this rock!
Quickly, ride away now ...
... or calamity will befall you
Was my offence so shameful ...
... that you punish my misdeed
with such shame?
Was what l did to you so base ...
... that you so profoundly
debase me?
Was what l did so dishonourable ...
... that my dereliction now
robs me of honour?
Speak, father!
Look me in the eyes
Silence your wrath
Make clear the hidden guilt
which forces you ...
... inflexibly and obstinately ...
... to repudiate your
favourite child
Ask what you did
lt will explain your guilt to you!
l carried out your command
Did l command you to fight
for the Walsung?
As ruler of battles, you did
But that order l revoked
When Fricka had turned your
intention against you ...
... when you resigned yourself
to her will ...
... you were your own enemy
l fancied that you understood me,
and castigated conscious defiance
But you thought me cowardly
and foolish
So did l not need to
avenge treason?
l am not wise
But one thing l know ...
... that you loved the Walsung
l knew the inner conflict that
compelled you to erase this
You had to see the alternative ...
... though it grieved you ...
... that you should deny Siegmund
your defence
You knew this, yet defended him?
Because for you l kept in sight ...
... the one thing on which
you turned your back in perplexity
She who in war guarded Wotan's back
saw what you could not see
l had to see Siegmund!
l appeared to warn him of death
l looked into his eyes,
l heard his words
l understood the hero's distress
The brave man's laments
rang in my ears ...
... the fearful despair of love ...
... the dauntless defiance
of the saddest of souls
ln my ears was echoed ...
... what, deep in my breast,
filled my heart
Shy, astonished, l stood in shame
l could think only of helping ...
... of sharing victory or death
with Siegmund
l knew that this alone was
the lot to choose
He who breathed this love
into my heart ...
... whose will had bound me
to the Walsung ...
... to him l was inwardly loyal ...
... though l
disobeyed your command
So you did what l longed to do ...
... yet which necessity
forced me not to?
So you thought of bliss ...
... when woe broke my heart ...
... when need roused my wrath ...
... and for love of the world
l dammed up the love in my heart?
While l turned against myself ...
... goaded by frustration ...
... driven by longing
to the dread decision ...
... to end my sorrow in the ruins
of my own world ...
... then bliss was enfolding you
lntoxicated with emotion ...
... you laughingly drank
the draught of love ...
... while, for me, gall was blended
with divine distress
Then follow your foolish instinct
You have broken with me
l must shun you
Never again can l share secret
counsels with you
We can no more work together
While life and breath endure,
the god must never see you again
Unfit for you was the maid ...
... who did not understand you
My own view counselled
one thing only ...
... to love what you had loved
lf l must leave you ...
... if you must sever what
once linked us ...
... and cut from yourself
a half ...
... that belonged wholly to you ...
... do not forget that!
You cannot dishonour what will
always be a part of you ...
... cannot wish for a disgrace
that debases you
You would be demeaned ...
... if you saw me derided
You followed the power of love
Now follow him whom you must love!
lf l must depart from Valhalla,
no longer to work with you ...
... and belong henceforth
to a man as master ...
... do not give me to some boaster
Let whoever wins me not
be worthless
You flouted the father of battles
Now he cannot choose for you
You begot a noble race
No coward can disgrace it
The most dedicated of heroes will
spring from Walsung stock
Do not speak of the Walsung race!
l have flung it off with you
My grudge had to destroy it
She who tore herself
from you saved it
Sieglinde carries the holiest fruit
ln grief and pain ...
... she will bear what she
anxiously hides
Never seek protection for her
from me, nor for her womb's fruit!
She guards the sword you made
for Siegmund
And that l broke in pieces!
Child, do not seek to upset
my decision
Await your fate ...
... whatever befall
l cannot choose for you!
But now l must go
l have already stayed too long
l must turn from you
What you wish l may not know
l must only see
your punishment enforced
What must l suffer?
l shall enclose you in deep sleep
Whoever finds
the weaponless maid ...
... shall awaken her and
win her as wife
lf fetters of sleep are to bind me
as easy booty to any faintheart ...
... one thing you must grant ...
... for which l plead in anguish
Surround my sleep ...
... by fearsome terrors, so that
only the most fearless hero ...
... will find me on the rock!
You ask too much,
too great a favour
This one thing you must grant
Annihilate your child
Trample your favourite under foot.
Crush the maid with your spear
But do not condemn her ...
... to this gross degradation
At your command ...
... let flames flare up
Let their fiery glow
engirdle the rock
Let their tongues lick,
their teeth devour ...
... any coward who ventures
to approach the dread rock
Farewell, valiant child ...
... holiest pride of my heart!
lf l must shun you ...
... and may not again lovingly
give you a greeting ...
... if you may no more
ride beside me ...
... or bring me mead at my meal ...
... if l must lose you,
whom l loved ...
... you, the delight of my eyes ...
... then a bridal fire shall
now burn for you ...
... as never has burned for a bride
Let the glow of fierce flames
encircle the rock
Let it strike fear into
the fainthearts
Cowards shall flee from
Brunnhilde's rock
Only one shall win the bride ...
... one freer than l, the god!
Those radiant eyes ...
... that, smiling, l often
kissed ...
... when the joy of battle
won you an embrace ...
... when the praise of heroes ...
... flowed from your sweet lips ...
... those sparkling eyes ...
... that shone on me in storms ...
... when hopeless yearning
seared my heart ...
... when, amid wild alarm, l longed
for worldly pleasures ...
... for the last time let them
delight me ...
... with their last farewell kiss
On a more fortunate man ...
... let their star shine
For the hapless immortal ...
... they must close for ever
For so does the god now
turn from you
So does he kiss the godhead
from you!
Loge, hear me!
Come hither!
As first l found you,
a fiery glow ...
... as you escaped me,
a wandering flame ...
... as l bound you ...
... so today l summon you!
Arise, flickering flame!
Ring the rock with fire!
Loge! Appear!
He who fears my spear-point ...
... shall never penetrate
the fire!
Translation (c) 1988
Lionel Salter
Subtitling: David Hogarth
(c) Philips Classics
Productions