- What's wrong?
- l'm just tired.
Have you travelled far?
Yeah.
You're a surfer, aren't you?
Yeah, l'm a surfer.
l always wanted to try that.
lt seems like it would be
so much fun.
Yeah, it can be.
lt depends.
- On what?
- On if you make it your whole life.
Have you?
l guess ...
What if l told you there's a wave
out there, -
- and when it hits a little island
off Mexico, it will be massive.
And all l can think about
is riding it.
So you want to surf, -
- and the waves where you live
aren't half bad.
And you start to improve ...
And then you hear about this wave
in a far-away country, -
- whose name you can't
even pronounce. What then?
How far are you willing to go?
What sacrifice
are you willing to make?
How good do you really want to be?
Ow ... ow ...
Man, this hurts.
Mickey! You promised.
So beautiful ...
We're dead.
Don't worry.
l'm just teaching her English.
l've watched him ride for four days.
As an expert, l know -
- he's one of those rare athletes
whose spirit matches their talent.
l think he's preparing himself
for something extraordinary.
lf l can do anything to help him,
l will.
Mickey's at it again.
He says he's teaching her English.
He's teaching her something.
- Ladies first.
How are you?
l am fine.
Your eyes are very beautiful.
And you are so very handsome.
And so strong.
Very good.
Now if you really want
to learn English ...
You listen to Country music.
They tell it like it is.
''You give your hand to me ...''
''... and then you say hello ...''
lt sounds like your daddy's here.
l'm really sorry, sir.
l was just teaching her English.
- There are lots of girls, Mickey.
- You have to pick the right one.
You've got to make them come to you,
or it's like marlin fishing.
- What?
- Marlin fishing, man.
A woman's like a big game fish.
lf you really want her, you need
a boat, bait, get out on the sea ...
And if you get a hook-up, you
have to drag it back to the boat.
l have a question for you.
At that point, who's tired?
- You?
- No, the both of you!
You know l say to them? ''You may be
a symphony, but l believe in song.''
- l don't get it. Do you get it?
- Sometimes.
Are you going to be all right?
Yeah, l'm fine.
Hey, English!
Come here.
No TV, you understand me?
No shopping malls.
No tour buses.
You hear me, English? No fast food.
Leave us alone!
Are they going to execute us?
l wasn't even doing anything.
Oh, man!
l'm going to have a heart attack.
Chin up!
The tide raises all ships.
Five more hours,
and we would have been out of here.
- We've got until ten.
- We'll never make that plane.
- The harbour's only a mile away.
- We're in jail, Mickey!
This ain't about being caged.
l've seen birds in cages,
and you ain't no bird.
Did you know that birds are
the direct descendants of dinosaurs?
You know what ''dinosaur'' means?
lt's Greek for ''terrible lizard''.
Think about that.
- That's my board! What do we do?
- Run like hell.
Come back here, you idiots.
l sense angels at work here.
There's that taxi again.
- Look out!
- He nearly killed me.
That's the most beautiful thing
l've ever seen. lt's an epiphany.
Not now, Mickey.
Can't you see we're in trouble?
No TV, no diet Cola, no shopping
malls. You hear me, cue ball?
l said, leave our women alone.
Come on,
this thing's going to take off.
Every sport has its own mythology.
lts legends.
Joe Louis, Muhammad Ali,
Mickey Mantle, Michael Jordan ...
Faces you see on television.
Surfing has a mythology, too.
Most of it is based on
what you never see.
Stories of rides on unimaginable
waves in obscure far-away places, -
- and of the people
who seek these moments out, -
- travelling like spirits
from country to country.
As for him ... Before enlightenment,
chop wood and carry water.
After enlightenment,
He's good to know
when your back's against the wall.
l like you, Mickey.
You're a good lad.
Thank you, Captain.
That's a nice thing to say.
Straight flush ...
l hope this doesn't
screw things up between us.
- Hey, Keoni! Happy birthday.
- Thanks.
lt's a good life.
This isn't just a skateboard ramp.
We build temples to adrenalin.
lt's like Chinese architecture. They
didn't build for the human body, -
- but for the human spirit.
You know where waves come from?
lmagine you're a giant
standing in the Bay of Alaska.
You drop a boulder in the water,
and the rings fan out.
They keep going
until something gets in their way.
An island, a continent, a reef ...
Something that forces them to peak,
then break, then roll.
Does that make sense to you?
Probably not. lf you understood,
l probably wouldn't be saying it.
Say a big swell hits Hawaii, and
you ride one of those huge waves.
The wave folds back together
on the other side of the island.
Then back out across the ocean,
to wherever it needs to go.
All you would need to do
to ride it again, -
- is find out where it's heading,
and beat it there, however you can.
That's what l've been doing.
l'm trying to figure it out.
Why, when the wave's just right,
when it's big and hollow enough, -
- and l'm inside of it, -
- everything, whatever l'm doing,
why l'm doing it ...
ln that moment, it all makes sense.
Most everybody
wants something else from it.
l'm afraid if l ask for more,
it'll all disappear.
Be careful. l know you're
the captain's daughter, -
- but we just got into trouble
because of a woman.
- You're very young.
- Yeah. l am young.
- Where's your home?
- Wherever the surf's good.
You know Mickey?
He was number two in the world.
Pro tour and everything.
Could have been number one, but ...
See him? He's the best in the world.
That's what Mickey says.
That's what everybody says.
But he won't compete on the tour.
l guess he doesn't like hotel rooms.
But he's a hot surfer.
That's all that matters.
When l'm old enough,
l'll go on that tour and cash in.
l'll buy my mom a house
and get her teeth fixed.
Everybody's got to have
beautiful teeth. Even Mom.
Salt water
is closely related to blood.
lt reminds me of our own essence.
She wants to go with you.
When my wife was alive,
we found her on the streets of Rio.
l brought her on board
to save her life.
She recognises herself in you.
The same eyes, the same heart.
Without lies,
taking only what you need, -
- giving only what you can.
She feels safe with you, -
- although she knows
she won't stay with you forever.
Kick his ass!
- Take this, Mickey.
- l have him right where l want him.
Kick his ass.
- How much did we bet?
- lf we lose, we don't eat.
l'm gonna kick your butt!
A little hot sauce
will fix this guy.
You enjoying your visit to Bali?
Jet lag's got me down,
but l'll get used to it.
As soon as we can,
we're going to move the car.
lf l understood what you're saying,
it would help.
Hey, nice to see you, man.
Tell him, nice to see him.
No problem.
These guys are friends of mine.
Guys, how's it, man?
How are you doing? Good to see you.
Good to see you, man.
lt's been a long time.
l've got to get back in shape.
lt's been a long summer.
- l believe these belong to you?
- Keep them.
You never know
when you might need them.
- Who are you?
- Just a fan.
l was hoping
l could train with you guys.
Very few surfers have the courage
and skill to ride really big waves.
And here, in a marketplace in Bali,
on the other side of the world, -
- he was about to become
one of them.
Some mornings I wake up
and ask myself, -
- "Will I die today?"
You never know when you'll go.
If something goes wrong,
the jet ski is your only salvation.
Jet skis, ropes!
You've got equipment on the brain.
ln Hawaii, l'll paddle into those
40-footers with my bare hands.
You can't paddle. lt's too big.
- lt's just a wave, man.
- lt's too fast.
- You can't paddle 35 mph.
- Horse shit! lt's just a wave, man.
You've got to be in the right place
at the right time.
- Dream on.
- Are you towing me in?
You, no problem.
As for him ... no way.
- And just why the hell not?
- Because you're crazy.
Thank you, Keoni.
l love you, too.
But l will tell you one thing.
For us, the partying's over.
Starting tomorrow, we train.
All day, every day. That's reality.
There are two types of surfers to
watch when surfing dangerous waves.
One is gung ho.
He doesn't consider the risks.
The other is gun shy.
He doesn't want to accept the risks.
ln this ''cage'' here,
one focusses on his abilities, -
- and the other, on his limitations.
Pete, what is the worst-case
scenario you can think of?
The worst thing l can see is
if someone goes down, -
- and gets held under,
and the rescue team can't find him.
Rush,
what is the worst-case scenario?
lf you let go of the rope too soon,
and you lose speed -
- and the wave comes from behind
and gobbles you up.
Shane?
l think the worst thing would be
to get sucked over the falls -
- and lose all your air on impact,
and get sucked down. 30 or 40 feet.
And it's getting darker and darker,
and all the clouds surrounding you.
Like you're just about to black out,
and it's really loud and dark ...
l think that'd be
a really bad scenario.
- How long have you lived here?
- Forever. l came for the surf.
l couldn't see leaving.
l travel, but l always come back.
- Are you a writer?
- Yeah.
Got a wife?
- Kids?
- Yeah, three. Girls.
- They surf.
- Of course.
The Navy's got
things called ''rebreathers''.
lt fits in your mouth
and pulls oxygen from the water.
lt won't be long
till we stay down indefinitely.
Rebreathers, my ass!
You sound like astronauts.
You guys don't tow me in,
l'm gonna paddle in.
You don't think l can?
l was number two in the world.
- That was eight years ago.
- Eight long years, bro.
Eight years! Eight years!
Eight years, my ass!
Eight years, eight years,
eight years ...
You understand, we can augment
our abilities through technology, -
- but technology isn't everything.
You need speed and strength.
You must be quick and agile to fly,
and flexible, to reduce injury.
With big waves, you can be
held under for more than one wave.
You could be held under
for two waves.
You could even be held under
for three waves.
We understand the risks
in what we're up against.
We know exactly
what our bodies are able to do.
We practise extreme safety
when we're doing extreme things.
Technology brings surfing
to another dimension, -
- allowing a rider to match the
speed of a 50-foot wave at 35 mph.
But the question is,
at what price?
When only the most skilled
can survive, -
- to ride waves this big
is to put yourself in God's hands.
- What's the matter? Side pain?
- l can't breathe.
- What's up?
- Take a deep breath. Breathe.
Relax, relax ...
Okay, let's walk him home.
He's burning up.
- Maybe malaria ...
- l'll be fine.
No matter what, no hospitals, okay?
Because l hate doctors.
One time my mom had
a skin disease ...
lt got really infected
and we had to take her to hospital.
A stupid doctor gave her
all the wrong things.
Ruined her teeth,
ruined her hair ...
He made her look old.
My dad freaked. He drove his truck
right through the doc's living room.
Right through the picture window.
You'll be okay.
You're strong.
The strongest man on earth.
- What is this place?
- My home.
There's a rock concert once a year.
We get invaded for three days.
Daddy, Daddy!
Hi, girls.
l've missed you so much.
Hi ... Look how big you are!
Oh God, l missed you.
Wyatt!
l'm not gonna die or anything, man!
l've just got a temperature.
Help me get him to my house.
Serena's with him.
l hope it's not malaria.
Welcome, travellers.
Time to rock.
Remember you're guests in another
people's land, so listen up!
There's trash cans and
port-a-potties galore. Use them.
If you choose to partake,
then for heaven's sake be discreet.
This is for you,
and this is for you.
- Why aren't you with your friends?
- Too many people.
l know what you mean. Come on,
l want to show you something.
All over the world, people
are returning to their tribes.
You may not realise it, but
you and your friends are a tribe.
lt's a tribe built on mutual respect
and a common understanding -
- of what it takes to do what we do.
- l never really saw it that way.
- What about riding the big waves?
- Are you frightened of them?
- Yeah.
What about using a jet ski
to help you get in?
That's one way ...
Mickey thinks you can paddle
into them. He hates jet skis.
- He says it takes the purity away.
- What do you think?
l haven't really
made my mind up yet.
lt's morning.
The night is over.
Hey, you okay?
Rough night, huh?
The guys are training.
l've got to get out there.
They'll take care of you.
Need anything?
- Come on, Mickey, focus!
- l got it.
Wait for the wind. Perfect!
Faster, faster!
This is wrong.
l got it, l got it.
As I watched them train today,
I was filled with sadness.
So many people aspire to greatness,
so few succeed.
I could see the separation
happening before my eyes.
Hawaii's big waves await them.
A challenge to one,
a threat to the other.