Yes, Yuko
Nowjust get down from the bus
Where do you want to go
I got it, OK
Got it? Where?
Let's go shopping together
What do you want to buy
We must have juice and candy
But they are waiting
It's alright
Come on This...
What
No
What's up
I can't move
I can't go inside
Are you alright? Come on
No
Cursed
Welcome
How are you
I am not a customer
I've made an appointment with your boss
Excuse me, where is Mr. Kitaura
He is in the office
I'm Ryoko in OK Mark
I want to see Mr. Kitaura Okay
You are too late
I've already waited for 30 minutes
It is ordinary
for small shopkeepers like us to wait
for people from big companies like you
Not such thing
The appointment should be at 2 o'clock
What's the point of standing there
Not even want to say 'Welcome'
Welcome
What
Do you want to persuade us to join your group
If you agree to join our group,
I promise to report it
to Mr. Tejima
Tejima? That good guy
How is that guy
He promised to visit us
when our store opens
He had an accident
Accident?
Did he die?
Not yet, but he was seriously wounded
How is it?
His legs are in great pain
How painful is it
Does it need to cut off the legs
Already cut off
It's two legs
Have both shanks been cut off
It's really serious
Did you hear that
Both shanks have been cut off
Then he can't walk anymore
Don't bother me
I'm watching closely on that part-time worker
If I pay less attention,
that girl
will take away the money
Can he still walk?
The situation...
How is it
Tell me quickly
Did he urinate on the bed
Is he in great pain
Does he look miserable
Please tell me
Let's go back to the merchandise
The sales volume of our goods
has been quite good
So I really don't want
to change the agent
If something wrong arises,
I think your company will not
help my small shop
Tejima had already told me
For your worriness,
that's why I come here today
I come here to explain to you in details
What's the point of explaining
All is the damn shit of your company
That stupid thing had already explained
That stupid thing?
That guy without shanks
He had already explained to us
Will you go?
Not yet
Your boss wants me to take stock
What a bad luck
Our headquarters will probably blame me
Excuse me, you are...
I am a part-time worker. My name is Nori
I only worked here for about a month
My name is Ryoko
I'm the staff of OK Mark
Does OK Mark want this shop
Yes
I want to persuade the owner
to join our group
It sounds good
Something like chargers of the
mobile phones can be put here
People can also draw money here
Customers usually don't come here
There are many reasons for this
It's better for the lights here
to be brighter
It's really a bit dark
I usually have a sort of
uncomfortable feeling
I have to go to the warehouse to take the stock
Try to finish it within three days
I will try my best
This shop really gives me a strange feeling
Mr. Kitaura?
Welcome
Wait a minute
666 yen please, sir
It doesn't have any custormer here
Do you know why the people nearby
do not come to this shop
That's why I guess
here is still in stock
This thing has already
out of stock in other places
Understand
Excuse me Yes
I got 1000 yen from you, sir
Now give back 334 yen to you
Thank you
Than you for coming
Pick it up
Who
Thank you
Thank you very much
Good morning, Mr. Kitaura
How is it going
Stock-taking will probably
be finished within this week
Believe me
Something strange is around here
Can't you feel it
Yes
My aunt also told not to do part-time work
Does only Miss. Nori work here?
Only me and Omori who works on night shift
Do you think there are ghosts here
Because I always think that
I am watched by somebody
The shopkeeper and his wife are also strange
So I have to finish stock-taking
as soon as possible
If we are able to purchase this shop,
it will definitely look different
When all the lights are changed,
many customers would come
Then I won't find other part-time job
and wait for your good news
The pay would also be better
I will have it reviewed
I go to work then Okay
What is it
Excuse me
Could you please explain it
The expiry date of this food
was three years ago
It has already expired
Why do you still keep it in the warehouse
This kind of goods cannot be regarded
as the assets of the shop
Yes, Mr. Kitaura
Are you sick
Sick?
Are you feeling sick
What are you talking about
This lady is really strange
Just ignore her
Are you alright
What do you mean
I think it is you who have
problems with your mind
Please be quiet
This is my goods
Don't take it, you thief
You are too much, Mr. Kitaura
The goods has already expired
What's the matter
Look over there
What
It rushed to the glass
You go back first
Let me clean up the mess
Miss. Ryoko
You have just said that here is strange
Is it true
Not such thing, don't worry
If it really does,
Nori will also...
What will happen to me...
It would be alright
In OK Mark,
it needs clever girls like you so much
This shop will change
You have to try your best to change this shop
Okay, please go
Please don't stop me
What do you want
I want to clean up the filth
Honey
You have to clean it without a single mark
I got it, honey
Thank you
You are early today
Should we now change shifts
It is gloomy outside
Please go
Thank you. I go now
I'm coming
You should not have time to buy food to eat
I buy it for you
I would be in trouble if somebody has found out
I pay it myself. What is to be afraid of
Thank you
I have to go now, bye
Welcome
The total is 699 yen
I got 700 yen from you, sir
Give back 1 yen to you
Thank you for coming
Welcome
The total is 999 yen
I got 1000 yen from you, madam
Give back 1 yen to you, madam
Thank you for coming
Hello
Hello, this is Mr. Tejima
What's the matter
You ring me suddenly
Are you discharged from hospital
Is that guy still over there
What
You say which one
Hello, Mr. Tejima
Did you hear me
There are many people
Many
Mr. Tejima
Many people are walking
Miss. Ryoko
They are walking very fast
Mr. Tejima
I cannot hear very well
Why only me
Ioses both legs
Don't you know
Only ghosts have no leg
Hateful, hateful
Hateful, hateful, hateful, hateful
What's the matter
It seems that somebody is in the fridge
Is anybody inside
Maybe I just saw the wrong thing
It should not have anybody
That's right
Am I a bit nervous
Did you buy it again
Did you buy this just for me
No such thing
I'm a Christian
I buy it to you so that you can go home
Christian?
I'm called Samson after being baptized
Samson
Omori, Samson
What
You doesn't match well with your name
Thank you for your help
Mr. Samson
Doesn't my name match with my appearance
Welcome
The total is 44.444 yen
Omori
Miss. Ryoko
Be calm
What's the matter
Excuse me
I'm sorry
Welcome
The total is 666 yen
Give back 334 yen to you, madam
Thank you for coming
Omori
What's the matter
Nothing
Before it is getting dark,
Nori, you go home now
But
it's very cold, very cold
Do you have shampoo
This is shampoo and also shower gel
Also a towel
Excuse me Wait a minute please
Wait a minute
The total is 907 yen
Can I help you, sir
I'm sorry
I want to buy one more bun
If so,
the total is 999 yen, sir
I keep you waiting
That's okay
Thank you for coming
What a beautiful store-assistant
Very cold
You have a message
Have you forgotten to bring your mobile phone
Where are you
Okay
I would go there later
You wait for me there first
I long for your food
Now I go to buy some desserts
The police of Tanage county have arrested
the director of Gantang office,
Konto,
who was suspected to kill
a four-year old child Tanage
According to our investigation,
the suspect, Konto,
suddenly became crazy
and killed his own dog
near his own shop
As Konto defended,
he only hit his dog
with metal stick
as usual
He didn't know that a child would suddenly
go into the area
It is reported that the people nearby
heard Konto calling pupils as stupid thing
And Konto always gets money by
pursuing those cats and dogs
which are roaming around
He will tie them up and
hit with metal stick
Now the police are investigating
the above events for further details
Now comes the next news
In Aogi of Yama county,
the firemen has found
a dead body of a 21-year old teenager,
Kinshi,
and his room-mate,
another 23-year old teenager, Kataoka,
At the beginning,
Kataoka was very agitated
But now the situation is under control
Now the death of Kinshi
is being investigated
The police have found out
a skull
and other bones at Kataoka's home
After laboratory investigation,
Kinshi's skin tissues
have been found on Kataoka
The police are now investigating
for further details
It is believed that this case
is directly related to Kataoka
But since Kataoka was very agitated,
the process of investigation was hindered
After he calms down,
it is believed that he would be interrogated
Maybe he would be brought back to the scene
and reorganized the case
The police now put Kataoka into prison
and refuse bail
The above are Japanese news
and reported by Hirayama
Is anybody there
Why nobody is there
Something is strange
I'm alright
Madam, do you walk past here every day
Are you their relatives
No
Then come with me
Here is not a good place to talk
What's the matter
It's better for the shop to close down
The shopkeeper has already
changed to several people
Not a single one can keep going
Each one also becomes very strange
Strange
You also think so
That couple doesn't look like normal persons
That land is the root of the problem
That land?
When a person buys the land,
he would become reluctant
to communicate with others
Iike that couple
Then there would even have murders
Sometimes mankind is really cunning
In order to achieve their aims,
they would hurt themselves deliberately
and cheat for insurance compensation
This kind of people deserve punishment
What are you saying? Derserve punishment
That shop is not made by
ordinary material
What material do you guess
Not ordinary material?
Mankind is really greedy
The shop is not made by cement
but the graves nearby
They broke the graves
and mixed the debris with other materials
The boss of that construction company
also died in a strange way
It serves him right
Miss. Ryoko
You also know that it is strange
I want you to tell me
If I were you,
I wouldn't pretend not to see anything
and not to feel anything
If so,
I would rather accept myself
to have such special power, right
I can listen to them
touch them
Of course can even look at them
Now
I am always able to see
Well
But
I will try to pretend not to see anything
even though it is wrong to do so
I have my own opinion
I will not think much about ghosts
Really
I think maybe because
I have done something bad
It is a retribution
So I am able to see those strange things
Nori, when you encounter
some strange things,
do you have such thought?
Maybe
But other people really cannot see anything
In fact there are some other things
which are not able to explain by logic
The issue itself may not be on Nori or me
These things are beyond
the control of mankind after all
So we don't need to think about
why there are strange things to happen
But just to face it
when these things have happened
Do you really think in this way
Miss. Ryoko
You would feel better
if you could think like this
Maybe you won't agree with me
But...
I would be very worried
Sometimes it sounds like
I'm thinking too much
I would feel better
if just regard it as an ordinary thing
What do you mean
And the issue is not on me
To regard it as an ordinary thing,
do you want to tell me these principles
You better quit that part-time job
Got it, Nori
Omori
Omori...
Go back
Hello
Many people
are here
Hello, Mr. Tejima
Mr. Tejima
Here is quite good
All are without legs
Mr. Tejima
Thank you for your care
for so long
Goodbye
Okay
Is Yuko
I just get down from the bus
Where do you want to go to buy things
I got it, OK
Go with me. It's beautiful
Where
Quick Okay
Oh! No, I can't move
My legs cannot move
What's the matter
No...
Ladies and gentlemen
I'm Sato
The shooting of Cursed
is finally finished. Thank you
The first time I saw the film
was on a small television
Though the screen is small,
some scary scenes in the film
are enough to frighten me
This is a very scary film
I also scared when the film was shooting
Don't you have the same feeling with me
Let's see the titbits of the film
Thank you
What do you want to say
The film has almost finished shooting
It will be finished very soon
I really feel a bit unhappy about that
While the film is being shot,
I have been very happy
If the film has finished shooting,
I will have a sense of loneliness
I really want to keep working with the staff
What did you feel
when you first saw the script
When I first saw the script,
I found the beginning quite straightforward
But having the experience of
being a store-assistant,
it is still valuable to me
At the beginning, I was not that concentrated
but later it was greatly improved
I think I am going to be a good actor
Do you watch scary films
No
When I see some scary scenes,
I would be very frightened
I would immediatedly use
my hands to cover my face
When did you first go to funerals
I went to funerals before
I will try my best
Is there anything that is
particularly hard to you
It is that
I had to get used to many new things
at the beginning
I was not used to at the beginning
Did you seek advice from other people
I did seek advice from my seniors
I once hurt my finger carelessly
I was very worried
but my seniors always encouraged me
I am very grateful to them
What do you think
I will try other films as well
and will work very hard
to train my acting
Please continue to give me encouragement
I'm Sato
This story is about
many scary things keep on
happening in a store
The story is really excellent
Please feel free to give suggestions
Mankind is the most terrible creature
Don't you know that
There are lots of people around us
What kind of people would you meet?
Maybe he would become
hysterical in front of you
Who? Who?
The scary legend of city
finally becomes a movie
Tokyo Psycho
A young writer with freshness
It's written by Hirayama
the new launch of
director Tomie, Katagawachu
What do you want to tell me?
I have forgotten
Oh! Yes
I have important thing to tell you
I have also just got it
We've found lgumi's present address
Please blame me louder
I like to hear those words
It feels good
This city is covered with craziness
It is adapted from real cases
The craziest, abnormal criminal
No
Coming slowly from beautiful girls
It is hard to believe
Everything becomes crazy
In this city
if you are not crazy
you will die