(beeping)
Taryn.
I know you're close to unlocking the
secrets of Quarran III.
That's right, Zhanna.
You taught me well.
There may still be a place for you in the
Empir e.
A Seer is always...
...useful.
My visions are my own now.
Are your troops ready ?
Yes, my lady.
The garrison on Corellia is on standby
and awaits your order.
Very well.
The artifact is the priority.
And Taryn Anwar?
I leave that to you.
I understand.
The ambition of the Emperor's Hand
clouds her purpose.
She may yet be of some use to me.
My lord.
Alert our contacts near the Corellian
system.
They are to observe only. No action is to
be taken.
Is that clear?
As you wish, my lord.
(beeping)
(alien language)
Private business. Open the lift.
(muted club music)
(driving club music)
(crowd chatter)
(club music fades out)
(alien whispers)
(club music fades in)
Whoa, beautiful! How 'bout joining us?
Sorry, I'm not very good company
tonight.
Whatever the lady says.
Struck out again, eh, Commander?
Ah, maybe I did and maybe I didn't.
(alien language)
Get lost.
She said take a hike.
(alien language)
I have what you want.
I believe you're right.
Was that r eally necessary?
Yeah.
Here's our girl. Told you she'd be prompt.
- You picked up a partner?
- You could say that.
Taryn, this is Cade. A friend.
Do you have it?
Yes... and...
...no.
Yes, we have it...
...and no. It's not his to give.
It's mine.
You lied to me.
Declan here tells me you'r e a Seer.
I need you to unlock the artifact.
I wouldn't take much stock in what he
says.
And I don't work with others. Not
anymor e.
Listen...
(club music fades into haunting choral
music)
(blaster fire)
(club music fades in)
- You'll work with me 'cause it was your
sister's dying wish.
You know, I knew Raux very well.
You'r e nothing like her.
You know wher e to find me.
Who is he and how does he know Raux?
You'll have to ask him
and you'll have plenty of time on the way
to Quarran III.
I won't work with him.
I don't trust him.
(Boushh speaking in Ubese)
Right. We'll take it from here. Let's go.
It's clear the feeling is mutual.
Taryn Anwar.
You are her eby under arrest for
treasonous acts against the Empire.
Now, Sergeant, I'm sure you can
understand why I can't accompany you.
I can shoot you here.
But you won't.
Stand down Commander. This is Imperial
business.
CorSec is still the reigning authority here.
I have reinforcements on the way.
I say again, Commander. Stand down.
Is there a back door to this place?
Unfortunately... no.
Declan?
Run!
VO: All fighters... man to deploy.
You could time that better. I signaled you
a while ago.
Switch over.
She's all yours.
And you'r e lucky I got here at all.
Your friend her e kicked up quite
a bit of Imperial interest.
There's patrols everywher e.
What about my ship?
Consider it impounded.
Two destroyers coming in fast.
I see 'em.
Switching auxiliary power to forward
shields.
We're in tractor range.
Not for long.
VO: Disable ship in sector 73.
VO: Do not destroy.
We have fighters approaching.
Take the aft guns.
VO: All TIES... disable fugitive fr eighter.
Roger. I have them.
Well, this has gone on long enough.
Let's see how well they fly.
I've alr eady taken the shipyard tour.
That should push the bounty up on me.
And we're clear.
I want some answers. Who are
you and where is that artifact?
You know, I r eally don't care what you
want.
Hey!
Have I ever doubted you? When you
came to me when you found out who
Zhanna was?
Did I hesitate, for even a moment?
And you.
How many times have I risked my life...
and my ship... for one of Raux's visions?
Now it's a long two day trip to Quarran III.
You two are supposed to be Jedi.
Try acting like it.
So.
How'd you meet my sister?
How did you end up working for the
Emperor's Hand?
Zhanna was a Jedi.
How was I supposed to know
she was a traitor to the Order?
You know, I always thought a Seer
would be mor e... perceptive.
Raux didn't see it. And
Zhanna trained her in secret.
You know what, you're lying.
Raux is a Jedi.
Not in the eyes of the Order.
My sister left the Temple at 13.
The Council felt her visions made her...
unstable...
...unsuitable for further training.
So you took her to Zhanna?
She offered. She was a friend, I trusted
her.
Look.
I thought I was helping to restore the Jedi
Order.
But she lied to me.
She used me.
No one hates Zhanna mor e than I do.
And I don't need a total stranger
passing judgment on me.
I know what I've done.
That seemed to go well.
I thought I told you to ease up on her.
Yeah, well.
Listen.
When Raux...
When Raux... died. I've been trying to
understand why.
Have I ever doubted you? When you
came to me when you found out who
Zhanna was?
And then I find that Zhanna trained Raux.
But what does it mean?
Now with her gone...
...what am I supposed to believe in now?
Tell me this.
Do you still believe in Raux's visions?
Without fail.
Well then, maybe...
...she saw a bigger picture.
What is thy bidding, my master?
I sense much anger in you, Lord Vader.
Directed at the Emperor's Hand.
She has an agenda, my master.
I am unclear if it is in your best inter est.
That is why I have you.
Yes, my master.
Lord Vader.
Too many Jedi have been eluding you
lately.
Make sure that your efforts in the
Outer Rim are mor e... productive.
As you wish.
(crowd noises)
(R2-D2 beeps)
(crowd falls silent)
(ominous music)
I come with a message from the Emperor.
Senators.
Honored delegates.
You have the distinct honor of assisting
me in bringing peace and order to our
troubled galaxy.
I have given system and sector control to
the Moffs.
(outraged gasps)
- All commerce and travel will now be
regulated
by the Empir e for the safety
and benefit of its loyal citizens.
In your eagerness to comply
I have complete faith that order
will reign in your home worlds.
Immediately.
- This is preposterous!
By what right... (chokes)
By the right of the Emperor's wishes.
(death rattle)
The Emperor thanks you for your
continued loyalty to the Empire.
Escort our guests to their home worlds
and see to it that the transfer of power is
complete.
Yes, what is it?
My lady.
Taryn Anwar has escaped.
We discovered her contact, a smuggler
named Declan.
She's on board his ship and we believe...
Does she have the artifact?
- We believe so.
- However, our troops have encountered
some unexpected resistance from the
local militia.
But we'd been able to determine that the
ship set course for the Quarran system.
Ready my ship.
Alert my crew.
My lady?
I will retrieve this piece in person.
And I will have the pleasure of
dealing with Taryn Anwar
myself.
Yes, my lady.
I think you should see this.
I'm sorry we left without you
but Declan, it's here. I can feel it.
It's not clear yet
but it will be once I'm on Keishing.
No matter what
you and Cade need to get the holocron
to Taryn.
She's the next step.
You and Cade won't like it
but I'm willing to do whatever it
takes to ensure the Jedi survive.
Taryn will...
She'll understand.
This is my choice.
This is the only option.
The pickup coordinates are in the nav
computer.
Cade will need a lift.
And Declan...
...don't be late.
Raux, what have you done?
- Obviously what she felt was right.
How long have you been standing there?
But you know that's typical of Raux.
Always giving orders. No explanations.
Like working for Zhanna.
I r eally don't see how you can compare
the two.
Zhanna would say,
"Investigate all reports in the system.
Bring who and what you can."
What, you never figured it out?
I'm going to say this again.
I trusted Zhanna.
She was the only one that believed in
my visions of the Temple's destruction.
Not the Council.
Not anyone else.
So when the Temple was destroyed
Zhanna seemed like the only hope.
She had a plan.
And when the Emperor declared
all Jedi traitors to the Empire,
as we were being hunted down one by
one,
she asked me
to help her rebuild the Jedi Order in
secret.
I wanted to find Jedi for her.
I wanted the Order back.
You never suspected that she was using
you?
I started to piece it together,
but it wasn't until she r evealed
herself as the Emperor's Hand...
She wanted me to be part of that.
And that's when I got out.
You know she killed every Jedi you ever
found.
I know.
Welcome to the prison outpost of
Keishing, my lady.
- You didn't need to come all this way.
- Commander.
I don't mind getting dirty.
Kneel.
Well, since you asked so nicely.
And I would have thought six months
would have softened you a bit.
Well behold a softened woman.
Put her on board my ship.
Try not to bruise her any more than
necessary.
And get her cleaned up.
Yes, my lady.
Let's see this holocron.
I've tried to access it but...
Well, it's locked.
Yes.
There.
Over 200 years ago the Council began
efforts
to infiltrate and destroy Sukaal's group.
Where so many have failed, I've
succeeded.
Now I have escaped Quarran III with the
holocron.
Without it the Seers are crippled.
Duty compels me to return to the Temple
and complete my mission and yet...
Maybe Sukaal was right and his
methods are the only way to save us all.
Guess he didn't opt for the Temple.
Wait... that's it?
I mean, that's it? Where's all the power?
On Quarran III.
Just like the myth says.
So much devastation.
What could have caused so much
damage?
Welcome to the Empire's testing ground.
So this is Quarran III.
It's all up to you now.
Lead the way.
We made need these.
Right.
There's so much energy here.
But it's...
...unfocused.
Undirected.
- Well,
I don't feel a thing.
- No. It's here.
But it's like the holocron. It...
...it needs a Seer to unlock it.
- This place looks like it's been here a
while.
- Do you think Sukaal built it?
- No. It was her e long befor e the Seers
came.
- Looks like our path is down into these
caves.
- Let's get going.
- You have always been ruled by your
emotions.
That's what makes you so reliable.
Give me the artifact.
No.
Give me the artifact...
...or your sister dies.
You'r e alive.
Raux. I...
- I saw you die.
She's got this whole place wired to blow.
Let her go.
- Lf you let her go...
...I'll activate it for you.
- It takes a Seer of great ability
to activate this chamber.
And that's not you,
is it, Taryn?
I took you in when the Jedi threw you
out.
Now it's time to repay your debt.
(echoing voice)
Download initiated.
From where?
- This console?
(echoing voice)
No.
From off-planet.
(echoing voice) Everywhere.
Systems. Networks. Ship logs.
(echoing voice)
So much data. Scattered.
These are identity tags. Some sort of
tracking system.
Some of it's old.
That's it?
No weapons?
No power?
The message on the artifact.
Raux, search on Sukaal.
(echoing voice)
Got it.
Master Sukaal.
My mission was successful.
I have eliminated the targets
enroute to the Yavin system
before they could join the
mercenary fleet assembling there.
I look forward to my next assignment.
My master is dead.
I'm continuing his important work
without the Council's knowledge.
I, too, have seen this vision.
This futur e of horrible death and
destruction.
The program still runs, buried deep
within the Temple's com systems.
It will run as long as the Temple stands.
It is up to us few that remain true to the
goal
to use this program's information.
The darkness that threatens the
galaxy must be destroyed.
A secr et order in the Jedi.
This r ecording's old enough
to be from the Sith Wars.
They must have been hunting Sith.
(echoing voice)
I've found Sukaal's recording.
Play it.
The Council believes they have
halted my tagging program.
Let them think they've stopped me.
They cannot see the truth of my visions.
They will not see the truth of my visions.
So many candidates fail to become
apprentices.
So many padawans fail their trials.
We reject these unpr edictable, untrained
children
and loose them upon the galaxy.
And still we are shocked
when they betray Jedi ideals.
My visions grow clearer.
One will turn to the Dark side
and destroy us all.
I will defy the Council to save the galaxy.
I will continue to tag all who seek to
become Jedi.
I will track those who fail
and destroy those who turn from the
Light.
Not Sith. Jedi.
They were hunting Jedi.
You didn't hunt Jedi.
You were trying to help.
Raux, pull up Quarran III.
I seem to be the odd man out.
It's still running.
Download all active tags to this console.
- Thank you Taryn. You've ensured
my place at the Emperor's side.
Rather than bringing your comrades to
me one by one
you've delivered therest of the Order to
me.
(echoing voice)
Download complete.
Deactivating system.
Kill them.
(lightsaber hum sounds)
You talk of paying debts.
You owe me your life yet all you've done
is use me.
Your visions of the Jedi Temple's
destruction were worthless to me.
I'm alive because I laid the charges
myself.
I would leave...
...now.
- What the-
- Don't question it.
We've got to get out of her e.
Cade will get her. We have to get to the
ship.
You better be right.
You won't win.
I already have.
Look how far you've strayed from the
Jedi path.
I strayed when I followed you.
I didn't make you hide your visions.
I didn't abandon your sister.
Fear and guilt put you on that path.
Taryn!
- We've got to go.
- She's got the disk.
There's no time.
I'll make time.
Move.
Move, Cade.
I have to do this.
- I've got to make things right.
- You can't follow her for ever.
You have to make a choice.
Taryn, let it go.
You haven't failed.
There's still hope.
Don't you ever do that to me again, you
understand?
Never again.
It was worth it.
We have a chance now.
Declan uploaded the last 100 years
of information from the console.
We now have the location of all the Jedi
that Zhanna has.
But Zhanna still has the disk...
It was never about stopping Zhanna.
I knew from my visions we
could never save all the Jedi.
It was about saving those we could.
But the Empire now has Sukaal's tracking
information.
They can finish us off.
Do you realize how many Jedi are going
to die?
Raux, surely in one of your other visions...
There were no Jedi in any future I saw but
this one.
There's no stopping the Empire
from getting the tagging information.
There's still hope, right?
We can save some.
Yes.
We will save some.
Because of you now I have
the power to destroy the Jedi.
They will meet their destiny.
You have indeed been useful.
Your service to the Empire is complete.
You have served me well.
Your loyalty will be rewarded.
My lord.
The fleet is awaiting your orders.
Set your course for Coruscant.
I will inform my master there is no longer
any concern
about the Emperor's Hand.
As you wish, my lord.
How did your meeting with the senator
go?
Surprisingly well, actually.
Senator Mothma's established quite a
network.
Things ar e starting to happen.
So, where will you go first?
Alderaan.
It seems that Senator Organa
is sympathetic to our cause.
We'll need his contacts. And his funding.
I'll start rounding up the Jedi.
Getting them on the move.
The Empire can't kill what they can't find.
It'll be like old times, eh?
Good.
Then I'll head to the Outer Rim
and look up my old friend.
I'm sure he can devise a way to r emove
these tags.
May the force be with you.
I'll meet you on Nar Shadaa.
I may be a while.
I'll wait.