Narrator: LIFE...
THE GREAT MIRACLE
AND THE GREAT MYSTERY.
WHO AM I?
SINCE THE BEGINNING,
HUMANS AND POKÉMON ALIKE
HAVE SEARCHED
FOR ITS MEANING.
WHAT AM I?
MANY STRANGE AND
WONDROUS LEGENDS EVOLVED
FROM THE PURSUIT
OF LIFE'S MYSTERIES.
WHERE AM I?
BUT NONE IS STRANGER
THAN THIS TALE
OF THE MOST POWERFUL
POKÉMON OF ALL.
I AM READY...
TO BE.
WHERE...AM I?
THIS--THIS IS NOT THE SAME.
WAS EVERYTHING BEFORE
JUST A DREAM?
WHY?
Female scientist:
DOCTOR, LOOK AT THIS.
Male scientist:
WHAT?
ITS BRAIN WAVES,
THEY'RE SURGING!
LET'S GO SEE!
SHE'S RIGHT!
Male scientist:
LET'S RUN ANOTHER SCAN.
ITS MIND IS RACING!
THOSE VOICES...
Male scientist: I HOPE
WE DON'T LOSE THIS ONE.
THEY'RE OUTSIDE...
WE CAN'T LOSE THIS ONE.
WHERE I MUST BE.
OH!
[ALARM SOUNDING]
RADIO GIOVANNI'S HELICOPTER!
TELL HIM WHAT'S HAPPENED!
Male scientist:
QUIET!
LET US HEAR
ITS PSYCHIC POWERS.
PSYCHIC POWERS?
FOR YEARS WE STRUGGLED TO
SUCCESSFULLY CLONE A POKÉMON
TO PROVE OUR THEORIES,
BUT YOU'RE THE FIRST
SPECIMEN TO SURVIVE.
THAT IS MEW,
THE RAREST OF ALL POKÉMON.
FROM ITS DNA
WE CREATED YOU--MEWTWO.
MEWTWO?
AM I ONLY A COPY?
NOTHING BUT MEW'S SHADOW?
YOU ARE GREATER THAN MEW,
IMPROVED THROUGH THE POWER
OF HUMAN INGENUITY.
WE USED THE MOST
ADVANCED TECHNIQUES
TO DEVELOP YOUR AWESOME
PSYCHIC POWERS.
SO, I AM SIMPLY THE END
RESULT OF YOUR EXPERIMENT.
WHAT BECOMES OF ME NOW THAT
YOUR EXPERIMENT IS OVER?
OUR EXPERIMENT ISN'T OVER YET.
IT'S JUST BEGINNING.
NOW THE SERIOUS
TESTING BEGINS.
THESE HUMANS,
THEY CARE NOTHING FOR ME.
CONGRATULATIONS.
WE'VE DONE IT.
[ALL TALKING AT ONCE]
IS THE NEW TANK READY?
NO. WE'LL HAVE TO
COME UP WITH A CAGE.
CONGRATULATIONS.
HA HA!
EXCELLENT. WE'LL START
OUR TESTING RIGHT AWAY.
IS THAT MY PURPOSE?
AM I JUST AN EXPERIMENT?
A LABORATORY SPECIMEN?
THIS CANNOT BE MY DESTINY.
OH!
AAH!
WE DREAMED OF CREATING
THE WORLD'S STRONGEST POKÉMON...
AND WE SUCCEEDED.
[HELICOPTER]
BEHOLD MY POWERS.
I AM THE STRONGEST
POKÉMON IN THE WORLD.
STRONGER EVEN THAN MEW.
THOSE FOOLS THOUGHT YOU
WERE A SCIENCE EXPERIMENT.
BUT I, I SEE YOU
AS A VALUABLE PARTNER.
PARTNER?
WITH YOUR PSYCHIC POWERS
AND MY RESOURCES,
TOGETHER WE CAN
CONTROL THE WORLD.
I DO NOT NEED YOUR HELP
FOR THAT, HUMAN.
A WILDFIRE DESTROYS
EVERYTHING IN ITS PATH.
IT WILL BE THE SAME
WITH YOUR POWERS
UNLESS YOU LEARN
TO CONTROL THEM.
I CAN HELP YOU DO THAT.
HOW?
TRUST ME, AND I'LL
SHOW YOU A WAY
TO FOCUS YOUR POWERS
THAT WILL MAKE YOU
INVINCIBLE.
SHOW ME.
[CHUCKLES]
YOU SAY THIS ARMOR
PROTECTS MY BODY,
YET IT SUPPRESSES
MY POWERS.
YOUR POWERS ARE NOT
BEING SUPPRESSED.
THEY'RE BEING FOCUSED.
LEARN TO USE THEM
TO ACCOMPLISH YOUR PURPOSE.
WHAT IS THAT?
PATIENCE, MY FRIEND.
YOUR PURPOSE
WILL BECOME CLEAR.
[ONIX GROWLS]
[SNAPS]
[ROARS]
SO, THIS IS MY POWER.
[MOOING]
I AM IN CONTROL NOW.
ALAKAZAM!
[GRUNTING]
KAZAM!
BUT WHY AM I HERE?
NOW I FULLY PERCEIVE
MY POWER.
BUT WHAT IS MY PURPOSE?
[FOOTSTEPS]
Giovanni:
TO SERVE YOUR MASTER.
YOU WERE CREATED
TO FIGHT FOR ME.
THAT IS YOUR PURPOSE.
THAT CANNOT BE.
YOU SAID
WE WERE PARTNERS.
WE STOOD AS EQUALS.
YOU WERE CREATED BY HUMANS
TO OBEY HUMANS.
YOU COULD NEVER
BE OUR EQUAL.
HUMANS MAY
HAVE CREATED ME,
BUT THEY WILL
NEVER ENSLAVE ME!
THIS CANNOT
BE MY DESTINY!
STOP THIS NOW!
I WAS NOT BORN
OF POKÉMON.
I WAS CREATED.
AND MY CREATORS HAVE
USED AND BETRAYED ME.
SO, I STAND ALONE!
AAH!
WHO AM I?
WHAT IS MY TRUE REASON
FOR BEING?
I WILL FIND
MY OWN PURPOSE...
AND PURGE THIS PLANET
OF ALL WHO OPPOSE ME.
HUMAN AND POKÉMON ALIKE.
THE WORLD
WILL HEED MY WARNING.
THE REIGN OF MEWTWO
WILL SOON BEGIN.
Narrator: TODAY,
ASH, BROCK, AND MISTY
ARE TAKING A SHORT BREAK
FROM THEIR POKÉMON ADVENTURES.
AS ALWAYS, ASH IS DETERMINED
TO BECOME A POKÉMON MASTER,
AND, AS ALWAYS, HE'S READY
TO ENDURE ANY HARDSHIP,
BEAR ANY BURDEN
WITH STRENGTH, STAMINA,
AND A WILL OF STEEL.
HUNGRY. NEED FOOD.
OH, ASH. YOU HAVEN'T
DONE A THING ALL DAY.
I'M TOO WEAK
TO WORK, MISTY.
I HAVEN'T EATEN
SINCE BREAKFAST.
OH.
THIS LUNCH IS GONNA BE
JUST PERFECT FOR YOU, ASH.
IT'S MY LAZY-BOY
NO-CHEW STEW.
TOGE TOGE!
PIKA?
TOGE?
[SQUEAKS]
HEY! YOU THERE!
I'M LOOKIN' FOR
A POKÉMON TRAINER
NAMED ASH
FROM PALLET TOWN.
YOU KNOW HIM?
YEAH, HE'S ME.
LET'S HAVE A MATCH.
UNLESS YOU'RE AFRAID
TO LOSE.
HA! I'M AFRAIDYOU'RE
GONNA LOSE THIS ONE.
ASH, YOU JUST SAID
YOU WERE TOO WEAK TO WORK.
THAT'S RIGHT,
I AM TOO WEAK TO WORK,
BUT A POKÉMON BATTLE
ISN'T WORK.
THAT'S PROGRESS.
AT LEAST HIS MOUTH
IS WORKING.
PIKACHU.
# I WANNA BE
THE VERY BEST #
# LIKE NO ONE EVER WAS #
# TO CATCH THEM
IS MY REAL TEST #
# TO TRAIN THEM IS MY CAUSE #
# WHOO WHOO WHOO #
# I WILL TRAVEL
ACROSS THE LAND #
# SEARCHING FAR AND WIDE #
# EACH POKÉMON
TO UNDERSTAND #
#
# THE POWER THAT'S INSIDE #
# INSIDE #
# POKÉMON #
# IT'S YOU AND ME #
# I KNOW IT'S MY DESTINY #
# POKÉMON #
# OOH, YOU'RE MY BEST FRIEND #
# IN A WORLD WE MUST DEFEND #
# POKÉMON #
# A HEART SO TRUE #
# OUR COURAGE
WILL PULL US THROUGH #
# YOU TEACH ME,
AND I'LL TEACH YOU #
# POKÉMON #
#
# GOTTA CATCH 'EM #
# GOTTA CATCH 'EM ALL #
GREAT JOB,
BULBASAUR. HA.
YOU DID IT.
# EVERY CHALLENGE #
# ALONG THE WAY #
#
# WITH COURAGE I WILL FACE
# I WILL BATTLE EVERYTHING
#
# CLAIM MY RIGHTFUL PLACE #
# COME WITH ME,
THE TIME IS RIGHT #
# THERE'S NO BETTER TEAM,
YEAH #
# ARM IN ARM,
WE'LL WIN THE FIGHT #
# IT'S ALWAYS
BEEN A DREAM #
#
# IT'S ALWAYS BEEN A DREAM
# POKÉMON #
# IT'S YOU AND ME #
# I KNOW IT'S MY DESTINY #
# POKÉMON #
# OOH,
YOU'RE MY BEST FRIEND #
# IN A WORLD WE MUST DEFEND #
# POKÉMON #
# I'M, OH, SO TRUE #
HA HA HA HA!
# YOU TEACH ME,
AND I'LL TEACH YOU #
# POKÉMON #
# I'LL TEACH YOU #
# GOTTA CATCH 'EM #
PIKA...
# GOTTA CATCH 'EM ALL #
CHU!
UHH!
OH, NO!
WE DID IT!
PIKA!
WELL, THAT SURE WAS
A SHOCKING ENDING.
SHOCKING THAT ASH
MOVED SO FAST.
TOGE!
HA HA HA!
PIKACHU.
THERE'S
ANOTHER CREDIT
ON PIKACHU'S
CHARGE ACCOUNT.
WE'VE GOT TO GRAB IT.
I KNOW WE GOT TO GRAB SOME
RARE POKÉMON FOR THE BOSS,
BUT IT WOULDN'T BE
SUCH A BAD IDEA
IF WE GRABBED A LITTLE
BITE TO EAT, WOULD IT?
WE DIDN'T COME HERE
TO STEAL A MEAL.
I'D SETTLE FOR A TASTE
OF THAT PIKA-CHOW.
PIKA. PIKA.
PIKA.
SQUIRT.
[GROANS]
I'M STARVIN'.
I CAN COOK SOMETHING.
THANKS, BUT THE LAST TIME
YOU COOKED,
YOU WIPED OUT
8 OF MY 9 LIVES.
[ALL SIGH]
PIKA PIKA...CHU!
[CHUCKLES]
[SQUEAKS]
HA HA HA!
[CAWS]
MASTER, SHALL I
EXTEND AN INVITATION
TO THESE TRAINERS
AS WELL?
AS YOU WISH.
[GRUNTS]
HUH? HUH?
HUH?
OHH!
YEOW!
AAH! AAH!
SQUIRT!
HEY, WATCH WHERE
YOU'RE FLYIN'.
HUH? SOMETHIN' FOR ME?
HMM...
Misty: WOW!
GREETINGS,
POKÉMON TRAINERS.
I BEAR AN INVITATION.
SHE'S REALLY SMALL,
BUT REALLY PRETTY.
YOU HAVE BEEN CHOSEN
TO JOIN A SELECT GROUP
OF POKÉMON TRAINERS
AT A SPECIAL GATHERING.
IT WILL BE HOSTED
BY MY MASTER,
THE WORLD'S GREATEST
POKÉMON TRAINER,
AT HIS PALACE
ON NEW ISLAND.
A CHARTERED FERRY
WILL LEAVE FROM
OLD SHORE WHARF
TO TAKE YOU TO THE
ISLAND THIS AFTERNOON.
ONLY TRAINERS WHO
PRESENT THIS INVITATION
WILL BE ADMITTED.
IF YOU DECIDE TO ATTEND,
YOU MUST REPLY AT ONCE.
MY MASTER AWAITS YOU.
UH, IS THERE
A REWIND BUTTON?
SHOULD WE GO?
OF COURSE WE SHOULD!
I'VE GOTTA MEET HER!
I GUESS THE WORLD'S
NUMBER ONE TRAINER
WANTS TO CHALLENGE
ME TO A MATCH!
PIKA.
HMM? WELL, WE'VE GOTTA
LET 'EM KNOW RIGHT AWAY.
I'M SAYIN' YES.
PIKA?
TOGE.
[GRUNTS]
WE WANNA KNOW
WHAT'S SO SPECIAL
ABOUT THE TWERP TRIO'S
SPECIAL DELIVERY!
HEY, LOOK!
"YES"? TO WHAT?
MEW.
[TOGEPI SQUEAKS]
PIKA. PIKA. PI.
RATICATE!
CHILL OUT, RATICATE!
KINGLER!
SAVE YOUR ENERGY, WILL YA?
THIS IS GONNA BE
SO COOL.
P.A.: OFFICER JENNY,
PLEASE REPORT
TO THE FERRY ENTRANCE.
OFFICER JENNY,
TO THE FERRY ENTRANCE,
PLEASE.
TOGEPI'S
TOTALLY SOAKED.
I CAN'T BELIEVE HOW FAST
THE STORM CAME UP.
AAH!
HUH?
WHAT?
THE FERRY IS
CANCELED?
BUT I'VE GOT TO GET
TO NEW ISLAND.
YEAH, SO DO I.
WHAT'S THE BIG DEAL?
IT'S ONLY
A LITTLE RAIN.
IT'S MORE
THAN JUST RAIN.
THE HARBOR MANAGER
THINKS THIS COULD BE
THE WORST STORM EVER.
LISTEN TO ME.
THE PROPHETS HAVE PREDICTED
THE RETURN OF
THE WINDS OF WATER.
FOR YEARS, I HAVE PRAYED
THAT MANKIND
WOULD NEVER WITNESS
THAT DEADLY STORM
EVER AGAIN.
ISN'T THAT
JUST A LEGEND?
THE ANCIENT WRITINGS
TELL OF THE STORM
WIPING OUT ALL
BUT A FEW POKÉMON.
IN THEIR SORROW,
THE WATER OF THEIR TEARS
SOMEHOW RESTORED THE LIVES
LOST IN THE STORM.
BUT THERE ARE
NO POKÉMON TEARS TODAY.
JUST WATERS WHICH
NO ONE CAN SURVIVE.
AND THAT'S WHY
YOUR FERRY
TO NEW ISLAND'S
BEEN CANCELED.
WELL, I'M GOING TO
NEW ISLAND ANYWAY.
ALL MY POKÉMON
ARE WATER-TYPE.
NO FAIR.
WE'LL JUST SWIM OVER
TO THAT PALACE.
I WARN YOU,
THE WAVES WILL BE SAVAGE.
YOU WILL NEVER MAKE IT.
AND BESIDES,
IF YOU TRIED THAT STUNT
AND YOUR POKÉMON GOT HURT,
YOU'D BE OUT OF LUCK,
BECAUSE WE HAD TO CLOSE DOWN
THE POKÉMON CENTER.
UH, HOW COME?
BECAUSE THE NURSE
IN CHARGE OF THE CENTER
DISAPPEARED LAST MONTH.
AND IF ANY OF YOU SEE HER,
PLEASE CONTACT ME AT ONCE.
THAT'S A PICTURE OF HER
OVER THERE ON THE WALL.
MMM. SHE'S CUTE.
HUH.
SHE SURE
LOOKS FAMILIAR.
AAH! AAH!
[ROARS]
AAH!
COME BACK HERE!
OR I'LL PLACE YOU
UNDER ARREST!
DEWGONG-GONG.
COME BACK! AAH!
SOME TRAINERS
HAVE NO FEAR.
HUH?
TO THEM, THIS IS JUST
ONE MORE CHALLENGE.
THEY FOLLOW
THEIR HEARTS.
THAT IS WHAT
SETS THEM APART
AND WILL MAKE THEM
POKÉMON MASTERS.
GOOD LUCK TO ALL OF YOU.
THE WORLD'S GREATEST
POKÉMON MASTER
IS WAITING FOR ME.
LET'S USE OUR POKÉMON
TO GET TO THAT ISLAND.
PIKA!
ASH, OUR POKÉMON
AREN'T STRONG ENOUGH.
THEY CAN'T HANDLE
GIANT WAVES LIKE THIS.
GUESS YOU'RE RIGHT.
PIKA PIKA.
[SCANDINAVIAN ACCENT]
YOU VANT TO CROSS MAYBE?
VE TAKE YOU,JA?
VE VIKINGS ARE USED
TO BIG VAVES.
VE GET TO NEW ISLAND
FASTER THAN YOU CAN SAY
FAHRVERNUGEN.
STROKE!
UHH!
UHH! UHH!
STROKE! STROKE!
STROKE!
OH, I THINK I'M
GONNA HAVE ONE.
I DIDN'T KNOW VIKINGS
STILL EXISTED.
THEY MOSTLY LIVE
IN MINNESOTA.
SOMETHING'S NOT RIGHT.
ARE YOU SURE
THIS BOAT'S SAFE?
WHOA!
PIKA!
DON'T VORRY. THIS SHIP
VON'T LET YOU DOWN.
VE ALVAYS SAIL
IN DA ROUGH VEATHER.
DON'T GET UPSET.
TELL MY STOMACH.
HEAVE.
HO.
IT'S ALL RIGHT, TOGEPI.
WE'RE GONNA BE OK.
HEAVE.
HO.
WHOA!
WHOA! WHOA!
PIKA!
WHOA!
WHOA! WHOA!
THOSE AREN'T VIKINGS!
IT'S TEAM ROCKET.
I SHOULD'VE KNOWN THERE WAS
SOMETHING FISHY ABOUT THEM
BESIDES THE WAY THEY SMELL.
HA!
PREPARE FOR TROUBLE.
MAKE IT DOUBLE.
Meowth: FORGET THE MOTTO.
WE'RE GONNA HAVE TO--
AAH! AAH!
AAH!
Staryu: HYAH!
HYAH!
ASH! MISTY!
UHH! OHH!
AAH!
HAVE YOU SEEN ASH
AND PIKACHU?
NOT YET.
AAH!
[GASPS]
STAY TOGETHER.
IT'S OUR ONLY HOPE.
PIKA!
WHOA! WHOA!
WHOA!
[GRUNTING]
UHH. SQUIRTLE.
SQUIRTLE.
[GASPING, PANTING]
HUH?
PI PIKA!
HMM?
HEY, LOOK!
[TOGEPI SQUEAKS]
MY MASTER BIDS YOU
WELCOME TO NEW ISLAND.
WILL YOU KINDLY PRESENT
YOUR INVITATION?
UH...UM...
HERE IT IS, MISS.
THE BEARERS
OF THIS INVITATION
MAY BE ADMITTED
TO NEW ISLAND.
I KNEW I RECOGNIZED
THAT FACE.
WHAT?
Brock:
AREN'T YOU THE NURSE
WHO'S MISSING FROM
THE TREATMENT CENTER?
YOU DO LOOK
JUST LIKE HER.
I FEAR
YOU ARE MISTAKEN.
I HAVE ALWAYS
DWELT ON THIS ISLAND
AND HAVE ALWAYS BEEN IN
THE SERVICE OF MY MASTER.
PLEASE, COME THIS WAY.
MY MASTER AWAITS
YOUR ARRIVAL.
UHH! UHH!
MEW.
MEW!
MEW. MEW.
UHH.
HMM...
HUH?
[DOORS CREAK OPEN]
NOW THAT YOU ARE HERE,
ALL TRAINERS
WORTHY OF AN AUDIENCE
WITH MY MASTER ARE PRESENT.
HUH?
Wigglytuff: WIGGLY.
WIGGLY.
THERE'S ONLY
3 OF 'EM.
AREN'T WE GOING TO
WAIT FOR THE OTHERS?
ONLY THE TRAINERS CAPABLE
OF BRAVING THE STORM
HAVE PROVEN THEMSELVES WORTHY
IN MY MASTER'S EYES.
DO YOU MEAN THAT STORM
WAS SOME KIND OF TEST?
PLEASE RELEASE YOUR POKÉMON
FROM THEIR POKÉBALLS
AND JOIN THE OTHERS.
IT WILL NOT BE LONG
BEFORE MY MASTER'S
INTENTIONS ARE CLEAR.
HUH? HUH?
HUH?
LOCKED OUT.
NOW WE'LL NEVER KNOW
WHAT KIND OF PARTY
WE'RE MISSING.
THEN WE'LL JUST HAVE TO
CRASH THAT PARTY.
YOU KNOW
ANOTHER WAY IN?
LOOK OVER THERE.
HUH?
AAH!
BUT, JESSIE,
HOW ARE WE GONNA
SWIM UP THAT THING?
PRETEND YOU'RE
A CATFISH.
HUH? HUH?
SOMETHING WRONG,
JESSIE?
NO. COME ON.
LET'S GET GOING.
I THINK THIS PLAN'S
ALL WET.
PIKA. PI.
[TOGEPI SQUEAKS]
PSY-YI-YI DUCK.
WHAT TOOK YOU GUYS
SO LONG?
UH, WELL,
HOW'D YOU GET HERE?
I DECIDED TO FLY OVER.
IT WAS EASY.
HURRICANE WINDS ARE A BREEZE
FOR PIDGEOTTO HERE.
HEY, GUYS, SAY HELLO.
[CHATTERING]
WHOA!
Fergus:
THOSE ARE MY POKÉMON.
IT WAS NO PROBLEM GETTING
THROUGH THAT STORM.
I RODE OVER
ON GYARADOS' BACK.
WOW. I HEARD IT
TAKES A LOT OF SKILL
TO TRAIN GYARADOS.
YEAH.
BUT ONCE YOU TRAIN IT,
IT'S THE MOST DEPENDABLE
POKÉMON THERE IS.
[ROARS]
YOU HAVEN'T MET
MY POKÉMON.
OVER THERE.
[CHATTERING]
[ALL YELL]
[TRAINERS CHUCKLE]
HUH?
[SQUEAKS]
PI?
YOU ARE ABOUT TO
MEET MY MASTER.
THE TIME HAS COME
FOR YOUR ENCOUNTER
WITH THE GREATEST
POKÉMON MASTER ON EARTH.
[ROARS]
[GRUNTS]
PIKA.
[SQUEAKS]
[GROWLS]
WHAT'S THAT?
PIKA.
HUH?
HMM?
HMM...
[GRUNTS]
AH. PIKA.
AH. AH.
YES, THE WORLD'S
GREATEST POKÉMON MASTER
IS ALSO THE MOST
POWERFUL POKÉMON
ON EARTH.
THIS IS THE RULER
OF NEW ISLAND
AND SOON
THE WHOLE WORLD.
MEWTWO.
PIKA.
A POKÉMON CAN'T BE
A POKÉMON MASTER!
NO WAY!
Both: QUIET, HUMAN.
FROM NOW ON I AM THE ONE
WHO MAKES THE RULES.
HOW'S IT TALKING?
IT'S PSYCHIC.
UHH!
AAH!
AAH! AAH!
HEE HEE HEE.
AAH!
WE'LL SHOW YOU!
LET'S GO,
GYARADOS!
[ROARS]
UHH! GYARADOS,
HYPERBEAM ATTACK!
[ROARS]
OH! OH!
OH! EEE!
GYARADOS!
Both: CHILD'S PLAY.
YOUR USEFULNESS
HAS ENDED.
HUH?
OHH. OHH.
NURSE JOY!
WHERE AM I?
AND HOW IN THE WORLD
DID I GET HERE?
Mewtwo: YOU HAVE BEEN
UNDER MY CONTROL.
I TRANSPORTED YOU HERE
FROM THE POKÉMON CENTER.
YOUR KNOWLEDGE
OF POKÉMON PHYSIOLOGY
PROVED USEFUL FOR MY PLAN.
AND NOW I HAVE CLEANSED
YOUR TINY HUMAN BRAIN
OF MEMORIES
FROM THE PAST FEW WEEKS.
WHO ARE YOU?!
I AM THE NEW RULER
OF THIS WORLD,
THE MASTER OF HUMANS
AND POKÉMON ALIKE.
YOU'RE JUST A BULLY!
PIKA!
HMM?
HUH? HMM?
HUH?
HMM?
[ALL GASP]
LOOK AT THESE.
THEY'RE POKÉMON.
ARE THEY REAL?
HMM.
[SIGHS]
I WAS HOPING
THERE'D BE A PARTY.
HMPH.
HUH?
[ALL GASP]
Computer: THIS IS THE POKÉMON
REPLICATION SYSTEM.
SYSTEM ACTIVATED.
POKÉMON BASED ON
GENETIC ANALYSIS.
POKÉMON
DNA SAMPLING SEQUENCE
NOW IN PROGRESS.
HUHH! HEY, PUT ME DOWN!
WHAT ARE YA--LET GO!
UHH!
HELP!
GRAB HIM!
HELP ME!
[ALL GRUNTING]
YEE-YEOW!
AAH!
I MADE IT,
BUT JUST BY A HAIR.
Jessie: LOOK,
THERE'S YOUR HAIR.
Computer: ANALYZING POKÉMON
BIOMATERIAL SAMPLE.
ANALYSIS COMPLETE.
POKÉMON IDENTIFIED.
BEGIN REPLICATION SEQUENCE.
James: WHO'S
THAT POKÉMON?
IT'S MEOWTH.
AAH!
HUH?
MEOWTH! MEOWTH!
BUTI'MMEOWTH.
SO'S THE ONE
IN THE TANK.
THAT'S YOUR CLONE.
HUH?
Male scientist:
I HAVEN'T GOT MUCH TIME.
[SCIENTISTS SCREAMING]
I PRAY THIS RECORD OF
OUR EXPERIMENT SURVIVES.
A YEAR AGO, WE DISCOVERED
A FOSSIL THAT PROVED TO BE
THE REMAINS OF
THE ANCIENT POKÉMON, MEW.
HUH? HUH?
HUH?
THERE WAS SUFFICIENT GENETIC
MATERIAL TO REPLICATE MEW,
BUT GIOVANNI,
WHO FUNDED OUR PROJECT,
INSISTED WE TRY TO DESIGN
SUPERCLONES
MORE POWERFUL
THAN ANY LIVING POKÉMON.
MANY ATTEMPTS FAILED,
BUT FINALLY OUR EXPERIMENTS
PROVED SUCCESSFUL.
WE PRODUCED
A LIVING POKÉMON.
WE CALLED IT MEWTWO.
BUT FOR SOME REASON,
THE CREATURE'S ANGER
IS OUT OF CONTROL.
WITH ITS PSYCHIC POWERS,
IT IS DESTROYING
OUR LABORATORY.
WE DREAMED OF CREATING
THE WORLD'S STRONGEST POKÉMON...
AND WE SUCCEEDED.
SOUNDS LIKE
A REAL POKÉNSTEIN.
SURE DOES.
ONE BAD CAT.
SO THIS MUST BE
THE LAB.
BUT IF MEWTWO
DESTROYED IT...
SOMEBODY
REBUILT IT.
YES. BUT WHO?
HMM. HMM.
HMM.
Mewtwo: YOU HUMANS ARE
A DANGEROUS SPECIES.
YOU BROUGHT ME
INTO YOUR WORLD
WITH NO PURPOSE
BUT TO BE YOUR SLAVE.
BUT NOW
I HAVE MY OWN PURPOSE.
MY STORM WILL CREATE
MY OWN WORLD...
BY DESTROYING YOURS.
SO YOU HATE
ALL HUMANS,
AND YOU'RE GONNA
DESTROY US
TO SAVE POKÉMON.
NO. YOUR POKÉMON
WILL NOT BE SPARED.
THEY HAVE DISGRACED
THEMSELVES
BY SERVING HUMANS.
THOSE POKÉMON ARE NOTHING
BUT SLAVES.
PIKA. PIKA PIKA.
SO...
YOU SAY I AM WRONG?
THAT YOU ARE NOT
THIS HUMAN'S SERVANT,
YOU ARE HIS FRIEND?
PIKA.
YOU ARE AS PATHETIC
AS THE REST.
PIKA.
Ash: HUH?
PIKA!
UHH!
AAH! PIKA-PI.
PIKACHU.
HUMANS AND POKÉMON
CAN NEVER BE FRIENDS.
ASH...
ARE YOU OK?
DON'T PICK ON PIKACHU.
IF YOU ARE POKÉMON,
THERE'S NO REASON
I CAN'T CAPTURE YOU.
GO, RHYHORN.
[ROARS]
OHH!
NO! RHYHORN!
Mewtwo: FOOLS.
YOUR POKÉMON ATTACKS
CANNOT WEAKEN ME.
MY POWERS ARE TOO GREAT.
NO TRAINER CAN CONQUER ME.
THEN YOU WON'T MIND
PROVING IT
IN A REAL MATCH.
IS THAT A CHALLENGE?
YOU BET IT IS.
HMM?
HUH?
[ALL GASP]
THEY'RE AWAKE.
BLAAAST!
[ROARS]
SAUR.
[SHUDDERING]
HMM?
James:
I'M SCARED.
Jessie: ME, TOO.
MEOWTH.
Mewtwo: LIKE MOST
POKÉMON TRAINERS,
I, TOO, BEGAN
WITH CHARMANDER,
SQUIRTLE,
AND BULBASAUR.
BUT FOR THEIR EVOLVED FORMS,
I USED THEIR
GENETIC MATERIAL
TO CLONE EVEN MORE
POWERFUL COPIES.
COPIES.
THEY'RE CLONES.
[ALL GASP]
[RUMBLING]
[ROARS]
BLAAAST!
A STADIUM.
MEWTWO PLANNED THIS
ALL ALONG.
YOUR FAKE VENUSAUR
CAN'T BEAT MY REAL ONE!
RIGHT, BRUTEROOT?
SAUR.
WE'LL BLOW AWAY
THAT BLASTOISE,
WON'T WE,
SHELLSHOCKER?
BLAAST!
IT MAY NOT HAVE
A NICKNAME,
BUT I DO HAVE...
CHARIZARD.
I CHOOSE YOU!
CHARIZARD,
I DIDN'T SAY START.
PIK.
YOUR CHARIZARD
IS POORLY TRAINED.
[GROWLS]
HMM.
Mewtwo: WHICH OF YOU
WILL OPPOSE ME FIRST?
SAUR.
I UNDERESTIMATED YOU
LAST TIME,
BUT THAT WON'T
HAPPEN AGAIN.
GO, BRUTEROOT!
RAZOR LEAF!
SAUR.
VINE WHIP.
SAUR!
[GROANS]
BRUTEROOT!
IT LOOKS LIKE I'M UP.
GO, SHELLSHOCKER.
BLASTOISE.
BLAAST!
SHELLSHOCKER,
HYDROPUMP!
BLAST!
OY!
SHELLSHOCKER!
YOU BETTER
FORFEIT, ASH.
THOSE CLONES
ARE TOO POWERFUL.
I'M NOT GIVING UP.
[ROARS]
CHARIZARD,
USE YOUR SPEED,
NOT POWER,
AND YOU'LL WIN.
[GROWLS]
ALL RIGHT, GO!
[BOTH GROWLING]
CAN'T CHARIZARD
MOVE ANY QUICKER?
THE CLONE IS TOO FAST.
PIKA.
CHARIZARD'S IN TROUBLE!
FINISH IT.
[ROARS]
NO, CHARIZARD, NO!
ARE YOU OK?
Mewtwo: AS THE VICTOR,
I NOW CLAIM MY PRIZE--
YOUR POKÉMON.
NO.
HEY, WAIT!
[GASPS]
OHH!
HUH?
WHAT ARE YOU GOING TO DO
WITH THOSE POKÉMON?
I WILL EXTRACT THEIR DNA
TO MAKE CLONES FOR MYSELF.
THEY WILL REMAIN SAFE
ON THIS ISLAND WITH ME
WHILE MY STORM
DESTROYS THE PLANET.
YOU CAN'T DO THIS!
YEAH, MEWTWO,
WE WON'T LET YOU!
DO NOT ATTEMPT
TO DEFY ME.
AAH!
UHH!
THIS IS
MY WORLD NOW.
OHH!
UH-OH.
LET'S GO!
WHOA!
[ROARS]
GYARADOS!
[BOTH GRUNTING]
GET AWAY!
GONG!
HUH?
PIKA. PIK.
[MOANS]
PIDGEOT!
[CAWS]
AW...
HEY, I KNOW.
MEWTWO
CAN'T CAPTURE THEM
IF THEY'RE ALREADY
INSIDE THEIR POKÉBALLS.
BULBASAUR, SQUIRTLE,
RETURN!
IT IS NO USE.
HA HA HA!
HUH?
IT IS FUTILE TO TRY
AND ESCAPE MY POWER.
UHH!
NEVER MIND
THE POKÉBALLS.
CARRY 'EM AWAY.
PSY-YI-YI!
HUH?
GIVE BACK MY PSYDUCK!
UHH! VULPIX!
[PANTING]
AAH!
PIKA!
UHH! RUN, PIKACHU!
PIKA PIKA PIKA PIKA.
PIKA PIKA. PIKA? PIKA!
PIKA PIKA PIKA
PIKA PIKA.
PIKA PIKA PIKA PIKA.
PIKA PIKA
PIKA PIKA PIKA.
PIKACHU!
PIKA...CHU!
[PANTING]
PIKA PIKA PIKA PIKA
PIKA PIKA PIKA.
KEEP RUNNING, PIKACHU!
PIKACHU!
PIKA PIKACHU!
PIKA PIKA PIKA
PIKACHU!
PIKA PIKACHU!
[PANTING]
PIKA PIKA PIKA PIKA.
UHH! WHOA!
PIKACHU!
[SQUAWKS]
PIKA.
PIK--
AAH!
PIKACHU!
EHH!
AAH!
PIKA!
WHOA!
HEY!
YOU'RE NOT GONNA
GET PIKACHU!
THERE GOES...
ALAKAZAM...
DEWGONG...
VILEPLUME!
Meowth: SANDSHREW.
NIDOQUEEN. VAPOREON.
BUT ME, I GOT A SPECIAL PLACE
IN MY TAIL FOR THIS ONE.
[THUD]
[ASH GRUNTS]
HUH?
OHH...
EEE!
LOOK THERE!
UHH.
AAH! I DON'T HAVE TIME
FOR YOUR DUMB MOTTO TODAY.
AAH! UHH!
AAH!
Both: WHO'S
THAT POKÉMON?
IT'S PIKACHU!
OW! LET GO!
STUPID MACHINE!
GIMME BACK MY PIKACHU!
AAH!
[ALARM SOUNDING]
WHAT'S HAPPENING?
AHH.
PBBLT-PFFT!
PIKACHU!
PIKA?
PIKA-PI!
[LAUGHING]
[SQUEALS]
I'M SO GLAD
YOU'RE OK.
[WHIMPERING]
THE COPIES
ARE HATCHING.
THEY'RE FABULOUS FAKES.
SEND IN THE CLONES.
BUT WHERE ARE
THE REAL ONES?
PIKA?
[ALARM SOUNDING
LOUDER AND FASTER]
I WONDER
IF THEY FEEL...
CLONESOME.
WHOA! WHOA!
WHOA!
[GASPING, WHIMPERING]
THE POKÉ ORIGINALS.
Tentacruel:
TENTACRUEL.
SQUIRTLE.
SQUIRTLE'S BACK!
PIKA!
HA HA HA!
SQUIRT.
BULBA.
PIKA! PIKA!
SAUR?
BULBA!
OH,
YOU'RE ALL OK!
Bulbasaur: SAUR!
HA HA HA HA.
Bulbasaur:
BULBASAUR!
HMM?
HUMANS, YOU HAVE SERVED
MY PURPOSE.
I AM SPARING YOUR LIVES,
FOR THE MOMENT.
[DOORS CREAK OPEN]
BUT YOU CANNOT ESCAPE
YOUR FATE.
THE HOUR OF MY VENGEANCE
DRAWS NEAR.
BEHOLD.
AH.
OHH.
Mewtwo: WITH POKÉMON
AND HUMANS ELIMINATED,
THE CLONES SHALL
INHERIT THE WORLD.
Ash: YOU CAN'T DO THIS.
I WON'T LET YOU.
IT'S ASH.
ALL RIGHT.
PSY-YI-YI.
DUCK.
PSYDUCK!
VULPIX!
Mewtwo: IT IS USELESS
TO CHALLENGE ME.
IT'S NOT GOING TO END
LIKE THIS, MEWTWO.
WE WON'T LET IT.
YOU'RE MINE.
AAH!
UHH!
UGH!
ASH, NO!
LOOK OUT!
AAH!
UHH!
WHAT?
WHOA!
OHH!
[LAUGHS]
CAN IT BE?
WHOA!
MEW!
[LAUGHS]
WHAT IS THAT?
I DON'T KNOW.
MEW.
SO, FINALLY,
WE MEET.
MEW.
MEW?
I MAY HAVE BEEN CLONED
FROM YOUR DNA,
BUT NOW I WILL PROVE
THAT MEWTWO IS BETTER
THAN THE ORIGINAL--
SUPERIOR TO MEW.
MEW.
MEW AND MEWTWO.
SO MEWTWO
WAS CLONED FROM MEW.
PIKA.
SAUR.
THIS WORLD IS TOO SMALL
FOR 2 OF US.
MEW.
WHOA!
OHH.
WHY DO YOU FLEE FROM ME?
ARE YOU AFRAID TO FIND OUT
WHICH OF US IS GREATER?
MEW!
HEH HEH.
[ALL GASP]
PIKA.
OHH.
UHH!
SO, YOU DO HAVE
SOME FIGHT IN YOU,
BUT I HAVE NO TIME
FOR GAMES.
DESTINY IS AT HAND.
WHO WILL RULE?
MY SUPERPOKÉMON
OR YOUR PATHETIC GROUP
OF SPINELESS,
INFERIOR POKÉMON?
MEW.
WE WERE CREATED
WITH POWERS FAR STRONGER
THAN THE ORIGINALS.
[MEOWING]
HUH?
HMM. MEW'S
GOT A GOOD POINT.
WHAT'S IT SAYING?
MEW SAYS YOU DON'T
PROVE ANYTHING
BY SHOWING OFF A LOT
OF SPECIAL POWERS,
AND THAT A POKÉMON'S
REAL STRENGTH
COMES FROM THE HEART.
MY CLONES DON'T NEED
THEIR POWERS
TO PROVE THEIR WORTH.
MEW!
AAH! AAH!
AAH!
Mewtwo: I WILL BLOCK
ALL THE POKÉMON'S
SPECIAL ABILITIES
USING
MY PSYCHIC POWERS.
NOW WE SHALL SEE
WHO TRIUMPHS.
GO!
[CREATURES ROAR]
PI.
PI?
PIKA.
[ECHOES]
[STRAINS]
AHH...
HUH?
# BROTHER #
# MY BROTHER #
# TELL ME, WHAT ARE
WE FIGHTING FOR? #
# WE'VE GOT TO END
THIS WAR #
# WE SHOULD LOVE #
# ONE ANOTHER #
# OH, CAN'T WE JUST
PRETEND #
# THIS WAR NEVER BEGAN? #
# WE CAN TRY #
# BROTHER, MY BROTHER #
[BOTH MOAN]
# WE FACE EACH OTHER #
# FROM DIFFERENT SIDES #
# THE ANGER BURNS #
# CAN'T REMEMBER WHY #
# IT'S KINDA CRAZY #
# TO CAUSE SUCH PAIN #
# OUR FOOLISH PRIDE #
# MAKES US
HATE THIS WAY #
[ROARS]
# WE WATCH OUR WORLD
FALL APART #
# TELL ME, WHAT GOOD
IS WINNING #
# WHEN YOU LOSE
YOUR HEART? #
PSY!
DUCK!
# BROTHER #
# MY BROTHER #
# TELL ME, WHAT ARE WE
FIGHTING FOR? #
# ISN'T LIFE
WORTH SO MUCH MORE? #
# TO LOVE ONE ANOTHER #
# OH, CAN'T WE
JUST PRETEND #
# THIS WAR NEVER BEGAN? #
# TELL ME WHY #
PIKA.
[CAWS]
# BROTHER,
MY BROTHER #
# YEAH #
WHOA!
# WE CAN TRY #
PIKACHU!
# BROTHER, MY BROTHER #
PIKA!
[CREATURE NOISES
INAUDIBLE]
POKÉMON AREN'T MEANT
TO FIGHT--
NOT LIKE THIS.
IT'S USELESS.
WHAT CAN COME OUT OF IT?
NOTHING...
BUT PAIN.
WHY CAN'T MEWTWO
UNDERSTAND
IT'S NOT RIGHT
TO FORCE POKÉMON
TO BATTLE THIS WAY?
THEY'RE ALL
LIVING CREATURES.
Misty: THIS JUST PROVES
THAT FIGHTING IS WRONG.
[BOTH MOAN]
James: I WAS PREPARED
FOR TROUBLE,
BUT NOT FOR THIS.
Jessie: MAKE THAT
DOUBLE FOR ME.
NOW I CAN SEE HOW HORRIBLE
FIGHTING REALLY IS.
EVEN THE BEST OF FRIENDS
WILL FIGHT SOMETIMES.
I'LL PROMISE NEVER
TO FIGHT AGAIN IF YOU WILL.
OH, JESSIE.
OH, JAMES.
[BOTH SOB]
HMM.
HMM? AAH!
[GROWLS]
HEY, WHAT AM I DOING?
[MEOWS]
LET'S GET SOMETHING
STRAIGHT, COPYCAT.
YOU-OWTH AIN'T GOING
TO PUSH MEOWTH AROUND.
[MEOWS]
YOU MEAN WE DON'T HAVE
TO FIGHT WITH EACH OTHER?
BUT HOW CAN I TRUST YOU?
YOU WAS BORN DIFFERENT.
[MEOWS]
I ALMOST MADE
A CLAWFUL MISTAKE.
BUT HOW DO I KNOW YOU'RE NOT
GOING TO PULL A FAST ONE ON ME?
[MEOWS]
HMM?
Meowth:
YOU'RE RIGHT.
WE DO HAVE A LOT
IN COMMON--
THE SAME EARTH,
THE SAME AIR,
THE SAME SKY.
[MEOWS]
MAYBE IF
WE STARTED LOOKING
AT WHAT'S THE SAME,
INSTEAD OF ALWAYS LOOKING
AT WHAT'S DIFFERENT...
WELL, WHO KNOWS?
[MEOWS]
[PANTS]
PIKA.
PIKACHU!
PIKA. PIKA.
PIKACHU.
PIKA!
PIKACHU!
UHH.
AAH!
UHH! OW!
UHH...
PIKACHU!
PIKACHU.
PIKA! PIKA!
[CREATURES GROANING]
CHU!
CHU! CHU!
PIKACHU!
CHU!
QUIT IT!
PLEASE STOP!
OHH!
ASH.
ARE YOU OK?
WE GOT TO STOP THIS.
BUT HOW?
ALL MEWTWO CARES ABOUT
IS PROVING HOW STRONG
THOSE SUPERCLONES ARE.
I'D RATHER RISK MY LIFE
OUT IN MEWTWO'S STORM
THAN WATCH THESE POKÉMON
DESTROY EACH OTHER.
OH, ME, TOO.
I WISH THERE WAS
SOME WAY TO STOP THEM.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT TO DO.
[BOTH ROAR]
I DON'T THINK
THEY'LL EVER STOP.
THOSE POKÉMON
LOOK LIKE THEY'RE READY
TO FIGHT TO THE DEATH.
THAT'S A FIGHT THAT
NOBODY'S GOING TO WIN.
SOMEONE'S
GOT TO TAKE A STAND.
SOMEONE'S GOT TO SAY NO
AND REFUSE TO FIGHT,
JUST LIKE PIKACHU.
CHU!
PIKA...
PIKA.
[ALL GASP]
[ELECTRICITY CRACKLES]
Ash: OHH.
OHH.
[STRAINS]
ASH, WAIT!
YOU'VE GOT TO STOP
RIGHT NOW!
STOP!
ASH!
OH, NO!
PIKA PI--
FOOL.
TRYING TO STOP
OUR BATTLE.
[MEOWS]
PIKA-PI!
PIKACHU?
PIKA.
PIKA-PI.
[BOTH GROWL]
PIKA...
CHU!
PLEASE, NO.
[SHRIEKS]
CHU!
[PANTS]
PIKA.
PIKA...
CHU!
PIKA.
PIKA-PI.
DEWGONG!
[BOTH GROWL]
SAUR.
SQUIRTLE.
[BOTH GROWL]
[GROANS]
[ALL MOAN]
[GROWLS]
[MOANS]
[GASPS]
OHH.
PIKA-PI.
PI?
PIKA.
HUH?
OH.
MMM.
PIKACHU.
PIKA-PI!
[LAUGHS]
TOGEPI!
SQUIRT.
SQUIRTLE.
[BOTH GROWL]
PSY.
[HISSES]
A HUMAN
SACRIFICED HIMSELF
TO SAVE THE POKÉMON.
I PITTED THEM
AGAINST EACH OTHER,
BUT NOT UNTIL THEY
SET ASIDE THEIR DIFFERENCES
DID I SEE
THE TRUE POWER
THEY ALL SHARED
DEEP INSIDE.
MEW.
I SEE NOW
THAT THE CIRCUMSTANCES
OF ONE'S BIRTH
ARE IRRELEVANT.
IT IS WHAT YOU DO
WITH THE GIFT OF LIFE
THAT DETERMINES
WHO YOU ARE.
MEW.
OH...
VAPOREON.
[GROANS]
SAUR.
SQUIRTLE.
VILEPLUME.
SCYTHER.
BLAST.
OOH! OOH!
[CAWS]
[CREATURES GROAN]
[ROARS]
GOGOBA!
PIKACHU!
MEWTWO,
WHERE ARE YOU GOING?
Mewtwo: WHERE MY HEART
CAN LEARN
WHAT YOURS KNOWS SO WELL.
WHAT TRANSPIRED HERE,
I WILL ALWAYS REMEMBER,
BUT PERHAPS, FOR YOU,
THESE EVENTS
ARE BEST FORGOTTEN.
[ALL GASP]
WHOA!
AAH!
THIS COULD BE
THE WORST STORM EVER.
YOU MUST LISTEN TO ME.
YOU HAVE GOT
TO FIND SHELTER.
Joy:
EXCUSE ME, PLEASE.
THE POKÉMON
TREATMENT CENTER
WILL BE OPEN
AS A SHELTER.
ANYONE WHO NEEDS
A PLACE TO STAY
SHOULD COME WITH ME.
Boy: YOU THINK THEY'LL
HAVE A PIZZA DOWN THERE?
NURSE JOY AND OFFICER JENNY
ARE REALLY GREAT.
THEY JUST KEEP GETTING
MORE BEAUTIFUL
EVERY TIME I SEE 'EM.
HEY, GUYS, HOW DID WE WIND
UP IN THIS PLACE ANYWAY?
WELL, I GUESS
WE'RE JUST HERE
BECAUSE WE'RE HERE.
PIKA.
YEAH.
LET'S EAT.
UH-HUH.
PIKA-PI.
Jenny: LOOK,
IT'S A MIRACLE.
HUH?
I CAN'T
BELIEVE IT.
THE STORM DISAPPEARED.
THAT'S SO WEIRD.
IT'S GOOD TO HAVE THINGS
CLEAR AGAIN.
HMM.
HEY, WHAT'S THAT?
Brock: HMM?
WHAT'S WHAT?
I DON'T SEE
ANYTHING, ASH.
EXCEPT THE SKY.
HMM.
THE DAY I LEFT HOME
TO START
MY POKÉMON JOURNEY,
I SAW A REALLY RARE
POKÉMON,
AND JUST NOW,
I THOUGHT I SAW
ANOTHER ONE.
WELL, MAYBE YOU'RE
JUST SEEING THINGS, ASH.
HUH?
WELL, MAYBE HE'S NOT.
HA HA!
HMM.
WELL, MAYBE WE'LL SEE.
PIKACHU.
Narrator:
MANY STRANGE LEGENDS
SURROUND THE MYSTERIES
OF POKÉMON
AND JUST AS MANY ADVENTURES
AWAIT OUR YOUNG HEROES
AS THEY CONTINUE
ON THEIR QUEST.
FOR ASH AND HIS FRIENDS,
THE JOURNEY'S
JUST BEGUN.
I DON'T HAVE A CLUE
HOW WE GOT HERE,
BUT WHO CARES?
THIS IS
PARADISE.
FOR ONCE,
A HAPPY ENDING.
All: TEAM ROCKET
SIGNING OFF AGAIN!
[ALL LAUGH]
James: DO YOU HAVE
ANY SUNSCREEN?
Meowth: YOU KNOW, I'D
REALLY LIKE TO GO SAILING
IN ONE OF THEM
CATAMARANS.
HA HA!
CAPTIONING MADE POSSIBLE BY
WARNER BROS.
CAPTIONED BY THE NATIONAL
CAPTIONING INSTITUTE
--www.ncicap.org--
Christina Aguilera:
# OOH #
# OH, YEAH #
# HERE WE ARE #
# SAFE AT LAST #
# WE CAN BREATHE A SIGH #
# IT SEEMS THE STORM
HAS PASSED #
# THROUGH IT ALL #
# NO ONE KNEW #
# THAT ALL THE TEARS
IN HEAVEN #
# WOULD BRING ME
BACK TO YOU #
# OH #
# NO ONE I KNOW #
# IMAGINED
WE WOULD MAKE IT #
# BUT IT ONLY MATTERS #
# THAT WE BOTH BELIEVED #
# WHOA #
# YOU AND ME #
# WE'RE A MIRACLE #
# MEANT TO BE #
# AND NOTHING
CAN CHANGE IT #
# MOUNTAINS MOVE
AND OCEANS PART #
# WHEN THEY ARE STANDING
IN OUR WAY #
# YOU AND ME #
# WE'RE A MIRACLE #
# ANGELS STAND
WATCHING OVER US #
# AND HEAVEN
SHINES UPON US #
# EVERY DAY #
[NEW SONG BEGINS]
# THE GOVERNMENT #
Baby Spice:
# ROCK AND ROCK AND ROLL #
# ROCK AND ROLL #
# FREE UP YOUR MIND #
# LET THE MUSIC
FREE UP #
# AND IT WILL HELP YOU
TO FIND #
# LET THE MUSIC
HELP YOU #
# THE BEATS
WILL GIVE YOU A SIGN #
# OOH #
# LET THE MUSIC
FREE UP YOUR MIND #
# FREE UP YOUR MIND #
# LET THE MUSIC
FREE UP YOUR MIND #
HELP YOU TO FIND #
# OOH #
# LET THE MUSIC
FREE UP YOUR MIND #
# FREE UP YOUR MIND #
Midnight Sons:
# IF ONLY TEARS #
# COULD BRING YOU #
# BACK TO ME #
# IF ONLY LOVE #
# COULD FIND A WAY #
# WHAT I WOULD DO #
# WHAT I WOULD GIVE #
# IF YOU #
# RETURNED TO ME #
# SOMEDAY #
# SOMEHOW #
# SOMEWAY #
# IF MY TEARS
COULD BRING YOU BACK #
# TO ME #
MZM:
# LOVE WILL FIND A WAY #
# DON'T SAY YOU LOVE ME #
# YOU DON'T EVEN KNOW ME #
# IF YOU REALLY WANT ME #
# THEN GIVE ME SOME TIME #
# DON'T GO THERE, BABY #
# NOT BEFORE I'M READY #
# DON'T SAY
YOUR HEART'S IN A HURRY #
# IT'S NOT LIKE
WE'RE GONNA GET MARRIED #
# GIVE ME, GIVE ME #
# SOME TIME #