Shit!
Stop, please!
In a related story,
the high court had also refused to stay...
Friday's execution of former
philosophy professor David Gale.
Gale had sought a review
of his 1994 conviction...
for the rape and murder of his
University of Austin colleague...
Constance Harraway.
The case has received
nationwide media attention...
because Gale and Harraway
were activists for DeathWatch...
a non-profit
abolitionist organisation.
Do you understand how much money
taxpayers pay in Texas...
to put one person to death?
- What do we want?
- No more executions!
Governor, can't we all admit
the capital punishment system...
in this country is not working?
They're not going to stay Gale.
It's on TV right now. Listen.
Defence lawyers
had hoped to argue...
that Gale's former activism
against capital punishment...
unduly prejudiced
the Texas judicial system.
The deal was Bitsey would get
the interview if the stay was refused.
He'll talk to her
for two hours a day:
Tuesday, Wednesday and Thursday.
Can't do Friday. No.
Friday's the day they execute him.
The lawyer said only Bitsey.
Gale's going down.
Only Bitsey means only Bitsey.
I don't get to make the rules, Joe.
Please, I'm a fat black woman.
What we need is
to put her on a plane to Texas.
Why do you get like that around
legal? Hold on, we're coming over.
What's this "Only Bitsey
means only Bitsey" stuff?
They asked for you,
and no substitutes.
- Who's they, exactly?
- Gale's lawyers.
More exactly, Gale's lawyer.
Some good old boy in Austin.
Why do they want me?
- You don't want the assignment?
- I'm not saying that.
I can't see why
a guy about to be executed...
should suddenly ask for me.
Maybe they liked your kiddie
porn piece, and going to jail.
Maybe he saw your picture
and thinks you're cute.
- So how much access do I get?
- Three interviews. No time for more.
By Friday, the guy's a goner.
- What exactly is our story?
- Rape, murder, death row.
Very intelligent guy.
Maybe he's even innocent.
Yeah, right.
No, tell him I'll call him back.
Thanks.
So what's your problem?
Hi, Barbara. 'Morning, Bitsey.
Okay, here's my concern.
Setting aside the cost issue...
although $500,000 in cash
for three days of interviews...
is not only illegal, it's obscene.
That's market value.
The guy's never talked.
Aside from that, I, we are still
uncomfortable with the arrangement.
Why?
You just spent
a very public seven days in jail...
for a very public
contempt-of-court citation.
For protecting sources. If you were
uncomfortable with the story...
why did you slap it on the domestic
and international covers?
What makes us uncomfortable is
that a rapistlmurderer...
has asked to spend
the last three days of his life...
giving an interview,
his very first...
to a reporter who is now famous
for protecting sexual deviants.
A reporter who is also
a very attractive woman.
This is disparate treatment.
Oh, boy.
I could go if I were an ugly guy?
The agenda issue would be diffused
with the presence of a male.
I hear lawyers gleefully saying:
"Bloom versus News Magazine Inc. "
"Your Honour, I started to notice
my assignments...
"were being determined
on the basis of my sex. "
You've got to let her go now.
- That's not what I meant.
- He's got to let you go.
All right. Enough.
But the intern
will be with you at all times.
What? Intern.
- No, you've got to be kidding.
- That's what he said.
- He's a jerk.
- He's the boss.
- Not an intern. I always work alone.
- Not this time, Bitsey.
I'm not baby-sitting.
Gale's DNA was everywhere.
His semen was inside her.
He was seen leaving her house.
His prints were all over the
kitchen, including one on the bag.
- Half a thumbprint.
- Half a thumbprint. That's enough.
He could've touched it
before it was a murder weapon.
You fondle your friends'
garbage bags?
Yeah, I get very touchy
around household plastics.
I'm particularly fond of Tupperware.
Tupperware?
I'm just saying the bag could've
been sitting on the counter.
He did it. Now he's going to die.
And you know something?
Maybe that's exactly
what he deserves.
But the murder's
way too fucking clumsy.
This guy is an intellectual. Top of
his Harvard class, Rhodes scholar...
tenured at 27, two books published.
He's an academic stud.
Look at his wife.
A regular Grace Kelly.
Old money svelte.
Father was ambassador to Spain.
- Shit! The light's on again.
- Ignore it, it's a rental.
- Do you smell anything?
- The guy's a flaming Liberal.
A person's politics
has nothing to do...
- with his tendency to commit crime.
- Wrong.
Shouldn't it smell
if it's overheating?
Seventy-three percent of
all serial killers vote Republican.
Throw your cigarette out,
so we can smell.
You'll stink up the car.
Throw it out.
I'm not going to fucking pollute.
There's definitely something wrong
with this car.
This is so irritating.
How far to Huntsville?
I'm going to pull off.
"News Magazine reporters
Bitsey Bloom and Zack Stemmons...
"entered the rest area
with car troubles.
"Little did they know it wasn't
just their car that was in trouble. "
I'm a reporter. You're an intern.
Whatever.
Is it hot?
Jesus, yes! Isn't it always?
What do I do?
Call the office and get
the rental road service number.
No signal.
God damn it.
I've got to pee.
Zack!
DAY ONE
'Morning.
Hi.
A little early for that, isn't it?
The non-smoking section's
over there.
I meant the book.
Dialogical Exhaustion by David Gale.
The guy's a genius.
- What time is it?
- 9:15 a. m.
There are 10 prisons around here.
Death row is in the Ellis unit...
but they're moving it to the
Terrell unit at the end of the year.
The waitress's boyfriend
works there.
Her last boyfriend
worked in the Huntsville unit.
The two before that in Walker.
The Estelle unit
has the cutest guys.
And I'm quoting, "My butt's too big
to get an Estelle guy. "
Ellis is 15 minutes out of town.
We've got five and a half hours.
Never eat in a place where
the menus have pictures of the food.
We should drive into Austin.
Check out the crime scene.
That could be
some great stuff for our story.
This isn't our story. It's not even
a story. It's an interview.
Most importantly for you
to remember, it's my interview.
What do I do
for the next five hours?
Drive around.
Look for a decent restaurant.
Your reputation
as Mike Wallace with PMS...
doesn't do you justice.
My reputation got us invited here.
I play by the rules,
even if my colleagues don't like it.
- It's called...
- Ambition?
Objectivity.
- What can I get you, ma'am?
- Just coffee.
Don't push me, smart ass.
You know you're in the Bible belt...
when there are more churches
than Starbucks.
When there are more prisons
He's ready for y'all now.
Yes, I am.
I'm not gonna debate with you the
rights and wrongs of the situation.
Our job
is to run the state prison system.
This is not France.
This is not Germany. This is Texas.
And we're gonna follow Texas law.
You're very welcome, ma'am.
Goodbye, now.
Thank you, Margie.
Correspondents Bloom and Stevens,
I presume?
Yes, hello.
- Stemmons.
- Sorry. Won't happen again.
I'm Duke Grover,
TDCJ, Community Relations.
He's usually real good with names.
And these days
I always like to ask...
do you prefer Miss, Mrs., or Ms.?
- Bitsey.
- Bitsey it is.
- Margie, I'm stealing your guests.
- Okey-dokey.
- You ever been in a prison?
- Yes.
- On death row?
- No.
ID's again, please.
All executions in the state of Texas
occur at the Huntsville unit.
But death row
is here for the time being.
This is home to all 442 offenders
prior to their date.
Average stay on the row
is nine years.
Some get commuted,
but most get put to death.
It'll put you off your supper,
but then, it's supposed to.
New York guests for Mr. Gale.
Can I get your bags?
We have three concerns here:
Safety, safety, and safety.
The visitation area
is entirely secure.
We just ask
that you don't touch the glass.
Windex gets expensive.
You're not carrying a weapon,
are you, Bitsey?
Sorry. No.
- Mr. Stemmons, you packing?
- No, sir.
Cell phone?
They're not working.
Then you won't mind
leaving them here.
We also have rules against the
carrying of large sums of cash...
and the wearing of open-toed shoes.
Those will do just fine.
You want to step on through now?
There you go.
Thank you, ma'am.
That's right.
- Open-toed shoes?
- Drives them crazy.
Your turn, Mr. Stemmons.
Right on through there.
Good.
Should anything unpleasant
occur in the visitation area...
we ask you to stay put.
Please follow the instructions
of our fine correctional officers...
should they see fit to give you any.
Anything you say can be overheard.
Any discussion of criminal activity
on your part is admissible.
You're not planning on a jailbreak,
are you?
The rain seems to be holding off.
You watch your step here.
This cement can get pretty slippery.
This is our Japanese garden.
We ask you
not to throw coins in the pond.
Right this way. Almost there.
Here we are. This is our
visitation area right here.
All yours, Mr. Belyeu.
That's it for me.
You folks have a safe visit.
Thank you.
'Bye now.
Ms. Bloom?
Yes.
Come right on in here
and make yourself comfortable.
Did that PR man
validate your parking?
He said the gift shop would do it.
She's a smart one.
Braxton Belyeu, Mr. Gale's attorney.
This is Zack Stemmons.
My good pleasure.
And right over here,
we have the man of the hour.
Hello.
- Hello.
- Hi.
GUARD Sit down, Gale.
Prisoner will not stand.
Why can't they turn that thing down?
My lawyer respectfully requests...
that you adjust the volume
on the speaker system.
GUARD Gale, sit down.
They're practicing
being cruel and unusual.
I'm sure you're biting at the bit.
It is our understanding that you are
to have three two-hour sessions.
Today, tomorrow, and Thursday.
All at 3:00 p. m.
I'm sorry
we can't afford you more time.
But contrary to popular rumour,
we have not yet begun to fight.
It is our understanding
that you will do this alone.
- The magazine would prefer that...
- Alone.
Understood.
Also, you'll use
no recording equipment of any kind.
Correct.
Excellent.
I have a few papers for which I need
your Jo Anne Hancock.
So if you'd stop by my Austin office
at your earliest convenience.
Thursday morning, say?
Expenses and so forth.
Fine. Till Thursday, then.
Good luck.
I'll stop by later.
What say you and me partake
of a death-defying cigarette...
in the visitors' parking lot?
Bye-bye, y'all.
So...
Please pull up a seat.
He's quite a character.
Yes.
He's about the only outside contact
I have now.
And a good friend.
Where's your ex-wife?
I don't want you to ask me questions
about her or my son.
What I offer you is one thing.
Questions about them
are not part of our deal.
Okay.
Just say, "Off the record,"
and I'll take it to my grave.
You can trust me on that.
Does this count
as recording equipment?
- How do we start?
- We start with...
you telling me what I'm doing here.
No one who looks through that glass
sees a person.
They see a crime.
I'm not David Gale.
I'm a murderer and a rapist.
Four days shy of his execution.
You're here
because I want to be remembered...
as much for how I led my life
and the decisions that I made...
as for how my life ended.
- Why me?
- Why not?
You've spent some time
behind bars yourself recently.
I certainly have.
Because you do
take things to your grave.
Protecting sources, even kiddie porn
scum, is the magazine policy...
- and mine.
- I know.
That's your reputation.
I have a hard story
for you to tell, Miss Bloom.
It's not going to be easy.
Where do we begin?
I should tell you
how I became Head of Philosophy...
at the University of Austin.
Come on, think.
I want you to reach back
into those minds.
And tell me, tell us all...
what is it that you fantasise about?
World peace?
Thought so.
Do you fantasise
about international fame?
about winning a Pulitzer Prize?
Or a Nobel Peace Prize?
An MTV Music Award?
Do you fantasise
about meeting some genius hunk...
ostensibly bad, but secretly
simmering with noble passion...
and willing to sleep
on the wet spot?
I'll take two!
What was that?
- I'll take two!
- Kimberley will take two.
You get Lacan's point:
Fantasies have to be unrealistic.
Because the moment, the second
that you get what you seek...
you don't,
you can't want it anymore.
In order to continue to exist...
desire must have its objects
perpetually absent.
It's not the "it" that you want,
it's the fantasy of "it. "
Desire supports crazy fantasies.
Sorry.
This is what Pascal means when he
says that we are only truly happy...
when daydreaming
about future happiness.
It came today.
Or why we say,
"The hunt is sweeter than the kill. "
Or, "Be careful what you wish for. "
Not because you'll get it...
because you're doomed
not to want it once you do.
So the lesson of Lacan is:
Living by your wants
will never make you happy.
What it means to be fully human...
is to strive to live
by ideas and ideals.
Not to measure your life...
by what you've attained
in terms of your desires...
but those moments of integrity,
compassion, rationality...
even self-sacrifice.
Because in the end...
the only way we can measure
the significance of our own lives...
is by valuing the lives of others.
All right,
I'll see you all on Monday.
Sorry about being late.
There was, you know, a thing.
There usually is, Berlin.
I know that I'm not doing too well.
And to torture a cliché...
I would do anything to pass.
Anything?
Any...
thing.
Okay, Berlin.
I will give you a very good grade...
if you would just...
study.
The TA's transcribed the Governor's
radio and TV comments.
Listen to this gem.
"Journalist: Governor,
don't you think...
"three executions
in one week is excessive?"
"Governor: I say bring 'em in, strap
'em down and let's rock and roll. "
It's good that our governor's
in touch with his inner frat boy.
Tell me
why you're not doing this debate?
Telegenics. You have a cuter butt.
- I hadn't noticed.
- I know.
I didn't mean that.
I've highlighted some stuff.
He'll do the whole
down-home wisdom thing.
"Capital punishment is God's law,"
"An eye for an eye" and all.
Stick to arguments about
rational facts, and watch your ego.
Don't come across as:
"I hate authority because
everyone here wears big hats...
"and nobody in charge
reads The New Yorker. "
Anything else?
I'm getting new stats
from Amnesty tonight.
Bring them by Greer's party.
I have papers to grade.
- Lf you have a hangover tomorrow...
- I'm walking away.
10:00 a. m.
Bright-eyed and bushy-tailed!
Bushy-tailed!
Hey, Jamie.
Did you mark your calendar yet?
I sure did.
One, two, three, four more days
until Mum comes home.
Only four more days?
That's great news.
Can I ask you something?
It's really important.
Of course you can.
Can we have pancakes for breakfast?
With syrup and strawberries?
- We'll have to see.
- And chocolate shavers?
No, it's chocolate shavings.
And whipped cream?
Whipped cream?
That's a lot of requests
for one little boy.
Why don't you go to sleep?
Do Cloud Dog, too.
Good night, Cloud Dog.
There you go.
You go to sleep.
Good night.
Don't forget to feed the fish.
What?
Okay.
I'll be back before midnight. Here's
the number if you have to reach me.
There's chicken in the refrigerator,
if you want some.
That's fine. Maybe I'll fix myself
something later.
'Bye.
Dad, did you feed the fish?
Yes, I did. Now go to sleep.
He's the Immanuel Kant of the NFL.
He's consistent, accurate,
effective...
and let's not forget boring.
- He is boring.
- Lf you want boring...
read William Bennett's
Book of Virtues. I'm still asleep.
Someone wake me up.
- John, how are you?
- Where's your better half?
My wife? She's in Spain.
Again? I am sorry.
John, have you seen Alma?
She's been looking for you.
My wife's affair is
just this big, open secret.
Hermeneutical bias.
The only fun truths are the ones
someone's trying to hide.
She's been to Barcelona
four times this year.
I don't think
she's trying to hide anything.
Her father is the ambassador.
Yeah, except the embassy's
in Madrid.
By the way, Berlin's here.
- Pretty livid.
- Why?
We've expelled her.
She got the letter today.
Took the opportunity
to throw a fit in my office.
Talking about me?
As a matter of fact, we were.
Did he tell you
I said when you were circumcised...
they threw away the wrong part?
Yes, he mentioned it.
It's called schmuck.
What?
The part of the foreskin
they throw away after circumcision.
It think it's called schmuck.
- Aren't we so fucking clever.
- Perhaps I should get another.
Black Bush.
You were a jerk this afternoon.
I didn't know about the expulsion
till just now.
Is that supposed to be an apology?
No.
It's more like a conciliation.
PEOPLE AT PARTY Ross! Ross!
All right.
"As the poets have mournfully sung
"Death takes the innocent young
"The screamingly funny
The rolling in money
"And those who are very well hung"
PEOPLE AT PARTY Gale! Gale!
"There once was
a lesbian from Cancun
"who took a young man up to her room
"Where they argued all night
as to who had the right
"to do what and how much
and to whom"
Enough!
I'm spent!
I have no more.
PEOPLE AT PARTY Ross! Ross!
Okay, I'm finished. I'm done.
I'm not a student anymore.
I do not think I want to know
what that means.
"There once was a girl named Berlin
"who liked a bit now and again
"Not now and again
"but now and again
"and again"
Cute?
Yeah. Very cute.
I have a secret.
But I have to come over there
to tell you.
No.
Here...
You stay back.
I come.
Woman.
You should stay...
I wasn't after the grade.
I don't think this is such a...
Now we can talk, analyse...
contemplate.
Or you can put your mouth
on my body.
Don't reject me.
Please.
Rip them.
What?
Rip them off.
No. From behind.
From behind.
Do it hard.
Harder.
Bite my shoulder.
Thanks for coming, people.
I don't care where you go. Come on!
All right, you guys,
it's time to go home! Good night!
It won't work.
That's a faulty argument.
Let's say we found an innocent
on death row. What would change?
After the retrial,
the Governor would go on TV and say:
"See? Thanks to the good people
at DeathWatch, the system works. "
If we had absolute proof
that he had executed an innocent...
we could demand a moratorium,
like in Illinois.
- Are you okay?
- Sorry. Yeah.
But that won't happen.
Dead men can't make a case,
and almost-martyrs don't count.
- Got it.
- So keep it rational.
And stop that!
What?
Active listening.
I hate active listeners.
They're too busy pretending
to listen to hear what I'm saying.
I can listen and actively listen
at the same time. I'm good at it.
- Did you bring the Amnesty stats?
- Yes.
No. I left them at home.
I have a copy.
- You want to tell me what's up?
- Nothing.
Everything.
Something profoundly stupid
happened last night.
I hope you used a condom.
Jesus Christ, David.
Was she one of yours?
It was Berlin.
Great.
That's great.
I can hear the grapevine:
"They suspended her so Gale could
dick her with a clear conscience.
"A power differential
equals coercion. "
That is great. You're so weak.
You're not my wife, Constance.
Thank God.
Don't worry, it's not a position
I aspire to. So fuck you!
I didn't mean it that way.
Are you okay?
Really?
Yes! Let's go.
There are 17,000 murders a year
in the United States.
Ten states that have abolished
the death penalty...
have a murder rate
lower than the national average.
If he starts with the religious
stuff, just say that...
nearly every denomination in
the U.S. Opposes the death penalty.
Are you listening?
Yes.
All right, 10 seconds.
Count them in, Mac.
Five, four...
Welcome back to Batter's Box.
We continue our special four-part
program with Governor Hardin.
And arguing capital punishment
with him...
is DeathWatch regional co-director,
Professor David Gale.
You are up, Governor.
I always say the same thing
and I'm gonna keep on saying it.
I hate killing, and my
administration will kill to stop it.
How about it?
Murderers are not deterred
by the thought of execution.
You know it. Every single study
done on the subject...
and there's been over 200,
you've read them...
has reached the same conclusion.
Maybe you should read your Bible.
Deuteronomy: 19:21. "An eye for
an eye, a tooth for a tooth. "
What did Gandhi say about that?
"The old law of an eye for an eye
leaves us all blind. "
I'm sorry, and with respect,
that's fuzzy liberal thinking.
You believe that?
Of course.
Interesting, 'cause you said it
in a speech in your first campaign.
He got you there, Governor.
How about it?
Yes, he did.
"If you're not a Liberal at 30,
you've got no heart.
"If you're still a Liberal at 40,
you've got no brain. "
- That's Winston Churchill.
- Touché.
What you're essentially saying is,
and this is to choose another quote:
"A healthy society must stop at
nothing to cleanse itself of evil. "
Yes, I'd have to agree.
Did I say that, too?
No, sir. That was Hitler.
Governor, can't we all just admit
the capital punishment system...
in this country is not working?
We are condemning people to death
based on phoney expert testimony...
on junk science,
on jailhouse snitches.
Did you know Texas has the highest
per capita incarceration rate...
in the world, including in China?
Forty-three people, Governor,
that you executed...
were represented by lawyers
at one time disbarred or sanctioned.
There are two men on death row
right now, on this day...
whose lawyers fell asleep
during their cross-examination.
I'm not a lawyer.
Texas Court of Criminal Appeals
ruled...
that it was not a basis
for a retrial.
Governor, that's just a flawed,
insane, crazy system.
And a flawed system
will kill innocent men!
All right. Let him answer.
All right, we'll play your game.
Name one.
Name one innocent man that Texas
has put to death during my tenure.
Of the 100 or so executions...
That's 131,
in case you've lost count.
Let him finish.
Fine. Whatever.
Just give me a name.
I'm gonna write it down.
A man
that you can prove was innocent...
and I'll call a moratorium.
Mr. Gale?
Are we through here?
We're running out of time.
I'd like to thank my guests,
Governor Hardin...
and Professor Gale from DeathWatch.
Roll credits.
I hope you will join me tomorrow.
Your exact words were:
"Tell me when my ego's
getting in the way of the work. "
- Now I'm telling you.
- I didn't want to do this.
You put up two seconds of protest at
the thought of being on a TV debate.
- What does that mean?
- DeathWatch suffers...
because you're so anxious
to finger authority...
to publicly prove David Gale
is smarter than the powers that be.
Work without an audience. Try
squeezing money from the donor list.
Have you licked
a single mail-out envelope?
- Mr. Gale?
- The Governor went that way.
Ramirez. Austin Police.
This is Officer Hasermann.
Is debating the Governor
a crime now?
No, sir. Rape is.
Berlin had my bite marks...
Gale, time's up.
...bruises, her clothes were ripped.
My skin was found
under her fingernails.
It didn't look like
anything but rape.
Then she drops charges
and leaves town...
making it look like I was guilty...
and she was too traumatised
to face trial.
My wife read all this sitting in
the airport wondering where I was.
Why I wasn't there to pick her up.
Took me almost two weeks
to get bailed out.
And the grad student, Berlin?
Why do you think she did it?
To poke her finger at authority.
Show the powers that be
how much smarter she was.
Grad student's revenge.
I don't really know.
Know where I can find her?
No.
First year I was in here
I got a postcard from San Francisco.
It was signed, "From the student
who would do anything. "
Did she say anything else?
"I'm sorrier than you can know. "
Move it, Gale.
I'm running out of time.
Can you imagine his wife letting him
stew in jail for two weeks?
Who can blame her?
Get an address for the Berlin girl
from the university.
Still don't think
he's telling the truth?
On the Berlin rap?
On the whole rap.
Who knows? Anyway, there is
no truth, only perspectives.
If you say there's no truth, you're
claiming it's true there's no truth.
It's a logical contradiction.
Working on our
philosophy merit badge?
With rape, an accusation
is as good as a conviction.
It sticks like shit.
- That's an appetising metaphor.
- Technically a simile.
I think he's telling the truth.
This you know
from sitting in the prison lobby?
It's just my perspective.
Three different courts
found him guilty.
That's enough perspective for me.
DAY TWO
What? 330... What?
Seven.
3303.
3305.
3307. Right there.
Jesus, look at the sign.
Hi. I'm Bitsey Bloom.
This is Zack Stemmons.
You want the tour?
There's a $20
mandatory donation apiece.
You get a re-enactment photo packet.
It's got five pictures.
- Okay.
- I got to collect first.
Sure.
I got it.
Got to sign the book. It doesn't
have to be your real name.
It says you're here
to do research on violent crime.
State requires it
for non-profit shit.
Take a re-enactment photo packet.
If you guys could share one,
it would be cool.
The fuckers that do my prints
jerk my chain.
That's me. My boyfriend took it.
We also got a video.
It's $50 'cause you can see my tits.
There's a version without tits.
It's $35.
- Do many people take the tour?
- Not so much anymore.
We thought it would be a busy week
with Gale getting the prune juice.
So you don't mind living here?
It's better than living
with my dickwad parents.
It starts over here.
She let him crash here sometimes.
He was constantly wasted.
Exhibit one.
He drank Scotch religiously.
The rest is in the kitchen.
Here's number two.
This is where the tripod was.
My boyfriend borrowed the one
we usually show to folks.
They never found a camera,
or photos, a video or anything.
Gale must have buried them.
These serial killer dudes
take photos to whack off to later.
He's not exactly a serial killer.
Whatever.
She was totally naked, right here.
The meter man
saw her through the door.
Gale handcuffed her,
taped her mouth...
then taped a bag over her head
so she couldn't breathe.
He used housewife gloves
so he wouldn't leave prints.
They found sticky stuff
from the tape on them.
We ask folks
not to touch the exhibit.
The totally sick part is where
they found the key to the handcuffs.
We know.
Wait. What? Where was it?
It was in her stomach, dude.
Gale made her swallow it
before he bagged her.
That's pretty much the highlights.
Got questions?
I can still smell
the cigarette smoke.
It's the barbecue!
Can you imagine?
That key was in her stomach.
That's so fucking cold, man.
Zack?
What?
Isn't that the cowboy
from the rest area?
The same truck.
Weird coincidence?
Coincidences are always weird.
That's why they're coincidences.
Off the record.
Okay. We're off.
Constance was murdered by what's
known as the Securitate Method.
You're handcuffed,
forced to swallow the key...
your mouth is taped,
a bag is sealed around your head...
and you're left to suffocate.
The Securitate did it to Romanians...
when they wouldn't inform
or confess.
Sometimes the bag was ripped off
to give you a second chance.
Otherwise, you died...
knowing that the key to your freedom
was inside of you the entire time.
It's a cheap but effective method.
The problem is...
I once mentioned it
in an article that I wrote.
Prosecution never knew that.
- Someone's framing you?
- It's more than that.
There was a tripod.
Right.
Facing her body.
- Are we back on the record?
- Yes.
The tripod
had no fingerprints on it.
That means somebody
brought it there, set it up...
wiped it clean, and left it.
Why?
It's as if they wanted me to know
that somewhere out there...
is a record of exactly what happened
that afternoon.
As if they wanted me to die...
knowing that the key to my freedom
is out there somewhere.
Maybe you're being paranoid.
I used to be the state's
leading death penalty abolitionist.
Now I'm on death row! Doesn't that
strike you as a little odd?
Any idea who "they" are?
No, but I've got someone
working on that.
Someone I'm relying on
to prove my innocence.
Belyeu has hired a detective?
A journalist.
She has to help me.
- You know I'm innocent.
- No.
No, I don't.
Wear me like a fur, Daddy.
Okay, who's your hero?
All right, you go get Cloud Dog.
Hey, Cloud Dog!
Call me when you land.
Has any couple ever really survived
a trial separation?
Isn't it contrary to the idea
of trying to work things out?
Don't.
Get in, sweetie.
See you later, alligator.
After a while, crocodile.
- Take it easy, Japa-nee-zee.
- Okey-dokey, artichokey.
Scoot.
- Listen.
- I sent you an e-mail.
- An e-mail?
- Just read it.
Come on, sweetie.
Just read it.
You could at least hide
the bottle.
Well?
Officially, you're on sabbatical.
Unofficially,
they want you out of here.
It was four to two.
How did Ross vote?
I'm not supposed to...
Against you.
And you?
For you.
And against my politics.
Please.
Madam, atencion.
My name is David Gale.
I have phoned before, yes?
Can...
Por favor.
What? No, never mind.
Can you please get Sharon Gale?
Yes, Miss Gale!
Hello?
I wanted to hear your feedback
on the idea.
Look, Professor Gale...
I could sit here like others have,
and plead departmental cutbacks...
claim you need more publications,
I need a minority.
Whatever.
All bull-geschichte.
Your record's brilliant.
You're an original voice, worth,
in today's scarcity-defines-value...
capitalist system under which
we toil, your weight in gold.
Hell, it's not even
your alcohol problem.
It would be nice to have a faculty
member whose crutch wasn't Prozac.
But to speak plain,
if I were to hire you...
in the eyes of the regents,
the alumni...
and every freshman
with an ear for gossip...
I'd be hiring a rapist.
Those charges were dropped.
People would say
you had a good lawyer.
I was innocent.
You don't get it, do you?
You're not politically correct.
Welcome to the club.
Socrates is sentenced to death.
I bet you didn't know that.
He was sentenced to death.
But Athenian law
let the condemned...
come up with their own
alternate punishment.
Isn't that a great idea?
Where are the Athenians
when you really need them?
So anyway, Socrates...
And he was ugly. Did I mention that?
Did I mention
that Socrates was ugly?
Socrates was ugly, Plato was fat,
and Aristotle was a prissy dresser.
So anyway,
Socrates comes up with this idea.
He says, "What if I pay a fine
instead of death?"
He suggests a fine.
All he has to do in order to live is
to come up with an appropriately...
punitive figure.
Guess what he suggested? $30!
Does that make any sense? $30.
That's 30 mina. That was
the currency of the day, a mina.
Well, minae.
That's plural. Minae.
$30!
Thirty pieces of silver.
And the judges are so pissed that
more of them voted to kill him...
than had voted him guilty
in the first place.
That doesn't make any sense.
Thirty pieces of silver.
Just like the Judas guy.
The Jesus-kisser...
who was also a prissy dresser.
Without a successful completion
of an alcohol treatment program...
you can forget visitation.
You'll be lucky
to get a Christmas card.
That's if there
even is a custody hearing.
What does that mean?
If your wife
convinces a Spanish court...
that you're a danger to the child,
you'll never see him again.
He just has to come home.
He's got to come back.
Pete, can we
have another round here?
I'm fine.
I'll just have to go get him then.
Europe's not Mexico, David.
They've got real borders over there.
You might be able to get in,
but getting out with a 6-year-old?
That's a whole different
kettle of crawdads.
You want to see Jamie again?
- Then you get your life together.
- I'm fine.
Pronto.
Who wants to start?
Hi, my name is David...
and I am an alcoholic.
AA GROUP Hi, David.
So, Mr. Gale...
tell me three personal qualities...
that you feel you have...
that would make you
a successful Radio Shed manager.
Three.
Okay.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry. Welcome back.
Thanks.
You look good.
I feel good.
There's something
that you've got to see.
Betty Sue Johnson
has been rescheduled.
Her execution date
is set for the eighth.
I have a call
with Washington tonight.
If the national director
commits to emergency funds...
She gets commuted
and you prove the system works.
But I'll save a life.
Where did you get that bruise?
Just doing chores.
Is your cowboy
getting rough with you?
There he is.
Dusty, does she ever invite you over
and not put you to work?
All right, tell me her story.
She was sentenced at 17.
I really want to get behind
this one. She's so articulate.
Who did she kill?
She'll put a face
on the death penalty.
Constance, who did she kill?
A cop.
You're crazy.
Not just your medium-range,
thinks-she's- Roosevelt's- bathrobe...
but I mean stark-raving,
screws-loose, in-the-belfry insane!
Seventeen.
Four years before she could
legally drink a beer.
But she killed a cop, Constance.
Will you help?
Of course.
You're burning up.
Hi, Mr. Gale.
How are you? It's good to see...
Caffeine jolt. We deliver.
Howdy, David.
Howdy, folks.
Hello. My, this is service.
Thank you.
Gladly. Latte on the left there
for you, John.
Mocha.
Thanks.
- She's on the phone to Washington.
- Sinclair, new National Director.
I'm sure we can get some
pulpit time, maybe some cable.
DIRECTOR
Good. I need to go.
I agree the first press release
should focus on the woman's youth.
I'll have Washington
look into counsel competency.
Though I'm almost sure
she's exhausted this on appeal.
- See what resources...
- David's going to go.
I almost forgot.
Gale's not around, is he?
- No.
- Good. Keep it that way.
His relationship
with DeathWatch is over.
Last thing we need is this
rape thing coming back to bite us.
These guys don't stay
on the wagon for long.
I'm serious, Constance.
Ban him from the premises.
I realise the two of you...
David!
Sharon, pick up the phone.
I'm begging you.
He's my son, all right?
He's my son, too,
and I want to talk to him.
You've not let... Hello?
Jamie, is that you?
Hey, little moose horn.
I miss you so much. It's Daddy.
Jamie, wait.
Don't hang up the phone!
God damn it!
Oh, fuck!
You scared me.
My sheep needs a manager.
A manger.
My sheep needs a manger.
Are you okay?
I fell off the wagon
and I hurt myself.
Come on inside.
Do you know why St. Jude
is the patron saint of lost causes?
'Cause his real name was Judas.
Judas! There were two Judases.
Judae, who was the saint guy,
and then the other one...
Judas, who was the bad one.
He's the one who ratted out Jesus
and tried to kiss him.
In medieval times, they would never
pray to the good Judas...
for fear of getting the bad Judas
on the line just by mistake.
Ergo, they never really
gave him business...
unless absolutely desperate.
That's why.
And then they changed his name.
Your mail is blowing.
Oh, shit.
Are you the doctor?
What's wrong with her?
She'll be fine.
- How do you know?
- Calm down.
She was opening her mail and fell
over. I don't know what's wrong.
Please. Is there a doctor?
Wait here.
I have to go with her!
Hold up, Professor!
You want to get arrested again?
How do you know who I am?
I watch the news. Now go wait.
How're we doing?
Fine. How's Constance?
Sleeping.
A leukaemia patient's
condition is...
very susceptible
to external stress...
What?
Constance's illness requires
a degree of regularity.
Constance has leukaemia?
You didn't know?
Wait.
No, I didn't.
It's funny how selfish
we can be, isn't it?
When I first heard Constance
was dying, I was so mad at her.
I thought,
"How can you do this to me?
"I mean, you know how hard
it is for me to need other people. "
Why hadn't she told you?
She said she was too busy.
I guess since death
was chasing her...
she wanted to help
other people avoid it.
That's what she did with her life.
Constance left this world
a better place than she found it.
It's a small but difficult thing.