Fuck.
Come on!
No!
- Josephine!
- What?
- What are you doing?
- Nothing.
Yeah, I can tell.
What's with the attitude?
I don't have
an attitude, Brian.
You see Hudson around?
- No, I ain't seen him.
- You haven't seen him.
Well, he punched his clock in,
So he's gotta be around
here somewhere.
I ain't nobody's babysitter.
Yeah, right. Seems like nobody
can find the guy, all right,
and if I find out you guys have been
punching his clock in...
people are gonna get fired,
you know what I mean?
I didn't check him in, Brian.
Yeah, whatever,
get back to work.
And enough of the lip.
Always a sweetheart.
That ain't nothin',
There's this guy around my way
called Tommy the Pole Hugger.
- Pole Hugger, huh?
- Yeah.
Tommy-- why he hug poles?
The motherfucker be hugging poles.
Shit, he be drunk as hell.
Yeah? Drunk?
I think that motherfucker
get high off of everything.
Every day, 2:00...
Every day at 2:00,
you can't miss him.
Here he come, down the street,
Staggering from pole to pole.
You gotta see him, man,
I'm telling you.
He can't even stand up barely,
but he make it from pole to pole,
all the way until he get home.
He'll get home, though?
That's some-- I'm tellin' you,
Some of the funniest shit
you ever saw.
It's funny as hell.
I don't even know how
he do that shit every day.
But shit...
I guess it's better to be
a drunk than to be a pervert.
Get out my face, Terry.
- Terry.
- Testy.
Get out of my face, Terry.
Get out of my business, Josephine.
You better hope Epstein
don't find out--
No, you better hope
Epstein don't find out.
What, you gonna tell him?
Next time you see me
over there with that girl,
why don't you just
go the other way?
Why don't you just try being
a little more professional,
and you ain't got
to worry about me?
Why don't you just
stay out of my business?
What the fuck was you
really lookin' at?
Uh-oh, what was
she lookin' at?
What you trying to see
a little something, huh?
There ain't much to see, I'm sure.
Oh, my bad, yeah...
Well, maybe you wasn't
looking at me.
Maybe you was looking
at the girl.
Right, right, I was
looking at the girl.
Yeah, I bet you was.
What was that, a confession?
Yeah, you look like
you could go that way.
Fucking dike.
What the fuck
you just call me?
I swear to God, Terry,
if you don't leave me
the fuck alone up here,
we always gotta go through this.
Ooh, I swear...
Go ahead, right here,
right here, right here.
Give it to me.
Get out,
get the fuck out, man.
I ain't gonna mess with her,
I'm just fuckin' with her, man.
If you mind your business,
we won't go through this.
I swear to God,
one more time...
Go ahead, go ahead, right here.
I'll give you one, go ahead.
Leave it, man. Leave it.
I'll give you a free shot,
right here.
You know what?
Fuck you, Terry.
No, fuck you.
What the fuck,
you like her or something?
No, it's work, man.
I don't fucking like her though, man.
She's weird as hell.
She act like she
can't be around us.
She over here, we over there.
But we cool.
She all by herself, man.
Fuck that.
Fuck her, man. And you?
I don't know about you, man.
Maybe you should be
fucking eating lunch with her.
- You think we like her?
- What?
You can't tell?
Every time I say
something about her
he's grabbing me, holding me,
saying, "Terry, don't."
It's not about her, it's about work.
Just keep it smooth, it's work--
But we ain't working
right now, we on break.
No need to argue.
A little bit of fun,
I'm just fuckin' with her.
It's fun? It's fun?
Yeah.
See how she left
up out of here?
Fuck her, man.
Is that Charlie Parker?
What?
You were humming.
Was it Charlie Parker?
No.
You know it's funny,
when I was a--
OK.
Miss...
Miss, did you see that?
Leave me alone.
What are you doing?
Somebody help me!
Help me!
Help!
Brian, Brian! Brian!
Yo, what are you
touching me for?
- He killed a guy!
- Josephine, get off me!
- Call the cops!
- You're fired!
Ah!
Is my lawyer here yet?
Not yet.
That's a nice necklace
you got there.
- That's not gold, is it?
- No, it isn't.
You don't look the type
to get fancy with the bling-bling.
I don't spend my money
on that stupid shit,
is that all right with you?
So, what you're telling me is,
You wouldn't spend
any money on it,
but you would wear it, right?
Is that what you're saying?
Can you just please go
see if my lawyer's here?
You holding out on me?
I told you everything I know.
You see, my problem is
that I believe you.
I believe that everything
you told us is true.
But what I don't believe
is that you gave us
everything that you know.
Your story's got
a lot of holes in it.
I need some more information
if I'm gonna be able to let you go.
If you believe me,
why am I handcuffed
to this fucking truck?
OK.
I'm listening.
Look, I told you
everything I know.
I was scared, I was running
for my fucking life.
I don't know why it happened.
Honey, that's the same story.
All right,
you're not going anywhere
until you start filling in the gaps.
Everything that you
told us is great,
but we need to find out
exactly what's going on.
So you gotta come forth,
let's do it.
I told you everything I know.
I just want to go home.
Look, I want to go home too.
But you and me,
we're not going anywhere
until you start
filling in the holes.
So I'll tell you
what we do know.
Nobody saw the young boy get killed
at the basketball court,
nobody saw Brian Epstein
get killed in the office here,
and nobody saw John Doe
get killed outside.
But what we do know
is that all three of them
were brutally murdered
using the same weapon
by the same person.
Are you that person?
No.
We interviewed some of
your co-workers earlier today,
and they said you had a big
disagreement with Brian Epstein.
Are you fucking crazy?
You think I did that to Brian?
I saw Brian get murdered.
The only thing you got
going for you right now
is that the lady
at the bus stop said
she saw you being
chased by somebody,
but she couldn't identify them.
- Was that Brian Epstein?
- Absolutely not.
You got anything else
you can give me?
Any information
to help me out?
Anything to help you out?
I can't even think straight.
I don't know anything else.
All right, you can go.
What's up, baby?
Hey.
How you feel?
What's up?
I'm so scared.
I know, baby, I know.
Don't worry about it.
You feel better now? No?
Just tired.
Come on, let's go in the room.
Tell Papi everything.
What's up?
What's on your mind?
Don't cry, baby.
Don't cry, please.
I saw Brian get killed.
I feel so bad because
I know we had
our problems...
I ran up to him
and I was standing--
I was right in front
of him when it happened.
And I feel so bad.
I mean, the guy playing ball,
I was just watching him
and I saw him get grabbed...
I don't understand why
somebody would do that
to somebody else.
Boo, a lot of people
these days,
they don't know
what they're doing.
They don't know why they do it.
The only thing you can do
is keep being you, you know?
You can't change that.
Try not to cry.
Let's lay down for a minute,
get some rest.
Don't leave the room.
I'm not going anywhere,
baby. Don't worry.
I'll be right here, all right?
Hello? Hello?
Steve, baby, get up.
They're breaking in!
- Who?
- I don't know!
Hurry up!
Baby, what's going on?
What's going...
What the fuck is going on?
Steve?
Stop! Stop!
No wait, come back!
Please, wait...
Please...
You gotta hurry up.
Come on, you gotta hurry up.
Jesus fucking Christ, woman.
Would you fucking die already?
Where the fuck is she?
- Sorry.
- Where is she?
- Help me!
- Come back!
Somebody help me!
I'm not gonna hurt you.
I don't want to hurt you.
I just want to cut
your fucking heart out.
Somebody...
Hello?
Anybody?
Somebody...
Sir, excuse me...
What?
Hi.
How are you doing?
You in trouble?
Can I help you?
I was just wondering
if any one of you were...
Oh, my...
Can I help you?
Help!
Help me!
Somebody help me!
Help!
Help me! Help me!
Help me!
They're gonna kill me!
- You gotta help me!
- Help you?
- You gotta help me.
- With what?
Get out of here.
Just get out of here.
- Listen to me, they're gonna kill all of us.
- I don't care.
Yo, who the hell are you?
I'm not helping you.
Get the hell out of here.
- Listen to me.
- Get the hell out of here.
They're gonna kill us both.
They're all over the place.
I don't care. Get out of here.
Who's all over the place?
You gotta help me!
Oh, man! Damn!
- Damn it!
- You have to do something.
Please do something.
They're gonna kill all of us.
Get out of here!
Come on, let's go,
let's go.
I'm gonna get you!
Come on,
you have to come on.
We have to keep going.
Stupid bitch,
leave me the hell alone.
I can't do this by myself.
I need to find a phone,
I have to find my husband.
Help you?
Listen, just leave me
the hell alone.
Get out of here, all right?
Look, I need to find a phone.
All I want to do
is get my husband
and get home.
We're in the woods.
How you gonna find
a phone around here?
Oh, we're in the woods?
I hadn't noticed.
I still need to get a phone.
I have to get out of here.
Look, I have to find
my husband.
I can't do this by myself.
Husband? He's probably dead,
all right?
Just get out of here
and leave me the hell--
How the hell did you
get out here anyway?
I'm part of a demolition crew.
Look, we were gonna
blow up a building
and all this fucked-up shit
started happening.
Now my husband is missing.
And who the hell are those people?
They seem to know you.
Listen, I don't know
who the hell they are,
all I know is I roll with the tribe.
Wherever they go I go, all right?
We live in abandoned buildings,
old mills,
anywhere until someone kicks us out,
and then we move on.
- Leave me alone.
- Oh great, so you guys are bums.
Where I'm from bums
don't eat people.
Bums? I'm not a bum,
all right?
Different strokes for
different folks, all right?
Whatever you say.
All right, look--
I don't know how
I got out here,
I need to find my husband.
Can you please help me
find my husband?
Listen, your husband
is probably dead, all right?
Just get out of here.
Whatever you do--
call the cops,
call the Navy,
Just leave me the hell alone
and leave me out of it.
But just leave me out of it.
Forget about him?
He's my fucking husband.
You know what, just shut up
and show me the way out of here.
You shut up.
Listen, let's just get
out of here, all right?
I'll show you the way out
but leave me alone after that.
Stupid... stupid, man...
All right, all right, all right,
don't go anywhere else.
Listen, this is what
you're gonna do:
You're gonna go right over there,
where those trees are.
After the trees
you're gonna see a river.
You cross through that river,
there's gonna be a big, tall mountain.
Go over that mountain,
there's gonna be a road,
once you get on that road
you'll see everything you need,
and just leave me the hell alone,
forget all the hell about it.
Go!
Thanks.
Yeah, whatever.
Just get out of here.
Damn.
Damn!
No!
Steve?
Wait!
Wait, please wait.
Please!
Shit!
Oh, man...
Are you all right?
Oh, my God!
Oh, my--
Do you have a cell phone?
Can you hear me?
They cut me.
Do you have a cell phone?
Talk to me!
Listen...
Oh, my God...
Please, please...
Come on...
Ahh! Josephine!
Josephine!
Steve? Steve?
Steve!
Josephine!
Jo-Jo...
Jo-Josephine!
Ahh!
Ahh! Josephine!
Josephine!
Steve?
Motherfucker!
Motherfuckers.
I swear to God...
You want to play? All right.
All right.
Motherfuckers.
Fuckers, all right...
Come on, come on...
All right...
Eat this, motherfuckers!
Yeah, motherfucker, burn!
Fuck!
Oh, Steve...
Steve?
Steve...
Come here!
Get her, get her.
Get off!
Tie her up! Tie her up!
Tie her up!
Stay still!
Let me get up
and I'll fuck you up!
Shut the fuck up!
Yeah, shut up.
Shut up.
She movin' still?
Just shut up.
Get her fucking hands.
We gotta get out of here.
Oh my G--
Oh, God.
Hey, Jo...
You gotta help me.
I'm fucking bleeding.
Who the fuck was those guys?
Come on, Jo...
I know I was fucking
with you before,
But I was only playing, man.
We gotta get the fuck out of here.
Shut up,
I hear somebody coming.
You done well, gentlemen.
Perfect.
Gentlemen, back off.
This is dinner, relax.
You'll all have your turn.
This one smells vile.
You're spoiling.
Smell that.
It's spoiled rotten.
It's impossible,
he's still breathing.
Impossible?
Maybe you should be
on this hook.
Now this one...
This is a whole
other ball park.
Yeah.
Gentleman, I will not
say "back off" again.
I said back off!
Yes, yes...
So fresh...
Open your eyes.
Look at me. Look at me.
Yes...
Knife.
Let's just have a sample.
I wouldn't do that if I were you.
And why not, huh?
I have diseases you can't
even pronounce.
Impossible.
We had your husband
about an hour ago,
and I feel great!
No!
Till death do us part.
No! Come back here, bitch!
- Come back here!
- Motherfucker!
Steve?
Hey, Doc, we should go.
We should get
out of here, Doc.
Time to go, huh?
Wrap that one to go.
That's fresh.
I like the smell.
Yeah... I like that.
You guys have done me well.
You guys are my brothers.
You smell that though?
You know what that smell is?
That smell is
a small smell of success.
Fresh flesh I consider a success.
And you guys are helping me
achieve that success.
You are my brothers.
- Am I right or wrong?
- Right, yeah.
It's me.
It's me, it's Josephine. Shh.
Those streets are ours.
- Am I right or wrong?
- Yeah.
What are we doing
down here hiding?
What do we have to hide from?
We own those streets up there.
They should be hiding from us.
That...
That's only a small portion
of what we could have.
He's one out of a million.
Let's go back up there
and take our streets, gentlemen.
Can we take our streets? Hmm?
Damn, right!
Can we?
I need your guys' help.
I can't do this alone.
I need you guys to recruit,
I need you guys to go up there
and back 'em down.
If they don't want to run,
bring 'em back down here
and we hack 'em.
Everything belongs to us
from here on out.
We don't need money.
We don't need wealth.
We need the flesh.
You know the drill.
Uh...
What's the name
of the mission, sir?
Operation...
Gumbo.
Now, as I was saying,
I need you--
Uh, sir...
Didn't we just have a mission,
Operation Gumbo?
OK, how about
operation gumbo 2?
As I was saying,
first things first.
I need you to take
the south side for me.
Uh, sir, no disrespect,
I'm sorry, but...
Operation Gumbo 2?
I mean, that's kind of
cheesy, right?
I mean, shouldn't we
name it something else?
Sequels are always the worst.
I'm right, right?
I'm sorry...
I can't really hear you.
I need you to open
your mouth a little bit wider
when you speak.
Step a little closer.
- What did you say?
- Operation Gumbo 2?
I mean, that's kind of
cheesy, right?
- And your name is?
- Benedict, sir.
- What's my name?
- You're the doctor.
Exactly.
Now, Benedict...
I will name my operations
whatever I see fit
to name my operations...
Bene-dict.
Cheesy...
Yeah!
Yeah.
Gentlemen...
Eggs Benedict tomorrow
for breakfast.
Yeah! Yeah!
Now let's get to work.
Right.
Shh, shh...
Come on.
Shh, be quiet.
Be quiet.
It's me, it's all right.
Come on.
Baby, come on.
Listen, come on.
It's Josephine.
Baby, it's me.
Listen, listen, it's me, baby.
Come on.
Sit down. Listen...
Baby, listen, listen, listen.
Don't move, OK?
I'm gonna find a way
out of here.
Don't move, OK?
Josephine!
Josephine! Josephine!
I'll bring her to you.
Josephine!
Hold him down,
hold him down.
Josephine!
And now for the finale, baby.
Oh, no. Oh, shoot!
Josephine!
I told you to wait.
Eat that!
Motherfucker!
Fucker! Fucker!
Where the fuck are you?
Hold it!
Drop the fucking knife.
- What's going on?
- Drop the knife.
Drop the gun,
we can talk.
Put the knife down.
OK, OK, OK.
Don't worry about it.
It's just me and you now.
I'll walk.
We can work together.
I see how you enjoyed it downstairs,
come on.
Why do you think I didn't
eat you a long time ago?
You took my life from me.
I gave you that. Relax.
Listen to me...
Listen to me. Look...
We're in the final chapter, man.
We're in the final chapter.
We can work together.
You enjoyed this.
You like this shit.
Get back.
Ok, relax.
I'll tell you what,
I make you feel uncomfortable,
put that gun down.
You don't want to use that.
You want to work with me,
you want to join me.
Everybody else is dead,
you're the only one left.
Back off!
OK, OK, listen,
I make you uncomfortable?
I tell you what,
I'll talk to you from here.
You're a queen, I'll get on
my knees for you, OK?
You made it through, listen--
Now we can listen
to the real man, all right?
You gotta be
fucking kidding me.
Are you fucking kidding me?
Are you fucking
kidding me, huh?
You can't have
a fucking gun with no bullets.
You faking me out, huh?
You know what?
I'm gonna fucking carve you.
Come on, baby.
Come on, Josephine,
the fun begins now!
Let's go, baby.
Whoo!
Come on, Josephine.
Come on, baby.
Come on, come on, baby.
Come on. Come on.
You can do better than that.
Come on, come on, bitch.
Huh? Huh?
What do I look like,
the rest of those motherfuckers?
Huh?
Is that the best you could do?
I gave you an opportunity, baby.
I gave you an opportunity.
Didn't l, huh?
I gave you an opportunity
to work on me, didn't l?
Oh, shit.
Oh, man.
Yeah...
Yeah, whoo!
Whoo. Yeah.
That's what I'm talking about.
You want throw 'em with me?
Come on, ready?
Come on.
Let's go.
Let's do it for real now.
Come on, attack me.
Yeah.
That's what I'm talking about.
Come on, again.
You ready? Again.
Why you running?
Aren't you hungry, bitch?
Yeah, motherfucker.
It isn't funny now, is it?
Is it?
You ruined my fucking life.
Look what you did to me.
Look what you did to me!
Look at me!
I don't fucking believe this.
You fucking coward.
You ruined my fucking life!
Look what you did to me!
Subtitles: Broadcast Text
www.broadcasttext.com