I'd like to think that fate had a hand
in what happened that summer.
That it was the pants' destiny
to find us.
Where they came from
and why they chose us...
...well, that will always be a mystery.
But perhaps that was part
of their miracle.
That they sensed in that moment
how much we needed them.
How much we needed
some little bit of faith to hold onto...
...when it seemed like everything
we believed in was about to slip away.
But wait a minute,
I'm getting ahead of myself.
Beautiful dress! Love it.
We'd been a foursome
for as long as I could remember.
-Where are we going?
-We're going over there.
In fact, we were a foursome
before we were born.
And seven. Anyone feel any kicking?
Our mothers met
at a prenatal aerobics class.
They really didn't have
anything in common...
...except their due dates.
One, and relax. Good work.
The first one out of the gate was Bridget.
Ladies, let's keep it together.
The rest of us followed within the week.
Bridget liked to take charge.
Way to go, Lena.
l'll handle this.
And you know what?
Sometimes, that worked in our favor.
Oh, my God.
And that's how it always was with us:
Give and take.
But mostly give.
Lena, l don't think
he's coming back this time.
It's gonna be okay, Carmen.
l'll come over first thing tomorrow.
And Tibby and Bridget too.
Just stay on the phone with me
until you fall asleep.
What Were They Thinking?, take seven.
We were there for each other...
...to understand the things
that no one else in the world could.
What were they thinking,
having another baby at their age?
And what was l?
Just some experiment
from their hippie days...
...and now it's time
to start their real family?
Go ahead.
They're out of their minds.
lt sucks.
-Totally.
-Cut!
Lena, don't you realize this is tragedy?
Can't you give me
a bit more enthusiasm?
There were some things
we would never make sense of.
Grief is never an easy burden to bear.
And we were there for those too.
And as we mourn the loss
of this beloved wife, mother and friend...
...it only makes her choice
that much more unfathomable.
What measure of despair compels
one to commit such an act?
We can only take comfort in the fact
that she is in a better place now...
...than she found here among us.
My deepest sympathies. Bridget.
We were there for the things
we couldn't face alone.
-Hey.
-Hey, Bee, you okay?
Yeah. l will be as soon as l get out
of these stupid heels.
Here. Hold them for me, will you?
Think l'll run home.
Or the ones we didn't
want to face at all.
Together, it was as if we formed
one single, complete person.
Wild, unstoppable Bridget.
Shy and beautiful Lena.
Tibby, the rebel.
And me, Carmen, the writer.
Can't buy anything new
at a vintage store.
We were 1 6 and had never been apart.
And all that was about to change.
-How about this one?
-lt's great.
lf you wanna go to Greece
looking like Laverne De Fazio.
-Who?
-'70s TV icon.
Am l the only one who's
not culturally deprived?
Tibby forgot to take
her happy pill this morning.
Actually, l'm saving them for when
l'm stuck doing time at Wallmans...
...while the rest of you jet off
on your little adventures.
Boo-hoo, Tibby.
You are such a drama queen.
l am going to South Carolina.
That is only, like, three states away.
lt's abandonment, nevertheless.
l hate you all.
You're the one who wanted
to stay here all summer...
...and angst it out
making your documentary.
Yeah, it's gonna be a huge hit.
Thrilling footage on
how to stack deodorant.
l think l'm gonna start my own genre,
call it the ''suckumentary.''
Lena, look at this! Oh, my goodness.
-They're perfect.
-l can't wear a bikini.
Don't you know all the beaches
in Greece are nude?
-What?
-She's just kidding, Lena.
God, l envy you.
You get to go to a place
where there's actually guys.
l thought you were looking forward
to El Campo de Futbol.
She sure was until she found out
it was girls only.
-No boys allowed.
-Don't talk about it.
Hey, pierce alert, pierce alert.
Sorry, young lady, no more holes.
Take those out right now
and try these on.
-Look. Here you go.
-Put them on.
-Go, go, go.
-Okay, Carmen-- Carmen.
Tibby, you're a babe!
Tibby, you look amazing.
Turn around. Look at you!
-Carmen!
-You look wonderful.
-lt looks good.
-lt looked great on you. Please buy them.
-You try them on, then.
-But l don't wear jeans.
Yeah. Or bikinis or miniskirts...
...or anything else that might actually
show you have a shape.
l do not.
Tibby, those look so great on you.
Why can't you just admit it?
Because l'm wallowing in self-pity.
-Lena!
-Are you serious?
-You have a body!
-Look at that.
Lena Kaligaris has a body!
-Stop it! l do not.
-When did this happen?
-You look good in them.
-Look at you.
You look good! Little Lena.
You're the one who loves jeans so much,
why don't you try them?
-Maybe because l'm 3 inches taller than you.
-Fair's fair.
-Hey, how can they be perfect on you too?
-That is a little weird.
l don't know, but it's really starting
to freak me out.
Okay, Carmen, it's your turn.
Carmen, you try them on.
-Oh, come on, honestly. Are you serious?
-You have to.
You think that a pair of jeans that fits
all three of you is going to fit all of this?
-Put them on. Now.
-We'll help your thighs get into them.
-Tibby! Come on, now.
-l'm just kidding.
Will you help me get out of them?
Carmen, we all tried them on.
Just try them.
All right.
My thighs.
Sassy britches.
Get over these thighs.
Okay, here we go.
What? l told you guys.
l'm just gonna take them off...
...and we're gonna pretend
like this never happened.
No, Carmen, come over here
and look at yourself.
-They look amazing on you.
-Look at them.
Call me crazy, but it's
scientifically impossible...
-...that a pair of pants could fit me....
-And me.
This is crazy.
Look, Tib, something happened today
that l can't explain and you can't explain.
-Whatever, let's just ignore it.
-We can't just ignore it.
-Why?
-Because it's a sign, the pants--
-Be quiet, you're gonna--
-You know what, Tibby?
-Sometimes you're much too much.
-Be careful.
-l'm fine, Lena.
-Oh, my God. You're gonna fall.
lt makes our butts look good.
That's enough for me.
-That's right, amen.
-Get up there. Go on.
-There is more going here than Lycra.
-But there's probably Lycra.
All right, guys, are you ready for this?
ln the name of the Father, the Son--
-Here we go.
-Carmen, this isn't church.
You guys! But it's still a sacred place!
l mean, this is where
our moms met, right?
Anyway, look,
we're gathered here today...
...to honor a gift
that has been sent to us.
-So why do we have to pay for them?
-Tibs.
Carmen, go ahead,
just finish what you have to say.
Tonight, on the eve of our separation...
...magic has come to us
in a pair of pants.
And l'm proposing
that we share them equally...
...and that this summer
they travel among us...
...and they'll link us
in hearts and spirits...
...even though we're far apart
from each other.
l think that tonight we're
the sisters of these pantalones.
-Sisters of the Pants?
-Yes!
We need rules.
Every sisterhood has rules.
Thank you. A manifesto.
-Okay.
-Good point. l love it.
Okay, rule number one:
Each sister is going
to keep the pants for...?
-A week.
Lena should be first
because Greece is the furthest away.
-Okay.
-Tibby, you next.
-What's your rule?
-l don't have a rule.
-Yes, you do.
-Tibs, come on.
No picking your nose
when wearing the pants.
-Honestly.
-That's not--
You can casually scratch
while really picking a little.
-Thanks for the allowance.
-Good rule.
When sending the pants,
we'll write a letter...
...detailing the most exciting thing
that happened while wearing them.
That's good.
So most exciting thing
that happens to you.
And what if nothing exciting happens?
-It will. It has to!
-No, I really doubt it.
And when it happens, and we reunite...
...we will document it
on the pants themselves.
-That's good.
-That's rule number six.
Rule number seven:
Any removal of the pants
must be done by the wearer herself.
Yes, you.
Touché!
He works, you know.
So he may not have that much time
to spend with you.
So if you get lonely,
come home, okay?
l'm gonna be fine, Mom.
We will never, ever
wash these pants.
Carmen, that's so unnecessary.
Why not?
Because you can't wash the pants.
-Why? Why?
-Carmen, we have to.
What? Are you gonna wash
the magic out of the pants?
The magic's not sanitary.
No, l have a better one.
No double cuffing.
Double-cuffing the pants
at the bottom, it's tacky.
-The '80s are over.
-You know what else is tacky?
Tucking in your shirt
and wearing a belt at the same time.
-l don't do that anymore.
-Good one.
l did that one time.
-Forbidden to cuff or tuck.
-Okay, okay.
-No cuffing or tucking.
-My turn, my turn.
-Okay.
-Yes, Bee?
You can never say you look fat
while wearing the pants.
You can't even think it!
All passengers,
this is the final boarding call--
Take care,
and be sure to write, huh?
You too. Bye.
You better get going.
Looks like they're starting to board.
-That's nine.
-So we need one more.
-We need a final rule.
-Final rule.
Okay, pants equal love.
Love your sisters and love yourself.
To the pants.
And the sisterhood.
And this summer...
...and the rest of our lives.
Together and apart.
You know, Papou,
l really wouldn't mind walking.
l'm sorry that my Greek isn't so good.
Mom said that l'd pick it up in no time.
You know, with all the talking,
just with you and with Yia Yia.
Lena!
lt's the evil eye.
Lena. l think l'll die
and never see my Lena.
l think l'll never see you, my Lena.
You like your room? And your bed?
l have put the most special
sheets and lace.
And from this window,
the most beautiful view.
She's precious. Like a jewel.
We guard you like a jewel.
You need rest.
When you hear your name called
and the color of your team...
...run over and join your coach.
-All right.
-Alma, Megan, green.
Anderson, Alice, green.
Adissa, Jessica, red.
Bo, Natalie, red.
Come on, come on, rapido!
Please, God, let me sprain
my ankle as soon as possible.
Come again?
This whole thing was my mother's idea.
She couldn't wait to get rid of me.
God, mine has been sobbing all week,
''What am l gonna do without you?''
l'm like, ''Get a life, Ma,'' you know?
What's yours do?
Nothing.
Hey, who's that?
Don't even think about it. lt's against
the rules to have flings with the coaches.
Marsden, Olivia, red.
Come on!
Vreeland, Bridget, red.
Hey, baby.
Here it is. l asked the school
to postpone sending this...
...because, Dad,
l wanted to surprise you.
-Ta-da! Straight A's.
-That's fantastic.
Dad, l brought my tennis gear
and l have been practicing like crazy...
-...so serve to me your absolute hardest.
-l'll do that.
You know, l was calculating it
on the train.
l haven't spent more than four
straight days with you since l was 1 0.
l mean, l love it when
you come for Christmas...
...but a whole summer
and just the two of us?
Mom taught me
how to make arroz con pollo.
l'm gonna cook that for you.
And platanos too.
Wait, where are we?
l have a surprise for you.
l moved out of Charleston.
And into a development?
Dad, you hate developments.
When did l say that?
At the Frederick Law Olmstead
exhibit at the Smithsonian.
You said, ''There's city and there's country,
and everything else is a wasteland.''
l was 9 years old. You came to D.C. for
one day to visit with a plastics company.
You remember everything!
l don't remember
you telling me you moved.
Who is that?
ls that your neighbor?
Actually, we live together.
Hey!
You must be Carmen.
Your daddy has told me
so much about you.
l just know we're gonna have
the most wonderful summer together.
-Kids! Kids, come on out here!
-Kids?
They're not kids,
they're teenagers, just like you.
They live with you?
Carmen, this is Krista and this is Paul.
-We're gonna be bridesmaids together.
-Excuse me?
l hadn't quite gotten
to that part of the surprise yet.
Oh, sweetheart....
We're getting married.
August 1 9th.
Say, you're a real natural with that thing.
Took me weeks
before l got the hang of it.
Yeah, well, we all have
our special talents.
Tibby! l thought
l made it perfectly clear...
...that employee headsets
are to be worn at all times.
Don't make me mention it again.
Excuse me?
Where are the shampoos?
Aisle seven.
Somebody help!
Girl down.
Somebody call an ambulance!
You've got a price sticker
on your forehead.
l'm sorry...
...l don't speak Greek very well.
Well, we'll have to work
on that, won't we?
Thanks for lending me a shirt.
Looks good on you.
Sorry if it smells like fish.
-ls this your boat?
-My grandfather's.
Yeah. All the ones
with the blue flags are his.
-Do you work for him?
-No, just in the summer.
l go to the university in Athens.
Kostas Dounas.
Lena Kaligaris.
Then you are Greek too, eh?
So how do you know English so well?
Well, l lived with my parents
in Chicago until l was 1 2.
Oh, my parents moved to the U.S. too.
But l'm just here for the summer.
l'm staying with my grandparents.
l have to throw the small ones back.
Would you like to help?
No. That's okay.
Okay, here, l'll show you.
Give me your hand.
Put your hand on my hand.
Put your hand close.
Good?
Luck was on his side today.
l have to go. l should go.
But thank you again
for saving my life.
Do you dance better than you swim?
-Excuse me?
-Saturday night. Meet me.
l'm sorry. l can't.
Pick it up!
Hi.
-Hi.
-l'm Bridget.
-Eric.
-l know.
So l hear you go to Columbia.
Yep.
Well, what have you heard about me?
Your high school won Nationals.
MVP. l play forward.
So l've noticed.
l'm 1 7.
Come on, l'll race you.
That's it.
Seven miles.
Oh, God, don't you love to run?
Yeah.
lt's the best high there is.
Exactly, it's--
lt's like you're just in this place where
nothing bad could ever happen, you know?
Like if you just push a bit further,
if you just keep moving--
Nothing can touch you.
Of course, the endorphins
don't suck, either.
-So Tami's feeling okay?
-Yeah.
ls she gonna do
baton twirling with you?
We don't know yet.
She might just have to hold the banner.
Sweetheart, why don't we say grace
before we start eating dinner?
-l would love to.
-All right.
Bless us, O Lord, for these,
thy gifts which we are about to receive...
...from Thy bounty,
through Christ, our Lord.
-Amen. Dig in.
-This looks great.
-l will get that.
-Oh, it's okay.
We don't answer the phone
during dinner.
Except that one time.
Tell us again how you guys met.
We've told that story so many--
-You wanna tell it?
-l don't.
-Want me to?
-All right.
-l dialed the wrong number.
-And l answered.
-Lydia answered.
-During dinner.
Just that one time.
And Lydia agreed
to go out with a stranger.
-ls that not what happened?
-Oh, no, come on. No, l did not.
-That is exactly what happened!
-We went bowling. lt was so much fun.
-Do you remember you bowled a two?
-A two is a bad score.
At least l didn't get the ball
stuck on my thumb.
The water in the toilet is blue.
-Blue?
-Yes, Mom, blue.
And by the way,
doesn't Dad hate bowling?
-Bowling?
-Well, he's down here bowling.
-And he says grace.
-Grace?
He says grace, Mom.
He gives thanks to God before he eats.
We couldn't get him to go to church
with us once. Who is this guy?
-I don't even--
-You need to talk to him, Carmen.
-Just tell him how you feel.
-l do talk to him. l talk to him all the time.
Yeah, like you talk to me? No.
This is important, Carmencita.
What he did was wrong.
l'm gonna get on a plane
and l'm just gonna come down there.
Look, you'd never want him to be happy,
and that's why you blame him.
And this is gonna work out great.
lt's going to be fine.
Dear Tibby...
...I think we may have been very,
very wrong about the pants.
The one time I wore them
I almost drowned...
...and then got plucked
onto a fishing boat...
...by a guy who made me touch
a live fish. It was disgusting!
At least I'm getting some
good sketching in.
I love everything about this island.
Oh, except that you're not with me.
Infinite X's and O's, Lena.
-How was town?
-Fine.
l have found this in the laundry.
ls it yours?
No, actually...
...l sort of borrowed it.
When l went down to the harbor,
l went swimming...
...and someone just lent it to me.
Oh, someone. Someone who?
A boy?
Which one? l know everyone.
Don't mind them, they're your cousins.
They're cousins too?
How many do l have?
Plenty of them.
Don't change the subject.
Out with it. Out, out.
His name is Kostas Dounas.
Dounas?
He's a Dounas?
You must never speak of them.
They are liars! They are thieves!
They are barbarians!
Your grandfather would die
if he know about this.
You must never see this boy again.
You understand?
-Yes.
-No, that's not enough.
You have to swear.
l swear.
Okay.
What am I supposed to be saying here?
Oh, just, stuff about your life.
Well, there ain't nothing
too interesting.
We're not really looking for interesting.
It's just real, you know.
-That's the point of a documentary.
-A what?
A documentary.
Like a movie, only boring.
Hi, l think this is yours.
They delivered it to my house by mistake.
They must've got
the numbers screwed up.
See, this says 721 and l'm 27 1 .
l'm Bailey Graffman.
Yeah, you're the one that fainted
the other day, right?
-At Wallmans. l was there.
-Oh, yeah.
You're the weird girl
with the price sticker on your forehead.
Wait here, l got something for you.
lt was lying next to you.
l opened it to see if there was an lD.
So you ripped off my wallet?
That's kind of like a thank you
but different.
l think l had more than $4 in here.
Do you seriously think
l would steal your money?
l opened it to see
if there was an lD in there.
Okay? There wasn't. There was a school
photo and a pathetic picture of a kitten.
So, what's in yours?
A Wallmans' employee card
or a license to ride a bike?
Excuse me, l get my learner's permit
next week and--
How old are you, like 1 0?
-Twelve.
-Whatever. Same difference.
No, when l was 1 0
l didn't have an iPod.
You're so cool. What are you listening to,
Teletubbies Hit Parade?
You woke her up. Thank you.
Must suck.
-What?
-Having to babysit on your day off.
Why are you working there, anyway?
lt just so happens that l need some
extra money for new video equipment.
When l finally got around to looking
for a new job, Wallmans was the....
Why am l telling you this?
Don't you have somewhere to be?
Not really.
Looks like you got a lot already.
-Are you making a movie or something?
-More like an ode.
-To what?
-Lives of quiet desperation.
Human existence at its lamest.
-Fascinating. Maybe you need an assistant.
-Maybe l don't.
You wouldn't have to pay me or anything.
l could carry equipment and stuff.
Hi, honey.
l'm sorry l'm late.
Who's your friend?
-She's not my--
-Bailey, Bailey Graffman.
Well, l gotta go.
See you around, Tibby.
There you are.
-Hi.
-Hey.
We should play tennis tomorrow.
-Really?
-Yeah.
-ln the morning?
Are you ready for this, old man?
You think your knees can take it?
-You actually think you can return my serve?
-l do, Dad. l do.
-Like to put money on that?
-l'll put money on it.
-Sweetheart?
-Yeah.
l gotta meet the caterers at the hotel.
Mind stopping by Paul's game?
Sure.
Well, he's an unbelievable
soccer player.
We'll just stop for one second, okay?
-lt's right on the way.
-Yeah. Yeah, okay.
-Hey.
-How are you?
Good. Didn't think your team
was scrimmaging till later today.
They're not. l just came out early
to check out the competition.
Well, you're looking at her.
You're awfully sure of yourself, huh?
When l know what l want.
You got it!
Take it down! Take it down!
What's that?!
Overtime! All right!
-Overtime, yes.
-Which one of those is yours?
Paul, Paul Rodman.
So you're the golden boy's dad.
He's a good player.
-Yeah, he is.
-Al!
Okay. Pass!
Pass, Vreeland!
Now!
Yep, nice shot.
We're not worthy!
Sub! Vreeland, you're out!
This is a scrimmage, Vreeland,
as in practice.
Everyone on the team
needs to get some.
We know you're a superstar, okay?
We got it.
Now save it for the championship.
-Who do we got, Deanna?
-Katie, you're up.
Okay, Katie, let's go, let's go!
Same thing!
Nice! Get up, Wendy!
Get there! Yes!
The hotel that's doing our wedding
had a water main break.
-The whole place is flooded.
-The repairs won't be done for months.
Oh, my God, the place
was just so perfect.
l'm never gonna find
another place in time.
We will find a place.
l'm sorry.
Lydia never had a real wedding.
My dad died just before my first and....
Come on, let's get you home.
We'll work this out.
Hey, Paul, you wanna
play tennis with Carmen?
Great shot, Paul.
-What?
-Lydia needs me, sweetie.
lt'll be a chance for you
to get to know each other.
Dad, Paul doesn't talk.
Yeah, he's a little shy.
Go on. lt'll be fun.
-We'll play tomorrow, okay?
-Okay.
Oh, my God, are you okay?
Oh, my gosh! Are you okay?
l'm so sorry, l'm sorry!
lt's swelling. l'm so sorry.
-lt's no big deal.
-We should just stop.
l'm tired anyway.
-Kalimera, Lena.
-No. l thought-- l didn't--
Well, here's your shirt. Thanks again.
Lena, wait.
l was just about to take her out.
Come with me?
No. l shouldn't even be here at all.
They told you, didn't they?
You think this is funny?
Our grandparents hate each other.
You knew my name. Why didn't
you say something the other day?
Well, because the arguments of old men
have nothing to do with us.
Well, they're not arguing about nothing.
What was the fight about?
What everything here is about:
Money and fish.
My grandfather says
your grandfather cheat him.
Your grandfather says
my grandfather...
...sold him fish that make
his whole restaurant sick.
So, what's the truth?
The truth is that
it's a beautiful day and....
Why should the rest of it matter?
Because it does.
Tibby.
Tibby, now, l have had another complaint
of receipt withholding.
-This is your second offense and--
-You're gonna have to dock my pay.
That's right.
Also, the dress code
strictly prohibits blue jeans.
Great.
What are you doing with my stuff?
Your mom gave it to me.
l told her l was your assistant.
-You what? Wait--
-She seemed to think it was a good idea.
Okay, look, you seem like a sweet kid.
No, you seem like a pain in the ass.
But look, l have my own friends.
Three best friends. Even though
they left me here to rot this summer...
-...l'm not looking for new ones.
-Neither am l.
l just think it'd be cool
to learn about filmmaking.
Besides, l think l found
a good subject for an interview.
His name is Brian McBrian,
king of ''Dragon's Lair.''
l've heard he's broken
every record there is.
Okay, he's definitely not
what you'd call lame...
...but l figured he'd be a good contrast
to all the loser types in the movie.
Start setting up.
Stand next to him.
Pretend you're a fan,
like you watch him all the time.
-Right.
-And action.
Video arcade wizards are fixtures
at most convenience stores.
Brian McBrian is a fixture at this one.
''Dragon's Lair,'' he says...
...is his calling.
So, Brian, you spend a lot of time here?
Sometimes all day.
So you prefer to spend most
of your time here at the Quick Mart...
...instead of out in the real world?
Well, maybe he finds the world of
''Dragon's Lair'' more interesting.
Tell us about it, Brian.
Well....
Basically, you're Dirk the Daring...
...in the year 1 305 A.D.
See, the goal
is to rescue Princess Daphne...
...who's being guarded
by Singe, the dragon.
See, chamber number one
is the Snake Room.
-See, snakes slither from the ceiling.
-Really?
You don't even get to see the dragon
until chamber number 23!
Yeah!
-Come on, come on!
-Yeah!
Faster! Faster! Go!
He's right behind you!
-Go, go, go!
-Yeah, l got it.
-Watch this, ready?
-Run fast!
Oh, you must have run out of tape.
What about the rest of the interview?
Well, we could always
come back tomorrow, l guess.
-l mean, if that's cool with you.
-Yeah.
You all right?
ls she speaking Spanish?
-Oh, is that okay? ls that all right?
-Oh, sure! Sure.
lt's just that nobody
understands it, sweetie.
Oh, come on, Dad,
you know that is not true.
He and my mom, they used to speak
Spanish all the time.
Especially when they
started being all gushy...
-...and they didn't want me to understand.
-Wow, it's 9:00?
-But l totally understood them.
-l gotta drop that check at the caterers.
Carmen, you're not gonna believe this.
We have decided to have the wedding
right here at home.
With a big party in the back yard.
Dancing under the stars.
lt's gonna be perfect.
Where's Paul?
-Oh, he had an appointment.
-At the hospital?
Why would you say that?
We were playing tennis the other day,
and l hit him, but it was an accident--
-No, no. He's okay.
-He's fine.
-He just--
-He just had to do something.
Yeah.
-Dad, Dad, Dad.
-Yo.
What's going on?
Where exactly is Paul?
He's in Atlanta, honey.
Visiting his father.
His dad's in a facility.
He's an alcoholic.
Every month, Paul takes a bus
to visit him.
Krista refuses to see him.
She's not ready for that.
Lydia doesn't want to upset her
by talking about it...
...so we just say
Paul's out for the day.
Okay.
Natasha.
Olivia.
Bridget.
Polly.
-Janna.
-Oh, tampons!
That's special, Mom.
-Jo!
-Now, welcome to camp.
Diana.
Shampoo. Very, very practical.
Hamburgers.
Did you guys hear? Actually, they're
finally giving us Saturday off.
Hallelujah. Can you say ''Cantina''?
Hey, where's the Cantina?
l don't know. l think somewhere
up the road. Why?
He wants me to go.
What?
Why else would he have said
that right in front of me?
This is my favorite part.
When he takes the big risk
and launches the catapult.
Bailey, come on, l'm trying to see if
there's something we can use from this.
Just one thing.
What was in the package?
Just some....
Just those pair of pants over there.
l'm sharing them
with my friends for the summer.
These?
-What's so great about an old pair of jeans?
-Nothing.
They just happen to
mysteriously fit us all perfectly.
Really?
l wonder what they'd look like on me.
On the off-chance you'd ever
let me try them on.
-Like now, for example.
-Go ahead, do whatever you want.
l need some quiet.
Tibby?
l need you to take the baby!
My Carma-poochie-ay,
I'm writing from the post office...
...and this express mail costs more
than I make in two hours at Wallmans...
...so these jeans
better get to you tomorrow.
Here we are on a typical
Bethesda corner...
...where generations of young entrepreneurs
have proved the old adage:
''When life hands you lemons,
make lemonade.''
So the question on my mind is...
...is this fresh-squeezed or powder?
-Does it matter if it's good lemonade?
-Let me ask the questions.
I'm sad to report that
nothing of consequence happened...
...while wearing the pants.
I spilled a Sprite...
...and my rat-faced manager
accused me of receipt withholding.
-Receipt withholding.
-In rat-faced manager lingo...
...that means forgetting
to give a sales slip.
You know, l was reading
that Bill Gates...
...when he was younger,
he ran a lemonade stand.
-You don't know that, that's not--
-Yeah, l do. l read it in a magazine.
-Where did you read that?
-ln a magazine.
Other than that, the only thing
that I have to show for the pants...
...is the kid that delivered them,
some wise-ass pain in the neck...
...who's decided to permanently
glue herself to my hip.
She's just tired. She's been there
a really long time, all day.
What is she doing right there?
Tell me.
-She's just thinking. She's strategizing.
-l think she's trying to grow a brain.
Too bad you can't express mail
1 2-year-olds.
And l wish you the very best of luck
on this endeavor.
Hey. Hey there, sleepyhead.
Hey, Carmen.
-Honey, time to wake up.
-Hi.
Hi there. Good morning.
Sorry to wake you...
...but l was just wondering if
Maria could grab your sheets.
-Maria?
-Yeah, our housekeeper.
l told her you usually slept late...
...but l don't think she understood me.
Her English isn't real good.
Okay, right.
Could l-- l'll just wash my own sheets.
No, no, no. Don't be silly.
Maria can certainly do your sheets,
not a problem.
-Lydia, it's really--
-lt's a beautiful day.
-You shouldn't be washing sheets.
-Oh, it's not a problem at all.
l usually do it myself anyway.
l do it all the time. l'm so used to it.
People wash their sheets all the time.
Okay.
Been here long?
Kostas. What are you doing here?
lt's a fish market.
This is where l sell my fish.
Right.
But you already knew that, eh?
Excuse me?
Lena, no one sits
near a smelly fish market...
...unless they're waiting for someone.
Well, l don't know
what you're talking about.
l just came to sketch
that old church over there.
May l?
Well, it's-- lt's not finished.
-You didn't tell me you were an artist.
-l'm not, really.
Lena, you are.
My parents were married in that church...
...before they left for the United States.
Why did they come back to Greece?
They didn't.
They were killed in a car accident...
...when l was 1 2.
l come back to live with my grandfather.
l'm sorry.
What made you choose to paint this?
l don't know.
l liked it because,
when you first look at it...
...it looks kind of forgotten, and then....
But then you realize that
that's why it's beautiful.
lt's perfect in all its loneliness.
You see?
Lena Kaligaris...
...you are an artist.
And you should finish it.
Well, maybe some other time.
l mean, l really should go.
-lf my grandparents saw me here, they'd--
-They'd what?
ls it really them you're afraid of?
Or is it something else?
What do you mean?
-You don't even know me.
-l'm trying to.
Or can't you see that?
He's right, Car. I am afraid.
There's a part of me
that wants to let him in...
...but then I feel myself
put this wall up...
...and I don't understand why.
Maybe that's what strikes me
most about Kostas.
That despite everything he's suffered...
...he can still look at life
in the most uncomplicated way.
I've never known that kind of faith.
It makes me so sad
that people like Kostas and Bridget...
...who have lost everything...
...can still be open to love...
...while I, who have lost nothing, am not.