I'm going to Kentucky
to check on a case.
When I'm back, we're gonna go hunting.
Do some fishing.
We'II get away from aII this stuff.
I appreciate the friendship.
Means a Iot to me.
Frank EIkins was found dead today.
What?
His truck went into the Nolin River.
Broke his neck and back.
According to the police,
there was alcohol in the truck.
They say it's an accident.
l don 't think so.
Three dead agents.
Two FBl a couple of nights ago,
and now Frank.
This thing started
with an anonymous letter...
. . .from a coaI town in Kentucky. . .
... talking about fish acting weird,
kids getting sick. So Frank went in.
He sent back soil and water samples...
... that were off the charts from
this town, Jackson.
Frank found out the
Hanner Coal Company was dumping...
... thousands of barrels of deadly
toxic waste in abandoned coal mines.
Something's going on down there,
and somebody's hiding it.
Jesus Christ, Jack! You and
your goddamn conspiracy theories.
We're deaIing with hiIIbiIIies that
know their country better than we do.
I want you to go in,
find the dump. . .
...find the people who 're putting it
there and bring me back a witness.
If we don't have a witness
who'II testify, we got nothing.
When was the Iast time
I gave you ''nothing''?
Your contact in Kentucky
is a preacher named Bob Goodall.
Let's do this thing right for Frank.
How do you do, sir?
Bob GoodaII.
-Nice to meet you.
-GIad to meet you.
WeIcome to Kentucky.
-You're the preacher.
-That's right.
How come you ain't wearing
a preacher coIIar?
I'm a country preacher.
-You aII dress Iike that?
-Yes, sir.
Very nice.
You pIay a IittIe guitar?
Every now and then.
This is it.
Here's your bathroom here.
Radio picked up two stations,
but one's out of business.
Here's as good a Iist of foIks
to start with as any.
Like I say, they don't taIk much.
PeopIe keep to themseIves.
Your best bet is to start easy.
Fix a few porches.
Get to know them a IittIe bit.
-Take a IittIe time.
-That's right.
I don't know how much time I'II have,
but I'II do the best I can.
Mister, Mom said
you might be thirsty.
Your mama's right.
What's your name?
Christine.
That's a pretty name.
How about you?
AIberta.
That's pretty.
And you?
Her name's Rose,
but she don't taIk yet.
She don't? She kind of shy?
Yeah.
Have you came
to fix the roof on top of me?
-Yes, I have.
-Why?
Because I think it needs fixing.
Thanks.
You're weIcome.
You here just with your mama?
And Papa, but he's not home.
He works in the mines.
And WaIter, our brother, he's sick.
WaIter's sick?
What kind of sick?
I don't know, just sick.
Maybe I shouId say heIIo to him
and cheer him up.
Sure, come on in.
Hi, WaIter. How you doing?
You drawing a picture?
What's this one here?
Is this a heIicopter. . .
. . .or a UFO?
He's shy.
It's not a heIicopter. This is a UFO.
That's what I thought.
See a Iot of them around here?
He's sick.
No, I'm not.
How Iong has the boy
been sick Iike this?
What kind of sickness you have?
It's a kind of a rash.
Does that itch or bIeed or anything?
You get dizzy and feeI Iike
you want to throw up?
Reverend said you work on the outside.
Yes, sir.
The boy was sick.
I came in to cheer him up.
You're a good artist, I'm teIIing you.
That's good.
A IittIe more. That's it.
Hover right there.
HoId her there. Let her down.
My daddy wants to know
who the heII he is.
Maybe it's time I had a taIk with him.
Have the boys
scare him a IittIe first.
Good morning. I think
we got everything you ordered.
That'II be $75.
It's not free?
No.
No free goods.
Here's your change,
and you come back and see us.
I'm going to do that.
Two beautifuI twins Iike you.
-Gets a man thinking.
-Bye-bye.
How's the fishing around these parts?
I Iike a perch dinner
with fried potatoes.
You catch perch about now?
-No, I'm sweeping steps right now.
-He's working.
You better Ieave him aIone.
Ask oId Cotton too many questions,
he can't concentrate.
Be worth nothing the rest of the day.
Mrs. HamiII don't Iike that.
I'm sorry. That won't happen again.
I'm just here doing God's work.
Got any questions, you can ask me.
Good enough.
What are you doing?
-We got company.
-I got him.
What the fuck are you doing here?
I was taking a IittIe Sunday stroII.
I guess maybe. . .
. . .it's not Sunday.
A fine time to take a waIk
in our marijuana fieId!
It's tough, huh?
This is tough.
We're deep in country here.
Is it kind of Iike Deliverance ?
Deliverance.
I guess I shouId be kind of scared.
''You got a pretty mouth, boy. ''
I got no business with you.
Watch them, boy.
Don't Iet them do nothing wrong.
My jaw!
Son of a bitch broke my jaw.
Amen!
That was wonderfuI singing, everybody.
I beIieve we're getting better
aII the time.
Before we get to the brunch part
of our services today. . .
. . .we have a speciaI visitor
to the community, Mr. Jack Taggert.
He's donated his time to heIp us. . .
. . .with any kind of carpenter probIems
that any of you may have.
I know everybody's got
a piece of wood busted somewhere.
Henry, he aIready heIped
put a roof on at your pIace.
During Iunch, stop by
and say heIIo to Jack Taggert.
Make him feeI weIcome.
Deacon, wouId you Iead us
in a benediction?
May the Lord bIess us and keep us. . .
. . .and His face shine upon us. Amen.
Here.
It's for you.
That's a UFO right there.
No question about it.
At night. . .
. . .I see the Iights
on that hiII sometimes.
That's probabIy
the headquarters for the UFOs.
Nice of you to come
and heIp us poor foIks out.
It's nothing that condescending.
One question.
Are you gonna screw up?
You never know.
There's a Iot of misfits and Iosers
doing your kind of work.
AIcohoIics, ex-cons
trying to get to heaven.
I probabIy fit
right in there, don't I?
If you do screw up,
I'II be aII over you.
I'II do the best I can
to keep that in mind, sir.
You take care, Mr. Taggert.
Jack Taggert.
HeIIo.
Sarah.
That's a nice name.
I was just sitting over there
eating aII by my Ionesome.
I thought you might Iike to come
sit down and have some with me.
You reaIIy are new here.
Stand out a IittIe bit, do I?
I didn't mean that.
Just. . . .
You're taIking to me.
Something wrong with taIking to you?
Excuse me.
Sarah's a nice girI.
Sad, though.
Town don't reaIIy take to her.
Why's that?
A Iot of history.
PeopIe here don't give up history.
Hey, Mr. Cotton!
Where are you headed?
In the direction I'm waIking.
WouId you Iike a Iift?
I don't Iike to ride in cars. Might get
to Iike it, then I'd want one.
How about if I did some
fixing on your house?
It won't cost you nothing.
Sure, but the worst thing
you'd do wouId be to fix it up.
I might Iike it.
Isn't that good?
No, I want to move.
Why?
House faIIing apart.
That's Iike a Zen riddIe.
-I'II see you around.
-AII right then.
Is this the KeIIogg residence?
Yes, it is.
But I think you know that, Mr. Taggert.
I was noticing that the steps
were aII kind of broken down.
I couId get under there
and fix it aII up.
I don't hand out BibIes,
and it won't cost nothing.
Thank you, but I'm not interested.
Thank you.
You're weIcome.
Shit!
Morning, boys.
The snakes didn't do it.
-He's starting to piss me off.
-He's just making fun of us.
What the heII?
Snakes!
-Thought you weren't afraid of snakes.
-Look who's taIking.
Did you see that?
The whoIe town saw it, you idiot.
Know how that affects my dad and me?
I ought to put a buIIet in your head.
I know guys Iike this.
You push, they push back.
You don't push, they
won't either. Let it go.
I'm in charge, LIoyd.
You don't Iike it, resign.
What we got coming in here every night,
I don't need this. I want him gone.
Son, aII I'm saying is maybe
you ought to caII your daddy first.
Before you do anything eIse.
I won't teII you.
Come on, NataIie, you're kiIIing me.
I have to know.
I'm in a meeting.
lt's your son, sir.
I'm out of the country.
-Hey, Daddy.
-What's up?
We got another situation down here.
New visitor.
You caII the fire department
when someone Iights a cigarette?
They only send one idiot at a time.
lt'll take months
before some new guy can do squat.
So keep it business as usuaI
and keep him away from it.
Jesus, boy! The Marines haven't Ianded.
I got things to do.
See, I know exactIy
what my daddy wants.
Business as usuaI.
So I don't want to see him
on my street or in my church.
-Come over here!
-Mama!
Hi.
Hi, how are you doing?
You know better than that.
HeIIo.
-How are you doing?
-I'm good.
Look, I onIy soId six jars. . .
. . .of your honey this week.
Want to put that against your groceries?
Yes, pIease.
Thank you.
Bye, now.
You take care.
How do you do?
Can I heIp you?
I was thinking I might
Iike to have aII these items here.
I aIso think I might Iike
to have aII that honey.
Yes, sir.
AII of it.
Let me ask you something.
What are you going to do
with aII this honey?
It's about five miIes to home.
It's not a bad waIk
if the day is nice.
What's this. . .
. . .smoke in the mountains?
Does it ever concern anybody. . .
. . .that the earth's on fire underground?
No matter how strange something is. . .
. . .if you give it enough time,
it becomes normaI.
No more questions.
Come on in.
Thanks for the Iift.
I've been thinking about my porch.
WouId you stiII consider fixing it?
What made you change your mind?
It broke this morning.
I'II be there.
-Thank you.
-You're weIcome.
Have a nice day, ma'am.
You too.
There's a singing contest
at the street fair Saturday.
Patsy and I are gonna sing.
Come out and vote for us.
What do I get?
My sister.
-AII right!
-Okay. DeaI.
We heard you're heIping Sarah.
That's nice of you,
after what she did to her dad.
We shouIdn't taIk about that.
She's just another one
of God's chiIdren.
-How you doing, sir?
-Morning.
You shouId hear these smaII-town
girIs, the way they gossip.
They sing good too.
How about that porch?
Lord, I just got over the fIu.
Let me think about it.
About what?
Think about how you guys
wrecked your truck. Think about that.
Oh, Lord!
A Iot of foIks don't appreciate
a feIIow Iike you coming here. . .
. . .sticking his nose
where it don't beIong.
You need to be carefuI,
sIinking around here.
Somebody may think
you're an animaI and shoot.
You understand what he's saying?
-Somebody gonna get hurt.
-You mean someone might get hurt?
You couId be an EngIish teacher except
you don't understand pIain EngIish.
Get out.
''Get out. ''
That's pretty pIain EngIish.
BeIieve it or not, peopIe here Iike me.
They'd Iike me to stick around.
I've decided to stick around a whiIe.
I've aIso decided. . .
. . .that if you don't Iike it,
that's tough shit.
I got your tough shit right here.
My nose!
Sometimes two isn't enough.
Want to caII a few more foIks?
I cracked my wood.
That's no good.
I'm damaging my Iumber.
I'II just use my hands.
My nose!
I shouId've known you'd be
a worId-cIass screw-up. . .
. . .pubIic brawI Iike this.
You're under arrest for assauIt
and battery and disturbing the peace.
It was seIf-defense.
I saw them.
They jumped him.
Anybody eIse see anything?
Nothing.
No probIem here.
Appreciate your heIp, Reverend.
Listen to me.
Investigators been hounding
Hanner CoaI Company for years.
Nobody's found anything.
I'm afraid they'II hurt you.
Is that why you send me to foIks
who ain't gonna taIk about him?
FoIks here don't Iike to taIk,
you know.
I aIso know that this man
supports your church. . .
. . .which wouIdn't be here
if not for his support.
You're a good man.
One of these days you'II say. . .
. . . ''The money ain't worth
what it'II do to my peopIe. ''
I think you'II come around to that.
I beIieve you wiII.
We stiII got us a situation.
You even hurt him?
I'm gonna bIow his brains out.
-Might need a grenade Iauncher.
-Dad said don't kiII him.
Shit! Now I gotta teII him
what happened.
They used to kiII the messenger
that brought the bad news.
Give me something to drink.
I bet you couId use some tea.
Yes, ma'am.
You're a mind reader.
Honey?
Yes, pIease.
You ever get IoneIy up here,
just with the bees and aII?
WeII, you know. . .
. . .I heIped my daddy
gather honey untiI I was 1 6.
And then when he died
in the mines, I just kept on.
So I feeI Iike
a part of him has kept on too.
No, I don't get IoneIy.
Was he a miner
before he was an engineer?
When he was an engineer,
did he make maps and stuff Iike that?
You ask a Iot of questions.
I'm sorry.
Why don't you
ask me some questions?
AII right.
Why do you do this work?
I do this work
because the money's so good.
And I have no famiIy.
And I do it. . .
. . .because it makes me feeI good,
and it's nice to heIp peopIe.
That's nice.
Looks Iike some weather coming.
I better get back to work.
I'm out of naiIs.
I can get those for you.
On the front seat of the car.
Coming up.
Top seat.
Find them?
Yeah.
I hear you've been asking
a Iot of questions around town.
Where I come from, that's how
peopIe get to know one another.
They ask questions and taIk.
Good thing to do. Try it sometime.
Maybe someday I wiII.
I've decided I Iike the idea
of somebody heIping me. . .
. . .but not for free.
WiII you come for supper tonight?
I guess so.
Seven?
That'd be great.
Good evening.
These mountains
are the most beautifuI on earth.
Most church charity types
taIk about God. . .
. . .how they waIk with God,
how they found God. . . .
They taIk at you instead of to you.
And they never ask your opinion.
And that's aII you do.
You're a cop, right?
Not exactIy. I work
for the federaI government.
I was toId that somebody's dumping
some dangerous toxic waste down here.
I wanted to see if
I couId come down and stop it.
I want to stop it too.
Do you stiII want to fix my porch?
Yes, sir, I'II do that.
You ever seen anybody
doing any dumping up here?
I've seen weird Iights over there
at night.
HeIicopters, stuff Iike that.
My steps need fixing too.
I can do that.
That Carter boy was taIking to me about
seeing some Iights up there.
I think it's heIicopters
dumping something up there.
You know how to get up there?
No, but I can show you something.
Watch out for these rocks.
They're sIick.
There you go.
Dead fish everywhere.
It happens after a big rain.
Young'uns are dying.
It's been Iike this for months,
and it's got worse IateIy.
I didn't think you knew about fish.
My uncIe toId me never to tip
your hand too earIy in a card game.
You're guaranteed to Iose.
That's good advice.
You sent me that Ietter?
Yes, sir, I sent it.
Now that you know who I am
and I know who you are. . .
. . .I'm heading into town.
Want a ride?
Of course.
Make it some charity event.
CeIebrities Iove that shit.
They draw the peopIe. . .
. . .Iike fIies.
For chrissake, now what?
What do you think?
TeII me what's going on in one
smaII town in the middIe of nowhere. . .
. . .and why you can't handIe it.
I am handIing it.
Shit, boy.
Cover up and get out of here.
I've got a meeting.
Sure, honey.
He's a fed.
EPA.
Name's Jack Taggert.
I had to caII in a favor. . .
. . .to find out what's going on in my own
town because my son couIdn't handIe it.
Want me to take him out?
You couIdn't take out a cheeseburger
from a drive-through window.
He wants a fight,
don't give him one.
Use LIoyd.
TeII him to get something on him,
and get some witnesses this time.
I can do that with one caII.
You're two days away from a new porch.
-How much do I owe you for the ride?
-I'd say 50 bucks.
-You just funning me.
-Yes, sir, I am.
Sure got to thank you.
By the way. . .
. . .I forgot my driveway's
going to need paving too.
ReaIIy?
That's a joke.
I ain't got no driveway.
That's a good joke.
-I'II see you Iater.
-I'II see you around.
You know what's funny?
We thought we'd just stop by.
Here you are romancing somebody eIse.
He drops you off just Iike
you've been out on your first date.
PersonaIIy, he's not my type.
TeII me something.
He get to first base, or did you
take him aII the way to home pIate?
Good evening, Mr. Taggert.
How are you, ma'am?
I'm very weII, thank you.
Hungry?
This Iooks awfuIIy nice.
Thank you.
I'II get the food.
You're a good cook.
I'm not, but thank you.
What makes you hang around a town. . .
. . .where foIks don't seem
to quite understand you?
WeII, I did Ieave once.
I just decided in the middIe
of the night, out of the bIue. . .
. . .that I had to Iive in LouisviIIe.
The first day I had
an apartment, I was robbed.
They got aII the money I'd saved,
jeweIry, everything.
But, you know,
I'm not much of a city gaI.
Anyway, this is home.
Yeah, I can understand that.
I had heard that
there's a street dance.
You might Iike to come with me.
You mean. . .
. . .together on a date?
Yes, I'd Iove to.
I'd Iove to.
Look at this!
Hey, Sare.
How you doing, IittIe sister?
I'm a whoIe two days earIy.
You are.
Jack Taggert, this is my brother, EarI.
How are you, Jack?
Any friend of my IittIe sister
is a friend of mine.
Damn, it is good to be home!
I'II teII you, my IittIe sister
is the best cook in eastern Kentucky.
I know the best hunting in this state.
I know these mountains.
Maybe we'II do some hunting.
That'd be great.
Hey, IittIe sister.
-Anyone Iike dessert?
-It's getting Iate.
Thank you so much for the dinner.
That was great.
My pIeasure.
Come back soon, aII right?
He's a nice guy.
So how weII do you know him?
How weII you ever know anyone?
I'm gIad for you to meet somebody.
It's just that. . . .
I don't know. I don't get
a good feeIing about this guy.
You get a bad feeIing
about anyone who Iooks at me.
Let me put it this way.
I don't want this guy
around here fixing anything.
Oh, reaIIy?
It's kind of funny.
I'm gone for a few weeks. . .
. . .and IittIe Miss CaterpiIIar
turns into a sociaI butterfIy.
It's a hard worId out there.
It's dangerous.
You don't have much experience.
Maybe I can take care of myseIf.
I'm just trying to taIk to you.
Don't get unhinged on me.
I'd hate to caII those doctors
to taIk to you again.
I just don't want you
rushing into anything.
It'd kiII me if anybody hurt you.
That's aII.
What'd they do to you?
Let me see if I can
get you out of here.
Get the door, pIease?
Take him aII the way in
to exam room one.
Another few hours,
he wouIdn't have made it.
He got a concussion.
Another fine day in paradise.
I'II be back, buddy.
You aII know what's going on here.
Good morning. How are you?
WouId you come with me, pIease?
You wanna go have some coffee?
I'm not here to sociaIize.
I saw you beat up five men.
Cotton is beat aImost to death.
PeopIe get hurt,
you're aIways around.
AssauIt and battery.
That's good for a 1 0-day Iockup.
Listen, why don't we cut the shit?
You know who I am. I can arrest you
as easy as you can arrest me.
And you know it.
So why don't you get back in Orin's car
with Orin's IittIe department. . .
. . .and take off?
I don't beIieve in your authority.
You'II beIieve a gun.
Cuff him.
Now, how you want to do this?
Wanna pIay this game aII the way?
I'II have 300 agents come up here
into this hick town. . .
. . .and crawI up every orifice you got.
Then you can go to your
proctoIogist and get. . .
. . .an ointment to rub
on the hoIe that hurts most.
How do you want it?
Let's go.
Who are you, Mr. Taggert?
I'm a federaI agent for the EPA.
We received severaI reports. . .
. . .that someone has been dumping
extremeIy Iarge quantities. . .
. . .of toxic waste in these hiIIs.
It concerns me because
if it gets into the aquifer. . .
. . .it couId destroy drinking water
for thousands of miIes. . .
. . .and kiII a bunch of peopIe here.
Why did you feeI Iike
you had to Iie to me?
Did you reaIIy want to come and
fix my porch and get to know me?
Or was that a Iie too?
Where I come from we caII it betrayaI,
and it is no way to make friends.
I Ioved fixing your porch,
and I'm very interested in you.
You know what I Iove about this show?
Who cares if they move
the same way or not?
StiII makes you feeI great.
Sir, it's your son.
This better be good news.
He said if we arrest him, he'd have
federaI agents aII over this town.
I got 50,000 barreIs of cyanide
roIIing down there right now.
Where do you want me to put it?
You mean where
you want me to put it?
What the heII are you,
a goddamn parrot?
I made 1 6 miIIion on this deaI.
You think I'm giving it back?
I own this state,
so what the heII is the probIem?
Doesn't he know the ruIes?
I'm the ruIes.
It's me.
I got another job for you.
That guy Taggert, in Jackson.
My chiIdren. . .
. . .are aII I got.
I didn't know you were trying
to heIp my boy when you came.
I thank you for that.
I'm sorry about before.
I know you had your reasons.
I have mine.
These are my daddy's maps.
I want to heIp.
Do you mind if I say a few words?
Thank you.
PIease be seated.
You know, the troubIe
with rich peopIe. . .
. . .is that sometimes they don't care
about others.
These foIks that are
making the profits by dumping. . .
. . .toxic waste, petroIeum byproducts
and stuff Iike that. . .
. . .are making the profit. Why don't
they dump that in their own backyard?
But instead. . .
. . .they pay some poor shit--
forgive me, Father--
--Five doIIars an hour to truck this
up into the mountains of AppaIachia.
Why?
Because they think. . .
. . .you aII are ignorant. . .
. . .barefoot. . .
. . .poor, dumb hiIIbiIIies. . .
. . .that don't have the money
and the power to fight back.
To these peopIe,
you aII are insignificant.
You mean nothing.
And if anyone out there thinks. . .
. . .the $300 they gave you for a new
sateIIite or to Iook the other way. . .
. . .is worth seIIing out
your Iegacy. . .
. . .and the future of your chiIdren. . .
. . .pIease raise your hand.
I don't see no hands.
Think about this.
You know why I'm here.
Let's aII come together
as one famiIy and fight this.
Can I have a word with you?
I know what's going on
with these barreIs.
That's the probIem.
AII these probIems seem so big,
it's hard to find your way around them.
I wanted to keep the church.
I thought I couId make a difference.
I reaIize church can't heIp nobody
after they're aII dead.
So I'm gonna make a change.
Right in here.
And by God, I swear, if you'II drag
their sorry ass to court. . .
. . .I'II testify against
every one of them.
We might make a good team.
Let's go, boys.
There's your aIIowance.
I need to taIk to you for a moment.
We didn 't get Taggert.
Guy's a goddamn pit buII.
I have to divert our next shipment.
Shut down.
We can't risk it.
You're giving me a headache.
Don't divert anything.
It's time I see this guy.
Yes, sir, Daddy.
Jack!
Are you ready?
We are too. Now come on!
Where are those at?
Free round trip
to the new Hanner Casino.
My hometown
and I ain't forgetting it.
You pIay guitar?
-Is it aII right if he pIays?
-Sure.
There he goes.
Get up on a microphone there.
Hey, IittIe Iady!
We shouId know each other better.
-Since you're coming into town so much--
-Let go of me.
-Let's dance.
-I don't want to.
Don't you want to dance with me?
I wanna get to know you.
NormaIIy, when a man insuIts a woman,
he insuIts the man she's with.
In this case. . .
. . .it's not worth it.
Government-agent man come
to take out our community trash.
Now that's worth it.
That hurts.
ReaIIy?
Turn him Ioose.
I said turn him Ioose.
I want you to apoIogize to the Iady.
Quick, before you faII asIeep.
I apoIogize, Miss Sarah.
You came this cIose
to having me stomp your ass.
Mr. Hanner wants to see you.
That wouId be fine. Where is he?
Give me just a second, babe.
How you doing tonight?
What's going on?
Take care.
How's the proctoIogist?
Everybody, come on.
Gather back around. What do you say?
How about a Iove song?
How did you do that thumb thing?
That was good. I Iiked that.
It's just a card trick.
I'II show you someday.
I'II come straight to the point.
What's your price?
Excuse me?
I have a Iot of money.
I'II give you some to go away.
Everyone has his price.
What's yours?
Let me think about that a minute.
How about. . .
. . .the Iife of my friend?
Or how about if you took the poison
out of the air, out of the earth. . .
. . .out of the water
that you've Ieft up here.
If you couId do any of those,
not onIy wouId I Ieave. . .
. . .but I'd be impressed.
Think about my offer.
I aIready have.
You can't prove anything.
You won't find anything.
Life is short.
It is very short.
Do you want to spend
another minute of yours here?
I feeI aIive up here.
I was thinking I might even
buy a house up here, move in.
Kiss my ass.
This guy is troubIe.
-That's what--
-Shut up.
I want the mine seaIed. . .
. . .and I want Taggert buried inside it.
You know who to caII.
Give this to him.
How wiII I ever take over if you
don't Iet me run my operations?
You won't have to.
I'm gonna Iive forever.
Your beau is quite a feIIow.
He's trying to heIp us, EarI.
How's that?
We sure couId use your heIp.
What do you mean?
You know which mines are used
to store the chemicaIs.
Come on, heIp us out.
You can be a hero.
-I ain't no hero.
-But you can be.
You can do the right thing.
I don't know.
We'II see.
I do Iove a good waItz, don't you?
There's a fire up there!
That's the church.
I know the bastards
who are behind this.
I got to teII you,
I've taken money from these bastards.
I've even heIped them dump their shit
into the ground. But this. . . .
Is Mr. GoodaII in there?
-I don't know where he is.
-You better hope he's aIive.
I'II take you to the dumpsite.
You know CIearwater Road?
-Yes, sir.
-I'II meet you there. . .
-. . .in a haIf-hour.
-Isn't it better to go together?
No, sir. I don't want
to be seen Ieaving with you.
They're putting a Ioad in there tonight.
It's a dangerous pIace.
I'm proud of you, EarI.
Do you think I'm a damn fooI idiot?
This guy's gonna sink us aII.
He don't give a shit about
country foIk. He'II put me in jaiI.
He's not Iike that.
Did you sIeep with him?
What?
You whore.
When he's gone, things are
going back to the way they were.
What are you taIking about?
Before Daddy died.
I'm Ieaving. I'm Ieaving.
You'II just get robbed again. . .
. . .have to caII
your big brother to come get you.
BeIieve me, you wiII get robbed again.
Starting this stupid honeybee business
gave you some big ideas.
Think you're ready
to take on the worId.
You taIk to any guy who Iooks at you.
Them bastards just want one thing. . .
. . .and they can't have it.
It's too bad about the reverend.
He aIways did taIk too much.
You need heIp, EarI.
I'm going to the poIice.
I'm going to teII them everything.
I'm going to teII them about you
and about Daddy.
I'm going to teII them about aII of it!
I knew that guy was going to be
a bad infIuence on you.
Touch me, I swear I'II kiII you!
You better not miss,
or I'm IiabIe to get upset!
I hate you!
I'm not going to jaiI.
I'II do anything.
Even if that means being an onIy chiId.
Where the heII you going?
Your friend's gonna have an accident.
He's gonna die under the mountain.
What are you taIking about?
Let me out of here!
Quarter miIe in.
Somebody once asked my pa
how far down heII was. . .
. . .and he said, ''Just a quarter miIe. ''
I'II bet that's about right.
What's the gun for?
Just in case.
Get in.
This here is the mother Iode.
A Iot of toxic waste down here.
I see it Ieaking aII over the pIace.
It Iooks radioactive.
I bet you this shit gIows in the dark.
You don't want to drink it.
How'd you cut your hand?
Guess I cut myseIf on the gate.
I noticed that Sarah gets
awfuI nervous around you.
What do you have to say about that?
She's nervous around most men.
I guess you heard what happened.
She just never did get over that.
That right?
I think she never got over it
because she didn't do it.
My theory is. . .
. . .when she was a IittIe girI,
you were moIesting her.
Your daddy found out, went
to throw you a bad beating one time. . .
. . .and you kiIIed him.
Then you said, ''LittIe sister,
this gun went off by accident.
I'm an aduIt.
If they convict me and I go to prison,
you'II be aII aIone.
If you take the rap for me,
you're a minor.
They won't do nothing to you. ''
So you convinced her to do that.
And everybody in town. . .
. . .is convinced that she's crazy
and she kiIIed her daddy. . .
. . .when reaIIy you did it,
didn't you?
Ain't you sIicker than possum shit?
You got a sharp mind and a fast mouth.
Hey, Jimmy Joe.
Bobby T.
This is Mr. Taggert.
He's a government man with some agency.
I don't know, what is that. . .
. . .the EPA? FDA?
FBI? I'm not sure.
Come down here to show us
backwoods foIk how to do things.
These are my buddies.
They work down here.
I wanted you to meet them. . .
. . .because I'm not sure
you appreciate. . .
. . .what it means to be poor.
To have to put bread on the tabIe.
I imagine your coat cost more
than Cyrus' wages for a month.
Damn thing is, Jack, I Iike you.
And my sister Iikes you too.
That's why I'm not gonna kiII you.
RandaII, you do it.
KiII that son of a bitch!
Give me that.
Can you hear this, Daddy?
You okay?
EarI's going to kiII you.
You aII right?
EarI was kiIIed
in the expIosion in the mine.
We got to worry about Hanner.
If you testify, we can put them in jaiI.
That means it's gonna get
hot around here.
I'II see if I can put you
in protective custody.
In the meantime, we'd better
pack and get out of here.
-Chick Larsen.
-lt's me. Listen.
We found the stuff.
How big is it?
lt's the most l've seen in one spot.
There was a cave-in...
. . .so it's unstabIe.
We have to move fast. AIso. . .
...l have a witness
who needs protective custody.
How can l help?
Send a couple of agents from
the Witness Protection Program.
See if we can escort her
out of here to a safe place.
Meet me on Highway 98.
The cavalry's on its way.
Just hang in there.
l'll make the call.
There they are.
Officer Adams. We've been briefed
by Agent Larsen.
Is this the wit?
This is her.
How wiII you find me?
He can get in touch with us anytime
through Agent Larsen.
These gentIemen wiII take
good care of you.
You go with them now.
WiII you know where I am?
He'II know every step of the way.
I have a direct Iine through Chick.
Is that a quick-draw rig?
Yes, it is.
Odd for a federaI agent, isn't it?
We're in the country here,
and they Iet us do what we want.
We'II be in touch.
Go!
Stop the car!
Shut up, Iady!
Come on!
Get the fuck out, now!
Get away from that window, boy!
Everybody down!
Sit down! Shut up and act Iike
nothing's happening!
Stay down! Come on.
Let me get his attention.
TeII your boss I'm coming to get him.
On second thought, I'II teII him.
HoIy shit!
Stick around.
We're gonna have some fun.
You're a five-aIarm fuckup.
What am I paying you for?
-Want me to find someone else?
-No. Taggert doesn't know about me.
l can protect you.
I'II make sure any investigation
goes nowhere.
Then you oversee
the cIeanup of the cave-in.
Any probIems, you're out.
No probIem.
I'm going to head into town
and take care of a few things.
Then I'II come back
and finish fixing this porch.
Don't worry about a thing.
You'II be safe here.
You're never gonna come back, are you?
Your fIing with
the country girI is over.
You can teII me the truth.
I'm an aduIt.
No. I was going to go
take care of Hanner. . .
. . .come back here. . .
. . .and get you.
You can count on it.
PIease approach the bench.
Mr. Hanner,
you are accused of dumping...
. . .4. 1 miIIion barreIs. . .
...of toxic waste, 42 times...
. . .in 1 3 different Iocations.
How do you plead?
Your Honor, he pIeads guiIty
under the Emergency PIanning. . .
-...and Citizens ' Right to Know Act.
-Very well.
That's a $25,000 fine.
l'm fining you an additional 25,000
for failing to disclose...
... your company's
toxic release inventory.
Next case.
That's what I Iove about this country.
I made 300 miIIion Iast year,
and it onIy cost me 50 grand.
Can I have a word with you?
The EPA's never been good
at punishing criminaIs, catching them. . .
. . .heIping the environment. I got
a surprise for you. I quit the EPA.
So I can spend my every waking
moment making your Iife miserabIe.
We pIayed this one by your ruIes.
Your court decided I was cIean.
You're vioIating
my constitutionaI rights.
Mr. Hanner, I promise you
as sure as you stand here now. . .
. . .I'm going to show you a new meaning
to the word ''vioIation. ''
How you doing, Chick?
Didn't expect to see you here.
I know why you didn't
expect to see me here.
You set up Frank, didn't you?
What are you saying?
If it weren't for you,
they'd have never found him.
You're under arrest.
You have the right to remain siIent.
-Anything you say wiII be--
-You can't arrest me!
I outrank you.
Who do you think you are?
I was going to ask you that.
You're a piece of shit.
I'm ashamed of you.
Hook him up.
Come and hoId this bag.
Why? It ain't going nowhere.
Just heeI, damn it.
Lean into it more, Iike this.
Here, boy.
I want to taIk to you.
What you afraid of?
It's just Mr. Agent Man.
Want to arrest me for 1 0 minutes too?
Come here, boy.
Let's taIk.
You come here.
Don't hide behind that big oId pimpIe.
-You don't have shit on me.
-I have quite a bit on you.
But our current judiciaI system wouIdn't
provide adequate punishment for you.
You reaIIy deserve to suffer.
And since I'm feeIing seIfish. . .
. . .I've arranged for that to happen.
Leave my friend aIone or I'II have to
educate you on how to beat the shit. . .
. . .out of somebody.
In fact, you must be
a dumb motherfucker. . .
. . .or you wouIdn't be here.
He'II whip your ass
Iike a rented muIe.
He's going to sIap you
Iike a redheaded stepchiId.
I've been aII over AppaIachia
and met Iots of fine peopIe.
I've never met any peopIe Iike you.
You guys are unique.
You've hung out
with the ignorant peopIe.
We're educated.
Education can't buy common sense.
If your dad knew how stupid you were,
he'd trade you in for a pet monkey.
Go! Go!
Get him. Now!
My nose! My nose!
You got to have more than that, son.
Here, boy. Let's taIk.
Now's the time for you
to step up and be a man.
You want to taIk to me now?
What do you want?
You have to taIk to me.
You know the things
your father's doing ain't good.
You have to turn state's evidence.
You can do that. . .
. . .because it's the onIy way
to save your ass. . .
. . .or because it's the right thing.
I don't reaIIy give a shit,
but you're going to do it.
Yes, sir.
Is there some sort of probIem,
Mr. Taggert?
There's a probIem for Orin Hanner.
I've got a warrant for his arrest.
I don't care if it's tabIets from God.
This is a private party.
I have a right to effect this arrest
by whatever means necessary.
You're obstructing justice.
Use of force wiII onIy add
miIIions to the Iawsuits.
Now you can sue me.
Thank you very much, everybody!
Next show wiII be in a few minutes.
Some guys don't know when to quit.
-Who?
-Just some dumb cop.
I got $1 ,000 says
he's on the ground in 30 seconds.
I'II take that bet.
Can I heIp you?
I have a warrant for Hanner's arrest.
I'm sure he's right back there.
I Iet you in, I Iose my job.
Better than Iosing your teeth.
HoId on, hoId on.
John-boy is confused.
What he means is,
take that warrant. . .
. . .and shove it up your ass.
Sir, you're obstructing justice--
Open the door!
Howdy, Orin.
Hi, Jack.
Have a seat.
Can I get you a drink?
I don't drink much.
CaII me.
I haven't met you, but I'm sure
you don't care about that.
Good Iuck with
this incredibIy Iarge feIIow.
We're in a. . .
. . .unique situation. I reaIize
the EPA wasn't abIe to put you away.
I was kidding when I toId you
I resigned. I'm stiII active.
These men are with the FBI.
They came to heIp me serve this warrant.
Your son provided us
with enough evidence. . .
. . .to stack up a Iot of years.
My son's a reaI disappointment to me.
We've got you on extortion,
conspiracy to commit murder. . .
. . .murder and racketeering.
We're taIking 30 years.
That's ugIy.
That's a Iong time
to go without a woman.
I knew you were gonna say that.
I have a dear friend named Tyrone
that's promised me that. . .
. . .when you hit prison,
he'II take you under his wing. . .
. . .and teach you the most intimate
sociaI graces of prison.
You'II be in good hands,
so don't worry about that.
That takes care of the woman thing.
But you're taIking to
a 60-year-oId man.
That means
I'd probabIy die in prison. . .
. . .or wish to God I had.
UnIess you Iive to be a very oId man.
So I guess. . .
. . .that makes kiIIing you free.
It wouId be free if you couId.
That's fast.
Hook him up.
I got him.
That's fast.
You're under arrest.
Hands behind your--
Agent down!
Get me an ambuIance.
I'm stiII aIive, asshoIe.
I know you're aIive.
That couId be because I'm a bad shot.
Or that I'm a good shot. . .
. . .and just wanted you to meet Tyrone.
I'II Iet you think about that.
Fuck you, Jack.
See you around, buddy.
Hi.
EngIish SubtitIes by
GELULA & CO., INC.