You have anything to drink?
Are you drinking there?
Doctor!
-Cover his head anyway.
-Do as he says.
And what is this?
Get back down there.
We knew him.
-Get back... inside, both of you.
-I'd like to stay.
If they notice we're up here, you'll
wish you were him if you don't already.
We don't need the doctor.
Go! We don't need you.
He's dead.
I said he's dead.
He's alive.
If he's alive,
I'm treating him.
Did anybody tell you
to get him?
I didn't need to be told.
Did anyone say
"Go for the doctor"?
There's no point in arguing.
You see.
Done.
What?
Do it.
No! Please, no!
Easy, now. Easy.
What he wanted, that's all.
Don't come for me anymore.
Ask me for nothing.
That's easy.
Make sure
they get his number.
Thank you.
Take the pack.
They're Hungarian.
I like our cigarettes.
It's shit tobacco.
I like ours.
What they need to do is invade Turkey
and then you'll taste a cigarette.
Get going.
You trust the Poles?
What do I care?
The Poles.
They don't trust the Poles.
They don't trust anyone in Number3.
Me?
I can't say.
I'm Hungarian.
But you're here.
So because I'm
with the Poles?
Rosenthal's worried. He's gonna say
that we don't have the time.
I know, we don't have time.
They wait for lulls.
-If the front...
-That's not gonna happen for us.
-No one really knows that...
-Never.
There's planes almost
every day now.
Not for us.
The Russians get 10 km from here we're
the first to go right out to the pyres.
Everyone keeps saying that.
Believe it.
You're dead already, either way.
It's just a matter
of deciding how.
You have gold?
Of course. So I say?
Tell him it's not happening
is what you say.
Get back and tell them.
Go!
Move it out!
It's all a way of putting it off.
Do you need to be here?
Every day counts.
They've been on just as long
as we have. They could go before us.
-I don't understand him.
-He doesn't decide.
He goes along. As far as
I'm concerned... he's no different.
They'd heard
about the old man.
-Who?
-Abramowics.
-What'd he say?
-That... he'd heard.
-Have you told anyone?
-Everyone knows.
The Doctor had no business
there. A man takes pills.
Why are you two in here?
We're nearly finished.
Nearly?
Inside. Yes, nearly.
-But not completely.
-I suppose not.
So I ask the question again.
Three of our men
were shot this morning.
What business is it
of yours?
We're gonna need replacements
and Hungarians.
That's not your problem.
You say we're lazy or disrespectful, but
don't leave us the manpower for the work.
Moll shot Lowenthal,
one of our strongest men.
-You want things to go fast?
-If it's my neck.
We're going to be moving...
Why do you want to do that?
We're thinking of a reprieve.
Our group is happy
to remain here.
Happy?
Why kill us now? We're
the best kommando you've had.
Did I say kill?
We both know
what we're saying.
So I'm a liar.
You're what you are.
It's not my decision.
Of course it's your decision.
No one is
to leave their areas.
You're telling me it's not
you're decision?
No one is to leave
their areas.
-The Doctor leaves.
-The Doctor is different.
There've been people
in the zones.
We haven't been.
We know what we see.
You're to keep with your units.
Each to each building.
-The bribes are taken.
-Nevertheless.
But we're going
to need replacements.
Get back inside!
Or I'll be replacing you.
We missed you this morning.
Missed me?
-The data are on your desk.
-Good.
We've arranged for more forms.
You should have said.
-I'm sorry we had to ask.
-Please.
-What about the lenses?
-They're on the way.
You are an astonishing
pathologist.
Thank you.
-That's not easy for you to hear.
-It isn't.
Something in you knows that our
situation is unique.
And as a scientist, you are
as true a one as I've known.
You understand
that when I'm sure every cell in your
body tells you to do otherwise.
They do.
This isn't our war.
Not mine.
Nor mine, I can assure you.
But to allow this all
to go to waist.
I understand your position.
Clearly, you do more than that.
As you wish.
Meaning?
There is no meaning.
We're going to be increasing
the volume of our research.
I shall need more staff.
Then you shall have more staff.
Yes?
-Pardon?
-You want to say...
-It's...
-Yes?
We had discussed last time.
Of course.
This gets you anywhere
in the camp.
-You wait until now?
-Me?
-This is too wrapped up.
-I got it that way.
-From whom?
-I never saw her face.
Where's Tsipora?
Where is she?
And?
And that's all I know.
I'd never seen her before.
-But they have her.
-I said that's all I know.
There's no way they don't.
I know Tsipora. They won't get
a thing out of her.
It doesn't matter.
The point is keep going.
They'll find us like they found her
and until then we get in.
It's hard to guarantee
how much we'll get anymore.
This is a chain.
You find another link.
I just said we did.
We found a stupid link.
So what's the trouble?
You don't walk out
of there everyday.
I do plenty more than that.
This isn't a contest.
Then don't make it one.
I'm prepared for anything, Dina.
-And so am l.
-You should be.
So, is there a problem?
If they find us, what do they
do with the rest of our group?
You're risking your own life.
Why should we risk theirs?
You both act
like we put everyone in here.
I don't make you do anything.
Be like them, both of you.
That isn't
what she's saying.
The whole barracks will be punished.
They'll be before they're killed.
Just like us.
What's the fucking difference
when you're dead anyway?
We made the choice,
they haven't.
I'm not listening
to this anymore.
Make sure these get into the cart.
How many bodies are there?
Eight.
You see, that's good.
The more bodies the better.
Get it?
I'll just take these two.
Idiots.
Is she right?
Of course she's right.
What have you been thinking
for the past two months?
I just wish I could slap the shit
out of her is all.
Ist ein problem?
Keine Problem.
I feel sorry for the world
if we don't win the war.
It's your position.
Men are tribal.
We'll end that.
There'll be one tribe.
No war.
There've been wars
within your tribe.
Yes?
Rhoem? The Night
of the Long Knives.
You know a good deal
about Germany.
That, of course,
was a putsch.
What's the difference?
A putsch is not a war.
It's a kind of war.
It's a putsch. If it meant war,
the word would be unnecessary.
Why have two words
for the same thing?
I'm German, you're Hungarian.
I should think I'd be the authority
in this room on the German language.
Of course.
In spite of your obvious
intelligence.
Of course.
There's a rumour around the Number3
Crematorium there'll be a rebellion.
The Number 3?
That would involve the First.
That would involve all 4, originating
with the Poles in Number 3.
What would I know?
They think we're going
to kill them.
Don't you always?
This is the best kommando
we've had.
Alright.
You let them know that.
They don't trust me.
You're their doctor.
I'm their doctor
but they know what I do.
What do they do?
They work under gunpoint.
I won't tell them
what I don't believe.
That we'll let them live?
That you'll let any
of us live.
What happens to you has little
to do with me.
You're treated well.
Better than anyone.
You should let us know.
-They're not going to...
-If you hear anything.
That's all.
Did you ever consider, Herr
Oberschaarfuhere, that these
headaches might be related...
Yes?
...to the increase, lately,
in the level of cargo.
Go on.
What I see in the courtyard, if
I just crack the window for some air.
Anyone would have difficulty.
You shouldn't be looking
out of windows.
-I'm only suggesting...
-Your job is to diagnose.
Alright.
If I get upset, if my head aches,
it's because I drink too much.
Then don't drink so much.
That's right,
I won't drink so much.
But that too should stay
between you and me.
-I would never...
-That's right, you would never.
Because you're just
as disposable as I am.
-Herr...
-I don't care! Shut up!
I don't care.
We're each of us a part of it.
Once any of you decide
to live this way.
And you especially.
Yes, Herr Oberschaarfuhrer.
Once you make that choice.
About half are in.
Yes?
Max, you'll botch this.
We don't have any choice.
It started with them.
So a bunch of Poles
from Number 3 get to decide.
They get to stall it until it's right
for them, and it's our people.
Who is our people?
On the fucking trains.
-Because they're Hungarian?
-Yes.
That's because Hungary's the only
country with any Jews left.
But that's your reason?
If we were burning Polish
Jews you wouldn't care?
If we were burning Polish Jews
we wouldn't be waiting.
What's another week
to these guys?
Another ten thousand Hungarians?
They don't care about us.
We're all after
the same thing, Max.
It doesn't seem like it.
Here he is.
Sorry.
It was hell getting over.
How is it over there?
They're locking us all in.
-Who said?
-Lopkowitz.
They're getting ready
to liquidate another section.
Which one?
I'd guess one of the Czechs. Better for
them, anyway. They're all starving.
Give me some vodka.
What's this?
Hungarian wine.
We got it in today.
Any gold?
They haven't come back yet.
Look here.
Check out the diamonds.
Lovely.
-I was gonna get it smelted, but...
-But what?
Smelt it.
Fine.
Looks like we got some god food in.
Smoked oysters, meats, a few cakes.
We should do alright tonight.
We hear you got
more machine guns.
-Who told you?
-Hoffman found out.
-Were you gonna tell us?
-Of course.
Doesn't seem like it.
He just said explosives.
No.
Why do you think I came?
Because Hoffman told you
to come.
No. I told Hoffman.
They were left inside the fence by
the partisans. And twenty grenades.
Who has them now?
We do.
So we don't give any more of ours,
you guys are better off now.
When did we ever need
from you?
So what's this business
about waiting?
-We have to re-coordinate.
-Why?
I don't like the way
you talk with me.
You don't like
the way I talk?
I don't like
the way he talks.
Wait, you don't like the way I talk?
It's difficult to understand?
Why are we re-coordinating?
Again.
-We have more guns.
-We had guns.
You think the partisans aren't
wondering why we've done nothing?
You think the women aren't wondering
with the powder they've got in?
-The machine guns.
-So?
What?
Escape.
Wait. Who? Us?
You think you think
we'll escape?
With guns.
So we kill more of them.
Destroy three of the crematorium.
And get out.
Is that what you're after?
If I get the chance,
fuck yes.
You tell them, if this is
about escape, we're out.
How can you speak
for all of us?
You gonna speak for yourself?
Are you serious?
What, you're gonna go back
to your normal life?
Forget that. The point
is it doesn't make any sense.
You live to tell.
You're not going to live.
You won't make it to the Vistula.
Others have made it.
Others from the camp,
not from the kommandos.
They'll give up on someone
from Buna, or the camp,
but not anyone who's been
inside the crematorium.
What we could tell they'll
turn Poland upside down.
If we want to accomplish anything,
it has to be one thing.
One end.
And that's the machinery.
You've got to tell them this.
And there's no time left.
Do they know that?
Kommando 8 lasted
three months and a week.
Not with this kind of cargo.
Even Moll admits...
Moll's not going to tell you.
And with them locking us in,...
Do you hear this?
You don't even speak German.
What the fuck does
that matter?
I speak enough.
And I speak Yiddish.
-You speak Yiddish?
-From the Poles.
You heard from the Poles!
Shut up!
Mussfeld told me they
are getting ready to move us.
No group has lasted more
than four months.
-All he's saying is...
-I know what he's saying.
We could be massacred waiting,
like every other group,
thinking we're different.
Which'll be worse even
than ting to escape.
We can tell them
we can work this out.
But it has
to be the crematorium.
Then they can do whatever they want.
You can run to high heaven.
But after we've done
the buildings.
I'd like a bottle
of that wine.
Give us the necklace.
Oh, c'mon.
It's good wine,
you fucking Yid.
You won't get that smelted and it'll be of
no use. We can get something for it.
-Two bottles.
-Fuck you.
Hoffman, give him two bottles.
Be careful.
They're liars.
What are they gonna lie about?
He wanted to keep the necklace.
He thinks he's going to live.
We're a fucking diversion.
These are Jews.
You keep saying that, Simon.
You trust Jews anymore?
No one would make it?
Suppose even you do.
Do you want to look anyone in the face
if any of your family's even alive?
What you've done
For a little more life.
For vodka and bed linens.
Anja, listen to me,
you're gonna die anyway.
We're dead.
They'll find the powder.
Don't say anything.
No matter what they do.
I love you.
This process of disinfecting is of
vital importance to your health.
One louse can kill you.
Cleanliness brings freedom.
You're all fine.
The quicker you get undressed, the
quicker you'll be cleaned, settled,
and reunited
with your families.
Filthy liar.
Remember the number of the hook
you hang your clothes on.
He's a liar.
I can't believe it's
Jews doing this.
He's lying everyone.
He's a liar.
Stop it.
You should listen
to your wife.
Think what you want to think,
but don't cause trouble.
-I'm causing trouble?
-Please.
Look me in the eye and tell me
I'm not gonna be killed.
Hang your clothes on the hooks and keep
them separate from your neighbours.
I'm gonna die, but I'll have lived
longer than you ever will.
You're dead already.
Be quiet. You think you're
gonna change something?
-That's right, what does it matter?
-At least I'll die with my dignity.
-Morris.
-Stop it!
At least I'll die
with my dignity.
How'd you get through
with herewith that?
What?
The watch, is what.
They'd have killed your whole car.
What does it matter?
See what you've done for yourself
now? Give me the watch.
Why?
Give it to me.
You're bathing.
Why do you need the watch
in there?
Get it from me after
of the Nazis will.
-Do as he says, Morris.
-We always do what everyone says.
I'm not giving you anything.
You're attracting
more attention.
Tell me, tell me I'm gonna live,
you fucking Nazi.
Tell me I'm gonna live.
Morris, give him the watch.
He's a liar, everyone.
These Jews are all Nazi liars.
And now he wants
to steal my watch.
-Give me the watch!
-No.
All I want is the fucking watch!
No!
No! Give him the watch!
Alright, let's keep it moving.
Remember what hooks you hang
your clothes on.
The hooks are numbered. You'll need
to return once you've showered.
Keep your shoes tied together by
their laces so you don't lose them.
The sooner you shower, the sooner
you'll be fed and reunited.
Move it, move it!
Keep moving inside.
Move it!
Move it! Move it!
David.
Stay.
David?
Do you want a drink?
No, thank you.
-You have work.
-Yes.
Always so young.
Adult siblings move away
from one another.
-How's it going?
-Alright.
He'll make twins?
With German women?
That's the goal.
What's this?
A gall stone.
What are you keeping it for?
He takes an interest
in such things.
-He collects them?
-I suppose.
In jars?
That's how I'm giving it to him. What
he does with it after is his business.
So, have you heard anything?
Heard anything?
-I mentioned last time.
-I told you...
Yes?
They don't speak to me.
You found your wife and daughter.
Who told you?
Does it matter?
I don't suppose.
You've been several times.
Brought blankets, medicine.
Yes.
In C-camp, is it?
-He gave you a pass.
-Yes.
What did you think
of it over there?
Think?
Did you tell them
what goes on here?
Of course not.
Do they have any idea?
How couldn't they?
Everyone talks.
-You denied it.
-I did.
It's best.
They're going
to be liquidating C-camp.
Who said?
Cuts in administration.
There's not enough food.
In the next two weeks.
We dispose of food.
The order is the order.
The entire section.
Two weeks?
That's what I said.
I'll speak with...
What does he have to do
with who stays and who goes?
What does he have to do...?
Because he gave you a pass?
I can assure you it
won't be allowed.
It will be easy to save them.
If there is an uprising
in this camp there will be a massacre
that will far outweigh
anything done to us.
These men will suffer.
That's a strange remark.
We let them live.
For a time.
Even if I...
they don't.
Someone will speak.
I want to know you'll help me.
If I'm spoken to.
Whatever you hear.
Yes.
Good.
As for your wife and daughter,
we must go to KZ Administration
and get them transferred.
How?
Find out which are
the safe convoys out.
They're sending some west
to the munitions factory.
Have them volunteer.
They will be chosen.
It's safe?
I'm telling you I will make it safe.
That's what I'll do for you.
They must keep it a secret,
though.
-If everyone volunteers...
-I know.
They save themselves,
that's all.
Just like you.
You and your gall stone.
Your gall stone of a Jew.
How did you get the powder
from the plant?
It doesn't matter how they
got the fucking powder.
What we need to know
is where it's headed.
I'm asking her that.
You think I don't have ears?
You're asking her where it came
from. It came from the plant.
The plant wants to know.
Of course the plant wants
to know.
They should have wondered
that before it happened.
You'll kill this one, too before
she tells us who has it now.
Where was the powder headed?
This is what you want?
You're going to kill me anyway.
You won't be so lucky.
We will do worse to your entire
block, after we're done with you.
Why don't you just gas them?
Revive her.
I got the girl.
You two got a date?
I said take the fucking body.
Why are you up here?
There's a girl...
I said what are you doing
up here?
There's a young girl on that cart
who survived the gas.
She's still breathing.
She'll be burned alive.
We're taking this one.
What do you mean, taking?
I mean taking the body.
Let me get the hair.
I said we're taking her,
hair and all.
If she leaves with hair,
I need to know why.
She's a twin.
What's the trouble?
I need this body
for the Doctor.
So let him get the hair.
What is it with you people?
We're taking now, with the hair.
If she's a twin,
where's the other one?
The other one was caught
before she got on the lift.
And why was she killed?
I thought they were taken alive.
Are you saying I'm lying?
I've kept this unit alive
nine months.
What do I care?
So you're alive.
We're all alive.
We're all shitting gold.
Make your fucking point.
I don't want trouble.
If you want trouble, send me down
to the Doctor with her head shaved.
Take her. What do I care.
Help them.
No, we've got her.
I said we fucking have her.
This will foul everything.
It's blood on our hands.
It's a goddam distraction.
And what do we do with her?
We figure that out.
We'll have to hide her.
And not just from them,
but from some of us, too.
We do not have time
to be dealing with this.
She was inside.
It'll be and she'll never make it.
What are you thinking?
I'm not going to kill her,
alright?
Just think if they found her
in the barracks, which they will,
because you'll never keep her
without it'll be worse.
How can that be worse?
Worse for her.
Forgetting
what they'll do to us.
She's not even conscious. She goes
the way she would have gone.
Meet us at the store room.
I can stop you, Max.
Stop me, then. Do it!
You know we're not killing her.
Where's Schlermer?
Down the corridor.
Where's she?
He won't bring her in until
he talks with the Doctor.
Why? Get him.
Who's gonna watch?
What's to watch?
There's no one in the hall.
He won't let anyone near her.
You'd better get her in here.
Go.
I know what you think.
It's not the same.
He's scared.
We'll put her on this table.
If anyone were to find out...
I know.
We're not murderers.
I know that.
We're sorry.
I hadn't been here long enough.
-I'm talking about...
-I know what you're talking about.
-Of course.
-It doesn't mean I'd act differently.
I've aborted suicides before
and would again.
-I understand.
-Anywhere.
I didn't.
I was summoned.
Not by me.
After midnight like this, to watch
what amounted to a murder.
Something I hardly need
to be woken for in this place.
I'm sorry.
-It's not how we...
-Then don't call for me.
I'm sorry.
-And you exclude me.
-Exclude you?
I don't know why you do that.
He told you?
Yes.
That there's no point.
I can't know
until you bring her in.
If there's no hope,
if she's dead already...
I'm at risk here, too.
I don't give a shit about you.
Bring her in.
Hoffman.
Get some blankets,
some tea, some warm broth.
Here.
Well put it over her.
Not there.
How many of those
will you give her?
She's had twenty minutes of gas.
Put it there.
It's alright.
Some tea.
Stop that! Let me do it.
Spoon.
This is just some tea.
Tea.
Good. Good.
-What was this convoy?
-Hungarian.
-Who found her?
-He did.
Where?
On the bottom.
The young are always
on the bottom.
How was she lying?
Lying?
It's a simple question.
On her side, what?
On her belly.
Can you hear me?
Hello?
You must speak with me.
Hello.
What's your name?
This is gonna take time.
It'll take time.
So simple,
and whom does it harm?
It harms only you.
If you refuse to tell us
what we're going to know anyway,
which is where was
the powder going?
Where was the powder going?
Is this what you want happening
to the people who have the powder,
or to the rest of your block
until we find them?
Where was the powder going?
Don't tell them.
Don't tell them. Don't tell them.
You're not supposed
to be in the zones.
I'm aware of that.
There were two girls caught with
explosives in the Polish section.
You think we're suddenly chummy
with the rest of the camp?
You have another piece
for the way back?
I'll get it there.
You're not supposed
to be in the zones.
You said that.
Give me the other piece.
And have two for the way back.
Or you won't be slapped,
you'll be shot.
No one's gonna harm you here.
We're Jews.
Are you Hungarian?
Yes, she's Hungarian.
The point is simple questions.
Give us some more
of that soup.
We're going to be found here.
He's right.
We're not moving her.
It's been over 2 hours since we started
the lifts. Someone will come right past.
And do we cart her down the hall
without getting through the unit?
The unit doesn't know?
What would that do?
At least get her
off the corridor.
Fine. The changing room.
The changing room?
I said.
Go see if it's clear.
We're gonna move you. Into another
room, you'll be more comfortable.
She's alive, you know.
Where can you keep her?
We can't.
This is a problem.
Yeah, it's problem.
Because we've revived her.
You understand that.
This wasn't my idea.
But she's been revived.
We have a responsibility.
Otherwise...
Otherwise?
Why did we revive her?
-If you tell Mussfeld.
-No.
-If you speak with him.
-Me?
The two of you.
What? Are friends?
None of us is going
to talk with Mussfeld.
He will not allow this girl
to live.
He doesn't save people.
Your family?
Who told you?
We heard.
You got the run of C-camp...
and found your wife and kid.
You wouldn't do the same?
-And got them out.
-You wouldn't do the same?
-I wouldn't have the chance.
-That's not what I asked you.
I didn't have the chance.
If we tell Mussfeld,
she's finished.
You hide her.
One of the doctors.
Impossible.
They walk in at all hours.
It has to be...
No. I said no.
For a few days.
What few days?
We're almost sixteen weeks.
Plus with men who've been
who've hardly seen a...
and she's what, fifteen?
Put her in your bed.
She's not staying with us,
alright? I want her out.
Forgetting for a minute
she's a girl,
what do you gain by putting her
with us when we're about to be...
Until what?
A suitable time.
There isn't going
to be a suitable time.
A day or two.
We don't have a day or two.
Nonsense.
What?
There's going to be an uprising.
When?
Alright, who?
Numbers 1 and 3.
How?
Out of Number 3.
An escape?
We're going to destroy
the crematorium.
You'll all be killed.
The things that come out
of your mouth.
We're to be killed
within the week.
How do you know?
Like I said, we're almost
four months.
We're dead.
Our time's up.
Were you going to ask
for our help?
Ask for your help?
The doctors.
Were you going to ask
for our help?
Even tell us?
I never asked to be doing
what I do.
You volunteered.
They wanted doctors
for a hospital.
You knew the sort of work you'd be
doing, and you continue to do it.
I don't kill.
And we do?
I didn't say that.
You give killing purpose.
We're all just trying
to make it to the next day.
That's all any
of us is doing.
You have no idea, do you?
I don't know
what you're talking about.
I do not wish to be alive
when all of this is over.
I don't believe that.
I know you don't.
I can help you.
You want to
help?
Get rid of this fucking girl.
Where have you been?
What do we got?
Plenty, but very little gold.
You're gonna have to divvy up.
They've got three of the women.
Where?
Block eleven. Someone says we're
hiding a girl still alive?
Keep everyone away
from this area.
-Is it true?
-We'll be up.
We heard. We got problems
of our own.
-What's he doing?
-I told him.
You told him?
I just told him. Come on.
-Why are you here?
-What's this about?
She survived the gas.
What're you gonna do with her?
Why is he here?
They caught three of the women
for the Unio, found powder.
Here?
In the camp.
How do you know?
They didn't come with the powder
and we found out. As far as we know...
They've been stealing and they aren't
going to find out where it was going?
I didn't say that.
-They are being tortured right now?
-Of course they are.
How long did you expect this
to go on, before they were caught?
-We couldn't have...
-We couldn't have what?
We couldn't mustered together at any
time once we decided it was time...
-No, we couldn't...
-Oh, God dam, no we couldn't have.
That's a lie.
It was...
-It was who? The Poles?
-No, it was the whole group.
So we waited for this to be killed
without the chance.
There are two women
being tortured right now.
Why are they being tortured?
Why are we still burning day
after day?
Because we've waited. Because
suddenly this became about escape.
And let's get it straight,
Hesh.
You were gonna deal us out.
We were just a fucking diversion.
How many times does this have to be gone over?
Every gun you guys have got you've
kept and we find out about it later.
Not shit from you guys.
Only plans and delays.
Your plans.
We changed our plans.
Changed your plans, but only
after we decided we'd be out.
Had to make a deal,
re-coordinate.
But were you gonna stay wait
until two crematoria were done,
or let us do that and run run,
like you always wanted to,
while we stayed and fought?
I don't know.
But when we're through
with the machinery, I can't run?
I have to stay here and be shot
because that's what you want to do?
Because you can't live
with it, I can't?
Fuck you, Max.
It's my fucking life.
I hope I live till I'm ninety.
Now we're ready to go today.
-What?
-Today?
Between the shifts.
Why else am I here?
To argue with this idiot?
-Who starts the fire?
-Us.
You see how easy it is once
the decision is made.
We have to tell the unit.
An hour. Everyone knows
what to do. It's a matter of when.
What about the girl?
What about her?
What do we do with her?
-It's got to be now, Max.
-We get her in the fence.
Out?
-The fence into the camp.
-You'll never.
-In a group we could.
-A group is worse.
-It doesn't have to be.
-We're locked in.
Don't do this.
An excuse could be found.
The Doctor's right.
We shave her head, dress her
she looks like a boy.
What happens on the other side
of the fence?
She gets taken in.
-Which camp?
-Does it matter?
Yes, it matters.
What do they do with her?
How do they account
for the extra...?
This is Germans we're talking about.
They stand corpses up in the snow...
They're going to suspect
someone of breaking in?
Breaking in from here.
She's not even numbered.
Don't fuck this up for one life!
You'll be shot and so will she.
Then there's alert
and today's impossible.
He's right, Max.
It'll drag us down.
No single person is worth that.
Look at her.
Does she even have a mind left?
Can she speak?
We don't know.
Can you speak?
The gas got to her.
Why are you even considering?
-We don't kill people.
-We don't?
We put them in the rooms,
walk them in and strip,
them look them in the face
and say it's safe.
What the hell is that?
-It's not...
-It's not what?
It's not pulling the trigger.
You leave the room.
Bring them in and leave say it's safe,
you'll see them when it's over.
Who put her inside? Now you
think she made it through.
God knows how you're a hero.
Not a hero.
Not a hero, not a killer.
What are you, Max?
Better we do it than them.
I'll make it easy for you.
We can solve this another way.
I'll fucking kill you!
You won't do shit.
We're not going to kill her,
alright?
I'm not saying we shouldn't have,
but we're not gonna do it now.
On the bench here.
What about me?
What about you?
If he sees me we're fucked
if he sees me.
There's hundreds of He's not
gonna know you. Just keep still.
He wanders around half drunk.
It's a fucking check.
Why is this door shut?
We were organizing
the morning muster.
Organizing?
With Lowenthal... gone.
We settled that.
Yes, Herr Oberschaarfuhrer,
but now with one short...
Who's going to replace him?
He is.
He's not capable.
You!
Yes, Herr Oberschaarfuhrer.
And who replaces him
is your business.
That's just the thing.
-What happens with...
-The duties in the room stay the same.
Yes, sir.
It's miserable outside.
I've grown to hate Poland.
How are you, Doctor?
I'm well.
Do you want to come over
for a drink?
I have some Hungarian wine
some brandy.
Later.
-If you've got a chill...
-I said no.
There's a convoy arriving,
and your group haven't finished
with the cargo from this morning.
-We just have to...
-You have to clear the elevators.
Yes, sir.
And it's filthy down there.
Yes?
What?
Why are you here?
Here?
This isn't your unit.
This isn't your building.
To help.
How did you get over?
I was moved.
-By whom?
-Almaier.
That's not true, is it?
Of course it's true.
That's how it'll go
for all of us.
First you, then us.
The last thing to do
is smile.
Your bombers only speed it all up.
We'll dispose of as many of you
as we can before they do it to us.
Why was he here?
He was moved.
He was not moved!
You were to stay
with your groups.
Why were the women
from the Unio hoarding powder?
We let you live.
You're not gonna let us live.
If something is attempted,
that's certain.
If you think we have powder,
tear apart the crematorium.
Move away from the bench.
Where did she come from?
Doctor?
Everybody out.
You give orders now?
It won't help anyone
if there's a row.
How will the work get finished?
Everyone out.
I'll take care of this.
What do you mean,
take care of this?
I want what you want.
Don't speak Hungarian!
What are you saying?
Leave quietly. Leave.
Let's go.
Save her. You've got
to fucking save her.
Shut him up. Take this with you.
And burn it with the others.
I've seen them strike the ones
that are slow getting in.
Hey steal, lie to each other.
I never fully despised
the Jews
until I experienced how easily they
could be persuaded to do the work.
To do it so well.
And to their own people.
They'll be dead
by week's end eve soul
and we'll replace them
with others' no different.
Do you know how easy that'll be?
Who are you?
She doesn't speak German.
I don't even think she speaks.
-You don't understand me?
-She's from a convoy.
I didn't imagine she's
from Osweicum.
-This morning's convoy?
-Of course.
So you're Hungarian.
They took her out
from the undressing room?
Why her?
She's related to someone?
She survived.
Survived what?
The gas.
All I can think is that,
with the wet floor...
It kills everyone.
If there was a pocket of wet air...
Should we speak in private?
If she doesn't speak German,
what's the problem?
I find it difficult to stand here
and discuss while...
What's to discuss?
I have the information
you requested.
The information?
At the time you saved my wife
and child.
Tell me here.
I don't want to tell you here.
You.
Stay here with her.
If you take her out from here,
both of you will be killed.
Stay here.
I used to think so much
of myself.
What I've made of my life.
We can't know what
we're capable of, any of us.
How can you know what you'd do to
stay alive until you're really asked?
I know this now.
For most of us,
the answer is anything.
It's so easy to forget
who we were before.
Who we'll never be again.
There was this old man.
He pushed the carts.
And on our first day,
when we had to burn
our own convoy,
his wife was brought up
on the elevator.
Then his daughter.
And then both his grandchildren.
I knew him.
We were neighbours.
And in twenty minutes,
his whole family and all its future
was gone from this earth.
Two weeks later he took pills
and was revived.
We smothered him
with his own pillow.
And now I know why.
You can kill yourself.
That's the only choice.
I want them to save you.
I want them to save you more
than I want anything.
I pray to God we save you.
You can hear me, can't you?
I thought so.
Yes. I thought so.
I don't understand, Doctor.
I don't know
how I can make it clearer.
Dr. Mengele says you're
the best surgeon he's seen ever.
I Jew, even, and he admits it.
Which is astonishing.
He says you do the work
of five men.
That without you his research
would be impossible.
Where is this leading?
Your expertise
has quintupled the torture.
I haven't...
Has quintupled the torture
of children in this camp,
and that is fact!
So that you can live here as you do,
which is better than any other Jew.
And better than all
but a handful of Germans.
Including me.
I haven't seen you once protest
and as the workload has increased.
And you've saved your family.
We do what we do.
You make up for that
with the life of this one girl?
I don't pretend.
Good.
Don't.
And who is to die in her place?
No one lives here
without someone else dying.
I don't believe that.
It's a fact of the camp.
It's numbers.
There's only so much food,
so much room.
This is one child.
Which you could say about anyone.
Your wife and daughter.
You save one, you take the life
of another.
Put her in a bed, give her food
someone else doesn't get,
dies or is removed.
To save her
is a meaningless lie.
It's your lie,
Herr Oberschaarfuhrer.
We want the girl to live.
If you tell me this information,
I will spare the girl.
There's going to be an uprising.
When?
I don't know. They don't want me
to be a part of it.
And they have powder.
The women got them powder?
-I said I don't know.
-Why did they tell you?
Because of the girl.
Because they wouldn't hide her.
-Who told you?
-The one you killed.
How did you speak with him?
He was here, wasn't he?
That's why you shot him.
No one else here speaks with me.
-But they have powder?
-I don't know.
-Weapons?
-I don't...
But powder from the women.
That's where the powder went.
I've heard nothing else.
-This information is useless to me.
-It's all I was told.
It's not worth the life
of the girl.
You agreed.
Wrong, Doctor. I agreed to save your
wife and daughter, which I have done.
Herr Oberschaarfuhrer...
There's nothing more to discuss.
What about your headaches
and your drinking?
Excuse me?
I'll tell him you're unfit.
And they won't move you
somewhere else.
I'll want to see her.
Not a hair on her head,
and on the other side.
Through the fence,
if you'd like,
but numbered, shaved and alive.
And to live isn't to kill,
Herr Oberschaarfuhrer.
Because we are not doing
the killing.
No. Please, no!
Because she knew.
Because all of you know.
And these two know.
I could say I don't want to be doing
this but that wouldn't be true.
It's less bodies for us
to worry about.
Keep track of.
Feed.
So, do us a favour
and remain silent.
But you don't seem
to be enjoying it,
murdering your friends
to protect,
who?
Polish partisans who hate you?
Sold Jews,
and stole from Jews early
in the war.
One by one...
We can do this until we're done
with your whole group,
and then we'll move
to the next block.
Or one of you any of you
tell us where the powder is,
where it was headed.
They don't know.
None of them know.
Tell them, please.
Tell them.
They don't know.
Don't you think they would say?
You know, and you're silent.
Stop the killing.
You know, because you had
to have been approached.
And you are getting it
for somewhere.
Stop the killing.
Please. Please.
No! No!
Don't shoot her!
Get a proper count.
It's all sentimental.
Do you understand sentimental?
Because they look you
in the eye twice.
Once before and once after.
Suddenly they believe
in heroics.
You wait here.
Hold her in here
until I get back.
Don't leave her.
They're saving her.
No, Max, the Doctor
will make certain.
You saw, or they told you?
The Doctor told me.
We did this.
Listen to me, listen.
What's going to happen to her will happen,
no matter what you do or see.
You're right, we did it.
We saved her.
The best thing you can do is to finish
the day quietly and wait for later.
That's it.
That's it for you.
The goddam end.
Hoffman, you have to get over to the
Third, tell them about Abramowics.
How am I to get through?
We'll load you up.
Here.
Exactly what happened.
I don't speak Yiddish.
Well, you can fucking convey
somebody getting shot.
And don't try to come back.
We're not waiting for you.
-I talked to her.
-Yes?
I talked, she understood.
What are you saying?
-We were alone while...
-Did she talk?
I said I talked.
What did you say?
-Everything.
-Everything?
You told her?
You would have, too.
What do you know
what I would do.
You would have.
What does that do for her?
Maybe it did something for me.
Fuck what it did for you!
What do you need?
She'll know who we were.
And why does she need
to know that?
I don't know.
That's right. You don't know.
Do you?
-Get going.
-Fuck off! I'm going.
Do you?
Fire! There's fire!
He said between the shifts.
Cohen, Lowy, we won't have time
to organize the groups.
Get the guns and down into the
corridors and barricade the doors.
Let's go!
Let's go, let's go!
Go see what's happening.
Get the fuel drums.
Have you seen the Oberschaarfuhrer?
Have you seen the Oberschaarfuhrer
or any SS men with a young girl.
No!
Please, have you seen
a young girl? She was alive.
We've only got two drums up there.
We're nearly out of explosives.
They're only the machine guns.
I don't need to know.
Go tell Schlermer.
We're dead up here.
Move down, move down!
Kaminski needs bodies
in the furnace room.
We're setting the explosives.
Have you seen Mussfeld
with a girl?
We need you in the furnace room.
Come on!
Get out! Get out!
Get out!
Surrender if you want to live.
It's over.
We're gonna blow the room!
Do it!
Why don't they kill us.
Did you ever see her?
No. Did you?
Why am I asking?
Why aren't they killing us?
The Russians will be here
before the year's out.
If it weren't that, we would
never have pulled this off.
You hid.
Will I be killed?
Do you want to be killed?
You would have fought.
Wouldn't you have?
I've spoken with Dr. Mengele,
and assured him that you had
nothing to do with any of this.
That you knew and did nothing.
You will continue
with your work.
That's right, Doctor.
We will both continue
with our work.
Because that's
what the living do.
We will have saved each other,
then.
We needn't save anyone else.
In Budapest, mostly.
My wife was from the city.
But we stayed north.
I still don't know why.
It's beautiful there.
Yes, it is.
But we were finally gonna move
near her family.
-Where did they live?
-Near the markets.
We would be neighbours.
Will they kill her?
They're gonna show her this
then let her live.
But why wouldn't
they have done it already.
You're asking for reasons.
I guess I was.
We did something.
Yes.
We did.
Yes. Bye.
Neighbours.
After there vo It,
half the ovens remain
and we are carried
to them together.
I catch fire quickly.
The first part of me rises
in dense smoke
that mingles
with the smoke of others.
Then, there are the bones,
which settle in ash.
And these are swept up
to be carried to the river.
And last,
bits of our dust
simply float there,
in air, around the working
of the new group.
These bits of dust are grey.
We settle on their shoes
and on their faces
and in their lungs.
And they become so used to us,
that's on they don't cough
and they don't brush us away.
At this point, they're just moving,
breathing and moving.
Like any one else, still alive
in that place.
And this is how
the work
continues.