It seems like
such a short time ago
that my pet and I
were just lazing about
in our little London flat,
living the humdrum,
bachelor life,
and wishing things weren't
so very, very dull.
Oh, that's my pet... Roger.
My name's Pongo.
You remember, I'm the one
with the spots.
- Oh, goodness!
- No, no, not that one.
Or that one.
Ah, that's me, living my
new life as a family man.
Never a dull moment.
I guess I got my wish.
Ahh!
I think I'm seeing spots!
Hey, seeing spots!
Spots...
I'm seeing spots
Everywhere I'm seeing lots
of those tiny little dots
Yes, it's true
They're on the beds
and the cots
In the pans and the pots
And they've left
little spots in the loo
Roger...
are you packing
or playing?
I'm playing
at packing, dear!
Well,
quit fooling around.
We're moving first thing
in the morning!
We'll have a Dalmatian
plantation
La la-la-la
la la-la-la
I see spots
on the walls
In the rooms,
in the halls
On the floors,
in the drawers, yes, I do
And every morning
when I rise
And I open up my eyes
I am taken by surprise
'Cause instead of seeing
skies
I see lots
of little spots
- We'll have a Dalmatian
plantation
- Spots, spots, spots!
- And never again
shall we roam
- Everywhere on the beds
and the cots
- Can't wait to begin
our sweet living that's in
- On the walls,
the rooms, and the halls
Our Dalmatian
plantation home
Dalmatian plantation,
we're home
Oh, Roger!
Yes, tomorrow
would be moving day.
Only one more night
in this little flat...
which was getting smaller
by the minute.
I mean, even I was beginning
to feel a bit smothered.
Really.
It was easy to see how one of
our puppies could feel...
well, just a little bit lost
in this...
sea of spots.
Hello, Patch.
Hello, mother.
Watching the television,
are We?
Yes.
Well, I've got to save
my spot, now, don't I?
It's the best spot,
after all!
Ahh! But you know
your show doesn't
start until after...
Dinnertime!
Oh, dear.
Oh, not again!
Whoo! Whoa!
Ooh. Ugh.
Ehh! Ah-ah-ah-ah-ah!
Whoo! Ugh.
Come on, you guys!
Make room!
Ugh!
No, you don't,
Mr. Roly-poly.
One bowl at a time!
There must be something
in here.
Right!
Is everybody ready
for the show?
My spot!
Thunderbo-olt...
Ugh!
The Mighty Thunderbolt
Adventure Hour...
Ahhh! Whoa!
- Heyyy!
...the one-of-a-kind
wonder dog
Kanine Krunchies...
the crunch your dog
loves to munch...
presents "The Thunderbolt
Adventure Hour,"
starring Thunderbolt,
the one-of-a-kind wonder dog!
And his trusty sidekick,
Little Lightning.
In last week's
thrilling episode,
wholesome Tommy
was kidnapped...
Help, Thunderbolt,
save me!
...and spirited away
by that black-hearted villain,
Dirty Dawson!
Help, Thunderbolt!
Save me!
Will our hero arrive
in time?
Help, Thunderbolt!
Save me!
What horrible fate awaits
wholesome Tommy?
Oh, I can hardly look!
Oh, I've seen this one.
This is brilliant!
Help, Thunderbolt!
Save me!
That mangy mutt
can't save you this time!
Hold on, Tommy!
Thunderbolt's coming!
- Ahh!
- Ahh! Hey!
This is just like "Double-cross
at Dead Man's Ditch,"
except that was a mine car,
not a train.
- Shh!
Grrrr!
Watch this.
Thunder's gonna grab the whip.
- Shh!
Patch, you're gonna
spoil it again!
They say
every dog has his day,
but this'n ain't gonna
be yours,
ya flea-bitten cur!
Huh?
Ugh!
Whoa! Ahh! Ah!
Whoo-hoo! Yes! Yes!
Huh?
This ain't fair!
Oww-hoo-hoo!
What was that supposed
to be? Heh heh heh heh!
It was the most pitiful bark
I've heard yet.
Yeah, it sounded like
someone sat on a squeaky toy!
Ahh, Thunderbolt,
you're one-of-a-kind!
Wow! One-of-a-kind!
Kanine Krunchies...
All right, bedtime,
everyone.
- Ohhh!
But, Dad,
we're not sleepy yet.
Nanny, do you have
the new dog tags?
Right here.
We'll put them on
as they come up the stairs.
Say, kiddies!
Is your dog
a one-of-a-kind wonder dog?
If you think your pooch has
what it takes,
bring him down
to the London set
of Thunderbolt's exciting
new adventure,
"Thunderbolt Versus the Hound
of the Baskervilles."
Thunderbolt's in London?!
That's right!
Thunderbolt's in London.
Just follow
a Kanine Krunchies truck
down to tomorrow's auditions,
where one lucky pup
will win the opportunity
to appear as a guest
on the show.
Dad! Dad! Dad!
56, 57, 58... careful.
Ugh!
59, 60, 61, 62...
63, 64...
Dad! Dad!
I have to see Thunderbolt!
J-J-Just a minute, son.
I'm counting.
But, Dad!
67, 68, 69...
I've seen every episode...
all 72.
72, 73... 2?
Uh...
Not now, Patch.
I'm busy losing count here!
76, 77, 78, 79...
But, Dad!
Dad! Whoa!
81, 82, 83...
Oh! Ohh!
Oh, dear.
Uh, 98, 99, 100, 101,
102, 103, 104,
and Patch... 105.
105?!
Are you all right, son?
Dad, I've just got to see
Thunderbolt tomorrow.
Yes, I know,
but tomorrow is moving day.
You're going to love it
on the farm, son.
There are big green fields
and a stream
and a barn and lots
of different animals.
Hey, maybe you and I
can chase some chickens, huh?
Uh, sure, Dad, but...
Here we go!
"Cherry Tree Farm,
Little Tichfield, Devon." Hmm.
Why, I imagine it's
the most splendid farm
in the whole country.
Oh, Perdy...
The farm will be
such a wonderful place
to raise our puppies.
And best of all,
we'll be miles away from
that evil, ugly monster...
Cruella De Vil!
Now, please let me in!
I can't do that,
Miss De Vil.
Mr. Fenwick, please,
something, anything.
You know very well that
the terms of your probation
don't allow me
to sell you any more furs.
Not even a stole...
a muff...
a pair of mittens?
- No!
- One mitten?
No!
Could things possibly be
any worse?
Cruella De Vil
Shut up, shut up,
shut up!
Ohh!
Ugh!
Oh!
What does Cruella De Vil
have left to live for?
- Ugh!
- Ohh!
Good grief!
Tell me...
what do you see?
Everything.
Darkness and light,
form and content.
And what else?
Chaos and order,
joy and pain.
And there is more than that?
The possibility of triumph,
the certainty of defeat,
the culmination of all
I've ever reached for
but could not grasp!
I see everything!
I see absolutely everything!
I feel faint in the presence
of such artistic truth.
Where is the artist?
I simply must meet him!
But... you already have.
I am Lars...
and I am
an undiscovered genius.
My name is Cruella De Vil,
and I'm
an overfinanced heiress.
Your passion for my work
both repels...
...and attracts.
- Ooh.
Could you bear the sweet
agony of seeing more?
You mean there's more?
Spots!
Spots! Spots! Spots!
I have yet to find anyone
who truly understood
their bleak
but beautiful meaning...
that is...
until I met you.
This could be it!
This could be
the cure for my craving!
My analyst said I should find
something to substitute
for my magnificent
obsession.
Who needs furs
when I can soothe
my tortured soul with art?!
Something tortures you?
Tell me what cloud dares
cast a shadow on...
the flower?
Oh, it's a sad
but familiar tale of
loss and disappointment,
probation,
and a restraining order.
But you...
you can help Cruella
to forget all that.
Will you do a painting
just for me...
to ease my pain?
I will create
a masterpiece,
if you will be my...
muse.
Ooh. Oh, darling.
Ohh.
Ahhh.
6...
7...
26...
202.
Dad?
97...
I can't sleep.
- 98...
- I've been thinking.
90...
Do you think
I'm one-of-a-kind
or just...
one of 101?
101. That's it.
101.
All right, everyone,
into the truck!
You're 90,
you're 91, you're 92,
you're 93, you're 94.
Hold it. Wait.
You're 98, you're 99...
you're 100...
and you're 101.
And you're 101,
Hold it. Wait.
How many 101 s are there?
Well, I've successfully
lost count again.
Right.
Anyone not here, speak up.
Oh, no!
Wait! Wait for me!
Well, that figures.
They didn't even miss me.
Then I'm not gonna miss
them!
Well,
what do you think?
Why, it's splendid!
Puppies, welcome
to your new home!
Right then.
That's 1 and 2 and, uh...
37, 36, 5, 50, 8, um...
minus 2, carry the 3, and, um...
101?
Finally, no more counting.
Huh?
Waaa!
All this place needs
is a proper dusting,
a splash of paint,
and it'll be good as new.
Now, where do you suppose
we'll put the music room?
I think you just found it,
darling.
Thunderbo-olt
Hounding hoodlums
with a howl... hear his growl
Thunderbo-olt
Desperadoes,
cringe in fear...
Ladies and gentlemen,
boys and girls,
pooches and pups of all ages,
are you ready?!
Desperadoes, cringe in fear.
Mighty Thunderbolt is here!
I don't believe it!
It's really him!
And here's his sidekick
extraordinaire,
the ever-trusty
Little Lightning!
- Yoo-hoo!
- Hello, handsome!
Over here,
you gorgeous hunk o' hound.
Oh, uh, hi, ladies.
Nice to meet you.
- Oh, no.
- We don't want you.
Get out of the way.
We want...
Thunderbolt!
- Ooh.
Sorry, little buddy,
but these ladies aren't
interested in the sidekick.
They're here to get
a big eyeful of...
hero!
- Aaah!
Heel, ladies, heel.
Thunderbolt!
All right, everybody.
Line up your dogs
for the audition.
We need to hear
their best heroic bark.
V-Very good.
Hey, that's very...
Oh, there's more!
Ugh!
Well... go ahead.
Uh...
What's the matter,
little fella?
Cat got your tongue?
Oh, that's funny,
'cause, you see, we're dogs,
and we chase cats, so...
Ah, well, it made me laugh.
Come on, kid,
we haven't got all year.
You're wasting
my valuable limelight.
Say, who sat
on the squeaky toy?
Hey, Thunderbolt,
over here!
Thunderbo-olt...
That's it, folks!
We'll announce the winner
of the audition tomorrow!
Have a megafantabulous day!
And remember, buy your pooch
lots and lots of tasty
Kanine Krunchies!
...only in the night
Nice work, Patch,
just brilliant.
Ladies, ladies,
you're wearing me out.
Oh, please?
Just do it one more time.
Oh, well, all right.
I guess just one more time
couldn't hurt.
- Aaah.
Golly, I'm good.
Hello, boys!
- Thunder!
- Lightning, little buddy.
It's just awful!
- Ooh. Ahh.
- I overheard
what they're planning
for the next episode.
Growl!
Bump!
Ah, don't be too harsh
on them, little buddy.
I know we don't have
the best writers in television,
but we can always improvise.
I'm pretty good
at improvising...
as long as
it's written down for me.
No, no, you don't understand.
Something really horrible
is going to happen.
Ooh, ooh, don't tell me.
Let me guess.
- The dam breaks.
The mine collapses.
- No. No.
Do I get an evil twin?
I've always wanted
an evil twin.
No! Listen, Thunder, what
happens is you... you...
Huh?
You die.
I don't believe it.
L-I die?
Oh, Lightning,
this is just... about
the greatest thing ever!
Ha ha!
I've always wanted to play
a big death scene...
the selfless hero
who sacrifices himself
to save the innocent.
Ha ha!
I'll kick bigger
than Old Yeller! Ha ha ha!
So, how do I make
my shockingly unexpected
and triumphant return?
- You don't.
- What do you mean,
I don't?
You don't make
a shockingly unexpected
and triumphant return.
You die. You're dead.
You never come back.
N-Not even
for a reunion show?
Not even for a cameo
in the remake.
They're writing me
out of the show!
They're gonna replace you
with a younger dog.
Oh, so that's
what those auditions
were really all about.
Oh, Lightning,
you gotta help me.
I can't end up
on the street, homeless,
foraging in trash cans.
Mange! I could get mange!
Well, I... I did have
this one crazy thought.
Or ticks!
I hate ticks!
They suck all the blood
out of you, do you hear me?!
out of yo-o-o-o-u!
What if... you went out
and did something heroic,
like you do on the show,
but in the real world?
You know, get your name
in the paper...
prove to 'em
that you still got it.
Wait a minute.
What if... I went out
and did something heroic
in the real world?
Or... that could work, too.
After all, you are
the one-of-a-kind wonder dog.
How hard could it be?
- Yeah, it'll be a catwalk.
- Cakewalk.
Pre-cisely. I'll just
go get a little press for
doing some easy hero stuff,
and they'll be begging
to keep me on the show.
But first... I'll have
to figure out a way
to sneak past
my adoring public.
Hmm?
Hmm. Sneak, sneak, sneak, sneak,
sneak, sneak, sneak, sneak,
sneak. Hide.
Hmm. Ha ha.
Master of disguise.
- Hi, Thunderbolt!
- Aaaaah!
Oh, I'm sorry.
You've got the wrong dog, kid.
I know it's you.
That's the same disguise
you used in episode 18...
"Gambling Gophers
of Gunfire Gulch."
Oh! For howling out loud!
Now you've blown my cover.
This is champion!
I'm your biggest fan,
Thunderbolt!
I know every episode by heart.
Remember the time when you
fought that grizzly bear
and rescued those orphans
and then the dam broke
and... and...
Hey, aren't you
the squeaky toy?
Yeah. Heh. That's me.
- Listen, pup...
- Patch.
Pooch... whatever.
You've got to understand,
sometimes danger and I
like to dance alone!
Good gracious gravy,
look at that!
A cat is stuck
up in that tree!
He is?
Oh, my heart goes
out to the poor,
helpless creature.
Now, if I were me,
what would I do?
Well, I'd read the script.
That's what I'd do.
Oh, no!
I don't have a script!
This is just like when
Tommy was trapped on that
cliff in episode 29.
- That one was a classic.
- Okay, okay, don't panic.
You can do this.
- Only it's also like
episode 64...
- You can do this.
You can do this.
- When he was drowning
in the water tower.
- You can't do this!
You can't do this!
- Yeah, that was great.
- You can't do this!
Who am I kidding?!
I have no idea
what I'm doing!
But episode 29
is still the best,
at least
from the first season.
- Pooch...
- Patch.
- Whatever.
I'm trying to panic here!
- Oh, sorry.
I just thought you were
gonna do what you did
on Raccoon Ridge...
you know, when you got
that barrel and dragged it
next to the cliff
and you found
a long plank of wood
and got a great, big,
round boulder, and then...
Pre-cisely!
Whoa!
Ohh!
Hang on, little kitty!
Help is on the way!
Heh heh heh.
The press is gonna love this.
Aah!
Phew.
There you are,
my good man.
No need to thank me.
The look on your face
is thanks enough.
Now smile for the cameras.
Hey, that's strange.
Where are all the photographers?
The press is always around
when I do something.
What's the matter
with you English people?
Are you all having tea?
How am I supposed
to get my job back
if you're all having tea?!
That was champion, Thunder,
just like on the telly!
You know, this stuff
isn't as easy as it looks.
I mean, maybe if I could
remember what happened
in every episode of the show,
you know, like squeaky toy
here, then I could...
Hey, squeaky toy.
Oh, darling,
it's just divine!
It's remarkable!
It's stunning!
It's grand!
But it's all wrong.
But... but it... it's
my best work yet... cupcake.
But it simply has to be better
than your best, darling.
I mean,
look at these spots.
Oh, the shapes
aren't at all acceptable.
They're not... soft enough...
you know, cuddly...
like something you want
to squeeze the life out of!
Oh, no, this one
is no good at all...
an embarrassing mediocrity,
a complete failure!
Your harsh words strike me
like blows from the fists
of a large dockworker.
I would cry now...
were it not so bourgeois.
There, there.
I know you'll get it right,
my depressive Da Vinci.
You simply have to keep
trying.
After all, you're the only one
who truly understands Cruella,
who can see
into her tortured soul.
Yes! Her heart is like
a vast, dark ocean
on whose waves
I am hopelessly adrift
in my dinghy of passion.
I shall not betray
your faith in me!
I shall create
another canvas,
and another and another
and another,
until I have found
spotted perfection!
I shall not stop until
the fires of your craving
have been quenched!
Junior deputy test?
Which episode was that in?
Uh, one of
the lost episodes.
But I only give it to pups
who I think might be worthy.
And who knows?
If you do real good,
maybe I'll even let you
be on the show with me.
Really?
Sure, kid.
I'm the star, aren't I?
Mother
of pasteurised milk!
That stagecoach
is out of control!
This is your first
junior deputy test, kid.
Okay. Well... this is
just like in episode 37,
"Stagecoaches
of Serpent Summit."
Very good.
Now, episode 37...
was that the one where
I leap, run, and pounce?
No, no. That was the one
where you run, pounce,
and leap.
Pre-cisely! Stand back!
Caboodle lay-dee-ooh-ooh
Caboodle lay-dee-ooh
Get hold of yourself, man!
You're out of control!
- Whoa!
- It's okay!
I'll get the brake.
Caboodle lay-dee-ee-ooh
Still no photographers.
- How odd.
- Aah!
There may be days
when things don't go right
And your shoes
refuse to dance
To make the winds of fortune
blow right
You might need
a second chance
So if you get one try
and that don't fly
Stop and count to 10
And if at first
you don't succeed
Try again
Here's your next test,
kid.
Wow! Banque robbers!
Uh... episode 4.
Beginner's luck
is overrated
- Ugh! Ugh! Ugh!
- Once you blink,
it's come and gone
- Aaaaaah!
- The only way
to cultivate it
Is to keep on keepin' on
- Yeah
- Hmm? Still no photographers?
Try and try and then
If at first
you don't succeed, yeah
Try again
Try, try again
Yes, my friend
Try, try, try again
Those men
are frozen with fear.
No wonder.
Those crazed badgers are
trying to eat their heads!
It's just like in
episode 27 when you
whupped those two grizzlies!
- Caboodle
lay-dee-ooh-ooh
- Huh?
Eeeb-a-dee-bop
sa-dum-wa-dum
Caboodle lay-dee-ooh-ooh
And don't you ever stop, no
Caboodle lay-dee-ee-ee
Mimmy-zop ba-dum, wa-dum,
yeah
What is it?
Looks like we've stumbled
on a band of cattle rustlers.
Uh, aren't those monkeys?
Even worse...
monkey rustlers!
Sounds like episode 34
to me.
Right answer once again...
junior deputy.
- I passed the test?!
- Think you can handle it?
You bet! Let's get
those monkey rustlers!
Now, if you find
you're batting zero
And a legend you are not
You can still wind up
a hero
If you give it
one more shot
If you don't give in,
you're gonna win
The only question's "When?"
So if at first
you don't succeed
Blech!
Try again
Try, try, try again
Try, try again
And again, yeah
Try, try, try again
Try again
Hey, get over on the right
side of the road, buddy!
Sheesh! London drivers.
I told you, Thunder.
This is the best day ever!
Yeah. You know,
I never knew it would be
so much fun out here
doing this real hero
stuff.
What do you mean?
Don't you do this
all the time?
Oh, well, kid, uh...
Well, you know, it's, uh...
Of course I do! Ha!
I do this all the time.
So, let's talk
about you, kid.
Me?
- Yeah. What's your story?
- Well, uh...
Hold on. Okay, go on.
Missing?! What do you mean,
he's missing?!
- We've looked...
- And looked...
But there's just no sign
of Thunderbolt anywhere.
This is a catastrophe...
a calamity...
- a cataclysm!
- Ohh!
We have to shoot first thing
in the morning,
and I find out
my star is missing!
How can you shoot a show
without a star?!
How... can you shoot...
a show without... a star?!
How do you spell
"cataclysm"?
How can you shoot a show
without a star?
without a...
A star.
This is it.
This is megafantabulous!
We'll rewrite this episode
and star Little Lightning!
I'm a genius!
Get the writers!
Fire the director!
This is going to be
a whole new direction
for "The Thunderbolt
Adventure Hour"!
A whole new direction.
What do you think of that?!
Thunderbolt, old pal,
finally I'll be able
to step out of your shadow,
you overrated,
overacting ham!
"The Little Lightning
Adventure Hour"...
it has a nice ring,
doesn't it? Hmm?
What do you think?
I have failed you, my muse.
Oh, fickle bird
of inspiration,
to what far shore
have you flown?!
Oh, poor, pathetic Lars,
do not despair.
I know exactly where to find
the inspiration we crave.
Oh, this is art,
after all.
Art! Our creativity
cannot be thwarted
by trivial matters
like restraining orders.
Yes!
Sacrifices must be made!
Gone? They're all gone?!
How unspeakably rude
of Anita to move away
without even leaving
a forwarding address.
Oh, Lars,
now what am I to do?
Why, you little...
What's this?
I know you.
Oh, this is delicious!
"Cherry Tree Farm,
Little Tichfield, Devon."
Oh, no.
Freckles, dear,
stop helping.
Oh, my! The tea!
Uhh! Yes, the paper.
No time to read this
if I'm going to finish
my new song.
Well, I come from
this really big family.
I knew a guy
who came from a big litter...
10 or 12.
I forget.
There's 101 of us.
101 Dalmatians?!
Hey, I heard about you guys.
Yeah, you were
on the Twilight Bark.
Well, that's just it,
isn't it?
I'm afraid all I'll ever be
is one of 101.
At least
that's what my dad thinks.
Hey, Thunderbolt,
how do you become
a one-of-a-kind
wonder dog anyway?
Well, in my case,
it all hinged on getting
just the right agent.
But, you know, kid,
getting there isn't so tough.
It's staying on top.
That's the real challenge.
You think
you're doing great,
and all of a sudden
there's somebody trying
to take your place.
- Crowd you out.
- Push you aside.
Steal your spot!
Pre-cisely!
You know,
you're all right, kid.
I'll tell you what,
little buddy...
I'm planning on doing
some more big-hero
stuff today.
You stick with me.
Maybe you'll get
your picture in the paper,
show the world that you're
not just another dog.
No, no, no, like this.
Ahem.
Uh-oh.
What?!
Patch? In London?!
Don't you worry. I'll
keep an eye on things here.
This is all my fault.
If only I hadn't lost count.
Oh, stop blaming
yourself, dear.
The important thing now
is that we find him
before
Cruella De Vil does.
It's not fair, Horace,
me lad.
It's just not fair.
How come she gets off
with probation
and a restraining order...
While we's left
rottin' away in here.
Off your bums, lads.
Sprung for your bail,
somebody has.
It must be Mum
come to spring us.
Mum never liked me.
It must be good ol' Dad.
Dad never liked you either.
Jasper, Horace!
- Aah!
It's time to finish the job.
Oh, no, not her!
We always get the worst end
of it with her.
Well, if she wants us
to work for her
this time,
we won't be made fools of.
You look just like Mum.
Shut up, you!
I ain't going through
with this, I tell you!
I ain't!
Here he comes now!
Whoa!
- Go on, Jasper.
- Go! Go on! Go!
Afternoon, love.
Something I can... aah!
Hello, there!
Uh, uh,
something I can do
for a pretty
young lady like yourself?
Of course you can,
you naughty man!
You can
just give me this truck!
What?!
Whoo-hoo!
They're all inside,
Jasper.
Go ahead and start it up.
Whatever in the world?
Hmm?
Ow!
Hey, where's he going?
- Kanine Krunchies!
Hey, it's
Kanine Krunchies!
Oh, my!
Yippee!
Mmm! Yummy!
Whoo-hoo.
It worked, Jasper.
Like a dream,
Horace, me lad.
Like a dream.
You?!
I should have known
it was you terrible men!
Now let those puppies go
right now,
or I'm going to
knock the stupid
out of both of you!
Here now, lady.
We don't want to have
to hurt you none.
So...
Aaah!
Uh...
Come on!
Ohh!
Ow!
Ah-ah-ah-ah-ah-ah-ah!
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh!
Whoa!
Aaah!
- Ugh!
Right.
That's it, then!
I've had just about enough
of this!
Ohh!
Oh, no!
There, now.
That ought to hold you
right proper.
- Jasper.
- What?
Can we just go back
to gaol now?
Your muse has returned!
But I am a failure.
You should despise me.
Oh, stop being
such a wet blanket
and come see
what I've brought for you.
A gift... for me?
How very "Christmas morning
with the twinkle lights" of you.
A gift of inspiration!
Well, of course.
These are only...
just about the most adorable
little puppies
I've ever seen
in my whole life!
Look at these cute
little darlings!
Oh, a fuzzy wuzzy
little puppy poo!
Poo-poo.
Little puppy poo.
Did you see that?!
He gave me a widdle kissy!
I'm gonna kiss him back.
He's havin' a wobbly.
And you mean for me to do
a painting of them, don't you?
That's an absolutely
lovely idea!
It makes me smile a lot.
"Painting of them," he says.
No, no, no, darling.
I don't want you to make art
of the puppies.
I want you to make art
with the puppies.
Use their coats as canvases.
Create a masterpiece
in a new medium.
Together you and I will
stun the art world
with our ruthless
originality!
But that means...
How could you do such a thing
to the cute little puppies?
- Poison them.
- Drown them.
Bash them in the head.
I may be eccentric,
but I am not a sicko!
- What?!
- You'll not hurt one spot
on these innocent
little creatures' heads!
Not as long as I have anything
to say about it!
I thought you were
a man of vision,
someone who understood
my passions,
who understood the complexity
that is Cruella!
Does no one get the point?!
Oh, Lars, you're such
a disappointment.
Oh, well.
If I can't have
a masterpiece,
at least I'll finally have
a fabulous Dalmatian coat.
That's almost as good.
Don't you agree?
Ooh!
What has gotten
into you, girl?
- Aah!
Kidnapped?!
How many?
Phew!
Oh!
Ohh!
Ugh!
Uh-huh.
Uh-huh. Uh-huh.
Wretched dogs!
Oh!
Ugh!
I just
can't understand it.
We've been out here doing
hero stuff all day,
and none of these
London photographers
seem to care.
Why do you want
photographers around?
Aw, kid.
Look, I got something
to tell you.
Something I guess I should have
told you a long time ago.
Oh, I don't know how to say
this, but the truth is...
Thunderbolt, listen!
There's an emergency!
Sounds like a kidnapping!
Hmm.
Being held in a warehouse.
A devil woman!
101 Dalmatians.
Hey, what a coincidence.
You come from a family
of 101, too.
What...
what's the matter, kid?
That is my family.
Cruella must have them again.
Cruella?!
The devil woman!
She's the one
who kidnapped us before.
Oh, this is awful.
What am I going to do?
Wait a second...
Thunderbolt!
You'll help us, won't you?
Yes...
well, kid, that's what I
wanted to talk to you about.
You see,
I'm not really a...
Of course I'll help you,
Patch.
Yeah!
The world-famous
Thunderbolt
rescues the world-famous
101 Dalmatians.
Ha!
Sounds like
a good story to me.
Newsworthy even.
Come on!
We'll let them know
I'm on my way.
The villains
will soon cringe in fear!
Mighty Thunderbolt
is here!
Oh, it's just wonderful.
I heard it through
the Twilight Bark.
Tell all.
Thunderbolt is going to save
those little Dalmatian puppies.
The ones
that were kidnapped?
That's right.
Oh, isn't he
just a dream?
More like a nightmare.
What if "Blunderbolt"
gets lucky and succeeds?
If the press got wind of that,
l-I'd never be rid of him.
Look... that must be
the warehouse.
Let's try over there.
Hey, do you think
you can reach that?
No problem.
Thunderbolt, old pal!
- Lightning?
- Lightning!
What are you doing here?
I came
as soon as I heard.
Thought you might need
a bit of help.
Thanks for coming,
little buddy.
Wouldn't miss it.
What's that supposed to be?
Oh, leave us alone, Jasper.
I think
it's kind of pretty.
So, what's the plan, kid?
See those guards?
I think you can sneak
past them.
Remember the end
of episode 39,
"The Flight
From the Forbidden Fort"?
The one where I ran,
jumped, and sprang?
No, no, sneaked, evaded,
and triumphed.
Oh, yeah!
Of course!
I get it.
Hey, you're a pretty
smart kid.
That's a good plan...
stealthy.
But we don't need
any of that.
This is Thunderbolt!
Villains always cringe
in fear
whenever Thunderbolt
is here!
So true.
What we need
is a full-frontal assault!
How hard can it be?
That's right.
Follow me.
Oh, I'm right behind you,
pal.
It sort of looks like you,
except you don't have
that much hair.
It's Patch! And he's
brought Thunderbolt!
He'll save us!
Here now.
Where did you come from?
Get outta here,
you stupid mutt!
Maybe
they didn't hear you.
Don't worry, kid.
This will be Take Two.
- Aah!
Ahh!
That's more like it.
Ah!
What have we here?
Oh, it's you.
I owe you a debt of
gratitude, my photogenic
little friend.
If it wasn't for you,
I'd have never found
your brothers and sisters.
And now I have you all.
Thunder...
are you playing dead?
That hurt.
That really hurt.
I knew
you were faking it.
He's been faking it,
all right.
Lightning, little buddy.
I am not
your little buddy!
And you are
no wonder dog!
This kid trusted you,
and look where it's got him.
What's he mean?
He's been lying to you
all day, kid.
He doesn't care about you
or your family.
He was just trying to get
his name in the paper
and save his job.
- Ask him.
- Wha...
No.
Well, yeah, but...
but...
But, but, but.
Hey, genius,
you're no hero!
You're a fraud!
And by the way...
there never was a plan
to recast you.
I just had to get you
out of the way.
Now I got to go take
your place on the show...
my show.
Thunder.
Thunder...
I don't understand.
You lied to me?
I put on an act.
I'm an actor.
That's what I do.
But you said I could be
your junior deputy.
I made all that up.
L-I just needed someone who...
who knew the script.
But you... you said
that you'd help us.
Oh, don't you get it,
kid?
All that "running around
and saving the day" stuff,
it's... it's...
it's make-believe.
It's not real.
You promised!
Patch, I just...
You lied.
I'm sorry, all right?
I'm not a real wonder dog.
I just...
acted like one once.
I'm hungry.
I want to go home.
It's scary here.
Where's mother?
Patch?
Are you okay?
Dad was right.
I am just one of 101.
I'm sorry, Lucky.
This is all my fault.
Hey, didn't Thunderbolt
get out of a cage
like this once,
you know, in episode 13,
"The Flaming Flea Circus"?
Episode 18.
Episode 18!
Did you see
what Patch just did?
Wizard, Patch!
Absolutely wizard!
Hey!
Shut your yapping!
I'm trying to get
me beauty sleep.
Okay, you guys.
Stick together and be quiet.
Oh, don't look
so put-out.
My favourite furrier will be
open in the morning,
and then we'll be
out of your hair.
Perfect.
Episode 53,
"The Mine Shaft Mix-up."
Everybody, stay here
until I tell you it's safe
to come out.
Aw, what is it with...
Aah!
- You let the puppies
get away!
Hold on!
They can't have gone far.
Here... start searching.
Oh, when that crazy bird
finds out we lost them again,
she'll skin us.
Horace, Jasper!
What are you looking for?
Nothing, Mum.
We haven't lost the doggies
or anything.
You let them escape?!
Jasper fell asleep.
You were snoring
like a train!
The lift is barking.
The mutts must already
be downstairs.
Funny how we never heard
the lift.
Shut up, you!
Come on!
They'll be back soon!
Aren't we going down?
Nope, we're going up.
Ready, Rolie?
Huh? No, no.
No, no, no, no, no, no!
Whoa!
Can I do that again?
Okay,
now the rest of you.
I'm just saying maybe the
puppies are still upstairs,
and they just tricked us
into coming down here.
Come on now, Horace.
Dogs ain't that smart.
They haven't got the big
educated brains we got.
97 away!
98 away!
99 away!
Ohh!
- Whoa!
- Oh-ho!
- Aha!
- Ugh!
Get him!
Who-o-o-o-a!
D'oh!
Thanks, Gus.
Cheers.
Come on.
We're gonna hitch a ride.
Here they come!
There they are!
Get them!
What's happened?
- She pushed me!
- Did not!
Who-o-o-o-a!
- Wee!
- Yay!
Aah!
The crazy lady's
right behind us!
Aaah!
Oh-ho-ho!
Ow! Ohh! Ohh!
He had a birdie in his mouth.
Oh, you idiots!
Here... take the wheel.
Speed up, you imbeciles,
or we'll lose them!
Ugh!
Aah!
Aaah!
Ha ha! That's one!
Just 98 more to go!
Okay, okay!
Quiet on the set!
We're rolling!
And action!
Wholesome, Tommy!
Aw, Lightning,
you're one-of-a...
Aaah!
Aaaaah!
Huh?
Hmm?
Whoa! Ugh!
Patch, help me!
Ugh!
Aah!
Well, well.
If it isn't the little
half-pint hero again.
Huh?
Ugh!
Aaah!
Wow!
Check out Patch!
Hmm?
Aaah!
Aaaaaaaaah!
What do we do now, Patch?
See those windows?
We can reach them
from the upper deck!
You go ahead.
I'll hold them off...
s-somehow.
Here's a feisty one.
Thunderbolt!
How are you doin', kid?
But... but I thought...
Come on!
Haven't you seen the show?
I always arrive
just in the nick of time.
Look, I may not be
a real hero,
but I can act like one.
Lightning,
don't let 'em hurt me!
Ooh, heart...
Ugh!
My heart!
Lightning,
this might be the end!
Give me that!
I'll put this mongrel
out of its misery!
Ugh!
Whoa!
Lightning, I can feel
the warm kiss of life
'ere it parts my cheek.
Oh!
Do not mourn me
when I am gone!
It is enough that you were
here at the end.
Goodbye...
old... friend.
Good night, sweet prince.
Aaah!
Aah!
Whoa!
Aaah!
- Aaah!
- Aaaah!
I got to get
through here!
- Aaah!
Dispatch to Car 47.
What is your situation? Over.
No, no!
Fellas, I'm not with them!
I was... I was trying to help
Thunderbolt!
Honest!
That's what I do!
I'm a sidekick!
We're a team!
Come on, fellas! Come on!
Don't you watch TV?!
Hmm. Now who's
the pathetic ham actor?
I am painting spots, but she
doesn't like them so good.
And then she says,
"No, you must kill them!"
And I'm not so sturdy.
She's very mean to me,
and then I pass out.
There they are!
Those are the ones!
- She made us do it!
Spots?
I do see spots, you know.
They're everywhere.
Spots, spots,
spots, spots!
Spots!
There they are!
Oh, this is wonderful!
They're all here!
Oh, come now!
Oh, stop it!
Stop it!
We were so worried about you.
Penny, Lucky!
Oh, my darling puppies!
Oh, Patch, you're safe!
We were so worried
about you.
We missed you very much,
Patch.
You did?
Of course, son.
Mum, Dad,
this is Thunderbolt.
He saved us.
I don't know how to thank you
for saving my family.
No, no, don't thank me.
It was your son, Patch,
who...
Mum, Dad,
the devil woman got us!
And we were trapped,
and then Patch got us out!
Yeah, and Patch made me
a trampoline!
You should have seen
Patch, mother.
He was fantastic!
Just like Thunderbolt.
You know,
they're right, kid.
Me, I'm just an actor.
But you...
you are a real,
one-of-a-kind wonder dog.
Hey, lads,
they're over here!
Whoo!
Say "spots"!
Say, kiddies,
is your dog
a one-of-a-kind wonder dog?
A one-of-a-kind
A one-of-a-kind now, baby
I'm the one
A doggone son of a gun
now, baby
A one-of-a-kind
He's one-of-a-kind
A one-of-a-kind now, baby
I'm the one
He's the one
A doggone son of a gun
now, baby
A one-of-a-kind
Oh, yeah
Wow! One-of-a-kind!
Kanine Krunchies
can't be beat
They make each meal
a special treat
Happy thoughts
for those who eat
Delicious Kanine Krunchies
You know,
they're right, kid.
Me, I'm just an actor.
But you...
you are a real,
one-of-a-kind wonder dog.
A one-of-a-kind
He's one-of-a-kind
A one-of-a-kind now, baby
I'm the one
He's the one
A doggone son of a gun
now, baby
A one-of-a-kind
Oh, yeah
I'm the one
He's one-of-a-kind
A one-of-a-kind now, baby
I'm the one
He's the one
A doggone son of a gun
now, baby
Wow! One-of-a-kind!
That's right!
All right!
Caboodle lay-dee-ooh-ooh
Eeeb-a-dee-bop
sa-dum-wa-dum
Caboodle lay-dee-ooh
Don't you ever stop, no
Caboodle lay-dee-ee-ooh
Mimmy-zop ba-dum, ta-dum,
yeah
So if you try that climb
one more time
You might hit the top
Now, if you find
you're batting zero
And a legend you are not
You can still wind up
a hero
If you give it
one more shot
If you don't give in,
you're gonna win
The only question's "When?"
So if at first
you don't succeed
Try again
Try, try, try again
Try, try again
And again, yeah
Try, try, try again
Try again
Try, try again
- Again and again
and again, yeah!
- Try, try, try again
- Again and again
and again, yeah!
- Try, try, try again
- Whoo!
Try again, yeah!
Ya-ohhh!
Ahhh-ah-ah-ah!
Oh, now, come on!
Down, boy!
Down, all of y'all!
This ain't fair!