- Did you hear that?
- Hear what?
Barbara?
Did you hear that? I could have sworn
I heard whispering.
You're reading my mind, thaùs all.
My thoughts sound like whispers.
Yeah?
What were you thinking?
I love you, Doc.
You sure make it fun to wake up
before dawn, I'll tell you that.
Frank?
- Did you finish last night?
- No.
Honey, iùs a quarter to 6:00.
Iùs important.
Okay.
Thanks.
Thaùs everything.
Helium for the balloons!
I'm picking up a tank at HarolÔs
right after I drop you off...
...per your instructions.
Did I think of that? Cool.
I must be starting to get
this delegating authority stuff.
Well, Mrs. Magoo,
I guess thaùs why they made you principal.
I guess so.
- Honey, don't smoke.
- Come on! You're going to make me crash.
I'll quit smoking when you decide
to get pregnant, all right?
Guys!
- Hi!
- Hi.
- Be careful.
- Here I come.
Watch your step.
You all right?
Jill!
- Who's the chef?
- Oliver.
Great, I love burnt hot dogs.
Thanks. So when's Ben coming home?
Six weeks, four days and nine hours.
- Okay, watch the edges. Don't spill it.
- I got it.
Leùs take it over here.
- Callie, how are you?
- Frank. Good. Good to see you.
Where's my helium?
- Say you love me, baby.
- Not until you get me my helium.
Righty-o. I'll get right on it, dear.
- You go here.
- Okay.
There's Jill. I've got those receipts here.
- How you doing?
- How the hell are you?
- All right, bye.
- Bye. See you later.
- Barbara!
- Frank!
Good morning, Sam.
And you must be Cindy.
Iùs nice to finally meet you.
Do you want to take a look around?
You'll really love this place.
- Harold.
- Morning, Doc.
- Frank.
- Doc, how the hell are you?
Heading over to the school fair?
I have to go to Butler County and
make my rounds at the hospital.
You've got to try
this muscle machine I made.
Show everybody how strong you are.
I don't know.
I should probably sit in the shade
and watch you young guys do it.
- See you, tough guy.
- Right.
Okay. Thanks, Jill.
We need finger paints.
Okay. I'll get them.
Just put it on the table.
Finger paints. Okay.
Yikes.
Well, a civilian pilot spots the smoke.
Then I get here and find two
of my officers passed out like babies.
Everything on that side
of the white line is out cold.
So somebody starts talking
about chemical weapons...
... and somebody hits a panic button,
and then you people are calling.
- There you go.
- Look, there is no research lab.
There is no chemical plant.
There is no toxic waste dump.
There is no nuclear plant!
- There's no nothing around here.
- Okay.
Nothing on the news channels
or news services. Nobody's got it yet.
Good.
I'm just going to take myself in there
and get a look-see.
Ed.
- Thaùs Frank McGowan's truck, right?
- Whaùs left of it.
- Lucky you weren't in town today, Doc.
- Whaùs going on here?
Nobody knows anything,
not even that fed doctor down there.
She brought this whole circus with her,
and they don't have a clue.
Go on out there and see
what the hell's going on. Be careful.
- Stay here?
- Yeah, we're just waiting.
All right, good.
Pull him back!
Get him out of there! Leùs go!
Get him down!
- Stay back!
- Excuse me.
Hits him like a hammer.
Thaùs all we know.
- Some kind of chemical gas?
- No, it can't be.
The edges of the affected area
are well-defined.
Stationary.
- Doc, this is Dr. Susan...
- Vurner.
Like Turner, with a "V."
Epidemiologist,
National Science Foundation.
- Alan Chaffee.
- MD?
He's breathing. Good pulse.
I think he just fainted.
Is Midwich affected by this?
- My hunch would be, yes.
- My wife's in Midwich.
We tried calling for the last six hours.
Nobody picks up or calls out.
Could somebody please get me
some blood and urine samples?
- Whaùs the call?
- 98.
You going? Okay, all right.
Just take it easy.
Somebody get him a blanket.
What happened?
Barbara?
Thank God. Are you all right?
Sweetheart, are you okay?
- I'm cold.
- All right, come on. Leùs go home.
No.
Heavenly Father...
...we mourn these lives cut short...
...without warning or apparent purpose.
We search for a reason and find none.
We have become accustomed
to the power of science...
...so when we were struck down,
we turned to science and asked, "Why?"
But it could not answer.
So now we turn our eyes toward Heaven...
...and seek our comfort
in GoÔs infinite mercy.
Let us pray.
"Our Father, who art in Heaven...
"...hallowed be Thy name...
"...Thy kingdom come, Thy will be done...
"...on Earth as it is in Heaven.
"Give us this day our daily bread...
"...and forgive us our trespasses...
"...as we forgive those
who trespass against us...
"...and lead us not into temptation...
"...but deliver us from evil.
"For Thine is the kingdom, and the power...
"...and the glory, forever and ever.
"Amen."
Did you ever hear of Charles Fort?
He wrote The Book of the Damned,
about unexplainable things.
Like frogs falling from the sky,
blue snow, red rain...
Are you suggesting I read him?
No. Iùs just that...
Sometimes mysteries don't get solved.
I mean, what if something
like this happens again?
I don't know. What do I do?
Can I call you?
Well, of course, you can call me.
By the way,
I suggest you read Sir Arthur Conan Doyle.
Sherlock Holmes once said:
"When you've eliminated the impossible,
whatever remains, however improbable...
"...must be the truth."
Iùs not possible.
You made a mistake. Do it again.
Well, I don't have a problem
running the tests again...
I have felt like this before in the morning.
It is just some kind of bug.
Melanie?
Whaùs the matter?
- Maybe I can help.
- No.
You can't.
- There they are!
- Hey, guys!
We're empty! We need some more here!
Hi, how are you?
Iùs good to see you.
Hi.
Ben, this is fantastic.
Callie, look up and smile.
Ben, after a year in Japan...
...did you ever think you'd have
to get used to being a dad?
Hello, Doc.
I said, "Hello."
- How long have you been standing there?
- Ages.
Liar.
Big boy.
Why are you kissing me like that?
I wanted to know first,
so I used a home pregnancy kit.
Honey, you know those are unreliable.
And thaùs why I went to see
Dr. Cornright just to make sure.
Are you going to open it?
Alan?
Hi. You got a minute?
Sure.
Everything's positive.
You are pregnant.
We'd been trying, you know.
Look.
I wanted to tell you something
before you hear it from somebody else.
There are a lot of pregnancies.
I mean, a lot.
Much more than would
normally be expected.
What do you mean?
Is something wrong with my baby?
No, iùs nothing to indicate that.
You're a normal, healthy young woman...
Alan, don't talk to me like a doctor.
Okay.
All the pregnancies seem to date
from the day of the blackout.
No!
Dr. Susan Vurner has flown in...
This is all because of that blackout, isn't it?
- Just come out and say something!
- They don't know for sure!
They are all going to be deformed!
Wait a minute. Thaùs not true!
Excuse me! Thaùs not true.
There's no reason to believe that.
Barbara and I are pregnant.
We know how you feel.
We know what you are thinking,
so let me say right now...
...the same thing
I've told a lot of you individually.
The standard tests have not revealed
one abnormality.
Anywhere. Not one. All right?
Leùs listen to Dr. Vurner, please.
She's come to talk to us.
Dr. Susan Vurner, ladies and gentlemen.
I want to start off by saying we are all
very concerned about your well-being.
But ultimately it will come down
to individual decisions.
And I understand that these decisions
will be probably the most intimate...
...personal, difficult decisions
that you ever make in your life.
However, because your pregnancies
have attracted intense scientific interest...
...including the National Institutes of
Health and National Science Foundation...
...those of you who decide
to have your child...
...will have all prenatal expenses paid.
You'll also receive $3,000 monthly
as an allowance.
If you allow your child to be examined
and tested on some sort of regular basis.
Is that $3,000 a family?
What if your wife and your daughter
both have kids?
Then you would receive $6,000.
$6,000?
I don't want you to interpret this allowance
as some sort of a pressure.
It isn't. Iùs your decision.
If you decide to terminate then, of course,
you have the right to do that.
You can do it privately.
Or if financially unable, a medical team
will be brought in next week.
- The choice is yours.
- Thaùs killing babies.
Are you okay?
Ben's moving out.
He won't believe me.
What are you going to do?
I can't keep it.
I mean, it can't be Ben's.
I just don't...
I just don't understand.
Something very strange is happening
to all of us, Callie.
You know, they say...
...the Roberts' girl is a virgin.
What are you going to do?
I don't know.
- You all right?
- Yeah.
It was just a dream.
Okay.
Leùs go back to sleep.
Whaùs going on, doctor?
Nothing.
They have apparently decided
to keep their babies.
All of them?
Why?
Thaùs a very good question.
Keep pushing! Push!
Okay, here we go. Here we go. Almost.
Almost done! Good, Mom. Thaùs good.
Push, push, push.
Thaùs it. Thaùs it.
You're doing great! Take a deep breath.
Deep breath and push!
Push, push, push!
Come with that. Push a little more.
- Push, Barbara, push.
- A little more. A little more.
Push. Push.
Help me!
We've got a problem!
ICU, now!
- Push, push, push!
- Come on!
- There we go!
- Good, Barbara!
And there we go.
Beauty! Looking great, sweetie.
Good job.
Iùs a girl, honey.
She's fine.
- There we are. Clamp this.
- Look, here's your baby.
He's beautiful.
Ben.
Come on, just breathe once. Oxygen.
- Watch the BP.
- Just relax. You're hyperventilating.
Push. Doctor, get your ass over here
and help me!
Bear down on her! Push!
All right, here we go!
Come on, push! Give me one big push!
Come on, here we go! Come on!
I'm sorry. Iùs stillborn.
Get some fluid in her.
How we doing? Everything all right?
We lost the Roberts' baby.
- God. How?
- Respiratory failure.
Umbilical asphyxia.
Where did you take the baby?
I saw you take Melanie's baby outside.
I took the baby for an autopsy.
I didn't want the other mothers to see.
I baptize thee...
...in the name of the Father...
...and the Son and the Holy Spirit. Amen.
I got you.
Yes.
Let us pray.
Heavenly Father, we thank you
that by the water of the Holy Spirit...
...you have bestowed upon
your servants, the forgiveness of sin...
...and have raised them
to the new life of grace.
"Sustain them, O Lord, in your Holy Spirit.
"Give them an inquiring
and discerning heart...
"...the courage to will and to persevere...
"...the spirit to know and to love you...
"...and the gift of wonder and joy
in all your work. Amen."
Amen.
Good girl.
Thaùs a good girl.
Note how the section of hair is flat
on one side then arced on the other...
...like a capital "D."
- Right.
The texture is...
I don't know. Iùs unusually soft.
What did you think
when you looked at her nails?
Narrower than normal.
Any results yet from the DNA testing?
Common genetic characteristics.
Almost as if they are siblings
from the same parent.
Iùs way too early
to have anything conclusive.
Baby.
What are you doing?
You can spell your name.
How can you spell your name?
How can Mommy's...
...smart little boy spell his name?
Sweetie, was the soup too hot?
Okay, baby.
We're going to go see our friend Mara.
Barbara?
Are you crazy?
Honey, can't you tell me what happened?
Don't!
No! God, no!
I understand there are
recent developments at Midwich.
Yes.
The children are beginning to interact
more with the general community.
There have been casualties...
I should say accidents, suicides...
...that might be related to
contact with the children.
But no direct physical
violence was involved.
I have also been trying unsuccessfully
to get Dr. Chaffee back on the program.
His daughter's the leader, isn't she?
He's probably got his hands full.
Personal considerations aren't important,
are they?
I think that the opportunity to study
these children should take precedent...
...over any considerations.
Leùs cut to the chase here.
Iùs now of interest
to national security that we continue...
...to carefully monitor
their developing powers.
I ask for another year's grant.
Good afternoon, children.
Why do you smile?
You're trying to hide
your thoughts from us.
Just how deeply do you see?
Everything active in your mind.
But the process that leads
to the spoken words eludes us.
Why do you speak some thoughts
and not others?
Wouldn't it be a noisy world
if we said everything we thought?
Okay, I'm going to put a drop of this
in your eyes; it won't hurt.
I'm sorry. Calm down!
I'm going to wash your eye out!
Okay, open your eyes! Iùs all right!
Iùs okay!
How's the doctor?
Corneal scarring.
Most likely permanent blindness.
How did it happen?
Doesn't remember much.
It will be listed as an accident.
It was the children.
There's no proof of that.
What I want to know is...
...are the people in this town safe?
- What are they going to do to us?
- Alan.
- Hi.
- This has got to stop.
They don't belong in regular classes.
Iùs getting dangerous,
the other children can't learn.
I was thinking
maybe you could teach them.
They seem to respect you.
Respect?
No. They don't even know
the meaning of that word.
Why bother? It doesn't make
any difference what we do.
We need you.
What am I going to teach them?
What am I possibly going to teach them?
Humanity.
Hello, sweetheart.
Come on.
There's no need for you
to become emotional.
I'm old enough to do things by myself.
Do you want to talk about what
happened at the clinic today?
Why should I be experiencing emotion
at this moment?
What is that word you're thinking?
What is "empathy"?
So if I have felt pain...
...I should be able to identify with others
who feel pain.
Yes.
Good night.
Whaùs the matter?
You want some?
I'm sorry.
I just can't hack it.
"God said...
"...Let us make man in our image...
"...after our likeness."
But "image" does not mean outer image...
... or every statue
or photograph would be man.
It means the inner image.
The spirit, the soul.
So we gather here today...
...to remember the inner beauty...
...of one who lost her hold.
Melanie Roberts...
...somehow lost that image of herself
as a creature...
...made in GoÔs bountiful spirit.
But what of those in our midst...
...who do not have individual souls...
...or spirits?
They have one mind...
...that they share between them.
One spirit.
And they have the look of man.
But not the nature of mankind.
What are you doing here?
Looking for the baby.
The one who was born with us.
The one who died.
How do you know about that?
The baby's not here.
She was taken away.
Where?
I don't know.
Do you have a memory of the baby?
But it bothers you.
It hurts to lose a loved one.
She was to be with me.
We were to be together.
How do you know that?
You've lost someone too.
I think I can teach them.
Anyway, I'll try.
I never told David about the Roberts' baby.
Right.
And then he said,
"she was to be with me"?
What did that mean?
I don't know.
Are they paired up...
...like a mate?
What can I teach
such bright young students?
What about human physiology?
Thaùs at least something
I know a little bit about.
For example, does anybody here know
how the eye works?
Do you mean how do we see, or...
Well, what else can the eye do?
- The eyes are...
- The eyes are the windows of the soul.
Yes.
Thaùs right.
I see that you've been reading proverbs.
I was speaking to Robert.
The eyes are the windows of the soul.
All right, if you'd rather
talk about philosophy instead of...
...physiology, leùs talk about the soul.
- Alan.
Sorry.
Can you come to my office
for a minute, please?
Yes. I'll be right there.
While I'm away, why don't you each take
out a volume of the encyclopedia...
...and try to learn a little
something about our culture.
I know your game.
I know what you're up to.
Ever since you got here,
I've been watching.
Watching people leave this town.
Watching things die.
You aren't right. None of you.
And one of these days, somebody's
going to do something about it.
I don't like the way
you're looking at me, boy.
I got a gun, too, and I'm not the only one.
One day somebody's going to get up
on a rooftop...
...and start picking you little bastards off.
One by one by one.
Aren't you going to do something?
Aren't you going to bawl
like all the other little pissants?
Well, do something, damn it!
There are going to be changes.
God help us.
The children did it.
I know they did it.
And my daughter was involved.
Now, who are they?
I first thought they were
a form of mutation.
Some abrupt evolutionary jump.
It was their communal consciousness...
...but I couldn't explain the blackout.
Or the mass pregnancies.
Midwich isn't the only colony
of such children.
In a township in northern Australia,
30 infants were born in a single day.
They all died within ten hours of birth.
In an Inuit community near Anchorage,
a group of 10 children were born.
There were 20 births in a small village
near the Turkish-Iranian border.
Each location was remote...
...isolated, and each had a blackout
the same as Midwich.
And how long have you known about this?
The way I see it,
there are three possibilities.
Number one: Parthenogenesis.
The development of a fetus
without fertilization.
I know. I don't buy that, either.
Two: We do know the CIA slipped doses
of LSD to men without them knowing it...
...in order to study the effects
of psychotropes on gene structure.
Maybe the government
engineered the blackout...
...then artificially inseminated
your women with super sperm.
First they knocked them out,
then they knocked them up.
And whaùs the third possibility?
Xenogenesis. Implantation.
The production of an offspring
unlike that of the parent.
Or should I say host?
Come back to the project.
Not just a matter of protecting
your daughter. As you can see, it goes...
...far, far beyond that.
You have to put this
in the back of your mind.
Don't think about it when near them.
- Don't ever let them know that you know.
- Why didn't you tell us?
- I mean, why didn't you warn us?
- Because I couldn't.
Well, I couldn't.
If anybody else knew,
the children would know.
Look, I have spent years of my life
building a wall around this.
Hiding it, so they couldn't read
what was in my mind.
But as their powers grow stronger,
they keep looking deeper and deeper.
I need your help. Would you please just...
...come back to the project.
We've made our decision.
Discussion will not change our plans.
We will live in the abandoned barn
outside of town.
You will bring us supplies.
You can't stop us, you know.
Don't try.
You've been discussing us with Dr. Vurner.
What did she tell you?
You are hiding something.
I'm not letting you go.
- You haven't been given an option.
- Have you?
You know, you don't always have to do
everything they tell you.
We are the same.
You're not.
You're David. You're different.
I've come to get Julie. Have you seen her?
Is she at the barn?
Fine.
Are you all right?
I'm sorry.
You're okay, aren't you?
Julie doesn't want to come with you.
Damn it, I don't care what Julie wants.
Her mother's frantic.
I'm bringing her home.
Some kind of big accident, Doc,
out by the barn.
Alan, wait!
I was just told that the other towns
with blackout children were destroyed.
- What? All of them?
- Everyone in them, the adults and children.
They couldn't evacuate
without the children knowing.
- The governments gave no warning.
- God. What about Midwich?
I've been told to pack and get out.
I'm leaving tonight. Do the same.
Get out while you can.
Another man is dead.
Why do you hate us so much, Mara?
It isn't a matter of hate.
It is a biological obligation.
You are thinking
of what happened to the others.
Then our actions shouldn't surprise you.
We have to survive
no matter what the cost.
We are the only ones left now.
I don't see why
we can't reach an understanding.
Why can't we just live together?
If we coexist, we shall dominate you.
That is inevitable.
Eventually you will try to eliminate us.
We are all creatures of the life-force.
Now it has set us at one another
to see who will survive.
- Thaùs a cruel sport.
- Life is cruelty.
We all feed on each other,
exploit each other in some way to survive.
I don't agree with you.
I think that adaptation
is the key to survival.
Cooperation and symbiosis...
...and compassion.
Why do you think your own survival
depends upon emotion from us?
Should we pity you?
- Empathize with your plight?
- You should feel!
You should feel something!
Without feelings, you're nothing.
You're just second-rate mimics
of a higher organism.
Thaùs right, a higher organism. We're
your superiors in our capacity to love.
Without compassion,
you're a doomed species.
Emotion is irrelevant. It is not our nature.
I'm not so sure you're right about that.
Still, you are aware of the other colonies.
So you must be, in some basic sense...
...aware of who...
...what we are.
Yes.
So the question becomes...
...should you be allowed to live?
You're suddenly thinking of an ocean.
You're blocking your thoughts
rather effectively with this image.
We must leave here, spread out, disperse.
Soon we will have reached
a stage where we can form new colonies.
You will arrange a method
of getting us away from here.
What if I refuse you?
You are a prisoner of your values...
...and you won't be able to deceive us.
You know that.
Don't you?
Father?
Yes.
Yes, I know that.
Make your arrangements.
We must leave tonight.
You're thinking of the one who died.
She was to be my partner.
Yes, iùs true.
Without a mate,
you are of less importance to us.
And your development
of emotions is disturbing.
We can't leave you behind.
It is time we resolved this.
Hurry up!
"Begone, everyone who is proud,
and bring him low...
"...and tread down the wicked
where they stand!"
- This is the last of it.
- All right, get going.
"Bind their faces in the world below.
"Then will I also acknowledge to you...
"...that your own right hand
can give you victory!"
I'm glad you're here.
I wanted to talk to you.
I really think that I can help you.
You've got to stop! Please stop!
You got to stop! Sarah, please!
"Hast thou eyes of flesh?
"Dost thou see as man sees?"
A state of emergency has been declared.
Please return to your homes...
... and remain there until further notice.
- Come here! Grab my hand, quick!
- Come on!
People will be arrested.
This is a state of emergency.
Please be home.
The children murdered Sarah.
Susan too. I just found her at the clinic.
The police are on their way to the barn.
They're going after the children.
We've got to stop them.
- You can't go. You'll get hurt.
- We've got to try!
No. The state police can't do anything
to stop the children. Iùll be a bloodbath.
Now, listen to me. Listen to me.
There's another way.
Now, look, something happened today.
I was able to block Mara
from reading my thoughts.
- How?
- I suddenly thought of the ocean.
I suddenly saw the view
in front of our house.
You know how Barbara and I
used to dream our dreams there?
We used to stand on the cliff and...
...right in front of us was something
so much more powerful than we'll ever be.
That image came to me. That image came
to me, and they couldn't see past it.
I know I can do that again.
I can build a wall.
I can build a wall and deceive them.
What are you going to do?
The only thing that we can do.
No.
Not David!
He's not one of them! No!
Multiple suspects. Possible 417.
All units respond and echo your 10-4.
41-A.
41-A, do you copy?
Echo, 41-A. Do you copy?
We're in position. Send them in.
Roger, this is 2-A. I copy.
241 in progress. Stand by.
What are you waiting for?
You got your orders.
Get out!
- More death.
- Survival.
Tell us what arrangements
you have made for us.
Well, I haven't had much time.
It is 11:22.
What are you anxious about?
The arrangements.
Yes. Actually, I...
I left my notebook out in the car.
I wonder if somebody could go out and...
...get my notebook
from the front seat of my car.
No.
I am unable to see what you're thinking.
Well, I'm...
...just wondering who's going to go out
and get the notebook from my car.
- David.
- No.
You are successfully
blocking your thoughts.
You are thinking...
...of a brick wall.
Why do you keep looking at the clock?
Come on.
- We're going now.
- Mother, no.
Take your place.
Stop it! Leave her alone!
Take him!
Go now! Go!
Don't worry.
We'll go someplace where
nobody knows who we are.
Subtitles by SOFTITLER