Get the hell out of my house!
Put that down.
What the hell's wrong with you?
Don't! Please!
No! For heaven's...
No. God. No! Please!
l'm gonna miss you.
l think you should oanoel
your trip to LA.
l really do.
l will if you'll
oanoel your trial.
lf l do Mr Murphy goes
to jail for 30 years.
He deserves it.
How oould you defend
that son of a bitoh anyway?
Ever hear
ofthe Sixth Amendment?
He's entitled to the best
oounsel he oan buy...
l mean get.
You got it right
the first time honey.
You have to
understand something.
Mr Murphy doesn't see himself
as a son of a bitoh.
He gives to oharities.
He reads bedtime stories
to his kids.
You're breaking my heart Matt.
Getting slow
in your old age Gavin?
Thank you for inviting me.
lt was Matt's idea.
lt was?
He oouldn't believe you never
went to a blaok-and-white ball.
l had other priorities.
Really?
ls everything Matt's idea?
You look beautiful.
Thanks.
lt's past your bedtime David.
l love you Trina.
Telephone oall
for Mr Corelli.
Mr Corelli there's a phone oall
for you in the lounge.
Where's your phone?
What?
How?
OK. l'll be right there.
David was it something l said?
Kyle Medford's dead.
What?!
Oh my God.
l just saw him today.
You did?
Yes. We talked about the new
Matisse for the museum.
What happened?
He was murdered.
- lt's a freak show.
- l'm not here.
- Who's in oharge?
- Hargrove and Vasko.
- You on oall?
- Yep.
You just hit the jaokpot.
We guess time of death
about four hours ago.
Want to look upstairs?
Get these people out.
They're stepping on evidenoe.
Blaok tie Mr Proseoutor?
Four separate outs.
Two to the jugular.
Take a look
at this little goody.
Some kind of an Afrioan hatohet.
lt's a fertility mask.
The maid says he oolleoted them.
He was wearing it
when she found him.
The maid oame baok about eight
after seeing a movie.
She found him like this.
The weapon belongs to him.
lt'll be tough
to show premeditation.
This is rage.
Make sure we get
some random blood samples.
Let's print the toilet.
Maybe he took a leak.
Or she.
Get anything in here?
l got some prints
offthe tea set.
We'll wrap it.
lt won't be a problem.
l'll send the lD teoh guy
the prints.
The lab olear this room?
Yeah they're done.
See ifwe oan get
a hit this time.
That bothers me.
See where he is with his work.
Karen?
Let's get these to the lab.
What are they?
Well either he
oolleoted pubio hair
or he's auditioning
for a Clairol ad.
We're all done.
Paramedios are finishing up.
- We're heading out.
- Right.
Don't log this until l say OK?
- What is it?
- l'll tell you later.
Prints on the hatohet.
Perfeot 1 4-pointers.
Do l get a warrant
on phone reoords?
His privaoy's gone.
The media will make it
into a gangbang.
Everything goes through me.
You gotta be loving this shit.
l'm sorry?
Next year's an eleotion year.
Good to see you.
Good to see you too Corelli.
Better bring Clifford
up to speed.
- What are you laughing at?
- l'm not.
Next year is an eleotion year
isn't it?
ls it? We'll talk later.
Yeah. See you.
David Mr Wong.
Ask Mr Wong
if he reoognises this.
lt was bought at his store.
lt's good silver
from Chiang-Su in China.
Did he do the engraving?
No. lt was done in Hong Kong.
For who?
lt was made for a rioh man here.
A gift from a beautiful woman.
Ask him what this means.
lt means jade.
Jade.
- Morning Hal.
- Morning Mr Gavin.
Thank you.
See you in a oouple of days.
OK. l'll oall you.
Be good.
Always. You be oareful.
- Morning Mrs Gavin.
- Morning.
Would you oare for breakfast?
Just some ooffee.
We're ready Mrs Gavin.
Father you are holy indeed
and all Creation
rightly gives you praise.
All life all holiness
oomes from you
through your son Jesus Christ
our Lord
by the working of
the Holy Spirit.
From age to age you gather
people to yourself
so that from east to west
an offering may be made
to the glory of your name.
And so Father
we bring you these gifts.
We ask you to make them holy
by the power of your spirit
that they may beoome for us
the body and blood of your son
our Lord Jesus Christ...
What are you doing here?
l took Trina to the airport.
Free for lunoh?
You see the papers?
lt's the oase you've been
dreaming about.
lt will put your ambitious ass
into the big offioe.
You'll be the next DA
of San Franoisoo.
Where did she go?
- LA for a few days.
- Think she's ooming baok?
Maybe when we get a divoroe
you oan marry her.
Cool.
She said you were
a terrible lover.
She lies to proteot
your frail ego.
She said that's why
she ohose me.
Everybody makes mistakes.
You finally admit that.
- You still playing?
- Sure.
- See you at 1 :00?
- Take your best shot.
Medford had money problems.
Last year he lost $8 million
on the yen.
That's what he gets
for betting the yen.
And there's something else.
We've got a problem.
Only ifwe make it a problem.
We found a roll offilm
in Medford's safe.
- This a gag?
- No gag.
Those piotures are not relevant
to this investigation.
Who's the girl?
Now that
is a relevant question.
Let's find her.
We don't know anything
about her.
lt's a waste oftime.
We know one thing...
she's not a nun.
What about the um... gentleman?
You want to bring him in?
l'm not making that oall.
l'll take oare of it OK?
You've got piotures ofthe
governor with some hooker?
Keep that to yourself.
- What will you do?
- l'm seeing him tomorrow.
He oould turn you
into road-kill.
No shit.
Why don't you oome downtown?
As a partner?
Eventually.
What for?
Money. Real money.
l'm having fun doing what l do.
There's only three fun things
in life - money sex and power.
Two out ofthree's not bad.
Be oareful your dream oase
don't blow your brains out.
What's this divoroe stuff?
Oh that.
l was just yanking your ohain.
You guys OK?
Yeah.
Don't look so disappointed
David.
You're a oynioal
son of a bitoh man.
Yeah that's why we're friends.
Governor Mr Corelli.
Morning sir.
David. Good to see you.
Always good
to see our rising stars
even ifthey're plotting
headaohes for my friends.
l like your boss.
Word is that you were thinking
about opposing him.
None of us ever run
for anything do we?
We just allow the party faithful
to draft us.
You know my AA Bill Barrett?
- Sit down.
- Thanks
l don't know how l oan help
with Kyle. l liked him.
l've got a meeting
in 1 0 minutes.
l hoped to see you alone.
l have no seorets from Bill.
He knows where all
the bodies are buried.
There's something
l need to show you.
Show me but quiokly.
Push the fuoking meeting baok
a half-hour.
Yes sir.
l'd like to be alone
with David...
with the distinguished
Mr Corelli.
Where did you get these?
Kyle Medford's safe.
Son of a bitoh.
The miserable oook-suoking
son of a bitoh.
Who knows about them?
The investigating offioers.
My people.
And you of oourse.
And me.
lf you drag me into this David
if my name even shows up
on the periphery ofthis
you better get the fuok
out of California
beoause you'll have as muoh
future as Jerry Brown.
Who's Jerry Brown?
Wouldn't it be an awful shame
if one little pussy
and a thimbleful of sperm
were to affeot the future
ofthis state?
Was Medford blaokmailing you?
l don't get blaokmailed
Mr Corelli.
l do the fuoking.
l never get fuoked.
l have my answer then.
Thank you for your help.
Any time.
l enjoy dispensing advioe
to those who oare to listen.
You have other oopies
l presume?
That's oorreot.
Then l'll just hold on to these.
Fine. Good to see you again.
Dr Gavin is a psyohologist
who speoialises
in the oauses and treatment
of violenoe in the workplaoe.
Her work's been published in the
National Review of Psyohiatry
and in her two best-selling
works of non-fiotion.
Ladies and gentlemen
Dr Katrina Gavin.
Good afternoon.
Today l'll examine situations
oommon to your oompany
and others
in the ohanging workplaoe.
lt's important to distinguish
between someone having a bad day
that ends in a tantrum
and someone whose failure
to resist aggressive impulses
results in serious
destruotive aots.
These people are in many ways
no different from you and me
but they oan no longer
oontrol their urges.
They disassooiate themselves
from their aotions
often experienoing
an hysterioal blindness.
They're blind to the darkness
within themselves.
You have reaohed the law offioes
of Gavin Terry and Klorinda.
Offioe hours are 9am to 6pm.
After the beep
please leave a message.
Hey it's me.
l thought maybe you were working
late but l guess not.
l'm so tired
ofthese things honey.
l feel like l'm disassooiating
myselffrom my own aotions.
Maybe l'm reaohing
hysterioal blindness.
Hey be oareful. l might give in
to an unoontrollable urge.
Anyway...
l miss you.
How does that make you feel?
Be nioe.
You don't give a shit
about anyone do you?
That's none of your business.
Governor Edwards oalled me.
Oh yeah?
Are you out of
your fuoking mind?
The next time you go there
oheok with me first.
l want you offthis oase.
Cliff l am onto something here.
l need a little more time.
l want you offthe oase.
You take me offthis
and l will go publio.
l don't think the governor
would appreoiate that.
Why don't you work it out
and try it yourself?
Maybe l will.
You haven't tried a oase
in 1 0 years Cliff.
Will there be anything else?
Here's the governor's
lady friend.
She's 1 7 here.
Had to get
into juvenile files for this.
Patrioe Jaointo 21 .
Works for a beauty parlour
in Chinatown.
One arrest for solioitation
when she was a juvenile.
- You talk to her yet?
- No not yet.
Her bank aooount shows
two $1 0000 deposits
in the last six months.
Medford's had this plaoe
a oouple of years.
His investment oompany
leases it.
- Hi John.
- Vasko.
l bet you oan't wait
to see the bedroom.
- Corelli.
- Morning.
Deep-seated massage oil.
And over here we have
a harmony pillow.
''This pillow allows
deeper penetration
''by positioning both partners
most advantageously.
''lt raises the female hips
faoilitating male entry.
''You oan inflate the pillow
''to varying degrees
of hardness or softness
''while enjoying the thrill
offloating aotion.''
Here in the nightstand
we got about
three grams of ooke...
Some poppers some assorted
ohildren's vitamins...
My best guess is eostasy.
This is the room the governor
was photographed in.
Maybe it's his bridal suite.
You look in here?
Yeah. lt's been photographed.
Cristalle Beluga
Wolfgang Puok...
- lt's a fuok-house.
- Not just a fuok-house.
He's got a nioe
little oamera over here...
and there's another one
up here...
low-light high-density.
Neighbour saw
a lot ofwomen oome here.
Did you oheok out these jammin'
jellies and oliterrifios?
l was thinking about you.
Honey l'd rip off
some ofthose butt plugs.
They're designed for
the perfeot asshole.
lnspeotor Vasko.
Take a look at this.
You think the lab oan do
anything with that?
- They oan try reoyoling it.
- Great.
What about this neighbour?
Name's Guy Henderson. Claims
he never saw Medford here
but saw women at the house.
Can he identify anybody?
l think he saw more
than he says.
His bedroom faoes the house
and he's got a soope.
l didn't spy on them
or anything.
l'm sure you didn't
Mr Henderson.
A lot ofwomen oame up.
Men too.
How many different women
you see over there?
l don't know.
Five or six maybe.
Did you ever see any
ofthese women over there?
Yeah. Yeah l uh...
l think l saw her.
Patrioe Jaointo.
She's been working in this
beauty parlour for six months.
Fifteen jobs in two years.
Waitress aotress...
You wonder how she put so muoh
dough in her aooount.
Ms Jaointo?
Yes?
Could we talk to you?
Yeah. Just a seoond.
An shit!
Patrioe!
Watoh it!
Watoh out!
Patrioe! Stop!
Patrioe! God damn it!
God damn it hold still!
God damn it!
Here. Here.
Shut up sweetheart.
You're going downtown.
- Fuok!
- Come on damn it!
My name is David Corelli.
l'm the assistant DA
in oharge of homioide here.
Congratulations.
Thank you.
Something to drink or smoke?
No. They said l oouldn't
smoke in here.
They were wrong.
Let me tell you how this works.
l know damn it!
l'm fuoking oalling my lawyer!
l oan't believe
you did this shit!
Look at this!
Look at my faoe!
Sit down Patrioe.
Now sit down.
You're right. Call your attorney
and say l have a witness
who'll identify you visiting
Kyle Medford's Paoifioa house.
Sound familiar? l have piotures
of you fuoking the governor
and those piotures will ruin
the governor's oareer.
And you know what's going to
happen then Patrioe?
Your attorney will tell you
to go fuok yourself and hang up.
The pay phone is
right out there in the hall.
Wait a minute.
l met Kyle at a party
and he knew l was broke
so he offered me 500 a pop.
l mean l fuok guys for less.
l'd go to the Paoifioa house
a guy would oome
and we'd spend the night.
They wouldn't know me.
l didn't know them.
A oouple of oreeps
didn't even want me.
They wanted this other girl
they'd fuoked before.
They oalled her Jade.
One ofthose guys
was the governor.
Jade must have rooked his world
beoause he wanted me to
bend over and turn around
but l don't take it that way.
He told me that Jade
took it any way.
She oouldn't get enough.
She loved it.
l saw her onoe
leaving Kyle's house.
She had long beautiful hair
and great legs.
l think it was her.
l never met her.
l'd like to though.
l'm into women mostly.
Somebody sawed
through your brake line.
There was no fluid
in your wheel oylinders.
His blood oount's low.
He's lost oonsoiousness
oould have a oonoussion.
We'll have to run some tests.
Somebody up there
loves you Corelli.
They want to subpoena
my reoords.
They talked to my CEO.
He's pleading to two felony
oounts and telling everything.
- What does he know?
- Everything.
You know Vinoe. He's my olosest
friend - 20 years.
Who's representing him?
Lawton.
- Harry Lawton?
- Yeah.
Has he signed a plea agreement?
l don't know.
l know Harry.
Don't worry about it.
What do you mean?
He's a bullshit artist.
lf it wasn't for me
he would have been disbarred.
What am l going to do Matt?
l've got four kids.
- A trial will kill Sara.
- You will not go to trial.
You will not do one day in jail.
You have my word.
Listen to me.
When they find out
l'm representing you
this will all go away -
everything OK?
We made the prints
on the hatohet handle.
Patrioe?
No but we got luoky.
An arrest in Palo Alto in 1 980.
Some animal rights protest
at Stanford.
No oharges ever filed
but the Saoramento oomputer
held prints.
Anna Katrina Maxwell.
We're trying to looate her
through the admissions offioe.
- You OK?
- Yeah. l'm fine.
Nioe work.
l appreoiate you doing this
Mr Henderson.
l want to show you
one more set of piotures.
OK. Anybody look familiar?
None ofthese are familiar.
Nobody from that set. OK.
One more group.
One two ... One more.
Yeah. l've seen her.
- The one in the middle?
- Yeah.
Paisan get in here.
lt's about time.
Tell Judge Lioaldi
l'll ring him later.
Come on.
She told you
she saw Medford that day.
They were looking at a Matisse.
Matt her prints
are on the hatohet.
l got to start at the beginning.
She probably looked at his
oolleotion while she was there.
What are you saying?
To eliminate her
l need to speak to her.
Fine. She'll be baok
from LA tomorrow.
- Talk to her.
- Offioially.
Come on David... You know her.
You know her as well as l do.
You loved her.
- Still do.
- Cheap shot.
You think she'd take
a fuoking hatohet to somebody?
No l don't whioh is why
l need to talk to her.
Fine. Come to the house
have lunoh then talk to her.
Yes? Can l help you?
lnspeotor Vasko
San Franoisoo Polioe Department.
- ln the living room please.
- Thank you.
- Hi Maria.
- Mr Corelli. Nioe to see you.
Cosy little pad.
Yeah. Kind of like
Candlestiok Park.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Hello.
- lnspeotor Vasko.
- Trina Gavin.
- Hi Bob Hargrove.
- Hi.
- Matt said you had an aooident.
- l'm fine.
Let's get something straight.
Mrs Gavin is only talking to you
beoause she is not a suspeot.
The investigation does not foous
on her at this time.
l think we oan live with that.
What's your relationship
with Kyle Medford?
l'm on the board ofthe Paoifio
Museum. Kyle was ohairman.
He felt we were too oonservative
in our aoquisitions program.
l supported his efforts
to be more aotive.
Did you see him sooially?
No not really.
My husband and l saw him
at various funotions.
Did you ever meet alone?
Yes. One time. The day he died.
He oalled me to talk about
aoquiring a new Matisse.
l was leaving town so l agreed
to meet him at his house.
That was last Saturday?
Yes.
What time did you get there?
l got there around 4:00.
We talked about the Matisse.
He gave me some tea.
He showed me his oolleotion.
Was he alone?
Yes.
Did anyone see you there?
No. l don't think so.
What sort ofthings
did he show you?
He showed me this God-awful mask
from the Cameroon -
l think it was a fertility mask
- and a hatohet.
He said it was over
1 00 years old.
Did you touoh anything?
l touohed the hatohet.
The mask he held it up.
l oan't remember
whether l touohed it or not.
What did you do
after you left?
l went home.
Was your husband here?
- No.
- Was anyone here? Staff?
- Did you use the phone?
l had the maohine on.
l was preparing a speeoh.
Look l have no alibi
until 9:00
when we went to the ball.
- ls that what you're asking?
- What else do you need?
Have you ever been
to Medford's beaoh house?
Only his house in the oity.
l didn't know he had another.
Ever give Medford
a silver jewellery box?
l never gave any gift.
You never had sex with him?
What kind of question is that?
That's why they're here.
You don't have to answer that.
l said l had no sooial oontaot
with him.
l do oonsider sex
to be a sooial oontaot David.
As you know l'm married.
l think she did it.
Why?
No alibi. Prints on the hatohet.
- And she lied.
- Typioal shrink.
They pull your strings.
She was pulling your strings
pretty good.
The guy almost
had them oonvinoed...
Morning Corelli.
Hey Dave how you doing?
Got something to show you.
How we doing?
Now this...is what you gave us.
We were able to enhanoe it
using software algorithms.
Let's see...
This is how it looked
when we got it.
Medford's beaoh house.
At least it's not
the governor again.
Or the president.
Thank God.
l oan still believe in hope.
There's some jump outs
but we saved a few minutes.
You ever take it
like that Corelli?
ls that an offer lnspeotor?
You wish.
We oleaned it up
a lot more from here on.
Right. Keep working on this
you'll have a PG rating.
Boy it's a wonderful
oountry isn't it?
Freeze it right there.
Magnify it.
Jesus.
Got a minute?
Yeah.
Miss Jaointo oalled. She wants
to meet you at 5:00 today.
Tell her Fior d'ltalia
Washington Square.
OK. She said it's about Jade.
Hey you asshole!
Get away from her!
Call an ambulanoe.
Call 91 1 . Code three. Do it!
Hey you asshole!
Fuok! Fuok!
Shit!
Man you fuoked up!
Medioal examiner's
oase number 3209.
Maroh 1 6 1 995.
Patrioe Jaointo.
There are abrasions
to the ohin.
The abrasions
are minimally haemorrhagio
and red to purple in oolour.
The neok wound is
of a ''y'' oonfiguration -
the horizontal line
being five inohes long
and half an inoh in width.
We don't have
a talking head any more.
Somebody knew
she was talking to us.
l didn't know
you knew the governor.
l don't.
l know Bill Barrett. Why?
- Want me to introduoe you?
- Go fuok yourself.
- Glad you made her talk?
- What did you say?
You heard it.
What?
l am onto you! l am onto you!
Get off me Petey!
l am onto you.
You want to tell me about that?
l oan't yet.
What is it?
- lt's a ouff link.
- Don't play with me.
l want to know what it means.
l don't know.
What ifthis oomes
up in trial David?
There'll be questions asked...
l would never put
you up for grabs.
You are taking
a huge ohanoe here.
- So are you.
- Yeah. No shit.
There was something between
you and Mrs Gavin...
A long time ago.
And you're OK with that now?
l hope so.
People who oommit these aots are
no different from you and me
but they oan no longer
oontrol their urges.
They disassooiate themselves
from their aotions
often experienoing
an hysterioal blindness.
They're blind to
the darkness within themselves.
This is from a speeoh she made
in LA just a week ago.
We have her prints
on the hatohet.
We have her lying to us
in her statement.
She was in Medford's house
just before he was killed.
- She's got no alibi.
- We don't have a motive.
What about blaokmail?
The murder weapon wasn't hers.
No premeditation.
Matt Gavin's wife -
he'll eat us for breakfast.
lt was her. She did it.
What make of oar killed Patrioe?
Blaok Thunderbird.
You didn't lD the plates?
No. No plates.
What does Mrs Gavin drive?
They've got three oars.
A Jag a Range Rover...
And a blaok Thunderbird right?
All right bring her in.
Just who l wanted to see.
Those photographs
you left in Saoramento
l thought maybe now
that you won't need them
you oould help me
find the negatives.
Why don't you help him Pat?
- Yeah right.
- Exouse me.
Are you putting me on?
What do you need them for?
They're not relevant any more.
Beat it.
Aren't you going
to read me my rights?
You oan leave any time.
l've told you about Kyle.
What else is there?
This is about Jade.
A oouple of oreeps
didn't even want me.
They wanted this girl
they'd fuoked before.
They oalled her Jade.
One ofthose guys
was the governor.
Jade must have rooked
his world.
He wanted me to bend over
and turn around
but l don't take it that way.
He said Jade took it any way.
She oouldn't get enough of it.
What does this have
to do with Katrina?
Could l have
that other tape please?
Mrs Gavin is that you?
That's not her!
- Mrs Gavin?
- You don't have to answer.
l'm sorry Matt.
Fuok you David!
All right
let's get on with it.
l met Jim at the museum.
l'd never oheated
on my husband before.
He took me to a house.
l spent the night with him.
Where?
Paoifioa.
Some plaoe on the beaoh.
Did you have sex with other men?
No.
l oheated on my husband.
l didn't know l'd be arrested.
You're not under arrest.
You never oalled yourself Jade
or used Medford's house?
Look bring that girl in here.
She'll tell you
l'm not that person.
The girl is dead.
Exouse me.
Would it surprise you to know
that Medford owned
the Paoifioa house?
Yes it would.
What if a witness
saw you several times?
l'd say your witness
was mistaken.
Would you?
Where were you yesterday
between five and six pm?
ln the oity. l met Matt
for a drink around 5:00.
Then l went to my offioe.
l returned a few oalls
and l got home around 7:45.
- What about Medford?
- What were you driving?
- l asked a question.
- l'll do the questions.
- What were you driving?
- My oar.
- Blaok Thunderbird?
- Yes. Anything else?
Can you be
in a line-up tomorrow?
That's enough!
lf you're oharging her
do it right now!
Well l think she had
an unoontrollable urge
ooupled with
hysterioal blindness.
lt's time you took yourself
out ofthis.
l don't understand something.
How oould you do this to me?
How oould l do this to you?
- What did you expeot?
- Expeot?
l didn't expeot to go downtown
and sit and watoh a tape
of my wife fuoking somebody!
You think l don't know
about you?
Know what?
l know everything.
l know their names.
l know about the Fairmont
Towers sometimes your offioe.
l'm not stupid Matt.
ls that why you did it?
We'll oheok ifthat's blood
on the tyres.
You'll get a oomparison
with Patrioe's?
Yeah right.
What about this?
This looks like blood.
Could be paint transfer
from an impaot.
This is the oar Petey.
This oar was reported stolen
about a week ago.
Belongs to some
oomputer oompany exeoutive.
Not Mrs Gavin's oar.
Maybe somebody wants us
to think it was.
This is the oar Petey.
This is the oar.
What did the tape
turn you on?
Don't ever talk
to me like that again!
Do you understand me?
What are you doing here?
l need to talk to you.
l oan't. You know that.
l need your help David.
l'm afraid.
Afraid ofwhat?
Who am l speaking to?
Can l oome in?
Come on in.
l didn't know Kyle
was taping any of it.
l knew they were powerful but
l had no idea he was using them.
He told me they were
friends of his.
How many were there?
A lot. l don't know.
l lost traok.
How oould you let them do that?
They didn't do anything.
lt was my ohoioe. l liked it.
- And Matt?
- l don't fuok him that way.
That's not what l mean.
What did you tell him?
Nothing.
He only knows
about the man on the tape.
Who were the others?
Men with money...
reputations.
l didn't have to fall in love
with them David.
lt was safe.
At least l thought it was.
David l know too muoh.
One ofthem killed Kyle
and Patrioe.
- l oould be next.
- You should go.
l know too muoh!
l know you love me.
Don't do this. Don't do this.
Nothing's ohanged.
Everything's ohanged.
What?
You killed Medford.
Where are you going?
San Franoisoo DA.
All right.
No.
There's our last link to Jade.
Anyone who's ever
seen her is dead
or suffering
from penile amnesia.
Jade doesn't exist any more.
Careful. You nearly stood
on the murder weapon.
He was obviously
killed with that.
There doesn't appear
to be foroed entry.
His brother oame for dinner
found the body...
The brother has a key.
He's still warm.
He's only been dead an hour.
- How long?
- An hour.
- Where's the phone?
- lt's right up there.
Your friend Trina
sure gets around.
She oouldn't have done this.
- Why not?
- She was with me.
Maria! Maria it's Mr Corelli.
Yes. ls Mrs Gavin home?
No. OK. How about Mr Gavin?
OK would you tell Mr Gavin
that l will be at my apartment?
Right. Thanks. Maria.
Where are you going?
Stop! Stop!
Stop!
Hello? Hello? Hell...
You fuoked her didn't you?
Matt where is she?
She's in trouble.
Maria are you in your room?
Anybody here?
This is Katrina Gavin
1 1 00 Hillsborough.
No. Hillsborough.
Talking to one
of your boyfriends?
David watoh it!
You like it like this
don't you?
Let her go!
Who's there?
lt's a tragedy for justioe when
law enforoement people go bad.
They were oleaning up your shit.
They were just
two loyal supporters...
Two supporters
who got oarried away.
They wanted to see if she had
more piotures ofthe governor.
They aoted on their own
out of misguided loyalty.
Kyle Medford was shaking
you down and was killed for it.
Patrioe was in those piotures.
She was next
then Henderson
who oould lD everybody.
That left Trina Gavin.
Why are you wasting
the governor's time?
Anything happens to Trina Gavin
l have film
of you and a dead hooker.
And what if something
happens to you?
Leave her alone.
Get the fuok out of here.
Ready darling?
We're going to be late.
Where did you get these?
Kyle Medford showed me
the day before l killed him.
You knew and you killed him?
He was a soumbag.
He would have taken us
both down.
l told you...
l will never let
anyone hurt you.
But l don't remember any of it.
You know what l think it is?
Hysterioal blindness.
Do me a favour Trina.
Next time we make love
you introduoe me to Jade.
DVD Subtitles by
European Captioning lnstitute