Binh!
We should get married.
Our ages are well-matched.
You want someone
to make you dinner every day.
That was the idea.
What do I get out of it?
It will be a good arrangement.
I will be like a father to your children.
Everyone will have enough to eat,
even pig face here.
Why is he so grouchy?
If you marry me, I'll fix up the house.
You have to clean it!
Hurry!
I need it tonight.
Come!
Hurry! The celebration starts soon!
...since the liberation, significant progress
has been made in the spirit of Ho Chi Minh.
Will you marry Pham?
Who knows?
What did my mother say about the GI?
Your father?
Yes.
Why do you ask now?
- She must have said something.
- She cried about him.
That's all?
He had very big feet.
First, he tracks dirt all over the house...
then he takes off his leather shoes.
He puts up his big feet
so that everyone can see.
Is she alive?
If she marries Pham...
there won't be room for you.
She is alive.
In the big city.
- Why are you always angry with him?
- I can't bear the sight of him.
He's not one of us. I don't know why
he doesn't go to where he belongs.
And for my forefathers,
I pray for their souls...
and that we someday will be united.
For myself, I ask that my actions
will not harm others.
I do not leave with a bitter heart...
but with hope that I will have a better future.
You're Bui Doi, aren't you?
Go home. There's nothing for you here.
Consider yourself lucky.
I'm looking for Mai.
She used to work here.
She's my mother.
Does Mai live here?
Go away, beggar!
I know you.
You are very big, my brother.
Where is Mother?
She's at work...
in the big house.
If you have a problem,
don't bother our guests with it.
Mai! You don't work
in the dining room anymore.
Give me your uniform. Hurry.
Good evening. Do you know who I am?
It's me.
It's Binh.
I am so sorry, my son.
Mai.
Will you wait?
Thank you.
You're hungry?
What are you thinking?
I am thinking...
that I don't know you.
You know, we were married...
in a church.
He was Christian?
He never said...
but he wanted a priest.
Where is he? What happened to him?
He was here one day...
then he was gone.
Just like that.
Killed?
He was just gone.
It was a hard time for everyone.
Madam, if you have a moment.
It's her son.
He will be a good worker...
alongside her...
to replace the houseboy.
Far greater value than what you pay now.
Let me look at you.
Your mother is attractive.
How did you get to be so ugly?
I know you are generous, madam.
I know that you know
what it means to love a son, and...
He will shine my son's shoes.
The rugs need beating.
He can assist his mother in that.
And the fence has to be painted.
Work hard. Help your mother.
She's suffered a lot because of you.
Working hard?
Let me give you a hand.
Please, no. I must finish,
or your mother will be angry.
Is he Tam's father?
How dare you ask me that?
- You were gone a long time.
- I'm sorry.
Quiet!
- You have shortchanged me.
- No.
First he steals from me, then he lies.
That's what you get
for bringing such trash into the house!
I don't know how to protect you.
I have shamed you. I'll go back to Hoa Nam.
No. I'm proud of you.
Just stay out of his way.
Binh, help me.
Careful!
Put that down!
Thief! Bastard thief!
You must take Tam as well.
- Come with us, Mother!
- No.
I have a friend.
He knows of boats, special boats.
It will just be enough for the two of you.
This is my wedding certificate.
On it is an address in Houston, Texas.
He may help, but ask for nothing.
Keep a good heart.
Don't let Tam forget me.
You're going to go on a trip with Binh.
Mama, where will you be?
I'll come. Just not now.
Do what Binh says.
Mother will be along soon.
We'll all be together in America.
Where you going?
- America.
- What will you do there?
Sell shoes. Everyone needs shoes.
You have family there?
He's not Vietnamese.
He's a big American.
Tam, come here!
Tam!
Where were you going?
- Malaysia.
- Nobody tries for Malaysia.
America is a nice place.
Have you been in prison before
for political reasons?
For criminal reasons?
Was your father American?
- He Vietnamese.
- Open your mouth.
- What is his name?
- Duc.
You can put your shirt on.
Why do you leave Vietnam?
It's to your benefit to tell the truth.
Come.
Don't worry. Be here when you get back...
just like everyone else.
I'll be back soon.
English?
Good! My English very good.
My name Chingmy.
- What this place?
- "What this place?" This place hell!
- Me Chinese. What you?
- Vietnamese.
Vietnamese.
Why you here?
You know, boat from China. Sink off coast.
Many people go underwater, too.
- How I leave?
- You want to leave? Good!
No one leaves here. No country wants you.
You grow old. God take you a better place.
Not yet.
Or you can like me. I am a very clever guy.
I can go under the wall.
- There other way?
- Sure!
You grow wings, you can fly over the wall.
Or you can like Ling.
Ling go over wall on her back.
No?
Oh, thank you.
She earn big money.
She can buy her way out!
If I could, I would.
But, you know, I'm not pretty like her.
You want to leave?
Did you buy the birthday presents?
Tam, time to go.
You can help me with the food.
No.
- How you come here?
- Take boat.
Where you go?
- America.
- America, huh?
Beautiful country.
You like America?
What you do there?
Sell shoe.
- Where you from?
- Why?
I from Pingyao. Small village, North China.
Father leave when I very small.
I come here with man.
One day he say to me:
"I get you out.
First, go Hong Kong. Good life. "
Mother still in China?
- More good she think I dead.
- Why?
I shame her.
I'm hungry.
We'll try to find something to eat
after we wash.
I wash it for you.
- Why you like that?
- Like what?
You no look at me.
I look at you.
Never play like this.
Other mothers say, "No play with him.
"He have face of enemy. "
We must get out, Tam and me.
Leave here, take money. Big money.
I have dollars.
I think you in shoe store, when you gone.
Put on.
You leave this place.
I no leave you.
Boat come tonight.
How you know?
Boat go to America.
You have $2,000, they take you.
In America, you work for them. Pay rest.
How you know?
I no have $2,000.
Almost done.
Clean, very clean.
Get up!
Back!
Everyone back!
Get your things. Let's go!
You go first.
- No, come now.
- Too small for three. You go.
Here, $2,000. For you, for Tam.
You go now. Boat won't wait. Go.
You go.
This boat no leave without Ling.
I no swim.
I already dead inside.
In water, also dead outside. So you go.
Please.
Is Mommy on the boat?
Hold them there.
Thought you were from Miami.
Where'd you find these, then? In the ocean?
Okay, let's see the money.
Money, money, money!
Come down. You speak English?
You read?
Good.
The passage is gonna cost $8,000,
for the three of you.
It's a family discount.
- You work for the rest in US.
- In camp, tells me $2,000.
In camp, they're salesmen.
I'm a businessman.
$2,000 each for you and the lady,
$4,000 for the kid.
Why boy no cheap? Only small.
Eat little.
He's not a worker, is he?
He just takes up space.
Little space.
Big space in your mind.
$2,000, 50, 60, 70...
$2,773.
You can swim to America.
Be my guest, if that's your wish.
Where's the rest?
Have no more.
"Have no more?" Have no travel. Goodbye.
Have no more!
Sign your name.
No read Chinese.
You can sign your name
in whatever you want.
- Sign it.
- What it say?
Well, it says you'll give me $2,773 now.
When you get there, you'll all work,
including the kid.
If you're not lazy, you'll be free to leave
in a year. In your case, two.
We'll provide a place to stay,
food, and work.
I think you should sign.
Where boat going? Houston?
This isn't a taxi.
Everybody on deck.
Ladies and gentlemen, welcome aboard.
You're our most valued passengers.
We want you to arrive healthy
and fit to work.
So...
don't fight. Don't waste food.
We have enough, but not enough to waste.
You'll all be rich in America.
I'm told it's easy.
Come on.
Smells bad.
In America, always smell good.
- Why?
- They clean all day.
- People make money that way.
Lots and lots of money.
Cleaners have big car.
I want to clean in America.
Go to back of line.
We pay for food.
You no pay me.
Thank you.
My brother need water.
Don't look at me, chappie.
Come down.
You think this is funny?
You think he's ugly?
Be nice.
Come with me.
Now listen to me.
These are my passengers. Mine, not yours.
If I lose any of them, including you...
I lose money.
Are you scared of me?
You know, I've been to your country.
I've been to both of your countries,
and I'll tell you something.
You will always be out of place
wherever you go.
Yes, I know.
And poor.
You should think about working for me.
I can give you a job.
- You like looking at me?
- Yes.