Have you ever witnessed
Frank Mantajano kill anyone?
I've heard about it,
but it's not an everyday occurrence.
- Have you witnessed him kill anyone?
- People say things. You pick up on it.
It gets around the block.
Have you ever witnessed Frank
Mantajano in any kind of illegal activity?
Have you ever witnessed him
in any kind of illegal activity?
Again, as far as I'm concerned,
the guy did right by me.
- Who hired you?
- I would assume it's Frank.
- How long have you worked for him?
- We ran together in younger days.
- We dated the same girl.
We had the same friends on the streets.
That kind of stuff. Things happen.
Somebody ordered a takeout.
Good night.
Your answers have to come faster.
This is a federal case.
You've got to have your ducks in a row
if we're gonna nail Frank Mantajano. OK?
- Can we take a break? I'm hungry.
- OK.
But remember, you're gonna be
on the stand for hours at a time.
You've got to watch your body language,
your facial expressions, your posture.
To be effective, the committee
has to like you. Get it?
I got it.
- Got any Szechwan chicken over there?
- Could you get him some chicken?
Mr Paine, does the Attorney General's
office have any final remarks?
May I remind the committee that Frank
Mantajano is an execrable criminal,
moving Cuban organized crime
into America.
I object to that characterization
of my client.
The Attorney General's office is making
accusations, disguising them as truth.
The fact is, my client
has never been convicted of any crime.
- But he will be, Mr Foster.
- That's enough, gentlemen.
This committee will stand in recess
until 10am Monday,
at which time I hope that the Attorney
General's office will have evidence
to back up their accusations.
- I'll produce it all right.
- Good. We're adjourned.
Our witness is dead.
My witness is dead?
- Mantajano's people got to him.
- He was in a safe house. How?
Some Cuban delivered him
a carton of Chinese food full of C-4.
I just told the Committee on Organized
Crime and 60 million TV viewers
that I would produce a witness
in 72 hours.
I understand,
but what are we going to do about it?
"We"? As a federal marshal,
you are directly responsible
for the custody and protection
of all witnesses.
So the problem is,
you got my witness killed.
You do something about it
by Monday morning
or start thinking about
an early retirement.
Sweet little kitty.
Got them virgin hands.
Cute little kitty cat like you
ain't supposed to be shovellin' ditches.
This here is man's work.
Hey, bitch, are you listenin' to me?
You know, I'm lookin' for a little pussy
like you to keep me warm at night.
Now that's using your head. Come on!
Don't you think he's had enough, convict?
You been here one day.
You wanna fight everybody?
- I ain't supposed to be here.
- Ain't nobody supposed to be here.
Break it up!
Get your big ass out of the way.
- Causin' problems already, Piper?
- I had nothin' to do with it.
- It's true.
- Shut up, Dodge.
- Wait a minute.
- I said shut the fuck up!
You guys need an attitude adjustment.
I got just the thing for you.
All right, Kevin.
Kinda like a wedding ring.
I now pronounce you
convict... and convict.
Now get the fuck on the bus.
You move when I say you move.
Right.
Come on.
- Should we break it up now?
- No.
Just keep a lookout
and watch for my signal.
Gimme the keys to the bus.
- What's goin' on?
- How should I know?
Radio for help.
- Let's go.
- I'm not goin' anywhere.
You move when I say you move!
Here, pussy, pussy...
Let's get outta here.
- Anything else, Gib?
- I ain't got nowhere to put it, honey.
- Hey, Gib.
- What's goin' on, Sandra?
You. Lieutenant Clark says meet him
at Gwinnett County Detention Center.
- He say why?
- Nope, but he's waitin' on ya.
How are the ribs today?
Same as they were yesterday,
and the day before, and the day before.
- I'll see ya.
- See ya, Gib.
Get me a half a slab of rib
- and a peach cobbler.
- You got it.
- Hey, Gib.
- Afternoon, Warden. What's up?
Prison break.
- Who fled?
- There's three of 'em took off.
Paul Milliner, Charles Piper
and some kid named Dodge.
Dodge? That explains why
the Lieutenant called me out here.
I busted him about nine months back.
- What's he done now?
- From what we can gather,
Piper and Dodge got into a brawl,
distracting the guard,
and this fuck Milliner
grabbed Kevin's gun.
The three of 'em started shootin'. They
killed Kevin, Bailey and two other guards.
- Dodge killed someone?
- Afternoon, Gibson. Warden Nichols.
This is Marshal Schiller,
Attorney General's office.
Welcome to the land
of CNN and Coca-Cola.
We don't want to be on CNN and hope not
to get too thirsty capturing these fugitives.
The Marshal will head the manhunt.
Since you arrested Dodge,
you can give Schiller a jump-start
on where to look for these boys.
He's probably headin' back to Atlanta,
about 30 miles from here.
If we put out an all-points and local news
profiles, we should have 'em by nightfall.
Let me talk to you for a minute, Matthew.
This guy Schiller is no regular cop. He
was sent by the Attorney General's office.
They want a press blackout on this.
- We do want to catch these boys, right?
- Damn right.
But we don't want police reports
all over the six o'clock news.
So I'm supposed to play Seeing Eye dog
to the Attorney General's trigger man
without askin' what, when or why.
My job is to make sure you give
these boys what they need. Are we clear?
- Yeah. We're clear.
- Good.
Now let's get Marshal Schiller
on these fugitives' trail.
Right.
Hold up a second.
Shit. What are you doing?
Shit.
Are you done?
Not unless you wanna
wipe it off for me, convict.
Let's go.
If we position ourselves here,
they'll be cornered.
If we do that, we leave this whole area
along the river open to the city.
I've been doing this ten years.
They're headed for the border.
They want to leave Georgia
as fast as possible.
- Why do you think they're all together?
- Let's mount up and move out.
You heard the man. Let's do it.
Never seen nothin' like it in 20 years.
What's a US marshal
like Schiller doin' here
on a local manhunt
for some minor criminal?
These guys shot up a whole road crew.
They should be shot for what they done.
- I'm not sure they done anything.
- What is that supposed to mean?
I brought Dodge in for hackin' into
some telephone computer system.
They only gave him 18 months. He's
served nine. Why would he break out?
All I know is he left a good friend of mine
dead out on that road.
That's my point. What was Dodge
doin' there in the first place?
Just a prison ordinance.
A routine directive.
You make the directives, Dale.
Road crews, chain gangs, are reserved
for felons with
five-year sentences or more.
So what was Dodge doin' on that road?
We got a call
from the Attorney General's office.
They wanted Dodge out there.
- Why would they want him out there?
- I don't know.
They've been tryin' to question him
since we had him in lockup.
You got to believe me, Gib.
I had no idea this was gonna happen.
Attention all units. Suspects spotted...
There. Schiller's closin' in on 'em now.
- Stop the car.
- What?
Stop the goddamn car!
- Come on!
- Hold up.
- What's the problem?
- You're draggin' me like a rag doll.
You almost ripped my arm off
twice back there. Shit.
- We gotta get into a rhythm.
- What the fuck you know about rhythm?
- I'm a foster child, raised by the state.
- What's your point?
There was this caretaker who was
like a father to me. His name was Titus.
He taught me that everybody
lives their life according to a rhythm.
You make love to a rhythm.
Your heart beats to a rhythm.
If we're gonna run together,
we gotta get into the same rhythm.
I got your rhythm, convict.
If we hurry, we can get you back
in time for evenin' chow.
Goddamn.
Something's down there. Check it out.
Wait! Look.
- In there?
- Yeah. Let's go.
- How do we get to the state line?
- We don't wanna go there.
Why not?
Come on!
Didn't you see "The Fugitive"?
The first thing Tommy Lee Jones did
was set up roadblocks at the state line.
- That's your plan, Dr Kimble?
- I ain't got a plan.
- I'm trying to figure this shit out as we go.
- No shit!
- All right. I say we give ourselves up.
- What?!
- You're jokin', right?
- I look like I'm jokin'?
- It was your idea to run.
- People shoot at me, I run.
Your white ass didn't know shit.
- So you don't like white people now?
- No, I just don't like you.
I got nothin' against whites. I just ain't
had many good experiences with 'em.
Fuck! I was out in six months.
Six months I was goin' home.
Yeah? Forget about that six months shit.
You can add on another 12 to 18 months
because you ran, no matter what you say.
You are a convict.
Nothing is ever gonna change that.
That's your reality, baby, not mine.
My reality and yours are the same.
We're both fucked.
- Not me. I take my chances.
- Not with my life, you don't.
All right, all right! Hold up.
- How much?
- What?
- Name your price.
- You ain't got shit to bargain with.
- I got more than you think.
- What do you mean?
I'm talkin' about five million dollars.
I got your attention now, convict?
What do you think I was locked up for?
Runnin' a red light?
I hit a major corporation for five million.
- You're lyin'.
- Am I?
All right! Hold on. Why would I lie?
One: to keep me from kickin' your ass.
Two: same reason.
Three: prison life
ain't exactly worked out for you.
That's why I'm offerin' you
a million dollars.
More than you'll ever see in your life.
Yeah. I'll be lookin' over my shoulder
for the rest of my life, too.
What else will you do when you get out?
Work for 7-Eleven?.
They ain't hiring convicts.
You think about that.
- All right, I want half.
- Half? Fuck you! This ain't divorce.
No. We married, baby.
For better, for worse, in sickness
and in health, till death do us part.
The chopper's comin' back around,
Dodge. You better hurry up.
Come on, baby. Say "I do. "
Shit! All right - half.
- But after that, that is it! We are even.
- No.
Now we're even.
- Where are we?
- I don't know.
- Which way?
- This way.
What?
Nothin'.
- What the hell is that?
- Sounds like a train.
Run!
Let's go!
- We won't make it.
- We have to jump.
I can't swim!
I never met a white boy
that couldn't swim.
- Keep your head up.
- OK.
First thing I'm gonna do
when this shit is over
is set my ass
in a steamy, hot, bubble bath.
You know?
I hope you choke
and drown on the bubbles.
What are you doin'
chained to that white boy?
You know, I've been askin' myself
the same damn question all day.
Now look here, chief.
I know what you're thinkin', boss.
You got two convicts. If you turn us in,
maybe you'll make some money.
Might even get your face on TV. Right?
Maybe I oughta shoot your black ass
right now and call it a day.
Why not? In fact, why not have
an old-fashioned lynchin'?
Y'all still hang niggers
in Georgia, dontcha?
He's such a kidder!
Would you excuse me?
- He's got a gun.
- And we don't.
Quit provoking him.
He doesn't want to shoot us. Right?
He won't shoot you, but he damn sure
wants to blow a hole in my black ass.
- Dontcha, boss?
- Hold on. We don't want any trouble.
Don't do anything you'll regret later.
Now, I can see that you're a fine,
upstanding member of your community.
And, despite our appearance,
I can assure you we are not bad people.
- Fuck this. He's a redneck.
- Don't say that!
- He is. Show him your neck.
- Shut up.
Show him your neck!
- What the hell's wrong with you?
- What?
- Didn't you see "Deliverance"?
- We're alive, ain't we?
- What if he'd shot sooner?
- Then we'd be dead.
- Shit.
- What?
- We got a problem.
He ain't breathin'.
- Shit.
- What?
He's havin' a heart attack.
- Turn the radio down.
- This is a good song.
It'd be nice to hear the cops
before they get to us.
All right, all right.
We gotta get him to a hospital.
Where is it?
It's comin' up. We'll get there.
Where'd you learn first aid, anyway?
In the joint. CPR.
They got courses like that.
A Suzuki.
Nice bikes.
While you take that bubble bath,
I'll get a Ducati 916 racing motorcycle.
- Ride off into the sunset.
- I won't be sorry to see your ass go.
Shit! Look at this.
- Put that away.
- We can shoot the cuffs off.
Don't point it at me!
Gimme that before you hurt yourself.
How would I know?
I never even held a gun.
Then how the helI'd you rob somebody
for five million dollars?
Hackin', my friend. Hackin'.
- Computers?
- You got it.
I got the sweetest Mac 5300.
16 megabytes, 750 hard drive.
So fast, it's like the Ducati of computers.
On the Internet,
my call name is the Cyberthug.
- What's so funny?
- That ain't no robbery, man.
One of these, a ski mask -
that's a robbery.
I didn't get busted for robbery. All right?
I illegally accessed
the phone company's computer system.
- You robbed Ma Bell?
- No, not exactly.
Ma Bell just gave me a little help.
I used the phone company's computer to
access the accounts of a big corporation.
- Which one?
- A greedy one.
They took and never gave back.
I taught 'em a lesson.
- Real nice, but how'd you get the money?
- Once I was in, it was easy.
I transferred money from their accounts
into a dummy company I had set up.
I wrote a corporate cheque to a friend.
He closed the account, gave me the cash.
Very smooth.
So who's your friend?
- You writin' a book?
- I wanna know who's sharin' my money.
Everything was planned, sir.
I can't control it if some convict
starts shootin' up the road crew.
He won't be shootin' anybody else.
The most important thing is
Dodge is on the move and we are on him.
The locals have no idea what's goin' on.
Politicians put a lot of pressure
on you with this, huh?
- You mean the Attorney General's office.
- Right.
- Who said I was talkin' to them?
- You just did.
- You think you're pretty smart, don't you?
- Nope. Just average for a country boy.
- Did you notify the fugitive's next of kin?
- They're not a priority on my list.
What exactly is a priority on your list?
Bringing these fugitives to justice.
My hunch is
they're more pawns than fugitives.
It seems to me your hunches are more
like a Hardy Boys mystery than real life.
And I think that
you are spittin' in the wind.
And you know what they say
about spittin' in the wind.
It can blow back in your face.
- Come on. Hurry up, man.
- I'm fixing him so he won't fall over.
Pop the brake.
- Come on, before somebody sees us.
- All right. Ready? One, two, three.
Push.
Shit!
What the hell's wrong with you, kid?
You almost got yourself killed.
Forget that. Why do you guys
have those chains on?
Go on, beat it. You bother me.
- Son of a bitch. They did it!
- What?
They built a recreational centre
and a playground.
- Who?
- Brigantine International.
- That's who I hit for the $25 million.
- You said five, you lyin' SOB.
When I was in their computer system,
I hit 'em for 25.
But I only kept five.
I gave 20 to charity. Like this.
Shit! That's nice, Robin Hood,
but we gotta fled. Come on.
Don't do anything stupid!
- It's OK. Just drive.
- Look, guys.
I have groceries in the back
and about $20.
- Take it and get out.
- You don't tell us. We tell you.
Come on. Put that away. All right?
We don't want your money or your car.
We just want a ride.
- Let's go! Drive.
- All right. All right.
- Where to?
- I don't know.
- Where do you live?
- Three blocks that way.
- OK. We'll go there.
- My house?
- Let's go!
- All right, all right!
But I'm warning you, it's messy.
- Excuse me.
- Hi.
- Workin' hard as usual, Jocelyn?
- Well, not as usual.
And what are you doin' here?
Got a problem with your insurance?
No. I'm here tryin' to figure something out.
- What are you tryin' to figure out?
- Well, I busted this kid, name of Dodge,
for hackin' into
a telephone company's computer system.
They've also listed a bunch of
other companies and different offences.
He used the phone company's computer
to get into other companies' systems.
That's what I figured. But these people
here, Brigantine International,
they didn't list any offences,
nor did they press charges.
- Let me check on Central's computer.
- That would be wonderful.
Someone else accessed
this information today.
- Who was that?
- Savannah Detective Agency.
According to this,
they're a holding company
for corporations with offshore accounts
in Europe and South America.
Can you figure out on that thing
who owns Brigantine International?
The primary stockholder
is a Frank Mantajano.
- Manta-hano.
- Whatever.
Beautiful vessel, isn't she?
- Would you like a drink?
- No. I don't drink.
Tobacco?
I want to congratulate you on your...
Chinese cooking.
I enjoy my work.
We want to commission you
to do another job.
We want you to locate Luke Dodge,
a convict that escaped
from a Georgia prison today.
We need to find him before Monday.
He has a computer disk
that belongs to us.
All of our accounting information
is on that disk.
We want you to retrieve the disk,
then terminate him.
We have a contact in Atlanta
that will provide you with a lead
as to where Luke Dodge might go to first.
It's only for information, Santiago.
He won't get in your way.
It's done.
- Where do you want these?
- In the kitchen.
What a chivalrous convict.
You got something
to cut these cuffs with?
Under the sink.
- Hold the chain.
- All right, all right. Easy.
- Where are you goin'?
- To the bathroom. Do you mind?
- Yes, I do. Wait a minute.
- What?
Didn't you see "The Godfather"?
The restaurant scene when Michael blows
everybody's freakin' head off. Forget it.
Go ahead. It's OK.
Thank you.
- What is your problem, man?
- What the hell's goin' on with you two?
First the thing with the gun, now you're
carrying groceries, speaking Spanish...
And then this. Are you a Boy Scout now?
Just cos I been locked up
don't mean I got no manners.
You don't bust into somebody's home
and tell 'em what to do.
She could be in the other room
callin' the cops.
Hold on.
Come on!
I thought you two bandidos
might need a new disguise.
My ex-husband was about your size.
But you...
You might be a little too small for this.
They smell like mothballs because they
were packed away for a very long time.
But they will certainly smell better
than what you have on.
Jesus. What is it?
Thank you.
Where did you get a key for the cuffs?
My ex-husband.
He's a cop.
I wonder what it feels like to want to be
a politician and not hold office.
Like a cop without a job.
I talked to Schiller. You ain't makin'
any friends mouthin' off.
Well, I'm not tryin' to make any friends.
I'm tryin' to do my job.
Oh, yeah? What job might that be?
Say, where are you goin'?
Let me talk to you for a second.
Why do you think the Attorney General
and a US marshal are involved in this?
They're following orders from superiors -
which you can't seem to do.
Would you listen for a sec?
Warden Nichols said the Attorney General
had Dodge placed on that road crew.
Plus, Dodge hacked into Brigantine
International's computer system.
- Why don't we have a record of it?
- Because the key stockholder
is a Frank Mantajano, who is currently
under indictment by the Attorney General.
So?
So whatever Dodge discovered
inside their computer system,
they wanna keep it secret.
Great police work. Maybe I can
get you assigned to the Hoffa case next!
Henry!
Are you outta your fuckin' mind?
Blanks. Found 'em on the road
where Dodge escaped. Police issue.
It's all right. It's OK.
Listen. I don't have all the pieces
to the puzzle yet, but just think about it.
Dodge makes off with $25 million
of Mantajano's money
and the corporation
doesn't press charges.
This is evidence. Did you tell Schiller?
My guess is he knows. He had Dodge
put on that road so he'd run.
But things went sour. People died.
So Schiller wants this out of the press.
- What the hell does that prove?
- What it proves, right,
is that Dodge has something big
on Mantajano
and the Attorney General wants it bad.
Now, I have got a hunch,
and I need an old friend to turn his back
for 24 hours so I can play it out.
OK, you got 24 hours. Not a minute more.
And, Matthew,
you fuck this up,
friend or no friend, it's your ass.
I know, Henry. Believe me, I know.
So where'd you meet your husband?
Well...
I was sneaking across the border
and he caught me.
So he deported me back to Mexico.
But he asked me for my phone number.
So first, he started calling.
Then visiting.
Then we fell in love and got married.
And he brought me to the States.
First to California.
And then we moved to Atlanta, Georgia.
And then what happened?
He left me.
So, I was stuck here with no money,
no friends, no family... and no job.
- So what'd you do?
- I cried.
I cried for a long time.
Then I got my shit together.
My mother had taught me how to cook.
So that's what I do.
- You work in a restaurant?
- No. I'm self-employed. I'm a caterer.
I make my own tortillas
and all the sauces.
That's my speciality - a mole.
- What's mole?
- You wanna try some?
Nothin' like real soap
to get that prison stench off you.
You oughta try some.
So, did you ask her?
- Ask her what?
- You know.
- No, I don't know.
- You don't remember? Scrub-a-dub-dub.
- Go ahead. Go on, ask her.
- Ask me what?
- Nothin'.
- You got nothin' to be ashamed of.
That's right. I'm a grown man.
All day long he's been talkin'
about wanting to take a bath
with some Mr Bubble, the one kids love.
- That's foul.
- I didn't know you were so sensitive.
- You guys know each other before jail?
- No.
- Became friends inside?
- We ain't friends.
Cell mates?
Just asking.
Hey, where do you think you're goin'?
You want your cut of the money?
Then I got some business to take care of.
Now I got a plan.
You'll just have to trust me.
Trust you?
All right.
See this? My daddy gave me this when
I was eight years old. I'm givin' it to you.
You better make damn sure I get it back.
It's for good luck.
You try to fuck me, I will find you.
Santiago. Have your playmates arrived?
- Yes, they have.
- Have you received my fax yet?
- Yes, I have.
- The one fault that is universal to men
is our love of women.
Find her, and you'll find Luke Dodge.
Just make sure you have the disk,
or be certain no one else can get it
before you do away with Dodge.
I find the girl, we get to Dodge,
and if he doesn't have the disk
- we kill him.
- Si. In that order.
Are you raiding my private files?
I gotta get to Puffy.
Now's the time he's on the Pyramid Web.
- Hasn't he caused enough trouble?
- Yes, but he'll get us out of it.
- This is a guy thing, right?
- Right.
- Nice tits.
- I agree.
Knock it off.
OK, here we go.
- I knew he'd be up to no good.
- Puffy, no good: hand in hand.
OK, here we go.
What's up, Puffdawg?
"You're out! How do I know it's you?"
Do you want me to tell you
at what age you stopped wetting the bed?
Jerk.
"You do that and you won't get
the surprise I've got for you. "
Then we should meet.
"Tonight at the witching hour. "
Where?
"I've got a jonz in my bonz
and I need a fortune cookie"?
It's our code. It means meet at midnight
at the Tokyo Massage Parlor.
- He wants to meet at a massage parlour?
- So what?
Baby, if it's a massage you're looking for,
why not let my fingers do the walking?
- I couldn't wait to get you outta that club.
- I had to do something to pay my tuition.
Besides, I like being independent
and taking care of myself.
Yeah? Well, I'm gonna
take care of you now.
So where do you wanna go?
Name your place.
Dinner.
Really?
I got a better idea.
Let's order room service
and stay right here.
I guess this is it.
You know where you're going?
I'll play it by ear, see what happens.
You know, I was thinking.
Maybe once you figure out
where you're going, get settled,
maybe you wanna drop me a postcard,
gimme a call.
Well, how can I keep in touch with you?
Here's my phone number
and my address.
I'd like to know you're OK.
Wait. Here.
I thought you might need this.
Maybe you better keep it.
Room service?
No!
Fuck you!
You're probably dangling there wondering
how you got into this predicament.
- What do you want?
- What do I want?
- I want the disk.
- What disk?
The disk that you used
to steal $25 million from my employer.
- They would like it back.
- You didn't have to kill her.
You're assuming I have a lot of time.
I don't.
Manny.