I want a car.
Chicks dig the car.
This is why Superman works alone.
Do try and bring this one
back in one piece, sir!
Don't wait up, Al.
I'll cancel the pizzas.
Batman,
a new villain has commandeered
the Gotham Museum.
He's frozen
the antiquities wing.
He's turned
the security guards into ice.
He's calling himself, "Mr. Freeze. "
Mr. Freeze.
Stop! Drop your weapon...
...or we'll shoot!
The Iceman Cometh.
Please, show some mercy.
Mercy?!
I'm afraid that my condition has
left me cold to your pleas of mercy.
In this universe...
...there's only one absolute.
Everything...
...freezes.
Hi, Freeze.
I'm Batman.
You're not sending me to the cooler.
Nice catch.
You break it, you buy it.
Grab the gem!
Kill the heroes!
Kill them! Kill them!
Destroy everything!
It's the hockey team from hell.
Get the ice...
...I'll get the Iceman.
Thanks.
Sweet.
I got mine.
Where's yours?
What killed the dinosaurs?
The Ice Age!
Hit me, boys.
Thanks for playing.
I was hoping you'd drop in.
Watch the numbers...
...for they are
the harbingers of your doom.
Can you feel it coming?
The icy cold of space.
At 30,000 feet,
your heart will freeze...
...and beat no more.
After you're frozen, your icy tomb
will plummet back to Gotham.
Freeze, you're mad.
This capsule explodes,
it'll slaughter thousands.
Freeze well.
-Who invited you?
-I was hanging around.
I thought you'd stay in the museum,
round up some thugs.
How about, "Nice to see you.
Thanks for saving my life. "
A Batbomb?
We must blow this up
before it turns Gotham into a crater.
Now what, call a taxi?!
Watch the first step!
Surf's up!
Gotcha!
Cowabunga!
He's freezing the furnace!
I got him.
Stay cool...
...Birdboy.
Can you be cold?
You have 11 minutes to thaw the bird.
Will you chase the villain...
...or save him?
Emotion makes you weak.
That's why this day is mine.
I'll kill you next time!
Did we get him?
Drats!
My experiment to mate the orchid and
the rattlesnake has failed again...
...but I still have hope for
the animal-plant crossbreedings.
If I can only find
the right dose of venom...
...these plants will be able to
fight back, like animals.
I will have given flora...
...a chance against
the thoughtless ravages of man.
Personal note:
My work would proceed faster...
...if Dr. Woodrue didn't whisk
my venom samples...
...back to his mysterious
Gilgamesh Wing.
Why won't he let me in the lab?
What is he doing in there?
Ladies and gentlemen
of the un-United Nations...
...and...
...our mystery bidder...
...may I present...
...Antonio Diego...
...serial murderer, serving life...
...in prison...
...and sole surviving...
...volunteer.
And what a charmer he is.
By merely drilling three
concentric holes directly...
...into Antonio's cranial cavity...
I have...
...created viaducts into
the most primitive part of his brain...
...the limbic system.
And now I add...
...my Super-Soldier Serum...
...code-named...
... "Venom" ...
...to which I add
my very own recipe of steroids...
...and toxins.
Plug him in.
Time to scream.
Genius!
Behold...
...the ideal killing machine!
I call this little number...
... "Bane. "
Bane of Humanity!
Imagine it.
Your own private army made up of
thousands of these super-soldiers.
Bidding begins at a mere...
... 10 million!
Turbo!
Show off for Daddy.
Dr. Isley.
Welcome to my parlor.
What?
You monster!
How could you?!
Our original sponsor had
no stomach for military applications.
He cut the funding for our work.
Without your research...
...I couldn't have come this far.
Join me.
The two of us,
entwined, side by side.
Join you?
I have spent my life trying to
protect plants from extinction...
...and now you...
...corrupt my research...
...into some maniacal scheme for
world domination.
When I get through...
...you won't be able to get a job
teaching high school chemistry.
Do you hear me?!
You psycho!
Well...
...I can respect your opinion.
Sadly, I'm not good at rejection.
I'm afraid you'll have to die.
Let the poisons and toxins
burn a grave for you...
...deep into the earth
you love so much!
Bye-bye, dear!
Fellow maniacs...
...bidding...
...begins!
Gotham University Labs
security video, 2 years ago.
Dr. Victor Fries...
...2-time Olympic decathlete and Nobel
Prize winner for molecular biology.
After his wife
contracted a rare disease...
...Macgregor's Syndrome...
...he hoped to freeze her in a cryogenic
sleep until he could find a cure.
Now, here's where
everything goes north.
That's got to hurt.
That liquid is 50 below.
But, he survived somehow.
The cryo-solution mutated his body.
-What happened to his wife?
-No one knows.
She's presumed dead.
Freeze needs
extreme cold to survive.
His cryo-suit uses diamond-enhanced
lasers to keep him at zero degrees.
If it's ice the Iceman wants....
Coming, sir.
Yes, sir?
We need the Wayne diamonds.
We going to trap a snowman?
Yes, right after you spend
10 hours in the simulator, training.
I made a mistake. I'm sorry.
It won't happen again.
You were reckless
and almost got killed.
I'm fine! See!
Me, here, alive!
How we supposed to work together
if you won't trust me?
How indeed?
He's overeager, he's impulsive.
I can't trust him not to get hurt.
Perhaps the truth is
you really don't trust anyone.
Don't tell me
you're on his side again.
Despite all your talents...
...you're still just
a novice in the ways of family.
Master Dick...
...follows the same star as you...
...but gets there by his own course.
You must learn to trust him,
for that is the nature of family.
I trust you, Alfred.
But I shan't be here forever.
Good night, Master Bruce.
Good night, Alfred.
Oh, dear, Master Bruce.
Good gracious, what a tumble.
There's a brave boy.
Yes, sir.
I am so pleased you won the bidding,
Your Supreme Ruthlessness.
We're making the final modifications
on Bane right now.
We'll have a flawless super-soldier
out to you tomorrow by overnight mail.
Dr. Isley?
Pamela?
You look great.
Especially for a dead woman.
Hello, Jason.
I think I've had a change of heart.
Or quite...
...literally...
...the animal-plant toxins had
a rather unique effect on me.
They replaced my blood with aloe...
...my skin with chlorophyll...
...and filled...
...my lips...
...with venom.
And, Jason, one other thing.
I probably
should have mentioned this earlier...
...I'm...
...poison.
It's a jungle in here.
I am Nature's arm...
...her spirit...
...her will!
Hell, I am Mother Nature.
And the time has come...
...for plants to take back...
...the world so rightfully ours...
...because it's not nice...
...to fool with Mother Nature.
"Wayne Enterprises. "
Coming, Bane, darling.
We've got a plane to catch.
I'm Mr. Icicle
I'm Mr. Ten Below
Sing! Sing!
Come on, sing!
Louder! Come on!
Sing! Sing! Sing!
He's Mr. White Christmas
Louder!
He's Mr. Icicle
Freezy...
...I'm feeling hot.
I find that unlikely.
So my hair is
brittle and my skin is dry...
...I'd weather blizzards to have you.
You're the most perfect man
I've ever known.
Let's heat things up.
My passion thaws
for my bride alone.
Talk about your cold shoulder.
Frosty!
Yeah, boss?
Energy.
Battling the Bat
exhausted my power.
But...
...I was successful nevertheless.
Absolutely, boss.
One more giant diamond of this size...
...and my freezing engine
will be complete.
I will freeze the city.
Then I will hold Gotham ransom.
Unless the city bows
to my demands...
...it's winter forever
in Gotham.
The city fathers
will have no choice...
...but to give me the billions
I need to complete my research...
...so I can find a cure.
Leave us.
Sure, boss.
We need quality time.
Soon we will be together
once more.
Soon.
I'll get it.
I must've dozed off.
My sincerest apologies.
No apology necessary.
It's the first time it's happened
in thirty years.
Please be looking for me.
Actually, I'm looking for
Alfred Pennyworth.
Uncle Alfred!
My dear.
Oh, my dear...
...what a most wonderful surprise.
How did you manage
to come here all the way from England?
My dear, you are so kind
to your old uncle.
Uncle?
Barbara is the daughter
of my dear sister Margaret.
Both my parents were killed
in a car accident 5 years ago.
Uncle Alfred's been supporting me
ever since.
-You have?
-Secrets, Al?
Secrets are a virtual prerequisite
in this house.
Don't you think, sir?
I'm on break from--
Oxbridge Academy,
Alfred's alma mater.
The new computer sciences division.
-How'd you know?
-Says so on the patch on your sweater.
-What is it? It's beautiful.
-You can say that again.
It's a competition racer.
I've been fixing it up.
I'll show you how to ride it.
You certainly will not!
Don't worry, Uncle Alfred.
I'm terrified of these things.
Barbara, I hope you'll stay with us.
Oh, I don't know.
All this luxury really isn't
my style, but...
...yeah, I'd love to.
Then it's settled.
But, sir, we...
...we do get so busy here.
Don't be silly.
After all, she's family.
Uncle Alfred?
I came to tuck you in.
You came to tuck me in?
That's quite a switch.
What're you working on?
I'm trying to find my brother,
your Uncle Wilfred.
He's first butler
to the Maharajah of Miranjapore.
But Miranjapore is a floating court.
It travels through India.
I remember Mom getting postcards.
So Wilfred can be
rather difficult to find.
I don't suppose they have
fax machines on elephants.
I've been trying to reach him
with no success.
When one grows ancient,
one yearns for family.
I have the same picture of Mom
by my bed.
Peg?
My nickname for sweet Margaret.
It's good to see you again.
I've missed you.
As I have you.
Sleep well, child.
You sleep.
Go to bed.
Good morning, Gotham.
It's Gossip Gerty reporting to you
direct from the Gotham Observatory...
... where billionaire Bruce Wayne,
chairman of Wayne Enterprises...
...is about to make yet another
legendary contribution to the city.
Gotham Observatory, Bane.
And step on it.
Step.
My father told me, "To succeed,
we need only pick a star and follow it. "
So Wayne Enterprises is donating
the world's most advanced telescope...
... to Gotham's
Observatory Restoration Project.
With any luck...
...this telescope will give
future generations a chance...
...to follow their own stars.
Brucy...
...is it true that this new telescope
can see around the globe?
Yes. If you'll watch
these monitors right here.
Satellites in orbit allow us to reflect
light from anywhere on the planet.
From here, we'll be able
to see the sky anywhere on Earth...
...and through this
intricate network of satellites...
...reflect it back to our
very own Gotham City for observation.
Just don't point it at my bedroom.
Brucy, you and the exquisite
Julie Madison...
...have been going out forever.
Are you going to tie the knot?
Marriage?
You want to give me a hand here?
Bruce and I are recklessly in love.
And that's most certainly
enough for us...for now.
If you will follow me,
I'll show you the central control grid.
You're a lot of help.
Miss, you need to stop.
Move, fascist bulldog!
-You need an appointment--
-No, I don't!
Miss, you're not authorized
to be up here.
She has no pass, sir.
Little overly protective,
but you won't hurt me, Miss--?
Dr. Pamela Isley.
Doctor...
...what can I do for you?
Actually, I already
work for you, or did.
Your arboreal preservation project
in South America.
We cut our funding.
There was a conflict of ideologies.
Dr. Woodrue was a lunatic.
I see you knew him.
Yes. That lab burnt down last week.
I'm glad you escaped.
I have here a proposal showing
how Wayne Enterprises can immediately...
...cease all actions
that toxify our environment.
Forget the stars,
look here at the earth...
...our mother, our womb.
She deserves your loyalty
and protection.
And yet, you spoil her lands...
...poison her oceans...
...blacken her skies!
You're killing her!
Your intentions are noble,
but no diesel fuel for heat...
...no coolants to preserve food,
millions of people would die.
Acceptable losses
in the battle to save the planet.
People come first, Dr. Isley.
Mammals!
A day of reckoning is coming.
That's right.
The same plants and flowers
that saw you...
...crawl from the primordial soup...
...will reclaim this planet
and there will be no one to protect you!
You must be new in town.
In Gotham City...
...Batman and Robin protect us...
...even from plants and flowers.
Maybe you'd like to meet them.
Caped crusaders are
going to help us auction...
...a diamond to raise money
for our botanical gardens.
Just a few mammals doing what
we can for the world's plants.
Thank you all for coming.
Good day, Doctor.
Batman and Robin...
...militant arm
of the warm-blooded oppressors...
...animal protectors of the status quo.
First...
...I'll rid myself of the fur
and feathered pests.
And then Gotham...
...will be mine...
...for the greening.
Excuse me, chief.
I got something here
you might want to see.
I hate when people talk
during the movie.
One more diamond, my love.
One more.
"Bruce Wayne. Diamonds. "
Very nice.
Ladies and gentlemen...
...Gossip Gerty
of "Good Morning Gotham" and I...
...welcome you
to the gem of the evening.
Our own Commissioner Gordon...
...displaying...
...the famed Heart of Isis,
on loan...
...from the collection of my
close personal friend, Bruce Wayne.
Think Freeze will take the bait?
He'll be here.
...to dance with one
of our fabulous flowers...
...the famed diamond
draped around her neck.
Let's start the bidding!
I'll give 10,000 for the orchid!
20,000 for the tiger lily!
And I bid...
...30,000 dollars
for the lovely magnolia!
Boys, please...
...let's show some gusto!
Hi, there.
And you are?
Poison...
...Poison Ivy.
Why not send junior home early?
I've got some wild oats to sow.
On the other hand...
...youth does have its advantages.
Endurance, stamina.
Forget the geriatric Bat.
Come, join me.
My garden needs tending.
I'll take it from here, pal.
Wouldn't you like the earrings too?
Some lucky boy's
about to hit the honey pot.
I'll include an evening of my company
for the winner.
I'll bring everything you see here...
...plus everything you don't.
I bid 50,000 dollars for Poison Ivy!
100,000!
And I'll bid...
...500,000 dollars!
One million dollars.
-2 million.
-You don't have it. 3 million.
I'll borrow it from you. Four.
5 million.
That's a utility belt, not a money belt.
6 million.
7 million.
Never leave the cave without it.
You boys aren't going to start fighting
over little old me, now are you?
All right, everyone!
Chill.
Get the gun!
Look at you!
Let me guess.
Plant Girl?
Vine Lady?
Hand over the diamond, Garden Gal...
...or I'll turn you into mulch.
Pheromone dust...
...designed to heat...
...a man's blood.
Doesn't work on the cold-hearted.
If you please!
If you insist.
Clever little clover.
That's my exit cue.
Thanks.
Good night.
Cool party!
Commissioner, you have 11 minutes
to thaw these people.
Miss Ivy, you've just met
one of the most sinister men in Gotham.
That's not a man...
...that is a god.
Enough monkey business.
We've got work to do.
Monkey work.
You can't make the jump.
I can!
Pull back!
I can make it!
Redbird control codes.
Disable engine.
Don't do it to me! !
We won't make it!
It's a cold town.
I could've made that jump.
You could've splattered your brains
on the building's side.
The Flying Graysons were a team.
We had to trust each to do his job.
That's what being partners is about.
Counting on someone is the way to win.
Your head wasn't on the job.
It was on Poison Ivy.
Maybe she wanted me instead of you.
That's your idea of friendship?
It's your rules.
It's your way, or the highway.
It's Batman and Robin,
not Robin and Batman.
-I'm sick of it!
-Yes, it's my rules that keep us alive.
If you want to stay in this house,
on this team, you'll abide by them.
This is no partnership.
You're never going to trust me!