I can't hide it any longer
How I regretted for all these
I've lived in shame
but, today...
I can't face myself any longer
Lin Qiuhua, 21 years old
A typist of
The Far East Insurance Company
Upon initial investigation,
occupational neurasthenia
Could be the cause of her suicide
Did she leave behind any note?
No
but there's not a hint of
struggle at the scene
Her fingerprints are there
on the windowsill
There's no sign of any kind of struggle
All these conform
to the report of the witnesses
That's all for today's report
Good, thanks
A typist?
Commits suicide because of
occupational neurasthenia
There's no news value at all
Section Chief, Miss Lin Hongzhu is here
I have taken her to the autopsy
There's no doubt that it's her sister
Good, bring her in
Yes
Please come in
Have a seat
I'm very sorry for your sister
May I ask if she was engaged?
She wasn't
Did you notice her behavior lately
Or where she usually hung out?
I didn't pay attention to that
Has she ever stayed out even for a night?
Never
There was this once though
When was that?
About six months ago
When she met her first boyfriend
What's his name?
You have no idea?
I'd better be honest with you
Your sister was pregnant
been carrying for six months
I'd think that's
the main cause for her suicide
We didn't give out the truth
For the sake of your sister's honor
Can you give us any kind of clue?
I hope you can tell us what happened,
like...
between your sister and her boyfriend
That man is not her boyfriend
He is some other man
My sister slept with a man
Only once in her lifetime
but she didn't even
Know his name
I only came to know all this
by reading her diary
She's so silly
I mean,
how could she sleep with someone...
She has metjust once!
Can I take a look
At your sister's diary?
I've burnt it
June 10, Lin Qiuhua committed suicide
because of occupational neurasthenia
This happened six months after I met her
I am writing this down as a memoir to her
Excuse me, I'd like to inquire about
Two guests who stayed here some time back
Can I?
Well...
That was six months ago
A young couple came here one night
This is the picture of that young lady
Can you look up for me
Their registered names
I'm sorry
We have many guests
coming in and out each day
And six months is such a long time
Thank you
Can I talk to you
Sure
What is it that you want?
I want to know about a young couple
...who stayed here six months ago
The man drove here in his big,
grand automobile
He's a tall guy, about 30 years old
He could be one of your old customers
One of our old customers?
This is the picture of the lady
very slim, short hair
A bit shy
I remember now, it could be Mr. Zhou
Mr. Zhou?
It could be him
During summer...
He often brought his girlfriends here
He has a gorgeous car
With a blue license plate
Yes
but, he may have changed his car now
I heard he's in the automobile business
He owns gas stations
and a car-dealing company
Thank you so much
Hello. Yes, hold on
Mr. Lee, someone is here
for the General Manager
Excuse me, I've a call
This is Li Donghai. Who am I speaking to?
The GM is not in his office,
anything important?
I'd like to ask his opinion
about something
Can you give me his home address
And let me meet with his wife
What?
Our GM is still single
And he always stays in a hotel
The Palace Hotel
We are calling from the Jet Airlines
Can you give me the room number of...
Mr. Zhou Guoxiong
Mr. Zhou stays in room 305
Yes, he comes back
around 12 p.m. Everyday
Who are you?
May I have your phone number?
And I'll ask him to call you back
It doesn't matter
Mr. Zhou, someone called you just now
As you said,
I told her that you'll be back late
She hung up when I asked for her name
Xiulan, you are becoming ever so gorgeous
Really?
Thanks
You are the only one
who knew of my returning
At first I planned to stay in Japan
for another year
One more year?
Don't get anxious; on seeing you...
I think I'll give it a second thought
Lady, you're back
I know you wouldn't want to meet
with my mom
My mom said it seems that...
You're not very interested in
doing business
May be she likes Li Donghai
I for one don't like him one bit
I felt uneasy whenever I saw him
I'll call you later
Goodbye
See you
I hear Miss Xiulan is coming back soon,
is it?
Yes! Actually she should be settled down
Xiulan should not go to study in Japan
being so far away
Let you...
Mom
I'm back
Xiulan
You're back
Mom, this is for you
You are nice to me
How come you
didn't inform me of your return?
I'd have sent someone to pick you up
Oh, thought I'd make it a surprise
You're so naughty.
Let me look at you carefully
Miss Xiulan,
you're more and more beautiful
The future belongs to young people
like you two
These past few years
I've just been getting worse
Come on, open it mom
Xiulan
What?
God, it's been so long since we've met!
That's true, almost a year
Are you happy tonight?
Of course I'm happy
Strange! Why did you ask such a thing?
Guoxiong, where are you going?
This way doesn't lead to my home!
Guoxiong
Let's go up for a while
Xiulan, you know how much I love you
but this is totally different from love
Haven't I told you before
I mean, before we got married
We should keep a pure
and clean relationship
I know, but... I need you
Stop it
We should keep on waiting
Until when? Wait till when?
Until we get married.
by then everything of mine will be yours
Must we wait till marriage?
Xiulan, I can't wait any longer
Don't make it difficult for me, please
Tonight, I can go home by myself
I'm sorry
It's okay
Miss, you are bowling all alone
Shall we bowl together?
Sure!
How about we make a bet or something?
Gamble?
Sure, if I win...
I will treat you to a dinner and dance
You pay if you win?
Strike
In this case, I'll surely make a bet
Really?
Please
Is this your car? very cool
Let's go for a ride first, okay?
Sure. I'll go anywhere
with a man as handsome as you
Do you like me?
Of course
Otherwise I won't bring you here
Really! That's good
Then we should meet more often, shall we?
Yeah
When?
You tell me when?
Tomorrow
Tomorrow?
I can't make it tomorrow
Then the day after tomorrow
Neither can I
When then?
So, you really like me that much
Then next Monday at 8pm
Wait for me outside the bowling center
Sure, I'll be there
Good morning, General Manager
So it's you!
Something important
came up yesterday night
That I wanted to report to you
I've called the hotel a few times
but you weren't in
Did you go out with Miss Xiulan?
That's none of your business
What's so important?
I'll tell you now
These are the ten cars that
we ordered from...
The volkswagen Company in West Germany
They'll be here on the 10th of this month
We've ordered another five Chevrolets
...of 1969 make from The States
Mr. Zhou,
you're here to write a novel again
This time it's lyrics,
for a record company
Who knows what he writes
but he is pretty handsome
What? Have you fallen for him?
bullshit
I don't believe that
One needs a special place to write
22nd of January, Liu Minghua
After I had an argument with Xiulan
I went to the bowling center alone
I saw a woman bowling all by herself
So I bowled with her
She seemed to have
just lived out of poverty
And like, enjoying her novae rich life
She really came
These kind of women get together
just for fun
It's better not seeing her again
Let's pick this one
No way, this one is too noisy
We should pick one
that's a bit more graceful
What do you know? This is a wedding gift
So what?
Looks like you're very experienced
Of course, everybody now talks of techno
Maybe they have a bug in their new house
And they can eavesdrop on every word
So make it a bit noisier
That way they can't hear us, right?
Whatever, pick what you want
Let's get this one!
Ten dollars
We'll send the gift over
Okay!
Qimei, let's go!
I've something to do
I'm not going
She never comes with us
That's true
So she is lying
It's not that
she can't attend the wedding
but she is saddened by the joy
Of the young married couple
A woman at her age
Of course wants to get married
She of course wants the comfort
from a man
This kind of woman
will have a different feel
A woman like her
Will desire the warmth from a man
I'm sorry
So you like...
Japanese movies
Watching Japanese movies
One can also see the scenery of Japan
It's so nostalgic
Are you Japanese?
No, I'm Chinese, but I lived in Japan
My name is Yang Gangtian
So the places shown in this movie
Are not new to you at all
Not all though
Do you come to Hong Kong often?
That's why I remain single
No worries at all
My friends are very concerned about
my love life
I don't care however
Think about this; each day, every year
And the whole life
spend with only one person
How boring!
Well, you don't understand
I do
because I'm also single
but you do know what being content is
Okay, tonight I'll let you feel
How it's like to be contended
Let's go to a new place for drinks,
how's that?
Sure, no problem
It should be my turn to pay
What? You think I'm broke
Don't worry, I enjoy paying the bill;
especially...
when it comes to treating someone
as pretty as you
Not a single man
has ever come to my place
You're an exception
Please wait a minute
Hold on, my friend is about to go to bed
You can take a rest here! Help yourself
How can I? You don't have to
Come, undress and go to sleep!
No, don't be so naughty
No, don't do that
No...
Come in
This woman
Isn't she the one that
I've known a while ago?
The police are looking into
Liu Minghua's boyfriend
Will they come to me?
No, I'm a Chinese Japanese named
Yang Gangtian
Even if they come to me
I can still prove that
I wasn't at the scene
because when she was killed
I was with Li Qimei
Where is Miss Su?
She's in the backyard
Miss Su
Is it true that
you will go back to Tokyo...
before the end of the year?
No, that will be rather too hurried
Maybe I'll spend the New Year with mom
Anyway I haven't decided yet
Have you heard something about Guoxiong
About what?
Someone asked me about him
Said he has other women...
Mr. Li, Guoxiong has other women
It's partly my fault
Your fault?
Yes, but, Mr. Li
You have nothing to do
with us other than business
So please don't interfere
into our relationship
Mr. Li, your phone call
My phone call?
Excuse me
Hello, this is Li Donghai
Call me only at work
Haven't I told you that?
It's been a while since he came here
Did you two argue again?
We had an argument
The day I came back from Japan
That's not very good!
You're too strong in temper
Just like a boy
A lady should be more gentle
Otherwise Guoxiong will not like you
Let me get it
Hello, Guoxiong,
we're just talking about you
How are you?
I haven't seen you for a long time,
I'm sorry
The company has got a very large order
And I'm very busy
Tonight I'm free
Shall we go see a movie?
Oh, I'm very sorry
Tonight I need to go to a friend's place
It's all arranged
Oh yes! I was free in the past few days
I felt so bored at home
And you didn't call me
What a pity. Let's meet some other time
Okay, bye
Whose place are you going tonight?
It's a lie. I'll let him down first
Then I'll see him at the office
...to give him a surprise
Mind you don't turn it into a tragedy
If you keep on fooling him like this
This kid is so unmannered
Is there a Mr. Zhou living in here?
Mr. Zhou, yes
Do you mean
the one who is writing a novel?
Writing a novel?
Yes, you're right
I'm his fiancee Su Xiulan
Mr. Zhou asked me
to wait for him in the room
To wait for him? That's strange
He just drove away
He's out?
It doesn't matter
Mr. Zhou said...
Just inform the security
and that will be fine
Well...
it's not supposed to be like that...
but...
It's okay, come with me
Please help yourself
Thank you
Diary of a lady-killer?
Hope one day
I can win the heart of Xiulan
True love is not
only a matter of spirituality
but also a matter of physical enjoyment
She is like a prey to my trap
So I took her to the hotel
She didn't resist at all,
I can do whatever I want
Guoxiong, how can you face up to me
You painting is very good,
you're so talented
You have a bright future ahead of you
Are you an artist?
No, I'm a special correspondent of
the London Times
I like sculptural art
Two weeks ago
I went to vietnam to conduct an interview
I stopped over in Hong Kong
on the way back
Hong Kong is known to be
the Pearl of the East
So I wanted to have a glimpse of
some Eastern art
With this chance of a stop-over
but, I didn't know that...
Maybe I have to give up this idea
She has a good hobby
Woman who likes art
will easily fall for a man
Miss Zhu, I have a good idea
Let's have a drink
I'd like to thank you
for being my charming escort
Let's have a good time tonight
How does that sound?
Good
Want to come up?
Come in!
Just put it here
Please take a seat,
I need to change my clothes
Don't look!
I need your help
It's okay, you can go back to your seat
Don't look
I said don't peep, and you don't listen
Ready yet?
Okay, have a seat
Come
You're so beautiful
Let's toast for your beauty
Please don't
A body as perfect as yours
Shouldn't be covered up by clothes
It should be shown
and admired by everybody
You really admire my body?
Of course, it's God's greatest work
Okay
I thought you're someone
who understands art
One who knows how to appreciate beauty
but, you're just as vulgar as
any other man
I've made a mistake
Don't be mad, Lizhen
Your body is too gorgeous
Let me look at it carefully
Who?
I'm Meiyun, open the door!
He's so heavy
Who told you to drink so much...
Disgusting
Why do you have to drink so much?
Drunk as a pig
You must be the new boyfriend of Lizhen!
I'm sorry, I'm Meiyun
I'm learning painting
Let's have a drink, how's that?
I need to go, please enjoy yourself!
Meiyun... come here
Who told you to drink so heavily
Wait
I'm sorry
It's okay
Are we still friends?
Of course
This is my phone number
When you come by, call me first
Good, I'll surely call you
Lizhen...
Goodbye
Liu Minghua has been strangled to death
And so is Li Qimei
Whether or not
these two cases are related
but, how could they coincide so?
It's a weird coincidence, if at all
Why is it that whoever slept with me...
is being killed one by one
It couldn't be true.
Why are these things happening?
Is there anything that you want,
General Manager?
Nothing
Hello
Hello, are you Guoxiong?
I'm Xiulan. I'm now in Tokyo
Tokyo?
How come you are in Tokyo?
I'll tell you later
Guoxiong, please come to Tokyo at once
I need to talk to you
You must come
Guoxiong
I know why you asked me to come to Tokyo
Today is Easter
You want us
to spend the holiday in Tokyo, right?
Guoxiong, what are you thinking of?
I was thinking, I hope one day
We can find a place
that belongs only to us
We will love each other and nothing else
I'm yours, and you're mine
We'll lead a happy life together
A happy life together? How lovely
Tell me, Guoxiong
Can we really lead a happy life together
And stay with each other forever?
Of course!
Guoxiong
Guoxiong...
What happened?
Are you okay? Guoxiong...
Help me...
Are you feeling better now?
You suddenly fainted in the night club
God, you sure scared me!
Are you too tired?
I'm sorry
Maybe the performance proved too daring
What did you dream of?
You were talking in your dream
Xiulan
We've come all this way
to spend the holiday here
but I've ruined it
I'm so sorry
Don't say that, we are now together
...for a peaceful Easter night.
Isn't that better?
You know why I would suddenly
...come to Tokyo?
Why?
I need to think carefully about
our relationship
Xiulan
I think we should break up
Why?
I don't want to see you anymore
What? Xiulan, do you despise me
You don't love me anymore
I... but I...
but what?
I don't know what I should do
I'm so sad
Sad? Who makes you so sad?
You better ask yourself
I've read your diary
You...
Guoxiong, for one whole year
You were having affairs with those women
I have not the slightest idea at all
I still give out all my heart to you
How can you face up to me?
Xiulan, please forgive me
How can I forgive you!
We are engaged
And still you did such a thing
How wrong you are!
You can scold me, but please believe me
I do truly love you,
and will remain so forever
I know you love me
but I've never rejected you
I just want you to wait if you love me
Why can't you wait?
but instead, you turn to other women
It's exactly because I love you too much
So every time when you reject me
I got, like possessed
by an inferiority complex
So strong that I had no choice
but to overcome it by finding other women
I regretted so much every time
after the affair
I felt I have let you down
If so...
Why don't you go see a doctor?
I will. When I go back
I will surely find myself a doctor
Guoxiong
Know somethin'?
Actually I had decided that
I won't forgive you
but... l've failed
I do truly love you
Xiulan, I've let you down
I've let you down
What happened?
Let us calm down
Otherwise we'll go against your wish
Let's wait till we get married
Guoxiong, you're so good
I think this is
the most meaningful Easter
...we've ever had, isn't it?
It's raining
Someone is plotting against me
Guoxiong
Guoxiong, what are you talking about?
Xiulan, will you believe me
No matter what happened?
I will believe you
I need to return to Hong Kong tomorrow
...to deal with an important matter
What is it?
I can't tell you now
Nor do I want to see you...
getting involved in this
We can only lead
a true happy life together
...after this matter is settled
Then...
Zhu Lizhen, will she also get killed?
Now she's the only one who can prove
...that I'm not the murderer
Miss Zhu, you're back!
I've called you a few times
but you weren't in
Now is the school holiday,
no one is around
Can we meet?
I need to talk to you
about something important
Meet with me?
Tonight 11:30 at your home
Sure, I'll be there. bye
Good, nothing has happened to her
Maybe I'm too sensitive
This is strange!
Li Qimei's home is like this
when she got killed
Lizhen
Someone wants to trap me
with all these dead bodies
Miss Zhu, Miss Zhu
How come the door is opened
The diary of a lady killer is lost
Even though I didn't kill them
Still, the police will suspect me
They will come to me sooner or later
I just hope that it won't be today
When the first victim
Liu Minghua was killed
Where were you?
I'm asking, where were you?
I was in Li Qimei's room
So only Li Qimei can prove that...
you were not at the scene
but she also got killed
That was 22nd of March,
2:30 in the morning
Where were you by then?
I was in Zhu Lizhen's room
Zhu Lizhen also got killed later on
When Liu Minghua was killed...
The defendant was in Li Qimei's room
When Li Qimei got killed
The defendant was in Zhu Lizhen's room
That means except for the dead
No one can prove that
The defendant was not at the scene
That means...
Yes, someone else can prove that
Who?
That night a man and a woman came in
They are friends of Lizhen
They came for Lizhen,
and they even looked at me
What are their names?
I forgot
Where do they live?
I can't remember
Quiet
When Zhu Lizhen was killed
Where were you?
You can't answer that! No wonder
The night Zhu Lizhen got killed
The defendant was in Zhu Lizhen's room
It's a conspiracy
Someone intentionally killed them
one by one
Someone is plotting against me
Calm down
The court will now produce
the following exhibits
According to the test result
This panty hose is the means
which was used in murder
This was found in the defendant's room
At Apartment Luoyang
The second exhibit is this lighter
and cigarette butt
Found in the room of the victim, Li Qimei
The defendant
has already admitted that...
The lighter belongs to him
The third one is a tie
This tie is the tool
That was used to killed Zhu Lizhen
Also found in the room of the defendant
Doctor,
did you notice any sign of struggling
With Zhu Lizhen?
That's a bit hard to say.
blood stain was found
inside the right hand finger nail
of the defendant
What's the blood type?
Type Ab
What's the blood type of the victim?
Type O
And the blood type of the defendant?
Type Ab
Okay
In order to prove that
the defendant is guilty
The Court allows appearance of
a special witness
About a year and a half ago
Mr. Zhou rented a room in our place
He said... he is a novel writer
Mr. Zhou is the General Manager of the
Locally acclaimed Far East Company
When he stayed in our hotel
There was nothing suspicious about him
As of the murder case of Liu Minghua
The defendant is not guilty
due to lack of evidence
He's convicted for murders of
Li Qimei and Zhu Lizhen
And will be sentenced to
imprisonment for life
Guoxiong... Guoxiong
Guoxiong...
I need to appeal...
The Court is adjourned
Are you Lawyer Hong?
Yes, I'm Hong bolun. Have a seat
Please, take a seat
I'm Su Xiulan
I know, after Zhou Guoxiong was sentenced
He kept on calling your name
So, you were at the Court that day
To investigate in this case
I wouldn't call it "investigation"
I just happen to be
interested in this case
Lawyer Hong,
I hope you can help Guoxiong
He won't kill
I don't believe that he is a murderer
Do you have any proof?
No
but we have been engaged for
more than two years
Of course he has been wrong in the past
but recently he begged for my forgiveness
And I did forgive him
Our relationship has moved
a big step forward
So why would he want to kill...
when our relationship is
at it's best moment!
Lawyer Hong
I know you're very experienced
And you have saved
a lot of innocent people
So please help Guoxiong
No matter what
I know you love Zhou Guoxiong
And you believe that he is innocent
I also think that
this case has a lot of loopholes
I believe that he is not the murderer
That's why I'm willing to
investigate into it
but Miss Su,
you have to cooperate with me
I'd want to know about the past affairs
...of your fiance
I won't try to avoid the reality
I lost my mind because ofjealousy
I've no complains
I envy Mr. Zhou
For having such a loving fiancee as you
First, you need to investigate
into the hotels or apartments
that he lived in
Most importantly,
to check out on those women
who had frequent contacts with him
Record their information in detail,
understand?
Miss Xiulan, you're back
Yes, speeding again
Mom
You're back, Xiulan
Did you find a good lawyer?
Mom, I have good news for you
Lawyer Hong has agreed to help
Lawyer Hong?
Isn't he the famous Lawyer Hong bolun?
Correct
He's good at redressing mishandled cases
If he can help...
Guoxiong can be saved
Great! I too do not believe that Guoxiong
...would do such an evil thing
Why did you bring out the birds?
Madam
The boss of the sausage shop
told me today that...
birds need sunshine
Sunbathing will make their songs
more delightful
I've never heard of such a thing
He said his experience told him that
Okay then, you can bring it out
for more sunshine
Yes
Donghai
You too had the same kind of bird,
didn't you?
Remember to bring it out
for more sunshine
So that it can sing more beautifully
Yes
Sad, sad
Who makes you so sad
Is it the budding of plum flowers,
Or it's the rose
that didn't come into blossom
Who, who
Who had hurt you so much
Even if you dry up your tears
And bring out all your sorrow
There's only emptiness
The world is a place of fallacy
So why dream in tears
Dreaming for one that never comes
A lie, a lie
Where is true love if love does exist
If you know
Then you don't have to be sad
Miss Qin, I would like to know
If you have noticed any strange behavior
...on part of Zhou Guoxiong
Like nymphomania
Are you trying to ask if he has ever...
attempted to strangle me?
So the police has already asked you that?
A very detailed questioning indeed
Perhaps they hoped for me to say that...
Zhou Guoxiong has this bad habit
but I'm sorry, he didn't
Then... does he have other kind of
abnormal behavior
If loving women
is not considered abnormal
Then he's perfectly normal
So you two frequently went on dates?
Only once. Does that surprise you?
I'm sorry,
but... are you Miss Guo Meiling?
Yes!
So you're the famous lawyer, what's up?
Are you the ex-girlfriend of
Zhou Guoxiong?
Yes!
That was a year ago
We met at the beach
He asked me to swim with him
He's very handsome
He said he liked me
And actually I liked him too
So I accepted his invitation
We had a wonderful time together
Later I went with him
to a nightclub for drinks
And what happened thereafter
I'm sure you can imagine
Then, according to you...
is he really abnormal,
just as the paper described?
I'd say he is very much normal
Mr. And Mrs. Wang
It's me again
Did anyone come for Zhou Guoxiong lately?
No one
Really?
Then recently did he bring anyone back
...to this apartment?
He usually came back late
Moreover, he doesn't usually
stay overnight here
No wonder
You can't recall much about him
He doesn't come that often, you see!
I'm sorry, I've bothered you too much
It doesn't matter
Goodbye
What?
Nothing
Lawyer Hong
Miss Su, how come you're here so late
Anything important?
I feel uneasy at heart.
Even at home I kept tarrying
What happened to you?
Your head is bleeding
I almost got killed by a car
What happened?
I should know better
He will come sooner or later
I'm trying to prove that
Zhou Guoxiong is not the murderer
So the real murderer tries to kill me
because I'm investigating into this case
Then you...
Don't worry,
this has happened to me many times
So Miss Su, any news?
I went to the Apartment Luoyang today
It must be hard on you
Did you find anything?
No
Same for me;
we've come up with nothing so far
What's the use of this list of women?
We didn't find any clue in it
Miss Su,
besides the women on this list...
Do you know if Zhou Guoxiong
...has any other women?
I really wouldn't know that
I'm sorry. Shouldn't ask you this
but, I've asked Guoxiong
And he didn't tell me
Then... will that diary be useful
Diary? What diary?
I mean the diary of a lady killer
Diary?
Yes, please tell me
Where did you
put the diary of a lady killer?
I think the murderer
that plotted against you...
is related to one of your women
Tell me! Where did you hide that diary?
I have not hidden it
You haven't hidden it!
It's lost
When?
I remember the day when Lizhen was killed
I had it on the desk
When I went home
It's already gone
The murderer has destroyed
All the evidence
Mr. Zhou
Why don't you rewrite the diary
all over again
According to your memory
Rewrite it word by word
Otherwise we are hopeless
Next time when we go to Court
If we can't produce enough evidence
You want me to rewrite the diary
all over again
but who will believe in what I write
No one will believe in what I said
Forget it! Enemy of the women,
nymphomania
Enough of that!
before I got sentenced by the Court
This society has already sentenced me
Come in
What do you want, Mr. Li?
Nothing in particular
I went to meet you at home,
but you weren't in
So I came to look for you here
How did you know I was here?
Well... any progress with the case?
No
Guoxiong's appeal is a month away
My heart is so restless now
Of course!
If you need anything
Just let me know
Thank you
Then, I better get going. Goodbye
You're back, Lawyer Hong
Who is that man, one who just went out?
He is the General Manager of
the Far East Company
So he's the successor to Mr. Zhou!
Just now you mentioned about
something important
What is that?
From his diary, Mr. Zhou recalls a woman
...who has committed suicide
Her name is Lin Qiuhua
Among all those women
She's the only one that committed suicide
The date of her suicide
is a month ahead of the first murder case
You mean the suicide of Lin Qiuhua...
has something to do with Guoxiong?
Yes. Even though the newspapers mentioned
She had occupational neurasthenia
but I seriously doubt it
So I went to the police station
to double check
I found out that when she died...
She is already six months pregnant
Her sister came to inspect the body
This is her sister's address
I think we need to talk to...
Lin Qiuhua's sister
Miss Su,
I think it'd be more appropriate...
for you women to speak to each other
Do you mind to go?
No problem
Is there a Miss Lin Qiuhua
...living in here?
Are you asking about Miss Lin...
who used to live on the second floor?
Around October of last year
Miss Lin sold all her furniture
After that a lot of people
have moved in and out
So nobody did pay much attention
As of when she actually moved out
Did anyone come to look for them?
Let me think... oh yes
A reporter of some magazine
...did come two or three times
He wanted to ask about
her sister's suicide
After that no one came for her
Do they have any relatives?
I don't think so
Thank you
Don't get upset, we're still hopeful
We've already put in a classified
I hope we'll soon get a response
Once Lin Hongzhu appears,
we'll have a chance
Hello, yes
Please hold on
Someone said last year a woman
stayed at his place
She might be the one we're looking for
Hello, where are you?
Apartment Jielu in Yaumatei
Lawyer Hong, Apartment Jielu
Is the one that Zhu Lizhen lived in
Don't worry about that, I'll come at once
She is a model by profession
She used to tour overseas to perform
She came back only around two days a week
For the past two months
she didn't come back at all
It's good
she has a six month deposit with me
So I don't worry at all
Where is Zhu Lizhen's room?
That one
So she just lived here!
I never imagined it's that close
Isn't this that diary?
This is the crucial
diary of a lady killer
How come it's here!
The most important part of this diary
Are the pages about Lin Qiuhua
How come it's been torn out?
In this case, Lin Hongzhu is undoubtedly
...the sister of Lin Qiuhua
Will Miss Lin come back?
Maybe not
Why?
because she has left the diary here
She is hoping that...
We can discover this diary
That's right
Lawyer Hong, I have this feeling too
If Miss Lin were the real murderer...
She won't leave the diary behind
I guess we've paid too much attention
to this diary
And left out the fact that
someone hates Guoxiong
That's true.
We ought to concentrate on notjust...
the women included in this diary;
but to a wider area
Let's simplify the case
Miss Lin hates Guoxiong
because he is the cause of...
Her sister's suicide
Will someone then make use of this hatred
...to plot against Guoxiong?!
Maybe this person...
bears a deeper grudge against Guoxiong
And until now
He is still doing something against him
Hello. Hold on please
Miss Su, your phone call
Seems like it's a woman
Calling from the Apartment Luoyang
Hello
I wanted to tell you this
the last time you came
Around end of last year
Someone called looking for Mr. Zhou
Yes, he said he's a newspaper reporter
That's right.
He asked if Mr. Zhou is at home
Yes, it was a man
What time?
Around December of last year
by that time Mr. Zhou was not at home
He just went out a while ago
What?
That's right, so he hung up in a hurry
by that time
I wasn't paying much attention
When I found out
Mr. Zhou is not a man of the art
Then I wondered, why would he call him?
Yes, that's right
What's more,
when I talked to him on the phone
I heard a bird singing in the background
I remembered talking to my husband
That maybe the reporter...
is using the phone of a bird shop
very good! Thank you very much
She said that a newspaper reporter
has once called Guoxiong
Really?
Seems like the reporter that
went to see Lin Hongzhu
Is the same person as this one
Is this the sound that you've heard?
That's right, it's this sound
I've no doubt about it
Thank you
Mom, do you think
Guoxiong could be acquitted?
I don't believe that
Guoxiong is the murderer
Could it be that
someone is jealous of him
And is making use of
his lifestyle to set a trap!
And one by one...
Killed all the women that
he once got along with!
Xiulan, what do you mean?
I was thinking,
this could be a way to harm someone
What kind of strange idea that you have!
It's getting dark.
Looks like it's going to rain soon
It's getting late, let me take you home!
No, I'm not going back
Don't you know what to do
...To win over my heart?
Xiulan
Take a seat!
I need some water
Sorry, I forgot to put some water
in the fridge
It's not too cold
Isn't this the same bird
as the one in my home?
You forgot that
I've brought back two of these birds
...from New Zealand?
This is a precious breed
I'm afraid they are the only two
in Hong Kong
Everyday when I hear them sing
I feel like being with you everyday
Xiulan, I love you
Do you know that I've loved you...
Since a long time back
Not here, take me to the room
Okay
I've always been dreaming of
being with you forever
I believe this dream will soon
become a reality
Don't rush
I love you.
I love you so much I'm getting insane
Do you know that Guoxiong and I
love each other too
Don't mention that asshole Guoxiong
I'm so mad when you were in love with him
Everyday I kept thinking;
even if I have to kill him
I have got to win you over
What? You said you have to kill Guoxiong
And win me over
Well, I did think about that
In order to have you,
I've already done so
You devil!
You ruthless murderer
You killed all these innocent women
Just to satisfy your selfish desire
Stop, don't move!
Miss Su, are you okay?
I don't know since when
did I come to know that
I was in love with Xiulan
Xiulan... whenever I call this name
I'm thrilled with joy and excitement
but, when I thought about
Guoxiong and Xiulan
Joy turns into hatred and anger
So I've decided to plot against Guoxiong
but when I've given up Xiulan
And fell in love with Lin Qiuhua,
I found out that
She killed herself because of Guoxiong
I swear that I will avenge her
So I made use of Lin Hongzhu
who also wanted to avenge
her sister's death
I've designed a plan to have my revenge
And made him look like the suspect
In Guoxiong's room
I had read his diary of a lady-killer
So I started killing all those women
one by one
Hongzhu is frightened by my cruelty
She is not willing to cooperate anymore
but I can't let her go
because she knew too much
So after I locked her up for a few weeks
I've killed her too. I'm arrested today
Maybe I'm guilty
but at least I can face up to Qiuhua
She is waiting for me
In that faraway land
Calling for me
Guoxiong
Xiulan
Please don't ever leave me again