Mamma mia, I can't see anything!
Where do I go now?
Madam is right. I should
buy myself some glasses...
but I look so awful in them,
and they make me look old!
I'll have to ask Madam
for a little light.
How beautiful you are!
Do butterflies make you happy,
Medoro?
Giving happiness...
...is the most beautiful thing
you can do in this world.
Isn't that true?
If something comes into the world...
...and doesn't make our lives
more pleasant...
...it might as well
not have been born at all!
How long do butterflies live,
Medoro?
They say that a butterfly
knows no suffering.
It lives one day in happiness
and then dies forever.
The only thing I don't like about
death is that you die for too long.
It would be better
the other way around.
What would that be?
If you died for just one day and
then lived forever in happiness.
Have you ever died, Medoro?
Oh, I still have to finish being born.
And anyway, time doesn't exist,
Madam Fairy.
You're right, Medoro,
time doesn't exist.
But let's go now.
It's getting late.
Yes. Well, I don't remember
the way very well.
You don't remember
or you can't see?
This is the last time
I'll ask you, Madam Fairy...
...could we have
a thread more light?
Just a little?
All right, Medoro.
Thank you, Madam Fairy.
Let's go, little mice!
Who is that?
- Get it! Catch it!
Here it comes again, over there!
We've got to catch it!
Here it is!
Who is that?
- My persimmons!
Here it comes! I see it!
That's what it was!
It's coming this way! Catch it!
We've got to catch it!
You rascal! You scoundrel!
Yes, you really are
a nice-looking frame!
And now, you know what
I'm going to do?
I'm going to make you
a nice rose right here.
You don't like the rose?
Oh, I knew it.
Then we'll make a daisy!
For heaven's sake, what's that?
Such bad manners!
Whoever you are,
you're really very rude.
What is this?
Who does this belong to?
Just look. What a lovely
piece of wood.
Lovely, really lovely!
I'll make a nice puppet...
...one that can dance
and do flips...
...well-mannered
and obedient, though.
Yes, let's start
working right away.
I'll make the most beautiful
puppet in the world.
Come over here. You'll be
the staff of my old age.
Just look at what a lovely puppet
it's turning out to be.
It's as if it were
making itself.
Am I hurting you?
No, it's not a very hard job.
You see how lovely
you're turning out to be?
Two nice big eyes...
...some pretty black hair...
...and a cute little mouth
with a little tongue inside.
WOOD:. Will you let me try on your
yellow wig, Father, will you?
I've told you a thousand times
to be quiet!
I should have made
your tongue last!
And anyway, who told you
this is a wig?
Can you really tell?
- You sure can.
It's a big old yellow wig that
could make you die laughing.
It looks like you have cornmeal
pudding on your head!
Be quiet, you impertinent boy!
Can you believe it? I haven't
even finished making you...
...and already you're being
disrespectful to your father!
You're starting off badly,
my boy!
And just be quiet for a minute!
All right, I'll be quiet.
I'll be quiet.
I won't talk anymore because
my fath... What's the matter?
Oh, blessed saint Anthony!
He talks!
Yes, he talks!
I really do think
I heard him talk!
But let's try something.
How are you?
- Fine, Geppetto. And you?
Very well, very well, thank you.
Thank goodness
he doesn't talk.
Just what I was saying. How
could it be possible that a puppet...?
Hey, Father, close that door.
I'm all naked and there's
a draft in here, mamma mia!
A puppet that knows
how to talk.
Stop that, Father, you're
tickling me. No, no, stop that!
Ladies and Gentlemen,
I present to you....
That's right.
What name shall I give you?
Well, you came from pine wood.
I'll call you Pinocchio!
Nice name, it appeals!
- What a lovely puppet you are!
Your little shoes and little pants
are splendid.
Now, the finishing touch.
A hat made of bread crumbs,
painted by me!
Wait!
- I like this one better!
Father! There are
so many things in here!
What's this? What's this called?
Stop! Pinocchio, be careful!
Come here!
Where are you going, Pinocchio?
Come here! My hair!
No one knows I wear a wig!
Be careful! You're going
to hurt yourself!
Here's father's chair,
father's little table...
...father's whatchamacallit!
What do you see
out of that window?
Can I take a look, yes or no?
Oh, good God!
Where are you going? Get down!
Careful, Father! Jump!
Bye, Father! See you later!
I should have thought of this before.
Where are you going?
It's so beautiful out there, Father!
Come and see! Bye!
Don't go outside!
It's dangerous! Torna indietro!
What's that?
- Out of the way, puppet!
A puppet?
- What the heck is that?
Pinocchio!
Pinocchio! Pinocchio!
Who is it?
Get out of the way!
- Get out of the way!
You're going to pay me
for that wine now!
Got you!
Got you! Finally!
Who does this puppet belong to?
Let's figure out how much
there'll be to pay in damages!
Who does this puppet belong to?
It's mine! That wig is mine,
thank you! It's mine.
If you only knew what I've
been through! There was a goose...!
Quiet, puppet!
Pinocchio, my son?!
A fine father you are! This puppet
is a real pain in the neck!
What do you mean?
I struggled so hard to make him
into a respectable puppet!
Respectable? He's turned the whole
city upside down! It's your fault!
He escaped from the house
before I even knew it.
That's bad!
You have to be more careful!
Only an idiot lets a puppet
escape from right under his nose!
Now this one's coming
to jail with us. Let's go!
Who's he?
- My son, where are you going?
No, you don't!
Are you trying to escape, too?
You come with us!
You've got some damages to pay...
...or else there's no avoiding
a night in jail for you. Let's go!
Wretched boy!
A little bird! Hey, I see you!
Come here! Come here!
There are so many of them!
Here's a nest! A nest!
It's empty!
A squirrel!
It's so wonderful to be in
the world! This is really the life!
I'm going to warm myself up
a little. It's freezing.
What a great day I've had!
And now I'm so hungry,
I could eat the whole house up!
There must be some place
where my father...
Pinocchio.
- What's that?
It is I, Pinocchio,
the Talking Cricket!
No! A talking cricket?
Cricket, you don't
by any chance know...
...where my father keeps the cakes,
do you?
Woe to those children who rebel
against their parents...
...and run away from home.
They will never come
to any good in this world!
You're not talking to me, are you?
- Yes, I am.
Woe to you!
- Cricket, I'm getting out of here!
Because if I stay, I'll have to do
what every other child does.
I mean, I'll have to go to school
and to study...
...and I don't have the slightest
desire to study! I just don't like it!
Poor little fool!
You should know that if you do that...
...you'll become a fine jackass...
...and everyone will laugh at you.
Hey, Cricket, why don't you
shut up for a minute?
You've got an annoying voice...
...and I really can't stand
to listen to it! It's really annoying!
Well, if you don't want to go
to school, at least go to work.
To work? Me?
That's right! There must be
some job that you like.
Yes, there is one that I like.
There's one that I like a lot.
That's a good boy, Pinocchio.
You see?
And what is this job?
- Eating, drinking...
...sleeping, having fun...
...doing whatever I like
from morning till night!
You're really a puppet,
and you'll always be a puppet!
And you're a bad-luck cricket, and
you'll always be a bad-luck cricket!
For your information, dear
Pinocchio, those like you...
...always end up either in jail
or at the hospital.
You're really a nasty
bad-luck cricket! You really are!
Those like me end up in jail
or in the hospital, do they?
And those like you...
...you know where
they end up, Cricket?
Where, Pinocchio?
In the cemetery!
Got you! Got you!
Hey, Pinocchio, what are you
doing with that hammer? Stop that!
Got you! Got you! Got you!
Where are you?
I was joking. I didn't
really want to hurt you.
Where are you, little Cricket?
- All right, I'll trust you.
Can I really trust you?
- I can't hear anything.
There's an echo over there
where you're talking.
Couldn't you come a little closer?
- Where?
Well, for example, here!
Right here where I'm pointing.
That way we can talk.
- I'm coming, Pinocchio.
I'm coming, for I have
a great truth to tell you.
Those like you...
- Got you!
You fell for it! I'll teach you,
with your annoying voice...
I can't stand you!
Cricket, where are you?
I don't feel like playing anymore!
I'm starving, I'm tired,
I'm dying for some sleep...
...I'm freezing, I'm starving.
Cricket, I'm starving!
What a horrible town!
Oh, God!
What is it? Father!
Dear Father!
My dear little Pinocchio,
you were burning to pieces!
If you only knew what I've been
through! I won't forget until I die.
What happened, Pinocchio?
It was raining. It was snowing.
And you weren't there. I was
so hungry! Then the Cricket said:
"You deserve it. It serves you
right. You've been a bad boy!"
And you know what I did?
I hit him with a hammer!
I did the right thing.
I said, "I'll teach you."
At a certain point, I was tired,
I was hungry, I was sleepy.
And you weren't there,
do you understand?
Then I sat near the fire to get
warm, and the fire burned me.
Now I'm just
as hungry as ever...
...and I don't have my little
suit of clothes anymore.
Would you make me
a brand-new suit, Father?
Why should I make you
another one?
So that you can run away again
and get me sent back to jail?
I promise you that
from now on I'll be good.
I'll go to school,
and I'll distinguish myself!
Is that a promise?
The promise of all promises.
No joke.
I promise you with all my heart!
- Good boy, my son.
Here, take this! Look what
I have for you! It's a pear!
It was going to be for my
breakfast tomorrow morning.
Eat it up, and may it do you good.
- What a nice pear!
Could you peel it for me?
- Peel it?
Yes, because I really
can't stand fruit peels.
They really don't appeal!
- They don't appeal?
Father, Father!
Where have you been?
To buy you a brand-new spelling
book, so you can study! Here it is!
Nice!
But where's your jacket?
- I sold it!
Why did you sell it?
- I was too hot in it.
I'll never forget this!
Now, you go to school and
make sure you distinguish yourself!
I promise you I will!
Pinocchio, wait!
- What?
Your little hat made
of bread crumbs.
How does it look on me?
- It looks wonderful!
Bye, I'm off to school!
Bye! I'll be waiting for you!
- Bye, Father!
Today I want to learn to read...
...tomorrow I'll learn to write...
...the day after tomorrow to do
arithmetic. Then I'll be all set.
What's this music?
Excuse me, is that the school?
The school's in the opposite
direction.
And what's this building?
It's written right there,
can't you see?
I'd be happy to read it.
I don't know how to read today!
A fine ox you are! It says,
"Grand Puppet Theatre."
Bye, I'm going to school now.
- Excuse me.
I'm not interested myself...
...but if someone wanted to go,
how much would it cost to get in?
You'd need four pennies!
Would you buy my shoes
for four pennies?
No!
How about my hat, for four pennies?
- I said no! Bye!
And this spelling book, that
my father sold his jacket for...
...in this freezing cold, would
you buy it for four pennies?
You're going to make me late
for school! That's enough!
I'll buy the spelling book
from you for four pennies.
Oh, thank you!
Pulcinella!
Who's that calling me?
Were you the one
who took the salami?
No, no, no, no,
I didn't take any salami, Sir!
No, I saw you,
you're the one who took it!
Liar, that's not true. It wasn't
me who took the salami!
Liar!
- Thief!
In the name of the law,
who's the thief here?
It's him!
- It's him!
Silence! Celestial deities!
Do I dream or wake?
And yet, that looks like
a puppet down there!
It's him in person!
The puppet responsible for all
that commotion yesterday!
Wait, what's his name?
It's him in person!
It's Pinocchio!
Master, let's give Pinocchio
a grand welcome!
Come on, Pinocchio,
come up here...
...and let your puppet brothers
give you a big hug!
All right, I'm coming!
Here I am...
...my dearest friends!
What's all this commotion?
And you, who are you?
You, who are you?
Why have you come and created
this confusion in my theater?
Please believe me, most
illustrious Sir, it wasn't my fault.
-I was--
-Enough!
We'll settle our score
at dinner!
My apologies to the audience.
The show will be repeated tomorrow!
Curtain!
Harlequin, Pulcinella,
the water's boiling.
Go get that puppet
hanging on the nail!
Today I'll eat him!
Obey me! I'm hungry!
What do you mean?
Have pity, most illustrious of
all illustrious sirs, Fire-Eater!
The idea of being eaten
doesn't appeal to me!
Father, I wanted to go
to school, I did--
Poor Father. If I die,
you'll die, too, dear Father!
That's a good sign, Pinocchio!
Fire-Eater sneezed...
...and when he sneezes it means
his heart was touched.
-And so?
-So that's good.
When he is moved, his stomach
closes up, and no one gets eaten.
You're safe!
Come on! Come on!
Think of a way to move him.
Make him sneeze again.
What were you saying
about that poor father of yours?
Are your parents alive?
My father is, but I don't know
about my mother.
What sort of work does your father
do? How much does he make?
It's enough to make me cry.
My father doesn't do anything.
Most illustrious Fire-Eater
of all Fire-Eaters!
My poor little father is
the poor man of all poor men.
Yesterday he came close
to eating a wig...
...because it looked
like cornmeal pudding.
What a miserable family!
Do you have any brothers?
- No.
Yes, one.
- And how's he doing?
He's doing well. I mean,
he's not well, not well at all!
He's ill! Very ill!
He's dead! He's dead!
Now I remember.
He died, then he died again.
He died twice.
I have a brother
who's always dying.
Poor Father, he gave him
a funeral, but my father's so poor...
...that there was nothing there.
No people, not even the corpse.
And a rich family that lives
next to us gave a funeral...
...with seven, eight corpses,
because they're rich.
And my father,
not even one corpse!
Pinocchio, you're one terrific boy!
Come here and give me a kiss.
Pinocchio, I really feel sorry
for that poor father of yours.
Here are five gold coins.
Take them to your father
and give him my best regards.
Oh, five gold coins.
Thank you, most illustrious Sir!
So you're not going to eat me?
No, I won't be eating today.
Now be quiet, or I'll make
a stew out of all of you!
Good day, Pinocchio!
Good day, but how
do you know my name?
We saw your father
on his doorstep.
He was in his undershirt,
trembling like a leaf with cold.
Poor old man!
I'll go see him right now.
From today on, he'll never
tremble with cold again.
Why is that?
Why? Because I've become
a grand gentleman!
A grand gentleman!
There's very little to laugh about.
If you understand
anything at all...
...these are five beautiful
gold coins.
Five gold coins!
-Five gold coins?
-Five gold coins?!
I'll knock him out,
and we'll take off with the loot!
I'll throw a stone at him,
a stone, a stone!
Hold it! Not here!
Wait! Hold it!
Mister Pinocchio!
Accept our apologies, we haven't
even introduced ourselves.
I am the Fox, and this is the Cat.
Pleased to meet you, yes.
We're well-known around here
for being two respectable people.
-People!
-I can see that, yes.
And you, you who are such
a good puppet...
...what do you intend to do
with those five gold coins?
Do you intend to keep them
all for yourself?
No. I want to buy a brand-new
jacket for my father...
...and a spelling book for myself.
-For myself?
-For myself!
I want to go to school and study,
and earn an honest living...
...studying and working.
Goodbye!
-Studying and working!
You're really a puppet!
And to think that your five gold
coins could have become a thousand!
Two thousand!
Ten thousand!
Ten thousand? But how?
We'll tell you right now!
Instead of going home,
you'll have to come with us.
-With us!
-With you? Where to?
To a place where gold coins multiply.
Multiply!
-What's the name of this place?
-The Land of the Featherbrains.
Come on!
In the Land of the Featherbrains...
....there is a blessed field,
called the Field of Miracles.
What a wonderful place!
You make a hole and put your
coins in. After half an hour...
...a tree full of money comes up,
and all of a sudden you get rich.
But don't let anyone know!
It's a secret, keep it to yourself.
To yourself!
- I'll keep it to myself!
To myself!
- To yourself?
To yourself!
- To myself?
To myself?
- To yourself?
To yourself!
- That's enough!
I wasn't talking to you!
Please do serve us.
The meat was very tasty.
My compliments!
Tasty. My compliments.
Thank you, friends!
Pinocchio, you haven't touched
a thing yet! Eat your walnut!
Well, I'm not hungry.
I'm just not hungry!
Why don't we leave now?
Let's go!
No, no, no, it's still early.
We have to get a little rest!
Innkeeper!
- Tasty!
Show Mister Pinocchio
to his room...
...and remember to wake us
all up at midnight!
It's been a lovely little evening.
Get some rest now!
Rest now!
-Off to bed, then?
-Yes!
Well, then, good night!
-Good night!
-Night!
You know what?
I've changed my mind!
-No!
As soon as I pick the gold pieces,
instead of keeping them for myself...
...I'll keep two thousand,
which is enough for me.
And the rest I'll give to the two
of you as a present!
-Good heavens, no, Pinocchio!
-No!
You're insulting us!
You've got to give the money
to your father, who needs it.
The rest you can use to buy
a nice spelling book. Good night!
-Book! Good night!
-Good night!
-What good people!
-lf only there were more of them!
A walnut.
Well, it's midnight.
Where are my friends?
Aren't they ready?
They left two hours ago!
-Why?
-They told me:
"Tell Pinocchio that we'll be waiting
for him under the Great Oak...
...at the break of day."
Did they pay for the dinner?
You've got to be kidding! They
didn't want to slight you like that!
Too bad! It would have been a great
pleasure to receive such a slight!
-Here, take this.
-Thank you!
Who is that over there?
Who is it?
Pinocchio.
- Who is it?
It is I, the spirit
of the Talking Cricket!
Cricket! You really scared me.
Weren't you supposed to be dead?
What do you want?
Don't trust those who promise
to make you rich overnight.
They're either madmen
or swindlers.
Go back!
- But I want to go on!
The hour is late.
- I want to go on!
The night is dark!
The road is dangerous.
- I want to go on!
Children who want to do things their
own way always end up regretting it.
-The same old story. Good night.
-Good night, Pinocchio.
And may the heavens protect you
from dampness and assassins.
So now I'm supposed to be
in for all sorts of misfortunes?
I'm even supposed
to meet up with assassins!
It's a good thing I don't believe
in assassins, and I never did.
You can just imagine
how scared I am of assassins!
-Your money or your life!
-The assassins!
-We've got to catch him!
-Help!
Out with your money or
you'll be in big trouble!
Out with your money or you're
dead, you understand?
Go get some of those
dry sticks over there.
-We'll roast him!
-Let's burn him!
-Put them here, not there!
-There?
-Here!
-There, you mean!
Light the fire!
Look how it's burning!
Out with the money, puppet!
Where is he?
-Did you see him?
-I saw him!
-See you later!
-He's running away!
Get back here!
We've got to catch him!
-You're on fire!
-I am! And so are you!
Let's jump in, me over here
and you over there!
-Me over there?
-Me over there and you over here!
They're going to catch me!
Help me! I'm going to die!
What's that?
If I could only get to that
little house, maybe I'd be safe!
I didn't get that,
over here or over there?
-Come on, jump in!
-Over here?
Hey, is anyone home?
Is anyone home?
Open up, open up right now!
Be quick about it!
Wake up! Wake up!
Thank heavens, someone
is there after all! Open up!
There is no one in this house!
Well, then, you open up for me!
I am not here, either!
Then what are you doing up
there at the window?
No, don't go away, lovely lady
with the blue hair...
-The assassins are trying to get me!
-Now we're going to have some fun!
Please have pity...
...on a poor puppet who's
being chased by assassins!
You won't get away from us now!
Out with your money
or you'll be in big trouble!
Lovely lady! Help!
The coins!
-I've got them in my mouth!
-Open your mouth!
-Never!
-You're stubborn.
Farewell, puppet!
When we come back tomorrow,
let's hope you'll be so polite...
...as to let us find you
with your mouth wide open...
-...and, above all, dead!
-Dead.
Oh, Father!
My Father!
If only you were here!
What a shame,
he was a fine puppet!
Yes, he was a fine puppet!
-Good night, Madam Fairy.
-Good night, Medoro!
Madam Fairy,
there's an old man over here!
Yes, sir?
Medoro, that's you.
It's a mirror!
Well! Mirrors aren't what
they used to be!
Is he dead or alive?
I think he's dead.
It is my belief that the puppet
is already dead.
But if by some stroke of
bad luck he were not dead...
...then it would be a sure
indication that he is still alive.
I am sorry to have to contradict
my illustrious colleague...
...but in my opinion
the puppet is alive.
I know what sort of illness that
lousy puppet is suffering from!
He'll never become a respectable
boy! He'll always be a puppet!
He's a consummate scoundrel!
He's going to break the heart
of his poor father...
...who's made so many
sacrifices for him.
-And he doesn't even love him!
-That's not true!
Oh, Father, it's not true!
It's not true!
I love my father.
Gentlemen, if a living person
is not dead...
...it's a clear sign that doctors
are no longer needed.
Thank you for your enlightenment.
-Goodbye.
-Goodbye, Fairy.
This is the first case I've ever seen
of a dead person who cries.
I've never come across this before.
We'll need to reconsider everything.
He's alive, he's dead, everything
needs to be reconsidered.
He's burning.
Drink this, and in a few days
you'll be all better!
-ls it sweet or bitter?
-It's bitter, but it's good for you.
If it's bitter, I don't want it!
Listen to me. Drink it!
I don't like bitter things!
They don't appeal at all!
Drink it, and when you're done,
I'll give you a lump of sugar...
...to take the bad taste away.
Well, first I want
the lump of sugar.
Then I'll drink that horrible,
bitter medicine!
Here you are!
Delicious!
I just-- I don't want to drink
this horrible, bitter water!
No, no, and no again!
-You'll be sorry, my boy.
-I don't care.
-You've got a serious illness!
-lf you don't drink it you'll die.
-I don't care!
-Aren't you afraid of death?
-Not at all afraid!
I'd rather die than drink that
horrible, awful medicine!
I want to die!
What's that?
We have come
to take you away, Pinocchio.
To take me away?
What? But I'm not dead!
But you will be if you don't drink
that medicine right away!
But I wanted to drink it! She
didn't want to give it to me!
Dear Fairy, give me
the medicine right away!
Very well. This time we made
the trip for nothing.
Never mind, we'll be back
some other time!
This bed is great for bouncing!
I see the medicine
has done you some good.
Yes. Next time
I'll take it right away!
I have something very
important to do now.
Let me get my little hat.
Thank you for dehanging me,
dear Fairy. Bye!
Wait, Pinocchio.
Come over here and tell me.
-What did they want to hang you for?
-For the gold coins.
And what happened
to the gold coins?
I lost them.
-And where did you lose them?
-ln the forest nearby.
If you lost them in the forest
nearby, let's go look for them!
Now that I remember better,
much better, dear Fairy...
...I didn't lose the coins! No!
Good boy, Pinocchio!
I swallowed them, while I was
drinking your bitter medicine!
-But why are you laughing?
-Because of the lie you told!
How do you know
that I told a lie?
Because lies, dear Pinocchio,
are of two types:
Those that have short legs...
...and those that have
a long nose!
And mine, what type are they?
But, dear Fairy!
Dear Fairy, do you see
what a nose I have?
It's become so long,
so very long!
Everyone will laugh at me!
They will!
How am I supposed to go out?
Look what a nose I've got!
It doesn't appeal!
I don't want it, I don't want it!
The coins, dear Fairy...
...I didn't swallow the coins.
They're right here!
Good boy, Pinocchio.
You mustn't ever tell lies.
It's a nasty thing.
Yes, but, dear Fairy....
-I do love you so!
-I love you, too, very much.
I want to buy a jacket for my father,
since he sold his for me.
Have him come here!
I can surprise him! Bye, Fairy!
Bye! Come back soon!
I'll be waiting for you.
How did he manage to do that?
-Maybe someone cut the rope.
-Cut the rope.
-Yes. Incredible!
-Friends!
-It's Pinocchio! It's him!
-Wait, I'll handle this!
Dearest friends, oh, friends!
You're just the ones
I was looking for!
Pinocchio, we've been waiting
for you for so long!
-You know what happened to me?
-What?
Last night I met up
with the assassins.
-No! Those villains!
-Those villains of all villains!
-And did they get your coins?
-Oh, no!
No, you're right. In fact, here
they are. I've got all four of them!
Are we still in time
for the Field of Miracles?
What Field of Miracles?
-But--
-Of course, the Field of Miracles.
Let's go right away.
Which way is it?
It's over there!
-Over here?
-Over there!
Over there!
-We're finally here!
-We are?
-This is the Field of Miracles!
-It's lovely!
-But what about the trees?
-They've harvested everything.
We're late, hurry up!
Make a hole, come on!
But where?
-Right there!
-Over there!
-Over here!
Over here, all right.
Over here, then.
When I get rich...
...not only do I want to buy
a jacket for my father...
...but for the Fairy, too!
I'll buy the Fairy ten jackets...
...since she's the most beautiful
and the kindest fairy I've met!
Enough, that's enough!
Put the coins in
and cover up the hole!
All right, here they are!
Do we need to water them?
-When will they start growing?
-ln half an hour.
Take a little stroll.
You see that town over there?
It's the town of Saptrap.
Take a walk, come back
in half an hour, and you'll find--
Clink, clink, clink, clink!
-And all for you!
-For you.
Lucky, lucky you, Pinocchio!
Bye!
-Goodbye!
Excuse me, Mister Farmer,
has half an hour gone by?
Far too many half hours
have gone by!
Mamma mia, I hope I'm not late!
What do you have to laugh about,
Cricket? Hurry up!
-ls it me you're laughing at?
-Yes, I'm laughing at you.
Money doesn't grow in fields,
like beans and pumpkins.
You have to earn it honestly!
The same old lecture!
What do you mean?
You should know that
while you were away...
...the Fox and the Cat
took the gold coins...
...and ran off with them.
The Fox and the Cat,
they took--?
Two good people like them!
I can't believe it!
That's why I can't find them!
Thieves!
Thieves! I'm going to
report them right now!
There must be a judge in Saptrap!
I'll get the meanest one there is.
I'll give him first and last names.
They're going to
hear from me now!
Poor Pinocchio!
One was named Cat and the
other one Fox. A pair of thieves!
And I have a witness,
the Talking Cricket...
...who saw them right when they
took my gold coins and ran off!
A pair of thieves! The tree didn't
even have the chance to grow!
Is that all?
Yes! No! I also have a feeling they
stole another one of them from me...
...at the Red Crawfish lnn...
...because I ate a walnut, and they
made me pay a gold coin for it.
Expensive, that walnut of mine!
In compliance with Article One
of the Code of Saptrap--
Trap this sap and
take him to prison!
Five years!
I'm the one that
they were stolen from!
Come sap!
In you go, sap!
Well, there you have it.
I deserve it!
It serves me right!
The little Cricket told me so...
...but I'm a headstrong
and peevish puppet.
From now on, though,
I resolve to change my life.
I want to become a good boy,
well-behaved, obedient, honest...
...and I want to go to school
and work!
-A fine sucker you are!
-Who's that?
They've tamed you,
haven't they, puppet?
What's your name?
-My name is Pinocchio.
-How long are you in for?
Five years. How long does it
take for five years to go by?
-lt takes years.
-How many?
Five!
Dear Fairy!
-How long are you in for?
-I get out today. I was just leaving.
This place is all yours. I'll even
leave you my spelling book.
Are you a disobedient boy?
Yes, I am.
No one's going to tame me,
dear Pinocchio.
I want to show you something.
The other day,
instead of going to school...
...I ran away from home.
-You know what I did?
-No.
I went into a candy shop...
...and I stole all the lollipops
they had!
-No!
-Yes!
And did you lick all of them?
I was just about to give
the first one a lick...
...when I heard the voice
of a policeman:
"Stop, don't move
your tongue, thief...
...and hand over
the 28 lollipops you stole!"
They confiscated them...
...and told me that they had to give
them back to the owner of the shop.
But I think...
...they licked them all themselves!
There is one other thing,
though, the lollipops--
There weren't 28 of them.
There were 29!
Let me see.
-You know what flavor this is?
-No!
It's out of this world.
Smell it!
-No!
-Yes! Tangerine!
Listen...
...would you let me take a lick?
Just one?
You lick there, and I'll lick
here. Go ahead!
Delicious!
Listen.
When you get back home...
...are your parents...
...delicious, going
to send you to school?
Remember one thing, puppet:
There's only one person who
decides what I have to do.
And that's Lucignolo!
-And who is this Lucignolo?
-I am! Me!
-You?
-Yes!
Come on, Lucignolo!
Out you go! You've learned
your lesson, haven't you?
Now get yourself to school!
Bye, Pinocchio!
See you in five years!
Bye, Lucignolo!
Here, this is for you.
-What is it?
-Your supper. Pear peels.
A, B, C, D, H....
At least I know the first ones.
Now, horse and...
...elee...elee...
...phan....
What's going on?
Oh, Father, dear Fairy....
-Come on, come on out!
-What's going on?
Everyone's free! Free!
-So have five years gone by?
-No, four months.
A son's been born to the King of
Saptrap. In sign of jubilation...
...there will be great festivities.
All the criminals are being freed!
Hey, but I'm a criminal, too!
-What did you say?
-I'm a criminal, too.
Oh, well, in that case,
this way, please!
Long live the King!
Long live the King of Saptrap!
What I've been through! Who knows
if my father has waited for me?
Will I find him
at the Fairy's house?
I haven't seen him for so long.
I'm just dying to give him...
...a thousand hugs and
finish him off with kisses!
Will the Fairy forgive me
for the terrible thing I did to her?
Oh, let's hope so!
Let's hope so! Let's hope so.
"Here lies the Fairy...."
"Here lies the Fairy
with the blue hair...
...who died of grief
because of Pinocchio"!
Pinocchio! But that's me!
Oh, dear Fairy, dear Fairy!
Why did you die?
Oh, why didn't I die...
...since I'm so bad and you were
so very, very good, dear Fairy?
Dear Fairy, what do you
have to do to die?
If you truly love me...
...if you love your Pinocchio...
...come back to life,
like you were before...
...when I could look at you
because you were alive!
Dear Fairy, live again!
Live again, dear Fairy!
Live again!
DOVE: Tell me, boy,
what are you doing down there?
Don't you see? I'm crying!
Is there a puppet named Pinocchio
among your friends?
Did you say Pinocchio?
-That's me!
-Then you must know Geppetto.
Of course! He's my poor father!
Did he talk to you about me?
For goodness' sake, answer me,
where is he?
He's been roaming the world
for four months in search of you!
Is he far away?
Take me to him, please!
Follow me.
Thank you, my dear Dove.
I'll get to see my father again!
I'll see my father again!
Here I come, Father!
What happened?
What happened is that because
of his son, who he can't find...
...a poor father got
into a little boat...
...and went to look for him
on the other side of the sea!
But that, but that looks like...
...that seems to be--
That is my father!
Father, Father, Father, Father!
It's me, it's your son!
Father!
-Dear Father!
-Pinocchio!
He saw me! Here I am, Father!
Father!
I'll never leave you again!
Come back, dear Father!
Father!
Father! Father!
I want to save my father!
Oh, Father! Father!
And now what?
That was a narrow escape,
mamma mia!
What kind of place is this?
Are there are any towns in this place
with the sea all around it?
I want to go see,
just for the heck of it.
Dear Fairy, now that I've lost
you and my father...
...where will I sleep at night?
It would be better, a hundred times
better, if I died, too.
Yes, I want to die!
And I'm starving.
Excuse me, kind lady.
Would you give me something
to eat if I carry your jug for you?
What are you doing here, puppet?
If you only knew what
I've been through!
I'm fed up with living
the life of a puppet.
I want to become
like everyone else!
And you will be, if you prove
that you deserve to.
Really? How?
Respectable boys are obedient,
but you, on the other hand--
I never obey.
Respectable boys
always tell the truth.
And I always tell lies.
Respectable boys are happy
to go to school.
And me,
school gives me a bellyache.
School is really, it's really....
Excuse me, kind lady,
but you....
How can you know that l--?
But.... But it's you!
Oh, dear Fairy, dear Fairy!
If you only knew my sorrow
and the lump I felt in my throat...
...when I read "Here lies...."
I know, and that's why
I've forgiven you.
The sincerity of your sorrow made me
realize that you have a kind heart...
...and perhaps
there's some hope...
...that you'll get back
on the right path.
Oh, yes, yes, dear Fairy.
-I want to get back on it!
-Then you'll have to obey me.
Oh, yes! I'll study, I'll work,
I'll do everything you tell me to!
And I'm telling you that tomorrow
morning you have to go to school...
...and you'll go because
you promised me to.
Yes, I'll go.
Oh, dear Fairy.
The house in the forest....
Hey, boys, isn't this cute?
It's mine!
That hat's mine!
It's mine. I found it on
the beach and I get to keep it!
No, I'm the one who lost it.
It's mine!
-Then come and get it!
-My father made it for me.
Give me back my hat or
things are going to end badly!
We're really scared!
Look how he's dressed!
Go to school, puppet,
or you'll be late!
You're telling me to go
to school?
Only one person
decides what I have to do.
And that's Pinocchio!
-And who is this Pinocchio?
-I am!
Pinocchio!
His name is Pinocchio!
Yes, and I want my hat back!
Pinocchio...cuckoo!
Cuckoo to me?
I'll beat you all up!
A fight! My favorite!
This is the life!
My hat! That hat's mine!
It's mine, it's mine!
Take this, puppet!
Mamma mia, help me.
I don't feel very good.
-I'm dying.
-Dying?
-What happened to you, Eugenio?
-ls he dead?
Eugenio's dead! Let's go!
Let's go! Let's get out of here!
Eugenio! It wasn't me!
Breathe! Open your eyes,
Eugenio!
Oh, get up, Eugenio! Get up!
What did you do to that boy?
Me and my classmates
were just playing here...
...and at a certain point
he didn't feel very good.
This boy has been hit in the head!
-Who hit him?
-Well, not me!
And what was he hit with?
-With that book over there.
-And whose book is it?
-Mine.
-That's enough! Not another word!
- I knew it!
-This boy could die.
Eugenio.
You, take this poor boy
to the hospital!
And you, puppet,
you're coming with us to jail!
Put him in chains!
Oh, Policemen...
...could you please cover me
with your capes? I'm so ashamed!
You should have thought
of that before!
Nice Policemen, couldn't
we take another road to go to jail?
This is the road! Keep walking!
Stop! Stop him!
This way! This way! Faster!
What a strange-looking marten!
Hey, what are you doing
on my property?
You wanted to steal my grapes,
did you?
No, I'm a respectable boy!
I was going to school!
You go to school with handcuffs
on? Nice school!
You escaped from jail,
and you're dangerous!
I'm leaving that trap on your foot!
In fact, I really want to teach
you a nice lesson!
Since...
...my watchdog has died,
my poor Melampo...
...you'll take his place!
But I've never been a watchdog!
It's easy! If any thieves
show up, you bark!
-But how?
-Like this. Woof, woof!
-Let's go, my pretties!
-Woof, woof!
Loud, louder!
Again!
I'm so scared! Woof!
It's so dark!
But it serves me right.
I'm afraid it serves me right.
If only I could be born again!
But it's too late now.
I'll just have to be patient!
Woof, woof, woof, woof!
Thieves! Woof!
Shh!
Melampo, it's me!
Are you an idiot?
Act like a good dog!
I beg your pardon, but I'm not
a dog! I'm a puppet.
A puppet? I don't trust you.
If you're really a puppet,
answer this question:
What's the best
lollipop flavor of all?
I know! It's tangerine!
-Why?
-Because-- Why?
Because it's out of this world!
Lucignolo! Noble soul!
I'm so glad to see you!
What are you doing here?
If you only knew
what I've been through!
What are you doing here?
They've got the nicest chickens
in the area.
We can trade eight of them
for two rocking horses.
Help me!
All right, no, well, but you
know it's not nice to steal.
Set me free, and then
tomorrow morning...
...we can go to school together.
How about it?
That's a stupid way to talk,
Pinocchio.
They've tamed you, haven't they?
I'll set you free...
...but I'm still going to take
the four chickens!
I caught you in the act! Now we've
got some scores to settle! Thieves!
-Run! Run!
-Thank you, noble soul!
Pinocchio?
Yes?
Come in, come on in!
But it's late. I'd better--
I wouldn't want to bother you.
You're not bothering me.
Come in!
I'm not bothering you?
Well, all right.
So, tell me,
how did school go today?
Well, fine.
We learned rivers...
...and then numbers, letters.
Almost all of them:
A, B, C, H, L....
I can't remember anymore.
And then the teacher examined me...
...and he gave me
a 10 out of 10.
What did he give you?
He gave me a 10....
It's not true!
It's not true! It's not true!
I wanted to go to school, but
after what I've been through...
...and coming back home,
I said to myself:
"How will I be able to present
myself to my dear Fairy now?
What will she say when she
sees me? Will she forgive me?
She'd have to be too good
to forgive me.
Who knows if she's so good
that she'll forgive me?"
And then I said, "No!"
Then I said, "Maybe she will...
...because she's good
and beautiful."
Then I said,
"lf she forgives me...
...that means she's the best fairy
in the whole world!
If she doesn't forgive me,
she's not!"
But in my opinion, she is!
So she really
should forgive me!
We'll see when I get home,
who knows?
Because in my life, dear Fairy...
...I've never had a quarter
of an hour of peace.
Not even a quarter of an hour!
Do you see what happens when
you don't keep your promises?
Yes! And I deserve a punishment.
I'm afraid I deserve one!
No one will ever
punish you again.
In fact, now that
you've truly understood...
...I want to give you the most
wonderful gift there is.
Yes, your wish will come true.
You'll become a boy
like all the others!
Would you like that?
Oh, dear Fairy,
more than anything else!
-Will you become a good boy?
-I've already become a good boy.
I've learned my lesson.
This time I've learned my lesson!
I believe you, Pinocchio.
I can tell that you mean it!
Today is a day of celebration
for you, Pinocchio...
...and the Fairy wanted to invite
in her beautiful house of her...
...all of your future classmates
and your teacher, myself.
Pleased to meet you,
pleased to meet you all!
By hereby cutting the cake...
...I confirm Pinocchio's entrance
into the world of good boys.
You can even choose who you
want to sit next to at school.
All right. At school
I'd like to sit next to--
-One, and two--
-Wait a minute!
-What's the matter?
-Lucignolo's not here!
-Lucignolo?
-Yes!
Everyone else is here. Lucignolo
is at the bottom of the class...
...and I've already
decided to fail him.
He's a good-for-nothing.
It's better that he's not here.
EVERYONE:
Yes, yes, yes!
-So, one--
-No!
He's my best friend, and I love him.
He'd like to be here...
...and I'll find him.
Pinocchio, start being obedient!
You're making a mistake,
because Lucignolo--
Good boy!
That does you honor.
It's only right that on the most
important day of your life...
...you want your best friend
next to you.
That's a beautiful thing.
Good boy!
Go and come right back.
We'll be waiting for you!
Bye! I'll be right back.
Wait for me. Bye!
Lucignolo!
What are you doing over there?
I've been looking for you
for three hours.
Have you heard the great news?
Do you know about the good luck
I've had?
I'm not going to be a puppet
anymore!
I'll become a boy like you,
like all the others!
-Much good may it do you!
-What do you mean?
There's a party at my house.
You're the only one who's not there!
Let's go!
I can't. I'm leaving tonight...
...and I'm going far, far away.
Where are you going?
I'll live in a town that's the most
wonderful town in the world!
And what's it called?
It's called Playland.
What a nice name! Playland?
Why don't you come, too?
Let's go!
No, I'm staying here
with my Fairy.
Poor sucker,
you're making a big mistake!
I'm not making any mistake at all.
What kind of town is it?
I'll tell you just two things.
No one ever asks you to work
in that town...
...there are no teachers, no books...
...and you don't have to go
to school on Sunday.
What a lovely town!
But you don't have to go to
school on Sundays here, either!
Yes, but in that town every week
is made up of seven Sundays!
And just imagine, vacation
starts on the first day of January...
...and ends on the last day
of December...
-...that falls on a Sunday!
-Exactly!
And how do you spend your days
in Playland?
Playing and doing whatever you
feel like from morning till night.
What do you think?
Are you coming? Yes or no?
No! I promised the Fairy
I'd be right back!
Have a good trip, Lucignolo!
Bye, puppet!
Just imagine, a place where
there are no schools.
One last, one last thing.
Well, do you know for sure,
really for sure...
...that vacation starts
on the first day of January...
...and ends on the very
last day of December?
Do you know that for sure?
For extra-sure!
He'll be back!
I'm going, I'm leaving,
Lucignolo.
Bye, farewell, this time for real.
All right. Bye, Pinocchio.
-Here it is!
-What?
The wagon that's come to get me!
It's wonderful, wonderful!
So, Lucignolo, I'll stay
for another two minutes.
Then I'm leaving.
Good evening, my little dear.
Unfortunately,
the wagon is full!
If it's full inside,
I'll sit out here!
And you, my love,
what do you intend to do?
Are you coming with us
or staying?
What did I tell you?
It's paradise!
-Bye, Pinocchio!
-Bye, Lucignolo!
Pinocchio! Pinocchio!
Mamma mia, it's an inferno!
I've got to find him right away,
or it'll be too late.
Pinocchio, Pinocchio!
Dearest friends, here I am!
I'm up here! Friends!
Help! Help! Help!
Where are you, Pinocchio?
I've got to look for him.
Stop it!
A little peace and quiet.
Get out of here!
You'll all become jackasses.
Pinocchio! Where are you?
Saint Anthony!
Sacred deities!
I'll never find him!
And you, get out of this place!
How can I make you understand?
Leave! You'll all become asses!
Help! I can't breathe!
I'm suffocating!
I can't stand it!
Get me out of here!
Help! Help! Help!
Saint Anthony!
I can't take it anymore!
Oh, mamma!
It's an inferno!
Lucignolo! Everyone
is asleep already?
Where shall we go?
What shall we do?
-It's time to go to sleep now!
-No, not to sleep!
Come on, I feel like doing
all sort of things!
I know, but just
two or three hours...
...then tomorrow morning
we can start all over again!
I can't wait to start all over again!
-You like it here.
-Yes.
And to think that you didn't
want to come along.
It's true, Lucignolo.
If I'm a truly happy boy today,
it's all thanks to you!
You don't need to thank me.
I did it with all my heart!
Noble soul!
Lucignolo, the teacher
wanted to fail you.
At my house, he said,
"I'm going to fail that one."
I know, but I forgive him.
Noble soul!
Good night, my friend!
Thank goodness it's all over!
They're turning into jackasses.
You'll have to pay good money
for them...
...because they're all tender
young things, nice and fresh!
-That one's all set to go!
-I'll buy it!
-How many do you want this year?
-About 50. I want hard workers.
And make sure they
can take a beating!
They can, they can!
That's a nice one!
It certainly is.
How many do you want?
I want about 50, too.
When can we take them?
In a matter of minutes.
-Would there happen to be one?
-Of course there is!
We've got them in all shapes
and sizes.
All the boys turn
into jackasses here.
First the ears, then the tail,
then "hee-haw," just like that!
I'll take a hundred of them!
Look at this one, just look
at this pretty little muzzle!
What did you think you'd become?
Doctors?
Professors?
You're all jackasses!
All jackasses!
It's already morning!
I can't wait to start all over again!
It's great being here!
Let's go, Lucignolo, let's go!
But these are....
They are....
These are two genuine ass's ears.
And they're all hairy!
Just look!
I don't want them!
What shall I do now?
I'm ashamed to go out like this!
This must be one
of Lucignolo's tricks!
It's all his fault, yes!
I'm going to see him right now.
I'll give him a piece of my mind!
Lucignolo, it's me, Pinocchio!
Come in, come on in!
Good morning, Lucignolo.
How are you?
Fine!
So, Lucignolo, how come you're
wearing that cloth on your head?
The doctor ordered me to...
...because my knee hurts!
Poor Lucignolo!
How about you?
Me? Well, I hurt my elbow...
...and so the same doctor
told me....
-Poor Pinocchio!
-Yes, I know. It's unfortunate.
Lucignolo, would you do
me a favor, please?
-Gladly! With all my heart.
-Would you show me your ears?
Gladly! But first I want to see
yours, dear Pinocchio!
No, then let's do this.
I'll count to--
-Do you know how to count?
-Of course!
Then you count to three...
...and on three all three of us
will take them off.
All right!
One, and three!
What ears you've got, Lucignolo!
Just look at the ears you've got!
There's....
You've got something....
Lucignolo!
What's this here?
Oh, mamma mia!
It's a tail!
You've sprouted a tail!
-Do I have one, too?
-No, not yet.
What does that mean?
That I'll get one, too?
I don't know...
-...but I'm scared.
-It's disgusting!
What's happening to me?
Pinocchio, help me!
Help me, Pinocchio!
Lucignolo, Lucignolo!
Pinocchio! Pinocchio!
-You're here?
-Lucignolo.
Lucignolo, you've turned
into a donkey!
Help me, I've got a tail!
Dear Fairy, help!
I've got a tail.
CRlCKET:
You deserve it, Pinocchio!
Dear Cricket, thank goodness
you are here, Cricket.
If I had listened
to my good Fairy...
...I would have become
a respectable boy by now.
But from now on, I promise you--
What is there to promise at this
point? It's too late!
You missed your chance to become
a boy like all the others!
-What's going to happen to me?
-You'll become a donkey...
...Iike your friend here...
...good for pulling a cart!
No.
There's no use crying now.
-Farewell, Pinocchio!
-Lucignolo!
No, don't leave, dear Cricket!
I promise you I'll work, I'll study.
I'll do everything.
Don't leave!
Lucignolo, was that me?
Was that "mee-haw"?
Now, my respectable auditors,
ladies and gentlemen...
...the humble undersigned has
the pleasure of presenting...
...to this substantial public the
most celebrated donkey in the world.
Pinocchio, the Little Donkey!
I beg you to observe...
...the wild game transuding
from this mammal.
Admire him!
And then judge him!
That's a good fellow, Pinocchio,
play dead! And that's not all!
I've also given this animal
of a beast a training in dance...
...not to mention
the other relative forms...
...of jumping through
flaming hoops...
...and over velvet-covered poles!
Oh, my dear Fairy!
You don't bray in the face
of the audience, jackass!
I beg your pardon.
I promise that tomorrow I'll learn
some grammar and etiquette...
...to this hairy hoofed mammal!
Come on, Pinocchio, chin up!
Let this crowded crowd see...
...how I've learned you to jump
with the whip! Chin up, Pinocchio!
Go, Pinocchio, go!
Great fall, Pinocchio, a great fall!
What are you doing, jackass?
On your feet! What's the matter?
Music, maestro.
Hurry up, bring in the clowns!
Pinocchio, the Little Donkey!
He broke his leg. Throw
him into the sea! Drown him!
Pinocchio, the Little Donkey!
A round of applause!
Dear Fairy, dear Fairy!
You're the one who saved me!
I knew it! I knew it!
If you only knew what
I've been through!
But I promise you, dear Fairy,
that from now on...
...I'll be a good boy,
and an honest one!
Quick, Pinocchio, hurry up,
swim faster!
I'll go to work, I promise.
I can't swim any faster than this!
Come on, hurry up! Faster!
Come on, faster!
Then you love me, too,
dear Fairy?
When I'm with you,
nothing can happen to me!
Pinocchio! Watch out!
What?
What? What's this? Dear Fairy!
Oh, dear Fairy, help!
I've been eaten!
A monster fish!
Let's hope he won't be able
to digest me.
It's not fair. Right when I was about
to embrace my dear Fairy again!
Who's there?
I'm so scared. It's probably
full of monster fish in here.
What kind of place is this?
-Who's there?
-Who can that be?
MAN: Who is that?
-I'm so scared!
MAN: Is someone there?
-I'm a tuna fish!
And you, what kind of fish
are you?
I'm not a fish.
I'm a poor old man.
My name is Geppetto.
Geppetto! My father!
I'm here because of my son...
...who I never want to see again
because he's a bad boy.
And if I had him right here...
...I'd beat the living daylights
out of him...
...with my own hands! Bad boy!
Oh, yes? Was this son of yours
really so bad?
I put so much loving care into
making him into a good boy!
I went to jail for him,
you know, Mister Tuna.
-He's a bad boy.
-It's not true.
An ingrate, a liar,
and he has no heart.
No heart at all.
While I'm in here suffering...
...he's probably
running around somewhere...
-Father, I want my Father!
-...having a good time!
Do you understand Mister Tuna...
...what a bad boy I have?
But Mister Tuna...
...you're crying!
We tuna fish cry very easily!
But in any case, it's all over
for me now, Mister Tuna.
I'll never see my son again.
But if you saw him now,
what would you do?
What do you think I would do?
I'm a father, he's my son...
...and, in spite of everything,
I love him. If I had him here now...
...I'd hug him as hard as I could...
...I'd kiss him,
and I'd die of happiness.
But never mind!
Father!
-Pinocchio, my son!
-I'm not a tuna fish!
It's me, Pinocchio the puppet...
...your one and only son!
Pinocchio, Pinocchio my son!
-I don't know how to swim!
-I'll help you, Father.
-Save yourself.
-I'm not going without you...
...without my father.
Oh, look, Father!
-Look!
-I'm not coming, I'm afraid!
He's getting ready for the sneeze
that'll send us all the way home.
Father, let's go.
I'm not coming! I'm afraid!
Give me back my wig!
-Come and get it!
-You're the same old Pinocchio!
-Father, where are you?
-My wig!
-I've got your wig!
-Give me back my wig!
Lean on me,
and I'll take you home.
I need a glass of milk so badly
that I'll die if I don't get one.
There's a farmer nearby.
His name is Giangio,
and he has a nice cow.
Go see if he'll let
you sweat a little...
...in exchange for some milk
for me.
Giangio? All right.
I'll put you to bed. Then I'll go
to this farmer to get some work.
But you don't know
how to do anything!
Good boy, Pinocchio.
I worked an extra
two hours today...
...and so Mister Giangio
gave me a penny, too.
And with that penny,
I bought myself this lollipop!
A lollipop?
Yes, but it's for supper!
For supper.
And besides,
it's not all for tonight.
Half tonight and half
for supper tomorrow night!
Good boy!
Tonight I'll give it three
licks on this side...
...and tomorrow night
three licks on that side.
-May l?
-Yes!
One...
...and two...
...and three.
Three...delicious!
Look what I've got here, the nicest
carrots and eggplants in the market!
Good boy, Pinocchio!
Just two more hours--
No, Mister Farmer Giangio,
I want to keep going until tonight.
I want to earn
an extra glass of milk.
My father is expecting just one.
If I bring him two,
I'll give him a big surprise!
Good boy, you're a real worker.
Even my donkey can't push like that!
What?
You mean you have a donkey?
Yes, but he's sick.
I worked him too hard...
...and now he's at the end
of his life.
Just taste these carrots,
sweet as cake! Bye, Pinocchio!
Let's go, Cenerina, let's go!
Come on!
You'd drink another one,
wouldn't you?
Of course I'd drink another one...
...but I'm afraid I'll have to
wait until tomorrow.
Father?
Pinocchio!
What a pretty donkey!
How're you doing?
Well, my pretty one?
You're not feeling well,
little donkey?
Come on, cheer up!
I'm sorry you're not feeling well,
little donkey. You're very pretty.
But, little donkey, but....
You know....
Actually....
I think...
...I've seen you before!
Pinocchio!
Noble soul!
It's you!
Cheer up, Lucignolo, cheer up!
Come on, Lucignolo!
Look who's here, Lucignolo!
I'm so glad to see you again!
Lucignolo, you're not well.
Come on, look, Lucignolo!
Look what I've got!
It's tangerine.
It's tangerine, Lucignolo, come on!
Out of this world!
Come on, have some more.
It's tangerine, Lucignolo!
Tangerine! Come on!
Is he dead?
You're so moved by an ass?
Well, I'll tell you,
he was a friend of mine.
-He was a classmate of mine!
-Nice school!
-You had a jackass for a classmate!
-Yes.
I can just imagine the wonderful
studies you've done.
Get back to work, go on!
All right!
Good boy, good boy, I'm starting
to feel a lot better now, you know?
How about you? Why don't you
sleep for a couple of hours?
You look tired, son!
Who, me, Father? No, no, no.
I'm a strong puppet.
You built me well, Father!
I'll get some sleep later. Now I need
to make some wicker baskets...
...so I can sell them
and get some money...
...and buy you a brand-new jacket!
How about it, Father?
Thank you.
Good boy.
Yes, I really do need
a nice new little jacket!
If you can find it,
get one with black stripes.
Yes, I like black stripes.
-What are you doing, Pinocchio?
-What?
Are you falling asleep? Don't you
have to make the wicker baskets?
What? Yes, I'm going right now!
I'll do it outside so I won't bother you.
All right, Father? I'm going....
The milk, you drank it all up,
didn't you?
All of it!
- Good job, great! Bye.
Bye!
Good boy!
Oh, dear Fairy!
Dear Fairy!
Good boy, Pinocchio!
Thanks to your good heart, you
deserve much praise and much joy.
You did it!
Dear Fairy, you've taught
me so many things!
I'll never forget them!
Never!
Stay on this same path, and
in the future you'll be happy.
Bye, Pinocchio!
Bye, dear Fairy!
Bye!
Goodbye, Mister Pinocchio!
Bye, Medoro, goodbye!
Bye, you rascal of a boy!
Dear Cricket, you're here too?
You're leaving?
Yes, but if you like,
I can stay!
No, no, no!
I mean, I was just asking.
I imagine you must have
so many things to do. Bye.
Bye, Pinocchio, bye!
- Let's go, little mice!
Here we go again, Medoro!
This is the last time
I'm doing this for you.
Tomorrow you're coming with me
to buy some glasses!
He was a fine puppet, though!
Father!
You see this?
Take a look!
- What is it?
Touch it, pull it.
Go ahead and pull! Pull!
It's real!
Father!
Tell me,
what happened?
How are all these changes possible?
- It's all thanks to you!
Thanks to me? Why?
Because when children
go from being bad to good...
...they have the power to instill
a new, cheerful, and serene air...
...in everything around them!
And the puppet?
What happened to it?
There it is, over there!
You see it?
How funny I was
when I was a puppet...
...and how happy I am now that
I've become a respectable boy!
Pinocchio?
- Yes?
Come here!
Here you go!
What is it?
- Your books.
Go to school and distinguish yourself.
Thank you. Bye, Father!
Bye, Pinocchio!
Good morning!
- This way, please!
Edited by Raymy
www.ondertitels.nl