- Dad, are you awake?
- Yes.
It's time to get up.
What do you think?
- Is it breakfast time?
- Yes, it sure is.
- Well--
- Better get up.
I need a bite.
Need your glasses?
Yeah, on the
pillow there.
Dad, I got your breakfast.
Good for you.
It looks delicious.
Do you need anything else?
Piece of toast,
cup of coffee?
No, I don't need no
coffee this morning.
I think I'll do with
the orange juice.
- If you need anything, yell.
- Thank you.
[honks]
- Good morning.
- Morning.
So how's your mom
doing today?
She's doing good.
She working yet?
No, she hasn't found anything.
- Good morning.
- Hey, how are you doing today?
- Good. How are you?
- Terrific.
What can I help you
with this morning?
I think I'll have...
a twister.
- Okay. Is this
for here or to go?
- It'll be for here.
I want to get
a picture.
Okay.
- 'Cause you're
my bestest friend.
- Huh?
You're my best friend,
and I just need to get
a picture of you.
Where do you want me
to stand?
Here's really good.
It's almost too nice
to go in there,
you think?
Yeah, let's go back.
- I was talking to Judy
yesterday.
- Yeah?
She was telling me about
the huge order they have
coming in,
which means we're really
gonna have to pump up
production.
- That's great.
- That's what I thought.
We're already doing
too much as it is.
I think so too.
They need to get
some more help.
- What do you think?
- Yeah.
[machinery whirring]
So you think tonight
maybe you can give me a ride
to my other job
at the shovel factory?
- You know I will.
- Yeah.
I always told you
if you ever needed
a ride or anything,
all you had to do was ask.
I appreciate it.
No problem.
You been out
on a date lately?
No, not for a while.
No prospects, huh?
No. I've been busy
working pretty much.
I leave here and I only got
so much time before I have
to go to the other job, so...
It's about like
the rest of us,
I'm telling you.
Plus I gotta work nights,
so if I want to go out at night,
I can't do that,
unless I have a day off, so--
- I'm ready for the beaches.
- Yeah?
- Yeah. I want to go to Aruba.
- Oh, yeah?
I saw that on TV the other day.
The beaches are great.
I think I'm about done.
How about you?
Yeah. I'm gonna
go and smoke.
You talk to
your dad lately?
Um, no, not since
the last time.
It's probably...
six months ago.
Where's he at now?
Last I heard he was living
in Arizona, I think,
and, uh, I guess he got
remarried to someone.
I haven't heard
from him since.
- [TV playing]
- [sewing machine whirring]
[woman on TV, indistinct]
Also approved was $29,000
to retain Roseanne Buell
as the county's Juvenile
Justice liaison.
Nearly 22,000 baby boomers
in West Virginia
have no health insurance
as they near retirement.
A Marshall University study
says of those who
participated in the study,
75% say their health
is in excellent or even--
- Hi.
- Hey.
How's work?
It was all right.
How are you?
I'm all right.
You hungry?
Uh, no,
I don't think so.
- I'm just gonna go to bed.
- All right.
- Good night.
- You ready for your first day?
- Oh, yeah.
- Not nervous or anything?
- No. I'm fine.
Okay, that's great.
So tell me again,
do you have airbrush experience?
Yeah. I used to airbrush
T-shirts at the mall.
Great. When you were doing that,
were you working with
other airbrushers,
or were you just
waiting on the customers?
No. I just worked by myself.
They would bring me
what I needed,
bring me the orders,
and I would take care of it.
Okay, well,
that's really good.
We'll see what happens.
Good morning,
everybody.
I know you guys are all aware of
the big order that we've got in,
and we've been working hard
to get it done,
but we feel like you guys
need some help.
And so here she is.
Her name is Rose.
We were very fortunate
to find Rose
in the fact that she has
airbrush experience.
She's worked with stencils
before, so she'll be working
in the head-painting area.
I'm sure she'll have questions
throughout the day,
so please help her.
I found Rose,
when we were interviewing her,
to be very sweet
and the consummate team player,
so I think she'll
fit in really well
with our workforce here.
So I'll let you guys
introduce her through
the course of the day,
and, um, please help her out
with anything that she needs.
Get to work.
[airbrush hissing]
You know you got to
double-glue those before
you put 'em in the box, right?
Yes, I'm aware of that.
So do either
of you smoke?
- I don't.
- Yeah, I smoke.
- Do you?
- Mm-hmm.
Well, when you're done,
if you want to,
we can go grab a cigarette.
- Sure.
- Okay.
Where did you used to work?
I used to work
at a nursing home.
And what'd you do there?
I was a professional
ass-wiper.
You know, the bottom,
the CNA.
The one that everybody
comes to when something
dirty needs done
is basically what I did.
I took care of people,
the people who can't do
for themselves anymore,
you have to do everything
that they can't do:
shower them, dress them,
feed them.
Just depends on who you have,
what you have to do.
It's a hard job
that you really, really
have to be dedicated to.
You really have to like
what you're doing
or you just can't.
'Cause there's, like,
days you go in there
and it's just--
You just want to turn
around and walk out,
it's that bad.
This isn't as hard
of work, but...
I don't think I'm gonna
like this much better.
And what about you?
What was
the question?
Where did you work
before you came here?
I used to work maintenance
in an old factory.
- That's cool.
- Mmm.
I'm very ready
to get out of this area.
Why is that?
'Cause there's
nothing here.
Mm-hmm.
I'm living in this
little apartment
with my daughter.
She's two.
You can't make money
in this area.
It's just poor.
Everything's poor.
Are you married?
No, I'm not married.
I thought I would be,
but things don't always
work out like you think
they're going to.
You know.
Just another
bad decision.
Yeah.
What are you doing
right after work today?
Well, I probably have to...
get home and see my dad.
- Do you think you might
be able to give me a ride?
- I don't see why not.
I have another job
that I have to be at
like right after,
but it's not
that far from here.
Okay.
I'd really
appreciate it.
No problem.
Are you about done?
Yeah, think so.
[Rose] I guess we're gonna
go have a cigarette,
and we'll see you back up
there in a little bit.
Okay.
Ready?
Rose?
Where are you?
I'm in the bathroom.
Oh, my God, Rose!
What are you doing?
I'm taking a bath.
Do you do this
all the time?
No, not all the time.
Remember when I told you
I worked in a nursing home?
I sure did.
I got hit in the back
with a tray table
by this little old man.
And it messed up my back.
I couldn't pick Jesse up
for like a month.
But every once in a while
my muscles will contract,
and I get really sore.
And this feels
really good.
And my apartment
has no bathtub.
It just has a shower,
so I take advantage.
But I clean it when I'm done.
I clean after I bathe.
- Okay.
- [giggles]
I was kind of wondering.
I didn't know what would happen
if we'd get caught.
No. She won't be here
for a long time.
Oh, my gosh!
I mean, every room
was the size of
my whole living room.
The bedrooms--
You could fit my whole house
in two rooms in that house.
I could not believe it.
Gorgeous!
Chandeliers coming down
out of the ceiling.
- It was unreal.
- Hmm.
I mean, just fabulous,
fabulous, fabulous.
And then... you are not
gonna believe this.
She tells me how particular
this lady is.
And then she invites me
inside of this house
that she's cleaning.
Guess what.
She was in
the Jacuzzi bathtub--
I am not kidding--
taking a bath.
- She was supposed to be
cleaning it?
- Yes!
- Got sidetracked.
- I'm not kidding.
I couldn't believe it.
I thought I was gonna die.
All I could think about
was that lady coming home
and catching--
You know, here I am,
not supposed to be there,
in there checking
her house out,
and there's Rose
in the tub.
And you know,
I thought, "Wow."
Yeah, I'd be afraid of 'em
just coming home too early.
I'm not too sure
about her.
- Yeah?
- What do you think?
I don't know.
She seems fine to me.
- You think so?
- Yeah.
She scares me a little.
Hmm.
[air hissing]
I was working at a restaurant,
and they work day and night.
Turn two different shifts.
I just didn't have anybody
to care for him.
It was really rough,
and I didn't want to have
to put him in a nursing home.
- The expense for that is huge.
- Yeah, those places--
And you don't want to do that
unless you absolutely have to.
- Oh, really?
- Yeah.
Because a lot of times
they're understaffed
or they don't have all the
equipment that they need.
You know, you get people in
there that shouldn't be there,
that should be in other
facilities, that are violent.
You know, you just, you never
know what you're gonna get.
You don't know who they're gonna
put in the room with 'em.
You know,
because it's not...
The way that they put people
together is not necessarily
by what their sickness may be,
like, you know, put two stroke
patients in the same room.
Some people might be bedridden,
and some people might be up
walking around.
And they get into each other's
things and tear stuff up.
- Oh, wow.
- Yeah.
- Glad I didn't do that.
- No.
And as far as, like,
management,
they're so tight that
what they'll do is take--
You know, you might clock
out, but if they see you
walking across the parking lot,
they'll be like, "Can you come
just for a minute and come
help with this or that?"
And you end up staying over
an hour or better.
And that happens
three or four days a week.
So you don't even get paid.
But you need your job,
so what do you say?
- Yeah.
- You're kind of st--
You don't want to make
anybody mad, you know.
- And they do it to everybody.
- Oh, really?
So everybody kind of
just did it, you know?
[woman] Wow. I can't imagine
them doing that here.
We're gonna make quota
and get some of that bonus.
- Did you guys hear about that?
- No, I haven't heard anything.
Yeah, we're gonna get probably
about $50 if we meet quota
at the end of the week.
I thought
that was great.
That's awfully
nice of 'em.
Yeah, that'll
help me out a lot
with bills and things.
That's what
you'd spend it on
if you got it?
I probably will just--
I don't know.
I haven't really
thought about it.
What do you think
you'll spend yours on?
I don't know.
If the weather
keeps getting nice,
I'll get camping equipment
or something like that.
- Oh, that sounds like fun.
- Mm-hmm.
Well, if you're looking
to make a little bit
of extra money,
I was wanting to go out
this weekend.
If you want to baby-sit Jesse
for a few hours,
I couldn't pay a whole lot,
but I could give you
a little bit.
- What night?
- Friday night.
If that would
work out for you.
Sure. I think I could
do that for you.
- Could you?
- Yeah.
- She's really good.
- How old is she?
- She's two.
- Okay.
It'll be nice for her too,
'cause it'll give her
somebody else to be around.
She doesn't-- She's not around
too many other people.
[woman]
What's she like to do?
[Rose] She likes to color
and she likes to read books.
[woman]
Okay.
Yeah, and she goes to bed
at 8:00, so more than likely--
That's great, 'cause
that way I can sew after--
- Oh, yeah.
- That's good, that's good.
- Okay, no problem.
- Great. I'm excited now.
Are you about done?
Yeah, pretty much.
- Wanna have a smoke?
- Sure.
Now, you know I
probably won't be home
till about 11:00,
and I left a number hanging
on the refrigerator
if you need me.
- I was wondering if
you left me a number.
- Yeah, I sure did.
- If I need to get ahold of you.
- Yes, I did.
[Rose] So she should be going
to bed in about a half an hour,
usually about 8:00.
About 15 minutes before
you put her to bed,
just give her a few goldfish
crackers and some juice,
just enough to put
something in her stomach.
But she should be all right.
She may cry whenever I leave.
- Just kind of expect it.
- Okay.
All you have to do is lay her
down and just read her a book,
and she'll get her blanket,
suck her thumb
and she'll be done.
All right.
That sounds great.
She's pretty easy.
[gurgling]
Hey, sweetie,
what do you have there?
[knocking]
[gasps]
Who's here?
Watch out.
- Hey, come in.
Hello.
Come here, sweetie.
Who's the man?
- What are you doing?
- Oh, nothing.
[Jesse jabbering]
- So, this is your date?
- Yeah.
Oh.
We're going out tonight
for a little bit.
And, uh, who's driving?
I am. I borrowed a--
I borrowed a car
off my friend.
Oh.
He let me take it out
tonight.
I see.
Can I have a kiss?
Mommy's gonna go
for a little bit.
Are you gonna be okay?
- No!
- Yes, you will.
- I want my baby!
- Okay, you get your baby.
- I guess we're gonna go and--
- Okay.
- What's that?
- It's another baby.
You can take that baby
and go night-night with it.
- Love you.
- Mama, I wanna go with you.
No. You're gonna
stay here with Martha.
Yeah. You're gonna have fun.
- Come here, sweetie.
- No!
We'll read a story.
Would you like to
read a story?
- No!
- I see a really nice book.
Look! She's got a book.
and she's gonna read to you.
- No!
- I'll be back in a little bit.
- Here, give me a kiss.
- No! I want to go that way!
You might want
to get her now.
I go that way!
[crying]
- Come here, sweetie.
- No!
- Do you want to play
with some toys?
- No!
- Well, come on.
Oh, sweetie.
Yeah, but seriously,
it seems like every time
I think I'm saving a little bit,
getting a little bit ahead,
something comes up.
- Jesse gets sick.
- Yeah.
Have you been able
to save much?
A little bit. I don't have
a checking account
or anything, but...
I got drawer change
I've been saving.
- Drawer change, huh?
- Yeah.
Yeah, he's got
his own place,
and then Jesse and I
live together.
Yeah, he wasn't ready
for our baby.
He's an artist,
and he's very into his work
and what's going on with him.
He doesn't have time, you know,
for anybody else.
But he helps out with her.
He baby-sits while I work
sometimes, if he has time,
or whatever.
That's good.
At least he sticks around
a little bit and sees her.
Yeah.
He makes an effort.
So did you finish
high school?
No. Actually, I had anxiety,
and I ended up quitting.
What is that?
Oh, just when I got around
a lot of people, you know,
I'd get a little bit nervous
and sometimes I'd have
a panic attack.
- Really?
- Yeah.
It was pretty bad,
enough to quit.
Did you go to a doctor
or anything for that?
Um...
Yeah, I did at one point,
but they just kept prescribing
me pills that didn't work,
so I eventually
just quit going
and dealt with it myself,
you know?
There's not much
you can do about it, so--
Are you taking anything
right now?
- No.
- No?
And how do you do?
Does that bother you anymore?
It's not as bad now,
you know.
Usually, the places I go,
there's not 400 people
like school.
Yeah.
It's usually when
there's a lot of people.
Lately, it's only temporary
when it's bad.
Mm-hmm.
Did you finish high school?
No, I didn't finish.
What happened there?
I got rebellious
in high school.
- Oh, yeah?
- Oh, yeah.
Yeah, I ran away,
hitchhiked to Charleston.
- Yeah.
- How old were you then?
- Fifteen.
- Kind of dangerous, isn't it?
Yeah, a little bit.
It was fun at the time.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
And look now.
- I'd like to save up
and get a car.
- Oh, yeah.
- That's nice to have.
- Yeah.
So where do you live?
- I live with my mom right now.
- Oh, really?
Yeah. It's just
a matter of money, really.
Trying to save up.
It's the easiest way to do it.
Yeah, I hear you.
Is your mom home
right now?
Well, actually,
I don't know.
Well, would you rather
just like maybe
go back there
where there's not
so many people?
Well, I guess we could, yeah.
Okay.
Those are very pretty.
Your mom must like jewelry.
Yeah.
Look at that.
- It's pretty.
- Yeah.
Oh, we lost it.
- It's a giraffe.
- A giraffe. Oh, okay.
It looks like a dinosaur
a little bit.
- It's a giraffe-dinosaur.
- Yeah.
What's this?
A purple necklace.
- Is that a purple necklace?
- Yeah.
[baby talk]
Yeah.
- Hey.
- Hi.
Mom, this is Rose.
- Hi, Rose. What's up?
- It's nice to meet you.
Yeah, it's nice to meet you too.
What are you guys doing?
Nothing. This is the girl
that they hired at
the factory the other day.
- Hi. Kyle told me about you.
- Oh, really?
Yeah, he did.
So how do you like it there?
It's pretty good.
It's not too bad.
It's busy but,
you know, it's a job.
Yeah, jobs really
get that way.
You guys wanna watch this?
It's pretty good.
No. I think we're just gonna
go hang out in the bedroom
for a little bit.
- Okay.
- All right.
- [laughs]
- See you later.
- Bye.
This is a pretty interesting
room you have.
What's that picture of?
That's a tattoo.
My friend drew it
for me there.
He does tattoos
and stuff.
That is crazy-looking.
Yeah, it's pretty cool.
I like it.
Do you have any tattoos?
Yeah, I got two tattoos
on my arm here.
No kidding.
Are they
exactly the same?
Yeah. They're symmetrical.
That's cool.
Are you gonna get any more?
Yeah, I'll probably
end up getting up to
about here or so.
He'll probably come up with
something good I can put on.
A friend of mine in Marietta
did one on my back.
- Oh, yeah?
- Yeah.
I'm not ready
for another one though.
Did it hurt or anything?
No, it didn't hurt.
I'm just, I don't know
what else I want
that's like forever.
- Yeah.
- You know.
Oh, yeah.
It's definitely permanent.
Oh, yeah. Do you like
hanging out in tattoo shops?
Yeah. I got a couple friends
that are tattoo artists.
Yeah, it is fun.
You meet a lot of people.
Yeah.
Wow. That's a nice watch.
Where'd you get that?
Thank you.
It was a gift from someone.
I used to clean their house.
Oh, yeah?
Kind of like a tip?
- Yeah, like a big thank-you.
- That's nice of them.
Yeah, it was
very nice of them.
I see you've got
a lot of High Times stuff.
Do you smoke?
Yeah, I'm a smoker.
Oh, yeah? I figured.
[laughs]
Would your mom get mad
if we smoked in here?
Um, I think I can make it
so she won't know.
Yeah. I just don't want her
prying in.
Right, yeah.
Yeah, I think we can
get away with it.
That's cool.
Do you, uh,
want a drink or anything?
You know, that would be good.
Do you have any beer?
Yeah, I got a beer.
I'll be right back.
[TV playing]
- Thank you very much.
- Mm-hmm.
- Oh, man.
- What?
It's starting to get
kind of late. I'm gonna
have to get back to Jesse.
I told Martha we'd only be
a few hours, but...
I'll just let you have this,
and you can save it for another
time or later, whatever.
Okay. I'm sure I'll
save it for another time.
We can hang out and drink
a beer, and then we're
gonna have to take off.
All right, that's cool.
So I don't think
I wanna go back in there
because of Martha and all.
What about Martha?
I don't know.
She gave me a weird vibe
when I was in there earlier
like she was mad at me
or something.
For going out with me?
I don't know.
It could be anything.
She just gave me a weird vibe
when I was in there earlier.
Okay, that's fine.
I did have fun with you though.
Yeah, I did too.
Definitely have
to do it again.
Well, just, you know,
get ahold of me.
- Yeah, all right.
- I'll see you at work Monday.
- Okay. Talk to you later.
- Bye.
So how was your date?
Oh, it was all right.
I really wish you guys
would've told me.
Told you what?
That you guys were
going out together.
- Why?
- Well, you could've told--
- I felt like an idiot.
- Oh, I'm sorry.
- How was Jesse?
- Jesse was great.
Was she? Did you have
a good time with her?
Yeah. She really likes
those necklaces.
Yeah, she does.
She's something.
Sure is. She went to bed
about like what you said.
Had her juice and her crackers
and went up to bed.
[knocking]
- Hey, guess what.
- Hey.
Guess what happened
at my house.
- [door closes]
- What do you want?
Uh, a little bit of money,
a bag of herb...
and the truth.
That's about it.
- I don't know what
you're talking about.
- Okay, cool. Exactly.
- What?
- All the shit that's
missing from my house.
- Where the fuck is it?
- I was out.
- I wasn't at your house.
- Yeah, I noticed. He's cute.
- He is none of your business.
- Okay, then take his money.
- Don't come in my house,
in my face--
- Then don't come in my house!
I didn't go in your house
and take your shit, okay?
I don't have anything of yours.
You have my car, that you
like to drive around town,
that you're so happy with.
- I need the damn car, okay?
- You don't think I need it?
I take Jesse around,
I take her out shopping,
buying her fucking Happy Meals,
all that good shit.
But I can't do it
without my damn money.
- I don't have your money.
- Okay--
I don't have your
fucking money, Jake!
It's not here.
You can look around.
There's no money.
I have no money,
and I have no weed.
- You're childish.
- You are such a fucking baby.
It's all about Jake.
What Jake wants,
what Jake needs.
- I don't have your shit!
- I need my money.
- Go sell some of your shit
and make some money.
- It's the stupid principle!
Principle of what?
You coming into my house,
banging on my door
late at night,
accusing me of shit?
You need to pick my shit
off the floor.
Pick it up
and give me my money.
Unless you spent it all.
At least did you spend it
on Jesse?
- Huh? Did did you
buy her some clothes?
- Get out of my house.
Oh, excuse me.
- Was that Jesse's daddy?
- You know what?
Martha, please, just
mind your own business, okay?
Read your book.
[TV playing]
Hello, Sergeant.
Detective Taylor.
- Sgt. Davis.
- What do we got?
We got a phone call at 6:45
from a neighbor
stating that a child
had been crying
all night long.
She couldn't get anybody
to answer the door,
so she called 911.
We responded, made entry.
Once inside, we found
a 23-year-old female
on the living room floor
by the name
of Rose Hilliard.
Okay.
Any sign of forced entry?
- No sign.
- Any sign of robbery?
Doesn't appear to be.
- What about a struggle?
- Appears to be a struggle, yes.
- Let's go and take a look.
- Okay.
Dad, I've got your breakfast.
Well, how nice of you.
What are we having,
cereal this morning?
Yeah. Cereal and some juice.
Well, you're right, Sarge.
There's no sign of forced
entry into the apartment.
Doesn't look like a robbery.
Her valuables and her purse
are still here.
She's got bruising to the neck,
which is consistent with
manual strangulation.
She's got petechiae
hemorrhage of the eyes.
- Where's the baby?
- Baby's with the grandmother.
- So the baby's safe?
- Yes.
Ross, when you're doing
the fingerprints,
I want you to process
the bruising on her neck
for prints.
Okay, sir.
What did we find out from
the neighborhood canvass?
Officer Smeeks?
You wanna fill the detective
in on what you know?
Okay. Now, I spoke to
three of the neighbors.
Hey, Mom, you didn't
happen to pick up any
money in my room, did you?
No, I didn't.
I haven't been in your room.
- Didn't see in your room.
- All right.
Maybe you spent more than
you thought you did.
I had a little bit saved up,
so I might have misplaced it
or something.
I was checking if you were
in there and picked it up.
No, haven't been in there.
Haven't seen it.
Was it a lot of money?
No, just a little
I had saved up
for an emergency.
This is a ring that
my mother had given me.
When I turned 30,
she said I'd be responsible
enough to take care of it.
Okay, so it's pretty
sentimental, huh?
Yeah, it is, and this is
my grandmother's broach,
and that was handed down
through the family,
and my mother thought
she had gotten that,
but I got it.
You'll never guess
where this came from.
Where's that?
I found this in the park
with a metal detector.
- Oh, wow. Nice find.
- I thought that was
pretty good.
Jake? I'm Det. Taylor
from the police department.
I need to talk to you
for a minute. Can I come in?
Uh, is it necessary?
It's kind of important.
It's about Rose Hilliard.
I need to talk to you about her.
All right, man.
Come on in.
Right through this door.
- Did you do this on the walls?
- Yeah, yeah, most of it.
Very interesting.
Some would say.
How long have you known Rose?
Oh, man, I've known her
for a while, like...
We were together for at least
a year and a half.
Probably altogether,
I guess five years,
somewhere around there.
Okay. I guess you share
a child together?
- Yeah.
- What's your daughter's name?
- Jesse.
- Okay.
So when was the last time
you saw Rose?
Oh, man. Uh....
- What day is today?
- Saturday.
Uh, just last night.
- So it was last night
you were over there?
- Yeah, yeah, Friday night.
Do you remember
about what time that was?
Like 11 something.
It was later, man,
like she was coming
from a date.
Why did you go over there?
Because, man, she's ignorant,
and she stole money of mine.
- Did you get to talk to her?
- Yeah, I talked to her.
Was there anybody else
there at the house
when you were there?
Uh, I remember she had
some chick on the couch.
Do you know
who that person was?
No, not a clue.
Okay.
What did she look like?
Uh, looked like
a person on a couch, man.
I don't know.
- So you didn't pay
much attention to her?
- No, man.
Okay. Did you confront Rose
about her taking money from you?
- Hell yeah.
- Did you get into an argument?
Uh...
I don't know.
That's just kind of
how we talk nowadays.
- Just tell me--
- Yeah, yeah, man!
She took my money.
I wanted my money back.
Okay.
She wasn't about
to give it to me,
or just even
give me satisfaction
of admitting she did it.
Did you guys get into
a screaming match?
No, man. The kid was
sleeping upstairs.
So what happened?
Uh... We...
I went in and asked her,
"Where's my money?"
Like usual, she told me,
"I don't have it.
I didn't take it."
She said, "Get the hell
out of my house," and I left.
Do you have any idea
why I'm here?
No, man.
Rose was murdered.
Whoa. Okay.
Do you have any knowledge
about who did that?
No, not me.
I know that much.
From looking around your
apartment, I can tell you're
a very passionate individual.
- Artistic and passionate.
- [laughs]
Not passionate to beat
her ass or anything,
otherwise you probably
would've heard of me
a long time ago.
You've never been physical
with her in the past?
No, man, not really.
So when you left,
she was alive and
everything was fine?
Well, I wouldn't say
everything was fine,
but she seemed to breathe
and speak and move about.
So while you were there,
you didn't get into any kind of
physical altercation with her.
No, man! So you're--
She's dead?
She's dead.
Wow, man.
Wow. I need--
I need to call
some people, man.
I need to see
my daughter.
The darker the water,
the darker the bait,
which doesn't
make any sense at all,
but if the water you're
going to be fishing in
is real clear,
you'll want
the lighter colors.
...for the spinner rates,
and they lock down.
And then there's little boxes
that you can put
whatever you please.
Hey, that is nice.
And how much does this run?
$18.95.
[knocking]
- Kyle?
- Yeah.
I think you better
come out here.
- Somebody wants to see you.
- All right.
It's a cop.
How long
have you known Rose?
Oh, probably about
a week now.
Okay, and what's
your relationship with her?
Well, we worked together,
and we were friends.
Uh, you know,
we just met, so--
- When was the last time
you saw Rose?
- I was with her last night.
Okay. What did you guys do?
We went out
for a couple beers,
and we came back here
for a little bit,
then I took her home.
Was anybody else
with you last night?
- No.
- Okay.
About what time did you
drop her off home last night?
It was probably
around 11:00.
Okay. During the time
that you were together,
did she express any concerns
that someone might want
to hurt her?
[Kyle's mother]
Something happen to her?
Yeah. She was murdered
last night.
- What?
- She was murdered.
- Where?
- At her home.
Do you know of anybody
that would want to hurt her?
No. She didn't
say anything.
When you say you picked her--
What time did you pick
her up last night?
Um, it was probably
about 7:00. 6:00 or 7:00.
Did you go into her house
when you stopped to pick her up?
Yeah, I went in.
Was there anybody else there?
Yeah. Martha was there.
She was babysitting for her.
Who's Martha?
She's another girl
I work with.
Does she have red hair?
Yeah.
[Martha] And then I also
sew some doll clothes.
You do what?
I sew doll clothes
in the evenings
for the dolls.
- Really?
- Yeah.
It's a lot of fun.
You do that with anybody
or just by yourself?
Just by myself.
My dad's at home,
and that way I just
spend some time with him.
He usually watches TV
while I sew.
[chuckles]
- Hi.
Is Kyle here?
- Yeah.
- Care if I come in?
- Come on in.
- How you doing?
I'm okay.
How are you doing?
Terrific.
- Are you sure?
- Yeah.
Okay.
That's nice.
Hang on. I'll get Kyle.
Kyle, Martha's here.
- Oh.
- I don't know.
- Hi. What are you doing?
- Hey, Martha.
- I've been trying
to get ahold of you.
- I've been out all day.
I went to the beauty parlor and
went and bought a couple things.
- Has anybody talked to you yet?
- About what?
About Rose.
What about Rose?
She was killed
last night.
She was murdered last night.
She was strangled.
- No.
- Yes.
- Last night?
- Yeah.
Oh, my God.
[mother] There was
a detective here today.
[Martha]
You have got to be kidding me.
Yeah. He just came in today
and told us.
He asked me
a bunch of questions.
And this happened
last night.
- Yeah.
Yeah, they were asking me
because they thought I was
the last one that seen her.
- Then I told him you were--
- Well, you brought her home
when I was there.
Yeah.
You are not gonna
believe this.
When I was there last night
after you dropped her off,
this guy started
beating on the door,
and she goes to the door
and she opens it up,
and he comes in.
He came in
screaming and yelling.
She was okay when you left.
I mean, she was by herself.
She was fine, yeah.
When I left, she was fine.
But if he was waiting out there
when you dropped her off,
he was probably
waiting on me to leave.
- Yeah.
- And he went back in there.
Oh, my God.
I can't even imagine.
I know.
It happened too fast.
Well, I got these
for you.
Oh, well, thank you.
Thank you, Martha.
You're quite welcome.
Yeah, definitely,
you have to call
this detective too.
Oh, I will. You'll have to
give me the number.
[police scanner]
- Hi. How you doin'?
- Hello, Martha.
I'm Det. Taylor from
the police department.
I need to talk to you about
Rose Hilliard. Can I come in?
Oh, sure. Come on in.
I heard from Kyle today,
and he was telling me
that something horrible
had happened to Rose,
that she'd been murdered.
- Can I come in and have a seat?
- Sure. This is my father.
Sir, I'm from the police
department. I was just here
to talk to your daughter.
- Pleased to meet you.
- Pleased to meet you, sir.
I mean, at first I thought
she was a really sweet girl.
And then the longer
you get to know her,
the pushier she gets and
the more favors she asks for.
I mean, it was just one favor
right after the other one.
Did you feel like she
took advantage of you?
A little bit, yeah.
Did she do that
to other people?
I'm not really sure.
It seemed like she
picked on me a lot.
She didn't really buddy up
with the other employees.
She'd only been there a week.
Well, in talking with
the witnesses in the area,
they indicate that you were
the last one that was seen
leaving the residence.
[Martha]
Well, I-I know that--
Well, I-I don't know.
I probably was.
I left after he did.
And that fact that, as far as
the investigation is concerned,
you were the last one that
we know that saw her alive.
Okay.
At some point, I would like
to get fingerprints from you
to be able to compare
to evidence that we
collected at the scene.
Well, you know my fingerprints
are gonna be there.
I was there.
Right, but there's other
evidence that we have
- that would only be
the killer's.
- Okay.
Would you be willing to come
to the police department tonight
and give me
a set of fingerprints?
Okay. I would have to get
someone to take care of my dad.
And about how long
will that take?
Shouldn't take
more than 15, 20 minutes
- to get the fingerprints.
- Okay.
If you'd be able to do it
tonight, it'd really help
with the investigation.
I'll do anything I can to help.
- Hello, Martha.
- Detective.
Thanks for meeting
with me again.
I just got a few more questions
that we need to talk about,
- if that's okay.
- Okay.
Do you care if I record
our conversation?
- No.
- Okay.
I'll just go ahead
and start the tape.
What I like for you to do
is go over the events again
with me of Friday night.
Do you remember about what time
Kyle came to the house?
No, I don't.
Okay.
Did Kyle come inside?
Yes, he did.
And did he stay
very long?
No. They, uh...
They talked a little bit,
and, um...
They weren't there very long.
- Do you know where they went?
- No, I don't.
Okay, so when they left,
it was just you
and the small child.
- Yes.
- And what did you do
that evening?
The child and I just played,
and then I watched some TV
and read some books
and gave her some juice,
and she went right to sleep.
Rose had told me that it
wouldn't take her very long,
and she was very good.
Okay. Nothing unusual
happened then?
- No.
- What time did Rose come home?
It was close to 11:00.
Okay, and did you
immediately leave or--
No. When she came in,
we sat down and she
asked me how Jesse was,
and I asked her
about her date.
And, uh...
Then, of course,
that man came to the door.
Yeah, you told me
that an individual came.
- Yes.
- It was her ex-boyfriend?
Right. He had been--
I guess he had been sitting
outside waiting on her.
- And did they argue?
- Yes, they sure did.
You told me that they had
gotten into an argument.
Again, tell me
what that was about.
He had said that she had stole
some things from the apartment
and some money.
How did it end with them?
Did it turn physical?
Well, there was
a lot of yelling and...
I'm not sure
whether he shoved her,
but I know she had
grabbed ahold of him
to try to get him out the door.
Was she able to get him
out of the house?
It took awhile.
Okay. But he did
ultimately leave
the apartment.
Yes. Yes, he did.
Did you see him any more
that night?
No. I didn't--
I just got in my car and left.
Okay, and where did you go
when you left?
- I went straight home.
- Okay.
And I spoke to your dad
the night that we talked,
and he said you came home
about the same time
that you're saying.
Um...
Is there anything else
that you can tell me
at this point?
Well, the thing that,
you know, really bothers me
is that he was waiting outside
on her to get home.
Uh-huh.
So what if he was still there
after I left?
Okay. Do you remember
when we talked at your house
and you indicated to me that
you'd do anything you could to
help with this investigation?
Yes, I did.
Well, what you need to do is
start telling me the truth
about what happened.
So I am.
We have got the physical
evidence back from the lab,
and it implicates you in
the death of Rose Hilliard.
I don't see how. How?
Your fingerprints were
lifted off the bruises
around her neck.
I don't understand it.
Now, Martha, this is
the opportunity for you
to help yourself here.
Now, either you are
a cold-blooded killer,
- which I don't think
is the case...
- No.
or something happened
in that apartment that
caused you to do this.
There is no doubt
that you did this. None.
But only you can
explain to me
what happened,
and I want you
to do that.
I can't. I just--
I don't know.
Is there any way that you can
explain your fingerprints
around her neck?
No, sir. No, sir.
And the neighbors saw you
leave the apartment.
You were the last one
to leave the apartment.
The evidence is there.
You will be convicted of this.
You need to tell me the truth
about what happened.
I don't know.
I-I don't know.
Well, the jury's not
going to believe that.
I want you to look
at these photographs.
That what she looks like.
That's what you did you her.
A jury's not gonna have
sympathy for you if you don't
show some kind of remorse.
Now, it can be explained
how this happened.
Maybe you got into
an argument with her,
maybe things got out of hand.
But only you know that.
She can't tell us.
- I couldn't have done this.
- Well, you did.
No, sir. No. No.
Mr. Hightower, I wanted to
come over and talk to you and
let you know what's going on.
Okay. I was
wondering about it.
I just finished
talking with Martha,
and based upon
my interview with her
and evidence that we
recovered from the scene,
she's been arrested for
the murder of Rose Hilliard.
Is that right?
And I wanted to come over
and make you aware of
what's going on
because you
are her family.
Yes.
She's currently
at the jail
and that's where she'll be
until there's a hearing date.
What the hell.
Sorry to hear it.
Do you have
any questions for me?
Do you know when
her hearing will be?
It'll be fairly soon.
And they will give her
an attorney.
Hey, Martha.
Hi, Kyle.
I'm really glad you came.
It's horrible in here.
Yeah?
So what's going on?
I don't know.
I don't understand.
I don't even know
why I'm here, really.
And they think
I killed her.
Kyle, you know me.
You know I could not
have done that.
I think-- I really--
I think it's Jesse's dad.
And I can't-- I don't know.
I don't know what happened.
You got to help me, Kyle.
You know that
I would never do
anything like this.
Yeah.
I-I don't understand.
And it seemed like
the detective--
They think that I did this,
and I don't see how.
I don't see how
that can be right.
I don't know, Martha.
I don't understand it.
I don't know.
I don't know what,
you know, what I did.
I know that I had a really,
really, really bad headache,
and when he started yelling,
I just wanted to go home.
And I didn't know
who he was,
and when I tried
to ask her who he was,
she told me to
mind my own business.
And that kind of
made me feel bad
because, I thought, you know,
I thought I could talk to her
like a daughter.
I mean, after all,
she left me with, you know,
her most prized
possession: her baby.
Yeah.
And she's asked me for
all kinds of favors,
and I just didn't think
it was too much to ask
who he was.
And she was really mad
and didn't want
to talk about it.
I don't know, Martha.
You got to help me, Kyle.
You got to.
I mean, I don't
what I can do, but...
I... I don't know
how this happened.
We have to figure this out.
We have to.
I didn't do it, Kyle.
You know I wouldn't
do anything like that.
Yeah.
I don't know, Martha.
- I just-- I don't understand.
- I don't either.
[TV playing]
[Man]
Good morning, everyone.
We've obviously gone through
a very tragic set of events.
It is, um...
But we need move on,
and because of that,
we have gone out and we have
hired Kyle's mom, Helen,
with the idea that--
She can't take
the two ladies' place
because they are, you know--
We had a longtime employee
and we had a short-time employee
who was doing very well,
but we feel like with, um--
Even though Kyle's mom
doesn't have a lot experience,
that you guys can work with her,
get her up to speed
just as soon as possible.
Hi.
You show me what to do.
I'll do the best I can.
Help you out.
Oh, my God.