Why don't we watch TV?
You're originally
one of those on the screen
But you won't be the winner
You... why do you catch me here?
Your figure is not so good
Don't you wanna be the Princess?
I'll see if you can meet my standard
My figure is already good enough
What do you want me to do?
Don't bother me
To leave here, you have one only way
Your weight must be below 70 pounds!
Cherrie
You scared me, Hong
You're going out for a meal in the rain?
They forgot to buy it for me
Have you had it yet?
Yes. They've been finding you
Damn Hurry up
What? You let Sisi go on stage first?
I won't go on stage tonight
What should I do then?
Somersault or Muay Thai?
Don't be angry
You're the planned Princess
She's a clown. You're a star
She's much worse than you
And once you go on stage
no one will ever remember her
Look, she really performs Muay Thai
I've seen miss Sisi's resume
She's one of
the best Muay Thai players in HK
Really cool
Powerful punches
Cherrie!
Where have you gone?
Go get the clothes for Queenie
Yes...
Is it okay? Is it okay?
Sisi. Great, Sisi
Should have some tricks
to entertain people
Queenie, the next one is you
What?
It's your turn
Why don't you say it earlier?
Don't put your dirty stuff everywhere
My skirt worths $50,000
You can't afford to pay
Queenie! Get away!
Why so many people?
Why always block my way?
What monkey show do you wanna play now?
Go see the physician
Take care
You look so ugly putting these clothes on
And you'll probably get a cold soon
Who are you talking about?
Of course is you. Need to say it again?
Save the money. You can't get cured
So late?
That lady told me
to change the clothes again. So tired
No
Let's go and eat something
Sorry. I gotta remove the makeup
for Queenie later
You're not her assistant
just her fitness coach
Miss Kong told me to look after Queenie
Leave her alone. Let's go
Have a meal together No...
Let's go
I don't want her misunderstood it
The contest now reaches the climax
Tonight's Princess
of Weight Watcher is...
No. 12, Miss Fei Tong!
Calm down. Put down your knife
Don't kill me. No!
It's totally useless killing him
You're so pretty and have a bright future
Shouldn't get in jail for this pervert
My husband's never a pervert
You bitch!
Say it again or I'll slash him!
No... don't do that. Cool it...
Dare let him go
and fight with me with a knife!
I'm not that stupid
You come and I'll slash him!
Stay calm...
Who'll be the Queen
of Weight Watcher tonight?
Louder!
Louder Cool it...
Hold on!
Turn up the television's volume!
Alright...
No. 10, Queenie
I guessed it would be her
Sure... these are all setups
How about turning it off?
Okay...
Butt out!
You dare to hit my husband!
I like to do it
Actually all of you're right...
Let's sit down and talk
He is right? He didn't divorce his wife
He said he'd buy me a flat
but it's a lie
You son of a bitch!
Oh no
You can't promise what you can't to women
A man always makes promise
when he's on the bed
You're right Butt out!
Miss, put down your knife
Or he'll easily get hurt
If you hurt him, we can do nothing...
but accuse you of damaging others
Better find a social worker to solve it
I'll shoot you dead and shoot myself
Come one
Have negotiation specialists come?
Have they come?
Come to die!
Let him go, or I'll shoot you
and shoot myself
Have you opened the safety lock?
Help me do it
Your hand that held the gun
is still shivering
Give me the cigarette
You'll see if your wife knows you smoke
Therefore I smoke now. Give me
Treasure the happy times, fat guy
Yes, sir
I'll be more careful next time
Next time?
You go first
I'm gonna write the report
No. Last time you wrote
so many wrong words
And I was blown up
Let me do it myself
Bastard! Crying for a whole night
Doesn't seem like water
That guy won't get home so early
It's better, though. Won't bother me
You forgot it? I can't take the pill
Or I'll be as fat as a pig
He can't use condom. He's allergic to it
No
I won't have baby. It's so painful
I'd rather live without children
I can only refuse him every time
He's back. Talk to you later
Many things to do
Darling, I'm back
I'm loaded. See how cool it is!
Don't pretend to be sleeping
Deeper breath means you're sleeping?
You snore while sleeping
Don't you know?
I'm telling you now...
No... I'm really sleeping
I'm very sleepy. Don't...
1, 2, 3, 4
What do you mean?
You know why
I am not in the safe period today
I'll be busy when you're in safe period
Then use the condom
I'm allergic to condom! How to use?
So let's sleep earlier
We have... not that staggering
2 months
We haven't done it for 2 months
Are you calculating this kind of stuff?
Did you marry me just for this?
No...
I gave up working as superintendent
just for you
You know how much I sacrificed?
If I went on I'd be the commissioner soon
You... do you wanna do what I did today?
Listen. Today
I was forced to turn on TV
Then they took my gun
and then they pissed me
Do you wanna do what I did today?
How come you speak so loud?
You're annoyed so you blow me up!
I speak loudly? You speak so loud first
Isn't it loud?
Alright, let me find a girl
with lower voice
Go ahead
You petty guy aren't willing
to treat them a cup of tea
Who wanna know you?
Sure. Who wanna know me?
I'm not petty. I'm a saver
It's virtue. Kindness
Alright... you're so kind
and have virtue...
How about...
sleeping outside?
What? I can't hear it clearly
You sleep outside
Listen. I will not sleep
outside the bedroom!
What's up?
Superiors have decided
to transfer Inspector Ma
He's gone and you should get promoted
I don't care
Promotion means salary up
but benefits cut
and take the blame for others. Let it go
Don't say it this way, sir
We're more confident if you get promoted
Talk about it later
Yes sir
What? Got crazy just when you got up?
No. Just have a morning dance
Let's dance together. Come on
No. I gotta go to the toilet
Good morning... Good morning...
How are you? Fine, thanks
You look so fine, Tak
Sure. Nice sleep last night
Thank you
Good morning...
Come here, Tak
Something to talk with you
Yes, sir
You already knew that Ma is transferred?
No... why do I know?
Coz he made a serious mistake
This post is still empty
One must lead 3 teams
It's vital Yes...
And in these 3 teams...
You're the most experienced one
So I hope you'll work hard...
Yes, sure...
to work for your new boss
New boss...
He's called William, former HQ member
He's a Dr. In criminal psychology
Are you okay?
You look shocked
Good. Good idea
Criminal Psychology... Dr., good
You gotta have a chat with him
Sir, I'm going if nothing special
Tak, one more thing
A reporter of a pop magazine in Mainland
comes to HK to take some info
I want you to help him
He's called Tin Fuk
The paparazzi are so mad
I won't work with him if he's one of them
I don't know. Just helping him will do
Which bastard thinks of this bullshit?
My wife! That's her nephew
So... your wife... so let me help him...
Tell him to find me, sir
I never force you, do I?
No... you don't...
Good morning...
What? How impolite
Sorry, sir. Got the wrong info
Doesn't matter. I won't blame you
More relaxed, Even better
You looked so glad...
It doesn't matter...
Give me a pair of gym shoes!
Reporting. Inspector Wong of CID has come
Inspector Wong
Give way, please...
Cheung... how long has he died?
Damn. Cheung hasn't died
Ask the coroner, you fool
Sir, where's Tak Wong in CID?
The 3rd floor upstairs
Thank you very much
Tak, 2 men find you Who?
One old-fashioned and one cool
Okay, thanks
Good morning, Tak... Good morning...
Are you Tak Wong?
Wait a second
Welcome... You're Tak Wong, right?
Sure. Just call me Tak
With your leadership...
I believe we'll have a huge progress
Thanks... I'm here to learn from you
You're welcome...
We're hardworking staff
Just a bit lack
in newest technologies and theories
This way...
This is your room
Do you mind calling you William?
I don't mind, but...
But I like to call myself Tin Fuk
Tin Fuk...
So you're Tin Fuk?
Yes, who do you think I am?
Nothing... I thought you're Tom Cruise
What can I do for you?
Let me introduce myself
I'm a reporter of Unveil in Mainland
Investigating a man
suspected of sexual abuse in Shanghai
He works in HK and the victim was killed
We'd like HK police to find him for us
Yes, this is Ken
You're Tak Wong? Who are you?
William, William Hung
Nice to meet you William Hung
This is Tin Fuk, right?
Come into my room
Can you give me a cup of milk tea?
Thanks
This is Ken
Suspected of a sexual abuse case
in Shanghai last year
He held an actress
into the dungeon for 15 days
giving her nothing to eat
The lady ran out
and reported to the police
The police then arrested Ken
But in the court
the girl refuted her own statements
Ken is then acquitted of a charge
We believe Ken gave her
a lot of money in advance
making her refute
the statements on purpose
How about now?
Ken's found to have moved...
and is flirting
with a lady boss of a beauty company
We gotta know
if he's any link with this case
We'll help you as much as we can
But there's a strange murder case
here today
How strange?
It's famished
Famished?
What's up, Luck?
The dead's stomach
and throat was seriously hurt
Too much stomach acid...
Causes it to flow back
She's believed to have eaten very few...
and drunk so little when she's lost
I think it's the cause of death
Observing the hair follicle...
it may have stayed in a place
with high temperature
leading to dehydration of the body
And now she have 70 pounds left
70 pounds?
Yes, 70 pounds
One interesting finding
Her mouth was stuffed
with a piece of paper
What's that?
Have you been to the supermarket?
It's the price tag calculating the weight
Psycho
Many killers with abnormal psychology
in US act like this
They think they can control everything
They control the dead's body and behavior
Once they've succeeded
they'll probably do it again
You mean he'll break the law again?
Work or it'll happen again. Go
Can I work with you, Tak?
Can he work with us, sir?
No problem
Thank you
You haven't even lost a catty these weeks
Have you referred to the menu?
I'm already 120 pounds. It's alright
But our aim is 113 pounds
Just editing the pics
in the computer is ok
Have you drunk any alcohol?
Mind your own business
But our contract says
that you can't drink, and...
can't take medicines
not prescribed by a doctor
Get out...
Piss off!
I got it
Miss Kong, I'm gonna quit
Do you know Ivy is dead?
How come?
The police have just been
to Forever Beauty
They'll come just then. Go prepare it
But Queenie's attitude...
Okay... talk with me tomorrow. Go
The cops are coming
You gotta go... from back door
Who are you looking for, sir?
Hello, I'm Inspector Tak Wong
I'm gonna discuss a murder case
with your boss, miss Kong
What's wrong with the alarm?
Who opens the back door?
Sorry, sir. I gotta check the back door
Just sit down and tell me
where the door is
Over there
I'm going with you, sir
Just sit down here, sit down
Let him go... what a trouble...
Anything happened?
Sorry, miss
Don't take it...
So you've come here now?
That is Ken, isn't it?
Sorry... sorry...
Scared me
What a hit!
Lucky that I'm a policeman
If I were a wolf...
that's great
Bull
The one who ran is Ken
Ken? Who's he?
The one I'm looking for
Thank you very much
Call me if anything happens
Thank you...
You can call on me at any time
Sir...
Come on, talk something
Sir What's up?
What?
What to say in front of
2 senior barristers?
Just tell you their names
She said she's just
normal friends with Ken
They've been here so long
Ken's probably run
Still no Ken's departure record
I think he's still in HK
The cops have been finding you
Avoid them. Don't come out
You're back?
Still staying up?
You idiot. It's gonna be dawn now
Watching VCD
A housewife should watch VCDs
Or what else can I do?
What're you talking about?
A housewife has nothing to do
with other stuff but VCDs?
Go to sleep
Was that model really famished?
Yes
He must be a psycho
Of course. Dare to deny?
If he's not a psycho
can he do this kind of stuff? You...
He's not a psycho, I am
2 days later is ok. Is that good?
Keep your promise!
Go take a bath
According to criminal psychology
He left no traces in this action
It's so perfect. He must do it again
You mean he'll be mass murderer?
Yes
This kind of people
take killing as an art
They're usually nervous breakdown
lonely, and fleshless
How come? Why're they fleshless?
They usually forget to eat
which leads to malnutrition, so those...
who're fleshless can easily
be nervous breakdown
Nervous breakdown makes them even weaker
You think it like this?
What? It's not me
It's from a report
from Columbia University
What... what university?
Columbia University
Columbia University...
And they're not sociable
Hard for them to get along
with colleagues
Dreaming of being pursued every day
When did you read it?
When you're watching soccer matches
I thought you only know
how to put on makeup
According to criminal psychology...
The killer must be satisfied
with his performance
So he must act again
You study criminal psychology
Yes, I've just read a report...
from Columbia University
It says the fleshless people...
is easily be nervous breakdown
making them unable to eat
Unable to eat means they'll get weak
Get weak and be nervous breakdown
Nervous breakdown and they'll...
In a word, fleshless
You're so hard working. What a surprise
Yes, I love that...
Dr. Bin Laden
You've forgotten, honey
It's Dr. Shelton
Hello
Hello I am William
I'm Ling, Tak's wife
I worked as a police before
Really?
She worked here before
You're husband's good
in criminal psychology
Take a seat...
Take some food, thanks
Dr. Shelton
You study of criminal psychology, too
We women know nothing about it
It's my husband who tells me
He tells me when he's read the reports
He read a German
Dr. Ernest's report last week
His theories are similar to Dr. Shelton's
If you like them, I think you may even...
study the report written
by Robert. Ressler of FBI
I can lend it to you
Sure...
Honey. I'm here to tell you...
I've found an important clue
What is that?
Just discuss with us
The murderer is thin
If he dragged the 80-catty body
to the alley
He must need very much effort
So I believe...
the 1st crime scene is not far away
from the alley
And the body was not even
left traces of being dragged
Tak, I think we gotta set the boundary...
to the distance walking 5 minutes
from the alley
And we must keep an eye on the
spokespersons of Forever Beauty
Sisi and Fei Tong
I fear the killer will take them
as the next targets
How about this, director Chan
Fei Tong, you'll sit here...
So what'll I do then?
Eating
Eat again? Yes
Miss Si, Miss Lui
We're CID
We wanna record the statement with you
We're working, sir
It's about 10 minutes. Very quick
Let's finish these scenes first
Sir, how about asking you a question?
If correct
I'll record the statement right now
Is a dumpling masculine or feminine?
It's masculine. Why?
Coz it has phimosis!
Not funny? Sorry
Camera, action
Eat, and it will keep you young
Cut!
What's up?
I've played in the movie
for a whole month
Eating dumplings every day
Do I have any dialogue?
Haven't you seen the screenplay?
Speak when you have to. Now you don't
Eat'em! Hurry...
Sorry. Just kidding
Action!
No... director, I...
I gotta go to the toilet. I'm fed up
Need someone to go with you?
No. All human beings know
I master Muay Thai
Sometimes I'm even afraid of
my own ability
April
Don't be so passive
Feel dizzy once you see handsome guys?
What's up?
What happened?
Nothing, just gave a sigh
Crazy
Artists are all crazy
Sigh without reason. Crazy
Crazy again
What are you doing?
Playing Muay Thai
Nothing... I've eaten too many dumplings
Muay Thai can help digestion...
and keep the skin white
What's up, sir?
How about putting down your gun
and play it with me?
Not funny?
I'm going to the toilet. Bye!
Not yet. Can't wrap yet
Still long time to go
April
Do it 3 times?
Too bad if anyone marrying her
I'm a Mainland reporter
Can you give me an autograph?
I have interviews in HK
Mainland people also notice me!
I'm your fan
Help...
She's got trouble!
Are you okay?
Where's miss Si?
Somebody caught her...
Bull, tell all other spokespersons...
to stay in safe places and not to go out
Got it
You stay here I can help you...
Stay here!
Who?
I'm the cop who records
the statement this morning
It's you
Why hang up, Sisi? Got angry?
Sisi has trouble
Tell Queenie and other people
to stay in the Center
Queenie and I are in the Center
but the power is cut
I'm scared
Calm down. I'm coming
Lock the door and wait for me
Hurry, hurry...
I'm gonna see if Cherrie's fixed it
Goddamn! Stay with me!
It's me, Ken Is that you?
I'll let you go if you don't yell
Cherrie
I can only talk to you like this
Why are you here?
I wanna see you
Miss Kong misses you so much
We parted
You know I love you
The cops called me
and said they're coming
You gotta go
I won't go without you
If you do love me, listen to me. Go
What happened, Cherrie?
Don't play with me!
I won't go without you
You gotta go
Cherrie!
Are you okay?
Sure
Is it abduction?
Is it TV's funny program?
Are there many cameras shooting me?
Are you playing?
Then a host comes out and say I win
Give me car and house and something
Are you giving me anything?
No I don't want them. I just want money
$300,000 is enough. Stop it
Come out!
Do I look good? Where's my powder puff?
My powder puff's gone...
I gotta put on makeup!
I'm so scared...
Help me!
Let me go!
No problem
You meet my standard and you can go
Who are you? Where are you?
I can't see you
If you see me, you must die!
No... don't let me see you
I can't see you...
Let me go, please
You checked your weight, did you?
Yes...
Only 100 pounds. Thin enough
Not enough
You can go if you can be
70 pounds in a week
Did you kill Ivy?
She's just too weak to stand it
Don't kill me...
I can do whatever you want. No...
Okay
If you can make me laugh, you can go
When I was a child
I wanna be a model
but my career not good enough
Then I went to play comedies
Alright. If you can make me laugh
in 1 minute
I'll let you go
What does Bruce Lee like to say most?
Don't know? The answer is yelling
You know, when he fights
he says, Whatcha!
Yes. A riddle. Star Wars
Guess 2 objects
What's the 1st one?
It's jewel!
Jewel...
How about another one?
It's ball? Why?
Ball...
Not funny? Sorry...
Let me think...
Got it. You must laugh this time
Once upon a time...
What? Why do you laugh?
1 minute is over, idiot
No... this is really funny
Listen to me...
Once upon a time...
Listen to me!
This is really funny...
You don't need to send me home
This is our duty. No problem
Top floor? You gotta walk many stairs
Cheap rent, and I can take it as a sport
You can go now
Sorry, I really don't wanna come in
But I wanna go to the washroom. Can I?
Sorry, my home is a mess
Excuse me, the washroom...
Over there Thanks
Renowned spokesperson
of fitness company Sisi...
was help captive from the scene...
of Media Art at 3 am
Her assistant was hurt
and is now in the hospital
We'll now ask the chief inspector
Mr. Wilson Chow
Is this case related
to that case of Ivy last time?
We assume that the 2 cases...
Thank you
Are you okay?
Can I lean on your shoulder for a while?
Did you...
study in Pui Yin Secondary School?
Why do you ask it?
Because I did study there
You look weak...
but you got the gold medal
in shot put. Cool
It's about technique, not power
Technique? Really?
Which year did you graduate?
Did you ever see me in school?
No, I didn't
And which year did you graduate?
Maybe I didn't ever notice you
So many gals noticed me
I don't think so!
You finally laugh
Talk on phone later. Goodbye
Goodbye
Bull, where's Tak?
Wanna drink some soup?
Inspector Chow's scolding inside
What happened?
Sisi's dead, with legs chopped off
How come?
They said Sisi is just
70 pounds without legs
I said he'd do it again
Any traces found at the scene?
No
More perfect this time
Why's it become so big?
Sure. I can't get in charge of big deals
Do small stuff for the rest of my life
The case will be transferred
to Inspector Tit
Still pretending to be cool? How?
Tak
Your wife's come. Go have a chat
Come on... nothing
Have some soup
No appetite
It's just their business
Why're you so angry?
Damn it. Their business
I've been doing small jobs
Now it's getting bigger
and is then transferred
Aren't they pointing against me?
Why do they point against you?
You murderer!
When I hold a gun...
I feel frozen and can't say a word
Go tell the doctor
What? Doctor?
I'll get fired if other know it
I think it's work pressure
You still have many leaves
Better take some
No
I must catch that guy
red-handed this week
Or else I'll be a pawn
for the rest of my life
Excuse me, I wanna lose weight
Do you have many kinds of treatment?
Please introduce some
Can I help you, Mrs. Wong?
My pal said it costs
a lot for the 1st time
Need $100,000 or more?
Hello, my name's Cherrie
I'm the consultant
Are you Mrs. Wong?
Yes, I am
Take a bath and have a sauna
I'll give you treatment
on lymphatic system
Are there many renowned spokespersons?
I like stars so much
They often come
when there're few customers
Can you tell me
when they'll come? Thank you
I don't take tips
I'll try my best. Follow me
Thank you very much
The 1st victim is Ivy...
then Sisi the 2nd
If counting in fame
the least famous is Ivy
the next is Fei Tong
Honey
Wait... What?
Come on, in the middle...
Ready? Are you ready?
Sure
What? You brought me flowers
You... why're you so romantic suddenly?
Don't you remember? We'll do it tonight
I remember
Alright...
Wait... listen to me now...
We only talk about romance, not others
Okay, Talk for a whole night
after this...
Listen to me Put off your clothes...
Talk about this... No...
Wait... What?
Give me some time. It's quick
Okay... hurry up, hurry up...
I just thought
you'd take some underwear out
The people suspected in the case
Friend of Fitness...
Forever Beauty, 1, 2, 3, 4...
Good enough?
You reconstructed the case?
Cool. It's professional...
Better than the police. Look...
Look at the colors. Have all needed
It's so good to frame it here
Okay...
I know you're not admiring me
Kidding only. Kidding
Kidding? You've been looking down on me
It was really a joke
I'm not arguing with you tonight
Let's talk about romance. Take them away
You always think of these things
You know how much I've thought?
How much? You just wrote down...
These things... This is the truth
No... I really...
I shouldn't have said that, okay?
You always think I'm trash
I'm not...
You think I'm a fool!
What're you talking about?
I'm here not to argue with you...
I've spent so much time
but you just took a glimpse
Why are you so angry?
Look, what do you look like?
You idiot!
You hit me?
I'm gonna call the police
I don't wanna talk with you. Go out
What? What do you say?
I won't go out
I say I won't and I won't say it again
I'm lying here. See what you can do
Come on baby, come on
Don't trouble me!
You'll see
I'm back to mum's place
What should I do? I made her go
As a gentleman, I shouldn't act like this
She investigated the case. No big deal
She goes. What should I do?
Kick the bucket
What's wrong with investigation?
Just show her talent
Why acted on impulse?
Should apologize to her last night
Sorry, it's my fault
That'd be alright
It's seven years after we got married
We've gone through ups and downs...
Have you finished?
I've heard it. No need to be so loud
Sorry
Hide the necklace or you can't cheat me
I forgot. Too bad
Where do you go?
Go to lavatory and then mum's place
It's your mum's birthday?
You've dressed up
Just for your sincerity
let you off this time
You do?
What's the matter?
You do? Then I make it
What?
You agreed last night
It's just expired
Expired? This isn't the milk
I don't care about that. C'mon
This time no
No? No more excuse. C'mon
I've put on the necklace
Put it off
Why?
Why don't you put it off?
That'll bring bad luck
Put it off and open the door
Quiet
You can still put it off
Quiet, please
Can't imagine...
there're so many negative news...
but still
there're so many people coming here
The influence of media's really great?
There're 7 or 8 magazines
inviting them to take pix
Look. They don't eat nor sleep
How can they stand it?
You've worked for a long time
Take a break
I got to enjoy every moment
when I see Fei
Why don't you date her?
Why don't you have affair instead?
She and I are different
She looks perfect from this point
But she doesn't if I get closer
You have good imagination
Doesn't it sound good?
But you'd be disappointed
Paparazzi aren't entertaining
Those interviewees
either feel unhappy...
or hate us
Anyway we can't make them happy
Then you should change your job
You look smart. You can be an artist
Brad Pitt can't compare to you
Paparazzi?
They're from Pau Magazine
I knew them when doing reporting
of Pitt and Aniston
I drive them away
Don't... let them take pix
Yes
What? So awful
Got it
What's the matter?
Nothing. We got wind of the case
Ken's in a car dump. They go catch him
Let's go
Don't. Too many cooks spoil the broth
Back to the station
to see if they make it
Doing less is the best
What? Who's this?
Not sure. No number displayed
It must be those gals
It says Ken is in 103
Lai Ching Villa, Mau Shing Street
Need to tell Inspector Tit?
No. If these are fake then we're over
The team's gone. Don't tell him
So what should we do?
Let's go to see now
How about the gals? Right
You go and I stay here
Call me if anything happens
Give you a chance
No thanks
I have my wife
There's half an hour left
Last night...
didn't find you in the bulletin
Didn't you? I didn't
But I looked carefully
I found you look different
But I think you were more beautiful
Don't laugh at me
I think you're bushed
after working a couple of days
No I don't but I worry what's going on
Don't worry. I'll protect you
Sorry, we don't rent to a couple of men
CID
Sorry sir...
I'm so sorry...
Sorry... I'm so sorry...
Ken!
Ken! You can't run. Put your arms down
Don't go. Get back!
You murderer!
Repay my son's hatred!
Shit...
Are you okay?
How can you take us home
at the same time, sir?
Miss Lui...
Tell your assistant
to drive the car to get here
We follow your cars
My car's there and I drive it to get here
Thanks
When're you available? I buy you dinner
Sure
But...
don't tell anyone that I was ugly
You've told that?
No. Don't worry
It may be my car alarm. I go take a look
Stay in the car. Lock the car up
Start the engine and wait for me
Miss...
Miss!
He's been out so long
Does he have trouble?
We'd better go
Better wait for a while
Sure. Wait for a while
It's useless to wait
Let me go to see them
Go ahead, but I only wait 5 minutes
I'll drive away after 5 minutes
Okay
What's wrong with Bull?
How's Tin Fuk?
His arm and some ribs are broken
It isn't too serious
How about the gals?
Queenie and Fei are missing
Cherrie's in the room
I go have a look
Ling
I know her
Cherrie
It's you
I'm Tak's wife
He's responsible for this case
I went to Friend of Fitness...
just for any clues
Sorry
Take the murderer as soon as possible
Save Fei and Cherrie
We'll do our best. Don't worry
You should take a rest
But I'm so scared
It's so terrible
I'm so scared!
I understand
You can try to... sleep for a while
Have a sweet dream
Tomorrow's another day
Who is she?
Bull's mother
Is she okay?
Very sad
Sure
Me too
I know
The saddest thing is...
that I can't be too sad in front of her
If I'm too sad...
she may not be able to stand it
Bull has been working with me for years
He's been following me
when he entered CID...
Sorry, it's such a mess
What... this is a mess?
Thank you for going out with me
We're friends now
Do you have something to ask me?
What's the relationship
between you and Ken?
He's been seeking
after me but I refuse
And he hasn't given up
Does he give you money?
I don't get the money
I don't love him
Has he ever sought after other models?
I think not
Then he's quite devoted to you
We need you to save Queenie and Fei
He's been sending phone messages to me
But I never answer any
I got another one today
Meet in Hunghom station at 5 today
Lure him out
Team A, has the shop been open?
Yes but no customer
Team B, is the glass clean?
Clean
Team C, finished the breakfast?
Not yet
Keeping an eye on the kitten
She looks nervous
Team A got it Team B got it
Team C got it
The kitten's got a call
Should be SMS
Team B, have you seen the mouse?
Not yet...
Perhaps the SMS tells the kitten
where to dine out
Follow her?
Yes
Keep an arm's distance
Don't alert the kitten
Team A, any mouse?
No
The kitten gets off the car, Tak
It seems that she switches the place
What's she doing?
The kitten gets on the minibus
Follow her?
Wait a minute...
No minibus. Enter station
then go into tunnel
Shit! The mouse's found us
Team A, ambush the kitten Got it!
Team B... attention. The kitten's coming
You go back. There's accident
Tak, the kitten gets in the subway
Keep an eye on the kitten. I'm coming
Report location...
Where're you?
Where?
Tak, can you hear me?
Team C, the kitten
is going to your point
Got it
Tak... he's run away
Report location
We're inside the bus
Friend of Fitness?
Where are you?
We're going to Chatham Road
I'm Tak Wong
I'm not available at the moment...
I'm going to Friend of Fitness, Tak
Join me, quick
No...
Help...
Stop!
Stop. Police!
Help... Stop!
Stop!
Police! Stop!
Help...
What's up? Cherrie's inside
Don't worry, hold... hold on
Is that Ken?
Ran at the back door
You look after her
It's okay
Okay
You'd better get home
I'll work so long tonight
Let me send her home. She lives near us
Sure
Call me if anything happens
You gotta sleep early tonight
I don't know if I can sleep
Come in if you're free
Sure. I'm still staying up
Let's have a chat
How are you going?
It's heard that Ken ran again
Yes... we're searching for him
My paparazzi friends
in Hong Kong sent me a tape
It's about Fei Tong
I don't know if it's useful
I've sent them to police
Look
Tak, it's for you
Serve yourself, I change clothes
Okay
Read these rare books
The Fitness Consultant Cherrie
and I were in the same college
but 2 forms lower
Such a coincidence
But at that time...
No wonder she's a fitness consultant now
Mess things up? What a savage
Are you human being?
Ken loves you so much
but you don't go with him?
Remember the ballet team in college?
You're so fat
You're more than 70 pounds?
Totally different from other classmates
You can't participate in the X'mas Ball
Come if you keep under 70 pounds
Remember the attitude
of the manager last time?
Do you remember?
Do you remember!
We'll call you later
So fat, still want to be an OL
You'll never able to give birth, hurray
You're happy, you're happy now?
I've checked your body
You've taken too many pills for slimming
which affect your kidney and liver
You'll never be able to have baby
Now is my turn
You must revenge
70 pounds...
They spend so much...
to lose weight. What do they do for?
Flattering the guys
I'm working on it with Cherrie
It doesn't work. It's not fair
Everyone should have 70 pounds to be fair
Why don't you be one of them?
You're the one inside Cherrie?
I'm much cleverer
I just give Ken something
then he helps me to deal with those women
Help me!
I did them...
I did them all!
Cherrie, wake up
You can't let it control you. Wake up
Don't stop. You're right
Go ahead!
No phone number displayed
Miss!
What's up?
Help... It's me!
I can't control myself...
I did them all!
I'm Tak Wong
I'm not available at the moment
Please leave a message
Inspector Wong
we got Ken's body in Friend of Fitness
The forensic is coming
You're sick
See the doctor and you'll be okay
Shoot me
Shoot me!
Why don't you shoot me?
Coz you have no bullets
Why do you know?
It isn't your turn now!
I forget it, sorry
Honey... you scared me
Are you okay?
Do you get hurt?
Okay
Let's go
Why don't your hands shiver?
No. They've been shivering
Let's go. Call back-up, quick
She's nervous breakdown
She has dual personality
That's not the original Cherrie
Gotta save her
Don't worry. I didn't kill her
Call an ambulance
Thank you
Tea time!
What? You're free
Need to do nothing?
Sure Sure?
Go find some
Go home and do it