It may look like just another
perfect day in sunny Kuala Lumpur Malaysia
but it's not
Because at San Francisco University,
a young woman has her college interview
Today is the first day
of the rest ofher life
And while she may look like
just another carefree college applicant-
She's not
Excuse me.
Do you know where the admissions office is?
- Left at the fire hydrant.
Follow the path inside.
First floor.
Thank you.
You're a lifesaver.
Okay, that was weird.
She's Maya Dolittle
And she can talk to animals
I mean, how cool is that?
Hi. I have a 9:00 appointment with
Admissions. Uh, it's Maya Dolittle.
Dolittle. Maya Dolittle.
As in Dr. Dolittle?
As in the great
Dr. Dolittle?
He's my dad.
- Yo, Frank.
Come here, man. Check this out.
This is Dolittle's kid.
The guy who
single-handedly
saved that herd
of Sumatran rhinos?
Yeah, that's him.
That's my dad.
Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
Oh, my God. I totally love Dr. "D."
My cat, Mr. Smushy, and I have moved to
a whole new level in our relationship...
and it's totally because of
his article, "Feeling Feline."
Uh, I guess I
missed that one.
Guys, I'm kinda
late here. Admissions?
Oh, uh, down the hall
to the right.
Okay, thank you.
- No problem.
Bye.
- Bye.
Bye. - Dolittle's
kid. - Wow.
Hi.
- Good morning.
Okay, Maya. Come
on. You can do this.
You are confident
and capable.
You will be as good a
veterinarian as your dad... someday.
Okay, smile therapy.
Okay.
Hello, Maya. My name is Doris Park Weaver-
- Hello.
Dean of Admissions for San Francisco
University's Center for Veterinary Medicine.
Oh. It's nice to meet you.
- Oh, it is so nice to meet you.
Your father's been an invaluable resource
to this institution.
Oh, thank you.
I saw him lecture once.
A most impressive man.
Yeah, he's lectured me
many times.
I mean, he's quite the lecturer.
This is our admissions committee.
They wanted to meet you in person.
Oh.
- Your father's thesis on anxiety disorders...
in anubis baboons
was brilliant.
Brilliant. Will you continue his
research on wombat mating habits?
He's done so much
for the keel-billed Toucan.
So much.
- You must be eager to follow in his footsteps.
What's the title
of his next book?
Do you think he'd sign a copy for me?
- Um, yes.
I'm not sure.
And okay, why not?
All righty then...
let's have a look at
your transcripts, shall we?
Now then, uh
it appears your grades
are, uh-
Okay.
Yes, well, um, my emphasis
in the past year...
has been more on... social aspects
of maturation versus academics...
in the hopes to broaden
my... curriculum vitae.
Ah. What about
extracurricular activities?
Perhaps you've joined your father
on one of his expeditions.
I read about his latest trip up the Amazon
in Invertebrates Illustrated
Inspiring, truly.
- Mmm.
Well, I was on the homecoming
committee last year.
And it's a lot more
demanding than it sounds.
Yeah.
Well, let's look at your S.A.T. Scores.
- Right.
Uh-
I've never been that great
in classroom situations
I find that I do better
in a real-worid environment.
Perfect. We'd love to see you in action.
- In action?
This is the clinic nursery.
The committee and I
will observe you...
to see how you interact
with the animals
Great Riece of cake
You just go ahead and kick back
and leave the babies to me.
Yeah,
all righty then.
Smile therapy.
Listen. Listen up,
you guys. Come here.
Look, this is very,
very important
My interview didn't go so well just now,
so I really need to impress them here.
So if you guys would just cooperate, that
would be greatly appreciated, okay?
Okay, awesome. Um-
So, boys and giris, what would
we like to play today?
How about we sing a song?
Oh! Hello there,
little goat.
Uh, yes, I know that is
a sound a goat makes.
But you don't have to do that with me
because I can talk to animals.
She wants her bottle.
- Oh. Um, okay, yeah.
Uh, "bah-bah." I knew that.
Uh, okay. Um-
You wanna drink your bottle?
Come on. Here you go.
Hey! Over here, everyone!
Harvey's hatched! Harvey's hatched!
Oh!
Welcome to the worid, baby chick.
- Mama?
Oh, no, no, no.
I'm not your mama.
Mama. Mama. Mama.
- Wha-
Oh, don't cry, little kitty.
You're my mew-mew.
- Your "mew-mew"? What is that?
She thinks you're her mom.
- Hey, Mom Hey, Mom
Guess what. Guess what. Guess what. Guess what.
- What?
They all think you're their mom.
- I'm comin', Mama. Geronimo!
Excuse me. Sorry.
I got him.
I saved him.
Hey, Mom, you got any treats in here?
- Hey, wait! That's my purse!
Guess what. Guess what.
Bag, man
Where's all the good stuff?
Give me the- Look!
- Run for it!
This is fun!
- Told you you couldn't keep us locked down.
If you guys don't all stop this behavior,
you're all going to be on time-out!
Guess what. Guess what. Guess what.
- What? What? What?
That's what.
Mom!
- I'm in the kitchen
So, how'd it go? How'd it go?
- Don't ask.
So, uh, I'm guessing a game
of fetch is out of the question?
So, how'd it go?
- I blew it.
They wait-listed me. And they said
that was only because "I'm a Dolittle."
Oh, Maya,
so sorry.
Unless I can come up with a way to impress
the committee within the next four weeks...
they suggest that I find
other alternatives to S.F.U.
I don't know what I was thinking.
I am not cut out for vet school.
Oh, don't be so hard
on yourself, Maya.
You have so much
natural talent.
It's gonna take some time
for you to develop it.
But what if I can't?
You're only 8.
Have faith, little one.
You are gonna find your own way
of doing things. I promise.
Ain't ya? Yeah?
- Yeah.
Yeah. There you go.
You guys, my life is over
Les femmes,
always so dramatic.
Talk to me after you've had your butt sniffed
by a Great Dane in a public park.
Now that's hard to live down.
- You guys, I'm serious.
I have four weeks to impress the admissions
committee, and I have no idea how to do it.
Did you try dropping my name?
Everyone loves Monkey
I am- how you say-
the breakout character.
How 'bout I get stuck down a well
like on one of those TV shows?
It'll be a huge story
and we'll get famous.
Oh! I wonder if they'll get Lassie
to play me in the movie.
Sacre bleu!
It's animal control!
Quick, hide!
The monkey has left
the building.
Don't look now,
but he's heading your way
I'll get it.
Mmm, he's young, handsome,
winning smile.
You better get downstairs and
make a fool of yourself right away.
Hello.
- Hi. Mrs. Dolittle?
Yes?
- My name is Cole Fletcher. I'm an aide at the White House.
This gentleman is
with the Secret Service
We're here on behalf of the
president of the United States.
Oh, well, come in.
What can I do
for you gentlemen?
The president has asked to see Dr. Dolittle
at the White House right away.
The President?
- The White House?
Is he here?
I'm sorry. Uh...
he's in Antarctica saving
a pod of bowhead whales.
Can it wait a few weeks until he comes back?
- I'm afraid not.
It's an urgent matter, and no one else
is equipped to handle the situation.
He needs someone
who can talk to animals.
Well, I wish there was something
I could do to help, but-
I can go.
- What?
What?
- My name is Maya Dolittle.
And I can talk to animals,
just like my dad.
Really?
- Really.
Jack of spades.
- Jack of spades.
Oh, please. Four of hearts.
- Four ofhearts
Like father, like daughter.
Hold on. I need
to make a call.
Okay. Well, just
take your time.
Maya, I am not sure that this is a good idea.
- Mom.
The admissions committee said I
needed to impress them, right? - Mm-hmm.
So if I can get a recommendation
from the president of the United States...
what's more impressive than that?
- I don't know, honey.
Huh?
Yes, sir.
Yes, I understand.
Well, Miss Dolittle, looks like
you're going to the White House.
We are goin' to the White House!
We are goin' to the White House! Ha-ha!
This is unfair!
This is an outrage!
I'm sorry, Monkey,
but you can't come.
The last time I took you anywhere, we ended
up in jail for disturbing the peace.
If Olive Garden doesn't want you to
throw food, they should have a sign.
Look. I'm sorry, but
this is just too important.
My whole future is riding on this.
I'll bring you back some soap.
Later, Kong.
Once again, you underestimate
the tiny genius in the silly T-shirt.
# The TVsays I'm not
the girl that I should be #
#It drives me crazy #
#I'm not impressed
It isn't what I want to be #
#So call me lazy #
#Operator, operator #
#Don't call me
I'll call you later #
#Operator, operator #
#I'm just fine
I'll call you later #
# Why would I wanna be
anybody else but me #
#I'm never
gonna fake it #
# Why would I ever be
anybody else but me #
#I know I'm
gonna make it #
# Without a doubt
I know what I'm about #
#I'm everything
I ever wanna be #
#A girl like me #
- Wow!
#A girl like me ##
I felt the same way the first time
I walked through those doors.
Come on.
Ah, porter,
my bag is in the trunk.
Careful with the squeezy bone.
It's a family heirloom.
Ah, Miss Dolittle.
Maya, this is the president's
chief of staff, Mr. Harold Dorion.
Nice to meet you, Mr. Dorion.
- Welcome to the White House. This is Selma Dixon.
Both she and Cole are assigned
to my office as interns.
Pleasure.
- Thank you, gentlemen. I'll take it from here.
Cole, Selma, I need those G.D.P. Reports
on Kalampore on my desk in an hour.
You'll have them in half an hour, sir.
- Excellent.
This way, Miss Dolittle.
You know, the president
is very anxious to meet you, Maya.
And this is the West Wing. Although
the White House was finished in 800...
the West Wing wasn't
added until 902.
And the Oval Office itself
wasn't built until the 930s.
For over 200 years, some of our
nation's most important decisions...
have been made right here
in this office.
I can't believe you're making me go. It's spring
break! All my friends are going to Florida!
"All of your friends"are not
the president's daughter
Courtney, this
is Maya Dolittle.
Hi, it's nice to meet you.
We're hoping
she grows out of it.
Right, and I'm hoping they open
a Burger King for dogs, but I'm not optimistic.
Mr. President.
- Maya.
Thank you for coming
I'm a huge fan of your father's
It's an honor, Mr. President.
- And who is this good-looking guy?
The man's got my vote.
- This is Lucky. He is also at your service, Mr. President.
You obviously understand dogs.
I hope you can help with mine.
Please, sit down.
Harold?
Yes, sir.
Yes, everyone knows
and loves Daisy
Mee-yowza!
- Daisy's been with the family since I was governor.
She's been at my side
every step of my career.
She was instrumental in the
president's election campaign.
Look. There she is singing the
national anthem at a baseball game.
She was perfectly in tune.
- That is so cute!
Some people think she's a symbol
of this administration, of its humanity.
But lately, our
beloved First Dog has become, well
a nightmare
She's running amok and we
don't know what to do about it.
Ah, the woman of my dreams.
- Shh! Put a lid on it.
I beg your pardon?
- Oh, no, not you. Him.
Sorry It takes
a while to get used to
So, basically what I'm hearing
is, is Daisy just needs a talking to.
I can handle that.
- There's more to it than that, Maya.
We're having a diplomatic crisis
with the country of Kalampore.
You see, Maya, Kalampore is home to the
worid's second largest tropical rain forest.
The Boyd and Dunsmore Investment Group
wants to develop the land
and has made a very lucrative
offer to the royal family of Kalampore.
If the development deal goes through,
the rain forest will be totally destroyed...
and with it, thousands
of species that make it home
That's awful.
- But the president
has convinced the head of the
royal family, Prince Tharoor...
to reject the Dunsmore offer,
and instead has proposed a treaty
that would permanently protect
the land as an animal preserve.
The prince was all set to sign this historic
agreement last month in Kalampore...
and things went
horribly wrong.
Unfortunately, the president came down
with a terrible case of... food poisoning.
Oh, no, he didn't.
- Oh, no, don't say it.
Oh, yes.
All over the prince.
Jelly beans?
- No, thank you.
The deal didn't get signed.
The moment passed...
and the deal fell apart.
Oh, no.
We've invited the prince to the US
We're gonna hold a state dinner in his honor
It's a last-ditch effort
to repair the relationship...
and convince him to sign
the agreement.
And that's where you
come in, Maya. You see...
the prince's daughter
is a huge fan of Daisy.
She's practically
Daisy crazy.
And of course, she wants
to meet her... in person.
Yikes.
- Exactly
The prince arrives
in... eight days.
What- Eight days?
Maya...
- l-
we need you to deliver the old Daisy
before the state dinner.
We are counting on you.
Send in Daisy, please.
Hi, Daisy. I'm-
- Listen
If you think you can waltz in here with your
head-shrinking, animal-talking circus act...
and turn me into some perfect,
hand-licking First Dog
then you've got another
thing coming, sister
I'll chew you up like
an off-white athletic sock...
then I'll poop you out
in the Rose Garden.
Wh-What did she say, Maya?
Uh, she said, "Hi."
Ah.
Hello, Daisy.
Daisy! Uh, Maya, please
tell her not to do that.
Daisy, do not sneeze on
the chief of staff s pants.
Oh. Okay. Well, then how
'bout this sort of thing?
Daisy.
Oh!
Harold.
- Yes, sir. Yes, sir. Come here, Daisy-
Nice try, Harold.
- Daisy!
Daisy, sit!
- Daisy, no!
#I'm tired, baby
Tired of messin'with my head #
Whoops.
- No!
#Gonna pull myself
from the ledge ##
Whoops!
See ya.
Wouldn't wanna be ya.
What a ride.
Harold.
- Sir?
Have everybody pack up-
the staff, the interns,
the dog, Courtney.
We're going
to the ranch today!
The ranch?
The Sterling Ranch.
The president's... retreat.
I call shotgun!
Maya, come with me.
Anyone else who wants
the grand tour, hop in.
Go on. Go on.
I don't need you.
All right, here we go
Hey, anyone over there
got lotion? My skin is so dry.
Hmm, maybe I can find
some aloe in here.
Where do all the animals come from?
- Oh, different places.
Some were rescued, some were gifts
of foreign dignitaries.
We started the reserve to protect
a few endangered species.
And now we have
over 30 species.
Dozens have been bred
and released back into the wild.
Hey, hey! How's
the weather down there?
Wow! It's incredible.
Hey, guys, look-
people.
This land has been in my family
for over a century.
About 5 years ago, I
fulfilled a dream of a lifetime:
Created this nature preserve
and family retreat.
I'm not really
an animal person.
Allergies.
Hmph.
Many of the worid's
greatest leaders have stayed here.
And a lot ofhistory
made in this place
It's my hope that next week...
history will be made again.
Ahh. Free at last.
Now where can a monkey
freshen up around here?
And this brings us back
to the compound.
Everybody,
heads up! Incoming!
What's that?
Oh, that used to be
Courtney's play yard.
Now we use it for some animals who live
over there in a specially designed habitat.
Go take a look.
- Okay.
Hold up a second,
blokes Whoa Look at the sheila
Hola, chica.
- Wow, hey, guys.
Hi, darling. How ya doin'?
Hello, beautiful
lady person.
Oh, no. This is bad.
I am sensing very bad.
Don't mind him. He's a few
sandwiches short of a picnic.
Look out below!
Lucky, this is a wallaby.
A rock wallaby to be exact.
As in rock and roll! Bonzer good times!
Whoo-hoo! Oi, mates. Let's party!
Where's the Pop Tarts? Come on!
Let's go!
Okay, that wallaby
needs to chill.
Tell me about it Reminds me
of this guy I used to date, Javier
Always about how his fur
looked I'm Rosie, by the way
You need the 4
on anyone or anything?
These ears can hear a pin drop
from a thousand yards.
She calls it 411
I call it gossip
And gossip is bad-
very, very bad.
Oh, put an ant in it,
bug breath.
Let's party!
It was great. Yeah.
- You liked it.
Scintillating.
Wow. I love what
you've done with the place.
What happened?
- Daisy.
But we've only been here a few minutes.
- She works fast.
Welcome to Sterling Ranch.
Hope you have a pleasant stay.
Come on, Daisy.
Good girl. Here we go.
Mr Rresident?
Maya, I have to go
to a meeting.
The porters will show you
to your room.
I'm afraid you have
your work cut out for you.
Smile therapy?
Oh, forget it!
That doesn't work anyway!
Not on the bookcase
Well, I'm unpacked.
What am I gonna do? Daisy's not a dog.
She's Hannibal Lecter with fur!
I may be able to talk to animals,
but I cannot work miracles.
Maya, one thing I know about you is that
you underestimate yourself.
And sometimes you don't
apply yourself completely.
Have you been reading
my report card again?
Read it? I forged your
dad's signature, remember?
If I want a recommendation
from the president...
I'm gonna have to whip crazy Daisy
into shape in less than a week.
I don't know what I'm gonna do.
I think I've bitten off
more than I can chew.
Been there. Never forget that time
I caught the Volkswagen.
I wish I could reach Dad.
He would know what to do.
Why don't you just figure out what he would
do in the same situation, and try that?
Hey, that's not such
a bad idea.
We're not man's
best friend for nothin'.
Hey. Hey, can you fix my hair?
I don't have thumbs.
First of all, Daisy, I would like to thank you
for agreeing to meet with me.
That was very civilized
and mature of you.
Well, I got to thinking
about my recent behavior...
and decided it was
probably time to get some help.
Oh, okay.
So, um, tell me...
when did you first notice these
feelings of hostility surfacing?
Gosh I think, maybe, it
all began when the president
started bringing home
all these other animals.
I see. I see.
I think I might be,
well, jealous?
Yes, jealous.
I see. I see.
In fact, I just have so much
to get off my chest...
maybe it would be a good idea
if we all met, you know, like-
Group therapy?
- Yes! Group therapy!
I'll meet you at the
habitat in 0 minutes.
Maybe this won't be
as hard as I thought.
Hey, Daisy's back. How ya been, darlin'?
- What's the word, sister?
Hey, you guys. I got a problem
that I need you to help me get rid of.
Whatever you need, Daisy, girl.
- Your wish is my command, my Daisy.
Hello?
- Holy cow! You scared me to death.
Uh, sorry.
- Close the door. Close the door!
Would you please?
Would you close the door?
Rlease close it!
Uh, would you like to join us
for group therapy?
Oh, I would love to,
but what if I see my shadow?
What if I don't? It could affect the climate
of the entire planet if I do
Ah, the pressure is killing me!
- An agoraphobic groundhog?
Pretty twisted, I know.
Okay. Well, I guess
I'll just see you later.
Maybe.
Go to your safe place Go to
your safe place Go to your safe place
Everyone, this is Maya.
And she can talk to animals.
Hello, Maya.
Hi.
Wait a second.
Have we met before?
No, no, never.
I am, uh, Aldo.
Aldo, the Italian monkey
And I am from...
Napoli!
Okay, Aldo
So, as many of you
already know, this is Daisy...
and she's been having some issues
she would like to discuss with you guys.
Daisy?
Okay. Well, Daisy's
having a quiet moment.
Is there anybody else
who'd like to say something?
Hmm.
- Mmm.
Conflicts? Issues? Anything?
Come on, you guys. There's gotta be
something you wanna talk about.
Fine. I remember once back in New Delhi
at the zoo- Oh, this was very, very bad.
If I have to hear this story one more time,
I'm gonna throw myself on a trap.
You are rude. Very, very rude!
- I'm rude?
People. I mean, folks.
I mean, animals!
Everybody, just chill out!
Nyah.
- All right, that's just gross.
Now let's all listen and respect
what each other has to say.
Actually, there is something
I'd like to say.
Bombs away!
Bomb bay doors open!
Aha! Bull's-eye!
Nice shot Man
your battle stations!
To the barricades!
Pass the ammunition.
Anteater! Run
for your lives!
Fire at will!
Gotcha!
Mon dieu!
I mean, mamma mia!
You better stop-
Take-a this!
Stop it! Oh-
I demand you stop this behavior!
Direct hit!
One egg-a, scrambled!
So long, girlie!
Thanks for stoppin'by!
All right, let's
get back to work.
I guess she's
the comic relief.
Hi. Can I have some
roast beef, please?
How 'bout you accidentally drop a T-bone
on the ground for your old pal here?
Forget about it. You
know it gives you gas.
Uh- Oh, no, not you.
The dog.
Don't judge me.
Excuse me.
Nature calls.
Hey, how's it goin'?
Have you tried the steak?
So, Maya, how did it
go today with Daisy?
Uh, it was... colorful.
Hmm. Good colorful,
or bad colorful?
Like a medium colorful.
Well, I'm afraid a medium colorful
just isn't gonna cut it.
Maya, we need bold, brilliant, vibrant,
primary colors here.
We need a full-on, five-star
rainbow, and we need it fast.
Yes, sir.
- Oh, and, Maya...
that, uh, scene today
outside the barn-
Just make sure that kind of thing doesn't
happen in front of the president.
I will, sir. I mean, I won't.
It-It won't, sir.
Good.
Okay, check it out:
"Herro," Shaggy.
Rooby-rooby-doo!
That's my Scooby-Doo
Gee, with that material, I'm surprised
you don't have your own TV show.
Wait Hang on
"Herro," Reorge. Ruh-oh.
Astro?
From TheJetsons?
You have got
to get some new material.
Tough crowd.
- Thank you.
Maya, you want to join us?
- Sure.
Oh, I'm so sorry, Mayo.
Did you want to sit here?
It's Maya.
So, Maya, tell us
a little bit about yourself.
Oh, uh, well, I'm a senior
at Hamilton High in San Francisco.
Really? And where are
you going to school next year?
Um, well, I'm still
assessing my options.
But I'm considering
S.F.U.'s vet school.
But why can't I go?
- We've been over this before.
You can't go because I think
it's inappropriate...
for the First Daughter
to be at a party unsupervised.
This is so unfair!
Mom would let me go.
Well, your mother happens to be making a
four-nation tour, and I'm in charge around here.
What about you guys? Where do you go?
- We both go to Yale.
I'm a poli-sci major, and Selma's studying
International Relations.
With a minor in foreign languages:
French, German, Russian and Cantonese.
I intend to make an impact
on global politics by the time I'm 30.
What about you?
What's your long-term goal?
Long term? Um, I guess just
to take care of animals.
Oh, you mean like a
doggie day care? How sweet.
No, I mean, like a
veterinarian. A doctor.
But if you can't fix
the president's dog...
how are you gonna fix
other people's animals?
Oh. Could you pass
the mayo, Maya?
I'm sorry. Can you repeat that?
I don't speak snob.
What?
I just don't understand you.
I mean, the state dinner could be fun if-
Right. It's just so fun to have the
best years of my life sucked away...
by stupid press events, dull political speeches
and boring state dinners.
Thanks, Dad!
Maya!
- Yes, sir.
The chief tells me that
you're making headway with Daisy.
I want a full progress
report tomorrow, all right?
Yes, sir, sir.
- I'm counting on you.
How can I give a progress report
when I haven't made any progress?
I don't get why she doesn't dig me.
You think I should grow a beard?
Lucky, I have to find a different
way to deal with these animals.
Because Dad's way just isn't working.
What usually works with you?
Well, a biscuit always
seems to do nicely.
Yeah, right,
like that's gonna work.
Hmm.
You comin' out today?
I would, but I'm
shampooing my tail.
Suit yourself.
Hey, everybody,
look what I've got. Treats!
Ding, ding Round two!
Watch your
head, you monkey!
Say hello to my little friend!
- There you go!
Enjoy my spicy red ant special
That's gonna be hard
to get out of your hair!
Oh, forget it!
Come back soon, all right?
Maya What happened?
I, um-
See-
I'm sorry, sir.
I'm no good at this.
Maya.
- Please, just leave me alone.
I'm sure it wasn't that bad.
I'm never gonna get that recommendation,
so why keep embarrassing myself?
But what about Daisy and me?
You know, she completes me.
Look. I've already let down my family
and the president of the United States.
Forget it. I'm cuttin' my losses.
We're on the next copter out of here.
Cole, I said I just
wanna be left... alone.
Maya, am I...
interrupting?
No, sir. I was just
packing up.
I'm sorry I disappointed you, sir, but I should
have never come here in the first place.
Maya, let's take a walk.
You remind me a lot of
myself when I was your age
I do?
- Demanded a lot of myself.
Expected way too much
too soon.
Meet my friends
So, did you know...
that MichaelJordan...
didn't make his high school
varsity basketball team?
MichaelJordan? The best
basketball player ever? No way.
Way.
Did you know that Einstein failed
his first college entrance exam?
Wait. "E" equals "MC" squared Einstein? Really?
- Yep
Did you know in high school
I ran for class president?
I lost.
I came in fourth.
Well, that's not too bad.
Out of four?
- Okay, that's bad.
The only thing that
saved me at that time...
was I had a motto I kept
on my desk by Hank Aaron...
a famous ballplayer
before your time.
Two words:
"Keep swinging."
He used to say that no matter
how bad his slump was
no matter how badly
he felt...
he just had
to keep swingin'.
But, sir, I'm just afraid I can't-
- Maya.
"We have nothing to fear
but fear itself."
That was Franklin Roosevelt.
You come with me. There's
somebody I want you to meet.
Come on, Maya.
So, this is Lenore
She's a red ruffed lemur.
Give her some
gooseberries. She likes 'em.
She was captured by poachers as a baby,
delivered to a Malaysian circus.
Somehow she made her way
to an Indonesian zoo and then here.
She's an endangered species
And we had hopes of returning
her to her homeland...
but unless I can get the prince
to sign this agreement...
the rain forest
will be destroyed.
And the other lemurs like Lenore?
- Absolutely.
Did you know that, on average,
74 species a day become extinct?
I had no idea.
- Most people don't.
All of us have so much
more to learn
Maya, failure is a part of life,
even for successful people.
The trick is... what are
you gonna do about the failure?
Are you gonna quit, or are
you gonna keep on swinging?
Lucky, drop that bone,
unpack those bags.
I just got a pep talk from the
president of the United States.
And we are stayin'.
Whoo-hoo! Whoo-hoo!
Whoa. Getting dizzy.
Oh, getting dizzy.
Why do dogs have to do this
when they're happy?
#And if you think #
# That you
could do better #
#She's got some
pretty wise sage advice #
#For you if you let her #
#And she'll
let you know #
# We never go
in the heat of competition #
# Tell me everything
you know #
#About the human
condition And wait #
# Till the meter maids
are doin'their job #
#And they're callin'the cops
'cause they're afraid too #
# 'Cause it's makin'a lot #
What are you doing?
Did you know that Cavalier King Charles
spaniels were originally bred for British royalty?
Here you go, Daisy.
Okay.
So, what do you think?
What do you think?
Stee-rike one.
It's important that you keep me posted
on exactly when and where...
the prince and his-
when the prince comes-
Hold on a second
Maya, what are you doing?
Did you know that King Charles
spaniels are the happiest...
when they're sitting
in someone's lap?
I think it's working.
I'll have to call you back.
Stee-rike two.
Do you know that your breed is extremely
social and loves to play and fetch?
Two words: "Give up."
- Two words: "No way."
One word: "Later"!
Just keep swingin'.
Stee-rike three!
You're out.
Remember back in ninth grade when I had
that cafeteria feud with Wendy Boudreau?
Who could forget her? Her face looked like
the business end of a bulldog.
And how did I handle that situation?
I made friends with her friends.
Interesting. I would
have just pooped in her shoes.
Lucky, I think it's time for
another group therapy sessin.
Come on.
Hey, are you gonna join us today?
Ah, uh, yeah, I, um-
Remember what F.D.R. Said:
"We have nothing to fear but fear itself."
You're right You're right You're absolutely
right I'm coming out Here I come
Doh!
I just can't do it
- Okay. Whenever you're ready.
All right, Maya.
Let's go make some friends.
Hello, everyone.
How are y'all doin' today?
- Rats!
I think last time we started off on the
wrong foot. Let's start off fresh, shall we?
You have foiled my poop bomb.
I am most impressed.
Horacio, I know you miss
your girlfriends back in Venezuela.
Yes. This is true.
You're feeling lonely because you're the only
Amazon parrot within a hundred-mile radius.
Yes. This, too, is true.
You're feeling the pressure of having
to be exotic and colorful 24-7.
You have seen
into my soul.
Wait a second.
What's goin' on here?
Bruce, you're numbing out,
partying all the time
because you feel like, otherwise,
everybody's gonna think you're boring.
Isn't that right?
- Crikey, you don't know what it's like...
to be a party animal.
And, Rosie, you like
gossiping all the time...
because then you feel like
you're the center of attention.
But you feel some deep shame
when it's all over, don't you?
I just wanna be liked.
- I like you, mate.
Yeah. We all think that you're
an amazing chinchilla, don't we?
Don't we?
- I like you, Rosie.
Me too.
- Me three.
Hey, don't fall for this.
She's trying to trick you.
And, Aldo, my
monkey friend...
I know you miss your carefree days
ofbeing in the alfresco markets of Italy
You're sad because you
miss your family back in Naples.
You miss your papa's red wine
and your sweet grandmama's cannoli
Ah, sweet grandmama.
I am not Aldo or Italian.
I do not even have a grandmama.
L- It's me, Maya, your Monkey!
Oh, I know, Monkey. And I'm so sorry.
And I'll never
leave you again, okay?
Off you go.
- That is so beautiful.
Anteater? Come on. Blow.
Come on, you guys. Get it together.
Repeat after me:
"This is very, very good"
This is very,
very... good.
See? Now how does that feel?
- It feels very, very... good!
You seem all right, girlie Why would
you want to send Daisy to the pound?
What? The pound? Where would
you get a crazy idea like that?
I'll give you one guess.
Aha!
I'm outta here.
- Ay, Daisy, please
Don't go
- Daisy, come back
Oh, and I was
just starting to feel good
What am I gonna do? The
prince is gonna be here in two days
I just don't understand
why Daisy's behaving this way.
There must be something
I'm missing, but what?
Hello?
Hey, did you hear that?
- What is it, Lucky?
Yeah. Yeah, I
can totally come.
Clearwater Campground.
Okay. I'll be there.
I can't see. What's she
doing? What's she doing?
Something she
shouldn't be doing.
Just a second
Hey, Maya.
- Hey, can you do me a huge favor?
Can you drive me somewhere? No questions asked.
- I would, but I don't have a car.
Gotta be some wheels
around here somewhere.
You know, we can probably find somethin'.
- Okay.
Man, can you make
this thing go any faster?
I'm already pedal
to the metal.
This Clearwater Campground
has to be around here somewhere.
Stay here.
I'll be right back.
That's great
- Where did you get that?
Great. So now
you're following me?
It's bad enough I've got Secret Service on
my back. Now I've got the Dog Chatterer?
Your dad would freak out
if he found out you were here...
without Secret Service protection.
- I can take care of myself.
Yeah Right
- Wait a minute Now I know where I know you from
You're the president's freakin' daughter.
- What? No. No, I'm- I'm-
Dude, dude! It's the
First freakin' Daughter, man.
Who's got a camera?
- No!
Come on. Come on. One picture.
- No No pictures
She said, no pictures.
Oh, and what are you gonna
do, huh? Call Secret Service?
Ow!
- No, but I will.
I think it's time to leave.
He got served.
- Oh!
Cute
- How did you do that?
Fifteen years of tae
kwon do classes just paid off.
I'll be right back. You
giris stay right here, okay?
So...
I suppose you think I'm a spoiled, ungrateful,
irresponsible brat.
The thought
crossed my mind.
You have no idea what it's like
to be the daughter...
of a national hero- all the
expectations that are heaped on you-
And you feel like you'll never be able to
measure up to your father's greatness-
like you have to be perfect
all the time- so what's the point?
Yes, exactly. How did-
Your father.
- That's right.
Dr. Dolittle,
beloved veterinarian.
National hero.
- Mm-hmm.
This past year I lost sight
of my priorities.
I let my grades drop, blew off
my responsibilities...
and completely screwed up
my college application.
But I think the truth is,
I was afraid-
afraid I wouldn't be able to live up
to my father's reputation.
And comin' here helped me remember
what's important to me in my life...
and that's the animals- even though I had
to mess up big-time to figure that out.
It's just...
he always expects me
to be perfect.
Now do you really
believe that?
Or is that just what you tell yourself
so you can stay mad at him?
Your father is not perfect.
He makes mistakes
just like everybody else.
Did you know that he ran for class president and lost?
- No way.
Way.
So just give him a chance...
and you'll realize that he
just wants what's best for you.
Not a word from
either one of you.
No, pink's totally
your color
Come on.
Hop up here.
Hey! Who's hungry?
# You can't
see it coming #
# Until it's too late #
# You're struck
down by the hand of fate #
Hot fudge is comin' in here.
# With or without #
#And when you do it's always too late #
- Looks so good.
#Ooh, it's all sunshine #
- Sprinkles.
#Or it's all rain #
- Whoa, whoa, whoa.
#Ooh, it's all sunshine ## -
Enough sprinkles! - Let's eat.
Gotta get some
whipped cream.
Whoop!
Oh, you think
that's funny, huh?
That's funny? Uh, okay.
Here.
Whoa!
Courtney, where have you been? We have
been looking everywhere for you.
Well, I, uh-
Uh, s-sir, it was...
all my fault.
I snuck out, and Courtney
followed me and Cole followed her
Maya, this is not
fun and games here.
The prince's visit
is in two days'time
and as far as I can see, Daisy is no farther
along than she was a week ago.
I'm sorry, sir. It won't happen again.
- Make sure that it doesn't.
Cole, we'll talk about this in the morning.
- Yes, sir.
And your father wants
to see you immediately.
That was pretty cool of you back there,
takin'the hit for Courtney
That was pretty cool of you back at that party.
I don't know what we would have done without you.
Yeah, well, I'm
glad I could help out.
I've never seen Courtney
laugh like that.
Yeah, I have a feeling things are gonna
start changing for the better.
It's just the pressure of bein' the First Daughter.
- Who could blame her?
Yeah. Now if only Daisy
was that simple to figure out.
Wait a minute.
Maybe Daisy is that simple.
I can't believe it. It's been right
under my nose the entire time.
Oh, you are a genius!
I... didn't...
say anything.
Daisy!
Where could she have gone?
Come on, girl.
Dais-
Rosie, I have been looking for Daisy all
over the place. Have you heard anything?
I might have heard a
few things, but I can't say.
What? Why not?
- I gave up gossiping. I am a changed chinchilla.
Rosie, that's not gossiping.
That's helping out a friend.
Hmm.
Here. I think we should conclude
with this paragraph right here.
You guys, Daisy's gone.
She ran away.
What?
Well, let's go find her.
Cole, we have a presentation
due in two hours for the chief of staff.
It's just a dog.
Just a dog? You know what? If that's really
what you think, then I feel sorry for you.
And I hate to break it to you, but some things
are more important than your career
Come on, Maya.
There's Courtney!
Courtney! Courtney!
I've been looking for Daisy everywhere and
none of the other animals have seen her either.
I think she ran away
What?
- I can't find her anywhere.
Don't worry. We'll help you find her.
- Let's go this way.
Okay. Bruce,
you head out north.
Horacio, Monkey,
you guys go south.
Chinchilla, keep your ear to
the ground. Lucky, you're with us.
Leave no stone unturned.
We've got to find this dog.
Yes. We go south! I have
no idea which way is south.
Follow me. One thing
this bird's got is G.P.S.
You got it, baby.
- Game on!
Okay. Let's go.
Hey. Mind if I tag along?
I figured you could use
all the help you could get.
Thanks.
Come on.
Daisy!
Daisy! - Daisy!
- Here, girl!
Daisy, come on!
Daisy! -
Daisy! - Daisy!
We've been looking
for hours. It's no use.
There's a thousand acres here.
She could be anywhere.
Anything, Lucky?
- Mm-mmm.
Reporting in from units two
and three. No sign of the pooch.
Courtney, is there anywhere
she would have gone?
A special place,
somethin' like that? Think hard.
I don't know.
Wait.
I have an idea.
We used to play here
all the time when I was a kid.
There she is!
- Wait.
Can I have a minute
alone with her?
Come on. Trust me.
Okay. We'll meet you
back at the ranch.
Hey, girl.
- Go away.
Daisy, I know it's a lot of
pressure being the First Dog.
You can rebel all you want, but you can't
run away from who you are. None of us can.
I just want things to be
the way they used to be.
When he was governor,
we were a family.
We would spend time together, play fetch,
go jogging, but now everything's changed
It's always the cameras, meetings, events,
and I'm just a political prop.
You are so much more
than that, Daisy.
You are an inspiration
to the people of this country.
And there's not many animals
or people who can even say that.
I don't want to be
an inspiration.
I just want to be...
a dog.
Daisy, come here. Come here.
Come here, girl.
You are a dog-
an amazing dog-
and you have a family
that loves you very much.
But the thing is, every family has its own
set of problems, its frustrations...
and we're always wishing
that things were different.
But what if, instead of
running away from who we are...
we just started
embracing it.
You're right, Maya.
You're right.
You sure they're gonna be
all right out there?
I think we have
to trust her, Dad.
Hey, hey,
look, everyone!
Oh, Daisy!
Come on! Come on, girl
Daisy! Come on.
- Oh, good girl.
Yeah.
Don't you ever run away like that again.
You scared the daylights out of us.
I think Daisy is finally ready to talk,
if you guys are ready to listen.
Come on, girl. I've got
your favorite treats inside.
Courtney and I also had a talk this morning.
- Oh?
She told me everything: About the party,
about how you covered for her.
Gave us an opportunity for our first
really good talk in a long time...
thanks to you, Maya.
I'm glad I could help.
Excellent work, Maya.
All right, everybody, we have
a state dinner to prepare for.
# Whoa, whoa,
whoa, whoa, whoa #
#Someday #
- #I'll buy an old car #
#Mmm #
- #Someday #
#I'll get that car to start #
- #Hoo-ooh, hoo-ooh #
#Someday #
- #I'll learn how to drive too #
#Mm-hmm and
then someday #
#Imagine all
the things I could do #
# Whoo #
- #Someday #
#I'll get that car to start #
- #Hoo-ooh, hoo-ooh #
#Someday #
#I'll learn
how to drive too #
# Yes, I will now
And then someday #
#Imagine all the
things I could do ##
Your Highness,
thank you for coming.
It's my great pleasure
to welcome you to Sterling Ranch.
Mr. President,
it is indeed my pleasure.
I look forward to a fruitful
and productive visit.
You must be tired from your travels.
My staff will show you to your quarters...
and I look forward to seeing you
this evening at the dinner.
Thank you,
Mr. President.
We've got our work
cut out for us.
Ladies and
gentlemen, please rise
Ladies and gentlemen,
His Royal Highness
Rrince Tharoor
of Kalampore
Your Highness, welcome.
- Mr. President.
May I present my
daughter, Courtney.
My daughter,
Amina.
I'm so nervous.
It'll be fine. You've done everything you can.
- It's gonna go great.
Hi, Maya! Hey, it's us.
- Ay, beautiful fiesta.
I wanna go. I wanna go.
I wanna go!
Put a cork in it, Bonzo.
It's a people party.
Alas, my life story.
And now, the First Dog,
Daisy.
Where is she?
Oh! There she is
- There she is
We are pleased
to meet you, Daisy.
The Kalampore
National Anthem.
She's so cute.
Hold on.
Yes?
Everything's under control.
I have something that'll make those bad oysters
I gave him in Kalampore seem like high tea.
After tonight, there's no way
the prince will sign that agreement.
The only document
linking me to this deal...
is locked in a safe
in my office.
I assure you, Mr. Dunsmore,
that rain forest is history...
and you and I are
going to be very rich.
Oh, no. Oh, no,
the chief is a rat!
I gotta do somethin'.
I gotta tell somebody.
Oh, if only I could leave
this house, but I can't!
All right. Okay, if I leave this house,
what's the worst thing that's gonna happen?
Okay, people will think
that spring is early
But I'm not the only groundhog.
It's not all on my shoulders.
And the rain forest
The rain forest is at sta-
But there are
other rain forests.
I can't stand-I've gotta go!
I'm goin'! Stand back!
I did it! I'm goin'! I'm goin'!
We have nothing to fear but fear itself.
This is a wonderful night,
Mr. President.
Your family is lovely. This
place, the animals- so inspiring.
Well, I hope we managed to convey
to you how sorry we were-
Back home we say, "However
long the night, the day will break."
Ah.
- That is in the past. We must work to the future.
Rsst Maya Maya!
Under the table
Hey, you left your house. Congratulations.
What are you doin' here?
We got a big problem.
This is terrible.
Are you sure about this?
You think that I would've left
my house if I wasn't sure?
Okay. Well, round up all the
animals. I think I have a plan.
Oh, by the way,
can you whistle?
Nope.
Groundhogs talk to
each other by whistling.
You're not a groundhog.
You're a prairie dog.
Prairie do- Oh, no. Now
I'm having an identity crisis.
So, tell me again your
thoughts on my rain forest.
How might we come together on this issue?
- Oh, I'm so glad you asked me.
Everybody understand the plan?
- Are you sure about this, Maya?
If this goes wrong, you
could get in serious trouble.
That's just a chance
I'm gonna have to take.
Okay You guys get
the evidence from the safe
I'll make sure
the president doesn't eat.
Good luck.
Hey, shouldn't we
synchronize our watches?
Hey, where have you been?
- Oh, um, l-I'll tell you later.
?Ay, Dios mo!
Ha-ha!
Got it!
Let's go! Shh!
Nothing here?
Nope.
Nothin' in here.
Nothing here.
- Zilch-a-roonie here.
Hey, guys. I found it!
- Ha-ha!
Incoming!
Someone's on me tail!
Watch it, buster I am
not that kind of chinchilla
Shh Everyone be quiet
Monkey, where's your tail?
- Uh-oh!
Ooh, la, la
Back to work, everyone!
- Go, Monkey, go!
Now, where was I?
Ladies and gentlemen-
First of all,
I wish to say...
I appreciate all that you
have done, Mr. President...
for the global environment and for
making this such a wonderful night.
Thank you.
And I want to
announce at this time
I will sign the agreement.
Your Highness,
thank you.
And I would like
to propose a toast
To His Highness,
Prince Tharoor...
and to a long and fruitful collaboration
between our two countries.
And to President Sterling...
for going so far to arrange
this wonderful night.
You are a most generous host.
- I thank you.
To the president.
- Cheers
And now, dinner is served.
A little more to the left.
A little more.
Roquito mas
Keep going.
Keep going- Stop!
You're loving me for the ears
right now, aren't you?
Stop!
Uh, hi, Your Highness.
I'm sorry. Your Highness,
this is Maya Dolittle.
Ah! Yes, yes, yes.
Your father's reputation
is truly worid renowned. Mmm.
Thank you.
Oh, l-I'd-
Was there something
you wanted to say, Maya?
No. I mean, yes.
Um, I would like
to just tell a joke
It's an American tradition:
Joke before dinner.
Maya-
- So
Why do cows wear bells?
Because their
horns don't work!
You get it? 'Cause the
horns go, "beep, beep"-
Uh-huh.
Stop! Okay,
back to the right
The other right!
Okay. So there
were two fish in a tank.
And one fish says
to the other fish...
"Do you know how
to drive this thing?"
'Cause they're in a tank.
You get it? 'Cause-
Yeah. I really-
I love that one.
Maya?
- Hmm?
Thank you.
- But l-
Maya, thank you.
Yes, sir.
Well, folks,
let's eat.
Mmm.
You okay?
- I guess so.
Excuse me for one moment, Mr. President.
- Mmm.
I must confer with my adviser
about our agreement.
Of course.
To the left, and... stop! That's it.
Go, Rarrot, go!
Gotcha.
- Ha-ha!
Missin accomplished.
Got it.
- Go, dog, go! Vaya con Dios.
I feel weird.
Wait a second. It wasn't the
president's food. It was Daisy's!
Get this dog off of me! Now!
- Your Highness!
You have insulted Prince Tharoor
for the last time. The deal is off!
Your Highness, please-
- I said, the deal is off!
We are leaving.
Your Highness-
Wait! Stop!
Chief Dorion is responsible
for everything.
He spiked Daisy's food tonight
and he was the one who gave the
president bad oysters in Kalampore.
What? That's-
That's ridiculous.
This is just a sad and pathetic attempt to
cover up your own incompetence, Miss Dolittle
Secret Service, get her out of here.
- Harold, let's hear her out.
Sir, really, l-
- Harold.
He doesn't want you and the prince
to sign the agreement.
He's been trying to sabotage
the entire thing.
That's preposterous.
- It's the truth!
The groundhog overheard you on your cell phone tonight.
- The groundhog?
Well, he's a prairie dog
who thinks he's a groundhog.
So, your alleged proof
of this outrageous story...
is the word of a prairie dog
who thinks he's a groundhog?
Secret Service, please
Maya.
I'm sorry I disappointed you,
Mr. President.
Woof! Woof! Beg your
pardon Dog savin'the day
Comin' through. Make way.
Great dress, lady.
Comin'through here
- Come on.
Sorry about the saliva.
Hmm. Actually, it's the word
of a prairie dog...
and... these.
These documents show that
Chief Dorion is a silent partner...
in Boyd and Dunsmore
Investment Group.
And he stands to make millions
if the rain forest is developed
Where did you get
those documents?
Harold, I would get
a very expensive lawyer.
I never did
like that man.
The only thing I hate more
than animals is teenagers!
Miss Dolittle,
I cannot thank you enough
You have brought the people of
Kalampore and United States together
You are truly a hero.
- Thank you.
I wanted to change the worid
before I was 30.
She's changed it
before she's even 20.
You were so brave.
I barely got out with my life,
but it was worth it.
Who has got a pen?
We have an agreement to sign.
Way to go, Maya!
Maya, you did it!
We gotta kick this party up a notch.
- Leave it to the Monkey.
It's funky monkey time.
Everybody get down!
# You know you make me wanna Kick my heels up and #
- #Shout, shout #
# Throw my hands up and Throw my head back and #
#Come on now Don't
forget to say you will #
#Don't forget to say #
Shout
- # Yeah, yeah Yeah, yeah, yeah #
Ow!
- Oh, yes. I'm bad!
#Say you will #
- #Come on, come on #
Shout!
- #Say you will #
#Say it right now, you will Come on now #
Shout!
- #Say that you love me #
#Say that you need me #
#Say that you want me #
- Do zee monkey! Shake it!
#Come on now Come on now #
- #Say, say #
#AI-I-I right #
- Shout!
#AI-I-I right Come on now,
come on now # - #Shout, shout #
#Shout, shout, shout #
- # Yeah, yeah Hey, yeah, yeah #
Go wilder!
#Shout, shout #
- #AI-I-I right AI-I-I right #
Hey-ey-ey-ey
- Hey-ey-ey-ey
#Hey-ey-ey-ey #
- #Hey-ey-ey-ey #
Let your fur down!
- Hey-ey-ey-ey
#Hey-ey-ey-ey #
#Jump up and shout now
Jump up and shout now #
#Everybody, shout now
Everybody, shout now ##
Get the door
- Okay
Well, I'll be.
Huh.
"The president
of the United States"-
It may look like
just another perfect day
in sunny San
Francisco, but it's not
It's more than that
After receiving a glowing recommendation
- Let's see.
From the president
of the United States-
Mom! Mom, I got in!
Maya Dolittle was accepted
at San Francisco University
And a rain forest was saved
I mean, how cool is that?
I mean, how cool is-
Hey, wait a second She got in?
She's goin'away to college?
What's gonna happen to me?
Maya! Uh, Maya? Wait! We-We-
We have to talk about this
#If you're sad
and feelin'low #
#I've got the perfect
place to go #
#A bar on Madison Avenue #
# That's got more
animals than the zoo #
#It's the place
that really is down #
# The best party
in Memphis town #
# The Monkey
is the place to be #
#Monkey tail
for you and me #
#Down at The Monkey #
- #Down at The Monkey #
# The Blue Monkey #
- # The Blue Monkey #
#Let's get funky
down at The Monkey tonight #
Get down!
#Down at The Monkey
feelin'fine #
#Drinkin'myself
some monkey wine #
#I saw Butch
and Harry there #
#And a girl not wearin'
no underwear #
#My baby
She loves me #
#She showed me somethin'
at The Blue Monkey #
# When I saw it
It looked real weird #
#I never seen a monkey
with that kind ofbeard #
#Down at The Monkey #
- #Down at The Monkey #
# The Blue Monkey #
- # The Blue Monkey #
#Oh, let's get funky
down at The Monkey tonight #
#Oh, Jack and Jill
came down the hill #
# The went to The Monkey
with Betty and Bill #
#Jill was a-lookin'
at some guy #
#SoJack ate a piece
of Betty's pie #
#Muskrat Susie
Muskrat Sam #
#Came to bring
this crazy jam #
# The joint was jumpin'
They started to dance #
#But Sam was wearin'
Susie's pants #
#Down at The Monkey #
- #Down at The Monkey #
# The Blue Monkey #
- # The Blue Monkey #
#Let's get funky
down at The Monkey tonight #
Oh, look out #Down at The Monkey #
- #Down at The Monkey #
#Down at The Monkey #
# Tonight #
#Oh, down at The Monkey #
- #Down at The Monkey #
#Down at The Monkey #
# The Blue Monkey #
- # The Blue Monkey #
#Down at The Monkey #
- #Down at The Monkey #
#Down at The Monkey
Really get funky tonight #
#Hey, hey, hey #
#Down at The Monkey #
- #Down at The Monkey #
#Oh, down at The Monkey #
# The Blue Monkey #
- # The Blue Monkey #
#Let's get funky
down at The Monkey tonight ##
#I got ants in my pants #
#I got butterflies #
#I'm crying
crocodile tears #
#From my puppy dog eyes #
#I've been monkeying around
I'm a dog for you #
#I'm animal crackers
I'm the human zoo #
#I can sing like a bird
I'm a cowboy song #
#I'm a little hoarse
'cause I sung too long #
#Had a whale of a time
I'm a busy bee #
#I'm the black sheep
of the family #
#Living high on the hog #
#Just lyin'around #
#Happy as a clown #
#In this one-horse town #
#Got my head in the sand
but I never forget #
#A can of worms
I'm the teacher's pet ##