Every family is a story.
Every family is a ghost story.
Lottery ticket?
Not this time.
Careful out there.
You have a good night.
- Hello?
- Why?
Chick?
- Chick, listen...
I wasn't even invited?
It was their idea.
- They thought it was...
- That what?
Safe, or I was going
to do something?
I don't know.
I'm a monster now,
is that it?
I'm sorry.
- It's complicated.
- I wasn't invited
to my own daughter's wedding.
- Look, Chick, she's not a kid anymore,
- Never mind.
and if she was worried...
- Cathy.
- What?
Sorry, Cathy.
Where are you going?
Home.
Damn!
Come on, Charley!
Run! Run! Run! Run!
Mom?
All right, come on, let's go.
Dive, dive!
- Oh, man!
- Good work!
- Which one's yours?
- None.
We don't...
I was just closing
on a house nearby.
Okay, you're a baseball fan?
Sort of.
I write about sports
for a newspaper.
That guy over there,
he's a story.
Oh, yeah?
Chick Benetto.
Made the World Series in '73.
Supposed to be dead by now,
from what I hear.
Anyhow, he's a story.
Maybe I'm not looking
for a story.
All right, guys!
Go to first!
Come on, dive, dive!
You want to know why
I tried to kill myself, right?
Where I've been, all that?
But mostly, why I tried to kill myself.
It's okay, everybody does.
It's like they measure
themselves against me.
They figure
that I crossed some kind of line,
and they want to know
if they could ever get
as close as I did.
You gonna sit?
People are wrong.
There's no line.
There's only your life,
how you mess it up,
and who's there to save you.
Or who isn't.
I'm sorry you didn't
get a chance to say
good-bye, Daddy.
Your mother lived a good life.
Stop blaming yourself.
I was in the car.
- I was on my way...
- It was her heart.
You couldn't have known.
She lived 70 years,
I was gone for one day.
One day.
What kind of...
How could this happen?
That's not going
to bring her back.
The only thing that would eliminate
the pitching change
is if Henry can get Valet
to do an inning-ending double-play.
One ball, one strike.
And she has sealed
Barry's booth.
He cannot see or hear
what is going on...
Try the double dare.
Okay, if it works for you,
he misses again.
You receive an additional $200.
You will then have
a commanding...
I'm no good at it, Catherine.
It's Maria, Dad.
Maria.
I'm sorry, sweetie.
It's okay.
Look at me.
I want you to promise me
something, okay?
Okay.
When you get older,
you do what you love.
You understand?
You do what you love.
Maria, go to your room.
- Mom, I was...
- Promise me.
Now.
Don't say it.
- Chick...
- It's a slump, Mike.
It's a pretty damn long one.
- Mike...
- I've been looking out for you, but...
I just got to get
my swing back.
You can swing better
when you can see straight.
It's 9:30.
What time did you have
your first drink?
Damn it, Chick,
you got a wife and kid.
I know it's been hard
since your mom died...
- Listen, Mike,
- No, you listen to me.
I'm done,
I'm out of excuses.
It's a year now.
You got two sits left this week.
You got to convert one of them.
That's it, buddy.
Bottom of the ninth.
Now, who do you have later?
I don't know, Peterson.
Peterson, good.
Warm him up.
Come on, talk to him
about baseball.
All these guys wanted
to be an athlete,
just like you were.
Okay.
For God's sake, Chick,
stay a few drinks behind him.
I get up to bat.
As a catcher,
I figure I can steal a sign
from the second baseman.
I see him,
he signals fastball.
Now, I'm all set.
I'm gonna smack that pitch,
except the signs are reversed.
Perry throws a curve.
Wicked cheese.
I miss so badly, I fall over,
I mean, down.
Gaylord Perry.
He was something.
Lived on a spitball.
Now, back to the new binder line.
I'm not sure
we want to switch...
You couldn't hit
that damn pitch.
- You know, stay where we are.
- Dropped like that.
It must've been something.
Yeah.
I'm open!
Pass it, pass it!
Hey.
You ever hear
of sharing the ball?
- Benetto, come on.
- No, no.
You're supposed
to teach them, right?
This is a school?
In school,
you're supposed to teach.
Passing is not that hard.
You give up the ball,
then somebody else
on your team
gets to shoot it.
I played ball.
I know what I'm talking about.
- Daddy, please!
- No!
No. I'll show you. See?
You dribble, you dribble,
then you give it up.
Come on, Maria, honey,
you got to catch the easy ones.
This is not gonna be pleasant, folks,
I can tell you this right now.
Tie-breaking run,
standing down at third base,
and the person at one,
Cecil Espy.
Only one batter is going to retire...
Better catch it!
I smoked for 12 years,
and within just one day
of using Smoke Away,
I was done.
I haven't had a cigarette
in two years.
Do you want to walk
with your $2,000 in cash?
Or do you want to play
for $60,000 more?
He is dealing to Deivi Cruz
for strike one.
Lyon coming in from Triple A...
Hello?
I wasn't invited
to my own daughter's wedding?
Look, Chick, she's
not a kid anymore.
Damn!
Mom?
Mom.
That's enough.
Finish your homework.
Charley?
Charley, is that you?
Come on, come on,
stop it, stop it.
What are you doing here?
You're making a mess!
Well, you look like hell.
What's going on?
You're all cut up.
What's the matter?
I don't expect you
to believe me.
People don't see ghosts, I know.
What did she look like?
Like the last time
I saw her alive.
She was right there
in front of me.
I wasn't drunk.
But she'd been dead for...
Nine years.
I don't know how
to explain it.
Try.
It's like jumping
off the planet.
There's what you think,
and then there's
what happens.
I saw my mother alive,
right in front of my eyes.
I knew it was impossible.
But I didn't want it to end.
Does it sting?
I must have more of these
in the house somewhere.
Mom.
No, just hold still
a minute, will you?
Mom, what is this?
It's poison.
I'm poisoning you.
It's antiseptic.
Now, just hold still for a second.
Oh, Charley.
The trouble you get yourself into.
Oh, that's too hard for you.
Let's see if we can find you
something better than that.
Oh, hey, kiddo.
Give your mother a kiss.
Curious George?
You've read that
ten times already.
- Yeah?
- Yes, you mean.
I wanted a different book
but the lady wouldn't
let me have it.
Why not?
I am Mrs. Benetto,
and this is my son Charley.
Did you tell him that a book
was too hard for him to read?
Don't you shush me.
Did you tell my son
that a book was too hard?
He wanted
20,000 Leagues Under the Sea.
He's not ready.
He's not...
How would you know that?
Well, I've been helping children...
Never tell a child
that something is
too hard for them,
and never this child.
Where's the book?
Now, just a mo...
Okay, now you get a broom
and clean up that mess
on the floor.
I'll make you some breakfast.
You have something to drink?
You need to eat.
I don't feel like eating.
Get the broom, please.
Oh, look at you.
You're just a disaster.
It's out back.
Go, go, go, go, go.
Hi, Dad.
One.
Dad, what makes an echo?
My teacher says I have
to recite on Monday
what makes an echo.
You do your calisthenics today?
Because you're never gonna
make it into the big leagues
unless you do your calisthenics.
Yes, sir.
Doesn't it happen
in the mountains?
An echo?
I guess.
Weren't you in the mountains,
in the war?
When you were in Italy?
Put the pencil back.
I'll just ask Mom.
Hey, you want
to talk about school
or you want to play ball?
Go around back,
I'll throw you some.
First, calisthenics.
Excuse me?
- Yes, sir.
- Thank you.
All the way down.
Chick, go out back
and do them.
- But I can do them right...
- Chick!
Okay, let's go,
ready position,
eye on the ball.
Step forward on the throw.
Good.
A little bit more.
I can catch it.
See, I'm not afraid of the ball.
Don't be afraid of the ball.
Chick, you're doing it again.
I said don't be afraid.
It's not gonna hurt you.
Aw, come on.
Run, run, run, run, run.
He's stealing second,
let's go!
There you go,
nice job.
You got to be tough.
You can't back away
from the ball.
All right,
let me hit some to you.
Ready? Okay.
I took care of it.
Sit for breakfast.
I made them the way
you like them,
with greenies.
What?
You don't remember?
Chives, you used to
call them "greenies."
What time is it?
Why? You go someplace
more important to be?
Well, it doesn't
matter then, does it?
Oh, your toast.
Here.
You can spend a day
with your mother.
How about that?
With you?
You got another mother?
You know, the doctor says
you shouldn't eat salt.
High blood pressure,
they say it takes
five years off your life.
I say, what five years?
From 85 to 90?
Keep 'em.
I'd rather have salt.
Mom?
Here, have some.
- Mom!
- What?
This is impossible!
Eat.
This lasagna still ain't right.
I've tried ten different ways, Len.
I don't know what you want.
We play the Red Sox Saturday.
Yeah, what are you gonna do?
- Three hits and no strikeouts.
- That's right.
Strikeouts are for losers.
No sympathy for losers.
- You got that?
- Got it.
That's what you're
teaching him?
No, this still ain't right.
You make it next time.
You know what?
When I was a kid,
there was no Little League.
I had to work on Saturdays.
I'll tell you what, though.
If I had half the chance
that you have,
I wouldn't strike out.
I'd get some wood on that ball.
Strikeouts,
they're a waste of time
is what they are.
Mommy?
How did Daddy and you
get "gaged?"
"Engaged," you mean?
Chick, give me the bread.
I told you, sweetheart.
Daddy sent me a nice letter
from Italy.
During the war.
You know, there's more to life
than baseball, Len.
He's fine.
Aren't you, Chick?
His name is Charley.
I like Chick.
You just have him ready by noon.
I'll be coming from the new store.
One more headache
we don't need.
Hey, two stores,
twice the income.
I get it going, you won't have to work
at that hospital anymore.
Well, if anyone's interested,
I enjoy working at that hospital.
I'm a good nurse.
What's wrong?
It's not right.
You see?
Even the kid knows.
Thank you.
For what?
For breakfast.
Well, you're welcome
for breakfast.
We should go.
I just want to put on
some lipstick.
Not until you're older.
Mom, can me and Roberta
watch The Rifleman?
Roberta and I.
And no,
we're having a party.
Read.
"An echo.
"The persistence of sound
after the source has stopped."
And when can
you hear an echo?
"When it is quiet,
and all other sounds
have been absorbed."
Why do I have to do this?
Because if you're good in school,
you get to go to college.
Give your mother a hand.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Charley, don't mumble.
It makes you sound
uneducated.
Posey, let's go!
People are coming.
She's got lipstick
all over her face.
I'll get it!
Don't run!
We'll finish this later.
You want to be a mama's boy?
Let me tell you something, Chick.
You could be a mama's boy,
or you could be a daddy's boy.
But you can't be both.
You got that?
Wipe the lipstick
off your face.
Thank you.
Where are we going?
We're gonna pay a visit.
But first, I want
to show you something.
Ma, what are you doing here?
I live here.
Not anymore.
Then why did you come back?
I don't know.
The house...
Tell us what happened.
Charles, what happened?
You want to talk about this?
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
You can't be here.
Why not?
Because you died.
Oh, Charley.
You make too much of things.
Come on.
What happened to you?
Are you in any pain?
I haven't been so good, Mom.
What I want to show you
is over there.
First three years
I was married to your father,
I couldn't get pregnant.
People thought there was
something wrong with me.
Well, so did I.
I hope it's still there.
That's... There it is, look.
"Please"?
What is it?
It's a prayer.
I carved it one night.
For a child.
For you.
So, Charley,
whatever is going on,
just know that
from the very start,
you were an answer
to my prayer.
So, now you know
how much you were
wanted.
I think children
forget that sometimes,
you know?
They start thinking
of themselves as a burden,
instead of...
a wish granted.
- Come on, Chick!
- Let's go, Chicky.
Now's your time, son.
Now's your time.
You wait for your pitch.
You wait for your pitch, son.
- You wait for your pitch.
- Yea, Charley!
Let's go!
Keep your elbow up.
Keep your hands together.
Keep your eye on the ball.
- Strike!
- Good cut, good cut.
Come on, Charley!
There's nothing up there
that can help you, Chicky.
that can help you.
Keep your eye on the ball!
Let's go, son!
Let's go!
Dig, dig, dig!
Run, run, run!
Dig, dig, that a boy!
That's the way we want it.
Come on.
Get back to that base.
Let's go, let's go.
That's what I'm talking about.
See what happens
when you listen to me?
Next time, don't look
at the ball when you hit it,
you just run,
you run it out.
Nobody on. One out.
Wynn cuts loose,
a change, it's high.
One and one.
Dad, what's your favorite drink?
Something you're
too young to have.
Mine's champagne.
Champagne, huh?
That's what they
pour on your head
when you win
the World Series.
Here, clean your face.
You know, the only way
you get to the World Series
is by practicing.
You understand?
You don't practice,
you're gonna be ordinary.
You want to be ordinary?
Good, because you're not.
And when I win
the World Series,
I'm gonna pour champagne
on your head.
I got to get to the new store.
- Maybe we...
- I said I got to go.
Hey.
You be ready
in the morning, okay?
Get the mud off your cleats
- and you look sharp.
- Okay.
And don't tell your mother
about the ice cream.
It's our secret, okay?
Our secret.
Every pitch, every swing,
I thought about my father.
Oh, hey, Miss Thelma.
Morning, Chickadoo.
Where's my dad?
Your mother's in the kitchen.
Turn it off, Charley.
I'll have cereal.
What time is your game?
Mom, do you have a cold?
No, honey.
What time is your game?
I don't know.
Dad knows.
I'll take you,
whatever time it is.
Why can't Dad take me?
Your father's not here.
Well, when's Dad coming home?
Mom?
When's Dad coming home?
Rose got too frail
to go to the beauty shop, so...
You know, old people
like to look nice too.
So she's alive.
Of course she's alive.
So are you.
Hello, Rose.
You remember my son Charley?
You came!
Well, sure I did.
You called me, remember?
Continued sunny and mild,
with highs around 70 degrees.
How are your children, Rose?
Oh, they call me once a week,
like a chore.
You get old and sick,
they get afraid,
like they're gonna
catch something.
You were never afraid, dear.
Thank you.
And you're the best
hairdresser in town.
Oh, you're sweet.
She was a nurse first.
Well, that was a long time ago.
Does your mother cut your hair too?
Oh, no.
Charley would never
let me touch it.
He always insisted
on going to a barber shop.
Children get embarrassed
by their parents.
Well, any child
who's embarrassed by his mother
is a child that hasn't
lived long enough.
Give me.
No!
Mommy!
Did the hospital
let you out early?
Give your mother a kiss.
What are you doing here?
Well, I was thinking,
ice cream.
Yeah, yeah!
I have baseball practice.
- Well, you can miss one practice.
- No!
I can't miss a practice!
Okay, honey.
Okay.
Did you do something wrong
at work?
I hate ice cream!
Chick!
It's okay, honey.
Some doctor couldn't
keep his hands to himself,
my mother had the guts
to speak up,
and they let her go.
But...
why didn't she file a complaint?
It was a different time.
She tried to keep us the same,
but back then,
a small town doesn't
let you be the same
if there was a divorce.
Would you turn that off, young man?
Sometimes I have it on too loud.
I only listen for the news.
Oh, did you hear about
that terrible accident?
A car veered
into the wrong lane,
almost hit a truck,
and crashed into the ravine.
Terrible!
Yeah, the news can be
depressing sometimes, Rose.
Oh, yes, so much so.
What's the matter?
It's nice you spend
the day with your mother.
Children should do that more often.
Yeah, Charley's a good boy.
Are you all right?
Why don't you answer the phone?
Hello?
Mr. Benetto,
Charles Benetto.
I need you to talk to me.
Come on, Charles,
I know you can hear me.
Who was on the phone?
No one.
Oh, no.
Charley, Charley.
Where's that ever gotten you?
Now's a time you have to remember.
Look at me.
Do you trust me?
Do you?
Good!
So long, Rose.
I'll see you soon, dear, won't I?
Yes, you will.
Good luck, Charley.
You look nice.
It's a special day.
What's the occasion?
I'm going to see my husband.
Bye.
She's dying, you know.
Rose?
She'll die tonight.
I don't get it.
She said she was going
to visit her husband.
She is.
Mom, how do you know this?
She called me.
I've been helping her
get ready.
Enough baseball, Charley.
Come inside
and do your homework.
Is he ever coming home?
Is he?
No.
What did you do?
What?
You made him leave.
Charley.
You did something to him.
What did you do?
Don't talk to me like that.
Tell me!
You're too young.
It's too hard for you
to understand.
Never tell a child
something is too hard!
- Get in the house.
- No.
Charley, I said get in the house!
Charley, you get back here.
Charley!
There you go.
You cut the crusts off.
That's the way
you always liked it.
I'm not a kid anymore.
Of course you're not.
You haven't mentioned
Catherine or Maria.
How are they?
She's fine.
They're fine.
No, they're...
Catherine and I aren't
together anymore.
And Maria doesn't...
She...
She doesn't speak to me.
She's ashamed of me.
Are you listening?
Sometimes,
children want you to hurt
the way they do.
Maria is not a child, Ma.
Do you know
how old she is now?
Do you?
Come on, Ma.
Things can be fixed,
you know.
How come they didn't
invite you to their party?
We're having
our own party right here.
Santa's coming.
And he may come by 10:00,
which means you, young lady,
had better be sound asleep by then.
10:00?
Is that Santa?
Ho, ho, ho!
Who's there?
No, you'll scare him away!
It's just Mom, stupid.
Stop it, it's Santa!
Santa's not a girl, stupid.
It's Mom.
It's always Mom.
- Stop it!
- It's always gonna be Mom.
Answer the door.
Answer the door, Charley.
Just leave it.
Maybe they'll go away.
No, they won't.
Charles Benetto.
Chickadoo?
Well, look who's all grown up.
I'm the only one
wearing a stupid tie.
It's your first day of college.
You're not going fishing.
Did we remember
your toiletry kit?
Did you pack it?
Yeah, I packed it.
Okay, third floor.
I can take those.
Oh, please.
I want to see your room.
Oh, come on, Ma.
I can make up your bed.
Okay.
You can probably
make up your own bed.
Okay, well, this is it.
Give your mother a kiss.
Study.
Bye, Mom.
Stopped up across the floor!
I wanted to kill him!
I've been thinking of you, Posey.
- Have you?
- I surely have.
Didn't expect to see you here,
Chickadoo.
What's the occasion?
I'm visiting my mom.
Will wonders never cease?
Grandma!
What just happened?
I hate that my family
sees me so sick and ugly.
Grandma, come play with us.
Could you, Posey?
Of course I can.
It may take a miracle.
I've got moisturizer.
Do you believe in miracles,
Chickadoo?
Two outs, guys.
Two outs.
Bring us home, Chicky!
Chick, let's go.
Win, win, win!
We got 'em!
Wait for it, Chick.
Wait for it.
Make it count.
Strike!
Chick, you can do it!
It's all right, man!
Hang in there, Chick.
Stay there.
- Stay in there, Chicky!
- Show 'em, Chick!
All right, Chick.
Here's your pitch, Chick!
Come on, man.
- We need a hit!
- Yeah, Chick!
- Here we go, come on!
- Chicky!
Let's go, Chick.
Here you go, Chick!
Way to go, Chick!
Great hit!
Good job, Chicky!
Way to go, kid.
All that time,
she never told you why he left?
After a while,
you just stop asking.
Why do you think
people keep secrets
from their family, I mean?
Can there ever be
a good enough reason?
I don't know.
You tell me.
Way to hit it
out of the park, Chick!
Nice hit, Chick!
Good game.
Thanks.
Nice follow-through,
staying behind the ball.
It makes the ball carry.
What?
You want to hit me?
No.
Tell your coach
I'll drive you back to campus.
I didn't hate baseball.
Of course you did.
I did not.
You didn't even come to the Series.
Well...
You got two tickets.
You knew your father
wasn't going to miss it.
What, you were expecting
a family reunion?
Do you two want to be alone?
Now, just hold still, Thelma.
But I loved it, Ma.
Forget about Dad
for a minute,
I loved the game.
- I was good at it.
- I know you were.
So why couldn't you support me?
I did support you!
At school.
At studying, yes,
but not at baseball,
not at what I wanted.
Why?
Just tell me why.
Because I knew it would
break your heart.
Swing!
- Nice hit, Chick!
- Let's go!
Hit it hard, now!
Can't get that one out.
Get another one!
- Way to go.
- Nice, Chick.
You're next in there.
Hey.
Say hello to Wally Peters.
You got a hell of a swing.
Outstanding contact,
opposite field power.
Your old man taught you good.
Thanks.
Keep it up, kid.
- Take care, Len.
- Yeah.
- I'll send you some gear.
- Sounds good.
Hey, Jimmy!
You want some gear?
From the New York Mets?
You're kidding.
He's a scout?
You have time for a beer?
See, hard work pays off.
Didn't I tell you that?
This is your time, son.
This is your time.
You just stay
in those cages.
You put in the hours,
and I will do the rest.
What about school?
You're too good
for college ball.
No, Dad.
I mean, school.
You can always go back
after your career.
No.
Excuse me?
I can't.
Mom will kill me.
You listen to me, Chick.
She has a hard head,
- but she will get over it.
- Dad, please...
No, no, no.
You tell me
if you don't want to play
Major League Baseball.
You do that,
and I don't say another word.
Remember,
this is your dream.
Your mother has
to understand that.
This is your dream.
Hello, Ida's Beauty Shop.
Collect call for Mrs. Benetto.
It is your son,
do you accept?
- Yes, I accept. Charley?
- Mom.
- Mom, don't get mad.
- Where are you?
I'm with a baseball team.
The Mets farm system.
It happened really fast,
but they're paying me, Mom,
to play ball.
Why aren't you at school?
I'm not in school anymore.
Mom, Dad's been coming
to my games.
I didn't know how to tell you.
- But he talked to the scouts.
- Hey, 4:00.
He got me a contract.
I'm playing professional ball, Ma.
I can send money to you now.
I don't want your money.
I want you in school.
But I wasn't getting any better
playing in college.
You were getting smarter.
I can always
go back to school.
Going back to something
is harder than you think.
I want to play baseball.
Mom?
I couldn't have hurt her
more if I tried.
But you were good at it.
I mean, you made the majors,
a World Series!
I got called up in September
to replace a guy who got hurt.
The team was great
before I got there.
I just went along for the ride.
But still.
I know.
World Series.
It never leaves your head.
I felt more alive
those couple of weeks
than I have the rest of my life.
Here come the greatest
players in history,
the New York Mets!
Ladies and gentlemen,
your 1973
National League Champions,
New York Mets!
We lost the Series,
and I never even got to bat.
It didn't matter.
I thought there'd be
a World Series every year
until the next spring.
March eighth, fifth inning.
I never saw the majors again.
Two surgeries,
three months on crutches,
an exhibition game.
Didn't even count.
Still, your dream came true.
Then that just means
you have to change dreams.
I stayed in the minors for years
trying to get back to a place
I'd already been.
And your father?
When I finally quit,
he pretty much vanished.
Bought a liquor distributorship
near Pittsburgh.
He didn't even offer you a job?
No sympathy for losers.
I miss those Saturdays
working with you.
We sure had fun.
Oh, we certainly did that.
You worked
at the beauty parlor?
Me?
No, we cleaned houses together.
How do you think I got
you kids through college?
You were a cleaning lady?
You mean,
you mopped people's floors?
Yes, Charley.
He was always a little proud.
- I remember.
- I was not.
It's just, I know what it's like
to take a job
that's beneath you.
It wasn't beneath me.
It was.
Just like my job.
What's wrong with what you do?
It's sales.
What?
It's work?
What, Charley?
It's ordinary.
Define ordinary.
You know.
Someone you forget.
Grandma!
You hear that?
That's what keeps me
from being forgot.
You do whatever
you have to do
to hold your family together.
And there is nothing
ordinary about it.
But you didn't do
what you wanted to.
Oh, I did what I wanted to.
I was a mother.
A miracle.
We're waiting for you!
I'm going to go visit
with them a spell.
I'll see you soon.
Would you please tell me
what's happening?
She was thinking of me.
When you hold someone
in your thoughts,
they're always around.
Wait.
She said she'd see you.
She's dying?
Soon.
Like Rose.
And I'm dying too.
Am I dying, Ma?
I didn't do what you did.
I didn't keep my family together.
I let it go.
I just... I just...
Charles Benetto?
Are you Charles Benetto?
Charles, are you with us?
What do I do?
It's up to you, Charley.
Mr. Benetto, are you with us?
Mr. Benetto.
- Mr. Benetto.
- Talk to me.
- Come on, can you hear me?
- Charles Benetto.
I always said I'd stop celebrating
my birthdays after age 70.
You said you were here.
You said, "This is real."
- It is.
- No, it isn't.
You're gone.
Well, once somebody's
in your heart,
they're never truly gone.
And they can come back to you
in the most unlikely times.
I let you die.
Well, you had nothing
to do with it.
But I should have been there.
Maybe I could have...
You could have what?
Saved me? Charley.
You know, you drink,
you hide,
you point your finger
at everyone else.
The one thing that
you had absolutely
no control over whatsoever,
that, you want
to blame yourself for.
No.
Why don't you ask yourself,
what's behind all of this?
I don't know.
I'm starting to count
my birthdays backwards now.
I'm getting younger every year.
Let's see.
"Birthdays come
but once a year,
a chance to share
with friends so dear."
What, is she going
to read every card?
Oh, shut up, Chick,
it's sweet.
Uh, let's see.
"Friends tomorrow,
"friends today.
Friends for every
new birthday."
Actually, I think this is
the same card
I gave you for your birthday.
No, no, no,
I'm kidding!
Thank you,
it's beautiful.
Let's see.
Hello?
Chick, that you?
Dad?
I tried your office,
I tried your house.
I couldn't figure
where the hell you were.
I'm at Mom's birthday party.
Listen. The Mets have
their old-timers game, right?
I was talking to Harrelson.
He told me Fitzgerald
crapped out.
- He ain't coming.
- So?
So, it's too late
to get a replacement.
I told him
you were around.
I'm not around.
You can be.
You leave now,
you can be here by late tonight.
They want me to play
in the old-timers game?
That's what I'm saying.
But I only played a month.
That don't mean nothing.
You were on
the World Series team.
They'll take you.
Now, look, you got just
enough time to get going.
I don't know.
Don't know what?
It's not about the game, Chick.
It's about the connections
you can make.
You get in there,
you throw the bull.
See if there's
a coaching spot opening up.
Maybe something
in the minors.
You tell them
you'll move anywhere,
you'll start anywhere.
Get back in the game.
Dad, I have a job.
Oh, yeah?
What are you selling now?
When is it?
Noon, tomorrow.
It's Mom's birthday.
Well, tomorrow it ain't.
What kind of client
makes you meet on Sunday?
I know, I know.
It's ridiculous.
I thought we were going
to spend the day together.
It's my job, Ma.
What do you want me to do?
Well, you could call him back
and tell him it's
your mother's birthday.
I can't call him back, okay?
Chick.
Look, I'll be back.
We'll go out someplace nice.
What do you say?
You do what you have to do, Charley.
Thanks, Mom.
And take some cake.
I'll call you, okay?
See you tomorrow.
Be careful, Charley.
Run those wheels!
Nobody out.
Next batter,
from the World Series team of 1973,
Charles "Chick" Benetto.
Come on, boy.
Let's get a hit, baby!
Give it all you got, yeah!
Come on, Chick!
Brought in from Tidewater
in late September,
this promising young catcher
would add invaluable
bench support
at a time the team
needed it most.
- One for me, Chick!
- Let's see one of those meatballs!
Let's see what you got.
Come on! Come on!
Nice try.
Easy, guy.
It's not worth dying over.
Next time.
Remember, fans.
Mets-Cubs coming up.
2:30 start time.
Ramone Santiago versus...
Hey.
You got under that pitch.
Yeah.
Don't matter.
You're rusty.
What did you expect?
How come you're
out here so fast?
Game's over, Dad.
Did you talk to Harrelson?
Did you at least
leave your number?
How they gonna call you
if you don't leave your numbers?
Get back in there.
Dad.
Come on,
before they all leave.
Dad, I haven't seen you in years.
So what?
Damn it, Chick.
How you gonna
get back in the game
talking to me?
I got to go.
What are you talking about?
I'll see you around.
Where are you going?
I wanted that day back
so many times.
The last thing
I told you was a lie.
It wasn't work.
It was...
Your father.
- You knew?
- Well, of course I knew.
I spent my life
watching your face light up
every time he gave you
the tiniest bit of attention.
When I found out you died,
the first thing I thought was,
"I have to call Dad."
Can you believe that?
I never saw him again.
I lost both of my parents that day.
I let him down,
I let you down...
Is that why you want to die?
I lost everything.
I lost you,
I lost my wife,
I lost...
I lost my little girl.
Now, you listen to me.
You have one family,
for good or bad.
And you can't ever lose this.
No, don't you get it?
I'm a drunk!
I'm no good to anybody.
And I want it to stop.
I just want it to stop.
Just let me go.
No, we have
one more stop to make.
Mom...
Yeah, then you can make
your decision.
Come on.
Where are we?
Collingswood.
Where Dad built his store?
I was only here once.
You see, many nights,
your father didn't come home.
After a while,
I started to think
he was spending
an awful lot of time
in the Collingswood store.
So one night,
I followed him.
What is this?
She's pretty, isn't she?
He had a girlfriend?
A wife.
What are you talking about?
He married her
in Italy during the war.
A lot of men died
in those mountains,
and I guess he got scared.
And, well, you know him.
He always had
to have a plan.
No, no.
He wrote you that letter.
- He proposed to you.
- Yeah.
When he saw that
the war was ending,
he wanted his old plan back.
That was me.
But how...
I don't know, Charley.
At a certain point,
he brought her over here.
He got another house,
another store,
another life.
It was her lasagna
he wanted me to make.
It's not right.
That is a lie.
He never would have done that.
Aw, you're still defending him.
I'm his son!
One of his sons.
I'm sorry, Charley.
Did he play baseball?
I don't really know.
So what did you do?
I drove home.
I waited.
When he got there,
I got in his car
and I made him
roll up the windows.
And I exploded.
I just let him have it,
until he stopped lying to me.
What are you doing?
They're my family too.
They are my family too.
They're your family?
He admitted the whole thing.
You told him to leave.
And to never come back.
Why didn't you tell me?
Well, I thought
of it many times.
Then why?
I couldn't stand
to hurt you that much.
You adored him.
I don't know,
maybe I hurt you more
by not telling you.
But you let me
treat you so rotten.
You let me believe
it was all your fault.
How could I have been
so stupid all of these years?
I picked him over you!
I made the wrong choice.
Children shouldn't have to choose.
Mom!
You have a child of your own.
Make it right with her.
What's happening?
We've been together
for one more day.
Now it's time to give
your mother a kiss.
Oh, no, wait.
I love you, Charley.
I don't want to lose you again.
Nah, you can't lose me.
I'm your mother.
We persist
like an echo,
even after the source is gone.
And when do you hear an echo?
- When it's quiet.
- Yeah.
When it's quiet,
you'll be able to hear me too.
I'll always be right here.
Wait.
You were a really great mom.
I never told you that...
Mr. Benetto, are you with us?
Mr. Benetto.
Charles Benetto.
Are you with us?
Stay with us.
We're going to move
you now, Charles.
Over here!
- Stay with us.
- One minute!
Come on.
Nice and easy.
I got you.
All right.
Let's get some help!
- Back it up!
- The truck driver...
Everyone's gonna be okay.
Easy, now.
It's been a long road to here.
You closed on the house, huh?
Good.
It should stay in the family.
Chick Benetto died last summer,
six years after we sat
in those bleachers.
I want to make things right.
But they were the best six years
we had together.
My name is Maria Lang.
Before that, I was Maria Benetto.
Chick Benetto was my father.
Every family is a ghost story.
Sometimes, the ghosts come back.
Sometimes, they never left.
Mommy.
I'm coming, Charley.
Subtitles By LeapinLar