The need for meat.
It is an extreme ecstasy
derived from eating it.
May I sit?
Please.
I want to eat you.
You can.
Really?
Eat me.
We'll do about three at a time.
We can't have too many people.
We can't keep up.
Okay. Roppongi at seven o'clock.
Bye.
We're ready.
- Then can we shoot?
- Yes.
- Let's start.
- Best regards.
Is everybody ready?
Stand by for a roll.
Camera is rolling.
Five seconds to action.
Four... three... two... one...
Cue.
Wow. Pretty serious from the morning.
I always eat a proper breakfast.
What is this dish?
It can be called Escalope,
Gypsy's Daughter.
Is it French food?
Yes, it is.
- Please.
- Thank you.
Let's try it.
- Delicious!
- Isn't it?
This meat is superb!
Moist and with body.
What is this meat?
What do you think?
Well...
Is the meat of a woman.
No! Stop kidding. It's still morning.
I get it from a special connection.
- I can't give it away.
- Is that so?
Whoever becomes your wife will be happy
to be able to eat like this every day.
By the way, do you have a girlfriend?
I'm looking.
Did you all hear that?
Not just plastic surgery, he's a great cook!
Dr. Yuji Kotorida is very eligible.
Wow. Superb!
Everything looks so expensive.
Can we shoot the contents later?
Go ahead.
What else can we shoot...
My management changed.
This time, they're more established.
Really. That's great.
Congratulations.
Thank you very much.
Doctor.
This refrigerator...
Hands off!
Sorry.
I have things inside
that I want sealed from the air.
Oh. I see.
Excuse me.
Light is ready.
All right.
- Well, doctor, please step over here.
- Yes.
Since when did people start calling you
"God-Hand"?
I don't know.
One after the other, the entertainers
I operated on became stars
and the reputation spread.
Let me take care of this lint.
AKIMOTO COSMETIC SURGERY
- Come in.
- Excuse me.
- Good morning.
- Best regards.
- Hello.
You are Dr. Kotorida's colleagues?
Yes. I'm Akimoto.
I'm Yanagihara.
She is the daughter
of the owner of this clinic.
Oh, excuse me.
I'm Tomino.
I'm pleased.
Have you known Dr. Kotorida for a while?
Yes. We went to the same university.
Their fates are tied together.
Must have been popular.
What?
When Dr. Kotorida was a student.
I guess you could say that.
- Say...
- Huh?
He was a different person.
We should have shown
his past photos on TV.
I might have our class picture at my house.
Really?
- In her case...
- Yes?
- her jaw bone sticks out.
- Yes.
By carving this, she will have smooth lines.
- It becomes sharp.
- Yes.
I'd like to have that done too.
To make it smooth.
You already are.
You think so?
Doctor?
Oh. Thank you.
Superb, as always.
Your touch is completely different
from other doctors.
Doctor...
Huh?
To me, you are God.
Doctor...
Huh?
That television reporter was our patient.
Yes. That's right.
Are you seeing her?
I'm not seeing her.
Doctor... tonight, if you'd like...
Sorry, I have a previous engagement.
Am I that unattractive?
Not at all.
I really have a prior engagement.
I don't have relations with my patients.
The television people are leaving.
My husband says I'd look ten years younger
if I got rid of the wrinkles around the eyes
and a face lift.
Is that so?
That is so.
That's good to hear.
I'm happy.
Well... Can you fix this too?
Yes?
Hello?
What do you mean, "urgent business"?
I have my circumstances too.
You could think about me a little more.
I'll wait. Can't you come?
This is the worst.
Would you care to drink with me?
I don't want to drink alone.
Am I intruding?
Please excuse me.
Wait...
Just a little bit...
Most women drop their guard when they hear
I'm a cosmetic surgeon.
When I share the cosmetic secrets
of entertainers...
it is more effective.
I first relax them with small talk.
I listen well and they start telling me
their everyday problems.
This woman, who was stood up
by her boyfriend,
does not turn me down.
THE NEED FOR MEAT, IT IS THE...
THE NEED FOR MEAT, IT IS THE DESIRE
TO EAT THE MEAT OF THE ONE YOU LOVE.
THE DIARY OF A CANNIBAL
DEC. 1 (SAT.): UNTIL I CAME UPON THIS
MEAT, I CONSTANTLY DESPAIRED AND...
...and was on edge all the time.
My parents never loved me.
I was born with bad legs.
I became withdrawn.
I was so quiet and introverted
that I hated myself.
I, who was having to repeat the same class...
was hired by her father's clinic
out of sympathy.
To be frank, I was baggage.
But on that day...
my fate changed in a drastic way.
I impulsively stole the fat.
I cooked it at home.
It didn't taste good.
The material injected before
the liposuction such as...
the saline solution,
anti-coagulants,
and anesthesia
made it bitter, salty,
...like medicine. It was a peculiar taste.
But for the first time, I was fulfilled.
Now that I think about it,
after having tried eating everything,
it was the forbidden fruit
I always craved.
I could no longer think
of eating beef or pork.
It became repulsive,
like bestiality with a cow or pig.
A small amount of fat and a salad...
in addition to supplements,
breathing exercises to stave off hunger.
My senses became sharper.
It was an incredible experience.
But the more I ate,
the more I wanted to eat a real woman.
By accident...
No. More like a hyena
smelling out dead meat...
my senses, which were
acclimated to flesh,
perhaps smelled out its presence.
BLOODLETTING
It took half a day to dismember the body.
I stored the various edible parts
in the refrigerator.
Since then,
at least once a day,
I cook and eat a woman's meat.
It is the equivalent of having intercourse
with a woman once a day.
Those were days of satisfaction.
I wanted to eat more.
I was limited to the meat I had and saved it.
Don't you think Dr. Kotorida
has been looking good?
That's right. He changed.
I wonder what happened.
Maybe he got a girlfriend.
- That might be true.
- I'm sure of it.
Wow.
That meat may have
changed everything about me.
You have become charismatic
in the world of cosmetic surgery.
No, not at all.
Your reputation is impressive.
What do you do on your days off?
I get this meat from a special source.
You're the only other person that's eaten it.
I'd like to show you to our old friends.
I always believed in you.
My parents were opposed.
I always believed
you could carry on our clinic.
To eat the housewife that hung herself
took me only ninety days.
There were no more bodies.
Of course, you couldn't buy human meat.
It was then that I was invited
to a world conference in Hong Kong.
I searched for a place
that had been on my mind.
A few years ago in this city,
there was a sick incident of a man
killing his lover and eating her.
Since then, there have been rumors on the
internet of the availability of human meals.
I searched for three days and nights.
Why are you following me?
From 334 A.D.
to 349 A.D.,
the ruler of the northern regions of China,
when entertaining important guests
at a banquet,
would choose a woman amongst the many
women of the court,
decapitate her,
and have his chefs prepare a meal
with her meat.
Please eat me.
Christy was also meant for sacrifice.
I could eat her exclusively
for thirty thousand dollars.
She came from Kanson.
She was going to send her family her share
of ten thousand dollars.
MAY 17 (FRI): I PICKED UP A CO-ED
AND DISMEMBERED HER.
I get it from a special connection.
I can't give it away.
Is that so?
Whoever becomes your wife will be happy
to be able to eat like this everyday.
By the way, do you have a girlfriend?
I'm looking.
Did you all hear that?
Not just plastic surgery, he's a great cook!
Dr. Yuji Kotorida is very eligible.
Yes.
It's Kanako. Do you have a minute?
Yeah.
What is it?
Sorry on your day off.
Were you sleeping?
No.
Is somebody here?
No. Come in.
Thanks.
Still eating breakfast, Yuji?
Want some coffee?
I'd like tea.
Oh?
Let's see, tea...
Tea.
Say...
Can I try this bacon?
Yeah.
This is it.
I craved for this meat.
Yuji...
Could you tell me once and for all?
What is this meat?
You came just to ask that?
What's the matter?
I'm... pregnant.
Huh?
Mine?
I don't know.
I'm seeing two other guys with O type blood.
So... what are you going to do?
I plan to marry Mikiya.
My parents approve of him.
Is that so?
Congratulations.
Thanks.
Let's stay friends.
Of course.
I'll provide that meat you like
for your wedding.
Really?
Yeah.
I'll really shine that day.
I'm the only one that can cook that meat.
Thanks. I'm so happy.
Oh...?
Smoke?
Yes.
A real man's day off.
Nice.
I used to go stream fishing.
I used to smoke the fish.
I've been too busy and it's been a while.
This is convenient.
It smells good.
Makes me want a beer.
I want to do it at home.
But the smoke is too much.
I can imagine.
Do you have a light?
Oh.
Can't even smoke these days.
Can't do this, can't do that.
It makes us crazy.
Yes... hello?
Hello... it's Rumi.
Rumi Ogawa.
Of the Akimoto Clinic.
Yeah?
Miss Ogawa, what is it?
I know your secret.
What do you mean?
I saw...
The other day...
I saw you go to a hotel with Kanako Akimoto.
I'm sorry.
I followed you.
And?
It's rumored that Dr. Akimoto
is marrying another man.
Well... right.
You should pick someone serious about you.
I'm sorry. I'm not attracted to you.
That's horrible.
You can tell the hospital director
if you want.
I wouldn't.
Sorry, but forget about me.
Doctor...
I'm holding a scalpel right now.
The one you use for surgery.
If I cut myself...
you'll heal it, right?
Doctor, you are a God to me.
All right.
Let's just have one meal together. Okay?
You mean that?
I'm happy!
See you.
I saw the TV show.
How was it?
It was good.
You mean that?
I'm so happy!
It was popular at the station too.
It looks like I can continue.
Yeah? That's great!
Doctor, I owe it to you.
No. It's your ability.
You brought out my attractiveness.
Doctor... I...
MAY 21 (THUR): I DON'T HAVE RELATIONS
WITH MY PATIENTS.
Today is an exception.
I wanted to see your face.
What?
It was nice during the day,
but night is even better.
May I sit?
Please.
I want to eat you.
I couldn't wait.
Go home.
Somebody here?
None of your business.
You liar.
Since I saw you at the clinic,
I never liked you.
Doctor?
Don't be fooled.
What have done to my precious face?
Oh, no.
I just wanted to die with you, Doctor.
Doctor?
What should I do?
It's all right.
Relax.
Calm down...
and think about what to do.
Here.
Pull slowly.
There, that's a good girl.
AKIMOTO COSMETIC CLINIC
First time here?
Come in.
Excuse us.
You're... the other day...
Tachibana of the Police.
This is Shimoda.
From five days ago,
a woman named Aiko Suzuki
has been missing.
Aiko Suzuki?
She is known as Saki Minemura,
an entertainer.
I remember her.
She is a patient.
She hasn't reported for work.
Concerned co-workers consulted her parents.
They asked the Police to investigate.
Is that so?
D. Kotorida, have you seen
Ms. Suzuki lately?
Recently, she interviewed me
for her TV show.
Other than that?
I'm at a loss.
Once, I had dinner with her in Yokohama.
Last week, Saturday night.
The night she went missing.
What?
Is that so?
Why hide the fact about the dinner?
Sorry.
I didn't want to be misunderstood.
I don't have personal relations
with my patients.
You know...
rumors about fooling with the patients.
I had dinner with Ms. Suzuki
in appreciation for her coverage.
After dinner?
I saw her home.
I see.
What?
You think I'm involved
in her disappearance?
No.
She was last seen having dinner with you.
I thought you knew something.
By the way,
did she have any problems?
Let's see...
Stalking fans...
Stalker?
Yes.
She mentioned she was persistently being
stalked by a male fan.
Dr. Kotorida, have you seen his face?
No, it was during the conversation.
Is that so.
There's an increase in young missing women in
the Kamakura area in the last two years.
So I've been looking for a clue to solve it.
Stalker...
Thank you very much.
Let me know if there is anything I can do.
That's great.
Sometimes people run away.
It's not always a crime.
There hasn't been one body.
Bustling, as always.
- Doctor...
- Huh?
Have you heard?
Ms. Ogawa has been
absent without leave for three days.
She doesn't answer her cellphone.
Maybe she went missing.
No way.
You're right.
But I was surprised when the Police came.
Better be careful, Ms. Ezawa.
Stop it.
YOU HAVE MAIL
SENDER UNKNOWN
...IT IS THE DESIRE TO EAT THE MEAT
OF THE ONE YOU LOVE.
I had a strange dream.
I dreamed I was eaten by Christy.
Could it be a premonition?
Yes.
It's Tachibana.
I was in the neighborhood.
- Come in.
- All right.
Where is your partner?
I'm off-duty today.
What can I do for you?
I'm embarrassed to say,
I can't forget about that meat.
Meat?
You know.
The smoked meat you were making
at the beach.
Oh.
When I smelled that aroma...
I was enthralled.
Just once, I wanted to try that meat.
I know it's presumptuous.
Please.
May I try that meat just once?
Yes, you can.
I recently made some.
Doctor...
You've been single?
Yes.
My colleagues keep getting married.
Another one is getting married tomorrow.
That's wonderful.
So this is it.
I'll eat it with my hands.
Go ahead.
Delicious.
I've never tasted meat this good.
Isn't it?
It's really different.
A young woman's meat.
Detective, you're funny.
I always wanted to try it.
The meat of a freshly killed young woman
as you say in your diary.
Diary?
On the internet.
I can tell even if you deleted your identity.
That is a fictional...
Doctor...
I've investigated.
You are the serial...
missing persons suspect.
But, you know...
I let you swim.
I even erased evidence I had to submit.
Do you know why?
No.
I'm also...
a fan of human meat.
From before...
I was secretly eating
dead bodies from the crime lab.
But it didn't taste good.
It was rotten.
It tasted like medicine.
I ate too much.
And I became like this.
It was...
perhaps like when you ate...
that fat for the first time.
But...
you took it to the next step right away.
I envied you.
So...
what are you going to do to me?
It's easy to arrest you.
But I don't gain much from it.
Want to make a deal?
I don't arrest you...
from now on...
you provide me with fresh women's meat.
Ridiculous.
You could do it.
And to you...
it's nothing.
Can the police make such a reckless deal?
If it's not possible...
I immediately call for back-up
and thoroughly go through your home.
The police...
we can do anything.
I'll give you half a day.
Please think about it.
I hope you can make the wedding.
We can do anything.
You're a God?
Not good.
Hello?
Yuji? What's the matter?
Sorry.
I might not make the ceremony tomorrow.
What?
What do you mean?
I don't believe you.
Really, I'm sorry.
What are you doing?
You're supposed to prepare the meal.
I'll prepare the meal.
I'll have it delivered.
You really can't come to the wedding?
Yuji, I want you to come.
Kanako...
What?
I still love you.
That's why...
I want you to eat the meat.
The secret of this meat...
I'll tell you.
Really?
I'm just a friend?
You thought so?
From back then?
I was that showing off?
- Talking about us?
- Yes.
Everybody, the time has come.
The food has arrived.
Please enjoy the meal.
It looks so good!
This is good.
It's tasty.
- The colors!
- Isn't it good?
- It's spicy and tasty.
- Really?
- It's good!
- Let's have more!
Yeah, let's have some!
- I've never had this meat before.
- I could eat it all.
Excuse me.
A delivery from Dr. Kotorida just arrived.
What could it be?
It's a big box.
It must be a present.
Please bring it here.
As you say.
A present from Dr. Kotorida,
who contributed today's wonderful meal,
and is best friends with the bride and groom.
The secret of this meat... I'll tell you.
Thought you could get away, Kotorida?