Texts of: Asper & redruM
Proofreading: KillaloT
DB4Ever
www.danishbits.org
-- Hey, what have you under the helmet?
-- Should we run ræs?
Come on.
Run faster.
NEVADA, 1957
Sorry, gentlemen.
The whole area is closed --
-- Because of weapons-test
the next 24 hours.
It includes all personnel.
Good afternoon, sir.
It is also, unfortunately, you, Colonel.
The Pentagon has ordered ...
PROHIBITED AREA
DØDBRINGENDE POWER USED
Russians.
-- This will not be easy.
-- Not as easy as it used to.
We have seen worse things.
-- Well ... when?
-- Flensburg, twice as many.
-- We were younger.
-- I am still young.
We had weapons.
Take your hands down,
you make us a laughing stock.
I put $ 400 on that we
come out of this predicament.
Let's just say $ 100.
Genkender you the building?
Drop dead.
Excuse me ... I thought
drop dead, pal.
-- How was he taken?
-- In Mexico.
They dug in the dark,
and were looking for it here.
You are not from here, are you?
How would you think I come from?
Dr. Jones ...
How you express your Rs
I will shoot in the eastern Ukraine.
Colonel Dr. Irina Spalko.
Three times I have
been tapperhedsmedaljen.
And a medal as champion
for better working conditions.
And why?
Because I know things.
I know them before any other.
And I do not know
to find out.
And that I need
to know now ... is here inside.
You are hard to read, Dr. Jones.
We do it here
on the old-fashioned way.
You must tell us. You must
help us to find what we seek.
At this store, you and your government
Saved all your secrets, yes?
It is a military warehouse.
I have never been here before in my life.
A rectangular box,
with dimensions of 200 x 50 x 66 cm.
Contents of the box,
mummified remains.
Does it not you know?
What have you to believe that I have
no idea what you talking about?
For 10 years since you were a part
of the team that examined it.
Listen ...
If I knew,
what you talked about ...
You must help us to find it.
Kompas.
I must use a compass.
I know ... North, South, East.
West.
Do you have no compass?
I need your bullets!
He will have my rounds.
The contents of the box,
is incredibly magnetic.
I will use gunpowder.
Do you want my help or not?
Do not playing with me,
Dr. Jones.
What is the point of this?
If it is still magnetic,
will the metal in this gunpowder --
-- Show the way.
Cartridges.
Give me haglgeværs cartridges.
A seaweed.
Drop the weapons,
or Col Dr. Spalko door.
Why, Mac?
What can I say, Jonesy?
I am a capitalist.
And they pay.
After all the years we spent on the
to spy the red ...
I thought we were friends, Mac.
There is no will
have gems like me.
All four.
I want all four.
I can not take
home empty-handed again.
Do you have any last words,
Dr. Jones?
I love fire.
Put the weapon.
Okay, buddy.
Shit,
I thought it was closer.
Come on ... came so.
Do not play smart, Boris.
You know him not.
You know him not!
You made yourself.
Hello?
Hey, I have a telefo ...
Just a minute.
It can not be good.
"To all staff:
There is now one minute to the explosion "!
"Take the glasses on, or look away."
"Do not remove the glasses,
and do not looking "--
-- "Until 10 seconds after the first glimpse."
It can not be good.
Hey, wait.
Wait, wait.
Yes, fine.
Just do not wait on me.
"15 seconds left."
"10 seconds left."
BLYINDFATTET
I had no reason to believe
the Mac was a spy.
He was in MI6, when I was in the OSS.
We made 20-30 missions together
by the Pacific in Europe.
Leave it to your range krigsjournal
ad us. We have all served.
Really?
Which side served you?
I think you know
how serious your situation is.
You helped KBG agents who broke into
a tophemmeligt military installations --
-- In the middle of the United States.
My country.
What was there in the stålkasse the train?
You must tell us.
You've seen it before.
No, you think of the failure in `47.
I was thrown on a bus
with tinted windows --
-- And 20 people, I do not
had to talk to.
Slæbt out the middle of the night,
in the middle of nothing --
-- The middle of one kind or another
important collection project.
And were shown what? Vragrester --
-- And a magnetic veil,
covering the mutilated remains.
None of us had ever
to know what was going on.
And we were threatened with forædderi,
if we ever talked about it.
So tell me,
what was in the box?
Indy ... Thank God.
Do not know that it is dangerous
to be in a refrigerator?
-- The tingester can be dødsfælder.
-- I am also happy to see you.
Relax, boys.
I can vouch for Dr. Jones.
What the hell is going on?
KGB on U.S. soil.
Who is the woman?
Describe her.
High, thin, middle of the 30s.
Goes with a sword of a kind.
A rapier, known enough.
Yes, it is her.
Are you sure she is here?
Yes, and away again.
Who is she?
Irina Spalko,
she was Stalin lyshårede girl.
His favorite scientist ...
If you can call surveys
of psyken, science.
General Ross.
She runs teams from the Kremlin, the whole
the world and looking for artifacts, --
-- Which she believes may have
Paranormal military properties.
General Ross.
Relax, Paul.
Not everyone in the army are communists
and especially not Indy.
What will I be accused of,
in addition to survive a nuclear bomb?
Not any more.
But your friendship with George McHale
do all your activities --
-- Suspicious.
Including them during the war.
Are you nuts?
Do you have any idea of how many
medals, the pigs here have won?
Wild many, certainly.
But he deserves them?
Let's just say that you are in
bureau's interest, Dr. Jones.
Significant interest.
Scalbrade is from 3100 BC --
-- And was inhabited for 600 years,
until the --
-- Apparently was left
in 2500 BC
There is no
clear evidence of why --
-- The residents chose to
leave a perfect environment.
Yes?
May I borrow you for a moment,
Professor?
Yes.
Open Michaelson
and read Chapter four through.
When I come back, we are discussing
the difference between migration and refugees.
What?
I had no idea that the pressure
come from the ruling commission.
FBI turned up in the morning
and ransagede your office.
And looking at all your files.
You are rector at the school,
why you stopped them?
It was not allowed to.
They had every right.
They were not troublemakers.
They were agents with
search warrants.
The university should not be messy
into the kind of controversy.
Not so højspændt a time.
So, you fired me?
Dismissal due
of absence, is all.
Instant dismissal.
You fired me after all?
They have agreed to pay
your full salary, until ...
I do not want their money.
Do not be stupid.
You have no idea what I had to be through,
just to get it in place.
What you had to be through?
What might you,
exactly through?
I came from.
How will you go?
With a train to New York.
Overnatter in London,
to start with.
Why not teach in Leipzig?
Heinrich owe me a favor.
I send you money,
when I get in place.
You can send me
the rest of my things.
There is hardly anything here,
holding you back?
I can hardly recognize the country more.
The government helps us to see
Communists everywhere.
When there is hysteria in the research,
it is probably time to switch careers.
How did Deirdre news?
How taking any wife
such news ...
Judging by their expressions,
a combination of pride and panic.
I should never have doubted
to you, my friend.
No, but you have reason to
doubt your friends these days.
Some brutal years, Charlie?
First father, Marcus.
You seems to be
reached the age where their lives --
-- Start to take things
instead of giving.
Do not even half a glass.
Professor ... hello.
Are you Dr. Jones?
You run out of platform, kid?
Are you a friend of Dr. Oxley?
Oxley, arkæologen?
What about him?
The beats him to death.
I have not talked with
Harold Oxley in 20 years.
He is a brilliant man.
He can get you to sleep;
just by talking to you.
That is how I fell
asleep when I was a child.
His voice was better
than a glass of warm milk.
My name is Mutt ... Mutt Williams.
-- Mutt?
-- Yes.
What is it for a name?
This is what I have chosen,
Is there something wrong with it?
Quiet now.
What was your relationship with Oxley?
My father died in the war.
He helped my mother,
to nurture me.
And you think that any
will kill him?
Six months ago,
my mother received a letter from the Ox.
He is in Peru.
He had found a kind of skull.
A crystal skull.
It, like him
Mitchell Hetckiss found.
Ox and I was occupied by
the skull in college.
How do you know of it?
Are you piss on me?
It was the only thing he talked about.
Is it a kind of statue?
A meso-American carved figure.
There are few krystalkranier in the world.
I saw one on "The British Museum".
Interestingly hand,
but more is not it?
Grin only.
Ox said that he had
found it, this time.
He said it was authentic and had to
to a place called Akator with it.
Akator?
-- Did he?
-- Yes.
Are you sure?
That was what he said.
He said Akator.
What is it?
It is a mythical,
disappeared town in the Amazon.
The Spanish erobrere
called the Eldorado.
It is assumed Buga tribe were selected
by their god to 7000 years ago --
-- To build a
giant city of solid gold.
With architecture and technology, which at first
would be seen again, 5000 years after.
Francisco de Arellano disappeared in
the jungle when he was looking for it in 1546.
I was about to die of blood poisoning,
when I was looking for it.
I do not believe it exists.
Why would Ox take the skull
to go?
According to legend, was a krystalkranie
stolen from Akator the 1500 figure.
And it delivered the skull back,
could use its forces.
Forces?
So it has a sort of forces?
What forces?
I do not know, kid.
It is just a vandrehistorie.
No, the letter she had received the Ox,
proved to be a card --
-- As she takes down
the office to find him --
-- But he has already been kidnapped.
Now they also have her.
Ox said,
he had the skull a place --
-- And if not my mother finds it,
beats the both of them to death.
She said that you would help me.
Me?
What's your mother?
Mary.
Mary Williams.
Can you remember her?
I have met many Mary'er, kid.
Keep your foot!
It is my mother, you're talking about!
Okay?
It is my mother.
You do not infuriate you up
all the time, to show that you're tough.
Sit down now.
It's fun, that it is you,
to find the skull.
As if you are gravrøver or such.
I am a professor of archaeology,
over 10 years.
So you are a teacher?
It will be a great help.
She called me two weeks
since, from South America --
-- And said that she had fled,
but they were after her.
She said she just had
a letter from the Ox.
She sent it to me,
so I could show it to you.
So dead link.
I opened it, but there
is no meaning in it.
It is nonsense. It is not
even the English letters.
Can you see?
Can you see the two tough guys over there?
When the disc.
I do not think they have come
to get off thirst.
Who are they?
I do not know.
Get involved
quietly, Dr. Jones.
It is the KGB.
And the roof of the letter.
The letter?
What letter?
The letter,
Mr Williams has just given you.
Me?
Ligner I am a postman?
I say this not again!
Get involved now ...
Or what?
Good attempt, kid.
But I think
you have taken a knife with that --
-- To a mid-air gun.
Outside, now.
-- Turn him there.
-- Who?
To my right, to create turmoil.
Can you just keep it here?
It is my girlfriend!
Go outside and fight.
Nak the slikhår.
Your mother fled not.
They let her go.
So she could send a letter.
You could give it to me.
And I could translate it.
Come on.
Go on, grandfather.
Skip.
Further, forward.
Move!
This is crazy!
Some people are injured.
Take care!
Run to the left!
Come on, the place!
Spread you!
We are running too strong.
It is what it is.
Excuse me, Dr. Jones?
Yes?
I had just one question
to Hargroves cultural model.
Read "Vergordon Child",
the section on fusionisme.
He spent most
of his life in the open.
If you want to be
a good archaeologist, --
-- You have to out from the library.
Who is it?
Francisco de Orellana.
A Spanish capture.
Can you remember him who disappeared,
when he was looking for the skull?
And just as I thought.
Koioma.
What is it?
A uddødt Latin American languages.
The early comlumbianere
spent is still the basic.
See, there is no sign,
Certainly, recalls Kioma.
Can you speak it?
No one speaks it.
It has not been heard in 3000 years.
But perhaps I can read it if
I will review it at mayan first.
For an old man to be,
are you good in a fight.
Thank you.
How old are you?
80?
It is a mystery.
Typically Ox, to write a mystery
on a uddødt language.
Follow in the ground the lines,
as only gods can read --
-- As the leader of Orellanas cradle, --
-- Vogtet of the living dead.
He talks about Nazcalinierne.
What is it?
Hieroglyffer.
Huge, ancient drawings.
The sign in the desert in Peru.
From the ground like that for nothing --
-- But from the sky ...
Only the gods can read them --
-- For it is only gods,
who live there.
Oxley tells us --
-- That the skull is in Nazca in Peru.
Finally.
They have seen him.
Ox went to town for a
few months ago.
He cried and screamed as a gal,
Police inserting him in an institution.
I have not read Spanish,
what they said?
Ketuwa, a local inkadialekt.
How did you learn it?
It is a long history.
I have plenty of time.
I read with Pancho Villa, and a
few of his friends spoke.
It is a lie!
You asked himself.
Pancho Villa?
Technically speaking, I was kidnapped.
For Pancho Villa?
It was a fight against Victoriano Huerta.
-- How old were you?
-- About your age.
Parents were safe
crazy, right?
It went straight.
There was high on at home.
My mother and I, have also
not too well with each other.
Treat her well, boy.
You have only one.
Sometimes, not very long.
Not my fault,
I think she is an idiot, --
-- Just because I
dissed out of school.
Are you drop out of school?
Yes, then. Several of them.
Fine private schools,
debatklubber, skakklubber ...
I am skilled with a knife, and then
I think it is a waste of time.
-- Passede you never entered?
-- No, it was the wrong books.
Because I love to read.
I used to read all the time.
-- But now I can choose.
-- How are you money?
Reparerer motorcycles.
Can you do the rest of their lives?
Yes, perhaps.
Is there a problem with it?
No.
Not if that is what you love.
Do not leave anyone tell you otherwise.
It is here.
Sister.
She says that Ox is here.
But she do not know where he is.
Some men came and took him.
Men with pistols.
They thought he was upset.
He subscribed to all
walls of his cell.
The mystery here in the Ox's letter,
it makes no sense.
Follow the lines
as only gods can read --
-- As the leader of Orellanas cradle.
Vugge?
Birth?
Orellana was not born in Peru.
He was born in Spain.
He was a Spanish capture,
who came here for gold.
What happened to him?
He disappeared
along with six others --
-- And the bodies were never found.
He must have lost the mind.
Ox, what happened?
It is not a
Mitchell-Hedges skull.
Try to see it extended the skull.
And the same word.
At different languages.
Again and again.
Returred, eltarred.
Returno?
Return!
Return where?
Or return what?
You think the skull?
It seems to have been
in the minds of him.
How should he return it to?
Sweep here.
Ox was not talking about Orellanas
place of birth.
It also has a second
impact on the mayan.
Bogstavelig spoken,
it means "resting place".
As in the "final resting place."
Ox felt Orellanas grave.
The drawing is scratched into the floor.
It is gravpladsen, where he is.
So it is clear that Orellana
disappeared and no one found his grave.
It seems that Oxley made.
Gravrøvere will be shot.
So it is good,
that we are not gravrøvere.
What we look for?
I do not know yet.
Perhaps a gravkammer
by one of the graves.
I think just, I saw something.
You are nervous over nothing.
This way down.
This way up.
It is giftpile!
Be there.
Are you ... teacher?
Deltids.
Dead End.
Maybe.
What are you doing?
Put it away, and give me some light.
Come with the above.
It is just a gimmick.
Dance in your spare time.
One of skorpionerne stuck me!
Door I do?
How much?
Kæmpestor.
Well.
Good?
When it comes to skorpioner,
the bigger the better.
If a small one bites you,
you should not keep it to yourself.
Their kranier.
Try to see their kranier.
It's like cartoons
in Oxleys cell.
This means that we are approaching.
It is good.
Why, it appears as?
Nazca Indians tied their
children's heads with rope --
-- To extend
skull on the way.
Why?
To honor the gods.
No.
God's head does not look like this.
It depends on who your God is.
You hasten you good enough, what?
Professor, it is a
impasse. Try to see.
Come on, klogesen.
Take the backpack.
This is unbelievable.
Uvirkeligt.
Do not to touch anything.
Footsteps ... Some have been here.
In recent ...
Two sets of tracks.
The same size. Could it
have been the same person?
Not bad, kid.
A.
Two.
Three.
Four.
Five.
Six.
Seven.
Orellana and his men, is perhaps
nevertheless reached out of the jungle.
Give me some light.
Do you have a knife?
It appears he died yesterday.
It is bandagerne.
They have retained him.
What happened right?
He has been wrapped in 500 years.
Air is not his best friend.
Thank you.
I will of course not borrow yours all the time.
Clear enough.
We had better put it back.
Is it here already open?
It is him.
It is Orellana.
They called him "The Golden Man".
His hungren after gold,
was legendary.
It is strange ... --
-- ... Some have been here
and moved again.
But they left all this ...
Gold.
And all artefakterne.
What they were looking for?
Keep it here.
Incredible.
No marks tool.
A whole piece of quartz.
Skåret against the layers.
Crystal is not magnetic.
It is gold does not.
What's this?
Perhaps you thought Nazca Indians,
that this was their god?
-- Do you think it is from ...
-- ... Akator.
Perhaps the Spaniards took the skull
together with all other prey, --
-- As they were on the way to their
Ships on the banks.
Perhaps sought Indians
them, or ... --
-- ... They came in-war over
booty, and slaughtered each other.
Indians bundled them into,
and buried them.
A few hundred years later,
dolls Oxley up here --
-- And find it here skull.
Removing it.
Perhaps the Akator.
Return?
Return, as he wrote
on the walls of his cell.
He put it back,
where he had found it.
Why?
Hey, Mac.
You are lucky,
that you are sitting here, Jonesy.
They will blow knoppen of you.
It is ... the third time today.
Release me free
and I give you a hug.
You had a Luger.
Pegede on your head with it,
the first time we met.
The situation was under control.
You are in debt to me.
What you owe them?
After that you betrayed
your country during the war --
-- How many names
gave you as the Red?
How many good men died,
because of you?
At a time release the me
out of this chair, pal.
And when they do ... --
-- ... So I break his nose at you.
Pal?
Do you think
that this is about Flakes?
About you? Do you think it here
acting on the lines on a map?
It is about money, is it not?
No, not money.
But a huge pile of money.
Do not wonder,
what the Russians want to pay.
It is nothing compared to,
what is in Akator.
A whole city of gold.
This is what erobrerne was after.
For heaven's sake, Jonesy.
We are rich.
Rigere than Howard Joeth.
The whole shebang is blood money.
Imagine now on, buddy!
Do it right!
As in Berlin, you know ...
I just go smutter
after a bottle of whisky.
Where was it fortunate that we do not
had beaten you to death, Dr. Jones.
You survived, so you could
make us even a service.
You know me.
I like to help where I can.
"I have been messenger of death."
"He who destroys worlds"
Genkender you the words?
It was your famous
Dr. Oppenheimers words.
After he created the atomic bomb.
He quoted from the
Hinduistiske Bible.
It was the beginning of the Cold War.
But now is the next
våbenfremskridt, our first.
And it is your turn
to fear us.
What do you mean by a new weapon?
A telepathic weapons.
A new step in the psychological
warfare. It was Stalin's dream.
Now, I understand why Oxley
put the skull back in the grave.
He found out,
that I was looking for it.
The skull is not
a standard icon.
You must also have discovered.
It was not created
of the human.
Who has made it?
Quite frankly ...
Kadaveret from New Mexico
was not the first we found.
We had already dissekeret Thursday
from similar facilities in the Soviet Union.
Small green men from Mars?
Legenderne on Akator
is all true.
Nation from the time could be impossible
had planned, let alone built it.
It was a city,
created by superior beings.
With superior technology
and Paranormal abilities.
You take the gas on me!
Perhaps you will think
on what you can see?
The copy from New Mexico
gave us renewed hope.
Unlike the others,
had it here, a skeleton of crystal.
Perhaps it was a distant relative --
-- Which was also sent to it
to find Akator.
Perhaps the leader we all
after the same.
It is the only
possible explanation.
There is always another option.
Kraniet were stolen
Akator from the 1500 figure.
-- Which brings it back ...
-- Will get control of its force.
I have heard the bedtime story before.
It is a legend.
What have you to believe that Akator
have existed?
The question
you should ask your friend.
Come with the professor!
We are convinced
that he has been there.
Oxley.
Ox.
It is me, Indy.
Ox!
"Through the eyes of the end
I saw in tears "
Ox. Now here.
Your name is Harold Oxley.
You were born in Leeds, England.
You and I read together,
at the University of Chicago.
And you have never been
so interesting here.
My name is Indi ...
My name is Henry Jones, Jr.
What have I done by him?
We have not made him something.
It is the skull.
He is ønskekvisten,
which will lead us to Akator.
But we need a
to decipher him to us.
His mind is dramatically weakened --
-- Let us hope that your are stronger.
Krystallet in the skull stimulates the
unused areas of the brain --
-- To open for a
telepathic contact.
Oxley lost minds, because he
gazed for a long time in kraniets eyes.
We have a theory,
that you can get through to him --
-- When you have done
the same as him.
Why do you not just themselves?
Kraniet talk apparently not to all.
You are probably not afraid, Dr. Jones?
You have spent your entire life
to look for answers.
Think of the truth,
can be found behind these eyes.
Perhaps there are hundreds
of kranier in Akator.
Those who find them, --
-- Will have control over the world
largest of nature ever.
Control over the human mind.
Take care,
maybe you get what you want you.
That I usually make.
Imagine --
-- You could look over to the other
page and see the enemy's secrets.
We could place our thoughts
in your leaders' minds.
Get your school teachers to teach
in the true version of the history of the world.
And your soldiers to attack,
In our orders.
We would be everywhere.
Stronger than whisper.
We would invade your dreams,
managing your thoughts, while I sleep.
We want to change you, Dr. Jones.
You all together.
The inside.
We will turn you to us.
And the best part is --
-- I will not even detect,
that we do it.
Return.
It is enough.
It is enough. If he dies,
we have no joy of him.
Cover it.
Henry.
Are you okay, Jonesy?
You have broken my nose!
I had said.
So it is enough!
You will speak with Oxley
and lead us to Akator, yes?
Njet
Before him outside!
Is everything OK, kid?
My motorcycle is
still at the cemetery.
-- Yes, but are you okay?
-- They left my motorcycle!
Hold on!
Stop!
So, I am ready.
You must not give the pigs!
You heard what he said.
I have clearly chosen
the wrong lever.
Maybe I can find
a more active one.
Come with gidslet!
Remove the hands from me,
your forbandede russersvin!
Indiana Jones.
-- It was you long for.
-- Mom!
Taxes.
Mom!?
What are you doing here?
Do not worry me.
Are you all right?
Mom?
I said explicitly,
that you should not come!
What you never said.
Even in the phone.
Is Marion Ravenwood your mother?
For heaven's sake, Indy.
So difficult it is not.
No, no ... I think
I thought not ...
The fact that I would have a normal life,
after you left me?
It was not what I meant.
I had a really good life.
Well, it is good ...
A very good, very good life!
I have also!
Leaves you still traces of crushed
menneskeskæbner in your wake, --
-- Or are you retired now?
Why?
Are you looking for a date?
With whom-as-preferably, but not you!
Will you help us now, Dr. Jones?
You just have to say yes.
Typically you, to be kidnapped,
Marion.
And what about you?
Everything is by the old.
Henry Jones, Jr.
It is right, Ox.
Listen here ...
"To pay their fair
hands on "--
-- "Golden key
which opens evighedens palace "
Palace?
It is of Milton.
He has said before.
Ox, you will have to tell us,
how to get to Akator.
Otherwise, turn the Marion to death.
"Through the eyes are crying
Finally I saw them "
"Here in the death drømmerige ..."
Harold, they will turn Abners
little girl to death.
You will have to tell us,
how we arrive there.
We must use fully specified ...
Get a paper to me
and something to write with.
Autoskrift.
I should have guessed it.
Henry Jones, Jr.
Yes, Ox.
It is me.
"Three times is the"
"Way Down"
Three times.
Piktogrammer?
Ideogrammer.
Well done, Ox.
Ox.
It is me, Ox.
It is Mutt, Ox.
Look at me.
It's me!
It is me.
The wavy lines mean water.
The closed eyes means sleep.
The sun in the lane over the sky is
time. Or duration.
The word "now" means up.
Horizon and the snake
means together "an idea".
Horizon has also meant "the world".
But not in the importance of the globe.
This meant large or powerful.
The water sleeps
until the big snake.
It is not just cartoons.
The instructions.
Provide me a map.
The big snake applies
of course the Amazon River.
But sleep ...
What water is asleep?
There, there.
"Sono." It is
the Portuguese word for sleep.
Yes, well.
He would have us
to follow Sonofloden here --
-- Down to the point where the
meetings Amazon River in the southeast.
I am not sure,
what we should then.
A kingdom of tears,
dreams and eyes.
I simply do not
what he thinks.
Perhaps this is the way, but it is
a completely unexplored area.
Running!
What pokker do we, kid?
They would beat us to death.
Maybe.
Someone was forced to do something.
Anything other than this,
would have been preferable.
I have at least one level.
You are insufferable.
Harold, Hurry up!
Mother!
Be there!
Stop.
Move you do not!
Movement will have you
to sink deeper.
I think I can ...
If I just ...
Stop it.
You withdraw against a vacuum.
As to try to lift a car.
Relationships you in peace.
Okay.
I am calm.
What is it?
Kviksand?
No, it's a dry sandgrav.
Kviksand is a mixture of sand,
mud and water, depending on ...
For heaven's sake, Jones.
We are not in school now.
Relax now. There is nothing to
worry about, unless there is ...
Luftlommer to collapse.
I find something to
to pull you up with.
Ox, do something.
For heaven's sake.
Go out and find someone to help.
Help?
Yes, help!
Help!
Help.
Download now some help!
I know that Mutt
can be a bit impetuous.
It is not
the worst he can be.
Keep your arms in the air. When the kid
come back interfere you get.
Indy, he ...
He is a good boy, Marion.
You should not be so hard at him.
Not all are suitable for it.
He says Henry.
Henry.
Good name.
He is your son.
My son?
Henry Jones, the third.
Why you let him skip school?
Dam, vulture!
-- Stick.
-- I have it.
Come on, Mom.
Drag.
Take hold of it.
Take the deal.
Take just hold of it, Indy.
It is a rottesnog.
Rottesnoge is not so great.
Well, it is here. It is
not even toxic. Take fat!
Find something else.
What, for example?
A rope or similar.
I can not just slip in Silvan
out here. Take the hold of the snake.
Maybe I can reach the bottom.
There is no bottom.
Take fat!
Well, I think I can feel it.
Seize now get on the tube.
Team looked up to call it that!
It is a snake.
What should I call it?
-- A rope.
-- What?
Say "grab the rope"!
Take hold of the rope!
Hold fast.
It is slimy.
Get the thing away from me.
Sønnike.
He is afraid of snakes.
You are a brittle old man.
Why do you always
be so cumbersome, Jonesy?
Thanks, Ox. It was beautifully done.
Help.
No, he was British.
My father was jagerpilot. Krigshelt.
Not one or another school teacher.
No, taxes.
Colin was your surrogate father.
I met him,
when you were three months old.
He was a good man.
Who, Colin?
Colin Williams?
Giftede you with him?
I introduced you to each other!
Since you left me a week --
-- Before our wedding, you
hardly right to judge me!
We was both aware of
that it could not function.
It could you not know. Why
you do not talked with me about it?
Because it was impossible
To win a discussion with you
It is not my fault,
that you can not keep up.
I did not want to hurt you!
Hold now, for heaven's sake, shut up!
Undrede you never over at the time,
why Ox stopped to talk to you?
He hated you because you're stuck with.
Stop now, in two!
Yes, Marion. We must not allow
the child see that the mother and father quarrel.
You are not my father.
You can just swear, I am.
And you know what?
To make the school finished!
What became of "there is no
something wrong with you, kid "--
-- "And do not say anything else?"!
Can not remember what you said?
That was before I was your father!
You are not my father!
-- Yes, he is!
-- You should have told me that!
I was right to know.
You disappeared!
I wrote.
Yes, a year later.
At the time
Mutt was already born --
-- And I was married!
So why tell it now?
Because I thought we were going to die!
Not yet!
Got it?
Shit!
I was certainly not the only,
who lived on.
You must have had plenty
of women, through the years.
It has been a few.
But they had all
the same problem ...
And what was it?
They were not you, sweetheart.
We must have Oxley
and the skull back --
-- And reach Akator before the Russians.
Take the wheel.
What he has now
going to do?
I do not think
he is thinking that far!
-- Nudge you right, sønnike.
-- Stop calling me sønnike!
I would keep me in the ears,
if I were you.
Duk you!
Move!
Run up on the page
of the amfibievogn.
Henry Jones, Jr.
Jones!
Bound!
Duk you!
Ox has the skull.
Marion, take the wheel.
It is cheating, she also got
allowed to run the truck.
Take a tudekiks and
find something to fight with.
Jonesy!
-- Jonesy.
-- Hey, Mac.
-- Indy!
-- Keep now shut up!
I am the CIA.
I cried the closest
to you in the tent.
I said "as well as in Berlin."
And what we were Thursday in Berlin,
my friend?
Dobbeltagenter.
Throw the skull over to me!
Throw the skull above!
The weight on the front foot!
Riposte!
It is not a skolekamp, mother!
You are fighting,
as a young man loves ... --
-- Eager to get started
and quickly finished!
Mutt, drag you back.
Hey ... I have the skull!
Handgun!
What glor you, dad?
She slip away!
Hey, passport p. ..
Allow me to!
It is rather dangerous here.
In return, Dr. Jones.
Jones!
Stop!
-- Siafu!
-- What?
Kæmpestore dræbermyrer.
For the place!
Kill them!
-- Siafu!
-- What?
Kæmpestore dræbermyrer.
For the place!
Kill them!
Running down to the river!
Go up in the car!
Hurry!
Dam, beware the abyss!
Skip down on the car.
-- Come on, Jonesy!
-- Spring!
-- Mom!
-- Set slow down!
Put down the road, tax.
You run out over the edge.
It is also intended.
It is a really bad idea.
Allow me to.
Trust me!
It is, you should never do again!
Okay, sweetheart.
"Three times the fall."
Bak!
Put it in reverse!
Way down.
He believes the country.
It was the path he took last.
Three times the fall?
Three times the fall!
-- What does he mean?
-- He believes ...
A!
Two!
Three ...
Are you all right?
Release, sweet!
"Through the eyes are crying
Finally I saw them "
"Without taking the golden revelation."
-- Gold.
-- Through the eyes and tears!
We have to go through the waterfall!
I will return the skull.
In other need not take.
Is it not the same thing?
The skull has not given us
other than problems!
See what it has done by him!
-- I have to return it.
-- Why you?
Because, it said,
that I should.
Okker, iron, turkiser.
How old is this?
4-5000 years old.
Like the pyramids.
The tilbad sun.
Like the Egyptians.
It is wet. It has
been used recently.
Several worshippers.
Yes, but it is not the sun,
they worship.
Someone came --
-- And learned Yucaerne on agriculture --
-- And irrigation.
Ox, what is there?
I think I understand it now, Ox.
There was no?
Are they the same?
There was more.
Look!
A circle of 13.
Show us the way, Ox.
Come on!
Running!
Indy!
Jonesy!
Oxley!
How did you pass them,
the last time you were here?
Come on, Mac!
Come, Ox.
"The golden key
which opens evighedens palace "
Well done, Ox.
The city of gold.
Where are all the gold so?
See where this is past due.
What a stupid legend.
What a waste of time.
Ox has been here before.
But he could not
enter the temple.
So he brought the skull back --
-- To the cemetery,
where he had found it.
"To pay their fair
hands on the golden key "--
-- "Which opens evighedens palace"
He who opens the Palace ...
Obelisken.
Is Obelisk key?
Ox, looking for you?
What are you doing?
You figured it out while you were sitting
in the cell. Not true, Professor?
Let me get to, Professor.
Well done.
Get one for yourself!
Listen!
Can you hear it?
Up to you!
Running.
Ox, run!
Faster!
-- Faster!
It does not look good.
Running, Ox. Running!
Fast!
I do not like it here.
I do not like it!
Jonesy!
He has lost it.
He has lost the skull!
Marion.
Keep it here!
Is everything in order, Ox?
Beautiful.
Okay, let's get going.
This road?
See now,
begins to resemble something.
There are treasures here, of all
ancient eras here.
Macedonian.
Sumerian.
This place
is the ultimate collection.
Etruskisk.
Babylonisk.
There is not a museum, which is not
would sell their soul, for it here.
The early Egypt.
Many museums!
Hundreds, Jonesy!
Collectors.
They were archaeologists.
How open Monday it?
I come back with the Ox.
I promise you that.
"No more waiting in eternity."
Now is the time.
I regret Jonesy.
What are you then?
A trippel-agent?
No, I lied just to
I was a double.
See them.
They are still waiting
in the which disappeared.
They have a cube-awareness.
They are physically separated,
but have a common awareness.
They are much stronger together,
than if they were separate.
Imagine,
what they can tell us.
I can not
imagine it.
It could based
Temple does not.
And you can not!
Faith is something you do
have not learned to have.
I pity you.
I feel pity sister.
That is why I stand here.
He talks mayan.
What does he say?
He says he is grateful
and that he will ...
"The" want to give us a gift.
A great gift.
Tell me everything you know.
I want to know everything!
I have a feeling,
that we're all wrong.
Indy.
The eyes.
Is the rumvæsener?
Interdimensionelle creatures, in fact.
Welcome back, Ox.
What the hell is this?
A portal.
An access to another dimension.
I do not think
we must take to the road.
I want to know everything.
I should know.
Tell me everything.
I'm ready. Tell me.
Mac.
Come on.
Mac!
Come on, for pokker!
Now, I understand.
I understand.
Seize address.
Use the legs, Mac.
I can not pull you up.
Jonesy.
I will clear me.
No more.
Cover it.
Running!
It is enough.
No more.
Jump!
As the viskede their
footsteps away with a broom.
Where did they go?
Based in space?
Not into space.
In addition to the space between the rooms.
There is something I do not understand.
Why traded
the legend of a city of gold?
Gold meant tax
on Yucaernes language.
But the tax was not gold.
It was knowledge.
Their tax was knowledge.
Did I just thought you,
to be seated here?
Night falls early on
in the jungle, kid.
Believe me, you can not
climb down in the dark.
Well, I can.
Who would?
Why are you
not hanging, Junior?
I do not know.
Why did you
it is not, dad?
Farmand ...
Dad?
Your grandfather is sitting up there
and laughs a place.
Vidunderligt. Perfect.
Make the letters larger.
Much more.
Henry Jones, Jr,
and Marion Ravenwood.
We are gathered here today because
The two want to live as husband and wife.
I have demonstrated your love
by your promises --
-- The combination of your hands --
-- And by giving
each other these rings.
I declare I am now
for the right husband and wife to be.
Let no man destroy,
what God has brought together.
So much of a life,
wasted in waiting.
Congratulations.
You may kiss your bride.
Good done, Henry.
Thanks, Ox.
Texts of: Asper & redruM
Proofreading: KillaloT
DB4Ever - www.danishbits.org