Rome, 44 B.C.
There are whispers of civil war.
The military conquests of Julius Caesar
have won him the love of the people
and the hostility of the corrupted senate.
To counter the cult of Caesar, his enemies
lure the people with bloody spectacles
where slaves are forced to fight to the death.
The republic is dying,
and the age of the gladiator has begun.
And before it is done, the fate of an empire
will fall upon the shoulders of one man...
a slave.
A gladiator.
We prepare honors at the senate steps,
and instead Caesar brings us here.
It's smart politics.
He gives the mob a voice.
The senate is Rome, Brutus, not the mob.
The senate is the republic.
You think the rumors are true, then?
He aims to be king?
Who else would have the nerve
to change the bloody calendar?
As if owning half the earth weren't enough,
now he aims to own the sun and moon as well.
King?
He aims to be a god.
Hail, Caesar! Hail, Caesar...
I see no senators on that chariot with him.
Mark Anthony, you look well.
Rome's favorite son returns.
Welcome home, brother.
Dear Atia.
Octavius?
Your nephew is delayed.
Noble Cicero.
Just read your latest.
Brilliant, as usual.
You're quite tough on me.
Think of it as advice from a cranky old man.
It's your time now.
You've proven yourself a conqueror.
Now Rome needs a unifying force.
Wise Cassius.
Triumphant Caesar. Rome exults in your return.
The senate has commissioned
12 statues in your honor,
including an ivory likeness to be presented
to you at the circus games,
so deep is our gratitude.
I thank you.
Most excellent senator Brutus.
Caesar.
Look at you... a model senator.
The legion wouldn't recognize you.
I've fooled them all.
Enough of pageantry.
To the arena.
To sport!
Hail, Caesar! Hail, Caesar!
Citizens!
Citizens! Citizens!
Your gladiators fight here today
in honor of our returning hero...
the Victor at Zela, conqueror of Gaul...
Julius Caesar!
Hail, Caesar! Hail, Caesar!
First let me introduce to you
the most fearsome warrior
since Hannibal of Carthage,
undefeated...
here is the Reterian!
And his opponent...
Citizens, I present to you Rome's champion...
Tyrannus!
Octavius!
I see things are about as I left them.
We, who are about to die, salute you.
I've seen Tyrannus fight.
I have 100 denarii says he makes short
work of this reterian. Cassius?
I can't keep track of the gladiators.
They die so quickly.
What's the difference, uncle?
It's not like real battle.
They bleed just the same.
And what do you know
of real battle, Octavius?
I've studied.
Let me show you.
Take me with you to Syria next month.
Let me fight in the Parthian wars.
Octavius.
No.
I have other plans for you.
You spoil him, sister.
Do I?
I wasn't the one who gave him
20 Libyan horses for his birthday.
They throw Rome's finest warrior to the dogs?
Yes, the mob's appetites have changed,
great Caesar.
They hunger to see the blood
of their heroes.
What kind of Roman ideal is this?
Fight, Tyrannus!
- Caesar, now that you've returned...
- Take the day off, Cassius. Enjoy the games.
But discussing this could put
everybody at their ease.
If you must know my mind this instant,
before I leave for Syria,
I will bring in the Decree of Rome...
a new set of laws that redistributes
the land from the influential few
to the people of Rome where it belongs.
Of course, the senate looks
forward to a vigorous debate.
Good. My reforms begin with the senate.
It will take old friends to see them through.
Hail, Caesar.
The 10th legion could use him.
Pity he's a slave.
Tyrannus! Tyrannus! Tyrannus!
Do they answer?
Your gods?
Sometimes.
Really?
How?
They give signs.
Can they send me one?
Maybe they have and you weren't looking.
That would be my luck.
And what sort of guidance are you looking for?
Perhaps Minerva will hear.
I'd ask her to send me far from Rome,
far from this boring life.
I hope she answers for you.
What's your name, Vestal?
Camane.
I...
Sorry, I must go.
Camane!
When will Minerva answer?
When she answers.
Why is it you wish you were far from here?
Being the nephew of Caesar,
some would say that
the world is yours for the asking.
They would be mistaken.
My family treats me like a child.
Perhaps you act like one.
There isn't a young lady in all of Rome
who wouldn't swoon at your glance.
And yet, of all those young ladies,
you choose to give me,
a Vestal, your attentions.
Only a child wants what it cannot have.
The Decree of Rome?
You've been keeping secrets from us.
I'm as surprised as you.
Really? I thought you and Caesar were like brothers.
Caesar's always kept his own counsel.
That's news to no one.
Now, what do you want?
We wish to know your heart.
For instance, if one day
you should find yourself
inheriting the mantle of Caesar,
could the senate depend upon your friendship?
Caesar has said nothing of succession.
You'd be blind not to see that
Caesar's forcing a confrontation.
Apparently he's decided that the only way
to maintain his grip on power is to rob us of ours,
to destroy the republic, and anoint himself king.
He has refused the crown,
and I take him at his word.
Your tone suggests otherwise.
I stand with Caesar.
- They sent four against me.
- Four, papa?
Thracians.
They fight with a shield and
a short sword. So...
...shield. Short sword.
One... two... three...
four... five... six!
- Get ready for bed, Piso.
- Oh, I want to...
Go, Piso. Do as your mother says.
Good night.
I don't want you to tell him these stories.
He doesn't understand.
Show yourself.
Hail, Caesar.
Rise, Tyrannus,
the pride of Rome.
Thank you, great Caesar.
We've met before.
At the gladiator school in Campania.
I was a senator then.
If I'm not mistaken,
you corrected my swords manship.
You held the grip too tightly, great Caesar.
Walk with me.
Were you born a slave, Tyrannus?
No. I stole a horse.
I worked on my father's farm in Cyprus.
The armies of Pompey were
very cruel to the people there.
I stole a centurion's horse
and was thrown in prison.
In prison, I was sold away
to the gladiator school.
Difficult life.
It was my fate.
But my victories bring some rewards
from the handlers. I've been allowed to marry.
I love my wife, my son, Piso.
- How old is Piso?
- Six years.
Does he marvel at his father, the gladiator?
Too much, I think.
So it should be.
And your dreams for him, Tyrannus?
To not have to fight.
To live as he chooses.
- A free man?
- Yes, of course.
I fought 10 years for the glory of Rome,
conquered five nations,
and filled our treasuries with gold.
Yet I return, and the only growth I see
is in the size of the senators' villas.
I didn't conquer the world for them.
Those lands and those treasures
belong to the people
and the soldiers who fought for them.
I intend to set it right,
and the senate will do all it can to stop me.
So I need a warrior to stand beside me...
one unentangled by politics,
who speaks his mind and is good with the sword.
A bodyguard?
That... and more.
The senate seduces the mob with blood.
But the mob loves you, Tyrannus,
because you represent what's best in us...
strength, courage, honor.
I need you to serve me these next few weeks.
And in return... I offer this.
The wooden sword.
Given to gladiators who show
exceptional bravery and skill in the arena.
The wooden sword means freedom.
Take it...
and your son will live in a world
without chains.
I... I don't know what to say.
Say "yes."
I have built the greatest fighting force
in the world,
advanced the frontiers of Roman control
from Britannia to North Africa.
I have conquered the world for you,
the people of Rome,
not for the senators on Palatine Hill.
There's still time for negotiation.
Name a single law or treaty
that Caesar has not broken.
The mob won't stand for it.
What's been set in motion cannot be unset.
Mother Noella.
- What's happened?
- The goats are sick.
Mother Noella, it's all blood.
The midwife told me of five stillborns
this week on the Palatine Hill, all boys.
- It's gossip.
- It's omens.
In the coming days,
I will present the Decree of Rome...
the most sweeping reforms
in constitutional law
since the publishing of the 12 tables.
The college augurs warn of blood
on the ides. We must tell Caesar.
I'll discuss this with the arval priests,
make my decision.
And you will forget what you have seen.
What will you do?
We need Caesar isolated.
How much?
Three semis, ma'am.
How beautiful.
Piso?
Did you see my son?
Ma'am?
Piso?
Piso!
- Tyrannus! Tyrannus!
- Moira!
What is it? What's happened?
Where's Piso?
He was there beside me
at the marketplace.
Someone must have taken him.
Wait here!
Piso! Piso!
Have you seen a boy about six years,
this high?
There's no sign of the gladiator.
We've searched his home
in the slave barracks... nothing.
Tyrannus will come.
Caesar, let the senate wait.
At least until the praetorian find Tyrannus.
I agree. Call it off, brother.
Present the Decree of Rome another time.
There is no other time.
Is it him?
It's a Vestal, Caesar.
Your name, sister.
Camane, lord.
Forgive me.
What I have to say, I speak for myself,
not the order.
The signs warn of blood on the ides of Markh.
You must not ride to Rome, not today.
Now this. You must reconsider.
What would you have me do?
Hide under the bed?
That would be merry news to the senate.
But the gods.
I've lived my whole life in defiance of the gods.
Let this day be no different.
Man your horse. We ride.
Uncle!
Have you seen a boy about this high,
about six years?
Piso!
General...
your presence is required for just a moment.
Papa?
Piso!
My brother in exile, great Caesar, I beg leniency.
This is an old issue.
There will be no pardon.
Rise, senator Cimber, and take your seat.
You have saved your boy.
But who will save your beloved Caesar?
And you, my child?
By the gods.
Caesar.
- Tyrannus.
- I'm here.
Protect him.
Protect who, great Caesar?
My heir. My successor.
Mark Anthony, of course.
No. Not Anthony.
Octavius.
My sister's boy.
He will save the dream of Rome, Tyrannus.
Teach him how to fight, my friend.
Teach him how to rule.
I will.
Anthony.
What did he say?
He said...
"protect him."
Protect who?
Tyrannus...
protect who?
What have these madmen done?
What if the mob turns violent?
I've made preparations.
And what about him?
This was a terrible day for us all.
Bastards.
You stupid bastards.
Cooler heads must prevail now, general.
What's done is done.
You say this to me with his blood
on your hands?
I should throw all your heads to the dogs.
A tyrant died today, nothing more.
Rome is saved.
Think carefully, general.
This is a moment of consequence
of great history.
I would like it to be the moment that
the great powers of Rome embraced as friends...
and united a land and a people.
You said Anthony would be with us.
He's the army. We need him.
He'll be back.
In the meantime, I told you,
I made preparations.
Mercenaries.
Gladiators, to be specific.
For a fee, princeps Rapax has agreed
to lead them in pursuit of our enemies.
Which enemies?
All Caesar loyalists are now enemies
of the republic to be arrested
and tried for treason.
Start with his family.
We'll wipe his name from history.
Is this supposed to win the people's hearts?
Winning the war comes first.
Spare the women if you must.
Now go.
- Octavius!
- Halt!
Leave him!
What in the names of the gods?
Lady, Caesar is dead, murdered in the senate.
You're lying.
Where is your son?
What do you want with my son?
Caesar names Octavius his successor.
No. That's impossible.
Lady, there's no time.
You don't understand.
He's not involved in this.
He is now.
How could this have happened?
I swore an oath to Caesar to protect Octavius.
And I will protect him.
I won't have his blood on my hands as well.
Mother!
You... you're the gladiator.
Say goodbye to your mother, boy.
- No!
- Do as I say!
I won't.
Your uncle has been murdered.
Go with him.
If what Tyrannus says is true,
then the assassins will come for you next.
You cannot stay in Rome.
Now go.
Ride, Octavius.
The Vestal order takes no position
on the actions of the senate.
There's talk of a purge of
Caesar's family, of loyalists.
The institutions of Rome must intervene.
Perhaps you can reason with these men.
Reason, sister?
Reason has abandoned this place.
Not all Vestals are neutral in this.
When the time comes, child, I shall call on you.
Moira!
Listen to me.
Take Piso by carriage to the port of Ravenna.
Buy passage on a merchant ship to Cyprus.
Go to the inn of Balbus.
- But I don't understand.
- Stay there until I come for you.
I don't know when.
Stay off the major roads. Travel only at night.
- Come soon.
- I will.
They're coming.
We'll go for the horses.
Leave the soldiers to me.
Take this.
If you have to use it, hold it loose,
like the reins of a horse.
I taught your uncle that.
Let's go!
It'll be morning soon. We'll have to ride
at least Toperugia before making camp.
I tried to stop him today.
I called to him.
He didn't hear me.
We have to keep moving.
Not since Alexander the Great has such a burden
been placed on the shoulders of one so young.
And all the world hinges on the outcome.
Watch over him, sweet Vesta,
for the trials of Octavius have begun.
Who ever thought a god
would hold so much blood?
The mob will slit our throats
when they see this.
They won't see this.
How could they miss?
We'll slip him quietly from the
City on the Via Attica.
That route's blocked.
The rabble chant around fires.
Then we'll avoid the thoroughfare and
take the footpath to Porta Ostiensis.
There, too, the crowd calls for revenge.
So we'll throw them a few loaves of bread.
- We were supposed to be heroes.
- Will you stop?
There's no way to get him out.
You said we could never do this.
Look.
None has ever been deader.
We'll clear a route to the city gates,
and this whole ordeal will disappear.
The mob will be quiet before he starts to stink.
Your path is now dark and dangerous,
young Caesar.
The senate has dispatched assassins to find you.
Stay off the major roads.
Avoid the villages.
Even in the north, they are rounding up loyalists
and burning down their houses.
But do not lose hope. You have allies.
Trust them. Trust us.
Let him see you.
What did you do that for?
He's an assassin.
Or maybe he was just going home to his family.
No.
Look.
See his sword?
He's a gladiator, armed at the arena
by the same senate that killed your uncle,
now after you.
Where are you going?
Back to Rome.
It's too dangerous.
No.
This is too dangerous.
In Rome I have friends who know
I'm no threat to anyone.
I'll get senator Cimber to call off the dogs.
I vowed to protect you.
I put my family in danger.
Well, I didn't ask you to.
No. Caesar did when he named you his heir.
You say that.
It's nothing. Not even believable.
Just the word of a slave.
Who do you think you are?!
Idiot slave.
Highness...
Filthy chattel!
Supreme exaltedness...
Enough!
I said, "enough"!
Give me a hand with this.
Then get some sleep.
We ride tonight.
Octavius?
Octavius!
What are you looking at?
Olivia? Are you here?
Octavius?
I need to speak to your father.
He's at the senate.
You have no idea what I've been through.
We invited you, Anthony, not your soldiers.
They're not soldiers. They're bodyguards.
You won't need them.
And did Caesar?
He was trying to disband the senate.
Tell us that's not your plan, too.
What's gathered here?
Great fortunes of Rome.
Grain from Etruria.
Grapes from Sicily.
Oil. Cattle.
Shipping. Slaves.
All without soldiers to protect them.
So, what's your price?
So, is that what this is about?
The people riot.
What did you think would happen?
Caesar's blood is on your hands.
Fine. We're to blame. Agreed, agreed.
But Rome needs your legions
for protection. So say it --
what do you want?
I want to honor Caesar as I always have.
I want to speak at his funeral.
There's not going to be a funeral.
He was a traitor to the republic.
He was Caesar.
Well, he's gone. The senate's in charge now.
Well, tell that to the mob...
as they tear out your throats. Go on, all of you.
Tell them.
The senate is in charge.
Only the will of Caesar can say who's in charge.
The Vestals say there was no will.
They said there was none.
Oh, it exists.
He told me not two months ago.
Caesar may be dead to his dear
and loyal friends in this room.
But the will of Caesar is still the will of Rome.
And until it is found,
divvying up the republic behind
closed doors is very premature.
A will?
Did it name Anthony?
Who else?
Why else such swagger?
"Honor Caesar," he says.
He wants to turn the public against us.
The public is already against us.
We should have killed him
when we had the chance.
Quiet.
We did not rid ourselves of
one tyrant to inherit another.
Caesar will not rule us from the grave.
Search his villa down to the joists.
Find his will. Destroy it.
What are you doing?!
You have no right!
I will not leave and let you
destroy Caesar's house!
Let me go!
Let me go. Let me go!
You're lucky Cassius wants you brought to Rome.
Otherwise, we'd kill you now.
So, you've been with Tyrannus, the gladiator --
the one we saw fight?
He's protecting me.
So he says.
From what?
I'm not sure. I need to ask your father.
What?
He was with my uncle when he died
-- Tyrannus was.
He says...
He says Caesar told him to make me
the next ruler of Rome.
Well, he must have hit his head hard in the arena.
Or maybe you have.
What are you laughing at?
Nothing. I'm not!
It's not that funny.
I'm sorry.
God. I have to get some water.
Get my father and soldiers
and tell them Octavius is here.
- Hurry.
- I will.
So...
emperor...
When will your father be back?
Not too soon.
We have just enough time.
Caesar's blood is on my hands, mother.
Caesar's blood is on the senate's hands.
No.
I was his friend.
When I said yes, it convinced the others
our cause was just.
Your cause was just.
You saved the republic.
If we saved the republic,
why do we cower in our rooms,
afraid of the people we're
supposed to have liberated?
Why does the mob attack us
in the streets if we saved the republic?
Why are we down on our knees to Mark Anthony,
begging him to bring order?
You whine to me.
I was his lover.
No one consulted me in the deed.
But am I crying?
Caesar's dead, and the sun still rises,
and neither you nor anyone can bring him back.
While you lament the past,
other men take position in Rome's future.
You mean Cassius and Anthony.
I mean you, my son.
Why not you?
But you're so beautiful.
Who would want to kill you?
Your father --
if he sees us like this.
I think he's home.
We'd better get up.
What have you done?
He's in here!
There he is! Quick! Quick!
Idiot brat!
Imagine Caesar's pain to realize
he had no one for his heir but you.
I can -- I can reason with them.
No, you can't.
Cicero.
I got your message.
Have you heard anything?
Cassius is going to move your brother's
body out of a vault near the curia.
And what of Octavius?
Rumor has it, the gladiator Tyrannus protects him.
You were Caesar's friend.
We had our differences. You know that.
Yes.
But the Rome Cassius destroys is the one
that you and Caesar built together.
You in the senate, him on the battlefield.
You can't let that die.
But what can I do?
The conspirators huddle together in secret.
You can let Rome know the will of Caesar.
So a will does exist.
Will you help?
Cicero...
answer the call of Caesar one more time,
and help my son.
What stupidity!
Siding with an enemy of the republic.
The only enemy of the republic I see here is you.
If you knew how your days were numbered,
you wouldn't be so flippant.
- What are you doing?
- Out. Out!
Stand up.
Where is it?
Where is what?
You're trembling.
Caesar names his nephew.
Octavius.
He's just a boy.
So was Caesar once.
Caesar was a boy, yes.
But not every boy is a Caesar.
Forgive me.
I know the Vestal matriarch has sworn
the temple will not take sides.
I take sides only with the truth
that this will exists.
By my vows and duty, I'll keep it safe.
What is this place?
Where are we going?
Keep moving.
I won't just run away.
We're not.
I can clear this up.
Clear what up?
That you're Caesar's heir?
Stop saying that!
Look, what you think you heard from my uncle...
- What I heard.
- What you think you heard... it's impossible.
You don't know.
You didn't know him.
He despised me. That's the truth,
which anyone who knew him more
than 20 minutes could tell you.
So if we could just end this charade.
What are we doing here?
I'll show you.
Tell me how you'll reason
with the people who did this.
You don't listen to me.
Maybe you'll listen to him.
My gods.
He wouldn't want your pity.
He'd want your strength.
Thirty stab wounds.
And he never dropped that expression.
Fearless.
Giving nothing.
Full of scorn for those who did.
And in his dying breath,
maybe he did say something to you.
But...
But it was nothing compared to
what you left unsaid.
What you did call me.
To my face.
Your displeasure while you lived.
Frivolous.
Unworthy.
Inadequate. Beneath contempt.
Do you know that's what you called me, uncle?
The opposite of your heir.
Why do the gods steal glory from you now?
Defiled by the people you save.
You sacrificed for Rome...
your whole life long.
And this is how you're paid.
I so admired you, uncle.
I wanted to be like you.
I really did.
But if this is what happens to a Caesar...
I don't want greatness.
If this is your will,
I fail you yet again.
So, he is with you.
The next Caesar, as his uncle would have it.
He does not believe it.
Yes, well, his uncle's will leaves no doubt.
He needs to see it.
I left it in the Vestal temple for safekeeping.
Meet us there.
Please.
A dozen men in Rome desperate to rule,
and Caesar names him?
They're clearing the rabble from Porta Ostiensis.
Our little procession can exit
the City without a hitch.
And Anthony?
They say he's in mourning.
He plays with us.
We gave him his chance.
Let him regret he said no.
What's going on here?
What are you doing here?
Saying goodbye to an old friend. And you?
What would the public think of so many wounds?
And what would they see, a tyrant or a victim?
They won't see anything.
You think a cloth can hide what you've done?
You watch your tongue.
Caesar can't protect you now.
Do I need protecting in this free, new republic?
You can't erase what
you've done so easily, Cassius,
or what he's done.
Oh, how courageous to defend
him now that he's dead.
And where was your heroic voice
when he was alive?
I was shouting down real tyrants
when you were a child.
The senate hall you defiled with your knives,
I helped to build.
You're just a mouth that flaps.
Rome has no place for you.
You stay here, and you're as dead as Caesar.
I swear by the gods.
I'm on to you, grandmother.
Now, move.
The alley.
This way.
Something's wrong. Do you hear?
It's Anthony. We'll be torn to pieces.
Murderers!
Traitors!
Is this how the senate treats your Caesar?
Caesar! No!
Murderers!
- Back inside.
- No.
- Back inside. We'll be crushed!
- If we run and hide, then what?
Cowardice now, and we've lost forever.
Or we can face this and win.
Who told Anthony our plans?
Not one of us.
We should've given him his audience.
You do not give to Anthony.
He only understands strength.
And the mob?
What do they understand?
Shame on you!
Get Atia from her cell.
We'll use Caesar's sister to quiet this crowd.
Go.
This is no way to honor him.
Friends of Caesar...
listen to me.
You are here uninvited.
But you are here.
An aggravation to those who would try
to slip Caesar from this city unnoticed,
to deny us our grief at his passing
and to deny him the honor he is due.
I will not name them.
You know who they are.
The very same senators who, one month ago,
heaped accolades upon Caesar, all unasked for.
What is he doing?
Well, this is not about Caesar's rule. It's about Anthony's.
They offered him the title "emperor."
It was Caesar turned it down.
And now they call him...
tyrant...
despot...
and tell us we should be grateful
for the violence they do.
I was asked not long ago,
what did I want.
What was my price...
now that my friend is dead
and Rome is to be divided as spoils.
I said then, as I say now,
all I want is to honor this great Roman
as he deserves to be honored.
Is this how Caesar should be treated?
Hail, Caesar!
Hail, Caesar! Hail, Caesar! Hail, Caesar...
Stop this.
For you? Why should I?
For your brother.
For his beloved citizens,
who will be trampled if Anthony persists.
Stop this...
or perish in the dungeon.
The choice is yours.
What are you doing, Atia?
Speak to us!
My brother loved you.
He loved you, the people of Rome.
It was in you, a free and proud citizenry,
that he found the strength to do all he did.
In you.
Not in armies that tyrannize.
Not in political alliance forged for personal gain.
In you.
Everybody claims to know Caesar when it suits them.
But I did know him.
He was my brother, and I tell you,
he would be touched by your presence here.
But I must ask you to respect him now,
to think what he would want,
what he would do.
Caesar!
We loved Caesar!
I have seen his will.
The will of Caesar -- it exists.
And that will is Octavius --
Caesar's one true heir, Octavius!
Hail, Octavius!
Octavius!
If this will exists, you show me.
Why? So you and Cassius can both destroy it?
- That whore dies!
- Octavius?
It's not up to Caesar to anoint his successor.
They're calling his name.
You think I can't hear? Come on!
Move along, there! Get out of my way!
I'm a senator!
Get away from me!
There they are! There they are!
Move! Move! Keep moving!
They defile him.
No.
No!
They honor him.
They do.
I've seen it before in the arena -- felt it.
This is the mob.
Its affections...
your inheritance.
Hail, Caesar! Hail, Caesar! Hail, Caesar!
Witness the birth of a civil war.
An empire is dawning.
An empire built on the rage of the mob.
It is the mob who will determine
the next ruler of Rome.
You're too young to understand
what Caesar has started.
- His succession.
- Civil war.
The first volley was just fired.
And now, lists of enemies,
secret trials, heads on pikes.
It will take a century to rebuild
what has vanished here in an instant.
Rome, sacred Vestal, is dead.
No, Rome lives as long as that fire burns.
- You think so?
- Those are my vows.
You're lucky to have them.
As for the rest of us,
our path is highly uncertain now.
I shall be leaving Rome.
You will return.
No.
Reason has fled, and locusts swarm the City,
and my day is done.
You think I'm a coward, don't you?
No.
No. I think you're quite brave.
But these times may need
all of us to be braver still.
Cicero, is that it -- the will?
I don't want to see it.
Read it to him, then.
Read it and be done.
No!
Stop.
Consider your place.
Sit.
We met just a few days ago.
It seems a lifetime.
Yes.
They consumed him.
The crowd did.
Screaming his name.
And they were screaming for me.
But not you.
Caesar.
For in the eyes of the crowd,
you're already no longer yourself.
I don't want to be Caesar.
I'm sure you don't.
I was called by your uncle.
Did you know that?
At the age of six. That's when we start.
I was just taken from my home, placed here...
and my instruction began.
They told me it was an honor
to be one of the only six Vestals
in all of Rome. But it didn't feel like an honor.
Not at all.
I know what it is to feel overwhelmed.
And I know what goes with that
-- to feel unworthy.
But the decisions in this,
they're not ours to make.
As always I'm a Vestal, and always...
you will be Caesar.
- So it's true, then.
- Yes.
He names me successor.
He named you his son.
Gaius Octavius Caesar,
as if you were his own.
And this is his ring,
entrusted to us for safekeeping.
It's yours now, truly.
Take this, my friend.
The names of the few who will help.
Protect him.
Protect them.
Protect us all.
In the name of the senate, open this door.
There are horses outside the city wall, this way.
Are you mad? What are you doing?
This is a violation!
You two, check the storeroom!
You, the back!
This is sacrilege!
Don't you lay a finger on her!
What have you brought to us?
Where are we going?
Far from here.
Cicero has given us a place to begin.
Trust me.
I swore an oath.
You leave Rome a hunted boy,
but you'll return an emperor.
The smoke of the fires
has obscured the moon over Rome,
just as the lies of the senate
have hidden the truth.
Cassius wants the people to believe
that Caesar was a tyrant.
If no one refutes this, it will become history.
I am a Vestal virgin,
one of only six in all the world.
My duty is to tend to the sacred flame.
Vestals are forbidden to engage in politics.
Though I am a Vestal, I am a Roman first,
and I swear the people will know the truth.
By morning light, I will see Caesar's will
and testament nailed to every door in Rome.
Listen, listen.
Is it official?
Read it out loud.
10 denarii for the name of the traitor
that posted this!
Traitor?
No, no, no.
From here, where your strength lies.
Again.
You don't have to do this.
Go take care of your family.
My family is my business. Again.
They've probably reached Cyprus by now.
I don't want to speak of them...
ever.
Now, try again.
We'll be at Magonius' villa
before the end of the day.
Maybe Magonius is the wrong place
to look for support.
Cicero has him at the top of his list of likely allies.
So, tell me,
how do I convince a seasoned general
he should commit his army to me?
I thought you said you knew him.
From parties,
where I most likely tried to seduce his daughter.
No one expects you...
to win a war single-handedly.
Just tell this Magonius your plan
and let fate determine the rest.
What plan?
This gate should be locked.
What does a general have to fear?
Something's wrong.
You invade my home?!
I will see you all hanged!
The senate demands that you commit
the fourth legion to its defense.
If Cassius was man enough to demand it himself,
he'd leave here without his head.
You're in no position to make threats, Magonius.
I'm not in the habit of making threats.
And I will not be intimidated,
at least not by the likes of Cassius.
Sir, over here!
My slaves.
Back to the fields! Away from my house!
Farm slaves?
Take them, also.
I will not tolerate the confiscation of my property.
Oh, you'll tolerate a lot more
than that where you're headed.
Take him.
Right, sir.
Let's go.
Come on, come on.
Cassius, Caesar's will is on the street,
posted everywhere.
There are accusations that
a Vestal virgin distributed it.
Well, that sounds like an invention.
There are witnesses.
Did you know that he left the majority of his fortune
to the common people of Rome?
Well, he pandered to them
because he knew they were his only power base.
He cared what they thought of him.
What's your point?
Plebeians are on the street killing senators,
chanting, "assassins!"
That doesn't disturb you?
There's so much suffering in this room. Am I with a woman?
The mob must understand that
the senate, not Caesar, now rules.
We'll begin by appointing consuls
to replace him and Anthony --
Caesar loyalists that please the mob,
yet men we can control.
Taking Anthony's consulship is
like poking a caged tiger.
Good.
Let him understand that without us,
he has no legitimacy.
Let his hand be forced!
I am so sick of your fear!
Rapax, clean your feet.
You're paying a visit to the Vestal temple.
For you, Octavius.
Only the pontifex maximus of Rome
has authority here.
Is this the Vestal Camane?
I'm not hiding.
She will be taken into our custody
to determine whether she's an enemy of Rome.
No.
Bring her here.
Lay a hand on one of our order,
and you risk far worse than
your commander's displeasure.
If the citizens of Rome do not strike you down,
Vesta surely will.
Sir?
Expect a return visit.
What happens when I can
no longer protect you?
Move to the right! Keep moving!
Faster!
My dreams are filled with blood, with torture.
I cannot tell if it is Octavius' or my own.
I've defied the Vestal order by choosing sides.
If I am charged with treason,
the punishment is death.
I will be buried to the neck,
and my head broken with stones.
And if the senate finds Octavius,
his execution is certain.
Get in line!
Now's your opportunity.
Go on.
You!
Arrogant fool.
They're gladiators hired by the senate.
That money will run out.
Cassius doesn't understand that yet.
He's like a little boy with wooden soldiers.
Why is he doing this to you?
He wants the fourth legion,
like you do.
It's true.
I need your support.
Cicero suggested you might sway
your soldiers to join me.
I prefer not to discuss politics when I'm in chains.
I recommend you concentrate
on the problems at hand.
Quit talking, you two.
Keep walking.
Can't put a man of my station here.
Where are we?
the combat dungeons of Arkham.
This way, general.
Don't look at him.
Don't look at him!
Don't look at anyone.
They'll think I'm weak.
Those are gladiator chieftains,
choosing slaves for death in the ring.
This is a combat prison.
If you show any sign of courage,
you'll be selected to fight.
I'm sure they'd be easier adversaries than you.
As fresh meat, all they'll give you is
a wooden sword...
against that.
And if you survive, you're a gladiator.
Is that it?
99 out of 100 don't survive.
And don't turn your back on a chief.
It's a mark of disrespect.
Don't do anything that makes you stand out,
because if you do, they'll put you in the ring,
and in the ring, you will die.
Do you hear me?
Octavius?
This one's wearing oils.
They perfume their whores that way in the city.
You trying to make your masters sneeze,
pleasure boy?
Are you showing me your eyes?
I'll show you the faces of the gods
if I get the chance.
The next time your eyes see mine,
I'll be spitting in your dead mouth...
whore.
Mark Anthony has disappeared
and left Rome to burn.
The senate has no choice but
to strip him of his consulship.
In this vein, we nominate
the noble Cimber
and the noble Quintilius as our new leaders.
I thank you both most dearly, but
I must decline.
Decline?
I'm needed on my lands.
My cattle are diseased, you see?
Though, of course, it pains me to be robbed
of the privilege of serving as consul.
Very well.
I'm sure the economic stewardship
of Quintilius will leave us in good stead.
Who will partner noble Quintilius?
- I'm losing my vision.
- What?
I have these spots in my eyes.
I'm nearly blind.
The consulship would require too much reading.
It's impossible, I'm afraid.
I put forth Cassius and Brutus
to serve as consuls.
Oh, agreed.
Their guidance through this difficult period
has been both shrewd and statesmanlike.
Let's not game each other, gentlemen.
In the public's view, we are the killers
of their beloved Caesar.
I'm sure you good men will not ignore your duty.
You made this stew, Cassius.
Don't expect us to eat it.
Should any of you expect on going protection
from the rioters, alert us now.
The number of our guards is growing limited.
We wouldn't want to forget anyone.
I'm sure Quintilius and myself can
find suitable candidates for consul.
Just keep walking.
And for mercy's sake, keep your eyes down.
Hurry up!
Move yourselves!
No fight, no food.
Does it hurt?
Good.
Maybe pain will give you some sense.
I'm a Caesar.
I will not dishonor myself
by displays of cowardice.
You think suicide is brave?
You could have used your famous might
to stand with me,
which is supposed to be your job.
You don't understand. I'm known here.
By whom? No one recognizes you.
Not by my face.
But I fight in the style of a Cypriot.
If I engage in battle with this man,
I'll kill him,
and they'll soon identify me
as Tyrannus of Rome.
Then you are revealed to your enemies.
I cannot protect you here.
Drink.
I don't want your pampering, mother.
If I'm in the mood to nurture,
I suggest you take advantage of it.
Our general Rapax failed to deliver
the Vestal Camane as ordered.
- Has she fled the city?
- No.
His courageous soldiers refuse
to move against the sisterhood,
fearing the retribution of the goddess Vesta.
What authority will move them?
This can't go unpunished.
Caesar was pontifex maximus,
the highest religious authority in the state.
Like consul, it's one ofthe many offices
he held that now stands empty.
Since his death,
there's been no replacement.
But a new pontifex?
Can we do that?
Fetch us olives, mother.
Get your own olives.
I've examined the writs.
During times of great crisis,
the pontifex may be appointed by senate decree.
Your mother's a clever witch, Brutus.
Whom do you favor as the new pontifex?
Take your new hat
and solve my Vestal problem.
Now.
Awaken to die!
Which one of you will be today's fresh meat?
Give the general a seat of honor.
It could be his last.
You -- pleasure boy.
He stole that move from Tyrannus of Rome.
I saw Tyrannus do it in Cyprus.
I want his face!
Face! Face! Face! Face!...
The whore is my property!
If anyone should have his face on a sword,
it's me.
Fight! Fight! Fight! Fight!...
Fight me.
Spare him! Spare him! Spare him!...
He's spared.
Protect Octavius.
Not ready.
Teach him how to fight, my friend.
Teach him how to rule.
Hail Caesar!
That jackal guard will be around again soon.
So be it.
We don't get to pick which day's our last.
Dying is easy.
Keeping yourself alive is a task worthier of you.
My eyes are open, Tyrannus.
I'm unarmed and marked for death.
You don't know what you're marked for.
Pay attention.
My arm's extended straight.
Where am I weak?
I don't know.
You said your eyes were open. Now, use them.
- The elbow.
- Good.
You pull me forward, step to the outside.
Try it.
Again.
You're weak.
Better.
Good.
- Like with the sword, right?
- Mm-hmm.
My son Piso...
his lungs are weak.
I'm worried he'll catch cold on his journey.
It's my fault, all of it.
I should have kept my eyes down.
Leave me with your master, boy.
This is Gaul.
They use smaller tridents there.
And this...
a leopard's claws.
I'm unlucky with animals.
Especially when they've been
unleashed in an arena, hmm?
Like in Dalmatia?
I served in Caesar's armies
-- nothing more.
Be as mysterious as you like.
You still dropped your hands to me,
which means I'll have to do you over slow
and ugly next time.
Water!
Have you gotten word out of here?
Is someone coming for you?
I can't reveal myself.
Your companion -- clearly,
he's not some house slave. Who is he?
A gladiator of some renown.
His identity must be shielded here as well as mine.
A brave servant isn't enough in here, young Caesar.
Offer him up if you have to.
He'd be executed.
His beating was intended for me.
He sent his family into hardship for me.
You ask for my help,
for my legion.
Then show the resolve your uncle had
to do what is necessary.
Are you saying you'd betray a loyal soldier
who more than once saved your life?
I'm not claiming to be the next ruler of Rome.
You are.
Steel in a Caesar's sword is useful.
Steel in a Caesar's heart is imperative.
Go.
So, boy,
you know the general?
I'm his farm slave.
A noble man's son...
that's what you are.
without protection.
Do you know the mother tongue?
Because I will be answered when I speak.
I'll see your heart turned on a spit.
Well, come and get it!
You're worth more to me alive.
Leave us.
Noble pontifex.
I'm not a noble pontifex.
I'm a political actor, as are you,
in a drama that's fast becoming a farce.
Why did you post the will of a dead tyrant
on the doors of the senate?
A dead tyrant who counted you
amongst his friends, I thought.
Answer my question.
The people that loved Caesar
deserve to know his last wishes.
You must denounce Caesar's will
and throw your voice behind the senate.
My vow is to Vesta, and I will not displease her
by parroting the lies of assassins.
No sanctuary can protect you, girl,
if you are officially accused of treason.
Is there no mercy in your maiden's heart
for a man pulled between love
of his friend and duty...
to his republic?
Vesta has mercy
and love for such a man
but only if he alters course
-- if he decides to live in truth and honor.
Truth?
Yes, and honor.
An altar asking the gods' protection.
For whom?
And who placed it?
The Vestal virgin, untainted by the crass
self-interest of her senate counterparts,
- or a girl with a crush on a prince?
- How dare you!
Yield a public retraction, denounce Octavius...
or I will make this temple shake.
Senator Cassius, this way.
I kept him back here, senator.
Tyrannus.
Well, are the accommodations to your liking?
Could be better.
Or much worse.
If any harm comes to me, Cassius,
the fourth legion will never back you.
Which is why, despite whatever bickering
has kept us squabbling in the past,
today we have no choice but each other.
See, a lawless dictator,
whether Anthony or Octavius,
only enrich themselves and threaten
the landowners -- us.
Are we wrong to protect ourselves?
I want that legion.
Killing Caesar could have re-established the senate
as the true ruling force in Rome
if the right man had been holding the knife.
Instead, the senate got Cassius.
The other senators laughed at your dinner invitations,
and now you think they'll follow you to the servian walls?
You're a eunuch, Cassius.
And since harming me would threaten your interests,
I can follow my heart instead of my head.
I'll throw my lot in with the boy.
Cut him to pieces.
Tell them who I am. Save yourself.
I would have followed you.
Hail, Caesar.
For a general, he wasn't much of a strategist.
I'll have his legion for the senate,
and for the anguish he caused me,
this estate for myself.
I'll alert my gardener.
Tell him what you told me.
We arrested Magonius here with two slaves.
They arrived on horseback, one a boy.
Slaves on horseback?
Oh, of course.
Octavius and the gladiator.
This would be their first stop.
Assemble the men.
We're going back to Arkham.
Hail, Octavius Caesar,
Freedom, at the very least, I'd say,
though I think a few hectares of land
might be in order as well.
Don't bother.
You rich boys fold up and die in here
Your troubles will be over soon.
You won't do it.
What happened?
The chieftain --
he discovered my identity.
Did you hide the body?
Hmm?
Octavius, did you hide the body?
He barely made a sound after I hit him.
I'm a murderer.
Murderer, soldier, gladiator --
what's the difference in the end?
You did what was necessary.
Listen to me.
The new Rome that Julius Caesar imagined
before he died is worth protecting,
and so is his heir.
At least I've come to believe so.
Wash the blood off your hands
and wait for my signal.
You afraid of a fair fight?
No, I said a fair fight.
Tyrannus of Rome.
It can't be.
Fight!
What's happening here?
Find Octavius! That's all that matters!
There! There's his bodyguard!
Where is he?
Where's Octavius?
Stop, Rapax.
All right, stop.
Put down your weapons.
Stand back!
Tell them.
There's two horses behind me.
Release all the other ones.
Now!
I should kill you for what you did to my uncle.
Oh, do that, by all means.
See how far you get.
One step at a time.
You'll never be Caesar!
Just tell me which senator
accepted the position.
It's complicated.
I'm not sure you realize the hesitancy.
The concern.
Stripping Mark Anthony of his consulship --
only a certain type of person would volunteer.
Who is it, then?
Someone from the outer provinces?
You couldn't find a senator
who wanted to be consul?
Please don't tell me it's a mayor.
The mayors value their lives
as much as the senators, it seems.
Who am I about to anoint leader
of the Roman republic and Roman army?
These are the aqueduct commissioners
of the servian wall,
Herteus and Panza.
The gods test me.
By emergency decree of the senate,
I here by appoint you, Herteus, and you, Panza,
to be co-consuls of the republic of Rome.
Don't miss, boy. I'm hungry.
You do it. I've had my fill of blood.
Whatever happens now, stay close to me.
But it's Mark Anthony.
Just stay close.
No more running, prince.