http://www.stephenkingshortmovies.com
& " Stephen King Short Movies" &
Subtitles by Cobra35
Fixed by Listening
"Sorry for Any Misunderstanding"
& All That You Love Will Be Carried Away &
Alfred Zimmer.
Friends call me Alfie,
Alfie Zimmer.
Room 19.
Allright.
- Mind if I tell you something?
- Not at all.
I've been selling in the
Midwest for twenty years,
and I have formulated four basic rules
for securing my night's rest.
One, always reserve ahead.
Two, always reserve at a franchise motel
if it all possible - your Holiday Inn,
your Ramada Inn, your
Confort Inn, your Motel 6.
Three, always get a room on the end.
That way, you only have is
one set of noisy neighbors of at all.
Four, always get a room that starts with a one.
Do you know why?
Why is that?
Because, I'm forty-four years old, too
old to be fucking truck-stop whores,
eating chicken-fried steak,
or hauling my luggage upstairs.
Okee Dokie.
Of course, the problem with
rooms that begin with a one...
...is that they're all
non-smoking these days.
So, I have a rule for that, too.
Ask for'em and smoke anyway.
Save Russian Jews.
Collect valuable prizes.
& FROZEN FOOD &
There is a market for gourmet foods
in Nebraska, Iowa, Oklahoma, Kansas;
even in the Dakotas, although
you might not believe it.
I've done quite well, especially
over the last two years...
as I've gotten to know the
market's deeper creases- but...
it's never going to equal the market for,
let's say, fertilizer.
Is it possible that behind those lights,
some farmer's wife is even now heating
up a pot of Cottager Split Pea Soup.
Or perhaps micro-waving a Cottager
Shepherd's Pie or Chicken Francais?
It is. It's as possible as Hell.
Her husband watches the early
news with his shoes off...
...and his socked feet on a hassock,
...and overhead their son plays
a video game on his Game Cube...
...and their daughter lies on a bed,
kicking her feet behind
her, reading Harry Potter.
Can I help you?
I just dropped by for a dinner.
That sounds a good
great idea. Come on in.
Can I help you?
Save Russian Jews.
Collect valuable prizes.
Can I help you?
Ma'am, according to at least
one source I've read recently,
'All that you love
will be carried away.'
Maybe then I could offer her...
...a sample box of Cottager
brand quick-serve gourmet foods.
Maybe she'd have
a particular taste for caviar.
Many did.
Even in Ohio.
Alfie Zimmer.
Frozen gourmet foods.
Charles More... Fertilizer.
- Yeah, I can tell you, remembered
the truck.  - Right.
How about that botany
make up around Mansfield?
You get called in there?
Yeah. Truck dropped that tassel.
I missed my last meeting.
You know why?
I already know
what it looks like inside this room.
It's square.
The walls are white.
On one wall is a picture of daylilies,
orchids or something.
It's cold in there right now,
but if I hit that "High Heat"
button on the Climatron,
it'd heat up real fast,
probably become too hot.
There are twin-beds, identical
gold bed spreads on each one,
first tucked under the pillows
and then pulled back over them,
so that they resemble
corpses of infants.
On the table beside the bed
there is a flesh colored phone,
a Gideon Bible.
In the bathroom,
if you turn on the light,
you get the fan, too.
There is no way around there.
And then, the smell.
Can come a harsh chemical
cleansers' smell...
...next with the mildew
on the shower curtain.
It's the room of my dreams.
I bought this notebook
seven years ago...
...in the stationary department of some
five-and-dime in Omaha or Sioux City...
- ...for a dollar and nine cents.
& "Elvis killed big pussy." &
& I suckt Jim Morrison's cock
w/my poutie boy mouth.
(Lawrence, KS) &
Restrooms are filled
with homosexual graffiti,
most of it tiresome
and repetitive,
but "poutie boy mouth"
is pretty good.
Poopie doopie you so loopy.
(Papillion, NEB)
I'm crazy about that one.
Something about the "-ie, -ie,"
and then, boom, you got "-y".
It could be no more than
an illiterate's mistake,
but why think like that?
What fun would that be?
No, I prefer to believe
that "-ie, -ie"...
...wait for it... "-y" was
an intended construction.
Something sneaky
but playful,
with the feel of an
"E.E. Cummings" poem.
Two today.
I found two today.
Two in one day.
Two on the last day.
Like some sort of omen.
& Save Russian Jews
Collect Valuable Prizes &
& All That You Love Will Be Carried Away. &
So many... so many entries
recalling thousands of truck stops...
...and roadside chicken shacks
and highway rest areas...
...the way certain songs
on the radio...
...can bring back specific
memories of a place, or a time...
...or the person you were with,
what you were drinking,
what you were thinking...
& Here I sit, I'm at a loss,
trying to shit out taco sauce. &
& I know I'm going to drop a load,
only hope I don't explode. &
& My mother made me a whore. &
& If I supply the yarn,
will she make me one? &
I started collecting
bits of graffiti...
...without at first
knowing why I was doing it.
They were just amusing,
or disconcerting,
or both at the same time.
Yet, little by little I became fascinated
with these messages from the innerstate,
where the only other communications
seem to be dipped headlights...
...when you passed in the rain,
or maybe somebody in a bad
mood flipping you the bird...
...when you went by in the passing lane
pulling a roaster-tail of snow behind you.
I came gradually to see...
- or perhaps only hope -
that something was
going on here.
The E. E. Cummings' lilt of
"Poopie doopie you so loopy",
for instance, or the
inarticulate rage...
...of 1380 West Avenue.
Kill my mother.
TAKE HER JEWELS.
Or take this oldie:
Here I sit, cheeks a flexin',
giving birth to another Texan.
The meter,
when you consider it, is odd.
Is not iambs, but some
odd triplet formula...
...with the stress on the third.
Here I sit, cheeks a flexin',
giving birth to another Texan.
Of course, it broke down
a little towards the end.
I thought on many occasions
I could go back to school,
take some courses, get all that
feet-and-meter stuff down pat.
Know that
I was talking about...
...instead of running on
a tightrope of intuition.
All I really remember clearly
from the school is iambic pentameter.
"To be or not to be,
that is the question."
& The real question is
who your father was, dipstick. &
I had thought about
writing a book once.
Just a little one.
The first title that
occurred to me was...
"Don't Look Up Here, You're
Pissing On Your Shoes"...
...but you couldn't call a book that.
Not and reasonably hope someone...
...could put it out for
sale in a store anyway.
And, besides, that was light.
Frothy.
I became convinced over the years
that something was going on here.
The title I finally decided
on was an adaptation of...
...something I'd seen in a
rest-area stall outside Fort Scott,
Kansas, on Highway 54.
I Killed Ted Bundy: The Secret
Transit Code of America's Highways,
by Alfred Zimmer.
That sounded mysterious
and ominous,
almost scholarly.
But I hadn't done it.
I'm just a little man,
after all,
with a little man's job.
I sell things.
A line of frozen dinners currently.
And now, of course...
...now.
Hi, it's me.
I'm in Wentworth.
Remember the casserole...
...you were gonna
take over to my mother.
She is expecting it, so...
Oh, she asked for
the Red Ball coupons.
I know you think she's
crazy on that subject,
but go ahead and humor her,
okay? She's old.
Tell Carlene that
Daddy says, "Hi".
I love you.
It's me again.
Don't forget Rambo's appointment
at the vet day after tomorrow, okay?
And the sea-jerky strips at night.
They really do help his hips.
Bye.
Okee Dokie.
The first thing anyone  would
see, responding to the shot,
would be my dead body of course,
my head hanging down and
bleeding on the nubbly rug.
The second thing, however,
would be the Spiral notebook.
Watch the blood.
"All that you love...
will be carried away."
Frank, looks like this nutjob
left a suicide note.
"Elvis killed big pussy."
I think we're lucky...
...this guy didn't decide to
visit a schoolyard with an AK-47.
Take a bunch of little kids.
But, I'm not crazy,
and the things I've written here
over the years aren't crazy, either.
I'm convinced of it.
They'll think I'm crazy...
...if they find this
notebook, though. They will.
And is that fair to
Maura or Carlene?
Carlene who's at her
j.v. basketball game right now?
No, of course not.
But, there's nothing fair about
what happened to me, either.
Sometimes when you're
cruising along the highway,
you see big curls of rubber
that have unwound from...
...the recap tires some of
the independent truckers use.
That's what I feel like.
Thrown tread.
The pills make it worse.
They clear your mind just enough
to see what a colossal jam you're in.
It's an embarrassment to me
if they find the notebook,
and I can't explain
the reasons behind it.
If I can't explain that
there is something profound...
...within the context
of these messages.
It would be like accidentally
hanging yourself in the closet...
because you were experimenting
with a new way of jerking off and...
...got found that way with your shorts
under your feet and shit on your ankles.
Behind the picture, maybe?
That might work.
But they'll still find the pills
in my coat pocket.
They're prescription, sure,
but not the sort the doctor
gives you if you're feeling sunny.
And if they find the pills,
they'll look harder.
Then, the things inside my
notebook will look worse,
even crazier, because of the
pains I'd taken to hide it.
I'll throw it in
Farmer John's field.
Soon, he'll come out
this way on his tractor,
the cab filled with music of
Patty Loveless or Larry Underwood,
or maybe even Clint Black and he will plow
the notebook under without seeing it...
...and it will disappear
into the scheme of things.
Someone in Cameron, Missouri
had once written:
"Relax, it's all just the rinse cycle."
See, a shot in the mouth
would be easier than any living change.
Far easier than struggling
to write a book few people,
if any at all,
are likely to read.
I'll count down from sixty.
If the light in the kitchen comes
on by the time I reach one...
I'll write the book.
In order to write a book like that,
you'd have to begin by talking about...
...how it was to measure
distance in green mile markers,
and the very width of land,
and how the wind sounded when
you got out of your car...
...at one of those rest areas
in Oklahoma or North Dakota.
How it sounded almost like words.
You'd have to explicate
that silence,
and how the badrooms
always smelled of piss...
and the great hollow farts
of departed travelers,
and how in that silence the
voices on the walls began to speak.
The voices of those who had written
and then moved on.
That telling...
...that would hurt,
but if the wind drops and the
spark lights of the farm come back,
I'll do that anyway.
If they don't,... well.
Either way.
Sixty.
Fifty nine...
Fifty eight...
Fifty seven...
Fifty six...
Fifty five...
Fifty four...
Fifty three...
Fifty two...
Fifty one...
Fifty...
Fourty nine...
Fourty eight...
Fourty seven...
Fourty six...
Fourty five...
Fourty four...
Fourty three...
Fourty two...
Fourty one...
Fourty...
Thirty nine...
Thirty eight...
Thirty seven...
Thirty six...
Thirty five...
Thirty four...
Thirty three...
& Based on a story by Stephen KING &
- Thirty two...
- Thirty one...
Thirty...
Twenty nine...
Subtitles by Cobra35
Fixed by Listening
"Sorry for Any Misunderstanding"