Mutants. Since the discovery
of their existence,
they have been regarded
with fear, suspicion, often hatred.
Across the planet debate rages.
Are mutants the next link
in the evolutionary chain?
Or simply a new species of humanity,
fighting for their share of the world?
Either way, it is an historical fact
sharing the world has never been
humanity's defining attribute.
"We are not enemies, but friends.
We must not be enemies."
"Though passion may have strained,
it must not break the bonds of our affection."
Lincoln said that in his first inaugural
address as our nation's 16th president.
It's one of my favourites.
SO, if you'll please have your tickets ready,
we can begin the tour.
Jackie, could you clear my schedule this evening?
I wanna have dinner with my son.
Yes, Mr President.
Excuse me, sir. Are you lost?
Perimeter breach at visitors' checkpoint.
Multiple subjects.
Mr President, security breach. Jackie, leave.
Let's get him out to the car.
Exits not clear.
We don't know how many they are.
Both sides secure.
- Something's in the corridor.
- To the shelter.
Negative! Not clear.
- It's outside the Oval Office.
- Lock this place down.
Don't shoot!
My God.
Neanderthals. We once believed that
they were wiped out by years of conflict
with the much more advanced branch
of humanity called Cro-Magnon man,
but recent research into our DNA suggests
that these two species may have interbred,
evolving into modern humans.
In other words, into what?
- Us.
- Us. Right.
Artie.
Not here.
Come on. Pay attention.
...makes me insane when she does this...
What are you looking at? Sick...
To the shelter.
They're gonna kill him.
Jean? You OK?
Yeah. Yeah, I'm fine.
It's just uh... just a headache.
It's not just a headache, is it?
Listen, uh, I wasn't really sure how to say this,
but you know ever since Liberty Island you've been...
- Scott.
- You've been different.
My telepathy's been off lately.
I can't focus. I can hear everything.
Jean, it's not just your telepathy. A month ago you had to concentrate just to levitate a book or a chair across the room.
Now when you have a nightmare
the entire bedroom shakes.
My dreams are getting worse.
Scott,
I keep feeling
something terrible's about to happen.
I would never let anything happen to you.
Hey, have you guys seen Bobby and Rogue?
Something's happening in the food court.
- My brother asked you a simple question.
- Why are you being such a dick?
Yeah, why are you being such a dick?
Because I can.
Can I have a light?
- Sorry. Can't help you out, pal.
- John, knock it off.
- Why don't you stop showing off?
- Uh, for her?
- I can't help it if your girl friend's getting excited.
- I don't think she's getting excited.
- Don't get shook up, We're trying to have a good time here, all right?
- I think you're the only one having a good time.
That's real cute, man.
What are you gonna do?
Suddenly you're not so tough.
Hello!
Honey, can you hear me?
Bobby, what did you do?
I didn't do this.
No. I did.
And the next time
you feel like showing off, don't.
- Breaking news.
- We're coming to you live from Washington,
where there's been an attack
in the Oval Office of the White House.
Details are still coming in, but we have been informed
that the President and vice President were not harmed.
Sources say the attack involved
one or more mutants...
- I think it's time to leave, Professor.
- I think you're right.
- In my opinion, Magneto's behind this.
- No, I don't think so, Scott.
While Eric's capable of organizing
something like this from prison,
for him it would be irrational,
it will only hurt his goal of mutant prosperity.
- You mean superiority.
- You're right, if Eric had his way.
And of course, he knows how the Government will
respond, they will reintroduce the Registration Act.
Or worse.
The president could declare a state of emergency,
place every mutant in the country under arrest.
- Do you think the assassin is working alone?
- Probably we will only know that if we find him before the authorities do.
I've been trying to track him using Cerebro,
but his movements are inexplicably erratic.
When I have exact coordinates, Storm, Jean,
I'll need you to take the jet and try pick him up.
It was close, wasn't it?
Closer than anyone's admitted.
- What do you need, William?
- Just your authorisation for a special operation.
No, thank you, Mr President.
And somehow I thought you were here
to talk about school reform.
Funny you should say that, Mr President.
- Senator.
- Mr President. Thank you for having me.
- Senator Kelly, this is Colonel William Stryker.
- How do you do?
His department has been dealing with the
mutant phenomenon since... before my time.
As I recall, you were a staunch supporter
of the Registration Act, Senator.
But it seems your ideas on
the mutant problem have changed recently.
For the best, I hope.
So what are you proposing, Mr Stryker?
May I, Mr President?
We've managed to gather evidence
of a mutant training facility
in the Salem region of upstate New York.
Where did you get this information?
Interrogation of one of the mutant terrorists
from the Liberty Island incident.
Eric? Eric Lehnsherr?
- You have access to him?
- Magneto, yes.
We developed the technology
that built his plastic prison.
- This facility is a school.
- Sure it is.
- What the hell is that?
- A jet.
- What kind of jet?
- We don't know.
But it comes up out of the basketball court.
If we'd been allowed to do our jobs,
Mr President, before this incident...
All right, listen.
William, you enter, you detain, you question,
but the last thing we need to see is the body
of a mutant kid on the six o'clock news.
- Mr Stryker?
- Senator Kelly.
This is Yuriko, my personal assistant.
- Quite a handshake.
- What can I do for you?
Uh, Eric Lehnsherr's prison.
I'd like to arrange a visit if possible.
It isn't a petting zoo, Senator.
In this conflict he is the enemy, you're just a
spectator, so why don't you sit this one out, all right?
Conflict? Mr Stryker, do you really
want to turn this into some kind of war?
I was piloting black ops missions
in the jungles of north Vietnam
while you were sucking on
your mama's tit at Woodstock, Kelly.
Don't lecture me about war.
This already is a war.
- You're dead. You're so dead.
- You're dead.
I don't wanna hurt you.
I'm not afraid.
Logan.
You miss me, kid?
Not really.
- How are you doing?
- I'm OK. How are you?
- Who's this?
- This is Bobby. He's my...
I'm her boyfriend.
Call me Iceman.
Right.
Boyfriend? So how do you guys...?
Well, we're still working on that.
Look who's come back. Just in time.
For what?
- We need a baby-sitter.
- Baby-sitter?
Nice to see you again, Logan.
Hi, Logan.
Hi, Jean.
Uh, I should go and get the jet ready.
Yeah, well, it's good to meet you.
- Come on, let's go.
- Bye, Logan. I'll see you later.
Storm and I are heading to Boston.
We won't be gone long.
The professor wants us to track down
a mutant who attacked the President.
So it was a mutant.
You'll be here when we get back,
unless you plan on running off again.
Well, I could probably think of
a few reasons to stick around.
Find what you were looking for, Logan?
More or less.
I'll see you boys later.
- Be safe, OK?
- You too. Bye.
See ya.
Aren't you gonna welcome me home?
Your bike needs gas.
Then fill her up.
Mr Laurio, how long can we keep this up?
- How long is your sentence?
- Forever.
Not necessarily forever, Mr Lehnsherr.
Just until I've got all that I need.
Mr Stryker, how kind of you to visit.
Have you come back to ensure the taxpayers'
dollars are keeping me comfortable?
Done. You can go.
Now...
Mr Lehnsherr.
I'd like to have one final talk
about the house that Xavier built
and the machine called Cerebro.
Logan, my tolerance for your smoking
in the mansion notwithstanding,
continue smoking that in here
and you'll spend the rest of your days
under the belief that you're a six-year-old girl.
- Can you do that?
- I'd have Jean braid your hair.
Welcome back.
- You want me to leave?
- No. Just don't move.
These lights represent
every living person on the planet.
The white lights are humans.
And these are the mutants.
Through Cerebro I'm connected to them,
and they to me.
You see, Logan?
We're not as alone as you think.
I found the base at Alkali Lake.
There was nothing there.
The broken line represents the path
of the mutant who attacked the president.
I've been finding it difficult to get a lock on it.
Well, can't you just concentrate harder?
If I wanted to kill him, yes.
There.
Looks like he's finally stopped running.
I need you to read my mind again.
Logan,
- I'm afraid the results will be the same as before.
- We had a deal.
The mind is not a box can be simply unlocked
and opened. It's a beehive with a million...
Spare me the lectures.
I have no doubt that your amnesia, your adamantium
skeleton, the claws are all somehow connected, but...
Logan, sometimes the mind
needs to discover things for itself.
I promise you we'll talk again when I return.
Oh, if you would be kind enough
to watch over the children tonight.
Scott and I are going to visit an old friend.
I'm sending the coordinates
of where the mutant's settled.
As soon as you find him,
bring him back to the mansion.
- Let's hope he cooperates.
- Yes, for his sake. Good luck.
Stryker, William.
What are you doing in here?
Garbage.
These are the coordinates.
He's a teleporter. Must be why
the professor had trouble locking onto him.
We're not here to hurt you.
We just wanna talk.
- Are you bored yet?
- Oh, yeah.
Sure you don't wanna come down?
- You have him?
- He's not going anywhere.
Are you?
Please don't kill me.
I didn't mean to harm anyone.
Why would people
have gotten that impression?
- What's your name?
- Wagner. Kurt Wagner.
There was so much shooting, such fear.
And then there was only pain.
I could see it all happening,
but I couldn't stop myself.
It was like a bad dream.
Perhaps he is testing me.
And before you were in the White House,
what do you remember?
Nothing.
I was here.
- I'd rather get him back to the professor.
- The professor?
Did you do these yourself?
And what about this?
- I need you to read my mind again.
- I'm afraid the results will be the same as before.
- You'll be indestructible.
- No memory.
Sometimes the mind needs
to discover things for itself.
Wolverine.
No memory. You'll have no memory.
The dozen tourists in the
White House during the attack
are still being held for questioning.
... best tasting food,
and machine that so darn easy to...
The President will address the nation...
For the White House assassin,
following hundreds of...
Can't sleep?
How can you tell?
Cos you're awake.
Right. How about you?
I don't sleep.
... Science Museum are claiming to experience...
Hey.
- Doesn't anybody sleep around here?
- Apparently not.
- Got any beer?
- This is a school.
- So that's a no?
- Yeah, that's a no.
- Is there anything other than chocolate milk?
- There should be some soda in the small cupboard.
- Thanks.
- No problem.
I'll take him from here.
It's all right, Scott.
- Nice shades.
- Thanks.
Charles Xavier.
Have you come to rescue me?
Sorry, Eric, not today.
To what do I owe the pleasure?
The assassination attempt on the President.
What do you know about it?
Nothing.
Only what I read in the papers.
You really shouldn't have to ask, Charles.
What's happened to you?
I've had frequent visits from William Stryker.
You remember him, don't you?
William Stryker.
His son, Jason, was once
a student of yours, wasn't he?
Yes. Years ago.
Unfortunately, I wasn't able to help him.
At least, not in the way that his father wanted.
And now you think that taking in Wolverine will
make up for your failure with Stryker's son?
- How long you been here?
- A couple of years.
And your parents just sent you off
to mutant school?
Actually, my parents think
this is a prep school.
Oh I see. Well, I suppose lots of prep
schools have their own dorms, campuses...
Jets.
- So you and Rogue, huh?
- Yeah.
I mean it's not what you think
I'd like it to be, but it's just...
It's just that it's not easy when you
wanna be closer to someone, but you can't.
You know, I've seen how you look at Dr Grey.
Excuse me?
Nothin'.
- You haven't told him about his past, have you?
- I've put him on the path.
Logan's mind is still fragile.
Is it?
Or are you afraid of losing
one of your precious X-Men, old friend?
Eric, what have you done?
I'm sorry, Charles.
I couldn't help it.
What have you told Stryker?
Everything.
The war has begun.
Scott!
You should have killed me
when you had the chance.
But now and then
every mother needs to get away.
Without her, the babies are helpless.
Sensing danger, the mother rat races home.
The babies can't even see the killer.
As someone uninvited is coming to dinner.
Hi.
- What is it?
- Shh.
You picked the wrong house, bud.
You all right?
Stay here.
- This way.
- Let's go.
John! Where's Rogue?
- I don't know.
- I gotta find her.
- Open it.
- Here, take her.
Go on, get in. Let's go. Come on.
Take him. He's stunned.
- I can help you.
- Help them.
- Rogue!
- Bobby!
This way.
Come on. Everybody, follow me up here.
Move.
Come on.
Let's go.
Come on, this way.
This is it.
Logan.
- You wanna shoot me, shoot me.
- Don't shoot him.
Not yet.
Wolverine?
Well I must admit this is certainly
the last place I'd expect to find you.
How long has it been? 15 years?
You haven't changed one bit.
Me, on the other hand...
Nature.
Wait, wait, you guys. We've gotta do something.
They're gonna kill him.
- He can handle himself. Let's go.
- Bobby.
Please.
I didn't realise Xavier was taking in animals,
even animals as unique as you.
Who are you?
Don't you remember?