(Man) Listen up, guys.
This is our last opportunity.
If we don't find something this time,
we've gotta wrap it all up.
Mario, it should curve off
to your left just ahead.
(Mario) Sì, Professore. Sì.
(Foghorn)
(Man) Now it should be straight ahead.
Good. Very good.
Buongiorno, Don Vito.
What do we have?
It's the last dive, signore.
Hopefully we will find something.
And I pay hundreds of thousands of euro
for clues on updated maps
of Marco Polo.
Perhaps his methods aren't so updated.
He's old! And useless.
(Sighs)
- (Rumbling)
- What's that?
Nothing.
Nothing. Let's go.
According to the map, there should be
a passageway right here.
There it is! Follow me.
(Sighs)
Yes. Artefacts.
We're getting very close now.
Wait. There's something ahead here.
It's a plaque of some sort.
It dates to the correct time period.
The inscription is in Latin.
Dio mio!
"Ingredi mortuus."
Here walk the dead.
The Medicis.
Confirming coordinates.
Grazie, Marco Polo!
(Screams)
Professore, get out!
Paolo, Mario, shark in the water!
- Shut up!
- What? Say again. You're breaking up.
What are you talking about?
The chamber should be
roughly 100 metres ahead.
(Screaming)
(Shrieks)
The water is very murky here.
The visibility is limited.
(Yells)
(Distorted signal)
(Voice trembling)
Professore, what's happening?
(Rapid beeping)
He's dead.
These images you're seeing now
were taken on an expedition
that I was on about four years ago.
This is the Andrea Doria.
She is another..."unsinkable" ship
that went down in 1956.
Sits at a depth of about 250 feet
in a place that, trust me,
most of you would not wanna be.
250 feet? Please.
Would you care to elaborate on that
rather astute comment, Mr Jensen?
I can dive 400 feet with my eyes closed,
no problem.
I'll bet you could jump
the very same distance
- with your eyes closed right off a cliff, too.
- (Laughter)
You see, kids, it's not only
the attitude or ego
that Mr Jensen is displaying right now
that causes most of the accidents
on expeditions just like this one.
It's not only about the depth or,
in Mr Jensen's case, size.
(Laughter)
Ocean weather around the Doria
that can go from one minute
completely calm and clear,
to the next minute, ripping currents that
can toss this 30,000-tonne ship like a toy.
And if that were not enough,
inside the ship's very dark corridors
can become like a maze or,
for some divers in the past, a tomb.
Many have lost their lives
inside this ship.
And if that weren't enough,
then of course there's...
the sharks.
No problem. Right, Mr Jensen?
(Knock on door)
You guys review chapter four.
I'll be back in one minute.
David, there's been an accident in Venice.
- Is my dad all right?
- He was on a dive.
Two of his colleagues are dead
and he's missing.
- What happened?
- Looks like a propeller accident.
- I knew I shouldn't have let him go.
- He could never take no for an answer.
- I'd better get over there.
- All right, David.
We'll take care of all your expenses.
Just keep us posted.
Oh, baby... I just heard.
I'm so sorry.
- Are you OK?
- Yeah, I guess so.
- What do you wanna do?
- I've gotta go.
- I'm coming, too.
- Sure you can get out of your classes?
I'm not letting you go through this alone.
Come on, let's go.
It's beautiful here.
Yeah, I know.
And look where we gotta go.
(Speaking Italian)
Capisce. Capisce.
Dr Franks? Lieutenant Sofia Totti
of the Venice Police.
My fiancée, Laura.
We're very sorry for what happened
to your father, sir.
What happened?
Well, it appears that your father
and two of his colleagues
were diving in a restricted area.
And, er... a boat hit them
as they were surfacing.
Now, is either of these two men
your father?
(Sighs)
No.
What did you say was the cause of death?
I didn't. But we were informed it was
a boat propeller from one of the buses.
But you don't believe that?
- Well, that was the report.
- Oh, this was no propeller.
- What do you mean?
- Well, if what happened to these two men
happened in water, then, Lieutenant Totti...
this was a shark.
I've done enough work in water
and seen enough attacks
to know that these lacerations
were not caused by any boat.
When we perform the autopsy
we will know for sure.
Well, thank you, Dr Franks.
My boss would like to see you, so if
you could just come down to the station
to fill out some paperwork,
that would be great.
Thank you.
(Talking, phones ringing)
- (Knock on door)
- (Man) Prego.
Ah. Benvenuti.
- I'm Captain Bonasera.
- Nice to meet you.
Welcome. Please, sit.
- I would like to convey my condolences.
- What for, Captain?
Mr Franks, your father
was diving in a restricted area.
With no permits and no insurance.
What he was doing was... illegal.
I just wanna go look for him.
We have already searched
the entire area.
It would mean a lot to my family.
I am afraid...
that would require special permission,
which...
Maybe the American embassy
can get involved to help expedite that.
Very well. On three conditions.
One, you have 48 hours.
Two, you will sign
a confidentiality agreement,
which includes no speaking to the press.
And three, Lieutenant Totti here
will accompany you...
at all times.
Agreed. Thank you, Captain.
One more thing, Mr Franks.
I hear you are talking about... sharks.
We do not have sharks in Venice.
Capisce?
Why is everyone so against the idea
of a shark attack?
Well, you must understand
the implications, Dr Franks.
Our streets are not like any other
in this world. They are canals.
To suggest that there is killer sharks
swimming in them
could have serious repercussions.
I'm gonna go on a dive,
so I'm gonna need a boat and another diver.
Well, it'll take a couple of hours
to organise that.
We can go to my dad's place
in the meantime.
(Bell chiming)
Oh, my God.
It looks like somebody's been here.
(David) Why am I not surprised?
What was your father
doing in Venice, anyway?
Working for the university.
On what?
An underwater excavation.
I don't have all the details.
- Are you sure it was legal?
- That's not important right now.
What is is who did this
and why you don't know about it.
- Who says we don't?
- Well, you never said anything.
Laura.
Give me a second.
What do you think
they were looking for, David?
I'm not sure. But knowing my dad,
whatever it was...
I'll bet it's still here.
What do you mean?
Dad has always been rather...
meticulous.
Oh, Dad.
Some things never change.
I knew it.
Help me with this table, would you?
What's all this?
Herein lieth...
the rub.
It's my father's notes.
"The eighth crusade,
sponsored by Louis XIV,
- "led by the Medici brothers..."
- (Father)... the Medici brothers,
three Venetian knights who assembled
an army of crusaders
that marched across Europe,
cutting a swath of destruction
and death.
They pillaged and plundered
everything in their path
on their way to the old Byzantine
port city of Antonia.
There, for 20 days and 20 nights,
they laid siege to the city.
The fighting was furious
but the Antonians were no match
for the ruthless invaders.
When the battlements were breached,
the city fell.
The streets ran red with blood
on their merciless quest.
(Shrieking)
They tortured anyone and everyone.
And if they did not get
the information they wanted...
Legend has it that
the Medicis knew of the existence
of King Solomon's treasures in Antonia,
which had been transported
centuries earlier on a galleon called Stella.
The Medicis' cruelty
and inhumanity paid off.
They found the entrance
to the long-lost tomb.
And inside
found what so many had thirsted for.
They plundered the King's chamber,
and with the help of Marco Polo's fleet,
brought the treasures by boat
back to Venice.
There were those who wanted
what the Medicis had.
The brothers hid the treasure
underneath the floating city
and murdered all those
who helped them bury it.
Shortly after,
they were murdered themselves
and the treasure was lost again.
Sounds like some kind of wishful fantasy.
Pieces of the Medici treasure
have been recovered, but very few.
- How would you know?
- She's an expert.
In the medieval time period.
She's... really smart.
Let me see.
This looks like some kind of coordinates.
Probably something
Dad was searching for.
(Bell chiming)
Continue on to your left.
OK. We go.
I think we're getting close.
Is this where the accident happened?
Well, we don't know exactly, cos the
bodies were recovered six hours later.
- They floated with the current.
- Oh, that makes it easy.
What do you mean?
Divers getting killed by
an unknown propeller, an unknown boat.
Chalk it up to an accident.
No questions, no answers needed.
You should be careful what you're implying.
Well, maybe you should be a little
less sloppy with your investigation.
- It was an accident.
- Oh.
And the ransacking of the apartment -
was that an accident, too?
Laura... let's concentrate on
us getting in the water.
Just be careful. I don't want another
accident to happen to you, too.
I'm gonna be very quick. Don't worry.
- Anything on sonar?
- It's a little murky.
Well, yes, unfortunately, our canals
are also known for their pollution.
That's why accidents happen.
Well, we'll have a pin-camera
and a transmitter with us.
You can track us with the sonar.
OK, signore, we stop now.
- All right. Transmitter on.
- (Bleeping)
- Receiving.
- Let's go.
- It's really narrow, Dr Franks.
- No, it's OK. It opens up just ahead.
- How's the read, baby?
- Visual's good. Sonar's clean.
I'm at the entrance of
some kind of tunnel.
Let's go.
I think it's this way.
Huh? No. This way.
How's the signal, Laura?
(Occasional bleeping)
Getting weaker.
I wouldn't go too much further.
My dad's watch.
Dr Franks, where are you? I've lost you.
David, Pietro, d'you copy?
- Shit.
- Here. I'll keep trying the radio.
You work the sonar.
Franks. Dr Franks, do you copy?
I see something right in front of me.
It's in Latin. "Hic ingredi mortuus."
Here walk... the dead.
The Medicis.
(Yells)
(Screams)
(Bleeping)
Do you read? Franks? Franks?
Pietro? Do you read?
Shoot.
It's only false positives.
Pietro?
Pietro, where are you?
- Pietro.
- (Buzzing)
David, come in.
Oh, no.
A shark killed Pietro.
Pietro's dead.
- Grande tiburón blanco.
- Great white.
Mayday. We need assistance.
We need an ambulance.
Canale stazione.
(Siren)
Canale stazione. Pronto.
The tank's very low.
David, please get out of there.
Laura, do you have a fix
on my position?
Find me a way outta here.
I think there's a chamber off to your right.
(Yells)
David, please get out of there.
It's impossible.
This is... this is not happening.
(Laura) David, can you answer me?
- Are you all right?
- I was bit.
But I can move.
- (Radio crackling)
- David. Are you there?
I can barely hear you.
Where are you?
I don't know.
Some kind of underground tunnel.
Is there a way out?
I'm gonna have to swim for it.
You don't know where you are
and I can't track you in there.
(Breathless) Laura, listen to me.
I'm bleeding and I can't talk.
I have to go. I love you.
Easy.
Take it easy, baby.
It's OK, you're safe now.
- How long have I been out?
- Two days.
You lost a lot of blood.
You blacked out under there.
A gondola driver found you
and pulled you out.
I thought I'd lost you.
- Pietro?
- I'm so sorry, baby. He didn't make it.
I have something to tell you.
I found the Medici treasure.
- Are you sure?
- Yeah.
Where's my...
- Where's my dive suit?
- What are you talking about, baby?
(Tap on door)
I hope you're feeling better.
Still don't think there's any sharks
in Venice, Captain?
Mr Franks...
may I remind you that you have
signed a confidentiality agreement?
People are dead and you still don't care.
Don't worry. We're leaving.
Just as long as
we understand each other.
Signorina.
- What are you going to do now?
- We're going home.
- Laura...
- David, you're not going diving again.
Your father was attacked by a shark,
just like you were.
Except the only difference is
you're still alive.
Dr Franks, I am Rossi. My employer
wishes you to join him for some dinner.
Who's your employer?
Someone you don't want to turn down.
Does this have
anything to do with my father?
Yes.
Don't worry, we are friendly people
here in Venezia.
Lo Rialto restaurant at seven.
Grazie. Please, sit down.
- Vito Clemenza.
- Hello.
Thank you for joining me for dinner.
So... how are you connected
to my father?
I helped finance... his expedition.
Oh. I thought it was sponsored
by the university.
And who do you think
sponsored the university?
What is it you're looking for?
Treasure. The same one you found.
Where did you get that?
That is not important.
What is, is that il tesoro
is worth over $200 million.
I need you to take us back
to where you found it.
I'm not so sure I can do that.
- Why not?
- It's complicated.
Down there there's many tunnels.
It can be very disorienting.
Doctor, you are the only one
who has seen il tesoro
in more than five centuries.
Mr Clemenza, even if he could find
his way back there I wouldn't permit it.
There are killer sharks down there.
Ten per cent. $20 million.
It's OK?
Look at this as a wedding gift.
Doctor, I'm serious.
This is an advance of $2 million.
A gesture of good faith.
Go ahead. Take it.
That's a generous offer.
We're not interested.
You should show us a little respect,
signorina.
Doctor.
It's obvious you are an intelligent man.
And you are interested in your future.
You don't want to disappoint me. Right?
Go ahead. Take it.
That's enough. We're leaving.
Take your time. Think.
That's a lot of money for a teacher.
- What?
- You don't love me.
(He belches)
You only want... one thing from me.
No.
No. You try to get me... drunk.
You are a bad boy.
(Screams)
You're doing the right thing.
For who?
I haven't recovered my dad's body.
Pietro's dead.
You nearly died, too.
Oh, let me rephrase that. You were dead
until they resuscitated you.
Laura, what I'm talking about
is living my father's dream.
It's the Medici treasure.
You heard Clemenza. Nobody has even
seen this stuff in five centuries.
It's what my dad lived for. And died for.
You can't enjoy it if you're dead.
- The sharks, I know. I've...
- I'm not talking about the sharks, David.
This guy, Clemenza, he's Mafia.
He's worse than any shark.
He'll own you.
You're not going to do this.
If you go through with this...
you're on your own.
This is crazy.
I'm sorry.
Let's do some sightseeing.
Then we go home tomorrow. OK?
# Amore, dolce amore
# Is a love song
# Just for you
# My troubles are gone
When I'm singing this song about you
- Tower of St Marco.
- (Bell chiming)
# Together we'll dance and romance
Till our days are all through
# Amore, dolce amore
# Tells of sweet love
# That I have for you
# My daydreams are full
of the memories... #
Don Clemenza, they are here
in San Marco Plaza.
We'll take this one. Thank you.
They are moving to the tower
in the square.
I will stay with them.
And here we have the tower of thingy.
And over here, too.
They are at the shore now.
Moving along the water.
- Some other beautiful things.
- Wow.
They are just starting to move along
the shops at the Calle della Madoneta.
(Man) Ferma qui.
Andiamo.
Oh!
- Ceramic horses. You love those.
- I do.
- Check 'em out.
- OK.
(Screams) David!
David!
(Cries of alarm)
- (Laura shrieks)
- No need to die, signore.
I asked you what you were doing.
- You told me you were going home.
- We were going home.
Well, that's a lie
cos you went to see Clemenza.
Two of his people showed up
and invited us to dinner.
- They said it was about my father.
- And?
- He offered me a job.
- All right. What kind of job?
What difference does it make,
Lieutenant? They've got Laura.
Some kind of an underwater excavation.
I told them no.
- OK, what are you hiding?
- I'm not hiding anything.
Mr Franks, OK, I want you
to understand one thing.
Here in Venezia we are very serious
about people that do business
with the Mafia.
I'm not do... This is ridiculous.
I to... I told them no.
Now, the guy who took Laura, his name
is Rossi. He works for Clemenza.
OK. Come on.
- Where are we going?
- I'm taking you back to your hotel.
- What about Laura?
- We will look into it.
That's not good enough!
Mr Franks...
if you continue to resist,
I will place you under arrest.
Now, let's go.
(Screaming)
(TV) Police are investigating
an unprecedented amount of
missing person reports here in Venezia.
24-hour dive teams are searching
the canals and outlying areas.
Anyone with information
is encouraged to contact
the Polizia Venezia
missing persons helpline at 6722.
Thank you for everything, Lieutenant.
- Am I under arrest?
- No, it is for your protection.
That's ridiculous.
You just want to keep an eye on me.
Well, that's right. Now I will follow up
on your fiancée for you.
Buonanotte. Good night, sir.
Guarda lui, per favore. Grazie.
Oh!
He's got a gun!
(Cries out)
- Andiamo!
- Sì.
(Shouting)
(Shouts)
(Man) Hey!
Scusi!
(Siren)
(In Italian)
(Groans)
- (Yells)
- (Chainsaw buzzing)
- Where is she?
- Fuck you.
- (Groans)
Where is she?
(Cries out)
Don't... kill me!
You're already dead!
No!
- Santana.
- Where is that?
It's a boat...
on the edge of...
Del Piero lagoon.
(Engine revving)
(Siren)
(Mobile phone ringing)
- Hello.
- I thought you were smart. I was wrong.
(Man) Welcome back, signore.
Up the stairs.
- We've been waiting for you, Mr Franks.
- Where is she?
I'll ask the questions here.
My bambina. Beautiful, isn't she?
- I brought all of them to Venice.
- You out of your mind?
Too many people want to dive here.
- So you feed 'em to sharks?
- It works.
I put bambino sharks into the canal.
They grow up and cannot get out.
They are my... How you say?
Cane da guardia.
That's it. My watchdogs.
And you knew this might kill my father,
didn't you?
- He was wasting my time. And money.
- You son of a...
I don't have time for chitchat!
You bring us the treasure
or you never gonna see her again.
I wanna see her right now.
Amore.
I understand.
Bring her in.
Oh... I think you know my friend...
Lieutenant Totti.
I should have known.
Bring me the treasure
or I'm going to kill her.
Nice and slow, but I'm going to kill her.
And I'm going to enjoy it.
I cannot waste more times.
My bambina attract too much attention.
Now mayor called the coastguard.
You got an hour.
You will lead Carlo e Rossi to il tesoro.
You bring me the treasure, you go free.
You don't...
I feed her to the sharks.
It's all silent.
- Where are you going?
- I'd like to say goodbye to Laura.
Bye.
Baby, you all right?
- David...
- Don't cry.
- Love you.
- I love you, too.
- Please be careful.
- I will.
(Clemenza) OK, time to go.
Don't you dare touch her.
Bring me il tesoro.
(Totti) It's all right.
- Ciao.
(Clemenza) Franks,
do you know where you're going?
Yes. Just stay with me.
Just remember, Mr Franks,
I have the girl.
Don't confuse my kindness
with weakness.
(Rossi) Wait. It's too small.
There's not enough room.
(David) There's plenty of clearance.
Let's go.
(Rossi) This better not be a trap.
Come on, Carlo.
You're falling behind.
(Carlo) Rossi, where are you?
I see you, Rossi!
(Screaming)
I think we lost Carlo.
I don't fucking pay you to think.
Get them back on.
Move.
(Rossi) Carlo, where are you?
Answer me.
Franks! A shark!
(David) I see it. Don't move.
There could be more!
Let's get outta here.
I screwed up. I saved you.
OK. Thank you.
Stay close.
There's nothing but traps in here.
Don Vito, we've found it.
It's fantastico.
Il tesoro di Medici.
Make a map and then bring back all you
can.
L'americano?
- You know what to do.
- No! You promised!
It's nothing personal, signora.
Think about what you're doing, Rossi!
What are you gonna do?
Fight that shark alone?
Maybe I'll take my chances.
(Groans)
Rossi! Rossi, come in!
(Gurgles)
Rossi.
Rossi, answer me!
Vaffanculo!
Vincente, Zaneri, go to kill that bastard.
Let's go.
Jump.
Vincente. Zaneri.
Come in!
Where the fuck are they?
(Bullets ricocheting)
(Screams)
You are going to be in heaven
in just a moment.
But first I'm going to put you through hell.
You appear to be in a great hurry,
Dr Franks.
I assure you there is nowhere to go.
All your men are dead, Clemenza.
- Where is my fucking treasure?
- Let her go or you can find it for yourself.
You are in no position to negotiate.
I said let her go! I'm the only one
that knows its location.
My patience is running thin.
- Giuseppe Canal. E block.
- Thank you, Doctor. That will be all.
- Come on.
- (Gunshot)
Stop! What... What are you doing?
Drop it. Enough with the killing.
- Are you out of your mind?
- Just drop your fucking gun.
- I gave you a living.
- Not any more.
You... are going to shoot me?
You... puttana!
- Shoot me.
- Don't try me.
You have gone too far.
Too many people have died.
Now drop your fucking gun.
This is your last warning.
(Gunshot)
(Groans)
(Siren)
Avanti! Avanti!
Andiamo! Andiamo!
Via, via, via!
Presto! Presto!
This is Captain Bonasera.
Put your weapons down.
Andiamo, andiamo.
(Speaks in Italian)
Andiamo!
(Siren)
This is your last warning.
Put your weapons down.
(In Italian)
(Italian over megaphone)
(Yells)
(Siren)
Arresti! Arresti!
(Screams)
Is she gonna be all right, Captain?
The doctor say she will recover.
She saved our lives.
Lieutenant Totti
said she had something to confess.
Something... you could corroborate.
I'm sorry you had to get involved
in all this.
- It never meant to get this far.
- You just get better, OK?
And what is it? This confession.
Well, Captain, it seems Lieutenant Totti...
shot one of Clemenza's men
and saved our lives.
And if you ask us...
she's a hero.
I see.
I will put that in my report.
Thank you, Captain.
Mr Franks.
Signorina.
And one last thing, Mr Franks.
I know, Captain.
There are no sharks in Venice.
Oh, I almost forgot.
How do you think...
this is gonna look with a wedding dress?
- Come here.
- It's beautiful.
Let's see.
But promise me one thing.
Anything.
We will not
honeymoon in Venice.
(Laughing)
Subtitles by LeapinLar