human beings closest encounter before death
I lie in the Coffin
whilst rites are being performed
but I am not dead
this is a Thai custom
to bluff the god of death
to dispel bad fortunes
difficult for lots of people to believe
but I believe
and not only me alone
today,in a thai province,thousands gather for a strange ceremony
to lie in a coffin to rid one of bad fortunes
bullshit
After the coffin ceremony
I can feel the bad luck
leaving mine body
when I leave the coffin
I feel that life has a new meaning
My daughter was in coma
I wrote her name on paper and prayed in the coffin with it
She woke after a week even doctors call it a miracle
my mother had stomach cancer
we tried all types of cure to no avail
that is why I brought her here
she will become better after it
tens of thousands attend it over the 3 days
making it the world's biggest live burial and Guiness record
when are you coming back to Hong Kong
everybody is in a panic about it
cannot have a wedding without a bride
Mariko
close your eyes and now open it
you don't like it
why do you draw it with those piercing eyes
very penetrating
this is the beauty of it
1.2.3.4. contact
no pulse
no blood pressure
contact
his pulse is back
below 98
how long did his heart stopped
6 minutes 42 seconds
not possible
you sure?
affirmative
what happened?
why am I here?
You became sick during the ceremony
no heartbeat when to the hospital
but you seem alright now
the burial ceremony
stay calm
don't get up now
he thinks you regreted, are you?
the wedding ceremony is next week
are you feeling better now....yes
you look like you're half dead
how do you know I am here
looks like an emergency
we will always contact your best friend
you must have checked my phone contacts
dont be too cleaver when you are sick
how do you feel
I am okay
what did the doctor say
very series depression disorder
resulting in serious illusions and mental disorder
the last part, I added in
I never knew you belief in coffin ceremony
it is because of Nariko
I did what I had to do
after all, nothing to lose
think of yourself, don't do it again
unless......
there are pretty attendants ..
I get the attendants to get you something to eat
and give me a jab as well
Mike
your dinner's been heated up
are you okay?
Sue, come and help me
do I look like a bridegroom?
even your tie is not properly done
that's why you marry me
to help you with your neck tie?
ready
why do you agree to marry me
no idea, maybe was drunk
come on, give me a good reason
cause your dad is very rich
not a good reason
cause you're good in bed
even worse reason
cause you need somebody to take care of
sue, how're  you, you got me worried
Nan, how come you're here
They contacted me in school
found me card in your purse
why you never mentioned to me your coming to Thailand
sorry, it was a last minute decision
I understand you very well
you never make rash decisions
Sawaadee Khar
Sawaadee Khrap
Miss Wong, how do you feel?
Very much better
You are very lucky
we were worried you would have broken bones
piercing your vital organs
I have seen all the x-rays
nothing  wrong at all
some external cuts, nothing to worry
anyway,it doesn't matter
what do you mean?
did you not see the cancer tumours
you have cancer?
nothing of that sort,Miss Huang
you take a good rest
Sue, I don't understand
what is really happening
why didn't you tell me
what happened to this patient
oh, we transfer her to room 406
she awaken last night
it is at the end of the hallway
thank you
treat it as if you're at home
I cannot belief the cancer is gone
I don't know
will the tumours reappear tomorrow?
It won't happen
remember, you were always lucky
You should go back to Hong Kong
happily get married
okay then
I will get you the air ticket tomorrow
thank you...'mummy'
Jack
You're here
when did you got here
sorry, I should have told you
Nan informed you? when did you come
I  missed you
I know, same with me
wei? ann?
I am alright
don't worry about me, Jack's here
Everything is well, I will inform...
what nonsense are you talking about?
He is right here beside me
and he is well
Ann , I will call you
anything wrong
no
I need to go and see Nan
sorry
Ann just called
Sue?
Jack had an accident
he is dead
You need to stay calm
Jack is in your room
there is nobody in the room
what is wrong, nobody, right?
yes, nobody
I thought I will lose you
I am here
alive and well
It is beautiful here
we can have our honeymoon here
honeymoon?
sorry
I thought we could have
no, you did not
you mean......
I agree
you're sure?
you mean you are not sure?
I am, only that
you said I can continue painting in Thailand
don't worry, I won't fall into coma again
you can have it anytime you want
that is not what I meant
thank you for always taking care of me
It's getting cold, lets go inside
No, I want to see the sunrise
okay, I'll go bring some clothes
thank you
what happened?
Mariko
Is she well?
still not stable
I need to spent time by her side
chris, we come empty to this world
and we will leave empty
It is the same woman
what?
the woman I saw
Is the same as what Nariko saw
impossible
I don't know
do you know who she is
maybe the coffin you laid in was her's
not possible
the coffins were new
you sure they use new ones
Ah Chan, thank you for meeting with us
It is my pleasure
I'm sorry to hear about your fiance's death
thank you
Unusual happenings with their coffin ceremony
I am not an expert
Every one have his curiousity
why did he die
this was taken less than 1 hour before his drowning
we went for excursion after our graduation
we raced to see who could reach the shore first
trying to impress the girls
he was chasing after me
suddenly he disappeared
at Joe's funeral ceremony
only his mother did not shed a tear
after his cremation
she told us the real reason
I cause the death of my son
I had stomach cancer
but I never mentioned to anyone
I don't want him to worry
the doctor said it was terminal
it was terminal and I don't have long to live
later,someone told me about the coffin ceremony
I don't belief in these things
but then I thought, why not?
that is when I went to the ceremony
when death is right in front of you
you try to evade it
after the coffin ceremony
I did not feel any difference
but the doctor told me
my stomach cancer is gone
how do you explain
this and Joe's death
is there a relationship to it?
because on the day of Joe's death
the doctor told me this news
that my cancer is gone
do you know?
you cannot escape retribution and bad luck
you can only pass it on to your loved ones
auntie, are you better?
did you see it?
see what?
just a while ago..
honey!
my honey!
give me child back to me!
give my child back to me!
are you alright?
any connection to what is happening now?
I have collected a lot of information
recording what has really happened
Surachai....43 years old
colon cancer, went to the coffin ceremony
on 17 July 2004
was cured 1 week later
would have died if nothing miraculous occured
Suhontha,67 years old
went to coffin ceremony 27 April 2001
few days later, heart problem improved
but at the same time, grand daughter seriously injured
anybody encountered supernatural happening?
only one!
happened 5 years ago
but I cannot reveal too much about this case
unless someone has experienced it before
why did you go into forbidden area?
I saw a woman entering the area
No woman in the temple
only female ghost!
why do you look so pale?
nothing
how long have you been a grave caretaker
even before you were born!
taking care of the dead
makes me treasure my life
how many bodies have you cremated?
3248 including the one inside
did you cremated a woman and child recently?
I have booked tomorrow's ticket for you
thank you
remember our school days?
I dried your hair
sleep in the same room
eat instant noodles together
wear the same clothes
play truant together
fall for the same guy
sorry, talked too much
never mind
what I meant was
my dad died of liver cancer
I don't want to die the same way
I eat proper meals
took care of my health
I exercise everyday
follow the rules of good health
you are very well now
right but not Jack
Jack is dead
he died because of me
don't say that
I was thinking when I lie inside the coffin
why is it not Jack
he smokes everyday
it is not fair
I am sorry to hiim
its okay now
let it be
I go to Hong Kong with you
thank you
I enjoy it
I will go and change
you take whatever you want from the cupboard
what do you want from me?
what do you really want?
what do you want me to do?
I want to go and see Ah Chan again
please
Chris!
I cremated alot of bodies
never met with anything unusual
none we could not burn
if there is a preparation problem
like the burial door that is stuck
or the burner could not lit
or the coffin keep shifting
then we bury them here
they should be waiting for you
Chris?
No!!! Chris?
No!
Mariko?
Mariko!
okay
what should I do now?
You lie in the coffin once more
death is not death, it is actually life
death before dying
sawaadee khrap
how are you, Chris?
I am well
This is Nan
Sawaadee Khar
She is Sue
Ah Chan told me about your problems
my condolences
Chris, why is this happening?
Life keeps revolving nonstop
but was broken by us
how to resolve it
I haven't done anything
the night I found May's body
Mariko fell into coma
she's been in coma since
she died 5 years ago
sorry, I did not know about it
it's all right
both my parents died when I was young
thinking of my loved ones leaving me
makes me feel more terrible than being dead myself
apologies
I could not help you much
you have been a great help
I am sorry, May
If I had known I will harm the both of you
I would not have joined the coffin ceremony
It's not Mariko's fault
he could have been a good man
when I got home
the house was on fire
I wanted to save him
but I failed to do so
you left me because of him?
If he is your child
I would have stayed behind
I am sorry
Chris....
I missed you
the same with me
I have to leave
will we meet again?
My cancer has returned
After the second coffin ceremony, my cancer returned
and I did not see Jack again
I have been under therapy for some time now
it has been unbearable
but life keeps revolving
I will not try to stop it again
Do I look like your bridegroom?
English subtitle prepared by Teddytay