************
Hello
Sam where are you?
Mother
l am calling to you on motel.
They are telling me..
you are not come back.
whole night.
Chill Mother
When your father has gone..
you give me much tense.
Mother i was 2 years.
when father died.
Shut Up.
And tell me.
where are you?
On my friend house.
lf you find your own home.
then you didnt live at your friend home.
Who is this friend?
Close Friend
Mother.
Todays is your firstjob day.
you must take name of God beside Friends.
l did like that mother.
Whole night.
Alright.
Call me tonight dont forget.
Okay mother.
-Ok Bye.
Hey Sam..(Sameer)
-Hi i am Kunal.
l know ...
How you know that.
Oh kunal.
Oh Kunal Oh Kunal Ohhhh.
Kunal...
l cant heard anyone name in one night.
Hi Sexy..
There is one bad news for you.
What?
Again tonight you want to invite at
your home for creative meeting?
Verry Funny..
Now your this sense of humor.
must help you for finding new home.
Finding home!
Oh No..
-Oh Yes Yes..
l found new tunnel.
l am really sorry..
But i am getting late.
Why you cant arrange other
One Cab..
Wait a minute.
Why i can hire other cab..
l stop this first.
First i stop it.
Before you i hire..its my Cab
-No Dude its my Cab..
lts strange isn*t.
we meet eachother like this.
lts Like..
-Maybe Luck isn*t?
But we must see.
This home is in which ones luck.
Hey why you scaring me?
Oh are you indian.
No i am chinese.
lts your home.
-No its my neighbour home.
Can i call him.
No we want to see the home.
-You see.
lts Good.
Now Go..
Mean...
-Meant arjun cant tell you.
Baby live here alone.
Baby
-Baby
Look Baby jee
Baba Not allowed here.
l want more babys
in other two rooms.
After all security and respect
is most important thing.
You heard this?
Yes
Security and Respect.
But whom.
Not that there is two room.
Sweet
-You said sweet.
You did line on me?
-No No
Get Out..
OUt....
She dont want baba.
She want baby..
l also want this.
But Not like her.
What you do?
beside meet with me?
No actually i am a nurse.
So you also wear short skirts.
lts Too Bad.
What you do?
- l am photographer.
Cool.
So you with a models....
You know...
When you come from india.
-Before 3 Years.
You are finding home since 3 years.
- i live at my friend home.
But now it was remove from there.
And within 2 weeks.
Kunal Kunal
-are you mad?
Hey listen to me.
Dont touch..
l am not like that
You are like my brother.
You are desprate.
but i am not desprate.
What you want to do?
Do lt.
lf i did then i did it alone.
But she cant belive on me
as i am alone.
Listen to me.
You admit that appartment is brilliant?
Correct.
Right.
lf we want this house and tell to this.
old women we aer Gay..
So what?
There is diffrence.
l am not Gay
-l know.
l know that.
- you know that.
and if you want then i tell to all miami
girls you like a girls.
Just think..
there is two room in this apartment.
Apartment near to us.
and you are too disprate.
beside me.
l mean there is your 2 weeks deadline.
You come back again,
Baby...
You take action.
if baby is alone
No no i think you misunderstanding.
about us.
What is the meaning?
Can we come inside and tell you.
-You become a naughty.
No No we want a permission.
Okay
What are you seeing here and there
You did a plan of stealing.
Actually we must tell you before.
we take this home.
How you get this.
i told you just babys live here.
Yes we are babies.
Kunal and i both live together.
l see that.
No i mean
We are with eachother.
Kunal is my important friend.
My very best important friend.
We are a gay and he is my
boyfriend.
Please sit please sit
Relax aunty we tell you because of this.
you take decision after thinking.
and if beside us there is
2 babies.
So think what will happened.
She takes her boyfriends at night.
and parties cigrattes and wine.
Sex
and we both live here so there
is no question of 3rd.
Look we are together.
and live forever.
am i rite kunal?
and you told there is security angle
and we both guys strong and healty.
if live with you so its
security for you.
and aunty now a days who see teh age.
and evrything is possible if
you live alone at this home.
Why you scaring me.
i cant live here.
Neha Living here.
Neha?
Our sister daughter.
Girl.
Sister daughter.
You sit here.
i am come back.
Twist in story.
when neha coming in this story.
We must tell to neha this.
what we said to aunty.
Are you crazy?
You want to tell everyone?
As we are Gay..
You are too kunal.
You dont think - Think.
if aunty is like that.
so how is Neha.
lf i want that then i tell to whole family
of aunty who is neha?
l am
Yes .. Baby nice you come here.
the both guys are come to seeing this house.
Aunty.. i know they are boys.
hey tall guy whats your name.
Sameer
-and what is your name?
l am kunal
- i am neha.
Sameer
please just one minute.
Enough
its too much.
Lets go.
What?
Why?
Aunty how can i live with these Guys.
-Dont worry what we are they are not like this.
What?
Sindhi?
Not Sindhi.
They are modern type boys.
l cant become a gay infront of a girl.
Ok Not to be gay
l wont live in this home with this girl
like a gay.
This is not on our time.
on our time boys like girls.
Just one time she talk with us.
who know this girls requirementjust aunty.
Yeah..
Okay i am going.
almost you see this.
Well there is two rooms.
But bathroom is one.
lts connected.
wow
actually we like too much sharing of bathroom.
Whats a rent?
2000rs of every room.
You decide it which one you want?
Personally i love this.
-Whats that mean?
You both of guys live together right?
-What?
Kunal
Shut up you
We cant share room.
lts too expensive for you
Yeah kunal neh is right its too
expensiove for us.
Alright we see on other way.
Neha actually we tak both rooms.
lts also too easy for you.
Tell her truely.
Take away to aunty.
When we buy then no think.
and Bank loan.
Mean its your personal choice.
because your aunty just scaring us.
because when we come.
No we want girls not boys.
This girls and boys problem
just with her.
what are you doing?
all of these are not allowed here.
Stand staright.
What you do?
-What?
l am photographer
You take some picture of mine modeling.
Tall man
why are you laughing?
What are you doing?
Nurse.
-Nurse?
Nurse
you also wear short skirts.
When you make like this?
Before 3 years.
3 years
tell me your love story.
Love story.
When you meet with each other.
We we ...
we we...
Come on tell us.
We meet in venus.
Venus.
i meet with kunal on Venis.
On this first meet kunal give
me thousands dreams.
l feel i an stand and earth is moving.
My heart is beating and breath is down.
is this my first love
Next some days destiny meet with eachother.
some time on this turn.
and sometime on other turn.
and finally i tell him.
You follow me.
my my tongue was not cut.
He turn like this then he didnt come back.
l am find him too much.
i call him with diffrent name.
beloved , lover my love.
But i cant find him.
i reached to my hotel.
by thirsty of love.
There is one letter waiting for me.
My First love letter.
l wear my new armani jacket.
and go to my destiny.
When i reach there.
i saw kunal is on other site.
i move on there.
l take bath on moon light and.
on erose on my teeth.
Kunal....
And one breath come out on his
soft lips.
lts sweety
sweety.
alright.
######
Ok Mother.
l*m putting down the phone
What happened?
My Mother
l came from London but my mother
doesn*t leave me alone
Come on Sam.
Who wanna get rid of his mother?
She always cry and all that
She always says one thing
Why dont you get married?
Mrs.Khanna has 2 daughters.
Select any one of them
Ohh my god.
You didn*t tell your mother about yourself?
l mean you and Kunal
No.
She is so conservative
Tell me Neha.
lf me and Sam are not gay
Then will you make us your friends?
Ofcourse not.lf you both couldn*t be gay,
then any one of you will be interested on me.
You are so modest
My parents will not allow me
You have parents?
No.
They are died in car crash
lf l*ve to take any important decision,
l think about them
What they think?
What they suggest?
So what are they saying?
For what?
About our situation
l think they are happy and sad too
What do you mean?
They are happy that l live with
2 strong boys
And what about sadness?
Sadness
What about sadness?
They are sad that they do security of my room.
lnstead of my husband or boyfriend
Yes you*re right.
We are men
We are regular Gabbar
Gabbar Singh from Sholay
What*s the link of Gabbar here?
Don*t you see that film?
He wasn*t gay
lf a person asks in whole film that
how many peoples were? lt means he is gay
Gabbar wasn*t gay
Now dont say that there is nothing
in between Munna Bhai and Circuit
Come on.
Dont say this
He call Munna Bhai
So?
l also call you brother
What are you doing here?
We have to submit documents
l know but gay couples are standing there
Gay couples row?
lf you submit your documents as a couple,
then you*ll get residency permit soon
Or else it*ll take 5 years
Sam l*ll get papers in one year
You had a problem in telling it to Neha
Now you are going to make us officially gay
You just have to sign a single paper
lf we captured, we will go to jail
l will do anything for you
Anything
l*ll use bathroom first
You have to make coffee for me
You have to introduce myself
to models
l wanna see Aunty*s sexy photo shoot
You are so desperate.
Lets go
Only you know what l wanna
hear in the morning
You are taking there side
They are hot, sweet and funny.But..
Then what?
They both are gay
Yummy.
Why dont you introduce me?
Why you have these letters?
What about competition?
l*m leaving this job
Deva offer me a new job
Dont you think that l can be a Editing Chief
They are lieing because they hates me
Who will get this position and office?
Actually this is my decision
Tomorrow there is a dinner at my home
l*ll introduce Sam and Kunal
What you say yes?
Her boss wanna meet us
and you said yes
Guess what Neha
We are not Gay
We were lieing.
Because your house is so beautiful
What*s written in it?
Open it and read
They agreed our request
Only your name written
lt can be happen
l*ve written my London address in form
Then?
Then my mother
l wont do anything with any man
l told this before and now listen again
My boss will be here any moment.
He promised me. But l didn*t
Sam you promised me
Sam will be here and you have to pretend
lts so fabolous but l dont need this
Sorry aunty.
What*s hanging on your neck?
He has a sore throat thats why
Put this in kitchen
And l think there is a micro wave bell rings.
The dinner is ready
You didn*t tell me that you boss is very hot
Shit. Now what will we do?
He will do everything
He wanna see are we real gay or not
Please tell me what will we do?
think like girls
Think like girls. Dont think about them
Like about their hairs and shoes all that
You know this kinda thing
You both are new here?
Yes. l*m from London
l work in Howard Medical Centre
Lets have fun.
Means fun
Lets have some music and dance
Mother!!!!!!
l thought l saw a bad dream
What*s happenning here son?
We were playing game and it was my turn
Now you relax!
Live life for others and to say lie.
lt hurts
l*ve never told to my parents that l*m a gay
No!!!
This is not a place to live
Dont call me mother
You dont respect my old age
What are you in his lap?
Dont you dare to touch my son
You wont live happy
Lets go to home.
Lets go to London
You were fine there
You were fine with girls.
And here you...
Whether its London or Miami,
your son is a gay
Shut up
Mother dont listen to him.
l*m not gay
You told me that you are gay
You lied me.
Samir is not lieing
lts not like that
He is lieing
He*s Sameer*s boyfriend
You told me that they both are single
You were lieing to me
l know everything. l got that letter.
Thats why l*m here
God let me die
Why are you giving me punishment?
Why this police man is behind my son?
Now dont hide your love
l think its time.
Tell your mother your Bellis story
When you went to Bellis?
lt was my fault. All this is because of me
Love is not a mistake
Love is blind
lts not that blind that you can*t
differentiate between a girl and a boy
lts enough. You made me happy
Listen to me mother
Mother please
You wont hold my hand in my old age
^^^^^^^^^^
What happened?
ls anyone said you something?
No. Nothing
Are you practicing for crying?
l*m not lieing.
Nothing happened
Lets l*ll do this formality
Why are you crying?
No
l*m not crying
Something has happened.
No aunty nothing has happened
ls someone said you anything?
Now tell me
They told me that l*ll get promotion
But now they gave that position
to someone else
lts not a big deal.
Why are you crying?
l worked very hard
l thought so many things.
Everything is vanished
You are fired.
Out!
l*ve never seen a cheap person like you
How can we meet?
We 3 loosers
Or anything you want.
Our friendship is more rocking than any plan
Listen.
Will he fired from the job?
lf he*ll do this then l*ll say to Kunal
that break his legs
This body will come for use that day
Chill and be ok!