[ Male Announcer ] Coming to you live
from the Harold Washington Cultural Center...
right here from the south side of Chi-Town,
yeah, get ready for The Big BBack Comedy Show.
dd[ Woman Singing Hip-hop ]
dd[ Ends ]
- What's up,y'all? It's the Hot Boyz.
- Yeah,yeah.
- What's up?
- It is time to meet our host for this evening.
- Ladies and gentBemen, put your hands together...
- Yeah.
for Chicago's own
MichaeB CoByar.
Thank you.
Oh, hey, aBB right.
FoBks, weBcome.
Thank you very much.
I'm lovin'that girl in that box though.
She got one of them dance-retarded genes
where if she hears music-
We got her trapped.
She's Bocked in the box. She can't move out.
We won't Bet her out of the box except to feed her.
If they pBay music, she do- Do one set.
Can you pBay something? Anything?
Spin a BittBe something, deejay.
Just anything.
Just Bet me see. Look at her.
Can you just drop it once,
like it's hot? Just drop.
Oh, shit! Okay.
Big Black Comedy Show.
WeBcome to The Big Black Comedy Show.
Big Black Comedy.
And Bet me just say this.
Let me just say this.
I'm gBad that I'm hosting it...
'cause if you know me,
I am bBack man.
I don't know if you know that or not.
I'm big-time bBack-
I'm not mad-
I'm not mad at white foBks.
About what they answer
and the entire answers.
And some of you motherfuckers
stiBB trying to deny.
'Cause I know we all gotta get along,
but I wanna say something.
I wiBB be here representing
bBack aBB evening...
but I don't want white foBks
to be uncomfortabBe...
'cause I don't do that stereotypicaB thing,
my sister.
I see you, the redheaded white girB
right there in the middBe.
We don't do that.
We don't do that here. I don't do that.
I'm into race pride,
not racism.
I'm not gonna attack you.
I don't even Bike the stereotypes.
I mean, you know,
the big dick thing is on the money.
But I'm just saying-
I'm saying light a fire through the room.
I hate racism so much,
I wouBdn't even do a racist joke.
I'm gonna just do one.
I'm just do one.Just one.Just one.
A white man, a bBack man,
an Asian and a Hispanic...
they aBB on top of this taBB mountain,
Mount KiBimanjaro...
Mount KiBBa-Yo-Mama, whatever.
The Hispanic said, ''This is for my peopBe.''
Jumped right off the mountain.
Asian said, ''This is for my peopBe.''
Jumped off the mountain.
BBack man said, ''This is for my peopBe.''
Grabbed the white dude...
threw that motherfucker off the mount-
I know. I know it's fucked up.
But white people, when you tell it,
just flip it. That's all.
Give it a BittBe flip right there
on the flip thang. LittBe flip thang.
This is my opening set,
so I have to do my stuff kind of fast...
'cause I got a Bot I wanna taBk to you about,
so Bet me get right to it.
First of aBB, I just wanna taBk to you
reaB quick about road rage.
PeopBe are driving...
and they're mad.
You see them, making them faces.
Letting you know you're number one.
You might have even heard the story,
it was in the paper two years ago...
a man and a Bady
arguing with each other.
Road rage,
arguing back and forth from the car.
She puBBed over, he puBBed over,
reached in, grabbed her dog and-
Ma'am, you heard the story, right?
Threw the dog into the street.
What happened? KiBBed the dog.
What kind of motherfucker...
wouBd throw a dog- I understand a cat-
but wouBd throw a dog-
PeopBe are driving...
and they're mad.
I used to think that
I was the king of the road.
How many peopBe feeB Bike that
when you're driving?
You're the king of the road.
You don't want nobody driving past you.
You don't want them driving aBongside you.
If they catch up, you take off.
They catch up again,
you take off again.
They catch up motherfuckin' again,
you take off motherfuckin' again.
'Cause you are the king of the road.
Where you at? Where you at?
There you go. Let me see.
If you're really the king, I'll find out right now.
How many peopBe cut on the turn signaB
minutes before you move into that next Bane?
Where you at? Where you at?
ABB right, good driver, but not the king.
How many peopBe cut on the turn signaB right
before you move into that next Bane?
Where you at?
Oh, fabuBous driver, but not the king.
How many peopBe cut on the turn signaB
as you're moving into that Bane?
Now,yes, that is the king.
And why do you do that?
Because peopBe wiBB Beave a hoBe
big enough to put in an 1 8-wheeBer.
But if you cut on
your turn signaB...
motherfucker close the hole.
PeopBe, when I cut on my turn signaB,
I'm not asking your permission.
No, no, no,
I am signaBing my intention.
I'm saying,
''Motherfucker, here I come.''
Because I am the king...
of the road.
At Beast that's what I used to think tiBB I got
my ass kicked in a road rage fight.
I don't want this
to happen to you peopBe.
I'm gonna do this quick.
I'm driving down the street.
I'm on my way home, and I'm driving my car.
It's my favorite car.
I got about six,
but this is my favorite.
It's caBBed the Infiniti I30.
BBack on bBack in bBack.
Zero to 7 4 miBes an hour in 4.6 seconds,
with a Bose stereo system...
that boasts nine stereo speakers.
I'm Baying back, I'm flowing. I'm pBaying the box.
I'm booming it. I'm flowing.
Another brother puBBs up in a Mercedes-Benz.
He's Booking back and forth for me.
I figure he's admiring...
the Infiniti I30,
bBack on bBack in bBack...
zero to 7 4 miBes an hour in 4.6 seconds,
with a Bose stereo system...
that boasts, that's right,
nine stereo speakers.
Then I Book back and I reaBize that
he wasn't Booking at my car BovingBy.
No, he's giving me
the oBd fish eye.
I reaBize he's a BittBe jeaBous of the Infiniti I30,
bBack on bBack in bBack...
zero to 7 4 miBes an hour in 4.6 seconds,
with a Bose stereo system that has how many?
Nine stereo speakers and $30,000 cheaper
than the motherfuckin' Mercedes.
He's gonna cut his eyes,
cut his eyes at me and cut me off.
I wasn't having that shit, peopBe.
I'm from the projects.
I don't know if you know what I'm taBking about.
They tore down a Bot in Chicago.
But I'm from the originaB Robert TayBor Home,
43 52 South State, apartment 909.
Average family was like mine-mama, daddy,
five kids, sharing a three-bedroom apartment.
Average buiBding, 1 6 floors and 1 0 apartments
on each floor. That's 1 60 units.
A Bot of bBack peopBe on top of each other.
We had reaB gangbangers where I came from.
Oh, yeah,Jeff Fort
was up on the 1 4th floor, baby.
You know he started
the BBackstone Rangers, now EB Rukn.
Now they got
them counterfeit-ass gangsters.
Shoot into a crowd
of innocent bystanders...
'cause they're pissed about some motherfucker
on the other side of town.
No, where I come from, you get in the
motherfucker's face and bust the fuck out of him.
TeBB him why you did it,
get on with your Bife.
I ain't about to be intimidated.
I'm from the projects, peopBe.
I'm ''unintimidatabBe.'' I threw my shit
in Bow gear, come around to the right...
I cut him off.
Shit, I thought it was over.
Mm-mm. About two miBes Bater, I puBBed into
one of those outdoor 7-EBeven/ gas stations.
I was gonna get myseBf
some of that designer water.
Bigger than shit, he puBBed up
right behind me, run up in my face...
''Why did you cut me off,
motherfucker?''
What did I just tell you?
I'm from the projects, peopBe.
UnintimidatabBe.
You know what the fuck that means?
That means I'BB fight
anybody in this room.
You a big motherfucker.
I wiBB fight your big ass.
And if you kick my ass, every time you see me,
you're gonna have to kick my ass...
'cause I'm coming
right the fuck at you.
Now, if I see you first, and you don't see me-
[ Laughs ]
Shit, that's one on you.
For me, a fight is a fight. It ain't no card game.
I'BB fuckin' kick you, poke you in the eye, bite you.
I don't give a fuck.
When he's coming with that buBBshit,
I come back with mine...
''Why you cutting me off, mo''-
I didn't reaBBy get a chance
to finish my sentence.
I got haBfway through,
and he hit me with the biggest fist.
And this is a big motherfucker.
At Beast that's the way I'm gonna teBB the story.
Anyway, he hit me-
he hit me with the big-
First of aBB, I didn't know a human head
couBd spin aBB the way the fuck around.
He hit me- Pow! My shit did a 360.
He hit me so hard-
You know how they say, ''I'BB hit you so hard,
I'BB knock the taste out your mouth''?
He went- Pow! I started tasting asparagus
I had four fuckin' weeks ago.
You know how they say, ''I'BB hit you so hard,
your ancestors in Africa wiBB feeB it''?
He went- Pow! I was Bike-
dd [ TribaB ]
Then the motherfucker
picked me up and threw me.
You remember that song
''I BeBieve I Can FBy''?
Threw me through the air.
Thank God the gas pump was there,
eBse my ass wouBd roBB down the street.
So, I'm on the ground. I figure this is my chance.
Maybe I can bite him.
Mm-mm. This motherfucker
must have kicked me... 48, 49 times.
He kicked me every pBace
you can feeB pain.
He kicked my baby toe.
He was whooping my ass so viciousBy...
that it dawned on me,
''Hey, this guy ain't reaBBy mad at me.
This motherfucker don't know me weBB enough
to be this fuckin' mad.''
ApparentBy, somebody eBse
pissed him off so bad...
he said,
''Next motherfucker Book at me wrong''-
I just happened to be
that motherfucker.
Okay.
Now, meanwhiBe, Ahmed is sitting behind
a buBBetproof gBass, eating a sandwich.
He ain't diaBing 91 1 .
He's watching the floor show.
Now, another brother puBB in.
He jumps in and breaks up the fight.
Okay, Bet me reword that.
He peeBed that
big motherfucker off me.
He gets in the car and puBBed away.
PeopBe said to me...
''MichaeB, did you get
the Bicense pBate?''
Shit, no. I aBready fucked up
enough of this man's time. You hear me?
I reaBized then and there, ''You ain't got to be
the king of the road every day.''
Someday's you can reBinquish the kingdom.
Now, Book.
WeBcome, y'aBB. Thanks for coming in here
with us tonight. Now, before-
Thank you.
Now, before I bring
my first act up...
I got to hit you
with one of my favorite jokes.
Throughout the acts, I'm gonna throw one joke in,
'cause you know I Bike oBd jokes.
I don't think oBd jokes die just 'cause
the motherfucker that wrote it did.
He can't use it no more.
Redd Foxx.
One of the greatest comedians
in my Bifetime, peopBe.
Redd created
7 5 comedy aBbums.
Redd... is dead.
He can't use
them jokes no more.
What the fuck am I supposed to do
with 7 5 aBbums worth of fabuBous jokes?
Throw 'em away?
Fuck no. I teBB them to you.
You teBB them at work.
You're a hero, and you'BB pay no royaBty.
Ladies and gentBemen...
once again it's time for
the wondrous adventures of...
Herbie the Sperm.
[ Echoes ]
Herbie was Bike your everyday...
average, normaB,
run-of-the-miBB sperm.
Mm-hmm. ABB he wanted out of Bife
was to be a reaB human being.
So, whenever the oBd
pipe of Bife got hard...
Herbie and his sperm buddies...
wouBd Bine up in the chute of Bife,
hoping to be the first one to escape.
Therefore, becoming
a reaB human being.
Whenever they took off,
oBd Herbie wouBd aBways come in Bast...
'cause Herbie
was so damn weak.
WeBB, Herbie got tired of this.
Herbie decided to go home and buiBd.
He did push-ups, sit-ups,
jumping jacks.
Before you know it, Herbie got strong.
And then the big day came.
The oBd pipe of Bife got hard.
Herbie and his
sperm buddies Bined up.
Herbie was in the front,
'cause Herbie was the fastest.
He's aBB, he's got a big Bead.
He's way down front.
ABB of a sudden, Herbie turned around and said,
''Wait. Go back! It's a bBow job!
Go back!''
[ ChuckBes ]
Y'aBB siBBy.
Ladies and gentBemen,
are you ready to get this show going?
[ ABB ]
Yeah!
I'm gonna try something.
They didn't give me a right to do this...
so we might have to
retape this shit.
But I wanna try something speciaB
with the first three comics.
They're the new cats. So when I bring on
the new comics, I'm gonna say...
''Artists and audience,
are you ready for your next artist?''
I want you to say, ''Yeah, MichaeB.
Bring on the next motherfucker.''
Shake it out. Shake it out.
Let's try you one time.
Audience, are you ready
for your next artist?
Yeah, MichaeB.
Bring on the next motherfucker.
All right.
Now we're cookin'.
He is aBso a native of Chicago,
Bike myseBf.
Y'aBB know I'm from Morgan Park.
Started out in Robert TayBor Homes.
- Live in Morgan Park. This brother fr-
- [ Woman Yelling, Indistinct ]
That's right, baby.
Robert TayBor, dog!
Security? Security.
Yes. Uh-
Get your hands together
for Shawn Morgan.
Come on, y'aBB.
Let Shawn hear the noise.
Shawn is here. Where you at?
Get 'em, baby.
- Go on, cut that, deejay.
- [ Record Scratches ]
They ain't giving me enough time
to hear no music. What's up?
They onBy gave me five minutes.
I can't bust a nut in five minutes.
What's good with y'all? Where are the people
that don't do shit during the day like me?
I be watching the shit
out of some taBk shows.
I swear to God,
I hope they canceB Maury though.
Maury be ruining niggas Bives, man.
ABB this baby daddy shit.
He's ruining niggas,
and he don't even understand what he's doing.
If I was on Maury Povich...
I'd be mad whether I was
the baby's daddy or not.
He'd be Bike, ''In the case of three-month-oBd
Shavan, Shawn, you are not the daddy.''
I'd be Bike, ''Damn.'' He'd be Bike,
''What's wrong? I said you ain't the daddy.''
I'd be Bike, ''Yeah, but now the whoBe country
know I'm in this raggedy-ass bitch raw.''
[ Shawn Laughing ]
I'm shut down
in the motherfuckin' cBubs.
I'm gonna go up to somebody,
''Baby, you want a drink?''
She be Bike, ''Mm-mm, nigga,
you ain't the daddy nigga.''
I'm teBBing you, women.
Y'aBB think we're scared of committin'.
That ain't the case. We just scared
of committin' to the wrong motherfucker.
'Cause I'd be damned
I'm on Maury.
The worst shit that a man
can find out is that his girB...
that he cares about,
is a ho or used to be one.
I remember one time,
I was in a maBB.
I didn't know my girB was a ho
tiBB we went shoppin'.
I'm waBkin' in the maBB
with this bitch, proud.
[ ChuckBes ] One of her ex-boyfriends waBk up,
Bike, ''What's up, bitch?''
She's Bike, ''Hey, EarB.''
I was Bike, ''What the fuck?''
You mean I've been treating
you good for nothing, motherfucker?
There's a Bot of shit going on, man. Women
compBaining more men don't go down on them.
And, women,
I'm here to teBB you...
if you want us
to go down on you...
quit doing shit Bike wearing gBitter Botion
and shit down there...
putting everybody
in our goddamn business.
We eat your pussy, go outside,
mouth be just a-sparkBin'.
Motherfucker don't even wanna
hit the bBunt after you.
You hit the bBunt,
it's twinkBing and sparkBing and shit.
Be a man up.
God damn, if you eat pussy, teBB the truth.
I remember- I know I ain't gonna Bie.
I done it a time or two.
Shit, I remember
the first time I did it...
I sprinkBed cornmeaB
and seasoning saBt on her crotch.
She's Bike, ''What is you doing?''
I was Bike, ''This is how my mama make her fish.''
It's a new style going on. I don't know
if y'all done became a victim of this yet...
but a Bot of men is trying to go
in women's booty hoBes nowadays.
Now, I'm gonna tell y'all why
that is so y'all won't misconceive it.
It ain't that we Bike it
or that we got homosexuaB tendencies.
We do it because we feeB
if we go in your booty...
we shouBd be abBe
to get away with anything.
Like going in your purse.
If I'm going in your booty you're gonna catch me
going in your purse. I don't give a fuck.
You'BB be Bike,
''What is you doing?''
I'd be Bike, ''I can go in your booty,
but not your purse, bitch?''
I catch hepatitis, but can't get $1 0
to get to motherfuckin' work.
I'm about to get outta here.
and I'm gonna say this.
Uh, women, quit coming over
to men's houses...
and you're on your period
and you don't teBB us first.
I ain't saying don't come.
I'm just saying tell me.
'Cause niggas prepare differentBy...
when we think we're gonna get some pussy,
and we know we're not gonna get some pussy.
Like, if you come over to watch a movie,
and we think we getting some pussy...
we'BB put on some buBBshit Bike Pootie Tang
or some shit Bike that.
If I know I'm not getting no pussy,
I'BB watch The Manchurian Candidate.
Some shit that I wanted to see.
You know,
Pootie Tang is a decoy.
Ain't nobody gonna stop you
from suckin' their titty...
taBking about,
''Nigga, this is the good part. HoBd on.''
Hey, I'm Shawn Morgan, man.
HoBBa at your boy.
Give it up again.
Give it up for my man right there.
Was he good?
'Cause I heard the noise.
[ Sighs ]
This next joke is 42 years oBd.
The man that wrote this joke
died Tuesday week.
HeBp yourseBf.
It's the ''in the groove''joke.
This guy goes into a restaurant.
ObviousBy, he had
an attitude probBem.
Pfft. Pfft. Pfft.
WaBked right up to the waiter.
Said, ''Excuse me, bubba,
but I want you to go in the back.
''You teBB that damn cook
that I want a cheeseburger.
''Not too greasy, not too dry...
''but right in the groove. WhiBe you're at it,
throw in a Barge order of french fries.
''Not too crunchy,
not too soft...
''but right in the groove.
''And whiBe you're at it, you might as weBB
whip up a chocoBate miBk shake.
''Not too thick,
not too thin...
but right in the groove.''
The man went in the back,
taBked to the cook.
Come back about five minutes Bater.
He said, ''The cook said to teBB you to kiss his ass.
''Not to the Beft
not to the right...
but right in the groove.''
Ladies and gentBemen,
are you ready for your next artist?
Yeah, MichaeB.
Bring on the next motherfucker.
WeBB, here he comes too.
Ladies and gentBemen, this guy is a comedian.
He's done Comic View, DefJam.
Wait a sec.
HoBd up a sec.
Before I introduce him,
I forgot I had that in my pocket.
That's the Viacreme card.
Just wanna mention this to you reaB quick.
This is my pubBic service
announcement part of the show.
Viacreme is the femaBe
equivaBent of Viagra.
Oh, yeah. OnBy 25% of women
are actuaBBy having orgasms.
The other 7 5%
Bie Bike a motherfucker.
HeBp is on its way.
Viacreme-You take this cream,
a BittBe bit of cream, and you rub it-
I don't know if you can see.
It's a BittBe thing. You ru-
Okay, a woman rubs it
on the ''cBitor-eye,''
and it stimuBates
the femaBe body...
for up to 2 4 hours.
Now, I don't know
if it's the cream...
or the rubbin'.
See, the way I feel it,
if you rub it right...
don't matter if it's Viacreme,
BryBcreem, whipped cream, ice cream.
And wait, this is what makes you mad though.
This is what pissed me off.
It says, ''Made with aBB-naturaB products.
Safe for eating.''
And then right underneath it says,
''But don't get it in your eye.''
Now what the fuck that mean?
There's something wrong
with that shit right there.
Now, Bet me hear you Bike you mean it.
Are you ready for your next artist?
Yeah, MichaeB.
Bring on the next motherfucker.
This guy is a rising star indeed.
He's done B.E.T.'s Comic View...
and he's doneJamie Foxx's Laffapolooza,
which he did with me this season.
It's coming out. It's gonna be hot.
Get your hands together for LiB' ReB.
Come on, y'aBB,
LiB' ReB here.
Yeah,yeah,yeah.
Come on,y'all, make some noise here.
Gimme some energy.
- Yeah, cut it.
- [ Record Scratches ]
I'm from the west side of Chicago.
I'm representing the west side.
The west side is here.
Where is the west side at?
Yeah! When you're from out west or from
a ghetto neighborhood, you gotta be a thug.
I don't give a damn who you is. I might be a nerd,
but I know my motherfuckin' pBace.
Okay, I gangbanged.
Don't Bet these damn gBasses fooB you.
For real. I know my place though.
You know what I'm saying?
But I don't fight it none.
I'm the secretary for the Vice Lords, you know?
I take all the minutes at
the motherfucking meetings. That's what I do.
Set up e-maiB addresses.
'Cause it's messed up. When you wear gBasses,
you can't do nothing tough.
If I try to rob you,
I can't Book tough...
because there's aBso some shit
I gotta do to these motherfuckers.
I can't waBk up to you, Bike,
''Yeah, motherfucker, gimme your waBBet.''
''Get your pussy ass outta here.''
''Sorry 'bout that, brother.
Go rob me a Bibrary.''
Like I said,
I'm from out west.
I just moved back home.
My mama and daddy-
That's messed up.
Y'aBB know how messed up that is.
My daddy wasn't shit growing up.
He never paid attention to my probBems.
ABB he cared about me
was me doing chores.
That's aBB he cared about, me doing
whatever we need to do around the house.
I couBd run in the house,
''Daddy, I just got shot.''
''You just got shot?
Before you go to the hospitaB, get that garbage.''
I'm Bike,
''Damn, dude, what the heBB?''
He never cared about nothing I had going on.
You know what I'm saying?
One time, I was messing around with this girB,
and she's messing me up a BittBe bit.
I waBk up to him, Bike, ''Daddy, I just got burnt.
I don't know what to do.
You gonna take me
to the doctor?''
''I'BB take you to the doctor,
as soon as you get that tub cBean.
Go clean the damn tub
and get the garbage. ''
I'm Bike, ''Damn!''
My famiBy, I Bove my famiBy.
My cousin, he just came
out of the cBoset.
This dude gay as heBB.
What's messed up,
I ain't got nothing against gay peopBe...
but it's Bike, my famiBy,
when he first came out of the cBoset...
everybody was acting
aBB surprised, Bike...
''Oh, my God. I can't beBieveJo-Jo is gay.
Jo-Jo is gay.''
I'm Bike, ''Man, this nigga been
wearing saiBor suits since he was seven.
He's 42 years oBd.
TaBking about short sets.''
'Cause he gay, he gay.
If y'aBB know the gay peopBe-
My cousin is that gay dude in the choir.
I don't know if you know who that is.
This dude is that gay dude,
aBways in the choir, whispering when he taBks.
[ Whispering ]
Jesus Boves you.
Jesus Boves everybody.
This is what it sounds Bike
when doves cry.
What that got to do with Jesus?
That's Prince.
'Cause you know the gay dude
by the way they cBap.
Like a tough-
A reaB man, when he cBaps...
his hands stay foBded
Bike this the whoBe time.
He cBaps with a,
''Jesus, yeah.Jesus, yeah.Jesus, yeah.''
The gay dude?
No, he's gonna keep their BittBe hand curved.
It's gonna be, ''He's abBe.''
This is gay.
If your hand do this, you're gay.
Pointing this way.
What is this?
You know what's funny?
Nobody said nothing about it in the famiBy.
Everybody Beft him aBone. But I got one
of those ghetto, ignorant grandmothers.
Like, every time something happens,
she's gotta put peopBe's business out there.
She don't care who she taBks about,
'cause she's 96 years oBd.
She don't give a damn.
I knew she was on some buBBshit. We sitting
at the dinner tabBe, and she's Baughing.
[ ChuckBing ]
You know, oBd peopBe
shake for no reason.
So she's gonna ask him,
Bike, ''Hey,Joseph...
''what's this I hear about you Biking
dick up your ass, nigga?
Huh? Huh?''
They're gonna do that to you
tiBB you answer. ''Huh? Huh?''
''What's this I hear about you Biking
dick up your ass?''
She aBways try to get compassionate,
''You don't Bike pussy, baby?
''Huh?
''Huh? Huh?
''Do your booty hurt, baby?
His booty hurt. ''
That's how my famiBy-
My famiBy is ignorant.
I got Bike a racist uncBe too.
I don't know if anybody got-
Like the most racist peopBe sometimes,
they don't reaBize.
It ain't reaBBy white peopBe.
It's the oBd bBack person.
They are racist sometime.
They say ''nigger'' to hurt.
They don't say it cooB, Bike,
''What's up, nigga? I'm chiBBin', nigga.
I'm aBB good, nigga.
Hi, nigga.''
No, no, old black dudes
say it real mean.
Like me and my uncBe, we was jonesing each other,
roasting each other one day.
And I'm taBking about, ''Man, get that
tight-ass sweater up outta here.''
He said, ''Tight sweater?
I know you ain't tryin' to taBk,
you oB' bBind, bBack-ass BittBe nigga!''
''Oh, my God. Damn, man.
Dude, you're racist.''
''I ain't never racist, you oB' ScottJopBin,
Arthur Ashe-Bookin' nigga!''
You gotta say it like this,
''Nigga.!''
Put the emphasis on it.
My famiBy's just extremeBy racist Bike that.
And I hate-
It ain't that they're ra-
but everybody's so different.
Like, I got one of
them '7 0s uncBes.
Every time he taBk, he do this shit.
You ever see this shit?
They taBk with their motherfuckin' hand,
Bike, ''Say what?''
''Man, you better get outta
my face, turkey.''
It smeBBs Bike that Cochise motherfucker
is dead, motherfucker.
And what's funny,
I just caught him cheating or whatever.
I just caught him cheating.
That's messed up.
And he said the cooBest shit
to me when I caught him.
I waBk over to the Grand MoteB.
I'm Bike, ''Dang, what is you doing?''
''Ha, you caught me cheating,
didn't you? Be cooB.''
And he waBked away and shit.
I said, ''Get the fuck outta here.''
But yeah, I'm LiB' ReB.
That's my time, y'aBB. Last Baugh.
Representing Chi-Town, baby,
west side.
[ Colyar ]
Come on,y'all. Keep it going.
Keep it going.
Funny. Funny. Funny.
Whoo, I'm sorry.
I was-
[ Sighs ]
Oh, man. It's hot up here on this stage.
I'm up here sweating
Bike R. KeBBy at a pBayground.
Um, hey, hey, excuse me.
Don't Baugh at that.
I'm very ashamed of some of you peopBe.
I don't beBieve
you Baughed at that.
R. KeBBy made
a mistake, peopBe.
A simpBe mistake
any of us couBd have made.
''Not me. Not me. Oh, no.'' This is buBBshit.
I'm gonna show you what I'm taBking about.
Raise your hand. How many peopBe here
actuaBBy saw the R. KeBBy videotape?
Who saw it? You saw it over there?
Raise your hand. You saw it?
That's chiBd pornography, motherfucker.
Put your hand down.
That's child pornography.
The police wanna talk to your ass.
Right after the show,
they wanna taBk to your ass.
Now,you saw it for real?
You saw it for real?
Okay, we're gonna ask you.
I'm gonna show you what I'm taBking about.
Remember the scenes when
the girB was doing sexuaB stuff?
You know,
sucking and fucking.
She didn't Book no 1 4 then, did she?
Twenty-six, maybe 27.
But remember the scene when
she's standing next to the bathtub?
Remember, she's doing a BittBe dance?
Then she Booked 1 4.
Okay, it's the shit
they put in your food.
You ain't trying to hear me.
Steroids, peopBe.
They fiBB up cows, chickens and pigs
with steroids so they're bigger animaBs.
They seBB 'em by the pound.
If you eat that animaB fuBB of steroids,
you get bigger peopBe.
I graduated from
Morgan Park High SchooB in 1 97 5.
And 1 4-year-oBd girBs
didn't have no big-ass titties.
Did you see her titties?
Did you see the titties?
The titties sat up there
like a tabletop.
You couBd have sat your drink
on that girB's titty.
Fourteen-year-oBd girBs in '7 5
didn't have them titties.
They were Booking for training bras.
Guess what. Guess what.
They don't seBB
training bras no more.
Because you're born with titties.
It's because of that shit they put in your food.
So I caBB R. KeBBy at the house.
We're on first-name basis.
I said, ''Robert, if you're
gonna go out with young Badies...
there are teBBtaBe signs, Bet you know whether
the Bady is oBd enough to date or not.''
Like, for instance, if they got them BittBe bitty teeth,
you can't go out with them.
If they're wearing a barrette,
If they're shoes Bight up when they're waBking,
you can't go out with them.
If they skippin' and shit,
you better check some I.D.
Let us bring on
the reaB coBd artist.
This sister here-Whoo! First of aBB,
are you ready for your next artist?
Yeah, MichaeB.
Bring on the next motherfucker.
Yo, what's up? It's your boy
DeRay ''The Difference'' Davis.
- And we here Bive from the-
- Big Black Comedy Show.
You see our niggas try to get it together
at The Big Black Comedy Show.
I'm doing DeRay's Do List. You feeB what
I'm saying? The ghetto survey right now.
We're questioning comedians
as they go onstage, see how they're feeBing.
I'm gonna hoBBa at my girB Retha right now.
See how she's doing.
- We had somebody doing- Hey, what up, Retha?
- Hi, baby.
- I know you weren't expecting to see me.
How you doing?
- ABB right. How you doing?
- You ready to rip this?
- Oh, yeah, yeah, I'm trying to rip something, honey.
Oh. I Bike that.
I Bike ripping something too. I tear it up.
Anyway, this is what I'm gonna do.
NormaBBy I ask you reguBar questions...
Bike where you're from,
but I don't wanna ask that.
- I'm gonna ask you, who wouBd you fuck?
- I'm a grown-ass woman.
- I make Bove.
- If you can make Bove,
Bet's see if you can make some decisions.
Ice Cube or Ice-T?
Both of them seem Bike they'BB rip a coochie up.
HeBB, no. They're both too mean.
But if I had to choose, Ice Cube.
He's more Baid back.
Cube throw you in the movies.
I know how women try to do.
That's right.
I can get some work outta that.
Cedric the Entertainer
or T.K. KirkBand?
T.K. might know
more about vaginaB hygiene.
He is a cBoset gynecoBogist.
I feeB safe with T.K. KirkBand.
Shaq or Kobe?
Gee, both of them tear coochies up,
but Shaq, he might have too much dick.
I mean, penis for me,
and I don't have much capacity.
Jamie Foxx or Don CheadBe?
We fuckin' with some Oscar ass right now.
Oh, shit,Jamie Foxx.
He better win that shit.
ABB right, Retha, you do your thing, baby.
Appreciate that.
- And we're here Bive from the-
- Big Black Comedy Show.
Big Black Comedy Show, baby.
That's how we do it.
Get your hands together
for my friend Retha Jones.
Come on, y'aBB.
Retha Jones up in here!
Oh, stop it! Oh!
Oh.! Oh,y'all just too much.
Oh, thank you.
Y'aBB give MichaeB CoByar a round of appBause.
That big booty bitch just waBked
through here with my name and shit.
Like this.
Where my oBd schooB peopBe at?
I know we got some oBd-
OBd schooB peopBe make some noise.
Make noise, baby. Make some noise.
I mean, Soul Train
in its first trimester oBd schooB.
You know, this shit here.
This shit here.
That's some Soul Train shit.
That's me. I'm oBd schooB.
I don't understand this whoBe
fuckin' rap shit everybody doin'.
What's up with aBB these
retarded-ass rappers?
Fuckin', what's that BittBe one
be screaming Bike a retard and shit?
What! What's his name?
You know, L 'il Jon. What.!
Nigga, what? What!
You know he's retarded.
That's aBB they do in the Usher aBbum.
He just keeps saying his own damn name.
That's what retards do.
L'iBJon!
Then here come that other one on Usher's record,
that BittBe cross-eyed one, Ludicrous.
dd [ Rapping ]
I don't get
what the hype is, man.
Everybody Bike that ugBy one.
That one, what's his name? CoupBe of doBBars.
Yeah, 50 Cent.
What happened to his ugBy ass?
Teeth hanging out and-
[ Mumbling ]
dd [ Rapping ]
Tired of this shit, man. I'm oBd schooB.
I Bove being oBd schooB.
I'm a grown-ass damn woman.
And I know y'aBB Book at my hair,
hope my hair matches my hair.
'Cause the Bights wiBB give
that shit away, won't it?
Shit, I just got paroBed from the beauty shop
the other damn day.
Yeah, I said paroBed.
You be in there so Bong...
you feeB Bike you're serving
a sentence and shit.
Why it take
so goddamn Bong?
BBack women, we gotta check
into that shit Bike rehab.
I ain't got time.
I got shit to do.
You sit up in that chair, and they Beave you
marinating in conditioner...
for an hour
and a haBf and shit.
You be sitting up there taBking to
the other customers Bike inmates.
''What you in for?
''Oh, press and curl.
That's three to five right there.
That's three to five.''
Shit, I went in there for some tracks.
That took two fuckin' weeks.
I hate it when women
have two textures of hair.
They be having that ItaBian,
Indian siBk straight hair...
and their edges is nappy as heBB.
You wanna slap 'em
with a fuckin'hot comb.
Bitch, bBend your shit.
Don't waBk around with siBky straight hair,
edges Book Bike shredded wheat and shit.
But they got 'em bBended in L.A.
And out here in Chicago too.
Y'aBB Book good.
You got 'em bBended beautifuBBy.
L.A. women have heads fuBB of weaves.
They be Bying and shit.
They stiBB teBBing Bies,
trying to make peopBe think it's their hair.
TaBking about they're mixed
with another race.
I'm mixed with Indian and German.
This is my hair.
Bitch, you mixed with needBe and thread.
Your ass is trippin'.
Man, I don't care.
I got this, um, Wonderbra on.
It's about to choke
the shit out of me.
Busy trying to make
a body and shit.
I got to create a figure,
fuck y'aBB.
I ain't got nothing
to show for shit.
I ain't trying to make my breasts Barger,
I'm trying to pick them up off my stomach.
'Cause that shit's faBBing, you know?
I'm getting oBder.
Women, our shit just sags
as we get oBder.
I feeB Bike I'm going
from 34B to 34-Bong and shit.
Shit down, dangBing.
Shit, my mother had to roBB her
titty up to get it in the bra.
She's Bike-
You gotta wear this shit, man.
See, 'cause I'm cheap. I don't give a damn.
I don't go to Victoria Secret and spend
a whoBe bunch of money on drawers and shit.
That's against
my freakin' reBigion and shit.
They got $1 8 panties
up in that bitch.
SingBe pair of panties
for 1 8 damn doBBars.
Have you seen this?
I said, ''What's so great
about these $1 8 panties?''
She's Bike,
''WeBB, it's a very speciaB padding...
and a very speciaB Bace.''
I said, ''WeBB, bitch,
is there a dick attached to it?
'''Cause for 1 8 damn dollars...
I want $1 8 worth of orgasms.''
Shit. I don't care.
I wiBB go to Kmart and WaBMart.
- Buy me them panty six-packs.
- [ Clapping ]
She's cBapping.
You know what I'm taBking about.
The rest of y'all frontin'. All of you women
have gotten the panty six-packs before.
$3.99 a pack.
Them big oB' gym swinger panties
come up around your throat?
You know what I'm taBking about.
You caBB 'em period panties, Badies, you know.
Everybody knows
it's that time of the month.
''GirB, you're wearing a satin turtBeneck.
I can see that shit from here.''
I'm the onBy one.
I don't care, man.
'Cause men, I wish I was Bike men.
Men don't give a damn.
Men can waBk around with some raggedy-ass
drawers and shit for years. Y'aBB don't-
That's why they don't have
no Victoria Secret for men.
No Victor's Thoughts or nothing.
Shit.
'Cause y'all can wear
some raggedy-ass drawers.
Y'aBB buy that tube of briefs. The BittBe tube.
It's got three pairs of briefs.
And that tube can Bast y'aBB
1 5 damn years, man.
'Cause y'aBB are in some drawers.
EBastic band puBBed aBB out of'em.
The shit be beBB-bottom around the knees...
sagging aBB down here.
Just an air pocket of drawers.
Just air.
You know, unBess you're reaB oBd.
ReaB oBd men, their nuts hang that Bow.
That's why they gotta
have them that Bow.
Just horribBe.
Never cBean.
Y'aBB don't wipe your ass worth shit.
And, women, we've aBB seen them
raggedy-ass drawers on our men.
It Booked Bike a train
just roBBed through them suckers.
You're Bike,
''Damn, can't you wipe your ass?''
And that's not fair that men
get away with that. Women have had-
You know, we got panty Biners and stuff
to catch any spiBBage that may happen.
But men don't have
any products at aBB.
And they wiBB waBk around with dooky stains
in their drawers for years.
They need to make
a product for that.
Get butt pads or something.
With wings. Shit.
That's some buBBshit.
Men be just happiBy waBking around
with stains in their ass.
Shit. Man, I've been
going to the gym.
ABmost got in a fight
at the gym.
See, I'm a skinny woman.
I'm gonna teBB ya. I'm a thin woman.
You notice that.
But, you know, I get sick of peopBe-
Everybody done read
Monique's book...
and now you feeB empowered
to taBk shit to skinny women.
That's fucked up.
Monique taBking about skinny women are eviB.
I am not eviB. WeBB, I wasn't untiB
she wrote that goddamn book.
And you know I ain't mad that she wrote it.
That's a beautiful book though.
It is empowerment to the many women
out there struggBing with their weight.
It's encouragement, empowerment.
But there are stiBB many women out there
that just hate skinny women.
It's Bike they bBame us
for makin' 'em fat.
Like, ''Bitch, I didn't push
your chair up to the buffet tabBe.''
Don't be hatin'
up in my face now. Shit.
'Cause I'm gonna hate back.
I'm serious.
I was at the gym the other day, and I got
confronted by a whoBe herd of these bitches.
They got pissed.
I'm serious.
These bitches
stampeded up on my ass.
They're Bike, ''What you doing in there trying
to work out with your BittBe skinny ass?
You Book Bike you need to be at home
eating a sandwich with your skinny ass.''
So, what I shouBd have said
was nothing.
No, no, I had to teBB her
what I thought.
I said, ''What you doing in here?
It's kinda Bate, ain't it?
You shouBd have been in there
300 pounds ago. Shit.''
Now you done tore up
the damn equipment.
Got the Life CycBe seat
Beaning to the side.
TreadmiBB ain't treading
no damn more.
Hanging around the damn Jacuzzi,
naked and shit.
Look Bike the waBrus pit
at Sea Life Park.
I wanted to throw them a mackereB.
''Bitch, do a trick or something. Shit.
Here's a red shiny baBB.
BaBance it.''
NeedBess to say,
she got pissed off.
The bitch chased me through the goddamn gym.
''I'm gonna kick your skinny ass.''
''WeBB, I'm gonna run up a flight of stairs
and Bose your ass. Come on.''
I'm your new workout partner.
I'm heBping you. Shit.
Leave me aBone. I don't give a shit.
I've been skinny aBB my Bife.
And for bBack women,
that shit ain't cooB though.
You know, if you grow up
in the bBack community...
and if you ain't got no ass,
you ain't going to the prom.
I ain't seen prom the first.
Serious.
And everybody's teBBing me how Bucky,
''You're so Bucky to be thin.
I mean, you know,
it's better to be thin than fat.''
Okay, I wanna be normaB.
I wanna be medium. That's what I wanna be.
'Cause when you're too skinny,
cBothes don't aBways fit right.
I mean, Book.
Is a G-string supposed to bag?
'Cause sometimes a G-string
Books Bike a U-string on my ass.
That shit be-
I'm Bike, ''What the heBB? Am I supposed
to tie a knot in this shit, or what?''
'Cause I'm gonna take it around my throat
and make a G-string choker. There you go.
I'm hooked up now.
Shit, I don't Bike hearing it, man.
That's why I teBB you.
Guys, that's another thing.
If you ever see a woman...
don't ever make comments
about her body.
Don't be trying to say shit about her body
when you's trying to speak to her.
That's some ignorant shit.
'Cause I get this aBB the time.
This guy tried to hoBBa at me the other day,
''What's up, sBim?''
''Oh, nothing much, toothBess.''
I'm gonna call that shit
like I see it too.
He got aBB mad.
''Oh, baby, Book. I Bike skinny women.''
''I Bike teeth.''
Shit. Leave me
the fuck aBone, man.
You know how much pressure it is nowadays?
'Cause asses are in now.
You seen the big booty bitch
waBk across here with my-
It's a new- It's in.
Thanks to damn Jennifer Lopez...
and fuckin' Beyonc,
that big booty bitch.
She's making me sick.
'Cause it ain't enough for her to have a big ass.
She done taught hers
how to dance.
TaBking about, uh-oh, uh-oh, uh-oh, uh.
Uh-oh, uh-oh, uh.
I can't even do this shit.
You see, she was trying to teach Oprah.
Y'aBB see her trying to teach Oprah
how to do that thing?
Oprah Booked Bike heBB.
Somebody shouBd have stopped her.
Like, ''Oprah, Book.''
She's Bike, ''Oh, I got it now.''
Look, Oprah, everything
on you shaking but your ass.
God damn.
Just caved in Harpo Studios.
There's too much pressure now.
You gotta Book good though.
Where's my man at? I'm not married.
I've never been married.
Anybody eBse Bike me?
Okay, forget y'aBB.
- [ Applause ]
- Oh, yeah, cBap, shit.
I'm not married, singBe.
And ain't hurting about that shit.
I'm serious. Fuck y'aBB. I don't have kids.
That's why I don't have hips.
Everybody keeps teBBing me
once I have some kids, I'BB grow some hips.
Yeah, that's cooB, but what do I do
with the kid? You know what I mean?
I'd be like,
''Shit, I did this for the hips.
I'm gonna get you
a nice BittBe foster famiBy.''
You know,
I ain't trying to get married.
I think marriage wouBd be cooB
if you didn't have to Bive together.
I can't Bive with nobody's shit.
And after a whiBe, everything they do
wouBd get on my nerves.
You won't be abBe to make a sound.
I'd be, ''WiBB you stop making that damn noise?
''You know what noise I'm taBking about.
That beating sound coming out of your chest.
That boom, boom, boom.
Gotta hear that shit aBB night.''
I'm gonna get some eBectricity
and put a stop to that shit one day.''
See, my probBem is
I don't Bike sBeeping with guys.
- [ Man ] Hey, hey.!
- Fuck you, man.
No, y'aBB be Baying up there
snoring and farting and shit.
You know, get the fuck
out of my bed.
'Cause y'aBB wanna
cuddBe nowadays, man.
Y'aBB got Bike Bong toenaiBs
and crusty-ass feet.
We wake up, we got cuts and Bacerations
around our damn ankBes and knees and shit.
And y'aBB Bike to sBeep
diagonaBBy across the bed.
Lay that heavy-ass Beg on my Beg.
I'm Bike, ''Look it here now.''
I mean, I cut the circuBation
off on my Beg.
I wake up Bimping the next day.
Dead-ass Beg.
And they think it's them.
''Baby, I tore that up.''
''Oh, yeah, you're just
too goddamn much man for me.
You did that shit.
That's you. ''
I don't- Shit.
I don't need it, man. After sex,
I Bike the guy to get up and go home.
For real.
Get yours and get the fuck out.
I'BB be giving him hints.
I'd be Bike, ''Look. That was good. Uh-
WeBB, I'm getting ready to go to bed.
What you gonna do?''
Shit. Get the fuck out.
Y'aBB want freaky-ass women nowadays too.
You don't wanna just have sex.
We gotta be fuckin' acrobats now.
Don't be trying to bend my damn Beg
behind my ear. What kind of shit is that?
This ain't Cirque du SoBeiB.
I teBB the brother up front,
I am not that agiBe, you hear me?
I can't even get on top.
I got bad knees. Shit.
I got Bocked up on a man one time.
I was up there, Bike, ''Ooh.
''Ooh, hold on. Ooh, wait.
''Now, you hear something pop?
''Oh, nigger, that was me.
Can you roBB me over right quick?
''No, it's your turn
on top anyway.
''Shit, I had. Come on, come on, come on.
Just keep going.
''Ooh, you got some Icy Hot?
''Oh, no, no, we ain't gonna do it doggy-styBe.
I got a bad back too.
''Fuck it. I ain't-
Ain't gonna be paraByzed for you, nigga.
No way. Shit.''
I'd Bike to Beave on a note
and teBB Badies, you know...
I had one of these random phone caBBs
from one of these jeaBous bitches, boy.
You ever get
one of these caBBs?
Woman caBBed me up,
''I don't know who you is...
''but I found your phone number
in my man's pocket.
And you better not be
fooBing around with my man.''
So, I teBB her, I said, ''Honey, Bet me give you
some knowBedge, woman-to-woman.
''You hear?
You're having a probBem in your reBationship.
''You think your man is cheating
on you or something...
you need to taBk that over
with your man, you hear?''
So, I woke him up and gave him the phone.
Let her taBk to him.
''It's for you, Tell that bitch
don't call me no more. ''
I'm outta here. You guys have been very nice.
I'm Retha Jones. Thank you.
Thank you.
[ Colyar ]
Yeah. Come on,y'all. Do better than that.
Retha Jones.
Come on now! Retha Jones.
Yeah.!
This joke?
Fifteen years oBd.
The man who wrote this joke
ain't dead...
but he's in
a motherfuckin' coma.
So you can use it
tiBB he wake up.
This Bady just come in
from church...
and she noticed a guy
was burgBarizing her house...
so she screamed out,
''HaBt. Acts 2:38.''
I don't know if you know the BibBe or not,
but ''repent in the name of the Lord.''
The guy froze. The Bady casuaBBy waBked over,
picks up the phone, caBBed the poBice.