Edited by KIRIOUS
SAO PAULO, BRAZIL
- you are alone?
- I am.
What up, father?
Baaba died.
- what you mean dead ?
- His wife called from the mortuary.
It was found nacked
in a hotel room.
- nacked?
- he was using condom.
- what happed?
- He died...
and we have to do the delivery
in two hours.
Tell the Africans
that will change the date.
The ship will sail in the morning.
It is now or never.
Where do you think
we gonna find a "mule"...
that he speaks "Yurumbi", or what
language it is, they will rape us of?
Don't worry.
Just come over here.
Fuck!
Shit!
- Who is it ?
- Open the door..
We need to talk.
The worst happened.
Baaba is dead.
- Paul, listen...
- Didn't you hear me? I Said Baaba died.
- Who is Baaba?
- "Who is Baaba?"
Take this
are you crazy?
What happend with you?
Why are you acting like this?
You dont remember?
He would negotiate
with the Africans...
and steal the money.
To steal from who?
Of my father.
You gonna steal your fathers money?
Everything was drifted.
We will split the money.
But he is your father.
How do you think we will leave from here?
With our beauty?
Our charm?
I will find a way. Go home
and wait for me to call you.
Paul...
I need to speak with you.
Don't worry, Angie.
We will leave tomorrow.
Nothing changed.
whats up, boss?
to your new house!
to your new life!
Wemba.
Wemba!
Sr. Rosso.
sorry, I didn't hear.
I didn't hear, sorry.
Hi.
- Where are you from?
- Nigeria.
- Speech loruba?
- Yes, some...
How come you came here?
- In Brazil?
- Sao Paulo.
I came to seek work.
In Nigeria, it is...
Is everything well?
Do you want to win some extra money?
- Money?
- Yes.
I don't know.
It depends...
How much money
So much that never again you will
need to wash plates as long as you live.
Don't give the suitcase before receiving
the money. Did you understand?
Yes, I understood.
Call me right after
everything has done.
Call me in that numbers
- Promise that you will call.
- Yes, I will call.
- you can leave.
- Right.
Wemba...
I dislike to do that...
but I will need
of a guarrantee.
- you guaranteed for...
- Your passport.
My passport.
it is better to have it with me..
I work for you
about 3 ...4 years.
I never took anything from you...
I dont do...
I don't do such thing...
I see you later.
- What was?
- I don't believe that you trust him.
I don't have choice.
Drive.
Wemba is a good man.
I trust him.
How does you know that is reliable?
They only negotiate with Africans
that you they speak loruba.
Do you speak loruba?
Just, stop complaining.
Who guarantees that he wont
flee with the money?
There you come again.
God damned!
He is on his way.
you cant bring him back.
He will give the cocaine,
be back in a few hours...
- and we will be rich.
- You will be rich.
I will have luck
in paying off my debts.
I never rised you to be come
a degenerate player.
No, you created me
to be a pimp.
- Stop the car.
- what?
Stop the car. Pull over now.
lets go, Lets go home.
I need to arrange packing.
You need to go to the nightclub.
I have a plenty time.
It is still early.
Listen here...
the nightclub is yours now.
Sell and skirt of Brazil. I only want
to go back to the United States.
Sell that dirtbag. Return to
New York and start from zero.
I am only tellingyou that this
is your last chance.
Dont destroy everything.
A taxi.
You call me
as soon as you have knews from him.
I will call you in the same moment.
Is everything well?
Everything is perfect.
I returned in businesses
with the dish washer.
Baaba did me a favor
by dropping dead.
- what?
- I will split the money.
I didn't make that agreement
with the dish washer.
you made a business
with the dish washer?
Yes, we will get rid of him
when he returns with the money.
Before he give them
to your father?
Honey?
Hi, babby.
Hi.
I can see you finished with the packing.
Yes, the housemaid
took care of almost everything.
Are you well?
I am great.
I am only having a headache.
- Do you want an aspirin?
- No.
I already took one.
I will prepare the boy.
How were the things?
They were well.
There was a small problem.
But I already took care of everything.
Our man should arrive there
at any minute.
- Do you have the tickets?
- Yes.
Everything is in this envelope.
- Which is my new name?
- I don't remember.
You don't remember me ?
lets go, little man.
- where are we going ?
- You know very well.
- I don't know,.
- yes you do.
- Tell me.
- We are moving away.
- Right. Where are we moving?
- I forgot.
We are going to a place...
hot, sunny
and entertaining.
Give a hug to your father.
I love you
more than everything in life.
Dad?
Do the monkeys fly?
- what?
- Do the monkeys fly?
Mom said not.
- Well, that is not true.
- But they don't have wings.
They don't have wings...
but your mother is not
specialist in primates...
as your father is.
you knows, Lazar...
There was a rare race of monkeys
that actually can fly.
Be looking. He will fly
direct to the moon.
I lost my monkey.
- I am sorry.
- We will find the monkey tomorrow, ok?
I 'll get that.
Angie, sorry
for that I did before.
I was overreacted.
- Everything is well now.
- Listen...
I am with the passports
and the tickets.
I cant make that.
why?
What did change your mind?
I cant.
I won't make that.
is Wemba?
No, Is your son.
What do you want?
Do you have any news from Wemba?
Not yet.
He will call soon.
- How can you be sure?
- Christ! There you come again.
I need the money
as much as you.
- Nobody said the opposite.
- He should not have gone alone.
Enough ! I will call you
when I have news.
Calm!
Be calm!
Nothing did happen!
Get the fuck out of my street,
You crazy transvestite!
what?
Disappear from here!
Cow!
Shit!
you are fucking dead!
You fucking shit!
Shit!
Try to win money
with that face now.
Let me get that.
Wemba.
I am with the money.
Everything ran well.
- I am going to the car.
- great.
you are halfway from home.
Come slowly.
Don't drive to fast, dont brake any traffic
signal, put the safe belt in the car...
Just take your time.
We will be waiting for you at the nightclub.
Wemba?
what happed?
I don't know.
Wait for me inside.
I will return as soon as I can.
Will we leave this night?
I hope so.
And what will happend
if you cant find Wemba?
I prefer not to think that.
- Dad?
- Yes?
Will you give me a new monkey?
sorry, Lazar.
Now I am not be able to.
- your Dad is busy now.
- What hell happend to you?
- What did with you happen?
- Nothing. What are you doing here?
I want them to be here
for couple hours.
- Where is Wemba?
- I don't know.
Don't know?
I lost contact with him.
Something happened.
- Where is he?
- He is missing.
- He is missing ?
- Wemba he is missing.
I don't know what happened there
I will tell you what happend!
The mother fucker went back to the africa
with our money!
Thats happened!
Stupid!
I will find the money, Paul.
I promise.
Now what?
Get in the car and follow him.
And me?
Catch the motorcycle...
and wait at Africans apartment
- Detective.
- Hi, man.
- sit down.
- Thank you.
So...
Why You came to visit us here?
- What happened to your head?
- That...
It was nothing. it is only a scratch.
you look very bad my friend.
- I should congratulate him.
- To congratulate? Why?
- You are taking over the nightclub ?
- Quite so.
he will retire,
You know?
He bought a house in the north.
He will move there...
...sit by the pool...enjoy the sun..
Good for him. He deserves that,
Your father is a good man.
Of course, A policeman's pension
cant allow him to do things like that...
...A policeman needs to accept
a humbler destiny.
They cant afort all to have a place in the sun.
Or do they have?
- I don't know if I am understanding you.
- Stop fucking arount.
I already know about the business
that you have this night.
I could have arrested you
6 months ago for dealing drugs.
- How much?
- I want half.
- Half?
- Yes. Half.
Let me explain something to you,
detective.
At this time, our "mule"
is missing in action.
I don't know where he is.
And is probably...
...never see him again in my life.
I want to be paid with one way or another.
How I can pay you if I dont have any money?
you are a smart man.
Use your brain...
I will return tomorrow night
to collect.
Who are you?
Does you speak English?
Yes, I speak English.
Fuck!
what happed?
Do you need some help?
No, everything its ok.
Who steals the key
of the car and doesn't take the car?
Cant make any...
..sense.
Thank you.
Thank you very much.
You are sure you are ok to drive?
What ?
Your father has just entered
in the fortune-teller's house.
- what? A fortune-teller?
- Yes, this one...
that he finds disappeared
people for the police.
He has the talent. it is famous.
Fuck! I call you later.
Angie?
Angie.
What is going on?
tell me.
Speak to me.
I cant do it.
No, listen.
we can Just talk, it is ok?
- I cant do this.
- Listen...
- Not now.
- Not now?
Then, when?
Now I need you
more than ever.
The world is collapsing
in my head.
We can have a talk about this.
what are you talking about.
Listen to your self?
We will leave tomorrow.
Why are you thinking,
I am doing all these?
I love you
more than everything in the life.
I only want to take care of you.
- Is not right.
- What is not right?
- is it because of him?
- What do you think? He is my husband.
you are playing with me?
He is a damned pimp.
A pimp!
He made you to suck
a thousand cocks before he marry you.
How you can even call him, your husband?
Let go me!
Edited by KIRIOUS
Angie...
Please listen to me.
Everything that I did...
I did it for you...
and for our son.
All the plans that have made.
- why we cant wait?
- I wish that we can wait, but we cant.
Everything are collapsing.
Please.
I am beging you.
Help me.
I send a man to do a job
and he disappeared.
He disappear with what?
With everything.
Be more specific.
He disappeared with the money.
A lot of money.
A million dollars
to be exact.
6 months ago, one of mine
girls was entertained a Russian.
His wife came from nowhere.
She had a wild glance in her eyes
like she had drunk blood.
It happened so fast.
Bang!
Shut up.
you could have given
them to the police.
I know, the police.
What the fuck you think they would have done?
Why I don't deserve
a reward in my life?
- I needed that money.
- You became a drug dealer.
I cannot help
you in this thing.
Clear.
I know about that.
I was hopping if you might make
an exception this time.
I 'am sorry, I am not able to do this.
I know.
I am leaving then.
If you dont have anything else.. ?
Maybe you can tell me.
Does My wife love me?
And...
does my little boy is my son?
- Wemba is here.
- what?
Wemba has just arrived here.
Come to the nightclub.
Are you well?
Everything is well.
Just come back to the nightclub
because he is here.
I am already coming.
was my wife.
My man returned back
I have to leave.
And that question...
..Just forget about it.
I am not interesting anymore?
Any way...
Good-bye, friend.
Good-bye.
- What ?
- Your father has just left the house.
- I know.
- How can you know?
Go inside there
and discover what he said.
Do you study?
Yes, I study.
What are you studying ?
A lot of things.
I take several courses.
- I don't know.
- You dont know or you dont want to tell me?
Bookkeeping.
What is bookkeeping?
it is similar to accounting.
Why you dont studying ccounting?
When I was girl,
I wanted to become a doctor.
But my grandmother said that was
easier to be a nurse.
If I wanted to be an accountant,
I could be one.
But you want to be a clerk.
Yes, clerk.
What kind of job do you do now?
can you drive quite,
please?
thank for your help,
but I don't want to talk.
Can we stop here?
I need to go to the bathroom.
I am not able to.
I cannot make that.
I cannot stop now.
- You have to Wait until we arrived to the city.
- Please, I am tight.
I cannot make that.
I don't have time to stop.
Do you understand?
I will right back.
I will drive now.
- Are you fealing ok?
- I am great.
Look, I am sorry for that I said befor.
You know about for you to being a clerk.
It should be a legal job.
Be silence. I don't want to talk.
I will take you to the city.
And Then, do what ever you want.
But for the rest of the ride I dont want to talk.
I have things
very important to do.
Shit! He doesn't want to speak!
- what?
- I said...
that he doesn't want to cooperate!
- Make him to cooperate.
- What you want me to do?
He is an old man!
- I want to speak with him.
- He doesn't want to speak!
Put the telephone
in his ear!
I will try!
But you don't scream, ok ?
Listen here, you old bastard...
It was a man  just in
your store.
I know that you spoke with him.
I want to know exactly
what you said to him.
And I want to know now.
I am waiting.
That bastard resistance
doesn't work with me,
This is your only chance to
come out of the game clean.
I seek a missing African
named Wemba.
I want you to Use what ever mystic
powers you have and....
...tell me where
I can find him.
I can hear you fucking breathing,
friend.
- Rodrigo!
- What I did tell you before?
If he doesnt cooperate,
you must kill the dog.
what?
I won't kill the dog.
- yes, you will kill his dog.
- Is not good,man.. is not good!
Let me explain something to you.
We are fucked
if we don't find the African.
We won't have the money.
Nor you, nor me, nor nobody.
it is the same as we placed ourselves
in front of a train!
you are understanding?
I am.
Well, take the telephone
and put it in his ear.
Then point the weapon
at the dog.
When I say, shoot.
Ready?
Listen, old man. I told to my man
tol kill your dog...
...if you don't cooperate
and answer my questions.
This is your fucking last chance, old man.
Say where I can
find Wemba...
or else I will burst the inside out
of your dog. Did you understand?
- Rodrigo!
- Yes!
- Kill the dog.
- But me...
Kill it!
Kill the damned dog,
you idiot!
Kill the damned dog!
Kill the god damned dog,
Fuck!
Shit.
Bring him to the nightclub.
I will make him talk.
Shit!
Angie.
What do you want?
Hi, father.
What the fuck is going on?
I want something to tell you.
Better to be good.
- It depends on your point of view.
- What the fuck are talking about?
- it is better to sit down.
- No.
- I need to find Wemba...
- what?
And fast.
- He is not here?
- No.
Why Angie tald me that
was here?
- You are out.
- what?
You are out.
Am I out of what?
you won't receive any part
of the money.
- Angie, what is he is talking about?
- She doesn't know anything.
Let me try to understood.
You thinks that you can take
my part of the money.
My Money for the house
and for my son's education.
- The money are mine, right ?
- The money are not yours for sure.
You found those
dirty money.
Dirty money belongs to anybody have them.
you are out of your fucking mind.
you needs those money to pay
a game debts?
Theoretically, yes.
But I won't pay them.
I won't pay anybody.
I want more for my life.
By Stealing your own father?
I am giving you the nightclub.
You are a god damned drug addict.
Why do you think that I would let
you steal my money?
You don't have a choice.
- Is Wemba part of that?
- No.
The dish washer betrayed us.
- You are the traitor.
- Enough...!!
We needed to find the
damned Wemba now!
Listen me you idiot.
I was seeking for him...
- and you call me, idiot ...
- I know where you were...
- And I know whata you were doing.
- How you gona find him here?
sorry for the dog.
Bastard !
Stop!
This is good. you can leave me
anywhere you want.
- Does your grandmother lives here?
- Yes.
- is it even?
- it is.
- In which building?
- In that there.
- Are you sure?
- Of course I am sure.
I would not know where it lives
my grandmother?
Everything well then.
Take care your self.
You too.
- Thanks, for the ride.
- You will be ok ?
I will be ok.
- Where are going?
- What?
you said that your grandmother house is there.
- Look your own business.
- where are you going?
I don't know.
I live here in the top flour.
Apartment 5B.
- Take the key.
- Look, this a very nice thing that you are doing...
Everything will be ok.
I will return late.
you can sleep in the bed.
I will sleep in the sofa tonight.
- No, I can sleep in the sofa.
- No, Its allright. I don't care.
ok
I need to go now.
Right. Thank you.
I dont even know your name...
Wemba.
Nice to meeting you, Wemba.
My name is Monique.
- What the fuck was that?
- I don't know!
- Keep your head down!
- And You keep your head down!
What the fuck is he doing?
Drive Faster! Come on!
What are you doing?
Why are you stopping?
If I ll speed the car...
- police will stop us.
- Let them stop us? You are fucking crazy?
what?
What does have the fucking bag?
is he?
it is him.
Lets go!
The key!
Try this.
Lets go!
It is locked on the outside.
We are truped!
Back!
He is coming!
Monique!
Everything well?
Monique, what happed to you?
Monique!
Which is your problem?
Where is Lazar?
- Sleeping at the Room 3.
- Lazar is fine.
you want to read him a bedstory, to sleep?
You realy become a picture...
..of an old and invalid father,
did you know?
Yes, it is true.
Dont you want the truth to come out?
we are a family here, are we?
The Secrets don't exist
in a family.
All the cards should be
open on the table.
Where do you want to get at?
Without secrets.
The honesty is
the best politic.
The truth sall let us free.
"You won't lie. "
"You won't commit adultery. "
"You won't covet the woman
of the neighbor. "
"You won't kill. "
Paul, your father's head is bleeding...
He needs a doctor right now.
what about my head? you think
that deserve any compassion?
Did you ever told her what happend
when momm was got sick?
Why you dont do it? Come on, tell her.
You cant?
Then, I will...
When the doctors cut
my mother's breasts...
and send her home to die...
he hired a nurse...
to change the diapers
and to give her  morphine injections.
One day, I was in the back yard...
and I heard a noise.
it seemed to me...
like a wounded animal.
So. I went inside the house..
I run to my mothers room...
and there she was her...
making some very strange sounts..
I couldn't understand her.
Where is the nurse?
I went down running and I found her.
She was...
in the table of the dining room,
lying on the back...
And he was siting on his knees..
and doing her...
something like a gynecological exam?
With his tongue...
Now you know everything!
..you can hear her upstares,
she was griping...
..from cancer in state of 4.
4 - C.
Doesnt have a fucking 5.
She couldnt breathe
nor scream... she was...
And you didn't make anything.
you only thought...
..how to suck the vagina
of the damned nurse.
And now you want my compassion?
Stop with that.
Just Shut up.
- You wouldnt shoot me?
- Shut up!
Alright...
you can shoot me
I tried to call you..
Did you bring the money?
Yes, I brought them
you brought the money.
Do me a favor.
- What is?
- Take my wife...
and my son far away from here.
Go now, before
the police arrive here.
- I need you to go.
- I cant leave you...
you have to go. They will see
all this and they will take Lazar.
- I wont go.
- you don't have other choice.
- Take her.
- I won't leave from here.
- No!
- Please.
- Take Lazar.
- We needed to go now.
- Come with me, please.
- I don't want to go.
Come with me, please.
Give it to me.
Please, African,
pass me the bag.
No.
Please, man.
Give it to me.
- I won't give you anything.
- Shit! Don't make me to kill you.
I am not afraid of you.
- Give me the fucking bag, man!
- You didnt do your last move, Rodrigo.
Give me the fucking bag, man !!!
Go...
- Can you hear me?
- Yes.
The question You asked me before.
Do you want to know the truth?
The truth?
I already know.
Edited by KIRIOUS
GREETINGS FROM GREECE