(Professor Broom) In 1944, a demon was
summoned to the Earth to wage war.
But the child of Hell
was rescued by good men
who taught him honour, kindness,
and a sense of right.
The scientists and researchers
that gathered around the boy
became the Bureau for
Paranormal Research and Defence,
an international organisation
that protects the world
from occult and supernatural threats.
There are things
that go bump in the night.
We are the ones who bump back.
(Woman's voice) Can this be him...
the one I have waited
centuries to see?
How strange.
So far from his path
that I barely see the promise of glory.
Can this be him...
this Hellboy?
Oh, crap!
(Abe) Is something wrong?
No... Yeah.
I'm standing up to my butt in crap,
that's what's wrong.
- Where are you?
- I don't know.
I got all turned around.
It's like a damn maze down here.
A maze of crap.
(Abe) Isn't that why we're here?
Company.
(Heavy footsteps)
(Roaring)
Crap!
Don't suppose this will work.
No, but it'll piss him off.
Go wide.
That's it!
I'll have to
remember that trick.
I'm guessing that's important.
(Groans)
No, I've got it.
Crap.
So, who do you think this is?
Not Hephaestus, surely.
Daedalus?
He designed the labyrinth.
Don't care.
(Growls)
Hey, Liz.
You can tell the professor
he was right.
- We took care of it.
- You can tell him in the morning.
He's already in bed.
All right. See you soon.
Who are these mortals,
who would have you
turn your back on your own kind?
Who?
(Distant howling)
(Rats squeaking)
Professor!
Professor Broom!
- You think she's here?
- Somewhere close. They both are.
(Gasps)
(Whimpers)
(Creaking)
(Screaming)
Father?
I am all right.
It's just...
Your fiancée,
she could still be alive.
But there's not much time before...
What?
- Blood.
- Fresh blood.
Father...
we will need you.
Yes.
Yes, of course.
(Banging)
Anna!
No! No!
Anna.
No! Not my Anna!
My sweet Anna!
(Sobbing)
Father, will you help?
No.
No. I...
I can't!
Yes.
If it will bring her peace.
(Loud clank)
We still have to find her.
Then assist me with this.
(Grinding)
Empty.
- (Gasps)
- Huh?
Where is he?
(Dripping)
Erzsebet Ondrushko.
Ah.
Ha!
(Men whimpering)
Wait! Stay together!
Come to me.
Stop! We mustn't panic!
Please! Stay together!
(Howling)
- We have to get out!
- No!
Run, Professor!
No!
(Barking sounds)
(Woman screaming)
You brought the others,
yet you did not flee with them.
Something to calm your nerves?
Holy water.
- Oh!
- (Sizzling)
My face.
You! You've stolen my beauty!
(Roars)
(Gasps)
(Grunts)
(Growling)
(Sighs)
(Knock on door)
Missed you at breakfast.
I just... overslept.
OK.
See you at the briefing.
No. No, no,
they were in Pakistan.
I'm sure of it.
How could I forget?
We found them after dealing
with that sand demon thing.
Or was it the Andes?
Actually, I believe
it was in Tangiers.
- Boy, can't wait until I see a little action.
- Careful.
I connect it with the ghouls
under Sidi Kasem.
Really? I remember webs.
Lots of webs.
You're both wrong.
They were in Budapest.
Of course.
- After the run-in with...
- That thing!
- In the choir loft...
- Mm-hm. With the arms.
Yeah!
Oh, God! What was
the name of that place? The... The...
The Monkey Paw.
Yes! The Monkey Paw!
Yep. That's where we found 'em.
Found what?
The best pastries on earth.
Excellent. The very best.
Yeah.
These?
This... is crap.
- Hi, guys.
- Good morning, everyone.
Professor Broom.
Professor Corrigan and I have
just a few assignments to... assign
and then we can all get on with our day,
how's that sound?
Coffee's cold.
Hot!
- You'd think he'd learn.
- Yeah, you'd think.
All right, then.
Let's get started.
Hellboy, you're going to Tibet.
You'll team up with Mr Clark.
Now, the Trung-Rom Monastery.
Yeah.
Reputedly built from
the bones of 9,000 monks.
It was dismantled and burned
by the Mongols in the 13th century.
800 years. Now it's back.
Is it just me or could we use
a nice, big conference table?
It's just you.
Miss Sherman, Mr Sapien,
you'll be going to British Columbia.
Ogopogo has been sighted again
in Lake Okanagan.
This time it's evidently
flipped a couple of houseboats.
- Think I'm being typecast?
- (Chuckles) Aren't we all?
Professor Broom?
Thank you.
All right. We've got
one more for this morning.
Small thing. A favour, really.
A friend of the Bureau
has requested an investigation.
An old house in the Hamptons
has just been purchased
by Oliver Trombolt.
Trombolt? The hotel and casino guy?
Yes, he wants to open it as a resort.
And... says it's haunted.
Oh, God.
Can you say "publicity stunt"?
A waste of time.
Look, Trombolt is a good friend
of Senator Langsford
and the Senator has his hands
in the BPRD budget.
So, no haunted house investigation,
no more doughnuts.
No more research equipment.
- No more...
- Give it to the new kid.
- Mr Leach.
- Thanks.
Excuse me
but I think it would be wise
to have Hellboy handle
the Hampton house.
Right!
The Senator would love
having a top agent like Hellboy
make an appearance.
Hmm. Top agent.
But it's more manpower
than the assignment requires,
and, well, we need Hellboy
in Tibet with Mr Clark...
and the 9,000 dead monks in...
Liz and Abraham should go too.
What about me?
Maybe I should go.
No, that won't be necessary.
It's more manpower than...
You see, it's just a political favour.
Oh, for God sake!
It's a publicity stunt, for cryin' out loud!
I have a hunch.
Oh, a hunch?
Oh, well, sure. Go. We'll...
just post a "No Swimming"
sign on Lake Okanagan.
Hey, everybody go!
We can wait another 800 years
for the bones to reappear in Tibet.
Or I could take a team
to Tibet without Hellboy.
Waller's back from Jakarta.
Fine. Just draw straws
for who goes where.
Wonderful idea.
The element of chance
will let fate take a hand.
Now, let's get started.
I just have to round up a few things.
We should leave within the hour.
We?
I mean, what's it been,
six, seven years?
More like 15.
I'm just saying.
Long time between missions.
I don't know.
You don't have to.
It's his decision.
But we're just gonna
have to watch him.
Uh, watch your step, sir.
Hellboy, I'm fine.
You needn't worry.
- Here you go, Professor.
- Thank you.
It's a trifle heavy.
A few special tools, just in case.
So, I heard Trombolt
inherited his money.
I guess if you're gonna
inherit something,
it might as well be money.
Miss Sherman,
you mind if take a look
at the assignment folder?
Call me Liz.
Call me Abe.
Call me...
only if you really need me.
Don't mind him.
He gets crabbier every year.
And he's older than he looks,
so that's a lot of crabbiness.
(Sniffs)
Somebody have garlic for lunch?
(Corrigan) Don't look at me!
Now, about the case...
there might be something here.
I've done a little research.
The Hampton house
has some history to it.
It was built by a millionaire eccentric.
A real nut job.
In the '20s, he played host
to a pagan fertility cult.
Who knows what went on?
Looks like a fun crowd.
There is some anecdotal
evidence of hauntings.
The usual stuff -
shadowy apparitions,
flickering lights,
swinging chandeliers, cold spots.
Which usually mean someone
left a window open.
- Wanna tell us why we're really going?
- Not yet.
Not until I'm sure.
- Are you sure you're ready?
- I'm quite fine, Father.
I'm just not used to the elevation
like you mountain men.
A moment's rest and I'll be ready to go.
No, no. I meant...
the sun is setting.
Would it not better if we came back
tomorrow in the daylight?
No, there is no time.
She has Anna.
We cannot wait.
Not if the girl is to have a chance.
We have dealt with
vampires before, Father.
A stake through the heart,
a clove of garlic on the tongue
and the villagers will
sleep peacefully again.
(Howling)
This one is clever.
But tonight, we send her to hell.
- Will we?
- You must have faith.
Yes. Yes, of course.
The power of God will protect us.
"Though I walk through the valley
of the shadow of death,
- "I shall fear no..."
- (Shrieking)
What was that?
Some sort of birds. Big ones.
Eagles. Hunting.
Just like us.
Keep that close, Father.
A vampire cannot bear
the sight of a cross.
Actually, it is the faith of the person
holding it that gives it power.
You'll be fine.
May I help you?
You're kidding, right?
We are from the Bureau
for Paranormal Research and Defence.
I believe we are expected.
Please come in.
Wonderful! You're here!
I'm Oliver Trombolt.
And of course I already know who you are.
Hellboy.
Liz Sherman.
Abe Sapien.
Ah, Professor Broom.
Founding father of the BPRD.
I'm honoured, sir.
And...
Agent Sidney Leach,
human metal detector.
Pleased to meet you.
Ah, yes, I'm sure that's very useful.
I know all about you
and your organisation.
And we've heard lots about you.
Nice digs.
Tell me you're not serious.
I hope this will be suitable.
Had them bring in some tables.
Plenty of power outlets.
No, this is great.
I'll set up.
We'll try to stay out of your way.
I'm impressed.
The Bureau actually
sent their A-team.
- Hey!
- It's for the brochure.
We don't do photo-ops.
Right, right.
Maybe we can get some later.
You and me out in front of the house?
Maybe when the Senator stops by.
You know, I've seen
some pretty strange things
since I bought this house.
- Really?
- But to tell the truth,
I'm not so sure I believe in ghosts.
Well, we hear that a lot.
Thermal camera?
Yeah, wouldn't want
to miss any cold spots.
I'll get it.
Ask me, this guy's just out
to make a buck.
You're most likely right.
But that doesn't mean there isn't
something happening in this house.
I did what you asked.
Leave me alone.
Fool! Your work is not done.
All right. Check the signal.
It's decent.
Wouldn't video cables
cut down on interference though?
Haven't used them
since a poltergeist
hung Raf Hurtado by his
heels in the Whaley House.
- Really?
- Occupational hazard.
The motion sensor
goes down there.
He was upside down for four hours!
We found him after two,
but that guy was such a jerk.
Did you...
Should I take a picture?
Dang!
Of what? A closed door?
Relax. I'm sure you'll get plenty of
thrills 'n' chills before we're done.
Is that why
Professor Broom is here?
I don't know.
It's not like we haven't faced
scary stuff without him.
Real scary stuff.
Give me the sensor.
Hellboy acts like he's going to
fall down and snap something.
This thing doesn't
have a battery in it.
Oh, I'm sorry. I've got some here.
- They're really close, aren't they?
- Oh, yeah.
You know, not everybody
thought keeping a demon
that the Nazis summoned
to win World War 2 was a good thing.
Kill it!
It's a demon come from hell
to destroy us all!
Aw, it looks more like a little boy.
Hellboy.
The professor raised him like a son
on an Air Force base in New Mexico.
That's got it.
So yeah, they're about as close as...
What?
The statues are crying.
Huh. Check for plumbing.
Remember, Trombolt
bought this place for tourists.
It's not for tourists.
(Liz) Are you guys OK?
Hellboy's not here.
You know how he is with delicate
equipment. Anything wrong?
(Liz) We've definitely got a ghost.
Young woman, Eastern European.
Sort of a peasant girl,
if that makes any sense.
Wait a minute.
Temperature's dropping.
Huh?
Liz? I think we have
more than one.
I'll meet you back in the parlour.
Come on.
Somebody's in here.
Show me what you got.
I'm not gonna hurt you
unless you make me.
So, there is something going on here.
Just how big is it?
What did you see?
Ghosts.
Looking for help, I think.
But they didn't want me.
You can't stay, Professor.
I'm no longer Director
of Field Operations
but I'm not ready to retire.
I'm not saying that.
But you shouldn't be here. You're too...
Old?
I'm sorry I don't share your
seemingly eternal youth.
You grew so fast at first.
In no time at all,
you were too big to spank.
Only cos the tail got in the way.
(Trombolt) So everything is in place.
So, do you think you might
get something tonight?
- We might get lucky.
- You too?
This is amazing stuff! Amazing.
It truly is. I don't
know what to say.
Yet, he just keeps talking.
Ah. Here you go. Some snacks.
Please, help yourselves.
- Going somewhere?
- I never stay in after dark.
(Liz) OK, let's cut the lights
and see if anyone pops up.
(Beeping)
Huh.
I think...
I think I'm getting a reading.
Oh, yeah. Here we go.
- Aah!
- (Crackling on headphones)
- Which rooms are these?
- (Liz) All of them.
They're everywhere!
What the hell? Where'd they go?
Professor!
(Prays in Latin)
Are you OK?
They were so frightened.
I was right.
This place is a gold mine.
Not if we have to quarantine.
Ah, let's not be too hasty.
A few ghosts, that can't be
that bad, can it?
It is very bad.
Devil.
Witch.
Hell.
And the names Marianna Molnar
and Treszka Balogh,
the two witches who trained
Erzsebet Ondrushko.
Ah, the Hungarian Blood Countess.
She thought bathing in the blood of
young women would keep her young.
Now we just go
to the plastic surgeon.
I've researched her.
In fact, she'll be the central image
of my marketing campaign.
Sexy witch, spooky legend.
It's the perfect thing
for these people.
It's not legend, it's fact.
Those spirits were her victims.
While she lived,
Erzsebet tortured and murdered
613 young women
to feed her vanity.
But her worst atrocities didn't happen
until after she was dead.
Vampire.
But you... destroyed her in 1939.
So I thought.
The point remains that, altogether,
Erzsebet is responsible for slaughtering
over a thousand people.
Yes, well, maybe not everything
has to go in the brochure.
It could be someone is trying
to bring back Erzsebet.
A hunch?
If there's no body, they would need
something intimately connected to her.
Huh?
Yeah. That'd probably do it.
Hecate. Greek goddess
and Queen of the Witches.
As a vampire,
Erzsebet claimed to be
a high priestess to Hecate.
We may be dealing with
something larger here.
There are things in this world
that modern man
relegates to fairy tales
and video games.
But they are real. They are ugly,
and they demand terrible
payments for their "gifts".
No gifts here.
These weren't cheap.
They're all originals.
Had them shipped from
the ruins of Erzsebet's castle.
Cost quite a bit to restore too.
I would imagine
they're still quite effective.
It's wax.
Just place it over there.
She's very beautiful.
Was very beautiful.
And she knew it.
Her vanity became her obsession.
Instead of losing her beauty,
she lost her soul.
(Wind whistling)
(Bird cawing)
(Creaking)
Hello?
Is someone there?
- (Growling)
- (Gasps)
(Screams)
(Whimpers)
I know you are coming.
You and that Englishman.
You should not.
Who?
You know.
How?
How could I invade
the sanctity of this church?
Please. You put your faith
in wood and plaster.
But where is your saviour?
Lt... lt is a symbol of God's... Huh?
My goddess gives me power
and eternal beauty.
Your God, what?
False hope?
Unanswered prayers?
A better life after death?
I have that too.
You are the forsaken one, Father.
Ah!
Yes, I'm serious.
They shot straight through us.
Must have been a hundred of them.
I mean, Marcos, you realise
I didn't anticipate any of this.
Back out?
Are you crazy?
I'm doubling my ticket prices.
Find me more houses like this!
We'll franchise!
Not sure what to do
about the professor, though.
Tends to be a bit... morbid.
Yeah. Takes all the fun out of a haunting.
Sure, sure. I'll...
I'll think of something.
OK. Yeah, OK.
I'll talk to you later.
Bye.
(Distant howling)
(Liz) Everything's normal on video.
Of course, we don't have
cameras in every room.
Not in the budget.
Thank you, Senator Langsford.
- (Electronic noise)
- Whoa, whoa, whoa.
I've got some kind of weird sounds.
I can't pin it down.
(Yawns)
Great.
Abe, why don't you and me
go check things out?
Maybe we can stir something up.
- I'll go too!
- Sure.
He'll protect us.
Maybe you can keep
an eye on the professor.
You know, he's...
Yeah. He's special to all of us.
Come on, guys.
What are we waiting for?
It is time, sister.
The stars are right.
All ye gods of the groves,
all ye gods of the night,
be with us now.
Let the triple goddess
aid us, favour us.
Renew your servant.
Feed flesh and sinew,
bone and tooth.
Return our priestess.
(Gasps)
Oh! You must be Anna!
Come here, child,
where we can see you.
Do I know you?
(Laughs)
Oh, everyone in the village
knows of the bride-to-be.
So beautiful, isn't she, sister?
Yes, and so young, like a kitten.
But you can't stay out in the night
with a couple of chattering old women.
It's not safe.
No, definitely not safe.
We've seen your wedding gown.
Oh, so beautiful.
Hurry along now!
Yes, my wedding gown.
Excuse me, then.
I shouldn't keep Marie waiting.
Goodbye.
- Goodbye.
Hello, Marie! How does it look?
Will it be beautiful? Marie?
Oh. I'm sorry if I startled you.
Here, let me take your coat
so we can get started.
Mm, what a lovely scent.
Where is Marie?
She is upstairs with the baby.
It was not feeling well
and took a turn for the worse.
I said her place
was at the baby's side
and I would take care of you.
But she said there was
to be a final fitting.
Are you a... seamstress?
Oh! One of the best, they say.
Oh, my gown!
I came here right from the opera.
So young, like a kitten.
I had no time to change.
But... I could come back.
Nonsense.
How could you walk away
from this?
Oh!
It is wonderful!
How is the veil?
Made of the finest lace,
but I don't want to cover the rosy cheeks
of such a young girl.
(Giggles) You talk like an old woman.
You couldn't be older than my sister.
Your... older sister?
- Yes.
- Really?
That old.
I'm so glad I came.
I almost didn't.
The killings, those girls.
You aren't afraid of the vampire?
Father Lupescu says no vampire
would dare enter a village
protected by his church.
Then I have the priest
to thank for your visit.
I must return the favour.
But he did meet
with the Englishman
who is supposed to be an expert
on such things as vampires.
(Gasps)
I am something of an expert myself.
(Growling)
(Anna screams)
(Door opens)
(Growling)
(Broom) What was that?
Sorry, Professor,
just the equipment acting up.
- Go on back to sleep.
- (Alarm)
Huh?
The basement motion detector.
Stay where you are.
We'll check it out.
About time.
Something's in the torture chamber.
It's just the old man.
Little late for a stroll.
You a sleepwalker?
I... I am the one who sold these...
showpieces to Mr Trombolt.
I must go. I have work to do.
What?
- Blood. That's blood.
- Where did it come from?
(Whimpers) No... I...
(Abe) Over here.
OK, cover your eyes.
Wait! Let me.
Human metal detector, remember?
Least he's not a psychic.
I'm thinking maybe
hidden doorway and, uh...
Yep. Heh-heh. Here it is.
(Clunking)
Trombolt.
He's been drained of his blood.
I... I found it.
Talk!
I didn't want to.
- Go on!
- I... I can't.
I saw you look at the professor.
What was that about?
Stop! He didn't do anything.
You're the priest.
I was once a priest.
- I thought you were staying back.
- Oh, like he would listen to me.
He was with me
when I last confronted Erzsebet.
- Are you all right?
- Erzsebet!
They are raising her!
She will need the blood
when she wakes.
This is your chance
to redeem yourself.
Where is she?
- In the grove.
- Take us there.
No. Please.
That's all right.
You've done enough for us.
Thank you, Father.
Thank you.
There is no redemption
for you tonight.
You have betrayed our Queen.
She still has work for you.
(Groaning)
(Bell tolling, monks chanting)
Anna, Anna.
This is a time for you to be
celebrating, not worrying.
You have a wedding
to prepare for.
But the terrible...
three women in one week.
And the way they were found.
Victims of some beast.
A wolf perhaps. Not a vampire.
What vampire would
dare trespass here?
The church, this church,
is too strong.
I walk these streets without fear.
In the bible, Joshua tells us,
"Be bold and strong!
"Banish fear and doubt!
"For remember, the Lord your God
is with you wherever you go."
And where you have to go is to Marie's
for that final fitting
of your wedding dress.
Oh, yes. Indeed.
Goodbye, Father.
Thank you!
Oh, thank you.
Good afternoon, Father Lupescu.
I hope I'm not interrupting.
Not at all, Professor Broom.
I have been looking forward
to meeting you.
I have to admit,
when the others told me
of your interest in this matter,
I was... concerned.
- For my safety?
- Not precisely.
Your profession.
You work with spiritualists,
mediums, attend séances.
Is there not a danger of falling into step
with the wrong element?
Do you not fear being influenced
by the forces of evil?
Not if I remain strong in my beliefs.
I know you doubt
but the trouble here
is the work of a vampire, Father.
A vampire aligned
with an ancient goddess
who has given her incredible power.
I will have no talk of false gods
in this house of faith!
I apologise, Father.
I meant no insult.
We must all hold on to our faith,
for in the end, it is the only thing
that will save us.
(Growling)
- What's that?
- The old man was alone, wasn't he?
We must get to the grove!
(Growling)
Get to the grove! We'll be fine!
You're starting to piss me off.
(Grunting)
- (Groaning)
- (Chains rattling)
A curious one, eh, sister?
His cold blood
is of no use to the Priestess.
True. But to us...
Oh, yes!
Now, how to begin?
Which one to use?
This one!
No, no, sister. This.
OK. One last dance.
(Growling)
(Squelch)
(Roars)
(Grunting)
Missed all the fun, kid.
Find Abe. I'm going for
the professor and Liz.
Find? Where? How?
I don't know, do your thing!
Maybe he has a metal filling
or something.
Are you all right?
I'm fine.
Just caught on a branch.
Liz, you must leave me.
Erzsebet must be stopped.
You have to interrupt the ritual.
Go. I'll be fine.
(Howling)
Maybe not.
(Growling)
(Barking)
We must keep moving.
Yeah. Stay close.
If I could see them, I could...
They're... leaving.
Because they've done what
they were meant to do. Hurry!
We're too late.
Erzsebet!
Stand back.
So young.
She's too much for you.
You'll burn.
You!
Let go of him!
My goddess Hecate,
aid your servant.
Hecate. Seen your statue.
Aren't you missing a couple of heads?
Why do you walk this lesser world?
Mortals, they don't know you.
We are greater beings
than they could ever dream.
Yeah? Well, I'm doing just fine.
Now, uh, I'm kinda busy.
I gotta go.
Why? To save them?
They're nothing to us.
Only a few remain
that observe the old rituals,
so I give them back the priestess
and they give me sacrifices of blood.
Now, accept what you are.
Come and walk with me.
Lady, I was gonna
cut you some slack
cos you're a major mythological figure.
But that, that's crazy talk.
Now leave me alone!
There you are.
Gotta go.
(Groaning)
Most intriguing, sister.
Yes, sister.
Let's cut some more.
Yah!
(Shrieking)
Harpies.
Should have known.
(Shrieking)
(Screams)
(Harpies laughing)
(Howling)
(Growling)
(Abe) Liz!
Liz!
I'm OK.
This time, I'm OK.
The years have not been
so kind to you.
Nor to you.
Ha! You're so frail.
Age has turned you to glass.
I pity you.
And I you.
(Sighs)
Growing old is not the worst thing
that could happen to a person.
But you ceased to be
a person long ago.
- Oh...
- (Sizzling)
(Whimpering)
No!
What have you done?
My contribution to your bath.
No!
(Moaning and screaming)
(Gasps)
(Roars)
(Screams)
(Gasping and shrieking)
(Flames whooshing)
Aagh!
(Sighs)
(Grinding)
Choose.
Lady, you just don't get it.
Damn.
Can we do this some other time?
You have made war against
members of your own family...
and mine!
Ancient spirits of air,
old gods of graves and shadows,
demons of hell.
You're stained with the blood
of your own kin.
Now come to me.
Oh, shut up!
It is inevitable.
(Harpie shrieking)
Hecate, Queen of the Crossroads!
Terror of mortal men!
Let us worship...
Sister?
(Shrieking)
(Groans)
Jeez.
Ow.
Stop this. Come to me now.
You do not belong in this world.
Looks like your high priestess
didn't do so well.
This fight's over.
Come on! Come on!
- Work!
- (Abe) Sid!
Abe! Where were you? I was trying to
find you, but the cameras are all...
- Where's Hellboy?
- Don't know.
- But...
- But what?
- I'm detecting metal.
- (Rumbling)
A lot of metal.
Professor, look...
(Screams)
(Liz) Don't know you...
don't like you.
Liz! No!
(Screaming)
Sorry! Sorry.
(Grunts)
Over here, ugly!
Now!
Use it!
(Screaming)
- Nice shot, kid.
- Thanks, I...
Ah!
Was... Was that the goddess?
If Hecate has come,
this could be very bad.
We've gotta do something!
We can't.
- Only Hellboy.
- But...
- we just can't let him...
- It's almost dawn.
(Groans)
Crap.
(Crash)
Great.
Don't you understand?
We are not like others on this earth!
We were born to walk
in greater worlds!
- This world's fine by me.
- Eurgh.
Too long among humans.
You have nearly lost yourself.
Ah! (Groans)
It's over.
No!
We are gods of darkness!
Here, have some sun!
- Crap.
- Stop this! Your destiny is...
Destiny is overrated.
(Groaning)
(Moans)
Broom, the car for the airport is here.
Almost ready.
You've never faced this sort of evil.
There's no need
for you to go alone.
- If you can wait a week, I could...
- I cannot wait, Malcolm.
Too many lives at stake
and I am grateful they accepted
the offer of my expertise.
The Transylvanian constabulary
is very experienced
and I should expect strong support
from the local church.
I'll be fine.
What... What is this?
Hmm?
It's old Lemurian.
It reads,
"Behold the right hand of doom."
"And I looked down into
the end of the world and saw the beast,
"and in his right hand
was the key to the bottomless pit."
There are those who think that power
can be summoned
and bent to their own ends.
Well, they're fools!
It's the apocalyptic thing.
It brings the fire
that will incinerate the world!
Perhaps.
But if evil finds purchase
in such creatures as Erzsebet,
then we must have faith that good
will choose an agent of its own.
Until then, we fight in his stead
for "that which causes us trials
"shall lead us to triumph.
"We must pass through
darkness to reach the light."
Professor?