- Hello?
- Hello.
- Yes?
- Who is this?
- Who're you trying to reach?
- What number is this?
- Well, what number are
you trying to reach?
- I don't know.
- Well, I think you have
the wrong number.
- Do l?
It happens. Take it easy.
- Hello.
- I'm sorry. I guess I dialled
the wrong number.
- So why'd you dial it again?
- To apologize.
- You're forgiven. Bye now.
- Wait, wait. Don't hang up.
- What?
- I wanna talk to you for a second.
They've got 900 numbers for that.
See ya.
- Hello.
- Why don't you want to talk to me?
- Who is this?
- You tell me your name,
I'll tell you mine.
- I don't think so.
- What's that noise?
- Popcorn.
- You're making popcorn?
- Uh-huh.
- I only eat popcorn at the movies.
- Well, I'm getting ready
to watch a video.
- Really? What?
- Oh, just some scary movie.
- Do you like scary movies?
- Uh-huh.
- What's your favourite scary movie?
- Uh, I don't know.
- You have to have a favourite.
What comes to mind?
Um, "Halloween."
You know, the one with the guy
in the white mask who walks around
and stalks baby-sitters.
- Yeah.
- What's yours?
- Guess.
- Um, "Nightmare on Elm Street".
- Is that the one where the guy
had knives for fingers?
- Yeah, Freddy Krueger.
Freddy, that's right.
I liked that movie. It was scary.
Yeah, the first one was,
but the rest sucked.
So, you got a boyfriend?
Why? You wanna ask me out
on a date?
Maybe. Do you have a boyfriend?
- No.
- You never told me your name.
- Why do you want to know my name?
- 'Cause I want to know
who I'm looking at.
What did you say?
I want to know
who I'm talking to.
- That's not what you said.
- What do you think I said?
What?
Hello?
- Look, I gotta go.
- Wait. I thought we were gonna go out.
Uh, nah, I don't think so.
Don't hang up on me!
Shit. Yes?
I told you not to hang up on me.
- What do you want?
- To talk.
Well, dial someone else, okay?
- Listen, asshole--
- No, you listen, you little bitch.
You hang up on me again,
I'll cut you like a fish, understand?
- Yeah.
- Is this some kind of joke?
More of a game, really.
Can you handle that, blondie?
Can you see me?
Listen. I am two seconds away
from calling the police.
They'd never make it in time.
We're out in the middle of nowhere.
- What do you want?
- To see what your insides look like.
Who's there?
I'm calling the police.
You should never say "Who's there?"
Don't you watch scary movies?
It's a death wish.
You might as well
just come out here to investigate
a strange noise or something.
Look, you've had your fun now, so
I think you better just leave or else.
Or else what?
Or else my boyfriend'll be here
any second and he'll be pissed
when he finds out.
- I thought you didn't have a boyfriend.
- I lied! I do have a boyfriend...
and he'll be here any second,
so your ass better be gone.
- Sure.
- I swear.
He's big and he plays football,
and he'll kick the shit out of you!
I'm getting scared.
I'm shaking in my boots.
So you better just leave.
His name wouldn't be Steve,
would it?
How do you know his name?
Turn on the patio lights...
again.
Oh, God!
- I wouldn't do that if I were you.
- Where are you? Where are you?
- Guess.
- Please don't hurt him.
- That all depends on you.
- Why are you doing this?
- I wanna play a game.
- No.
- Then he dies right now.
- No! No! No!
Which is it?
Well, what kind of a game?
Turn off the light.
You'll see what kind of game.
Just do it!
No, Casey! No! No!
No, Casey!
Here's how we play.
I ask a question.
If you get it right, Steve lives.
- Please don't do this.
- Come on, it'll be fun.
- Please--
- It's an easy category.
- Please.
- Movie trivia.
I'll even give you a warm-up question.
- Don't do this. I can't.
- Name the killer in "Halloween."
- No.
Come on! It's your favourite
scary movie, remember?
- He had a white mask.
He stalked the baby-sitters.
- I don't know.
- Come on. Yes, you do.
- No, please.
- What's his name?
- I-- I can't think.
Steve's counting on you.
Michael--
Michael Meyers.
Yes! Very good.
Now for the real question.
- No!
- But you're doing so well.
- We can't stop now.
- Please stop! Leave us alone!
Then answer the question.
Same category.
Oh, please stop.
Name the killer in
"Friday the 13th."
Jason! Jason, Jason!
I'm sorry.
That's the wrong answer.
No, it's not!
No, it's not. It was Jason.
Afraid not. No way.
Listen, it was Jason!
I saw that movie 20 goddam times!
Then you should know Jason's mother,
Mrs Voorhees, was the original killer.
Jason didn't show up
until the sequel.
I'm afraid that was
a wrong answer.
- You tricked me.
- Lucky for you there's a bonus round.
But poor Steve.
I'm afraid he's out!
Hey, we're not finished yet.
Final question.
Are you ready?
Please, please, leave me alone.
Answer the question,
and I will.
What door am I at?
-What?
-There are two main doors to your house.
The front door
and the patio doors.
If you answer correctly,
you live. Very simple.
Don't do this.
I can't. I won't.
Your call.
Did you water
over here today?
- It was just that water from the rain.
- They look great, don't they?
- Don't they smell strong?
- I told you you could send it back.
Mom!
- Jesus!
- What is it?
Casey!
Oh, G--
Casey. Casey. Casey!
- Where is she?
- Call the police!
- Casey! Casey, are you upstairs?
- Oh, my God. Casey, baby?
- Where is she?
- She's-- She's here.
- Mom.
- Oh, my God, l, I can hear her.
- Where is she?
Oh, my God!
I can hear her.
Hey!
Get in the car.
Drive down to the MacKenzies'.
- No. No, not my daughter.
- Just go.
- Not my daughter.
- Call the police.
- It's just me.
- Billy, what the--
What are you doing here?
- Sorry, don't hate me.
- Oh, my God!
- What, do you sleep in that?
Yes, I sleep in this. You gotta go.
My dad is in the other room.
You can't be in here.
- Okay, I'll just stay a sec.
- No-- You can't be in here.
Oh, no. You gotta go. Go, go, go.
-What's going on in there? Are you okay?
-Can you knock?
- I heard screaming.
- No, you didn't.
- No?
Oh, well.
I'm hittin' the sack.
My flight leaves
first thing in the morning.
Now, the expo runs all weekend,
so I won't be back till Sunday.
- There's cash on the table,
and I'm staying at--
- The Hilton.
- Out at the airport, so call if--
- If I need anything. Yeah, I got it.
I could've sworn
I heard screaming.
- Have a good trip, okay?
- Sleep tight, sweetie.
- Oh, close call.
- Billy, what're you doing here?
- Well, it occurred to me that I've
never snuck through your bedroom window.
- Shh, shh, shh.
Great idea. Now that
it's out of your system.
You know, I was home
watching television. The, uh--
"The Exorcist" was on.
It got me thinking of you.
- It did?
- Yeah, it was edited for TV.
You know, all the good stuff was cut
out. And it got me thinking of us...
how two years ago
we started off hot and heavy.
Nice solid R-rating
on our way to an NC-17.
And now
things have changed and...
Iately we're just sort of
edited for television.
Oh, so you thought you would
climb in my window and we'd have
a little raw footage?
No. No, I wouldn't dream
of breaking your underwear rule.
I just thought maybe we could do
a little on-top-of-the-clothes stuff.
- Okay.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
- If we ever fly away
Baby, I'm with you
Baby, I'm your man
Hey.
Okay. Okay, okay.
Time is up, stud-bucket.
God, you see what
you do to me?
You know what
my dad'll do to you?
Yeah. I'm going.
Okay.
Romeo and Juliet
Are together in eternity
You know, l-- I appreciate
the romantic gesture.
So, come on, baby
Hey, about the, uh--
the sex stuff...
I-l'm not trying
to rush you at all.
- I was only half serious.
- Okay.
Baby, I'm your man
Hey, Billy.
Would you settle for
a PG-13 relationship?
What's that?
My God.
You're just a tease.
Thirty-five--
Situation under control.
Roger, dispatch.
There's blood found?
All right.
They are doing drugs that
they buy in the classrooms...
and that they are
involved in the occult.
Occult?
Woodsboro, California, was devastated
last night when two young teenagers
were found brutally murdered.
Authorities have yet to issue
a statement, but our sources tell us...
that no arrest has been made
and the murderer could strike again.
- Do you believe this shit?
- Damn! What is going on?
- You don't know?
- No.
- Casey Becker and Steve Orth
were killed last night.
- What? No way.
And we're not just talking killed.
We're talking splatter-movie killed.
Ripped open
from end to end.
- Casey Becker, she sits
next to me in English.
- Not any more. It's so sad.
Her mom and dad, they found her hanging
from a tree, her insides on the outside.
Oh, my God!
Do they know who did it?
Fucking clueless. I mean, they're
interrogating the entire school.
- Teachers, students, janitors.
- They think it's school-related?
They don't know. I mean,
Dewey was saying this is the
worst crime they've seen in years.
Even worse than--
Well, it's bad.
- Here you go, Mrs Tate.
- Thank you, James.
Sidney. It would appear
to be your turn.
- Who's up next?
- Uh, Sidney Prescott.
- Prescott.
She was daughter of, uh--
- Sidney, how you feelin'?
- Fine.
- Hi, Sidney.
- Sheriff Burke, Dewey.
Uh, that's Deputy Riley
today, Sid.
- How is everything?
- Good.
And your dad?
How's he doin'?
- We're fine. Thanks.
- We're gonna keep this
very brief, Sidney.
- The police just want to ask you
a few questions. You okay?
- Mm-hmm.
Sidney, were you very
close to Casey Becker?
Remember, your principal loves you,
and I want you to be safe.
All students are encouraged
to return to their homes promptly
from school grounds. Avoid strangers.
- Walk in twos and threes.
Counsellors will be here tomorrow.
- What kind of questions
did they ask you, Sidney?
- Thank you.
- They asked if I knew Casey.
- Yeah, they asked me that too.
- Hey, did they ask if you like to hunt?
- Yeah, they did.
- Did they ask you?
- Hunt? Why would they ask you
if you like to hunt?
'Cause their bodies
were gutted.
- Thank you, Randy.
- They didn't ask me if I like to hunt.
- It's 'cause there's no way
a girl could've killed 'em.
- That is so sexist.
The killer could easily be female.
"Basic lnstinct."
That was an ice pick.
Not exactly the same thing.
Yeah, Casey and Steve
were completely hollowed out.
And the fact is, it takes a man
to do something like that.
- Or a man's mentality.
- How do you gut someone?
You take a knife, and you slit 'em
from the groin to sternum.
Hey, it's called tact,
you fuck rag.
Hey, Stu, didn't you
used to date Casey?
- Yeah, for like two seconds.
- Before she dumped you for Steve.
- I thought you dumped her for me.
- I did. He's full of shit.
And are the police aware
that you dated the victim?
Hey, what're you saying?
That-- That-- That I killed her?
- It would certainly improve
your high school "Q."
- Stu was with me last night, okay?
- Yeah, I was.
- Was that before or after
he sliced and diced?
- Fuck you, nut case.
Where were you last night?
- Working, thank you.
- Oh, at the video store?
I thought they fired your sorry ass.
- Twice.
- I didn't kill anybody.
- Nobody said you did.
Thanks, buddy. Besides, it takes a man
to do something like that.
- I'm gonna gut your ass
in a second, kid.
- Tell me something. Did you really
put her liver in the mailbox?
'Cause I heard that they
found her liver in the mailbox
next to her spleen and her pancreas.
Randy, you goon! Fuck!
I'm trying to eat here. Okay?
She's getting mad, all right?
You better "liver" alone.
"Liver" alone!
"Liv--" Ow! "Liver. Liver. Liv--"
It was a joke.
See you, Sidney.
I'll talk to you tomorrow, Sid.
So, you sure I can stay over, 'cause
my dad won't be back till Sunday.
No problem.
I'll pick you up after practise.
You okay?
Uh-huh. It's just, you know,
the police and reporters...
and everything,
it's like deja vu all over again.
I'll be there by 7:00,
I promise.
- Thanks, Tatum.
- Later.
The bodies of 17-year-old Casey Becker
and her 18-year-old boyfriend
Steven Orth...
were discovered late last night
by the girl's parents--
The Woodsboro double murder case.
Authorities are baffled by the lack
of clues and the savage--
The town's in shock, and no one can
quite believe what has happened here...
although this is not the first
time this small community...
of Woodsboro has endured
such tragedy.
Only a year ago Maureen Prescott,
wife and mother...
was found raped and murdered not far
from this peaceful town square.
- Hello?
- Practise ran late.
I'm on my way, okay?
- It's past 7:00.
- Don't worry. Casey and Steve didn't
bite it till way after 10:00.
Oh. Oh, that's comforting.
I'm gonna swing by the video store.
I was thinkin' Tom Cruise in
"All The Right Moves."
You know, if you pause it just right,
you can see his penis.
- Whatever. Just hurry, okay?
- Ta-ta, Sid.
- Tatum, just get in the car--
- Hello, Sidney.
Uh, hi, who is this?
You tell me.
- Well, l-l have no idea.
- Scary night, isn't it?
With the murders and all,
it's like right out of
a horror movie or something.
Randy, you gave yourself away.
Are you calling from work,
'cause Tatum's on her way over.
Do you like scary movies,
Sidney?
I like that thing you're doing
with your voice, Randy. It's sexy.
What's your favourite
scary movie?
- Oh, come on.
You know I don't watch that shit.
- Why not? Too scared?
No, no. It's just, what's the point?
They're all the same.
Some stupid killer stalking
some big-breasted girl who can't act...
who's always running up the stairs when
she should be going out the front door.
- It's insulting.
- Are you alone in the house?
Randy, that's so unoriginal.
I'm disappointed in you.
Maybe that's because
I'm not Randy.
- So, who are you?
- The question isn't "Who am l?"
The question is
"Where am l?"
S-S-So, where are you?
Your front porch.
Why would you be calling
from my front porch?
That's the original part.
Oh, yeah?
Well, I call your bluff.
- So, where are you?
- Right here.
- Can you see me right now?
- Uh-huh.
- Uh-huh. Okay.
What am I doin'? Huh?
Huh? What am I doin'?
Hello!
Nice try, Randy. Tell Tatum
to hurry up, okay? Bye now.
If you hang up on me,
you'll die just like your mother!
Do you wanna die, Sidney?
Your mother sure didn't.
Fuck you, you cretin!
No!
Shit!
- Billy!
- The door's locked.
I heard screaming. You all right?
The killer's here. He's in the house.
No, he's in the house.
He's got a knife.
He's gonna kill us.
He's gone. He's gone.
It's all right.
What?
Sid, what?
Whoa, whoa, wait, wait.
Wait, Sidney, wait!
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait!
What's going on?
Sidney, come back!
Sidney!
Sorry! I found this.
Come on!
- All right, hold your hands together.
- Do you wish to give up your right
to remain silent?
- I didn't do anything.
- Do you wish to give up your
right to speak to an attorney...
and have them present
during questioning?
Ask her. She'll tell you.
Ask her.
- What do you got, Dewey?
- I caught him, Sheriff.
- Wait, who is that?
- Billy Loomis.
- Sheriff, Sheriff, call these guys off.
- I didn't do it.
- Let's go.
Sheriff, wait!
Wait, listen. Call my dad.
Please, call him.
He'll tell you. Just call him.
Sidney! Sidney!
- How's she doing?
- Sid's tougher than she looks.
- She'd have to be,
all the shit she's been through.
- Sid!
Well, we're seein'
a lot of you today.
You gonna be able to come down to the
station and answer a few questions, Sid?
Oh, shit, Sidney! God, Sid, I'm so sorry
I was late. Are you all right?
- Tatum, you can't be here.
This is an official crime scene.
- It's okay.
Her dad's out of town, all right?
She's staying with us tonight.
- Does Mom know?
- Yes, doofus.
- Let's get you out of here.
- She'll be okay.
- Thanks.
- Come on, Sid.
- Oh, you won't believe this.
Creepy, huh?
- I'll be damned.
- What?
- Jesus! The camera, hurry!
My name isn't Jesus.
Sidney, is that you in there? Excuse me.
Is that Sidney Prescott they took away?
- I'm not talking to you.
- What happened to her?
- None of your damn business.
- I heard something about
a costume. Is that true?
- Can you tell me anything?
- Yeah, you're a real pain in the ass.
Leave Sid alone.
Where's she goin'?
- Look. Kenny?
- Yeah?
I know that you're about 50 pounds
overweight, but when I say "hurry"...
please interpret that as
"move your fat, tub-of-lard ass now!"
- Did you find him?
- Are you sure it was the Hilton?
- At the airport.
- He's not registered there.
Could he have stayed
somewhere else?
I don't know. I guess.
- Don't worry, Sid. We'll find him.
- Dewey, they got that mask in.
- Roger, dispatch.
- I'll be right back.
Hold on a minute.
Let me ask you this. What're you
doin' with a cellular telephone, son?
Everybody's got one, Sheriff.
- I didn't make those calls, I swear.
- Why don't you check the phone bill,
for Christ's sake!
- Call Vital Phone Comp. They got
the records of every number dialled.
- Thanks, Hank. We're on top of it.
- What were you doing over
at Sidney's house tonight?
- I wanted to see her, that's all.
And last night? Sidney said you crawled
through her window last night too.
You went out last night?
I was watchin' TV. I got bored.
I decided to go for a ride.
Did you happen to ride by
Casey Becker's house?
No. No, I didn't.
Sheriff, I didn't kill anybody!
We're gonna have to hold you, son,
till we get those phone records.
This is crazy.
You know that?
I didn't do it.
- Camera Two?
- Go. I do.
- Okay.
Are there any more
doughnuts in there?
- Move it, Kenny.
- They're not lettin' anybody in.
- I'm not just anyone.
- Bitch goddess.
- Kenny, are we on?
- Yeah, go.
- Hi, Gale Weathers reporting live
from Woodsboro police station...
- Hey, where's she going?
- where we hope to get a glimpse
of Sidney Prescott.
- Hey, watch it, lady.
- Hey, watch the hand! Do you
know who you're dealing with?
- No cameras, please.
Tell 'em.
Come on, Dad. Tell 'em!
- He's waiting for the lawyer, Billy.
- Sidney!
- Sidney, come on. You know me.
- All right, come on.
- Sidney, look at me!
- Don't give us any trouble.
Come on!
Sid, we're gonna get you out of here,
okay? Are you okay?
They sell this costume
at every five-and-dime in the state.
There's no way
to track the purchase.
- What about that cellular phone bill?
- Well, we're pulling Loomis's account.
We won't know anything
until the morning.
Oh, come on!
- You think he did it?
- Twenty years ago,
I would've said, "Not a chance."
But these kids today,
damned if I know.
- Hey, Dewey, can we go now?
- Hold on a second.
Goddamn it, Dewey!
What did Mama tell you?
When I wear this badge,
you treat me like a man of the law!
- I'm sorry, Deputy Dewey-boy,
but we're ready to go. Now, okay?
- Whoa.
Uh, take 'em out the back way.
Avoid that circus out there.
- Come on.
- Don't touch me!
- He's my superior.
- The janitor is your superior.
Let's get back to work!
- Isn't there a back way
out of this building?
- Yeah. Down that alley, I think.
You guys just stay here. I'm gonna get
the car. Don't move. Don't make a sound.
There she is. Sidney!
Hi. That was some night.
What happened? Are you all right?
- She's not answering any questions,
all right? Just leave us alone.
- No. No. Tatum. It's okay.
- She's just doin' her job, right, Gale?
- Yes, that's right.
- So, how's the book?
- Well, it'll be out later this year.
Oh, I'll look for it.
I'll send you a copy.
- Jeez. Nice shot.
- Bitch!
- No, I mean, camera shot.
- Where'd you learn to punch like that?
God, I loved it.
"l'll send you a copy."
Bam! Bitch went down.
"l'll send you a copy." Bam!
Sid-- Superbitch! You are so cool.
Thought you might want
some ice for that right hook.
Thanks.
I'll be right next door.
Try to get some sleep.
Yeah, yeah.
Do you really think
Billy did it?
He was there, Tatum.
He was destined to have a flaw.
I knew he was too perfect.
- Telephone, honey.
- Who is it?
- It's for Sid.
- My dad?
- I don't think so.
- Take a message.
- No, um, I'll get it.
How's she doin'?
- Hello.
- Hello, Sidney.
- No!
- Poor Billy-boyfriend.
- An innocent guy doesn't stand
a chance with you.
- Leave me alone!
- Looks like you fingered
the wrong guy again.
- Dewey!
- Who are you?
- Hang up, Sid.
- Don't worry.
-You'll find out soon enough. I promise.
-Dewey!
What?
- What?
Hello.
Sidney Prescott, who escaped
a vicious attack last night...
is the daughter of Maureen Prescott
who was brutally killed last year...
when convicted murderer Cotton Weary
broke into their home...
and savagely raped
and tortured the deceased.
Cotton Weary is currently awaiting
appeal for the death sentence...
handed down after the young Sidney
testified against him.
She was the key witness in
the State's case against the--
It's never gonna stop,
is it?
Billy was released.
His cellular bill was clean.
He didn't make those calls.
We're checkin' every cellular account
in the county.
Any calls made to you or Casey Becker
are being cross-referenced.
It's gonna take some time,
but we'll find him.
You okay?
Don't worry, Sid, it's school.
You'll be safe here.
- So how does it feel to be almost
brutally butchered?
- Hey! Hey, now leave her alone.
- Come on, Sid.
- People wanna know.
They have a right to know.
- Leave her alone.
- How does it feel?
- She just wants to get an education.
Turn that thing off.
What?
Just a sec.
- Stop right there.
- I'm not here to fight.
I just need to talk.
- Kenny, camera, now!
- Off the record. No camera.
- Forget it.
- Please? You owe me.
- I owe you shit!
- You owe my mother!
Your mother's murder was last year's
hottest court case. Somebody was gonna
write a book about it.
- Right. And it had to be you with
all your lies and bullshit theories.
- What is your problem?
You got what you wanted. Cotton Weary's
in jail. They're gonna gas him.
A book is not gonna change that.
- Do you still think he's innocent?
- Your testimony put him away.
It doesn't really matter
what I think.
During the trial, you did all those
stories about me. You called me a liar.
I think you falsely
identified him, yes.
- Have you talked to Cotton?
- Many times.
- And has his story changed?
- Not one word.
He admits to having sex
with your mother, but that's all.
He's lying.
She never would've touched him.
He raped her, and then he-- he butchered
her. Her blood was all over his coat.
He was drunk that night.
He left his coat at your house
after your mother seduced him.
- I saw him leave wearing it.
- No, you saw someone leave
wearing that coat.
The same someone who planted it
in Cotton's car, framing him.
No. Cotton murdered my mother.
You're not so sure
any more, are you?
Nice welt, sweetie.
Let's go, Sid.
- The killer's still
on the loose, isn't he?
- Come on, Sid.
- Those murders are related.
- I'm sorry I mangled your face.
- Wait, Sidney, don't go!
- Just stop, all right?
Jesus Christ!
An innocent man on death row.
- A killer still on the loose.
Kenny, tell me I'm dreaming.
- You wanna go live?
No, no, no. Not so fast.
We don't have anything concrete.
-This is huge. You can't just sit on it.
-I know! That's why we need proof.
If I'm right about this,
I could save a man's life.
Do you know what that
could do for my book sales?
This is a mistake.
I shouldn't be here.
I want you to meet me right
here after class, okay, Sid?
All right.
Hey, I haven't seen Billy around.
Is he really pissed?
Oh, you mean after you
branded him the Candyman?
- No, his heart's broken. Ow!
- Stu!
Why are they doing this?
Are you kidding me?
Look at this place. It's like Christmas.
- Stupidity leak.
- Ow. Easy.
Sidney!
- Ow!
- Jesus! Shit!
It's just me.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
You still think it's me.
No. No, l-l don't.
- It's just somebody was there.
- Hey, Christy, wait up!
- Billy, someone--
someone tried to kill me.
- I know. I know. I know.
The cops said I scared him away.
It wasn't me, Sid.
I know. He called me again
last night at Tatum's house.
You see? It couldn't have been me.
I was in jail. Remember?
I'm so sorry.
Please understand.
Understand what? That I have a
girlfriend who would rather accuse me...
of being a psychopathic killer
than touch me?
- You know that's not true.
- Then what is it?
What is it? Billy, I was attacked
and nearly filleted last night!
I mean between us.
You haven't been
the same since--
- Since your mother died.
- Is your brain leaking?
My mom was killed. I can't believe
you're bringing this up!
- It's been a year.
- Tomorrow! One year tomorrow.
I know. I think it's time
you got over that. I mean,
when my mom left my dad, I accepted it.
It's the way it is.
She's not comin' back.
Your parents split up.
This is not the same thing.
Your mom left town.
She's not lying in a coffin somewhere.
Okay, okay, okay, I'm sorry.
It's-- It's a bad analogy.
But it's just that...
I want my girlfriend back.
- Sid!
- Billy, I am sorry
if my traumatized life...
is an inconvenience to you
and your perfect existence.
What? What are you--
Nobody said that. Sid!
- Stupid.
- You make me so sick!
Your entire havoc-inducing, thieving,
whoring generation disgusts me!
So, two of your fellow students
just savagely murdered...
and this is the way that you show
your compassion and sensitivity, huh?
Let me tell you something.
You're both expelled! Get out!
Oh, come on, Mr Himbry!
It was just a joke.
Yeah, that's not fair!
You're absolutely right.
It is not fair.
Fairness would be to rip your
insides out, hang you from a tree...
so we can expose you for the heartless,
desensitized little shits that you are.
- She was never attacked.
I think she made it all up.
- Why would she lie about it?
For attention!
The girl has some serious issues.
What if she did it? What if
Sidney killed Casey and Steve?
And why would she do that?
Maybe she had the hots for Steve and
killed them both in a jealous rage.
What would Sidney want with Steve?
She has her own bubble-butt
boyfriend, Billy.
Maybe she's a slut
just like her mother.
- You're evil.
- Please, it's a common fact.
- Her mother was a tramp.
- Cut some slack.
She watched her mom get butchered.
Yeah, and it fucked her up royally.
Think about it.
Her mother's death
leaves her disturbed and hostile.
In a cruel and inhumane world,
she's delusional.
Where is God? Etcetera.
Completely suicidal.
One day she snaps.
She wants to kill herself...
but she realizes that teen suicide
is out this year...
and homicide is a much healthier,
therapeutic expression.
- Where do you get this shit?
- "Ricki Lake."
You are pathetic.
Pathetic.
Sidney.
Is someone there?
In what appears to be a prank, several
students were seen wearing scary masks.
School officials
have yet to comment...
but this is known to be
the same costume worn by the killer.
Seventeen-year-old Casey Becker
and her boyfriend Steven Orth
have already lost their lives.
Who's next? You can literally feel
the fear on this campus.
Hi. Gale Weathers,
field correspondent, "Top Story."
I know who you are, Miss Weathers.
How's the eye?
It's productive.
Is there a problem on campus?
No, everything's under control.
- Well, of course. You're here.
- You're not supposed to be here.
I know. I should be in New York
covering the Sharon Stone stalker,
but who knew?
- You look awfully young
to be a police officer.
- I'm 25 years old.
You know, in a demographic study
I proved to be most popular
amongst males 11 to 24.
Guess I just missed you.
Of course, you don't look a day over 12.
Except in that upper torso area.
Does the force require you to work out?
No, ma'am.
Because of my boyish good looks...
muscle mass has increased my acceptance
as a serious police officer.
I need your attention now, kids. Due to
the recent events that have occurred...
effective immediately, all classes
are suspended until further notice.
The Woodsboro police department
has issued a citywide curfew...
beginning at 9:00 tonight.
Looks like we've got
a serial killer on our hands.
Well, serial killer's
not really accurate.
Gotta knock off a couple more
to get that title.
Well, we can hope,
can't we?
I mean, we certainly
don't have any leads.
- Have you located Sidney's father yet?
- No, not yet.
- Well, he's not a suspect, is he?
- We haven't ruled him out
as a possibility.
- If you'll excuse me.
- I'm sorry. Am I keeping you?
If I may say so,
Miss Weathers...
you are much prettier in person.
So you do watch the show.
I'm 25.
I was 24 for a whole year.
Please, call me Gale!
It was just some sick fuck
having a laugh, Sidney.
No, it was him, Tatum.
I know it.
Well, you're not to be alone any more.
If you pee, I pee. Is that clear?
"Kizzo-kaskizzo is is-out."
I don't know what you did, Sidney,
but on behalf of the entire student
body, we all say, "Thank you!"
- Drop it, Stu.
- No, I say...
an impromptu party tonight,
my house.
- Celebrate this little siesta.
What do you say?
- Are you serious?
As long as this little vixen doesn't
invite the entire world, we'll be fine.
Intimate gathering,
intimate friends.
What do you say, Sid?
I mean, pathos could have its perks?
I will totally protect you. Yo,
I am so buff. I got you covered, girl.
- No.
- Come on, Sid. For me?
It could be fun.
- Okay. Whatever.
- Yeah? Nice.
Cool. You guys
bring food, all right?
Yes?
Hello?
- Damn little shits.
- What'd you call me? Huh?
- Not you, Fred.
- You prick.
School's out for summer
- School's out
- What if Cotton Weary
is telling the truth?
- With fever
- Maybe he was having
an affair with your mom.
- I mean, your dad was always
out of town on business. Maybe--
- School's out
- Completely
- Maybe your mom was just
a very unhappy woman.
If-- If they were having
an affair, then how come
Cotton couldn't prove it in court?
Well, you can't prove a rumour.
That's why it's a rumour.
Right. Created by that little
tabloid twit Gale Weathers.
It goes further back, Sid.
There's been talk about other men.
And you believe it.
Well, I mean,
you can only hear that Richard Gere
gerbil story so many times...
before you have to start
believing it.
Oh, I'm sorry.
You know, if-if I was wrong
about Cotton Weary, then
the killer's still out there.
Don't go there, Sid.
You're starting to sound like
some Wes Carpenter flick or something.
Don't freak yourself out, okay? We've
got a long night ahead of us. Okay?
Let's boogie.
- It's alive!
- Henry!
Oh, in the name of God,
now I know--
Excuse me, dude.
- Watch it, jerk.
- I'm sorry.
Dork.
Jesus, this place
is packed tonight, man.
- We had a run
in the mass murder section.
- Comin' to my fiesta?
- Yeah, I'm off early. Curfew, you know.
- Cool.
What's that werewolf movie
with E.T.'s mom in it?
- "The Howling." Horror. Straight ahead.
- Okay, thanks.
- Oh, now that's in poor taste.
- What?
If you were the only suspect
in a senseless bloodbath...
would you be standing
in the horror section?
What? It was just a misunderstanding.
He didn't do anything.
You're such a little lapdog. He's got
"killer" printed all over his forehead.
Okay! Really? Well, why'd the cops
let him go, smart guy?
Because obviously
they don't watch enough movies.
This is standard horror movie stuff.
- "Prom Night" revisited, man.
- Yeah? Why would he wanna
kill his own girlfriend?
There's always some stupid,
bullshit reason to kill your girlfriend.
- Oh?
- That's the beauty of it all:
simplicity.
Besides, if it gets too complicated,
you lose your target audience.
Well, what's his reason?
Maybe Sidney
wouldn't have sex with him.
- What, is she savin' herself for you?
- Maybe.
Now that Billy tried to mutilate her,
do you think Sid would go out with me?
No, I don't at all. No.
You know who I think it is?
You know, I think
it's her father.
Why can't they find
her pops, man?
Because he's probably dead.
His body will come poppin' up
in the last reel somewhere!
Eyes gouged out, fingers cut off,
teeth knocked out!
- See, the police are always
off track with this shit.
- Man!
If they'd watch "Prom Night,"
they'd save time.
There's a formula to it. A very simple
formula! Everybody's a suspect!
I'm telling you, the dad's
a red herring. It's Billy.
How do we know you're
not the killer? Huh? Huh?
- Hi, Billy.
- Maybe your movie-freaked mind lost its
reality button. You ever think of that?
You're absolutely right.
I'm the first to admit it.
- If this were a scary movie,
I'd be the prime suspect.
- That's right.
And what would be
your motive?
It's the millennium.
Motives are incidental.
"Millennium."
"Millennium." I like that.
That's good. It's the millennium.
Good kid.
"Millennium."
Good word, my man.
Are you telling me
that's not a killer?
You'll see him
in your nightmares
in your dreams
He'll appear
out of nowhere
But he ain't
What he seems
You'll see him in your head
On the TV screen
Hey, buddy
I'm warnin' you to turn it off
Ah, he's a ghost
He's a god
He's a man
He's a guru
You're one microscopic cog
in his catastrophic plan
Designed and directed
by his red right hand
Sure is quiet.
God, look at this place.
It's "The Town That Dreaded Sundown."
Yeah, I saw that movie.
It's about a killer in Texas, huh?
Hey, Sid, just think. If they make a
movie about you, who's gonna play you?
- I shudder to think.
- I see you as a young Meg Ryan myself.
Thanks, Dewey. With my luck,
they'd cast Tori Spelling.
I'm just gonna be
a few minutes.
You girls don't go too far.
- Is Billy gonna be there tonight?
- He better not be.
I told Stu to keep his mouth shut.
I think we can live without
the endorphin rush for one night.
Billy's right, you know. Whenever
he touches me, I just can't relax.
So you have a few intimacy issues as a
result of your mother's untimely death.
It's no big deal, Sid.
I mean, you'll thaw out.
Yeah, but he has been so patient with
me, you know, with all the sex stuff.
How many guys would put up with
a girlfriend who's sexually anorexic?
Billy and his penis
don't deserve you, all right?
- Dewey, where the hell you been?
- I was keepin' an eye on Sidney, uh--
- Thought you quit.
- I did. But damn it--
Dewey, Vital Phone
just faxed us.
Those calls are listed
to Neil Prescott, Sidney's father.
He made the calls with a cellular phone.
It's been confirmed.
There's no way a cellular
could've been cloned?
There's more.
Guess what tomorrow is.
The anniversary
of his wife's death.
We'll keep the roadblocks and the curfew
in effect through the night.
If he's not picked up by morning,
then we'll do a house-to-house.
- Where's Sidney?
- She's with my sister.
You want me to bring her in?
No. Not just yet.
Let's find Neil first,
make sure he's our man.
You stay close to Sidney.
Don't let her out of your sight.
Yes, sir.
Say a prayer
for the youth of America
God bless the youth
of America
And I can't stand
their sight any more
All right,
you girls have fun.
Not too much fun,
or I'll bust ya.
- Bye.
- Bye, Sid.
You're obsessed
Here, kids!
- Oh, that's mature.
- You guys were tardy for the party,
so we started without you.
My man!
- Well, were we spotted?
- I don't think so. Go get the camera.
I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to scare ya.
- Deputy, that's okay.
- What brings you to these parts?
Well, you just never know
when or where a story will break.
Not much of a story here.
Just a bunch of kids cuttin' it loose.
Then what are you
doing here?
Just keepin' an eye
on things.
I'm gonna check the party out.
- Do you mind if I join you?
- Not at all.
All right.
Let me just get my coat. Thanks.
- All right.
- Yeah, I'm fine.
Oh! Yeah.
- How many "Evil Deads?"
- One!
- Two!
- How many "Hellraisers?"
- Hellraiser right here.
"The Fog," "Terror Train,"
"Prom Night."
How come Jamie Lee Curtis
is in all of these movies?
She's the scream queen.
- With a set of lungs like that,
she should be.
- Yeah.
- Tits. See?
- Oh, I'll get it.
- Hey, Tate, grab me
another beer, would ya?
- There's more beer in the garage.
- What am l, the beer wench?
- She was nominated--
- She was nominated for "Terror Train."
- You're not gonna believe who's here!
- It's that chick from "Top Story!"
- Gale Weathers?
- Here!
- Shit!
- You're under age, son.
I'm kiddin'. Have a good time.
Watch the drivin'.
- Dewey.
- Hi.
Dewey.
- What is she doing here?
- She's with me.
- I'm just checkin' things out.
- So you did.
Now leave, and take
your media mouth with you.
- I just think you're awesome.
- Oh, thank you very much.
- I watch your show religiously.
- That's great.
- Hey.
I need a camera.
- Have you found my father?
- I'm afraid not.
- Should I be worried?
- Not yet.
- Get out, you're walkin'
- That's the one I want.
Too bad, I've spoken
When I look at you
you're forgiven
You're forgiven
Jesus!
Tatum, it's okay.
Shit.
Hey, shitheads!
Hello!
Shit. Piss.
Is that you, Randy?
Cute. What movie is this from?
"l Spit On Your Garage?"
Lose the outfit.
If Sidney sees it, she'll flip.
Oh, you wanna play
psycho killer?
Can I be
the helpless victim?
Okay, let's see-- No, please
don't kill me, Mr Ghost Face.
I wanna be in the sequel!
Cut, Casper.
That's a wrap.
Randy, what the hell
are you doing?
Stop!
Fucker!
No! No!
- Happy curfew.
- Nice party, Stu.
- Tatum, come on!
- There's nobody here but us chickens!
- Do you know where she is?
- No, I haven't seen her.
Oh. Billy. Hey.
Billy. Hmm.
What are you doin' here?
I was hoping I could talk
to Sid alone.
You know, if Tatum sees you here,
she'll draw blood.
I tell you what. Why don't you guys
go up to my parents' room?
You know, you guys
can talk, whatever.
Subtlety, Stu.
You should look it up.
No, i-it's okay.
We do need to talk.
- What's Leatherface doin' here?
- Cute. He came to make up.
There goes my chance with Sid.
Damn it.
As if.
That's all I'm sayin'.
Oh, really, Alicia?
"As if."
I'm gonna go check on them.
- Come on!
- Okay, everyone.
It was nice to meet all of you.
- Thank you.
- Stick around.
You're a genius.
- Oh, shit.
- What?
- I got a delay.
- How long is it?
I don't know. What'd it take you
to walk from the house, 30 seconds?
- It'll be fine. Just record it.
- All right.
Oh, the placement is perfect.
Tell me, Kenneth--
Has a cheesy tabloid journalist
ever won the Pulitzer?
- Well, first time for everything.
- You're damn right.
S-So, um--
So--
Look, I'm sorry.
I've been selfish,
and I want to apologize.
No, Billy, l-l'm...
the one who's been selfish
and self-absorbed...
with all this
post-traumatic stress.
- You lost your mom.
- Yeah, I know, but you're right.
Enough is enough.
I--
I can't wallow in-in
the grief process forever...
and--
and I can't keep lying to myself
about who my mom was.
Yeah, I think I'm really...
scared...
that I'm gonna turn out
just like her, you know?
Like "The Bad Seed"
or somethin'.
And I know--
I know it doesn't make sense.
Yeah, it does.
It's like Jodie Foster in
"The Silence of the Lambs"...
when she keeps having
flashbacks of her dead father.
But this is life.
This isn't a movie.
Sure it is, Sid.
It's all--
It's all a movie.
It's all...
one great big movie.
Only you can't pick
your genre.
Why can't I be
a Meg Ryan movie?
Or even a good porno.
- What?
- You heard me.
Are you sure?
Yeah.
I think so.
Look, look, look.
Here it comes.
Oh, man.
The colour of the blood is all wrong!
Why do they do that?
It's too red!
Wait. Here comes another.
Here it-- Here it--
- Ooh!
- Yes! Yes!
Predictable.
I knew he was gonna bite it.
How can you watch this shit
over and over?
When do we see breasts?
I wanna see Jamie Lee's breasts.
- When do we see Jamie Lee's breasts?
- Yes. Yes.
- Breasts?
Not until "Trading Places"
in '83.
Jamie Lee was always the virgin
in horror movies.
She never showed her tits
till she went legits.
- Could afford a decent pair.
- What did you--
That's why she always
outsmarted the killer in
the big chase scene at the end.
Only virgins can do that.
Don't you know the rules?
- What rules?
- You don--
Jesus Christ.
You don't know the rules?
Have an aneurysm,
why don't ya?
There are certain rules
that one must abide by...
in order to successfully
survive a horror movie.
For instance, number one:
You can never have sex.
- Big no-no! Big no-no!
- I'd be a dead man.
- Sex equals death. Okay?
- Yes!
Number two:
You can never drink or do drugs.
No, the sin factor.
It's a sin.
It's an extension of number one.
And number three:
Never, ever, ever...
under any circumstances say,
"l'll be right back,"
'cause you won't be back.
- I'm gettin' another beer.
You want one?
- Yeah, sure.
I'll be right back!
You see? You push the laws
and you end up dead.
Okay? I'll see you
in the kitchen with a knife.
Only virgins can outsmart the killer
in the big chase scene at the end.
- Don't you know the rules?
- What rules?
You don't know the rules?
There are certain rules...
- that one must abide by in order
to essentially survive a horror movie.
- Boring.
- For instance--
- The sheriff just radioed.
Somebody reported a car
in the bushes down the road.
I'm gonna go check it out.
- Would you care to join me?
- I'd love to.
If you're sure
it's all right.
Ma'am,
I'm the deputy of this town.
Be right back.
You see, you push the laws
and you end up dead.
- W-- Excuse me, ma'am.
- Mm-hmm?
I thought maybe we'd walk.
It's such a nice night out.
I got a flashlight.
- You're not scared, are ya?
- No.
- All right.
- Great.
Do you know what
that constellation is?
No. What is it?
I don't know.
That's why I was askin' you.
- What happened to Tatum, Stu?
- She probably got pissed
at me and bailed.
- Bye.
No, I'm just kidding.
I'm just kidding.
Look! Here comes
the obligatory tit shot!
- Yes! Oh! That was beautiful!
- Lovely!
- Oh, my God.
- I'll leave you guys alone.
You are so...
amazing.
Hello? Yeah?
Holy shit.
N-- Ho--
Listen up.
They found
Principal Himbry dead.
He was gutted and hung from
the goalpost on the football field.
- So what are we waiting for?
- Let's go over there
before they pry him down.
- Hey. Hey.
- To arms! To arms!
- Where did he say he was?
- Where are you guys--
Where are you guys--
- At the football field!
- Come on!
- Where you guys goin'?
We were just gettin'
to the good part.
Hello? Yeah?
Where are you guys--
Heigh-ho, Silver!
Let's go!
- So, is-- is Dewey your real name?
- No, it's Dwight.
Dwight?
- I'm sorry.
- No, that's all right.
Dewey's just somethin'
I got stuck with a long time ago.
Well, I like it.
It's sexy.
- Sexy?
- Mm-hmm.
Ah, it's just this town's way
of not takin' me serious.
What about Gale Weathers?
Sounds like I'm
a meteorologist or something.
People treat me like I'm the antichrist
of television journalism.
- I don't think you're that bad.
- No?
- No.
I think that's just 'cause
you kinda like me.
They sure are comin' fast.
Slow down!
Freeze! Jump!
- I'm sorry. Are you okay?
- Yeah.
I'm sorry.
I'm on duty.
Is that what
you're looking for?
My whole life.
- Damn!
- What?
- What is it?
- This is Neil Prescott's car.
- Sidney's father?
- Yeah.
Jesus.
What's he doing here?
We gotta get back.
You okay?
Yeah.
Yeah, I'm fine.
- Who'd you call?
- What?
Well, I don't know. When you're arrested
you're allowed one phone call.
So I was just curious.
Who'd you call?
Called my dad.
No, um, Sheriff Burke
called your dad. I saw him.
Yeah, but when I called
I didn't get an answer.
You don't still think
it was me, do you?
No.
No. I was just thinking...
if it were you it'd be a very
clever way to throw me off track.
You know, using your one phone call
to call me so that I wouldn't
think it was you, that's all.
Really.
What do I have to do to prove
to you that I'm not a killer?
- Oh, my God.
- Huh?
- Sidney--
- Billy, watch out!
Sid.