Be ready for some action!
You are Dead, bitch!
What the hell you are looking at?
Fuck... get out!
You run out of luck beautiful...
I will make you your Caesarean operation...
You son of bitch!
eat your vegetables...
In here, gome on...
There she is...
Get out of here!
Kill her!
Who is hes?
Where is the girl?
Kill him!
Holly God!
My God!
fucker!
Come on.. push... It comes!... push!...
My hand!
- Do you know what I hate?
- No..
I hate those idiot guys
with horse line hare hair
The horse line doesn't make you
look like neither sexy, young.. or cool...
Well... there it comes...
Now give me a good push!
what the fuck?
Kill him now...
Don't move...
you will make me miss the shot...
what piece of ckrack...
we are out of here...
sorry, for the messy
delivery mark.
Remain quiet.
Give him something to drink.
Bravo... Mr. hero... Bravo...
Why are you trying to kill
this woman?
Did I say something funny?
I just was remember a rhyme...
There was a very pregnant woman...
she had three kind, named:
Nat, Pat and Tat...
she said that it was amusing
to make them...
But it was a hell to breastfeed them...
Because she didnt have any teat for Tat...
You have caused me many problems...
but I will return the favor...
Teat for Tat... yea?...
It is the latest model
The gun shoots only
if it recognize your print
With This weapon for sure,
we ll have less crimes...
Kill him!
Who you are?
Lady... what is your name?
FAULK TRUCKS AND TOOLS
Nice teats!
God Damned!
F U C K
fuck you, you fucking.. fuckers!
F U C K Y O U T O
teat for tat... Mr. hero...
Teat for Tat...
Does he will return for her, boss
No, I get it how it is...
I am not the boss that just sit and warming
my chair, when anybody else do my job...
And now you will tell me how that fucker came..
Suddenly he appeared to save her...
We were about to kill the
woman and suddenly this guy came out, hey...
And who is the mysterious man?
I dont know...
After the woman escape,
we trup her here...
The guy was siting on a
bus stop in the dark...
Then he jumped toward to
us and he helped the woman
He took a gun, He start
shooting us and then you came...
Take it easy, shut up..
Uh... you are alright?
You mean, that an idiot
came to save her?
That is a disaster, doesnt it?
I won't make that mistake again...
I will stick a note in my mind,
to remind me that...
yea, I understand you...
Oh, my ass!
And let that to remind you, never to
fail me again.
Damned...
You can go... but you must
leave the baby..
Behind...
sweety, This job is all most done
Hey look, I have already booked
my flight home, ok?
Good. I love to,
bye-bye
You know that a gun is better than a wife?
Dont kNow...
You can make the gun to silence...
Sir, We spot the target in
3nd A and Jefferson... in the park
Turn us arround...
Don't worry boy, somebody
good will find you..
My God, look!
Somebody left a baby...
Fuck me in both sides...
Welcome back Mister Smith...
Where is Donna?
Smith Wait...
Mrs. Donna is with a
client, you cant go up there...
Smith...
I believed that Mary is about your
type... You cant go up there!
Come here!
sorry Sir, the bar is closed..
wait for your turn, Smith...
I have for all of you...
No, I dont want, I don't like the lactose...
Just tell me what you want, Smith...
Kinky.
I want you,
to take care this baby for a while...
$ 5000, to keep you out fo work
for a couple of weeks.
are you clean?
You know that I am a good girl.
Will you make it?
Fuck your self, Smith...
You can have kidnapped the boy.
I dont want to be an accomplice.
I Didn't steal the boy, trust me...
Trust you?
I do not even Know your true name.
Who are you really, Smith?
I am a British nanny
and I am dangerous.
Keep the baby for one day and you
can keep all the money.
Forget it, Papa...
Good...
Chest milk
Lets go
This ladys baby need to be feed...
Find me all the nurses,
Suckling prostitutes in the city
I already told you that you are not welcome
to the earth of milk and honey
I need cream for my coffee
and some answers
I am sorry...
Boys..
Give me a moment alone
with "Coffee Mama"
Calm... calm...
There was a man here with a baby?
Not long ago...
Yes
He wanted me to take care the baby
And what is this man name?
Smith...
Mr. Smith
How in hell can I know his real name?
He saw me a couple of times
when I offered normal sex
He always used the same name, Smith
I don't believe you
I believe that you know more
about this man
He was gaving a bad tips
Gets hoter with more shoots...
If I had anything else about him,
I would already have told you...
I can make it a lot more painful..
the closer I get...
Whach up Doc?...
You are a smart rabbit...
But not smart enough...
Yea?
That gun has 6 shots...
I have just counted 6 shots...
You have discharge alot...
And yours is the same? Your gun
is 9 mm and is empty?
You shot 8 in the roof
and one in the bathroom
And you were emptied the second
loader in the park
And you cant shoot me
with my man's gun
It is as mine, it recognize the print
Oh... seriously?
Do you want to bet?
You cant trust nothing more
than a good had job
Take your things, we go
I cant understand anything...
that you say,
and I won't apologize to you
Damned you are.
they could have killed me there
Be appreciated that I saved
your poor ass
Why you are waiting for so long?
You are a bad girl
and you deserved a punishment
Which car you want?
what?
I have already get tired of walking
HANDICAPPED
looks at this...
what is the deferency of this
deluxe car and a farm?
I give up.
Both have pig inside
Tell me about it!
Hello lover
Oh.. good, good. I am glad that
you Liked the flowers
Look sweety, I have
a small job to do..
and I believe that I will have
to stay a little longer
But don't worry
I will return on time for the
party of Timmys birthday
Hugs and kisses. Good-bye...
And what you wanted me to do?
They pursued a pregnant woman.
I couldnt be stopped..
Did you see that?
I hate that...
what? This car is changing lines
without the warning signal
So difficult it is, to use the blink?
Did you start shooting them?
No, I don't carry gun
I was with the woman.
She had a gun
They began to shoot me,
and I shoot them back!
I move my fingers 2
cm to use the blink
Why is so hard for him to do the same...
That they cannot move the finger
some cm to drive safe?
Do you want to know why?
Not especially
Because These rich bastards
they can kill even their own mother
in order to make more money...
So when they are driving,
they cannot help them selves..
they have the same attituded,
are incosiderable drivers too..
Why you didnt takes the baby to the police?
No, I cant go to them
Why not?
I Am "Unabomber"
They already caught "Unabomber"...
That was I think
Stupid!
Shit.. thats it..
You are the most furious man in the world
yea? If I remember well, you
liked it before..
How many men you've got?
How many local boys?
I need men, do you understand Me?
I need a lot more men...
MOUNT OF PITY
I want 4 loaders...
A box with bullets of 9mm
147 with hollow tip
And give me 50 bullets from a strong metal..
You dont have enough money...
You lied me, you said that
you have 5000 dollars...
can We make it with food Tickets?
You want to buy bullets with "Tickets"...
They are same as cash...
You are pathetic, Smith
we will wait for you outside...
I will endorse you this check from the Bank
of blood, it is that enough?
You can add the check from the Bank
of sperm and we have a deal...
I will get this check latest on Wednesday...
You can Take half box of bullets...
I ll give you the other half when
you will come on Wednesday...
Deal!
Damned you, Smith...
What the hell are you doing!
I am making money...
Making money?
To buy something for the baby...
To buy something to the baby?
A bullet proof jacket is the beter
investment for this baby...
That make me think, what you are thinking
to put on him when he will go to school?
So, this is it...
Is Not Rich but it is my home
Same old Smith.!
I am happy that you like it
Say hallo to Mickey
Maybe, I should take the baby
to the police
No, you will never make it...
They might have a Van to be watching over there and
they should have a policemen in their pocket...
already joined 50 men...
They must be enough...
WEAPONS
Stop the car.
It was here...
What makes you think he was here?
Trust me, I know what people think,
I always do..
Even When I was a kind i had this gift...
You had to see me playing arround the
"Paper, Stone and Scissors"...
Stop the car!
Do you think who wants this baby dead?
I have no idea who wants to kill it
Don't call it "that"...
For me it is an object
Tell me, Smith,
Is there something that you like?
Yes, my privacy
Tell me something that I dont know for once,
You son of bitch, bastard
I love you to speak this way to me...
Can I offer you something?
A carrot?
They are good for your eyes
From all of the places in the city,
He knows that Smith is here..
Did have a lucky guess?
No, He doesnt guess...
Thinks, things that we don't,
he was an investigator of the FBI
"Forensic behavior adviser"
How many times I have to say?
The details...
They are to important
in this business.
Hear, but...
Dont you think that he should ne bag soon?
the leader that stays
behind, He take it from the behind.
Also...
...it is very amusing to see violence.
No, baby, no...
We can call it Oliver.
Oliver?
yea, as Oliver Twist
For that is orphan?
For that I like the book.
Do you like it?
I Dint hate it.
That is a miracle
That birthday card,
you think that you can go with it?
Pretty and adorable...
Or... you are already a man
Sr. Hertz, how old is your son?
8 years...
Can you believe it? Not there is anything
in the TV about this
A bomb hurt...
Did you notice that?
That yea I noticed that?
look.
The politicians speak for gun control
...and it cries
We can change it to this hard Rock music...
...and he is quiet
That is strange
It should comfort him
Mr.?
The men are in the roof
That well
Anybody knows what
James cagney love scene, is?
It is when Cagney leaves
the good guy to live.
And when that happends in the show...
...I want alot more, in order not
to aks my money back
Let's kill this mother. Go!
I am not surprised that He likes Rock
You look like a substitute parents
No, I tell you, this means...
Go back!
My God, they are so bad
or this guy is very good?
Let us go boys!
They Still not safe
Kill the dog!
No.
why not?
I like dogs.
Give me a minute
That unfortunate rat
What it is?
the babies diaper
It is a terrible idea, Smith
It is the only one that we have
Your you believe that Oliver's mama
she lived near to a club..
...and that the baby could hear the
music from the club?
yea, for that reason he doesn't cry when
he listens rock music..
This is a ridiculous idea
He is not crying now
This is the only club
near where I saw his mom.
It is a very crazy hunch
yea, Can you explain all those
boxes of diapers?
Somebody needed those supplies
Lets find, who
Are you the owner?
Who asks?
I ask
Can I invite you for a drink?
No, I already imagined it...
This covered with hoops
Who occupies the room up stares?
go to hell!
Don't mess with me
You dont have the balls.
My God!
Who are those guys?
I Rent the room to a
businessman, 11 months ago
they pay for an entire year, cash
I never saw them again.
I believe that they entered from behind.
Open up.
This is very strange.
Sir.,There is nowhere to go this guy.
All the mothers have been killed.
Only one have escaped, temporarily.
We find the body, and
we confirm that she gave a birth
The child births suposed it was secret,
They start an manufacture
maternity, above a club...
...and it wasnt remain secret
We killed all the baby siters we find here.
When it happens, go to the left.
I Already made the call, they
must coming in any minute.
We will clean everything and we will try
to discover what happen
Thank you Mister,
I appreciate your trust.
Gentlemen, let find some answers.
Mind where you step.
The ice cream is melting.
What?
Your specialty is not
the donated sperm.
This this full with samples
That strange.
Seems to be only one donor
One donor?
yea, and is a very generous.
It is bone marrow blood, it should
to be for some cure.
How do you know that, Smith?
Youd didnt hear about my Nobel prize?
It is difficult to find compatible marrow
with that of the receiver
The possibilites improved if the
donors one has the same DNA with the receivers.
They were taking babys organs for
some guys transplante?
Exactly. And somebody didnt want
to avoid the transplante.
For that reason they want to kill Oliver.
No, baby, no.
So, I Called a guy that
I knew in NBC.
And I started to think,
Do you know what I hate?
Oh... there we go again
The movies that the good guy become
to betrayed by some one that he trust.
yea, it is as serious as
to kill baby seals
Call to ABC, CBS...
The Post, the Times, the local
news chanel and the FBI.
And what you ll do next?
I ll wait to see the news, and if the story
goes in publin, maybe we will be safe.
look. He finally get to sleep.
You just wait. As soon are closings
their eyes so soon they began to scream.
Your you are not able to pleasure
anything, realy?
You hate everything.
I don't hate you.
For that reason you bring it to me?
you know that I didnt picked you.
you dont have any idea
what you have done to me.
We can get out of this.
It is that you don't understand.
what?
You bring me this boy so I can feed him
and take care of him.
And the baby could be die
in any moment.
And you are not even asked me what
happed to my own son.
You are right.
It is unforgivable.
I have the blame.
He didnt even called me mama...
If I ll ask you for forgiveness,
will you translate that to me?
The eggs must not
dance with the stones.
You Know, Smith...
I think I know what you hate most...
yourself.
What killed your baby?
Forget it
Tell me...
My "Pimp" stick me in the stomach...
My baby...
He was borned dead.
Get off of me...
You like this, hey...
It is a gun...
Fist, sliding bar,
it embroidered, canyon, trigger.
This is the side that
it make it work.
You should never point this in
anything that you don't want to kill.
This is important.
This is the insurance.
You have to have in safety mode
in order not to shot alone.
But in fact...
...this it is your best insurance.
Are you hungry?
Speaking of a complete discharge.
looks at this.
This is a Hammerson Nite Tac.
They will leave it for sale in 6 months.
That strange.
All have one of these.
Dont even tell me
Do you know how many
men of ours had liquidated?
Why to weast my beautiful mind
for things like that?
Doesnt make you a little angry?
When getting angry you loose one
enzyme, triptofan hidroxilasa...
...that they can reduce
temporarily the intelligence
Not I can give myself the luxury
of making that.
How do you know of that?
My boy is trapped with
the Discovery channel.
Take me to the West side.
I need to report him in,
I think I PE-d on who our Mr. Hero is.
We will no longer discuss.
I need to do this alone. And
to know that you are safe.
This is the only place
that you will be safe.
In a tank?
A tank M24. They are safe
from bullets and other explosive.
You are crazy
I am
I also speak seriously.
Is forbidden to get in.
Don't worry... I will create
a diversion and you'll climbe inside.
There is enough food
for the baby for two days.
The puree of carrots
it is the best.
Do you know how to use this... really?
yea, but what if you dont come back?
That won't happen
we can be sure.
Yes there is.
But mama I want to go home!
Stop to complain!
Behave well or I give you a spanking!
I want to leave!
Stop to complain!
I hate that hit a boy.
Leave alone!
No if you dont stop hit the boy.
I can disiplina my kind like want.
Do you like to spanking to you?
Do you go?, it doesn't feel very well, does it.
Its not funny!
Not it is funny!
What you know about this
so spectacular soldier?
Anybody so good
he had to start very young.
And usually their papa
it was also good.
The papa of MacArthur was general
And Mickey's dad Mantle
juice baseball.
My son dominates the games of
videos, and I was good for Pong.
Please follow me, Sr. Hammerson.
In 1967 the Englishmen put on
hard the control of weapons.
Many makers of
you arm they moved in U.S.
I have a man in immigration.
...seeing how many of them had sons...
...and yea some of those boy was a great hardshoot...
I believe that have been affecting from the "factor men".
You dont have anything for this man!
yea, Duchess was a good girl.
Sit!
yea. Now you ll play for your cookie.
My man that his been looking for him...
...he remembered the son
of one guns maker...
that was a National Champion of guns
in age of 10..
Candidate for the Olympiads,
and He recruit it by the army
But after that the kind never come back again.
Kisses...
It seems that operations
quarter trained him.
That which takes me to a theory...
Theory?
That sounds as a gossip!
The only thing that you know about him,
its.. is a man without a name.
...who arrived to town on a
white horse to give justice.
I LOVE THE CATS
Do You know for the people
of this country, why they love the guns?
Not because they like the word "discharge"
No, people love the guns...
For that USA is the land
of the opportunities
...where a poor person he can become rich...
...and a pussy can
be a hard type...
...if he's got a gun in his hand.
I Hope you are not just a pusy
with a gun in your hand.
No, Mister,
I am not
I am a tough guy, with
that pussy in my hand.
I want you to put this guy
and the kind to a deardbag.
yea Mister...
Right away, Sir...
Don't worry,
dad will return soon.
Hold it! Hold it!
Well-well-well, Mr. Bunny, you just
keep going-going-going, dontcha.
You also
I promise you not to kill you, if you say to me
where this girl and the baby are.
Forget it!
Oh
Who trained you?
NSA, Black-ops, CIA, the Army?
What who ever is the sme. It seems that
you lost your aim, champion.
You should see me write
my name in the snow.
Hey ya know my boss here thinks such
you're the lone rangers or sumtin...
But I believe I've a better
idea bout who you are.
I found out how your
wife and son were killed.
My God, what a tragedy!
Some guy walks into the BurgerJoy,
he starts shooting up the police...
Oh my God, what a shame,
that your wife and son were there...
...having chicken nuggets...
What's the matter,
you dont like that story?
I want you to tell me one.
Children story, please...
oh... I know, tell me my favor it,
tell the one about the baby
Maybe later.
When I will put you to sleep.
Go go go!
So What you are you thinking
about the right to carry weapons, now?
Fuck you!
Ok buddy, drop your weapon.
You think we kill him?
God Dammit, Smith!
So I found out who tried to kill the baby.
Who?
A certain Hammerso, was born with one
tablespoon of the silver in the bottom.
It inherited a corporation
of firearms
It wins millions manufacturing weapons
Do You have any idea of who
needs Oliver's "death"?
Its ok, Oliver.
Rutledge wins in New Hampshire
Shit!
It Is the Senator Rutledge.
THE CONTROL OF WEAPONS KEY
If he select the presided he will
make that Hammerson business
Ok, but how are you sure?
The Mr. right "Arm"
I call to their men nannies.
The Secret Service calls to those
protective of VIP, nannies
The Senator Rutledge is
the one that needs the baby
We will contact this man and there will
be no danger anymore. And its over
You are crazy?
Hammerson and the whole government
of the USA are after us
We have to leave the city
Until I have the answers you are not safe.
They watch over all the buss stations,
trains and airports
TRAVEL IN THE GREEN BUS
This is safe
I will investigate well.
I will reach you before
get on the bus
And if you don't arrive before we leave?
Where should I get off?
Honey, It's better
if I don't know.
What?
trust me
I cannot know it
Smith, you Believe that this
will work?
Attempt to the plan,
and everything will be alright.
Run!
You can forget the belt
of security
What in hell is that?
My God they twisted.
That sick sunova'bitch.
Oh that sick son of a bitch
stuck at us again!
It is time to go boy.
I call for the guy that he
protects the Senator Rutledge
Just Tell him, that the man with baby calling
Hello, Does Smith Speak?
Your man they try to clean the place of your
hide hatchery with babies in down town
But nothing will you succeed if I wont give the baby
Only in Washinton they have
so much influence
We are in the same side.
We can make it with the easy way
or with the hard way.
I want to see the Senator
Good. he also wants to see you too
I will go to North Carolina.
There are elections in three days
You can go in the airplane with him.
Track 7 in two hours
If I see something that I don't like
everybody will know about it
what you were doing here inside?
I was cleaning my gun.
Seriously?
We never realy trying to kill you.
We only wanted to make
you surrendered.
That explains the bad aim.
The Senator Rutledge, continues
to the head of the Democrats...
...before the elections
primary of Tuesday.
I owe you my life.
Here is the place that you were gave
all those orders...
I heard about you
It is worse than in television
It is incredible what
a little make-up can do
And a lot of morphine
So...
...You realy discovered us.
You are very clever Mr. Smith.
Very clever.
It was easy. You are a candidate
important for the Presidency
With Your proposal of weapons control,
you made mad the wrong people
yea they are angry now,But wait
I until be the president
There are so many lobbyists of weapons...
...that we will have
to establish many commissions
And maybe we do this way
our first law of the year
Those of the weapons
they informed about your illness.
They discovered the incubator
of your babies and they resolved the problem
They killing you by killing the babies
Correct
Where this my savior?
My God a he/she arms!
Do you know that the most I hate are the lies..
What In Hell are you doing?
You made a deal with Hammerson.
You are crazy!
When you went to bed, you filed with
their dogs hairs
And judging by the hair in your
pants, Duchess likes you alot
I dont know what are you talking about
I would say that he
wont be a president
If he ends up here...
Do you know what I hate most?
the hypocrites
And you are bigest of them all
That accusation doesnt have been sold?
Our operation is to find the baby
You see, Rutledge calls us
and offered us a proposetion...
...with the something that we had never dreamt
In exchange of his life, he promised us
to protect our rights
To go hunting deers with an "Uzi"
Please, Smith. The guns
they don't kill people.
But yea they help
Back off, back off.
Back of or I will kill him
Please!
I have to do it!
I must be a president
To put your self
before the people
I can still do good, in other areas.
Are you gonna squeal
with the public?
It is a Constitutional right
Back off! Get back!
Finally they convinced me
They convinced you just saying "Hello"
Allow me to give you an advice
Never trust people that try to benefit
against the peoples life, they are bad
Dont be silly. The game is over,
you throw the dice and you lost.
Let him go, Smith!
There is no escape.
Maybe for me not, but
for the woman and the baby, yes
For your assasination, Rutledge...
...will be a lot of anger and
the will support your proposal.
They will vote in the Congress...
...for law antiarms,
go by an overwhelming majority.
Their legacy... will live on.
Don't do it!
Don't do it. Allow to recover
some my honor with my...
son of bitch...
You son of bitch!
God Dammit!
Don't move Mr. hero...
Not I can speak sweethaerd now...
I am halfway something
Good-bye.
Don't worry, Duchess...
It won't gona happendto you.
At least for some years
Well well well well well.
Somebody gets to be smart
and somebody gets to be dumb.
Looks like you and I are finally
changing places, boy?
Yes, indeed.
The circle of life
the cirle a jerk of life
You are very good with the words
Now
I want you to tell me where
the woman and the boy are
Tell me, or I will be forced to
cause you considerable agony.
Believe me..
...nothing can be more
painful than hear you jerk talking.
I ll ask you... Again.
Where the woman and the boy are?
Thats is the last time that
you be doing that
Tell me what I want to hear. You decide when
pain will stop.
Why you doing this?
Its over
Sortly we will be finished for sure...
No, I should thank you...
They gave me a biger contract
because of you
I wasnt just Hammerson hominate
what are you babbling now?
You realy believe that
people that hires me...
...they will accept not to
kill the sun of Senator
you can hide all this...
you didnt have heard the news?
The senator's airplane
crash at the river
And they havent been able to find
the body of Senator
Since I will silent you and
the woman, nobody will know anything
Again I ask you,
Where the woman and the boy are?
You know what will happend if you break me
another one of my fingers?
My son told me.
That You ll hit me in the nose
I ll Kick you in the ass.
I ll do something funny, I
ll brake one of that...
What if don't arrived before?
I know all of your story
The man that began to
shoot in the restaurant
He visited the store of weapons
that you inherited from your papa
Your you sold him the shotgun that
killed your wife and son
I won't tell you anything,
you God damned fucker
Where are you, Smith?
Well well well well
We will need something
a little more painful
Thats it
The guns are fabulous.
No, Hammerson?
Who is the great hardshoot now?
Oh yes, sir,.
It certainly was a pleasure
But before we part ways,
tell me one thing...
I am dying from the desire to know,
who you realy are?
As you say?
I said I am dead...
Stop!
Until there, you guessed right
is your wife
Hello, honey
she will leave me
Do you know what I really hate?
What I really hate...
...it is a maricon with
a gun in the hand.
CROSS THE COUNTRY
IN THE GREEN BUS
TRAVEL WEEKLY
Investigators discovered
the senator's body Rutledge
The FBI said that they received
an anonymous call
Don't worry baby, mama she will
watch you over, while she works
Oliver
Hello
What took you so long?
This is a robery!
Empty the box!
Everybody stay stll, dont you
move or I will shoot you in the head!
He said don't move!
So dont even breathe
If nobady move, than nobady will die
Don't move!
We are in a hurry friend, lets go!
Do you know what I hate?
Shut up and sit on this you foul!
Exactly, you heard him!