Je m'appelle Victoria
Comment allez-vous?
Santé... no... no...
My sister sent me a postcard
All it said was: come to Paris,
it will be good for you
48 hours after I arrived...
...she and everyone I've
met were dead
Open the bag
Sorry?
- Open the bag
- Open my bag? Ok
Have you been in Paris before?
No, I've never been
here before
I get nervous sometimes
- Ne comprend vous francais?
- Sorry? I don't understand
She asked you if
you understand French
No, I don't speak french
Are you staying in a hotel room?
I'm staying with my sister
Hey, welcome to Paris
Have you fun yet?
She's... I don't know where
she's staying...
...but she studies
at the Sorbone
Her address?
I don't know. I'm sorry
She's picking me up at the airport
I don't know
Welcome to France
This trip is gonna
change you forever
Aren't you excited?
Yeah definitely. I just
have a headache
There is the sister I remember
Where are we going?
This is where you live?
Yep. Is pretty creepy, right?
Got a good deal with the rent, though
You'll loved this
France's first serial killer
had a room on the fifth floor
He chopped a bunch of bodies
before someone complains...
...about the noise the bone saw
is making everyday
They making proud of him
But the guy went fucking mental
By the time the cops got here,
he already killed everyone in the fourth...
After the massacre
everyone moved out...
Too much bad blood, they said
- What?
- I'm just fucking with you
It's just a shit building
You gotta learn to lighten up, honey
There's not a homicidal maniac
lurking in every shadow
Alright. Turn the light on,
would you?
I don't know where the light is
I wasn't talking to you
What?
Is every single moment of your life
into scare the shit out of people?
Even that as a suggestion
breaks my heart, Carolyn
Don't take it personal. They do it
to everyone. Are you ok?
Yeah, I know is...
Where I'll sleep?
Sleep in Baltimore, Vic
Nor even the dead sleep in Paris
It's just I didn't sleep
on the plane last night
I was nervous about the flight
so I can't sleep...
Yeah, well... Sorry there's no time
We got a party to get ready for
Sorry? There's no way I can
go to a party tonight
Not dressed like mom,
you can't
C'mon. Let's go shopping
Do you feel ok?
Yeah...
Sure don't have anything
to say to Quasimodo?
What do you think so far?
Of what?
Of what? Of Paris!
Look around you, is the
most beautiful city in the world!
The City of light. Romance,
art, architecture, beauty...
It's hard to imagine that stays on top
of the larger mass grave of the history
C'mon. You can't go to a
party without the shoes
Oh, God! You scared me!
You? You usually are
so calm and collected
What are you taking?
Nothing... I told you I have a headache
Well, spin that ass!
The taxi's coming
Victoria, this is my dear friend Hugo...
He's one of the hosts of
the most fabulous party...
Hugo, this is my infamous
sister Victoria
Je m'appelle Victoria
We all speak english here, sister
- Ok
What am I? An amateur?
No. This is for your sister
For me?
- Ladies, please. Come in
- Au revoir, mon cherie
C'mon sis
Carolyn wait
Where are we going?
It's too late to turn back now
I don't understand
What kind of party is this?
This is the kind of party
that'll change your life
It changed mine, anyway
Seriously, why anybody want to
throw a party down here?
Because this is where the
dead bodies are
You're just trying to scare me?
Aren't you?
I'm not. I swear. Everything
I'd say is absolutely true
Paris' dirty old secrets
"Abandon all hope
here you enter"
Pretty
200 years ago, Paris ran out
of room to bury its dead
The graveyards were stuffed,
like fifteen bodies deep
The corpses were rotting
in the streets
Some brilliant person decides to
start over. Just dig out the bodies...
...of every dead person
in Paris. All seven millions of them...
...and stuck their bones in this
mines shafts under the left bank
- Seven millions?
- Isn't that funny?
Don't the police try to stop you?
They tried. They created a whole task force
to shut us down. The "catacops"
There's 300 miles of tunnels under the city
and we never go party the same place twice
Que-ce tu fais?
Do you remember Nico and Leon?
Hey
Let's move, Jean-Michele
is waiting for us
Who is Jean-Michele?
You'll meet him
He and Hugo were who came with
the idea of throw out parties down here
...have become more and more popular...
I have being accused in the press
of being in love with the death
A kind of necrophilia, I suppose
But in ancient Greece, it was
a practice of philosophers...
...to keep a human skull
on their desk
The idea was this...
...only with a conscious awareness...
...of our pending death
Can we appreciate our life fully
I always found myself
persuaded by that sentiment
The only problem is...
...I never own a desk!
Welcome to the Catacombs!
Hello!
Hey there!
A water, please?
Can I have a water, please?
You don't have to drink here
- Are you Jean-Michele?
- Carolyn has told me a lot about you?
What did she say?
She said you are
afraid of the darkness
I'm not, really
You're not? Because I am
We all are
Why the hell do you come
to this place, then?
"It is God's kindness to terrify us
so that we become stronger"
Where am I suppose to drink?
You're wasting your time, Jean-Michele
She doesn't drink alcohol
It's not alcohol
It's absinthe
- Go, go, go. C'mon!
- She did it!
I can see this going very badly
Hey! Space cadet!
Are you okay?
So, since you arrived in Paris...
Did you see a ghost yet?
- That line is getting so old...
- She's in Paris...
The most haunted city in the world
It is a legitimate question
Look around you
Six million people...
Torn from the ground and stacked
under your feet like wood for the fire...
If there are ghost anywhere,
there are ghosts in Paris
If there are ghosts anywhere,
there are ghosts in this place!
You know, he's absolute right
The catacombs are haunted
But not by ghouls or specters
The catacombs are haunted by people
The lowest creeps and lunatics drown
down from the surface by morbidity
Death is a spectacle
An opera
When the cult of the Black Virgin
began inverting the rites of...
...Catholiscism. Painting
the statue of Mary in black...
...and praying to Satan...
Even when those people claimed to have
given birth to the Antichrist
No sane person
took them seriously
But they did
They take a child...
...born of the incest...
...raised on raw meat...
...they never allow
him to see daylight...
...tought him he was
the destroyer of man
Dress him in a gruesome goatskin mask
What do you expect?
By the time the boy was eighteen...
They have succeeded
They have created...
...a hawking...
...unthinking lunatic...
...so evil...
...that definitive he could
be called the Antichrist
C'mon! A killer with a goat mask?
It's just another myth
A more frightened one, but...
...still a myth
There's articles in the newspapers
every week about people that come down...
...to the catacombs and
never make it out
No, this is not a myth
This monster they had created...
...is down here.
Somewhere
Ok, you guys don't go to graduate
school with Carolyn. Do you?
Let's go swimming
What do you say sis?
Do you like taking a dip?
C'mon Vic! Nobody gives a shit
Get over it!
Get naked. Get in the water
Carolyn...
- Carolyn
- C'mon! Take 'em out!
It just your body.
You have a beautiful body
You didn't see the Balboa
Is nothing, you guys. I'm just
a little cold. That's all
Yeah, right. Otherwise she
would been the first one in
But it's cold!
I'm wanna go home!
You know, Vic. You might try
for once in your life...
...to not be the lamest
person in the room
Leave her alone!
Well, it gotta be me, right?
I think I'm gonna go back to the party
That sounded much more
hateful that I meant
Can somebody show me
the way back to the party?
Is that way
Looks like you're stuck.
And you have to go swimming
- It's ok. I'll find it
- Vic, don't be a retard...
...you can go back alone.
You gonna get lost
It's a maze.
Vic! Seriously!
Vic!
As with us soon you shall be
Is what it says
- You scared me
- Good
People like you
need to be scared
I'm serious, dumbass.
Don't walk out like that. It's dangerous
Sound doesn't travel in the Catacombs.
You could get lost before you know it
You're not lost.
Are you?
No. I don't think so
Maybe I'm lost
Are you serious?
What's so funny?
Whoever wrote that doesn't think
it matters which way we go
What it's say?
"There is but one way
to enter this life...
...but the gates of death
are outnumbered"
That's great
What the fuck was that?
I though you said sound
doesn't travel down here
It doesn't. Stay here
I get it
The guys are just trying to
scare you. They live for that shit
Bye! Fuck off!
Carolyn, I wanna
go home. Please
Wait! Wait!
Can you feel that?
What?
The music in my feet. The bass.
We're almost back to the party
C'mon! Dance with me
What happened? Turn on the
light! What happened?
- Why it went out?
- The batteries must be dead!
- Hang on!
- What?
What do you mean
they're dying?
Batteries die.
The light starts to glimmer
Oh my God!
What we got here?
- The flashlight is dying!
- It's ok!
No it's not. The batteries
are dying
You're such a spaz!
Oh my God!
What are we gonna do?
Why they still doing that?
It's not funny!
You can't be my sister
You had to be adopted
All I wanna say is how
can you be so calm right now?
Because of the first rule
on the Catacombs
Always brings more
than one light source
Do you see, spaz?
Not everything is a crisis
C'mon. The party is closer
Carolyn!
Carolyn! No!
Carolyn! please!
Please!
Help!
Help me!
No!
My God
Please, light
Please, light. Please, light
Please...
Please, please, please...
C'mon, c'mon...
Help me!
No!
Leave me alone!
Noooooo!
Help!
Hello?
Hello!
Can anybody hear me?
Oh, not!
Leave me alone!
Help me!
Help!
Fuck!
He's trying to kill me!
Heeeeelp!
Help me!
Somebody help me!
Help!
Victoria!
Jean-Michele! Jean-Michele!
Jean-Michele
Jean-Michele...!
She's dead!
Oh no!
Hello?
Anybody?
Is anybody there?
Can anybody hear me? I'm
down here! Can anybody hear me?
Can anybody hear me?
I'm caught in here!
I'm here!
61... 62... 63...
...64... 65...
...83... 84...
...85... 86...
...91... 92...
...93... 94... 95...
...102... 103... 104...
1, 2, 3, 4, 5...
...6, 7, 8, 9, 10...
Hello!
Can anybody hear me
up there?
Somebody please help me!
Help!
Help me!
I don't understand what
you're saying!
Stay there!
Don't come near me!
Stop were you are!
Don't!
I don't understand!
Wait! I can't understand you.
I can't understand you. What?
C'est bloqué! C'est bloqué!
Bloqué! Bloqué!
- The exit?
- Bloqué.
- It's blocked?
No shit, asshole!
Hey, that's my flashlight, asshole!
Wait! I can't see!
You can't just steal somebody's
flashlight. You jerk!
Wait!
Do you know where you're going?
You have to be careful
Are you listening to me?
What is that?
Is that a map?
- Plan. Oui.
- A "plan" of this place?
Let me see
It's a street map. Up there.
A street map
It's moi!
For God's sake. Stop that!
Rue Saint Medard?
What? So...?
Hey, stop! Hello?
You know what you're doing?
These are the same as above on the
street level. The same intersections?
Sortie.
- There's another exit.
- Oui. Oui.
Where are we?
- Sortie!
- Oh, my God. That's so far!
So what happened?
Were... Were you at the party?
Were you at the party?
Did you get lost, too?
Hey!
Could you wait up?
- Attention!
- Please, slow down a little
Please, slow down
Don't touch me!
D'accord!
You're going too fast
I can't see anything
Hey!
Wait!
Where do you going?
What are you doing?
Why are we st...?
Why are we stopping?
We have to keep going
What are you hiding?
What is that?
Get away from me!
Don't touch me!
What are you doing?
What are you doing? Don't
touch me! Get away from me!
Get away from me!
You're fucking hysterical
Good
Henri
- Henri?
- Oui
Henri
- That's your name?
- Oui
I'm Victoria
Victoria
My sister died yesterday
At least I think
it was yesterday
Tu par fait?
Henri?
Henri!
Henri, goddamned you!
you son of a bitch!
Henri! Don't
you leave me here!
I'll die here!
Where the fuck did you go?
Give me the fucking lantern!
No. No, no, no, no
Tu fais pa. Tu fais pa
Votre lantern, mademoiselle
Fucking dick!
Get off me!
- Mon Dieu!
- C'mon, Henri. Get lost!
- We've to find the other exit
- Victoria?
- Remember?
Henri watch out
Be careful
Pay attention, Henri
Slowly
Be careful
Are you ok?
Henri! Henri!
Oh my God!
Is gonna be okay
Henri! Give me your hand!
Give me your hand, please!
Henri, give me your hand!
Get up, please! Please, please...
Henri, give me your...
Alright, alright...
One, two, three... Go!
Don't look at it!
Look at me!
Henri!
C'mon!
You can do it! C'mon!
Ok! Come here!
Pull! C'mon!
You have to pull harder!
Please!
Ok...
Henri, we're going to try
with two hands now. Ok?
Two hands
C'mon, Henri!
Victoria?
I'm sorry. I'm sorry
No, I'm sorry. I'm gonna find
the exit and I'll come back
I swear! Stay where
you are! I'm gonna come back!
I promise you that I will return
I promise it to you
No! Victoria!
Victoria! No!
Merde!
I think I got turn around somehow
Henri?
Jesus!
Hello?
Leave me alone!
Fuck! Stay on!
Stay on! Stay on!
You need to be strong!
Please! Don't die!
Don't die!
Turn on! Turn on!
Turn on... Please!
Please, just stay on.
Back on! Don't die!
Victoria?
- I knew it. My sister...
- Man, I'm hungry...
- Can we go eat?
- You really thought I was dead?
That's histerical
You really thought I was
dead this whole time. Didn't you?
I knew it! Oh my God...
That's histerical!
You thought I was really
dead this whole time. Didn't you?
We fake the slash
It's stage blood
There's no monster, it was just
a prank.
It was Hugo on a mask.
Will you show her?
Look. Do you see?
It was just a joke
A joke?
Not a joke.
A prank, an initiation
The cult of the Black Virgin.
The monster on the goat mask...
...it's just an underground haunted
house meant to scary us fast
This guys is been doing it for years
We're gonna explain everything
but the cops showed up...
...and raid us and separated us
It's been safer for you
be down there, sis.
We've been call you for hours
Hello?
Victoria! Stop running!
Victoria!
It's the walls.
You can't hear nothing
Leave alone me!
No...
My God. Henri!
Hey, stop being such a
drama queen
We kill him!
No, we shouldn't did what we did.
But that what's these guys do
Every single moment of your life is
into scaring shit out of people?
Didn't you see a ghost yet?
They just trying to scare you.
They live for that shit
We thought it would be for you
Hey!
You scared me!
Good. People like you
need to be scared
There's not homicidal maniac
lurking in every shadow
Jean-Michele always says when
you survive your own death, you reborn
Is the whole reason we
come down to the Catacombs
Only with the conscious awareness
of our pending death...
...can we appreciate our lifes fully
Why do you think I wanted you
to came here in the first place?
I thought it will help you
to get over your issues...
...to get rid of those stupid
pills once and for all
- Where is Jean-Michele?
- I don't know
Have you seen him?
- Merde, qui est qu'il est Ià?
- Holy shit! Jean-Michele!
God! Oh my God!
Stop shaking him!
Is he dead?
- Jean-Michele!
- God!
Get of him!
Stop shaking him!
No, no, not
Jean-Michele! No!
Check his pulse!
Jean-Michele!
How fucking this could happen?
No... no...
You stupid, fucking cunt!
His dead! How you could
to be so fucking stupid?
What's going on in that
stupid head of yours?
Look what you fucking did!
Get up and look what you did!
Look what you did!
Look what you fucking did!
- I'm sorry
- Stupid fucking bitch!
I fucking hate you!
Everything you ever done in your
fucking life is a mistake
You're sorry?
Always fucking sorry!
You ruined everything!
I fucking hate you so much!
Look what you did!
There's something wrong with you!
Look what you did
you fucking idiot!
I wish you were dead! You're so
stupid you couldn't even kill yourself!
What is fucking wrong with you?
You stupid... Everywhere...
You should kill yourself...
Crazy stupid bitch!
Everything you...
Nooooo!
My sister sent me a postcard
All it said was: "Come to Paris
It'll be good for you"
48 hours after I arrived...
She and everyone I've
met were dead
Airport, please