What are you doing here?
Who has touched you?
Imhotep!
My priest!
Pharaoh's bodyguards.
You must go! Save yourself!
-No.
-Only you can resurrect me!
I won't leave you!
Get away from me!
You shall live again!
I will resurrect you!
My body is no longer his temple!
HAMU NAPTRA - 1290 B.C.
HAMU NAPTRA - 1923
The Creature remains undiscovered.
And what of this one?
-Should we kill him?
-No.
The desert will kill him.
CAIRO, EGYPT
3 YEARS LATER
G IZA PORT - CAIRO
This one is strong.
Come with me
my Princess Anck-su-namun.
The language of the slaves...
...I may have use for you.
And the rewards...
... will be great.
Where are the other sacred jars?
FORT BRYDON, CAIRO
You saved me from the undead.
I thank you.
Kill them all!
Kill them...
...and wake the others.
With your death, Anck-su-namun shall live.
And I shall be invincible!
The Book of Amun-Ra.
Destroy him!
I command you to destroy him!
Give me that book!
Now you die.
Now it's your turn.