Dario!
A message from Peligro.
Ho!
Mambo, Mambo, Mambo, Mambo
Mambo
Ladies and gentlemen,
a very good evening to you all.
El Tropico,
the most fabulous nightclub in
the world, presents
its latest,
but not late show,
where we are taking you all
to the magical productions
of our Rodney the Great.
Ladies and gentlemen,
we are honored tonight
to have in our presence
the world's greatest
living race car driver,
here in Cuba for the first
Havana Grand Prix.
Ladies and gentlemen,
the one and only Fangio
for once, stationary.
Fangio! Fangio!
Fangio!
And now, a special treat
for a very special couple.
Forever newlyweds,
Dona Cecilia, Don Federico,
The Anniversary waltz
by Strauss.
Happy Anniversary.
A toast.
To the most
elegant couple in Havana.
Happy Anniversary.
And to this,
the happiest of families.
May it be that way forever.
Hear, hear. Salud.
Salud.
Dance with me,
as you once did?
You make me
sound like a relic.
My relic.
Donoso, would you
dance with me?
Watch yourself.
Uncle has two left feet now.
His elbow,
it works fine.
I would give an arm
and a leg and an elbow
for just one single waltz.
My kingdom for a cha-cha-cha!
Hear, hear.
Let's go dance.
I'll be right back. Wait here.
What's wrong?
So which one
of those dancers
is your girlfriend
this week?
Who are you
saving yourself for?
No one.
All the good ones
are already spoken for.
Fangio, I want to present to you
my wife Mercedes Fellove.
Come on, let's go.
This meeting was my idea...
because these are very
difficult times, as you know.
Cuba has always
lived in difficult times,
but through them all,
we have been able to survive
because we have
always been united.
But our country
isn't safe anymore,
and it threatens us.
Your uncle and I are all
that remains of our generation.
So, my sons,
you are the future.
The future of our family.
The future of this island.
Yes, and
look at me.
Look at me, because
this is for you, too.
If we want to
change the status quo,
we must go about it
in a democratic way.
You hear?
We must be patriots.
Patriots.
Patriotism is a refuge for scoundrels.
Do you
It is politics
that has become
the practical refuge of
Papi, do not make the mistake
of confusing me for
one of your students.
I'm not. I graduated.
Hey.
Show a little respect.
No, no, no, no.
Let him talk.
This is a democracy.
Oh, this country,
a democracy? Right.
Our family is a democracy.
This country is my family,
and the only way
to truly unite that family
is revolution.
Revolution?
Revolution, yes.
I just can't believe it.
A son of mine
that would support
the random violence
of revolution?
You better start believing it.
What you need is
a little evolution,
not revolution.
Correct.
The poet.
Club owner, poet.
You're lucky you're on
the other side of the room.
I feel lucky,
because it probably
stinks on that side of the room.
Please.
Happy Anniversary.
You are too much.
Did I forget to say that?
Happy Anniversary?
Just watch your mouth.
What? You've been watching it
the whole time.
If I hear one more
word of disrespect
coming out of your mouth,
I'm gonna
deal with it personally.
Do you understand me?
What?
You understand
what I just said to you?
I understand
You listen to your father
when he's speaking to you,
and you show respect!
Calm down, Fico.
No, you calm down!
Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay.
You want me
to come over there?
Okay.
Huh? You want me
to come over there?
Stop it!
Come on.
Stop it.
Four against one, huh?
Sit down.
Is this a democracy?
You got your little show.
Sit down.
Sit down, right? How is it?
Sit down!
Is this a random act
of violence, Papi?
Huh?
They shot Lieutenant Dario.
Did they get
good descriptions this time?
Did he mention Peligro again?
Mm-hmm.
What happened?
I'm not gonna
have this conversation
with you, you, you,
or any of you.
You know what?
You have no idea
what's going on in this country.
It's sad that you're a professor
and you have zero
zero idea of what is going on
in your own classroom.
Then can you enlighten me?
Can you tell me what's going on?
Discontent, anger...
desperation.
That's what's going
on in this country,
everywhere in this country,
and especially
at your university.
Revolution, okay? It happened in France,
it happened in Russia,
and it's happening here,
and it's happening now.
Nobody wants a revolution.
You don't want a revolution.
But like it or not,
it's coming.
The people, they want it.
How do you know?
Has the people of Cuba spoken to you
in your chosen ears?
No. Batista must be eliminated.
And then what?
Freedom. Democracy.
Right, yeah.
Power to the people.
That's easier said than done.
It can be done,
but the first thing
you have to do
is kill that son of a bitch.
Kill, kill, kill, kill, kill.
Have you ever thought
to live for your country?
Yes. Live. I am living!
I live, and I let die.
Let the tyrant die.
A fish is caught by its mouth.
You need the earth
on your hands, not blood.
Take sanctuary at the farm.
My son doesn't need sanctuary.
He just needs
to reform his character,
for a man's character
is his destiny.
What book did you get that from?
Maybe you should read a couple.
Where do you stand, Fico?
Where do you stand?
Right here with my family.
I see that.
You're just a spectator.
You just watch the parade go by.
Let me tell you something, Fico.
Your days of hiding in this cork-lined
palace are numbered.
Pretty soon,
you and you and you
and you are gonna
have to make a decision.
Are you in the parade,
or are you not?
I have made my decision.
That means good night!
Good night in Cuban!
Buenas noches!
Buenas nochesto you all!
Good evening.
That depends.
It usually does, doesn't it?
It was a great show tonight.
Great show.
Do you know a guy named Peligro?
Who?
Peligro.
Is he a percussionist?
Would you know a guy
named Alberto Mora?
Is he a friend of yours?
Someone here to see you.
I had nowhere else to go.
Have you seen him?
All the time.
Next time you see him,
say good-bye.
When I get to the pearly gates,
you know what
I'm gonna ask for, don't you?
A bottle of Bacardi?
No, a case.
Don't forget the Victrola.
You're not going anywhere
without your dance partner.
Okay, I'll stay.
Viejo.
What is he saying?
Uh-oh, the ticking clock.
Fico.
Well, I wanted to say
that in our house,
Sunday dinner is not...
A moveable feast.
Uh-huh. All my sons
are welcome, but not...
Not after6.
And it is 6 and 3 minutes, Fico.
I know, but I thought
he said after6.
Okay. Okay. Now, um...
I want to make a wish.
If change is going
to come to our country,
I wish that our home
remains an island,
and that despite
all of our differences,
we always put family first.
And food second.
Salud.
It's a joke, my brother.
I'm just kidding.
So it's all in the family.
It's all in the family.
I tell you,
I swear to God it is.
Hello, Senator. How are you?
I've been better.
I come to see your father.
No one knows more
about constitutional law.
Am I interrupting?
I mean, he's picking
for compliments, Senator.
Okay, I'm gonna give you one.
Do you think the light
interrupts the day?
Sometimes.
We intend to pass
a resolution
that will remove Batista
through the constitutional
process.
Senator Cossio has asked me
to prepare a speech for him.
This is the opening statement.
Uh, I've made reference to Seneca.
Read it aloud, Senator,
so we can hear how it sounds.
Okay.
Please.
Mr. Speaker,
I must protest...
as Seneca did in ancient Rome,
of the violence of office.
Today, we, the citizens of Cuba,
are being persecuted by a tyrant
and his reign of terror,
meted out to our population
by his police,
and especially by a certain
colonel in the force
whose name has become
synonymous with sudden death.
Seneca was persecuted
by two tyrants,
Caligula and Nero.
In spite of that,
Seneca advocated the return
to the Republic...
unafraid.
Mr. Speaker, Seneca,
not the Neros of this world,
should be an example to us.
Fangio, I am your biggest fan.
Get in the car.
Just get in the car.
Get in.
What do you want? Money?
Publicity.
Fangio freed,
Grand Prix cancelled,
26th of July Movement responsible.
And listen to what Fangio said.
All they wanted from me
is that I help them
further their cause.
But I don't know anything
about causes, only cars.
And when they ask him
how he was treated,
They were quintessential
gentlemen.
Do you think I'm a quintessential
gentleman, Mercedes?
Huh?
What was so funny?
What were you laughing about?
The funnies.
The funnies?
That newspaper has no funnies.
Why don't you try the one
about the kidnappers
who only wanted publicity?
Stop it!
That's funny. That's funny.
Leave him alone! Stop!
Yeah. Come on.
Stop! Let him go!
Please stop!
Stop it! Stop it!
Stop it!
Huh?
You want to be tough? Huh?
Wanna play in my city?
Spoiled rich bastard!
You do not want
to disappoint me.
Believe me.
I'm gonna go for a walk.
When I get back,
I want you to tell
me who Peligro is.
I'm back.
Who's Peligro? Huh?
You're not a good listener.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Ooh. No, I'm okay, I'm okay.
I'm gonna go for a walk, okay?
So you better be thinking about
who Peligro is,
'cause you're next.
Let's go for some coffee.
You're here about your brother.
Your little brother's a criminal
a dangerous criminal.
No doubt about that.
I've got his file
if you wanna read it.
No, thank you.
I know my brother,
and no file will ever change that.
Fico, we've known each other
since we were in prep school.
I've always
been straight with you.
That's true.
Have you ever known me
to change my signals?
Not when you were my catcher.
Fico, you're pitching
for your brother now.
You're pitching wild.
He's guilty.
There's no doubt about that.
I know it and you know it.
He's my brother, Braulio.
I need your help.
Okay.
I think you should
get out of Havana,
go to New York or Miami,
and I'm gonna take
care of the tickets.
Fico, Fidel's gonna
take care of me.
I'm leaving for
the Sierra Maestra.
Hey.
Fico, I have no choice.
What about your family?
Everything I do
is for my family.
I love you.
Uh, come in.
Can I help you?
Al sent me.
Who?
Al.
He's a friend of yours, isn't he?
Are you auditioning?
Yes, I am.
What's your line?
I'm a comedian.
I'm a stand-up comedian
who prefers to remain seated.
That's it?
That's your line?
Yeah.
Some jokes for your emcee.
He writes his own jokes.
They're lousy. So are yours.
Touch?
You want some help writing
some of your other material?
Nobody writes anybody's
material around here.
You just improvise?
You can call it that.
Try New York.
Too cold. Too rich.
Too close to home.
Well, I'm afraid
you're going to have to
find another line of work, then.
I can't.
The laughter
you just become addicted to it.
What'd you say your name was?
I didn't.
I said Al sent me.
If you know Al, you know me.
Oh, Al's friend.
Where've you been?
Where haven't I been?
Federico, remember your
appointment.
And don't forget your dancing
shoes.
You're going to need them.
Oh, Rodney?
Maestro?
Oh, never mind.
I think I have
a job for you after all.
Finally, after all these years
of sacrifice and dedication,
a break.
Why can't you tell
me who we're meeting?
It's better that way.
I love surprises.
Just don't say a word
no matter what.
Sit there,
pretend you're my security. That's it.
How's this?
Cozy enough?
Look a little bit more dangerous.
How about this?
More dangerous.
This is my meanest.
Save that.
Can I make a wish?
Be my guest.
I wish for a tall, athletic,
caramel-colored beauty.
Okay.
An open-door policy
is the sign of a great host.
Mr. Lansky, come in.
Welcome.
Should I call you Federico,
Mr. Fellove, or Fico?
Depends on whether
you shake my hand or not.
Call me Fico.
You can call my Meyer.
All my friends do.
Have a seat.
Who is this guy?
Don't mind him,
he's just a comedian.
A blind one?
Mute.
That's funny.
Would you like a drink?
A little seltzer,
unless you happen to, uh...
have an egg cream.
I have eggs and I have cream.
And you have a blind comedian.
Mute.
An egg cream
is neither egg nor cream.
Would you like
to know how to make one?
Well, that would've
been my next question.
Well, let? S see
how this goes first.
A little seltzer for now.
Cuts the humidity.
You hear that, comedian?
You said something on the
phone about a business opportunity.
Well played. Le Chaim.
I propose
a partnership between us.
20% goes to the house,
the rest to me, my associates.
It doesn't have
to be anything big.
I mean, this is very cozy here.
You could have a couple of tables,
craps, you know, blackjack,
a wheel or two.
This is nice.
Mr. Lansky
Call him Meyer.
Or Mr. Lansky.
You want him here?
Meyer, I appreciate the offer,
but, regretfully, I have to pass.
Now, I know this is
a tremendous opportunity for me.
However, El Tropico
is a place of music,
and that's how
I would like it to stay.
Let me rephrase.
We have the beginning
of a mutually
beneficial relationship.
It would be a pity to see it end
before it even began.
Yes, it would.
All right.
I was informed
you were a reasonable man.
I hope I wasn't misinformed.
You weren't.
What I can offer you in return
is what I offer all my friends
an open-door policy.
Consider my club
your home any time.
What, free seltzer?
As much as you want.
You know, in my business,
Mr. Fellove,
we have friends
and we have enemies,
but we don't
have acquaintances.
I hope to hear
some good news very soon.
Is that Meyer Lansky...
Meyer Lansky?
The head of the mob.
I resign.
Are you wearing false eyelashes,
or are you truly bashful?
I never wear false eyelashes.
That's my girl.
Am I?
Whose idea was that?
Rodney's.
Are you gonna be watching?
Always.
What's the matter?
What's wrong?
Luis has another woman.
Another woman?
He hasn't come home in two days,
and before that, we haven't
His mind is elsewhere.
Has he called?
Just to say that he's okay,
and that's all he says.
Fico, help me.
You're the only one
I can turn to.
I'm gonna take care of it.
She's worried about you.
She came to you?
She's always had a...
very special place
in her heart for you.
And you for her.
What's the matter? Talk to me.
I'm not gonna get you involved.
I'm your brother. I'm involved.
What's up?
Is it another woman?
Yes.
Liberty.
You involved with Fidel?
No.
26th of July Movement,
like Ricardo?
No.
Directorio Revolucionario.
We're no longer associated.
We have our own ideas for Cuba.
Pluralism,
the restoration of
the 1940 Constitution.
You know, democracy.
That's what Fidel says he wants.
Sure, that's what he says,
but he can't be trusted.
You think he's a Communist?
A Fidelista.
You have to promise me something.
What?
Anything happens to me...
you'll look after Aurora.
She'll need you.
Here, promise me.
Promise me, Fico.
I need this from you.
I promise you.
But you're gonna promise me
that nothing's gonna
happen to you, right?
Right?
There's no happiness
outside the revolution.
Okay.
Don't do something stupid.
Okay?
Ricardo Fellove,
26th of July Movement.
Fellove.
Are you the dancer?
Because we don't need any dancers.
Okay, get off the horse.
We're hungry.
It's not another woman.
Then why won't he come back?
He doesn't want us involved.
What is it?
The revolution?
He doesn't want us involved.
That's it?
That's it.
Am I supposed to
take that home and be happy?
I'm his wife.
I have the right to be involved.
If something happens to him,
it happens to me.
To all of us.
And then what?
I think it was the Mafia, Meyer Lansky,
but I can't be certain.
Havana is no longer a capital city,
but a capital sin.
This is
not new, of course,
but even Jesus had
to whip the moneylenders
out of the temple.
We're badly in need of a
of a Christ with a whip.
I don't know what to do.
Satyagraha.
Do you know what that is?
No.
It is the Hindu word
For passive resistance.
Gandhi resisted passively,
and he won.
My son, in the sea,
even a shark can drown.
Okay, we all know how to make it
into the Presidential Palace
by heart now?
So let's review one last time.
I will take over the CNQ radio station
and read our statement.
Carbo?
Machado and I will attack with
Peligro through the main gates,
along with Menoyo and his group.
Ignacio, you will
provide sniper protection
and reinforcements.
Any questions?
What do you think, Peligro?
It's time.
Mockingbird Pet Shop.
Can I help you?
The bird is in the cage.
He's in.
Long live a free Cuba.
Mr. President?
What is it, Pizzi?
There are urgent matters
for you to attend to.
I've been signing
edicts all week,
and you know what
I've been thinking, Pizzi?
I'm a fortunate man
for having had to sign
one single death warrant.
Mr. President,
if I might say so myself,
you are a fortunate man,
but also a noble man.
Thank you, Pizzi.
That's very kind of you.
No, no, no, no, no.
It is not kindness.
It is historical justice.
Have I ever told you
how much I appreciate you?
No, sir.
Oh.
Sorry I'm late.
I got stuck in Pinelarillo
what do you want?
I got 450 napkins and tablecloths.
I'm gonna need help
getting it out of here.
I don't have any deliveries
on my list today.
This is the front gate, right?
Yeah, it's the front gate.
They told me 3:00 at the front gate.
Can you check?
Can you
All right.
Stay there.
Is any deliveries on the list today?
No.
Let's go! Let's go!
Go ahead, go in!
Here!
What's that noise?
Come with me! Now!
Let's go!
Fico! The palace is being attacked.
Listen. Manzanita's taken over
the radio station.
People of Cuba, the dictator
Fulgencio Batista
has just met revolutionary justice.
The gunfire that extinguished
the bloody life of the dictator
can still be heard around
the Presidential Palace.
It is we,
The Directorio Revolucionario,
the iron hand of
the Cuban Revolution
who have accomplished the final
blow
against this shameful regime
still twisting in its own agony.
Cubans who can hear me,
he has just been eliminated.
Long live a free Cuba!
Que vive una Cuba libre!
Carbo! Carbo!
Luis! Luis!
Luis!
Pizzi, leave us alone.
With friends or without friends?
As you like.
Pizzi.
Yes, sir?
People of Cuba,
today alien forces
made an attempt on my life.
As you can see,
the news of my demise
is vastly exaggerated.
The President now declares
business as usual in Havana.
I lend a helping hand to
those law-abiding citizens
and our loyal oppositions.
The future of Cuba is safe.
Abuelo!
Our children are safe.
That is all.
Salud.
Life is becoming
a dress rehearsal
for a show nobody'll see.
What's the word on Luis?
He's nowhere to be found.
Are you sure he's alive?
Positive.
He might be abroad.
I'm leaving.
I'm sorry.
There's no news.
Was he part of the attack?
Yes.
Why won't you tell me where he is?
Because I don't know where he is.
Fico, if something happens,
I want to be there...
for him.
So do I.
May I offer a serious thought
from someone who's never serious?
No.
Well, that was it.
Mmm.
It's good.
A man with a purpose.
A man with less of a purpose.
Fellove, come on.
Please join me.
Mmm. Mmm!
In our house,
Sunday dinner is not
a moveable feast.
It is at 6, as usual.
Sorry.
All my sons are welcome, but...
not a minute after6.
You must always chew.
It's good for your health.
You chew and you chew.
Mmm.
And then you chew some more.
See, I'm a man of...
good digestion.
In fact, if I wasn't
such a modest man,
I'd say I'm a man
of great digestion.
That's why I'm still alive.
About our little business...
our business?
Yeah, our business.
My business is El Tropico.
And I would love to continue
going to El Tropico.
So unless that's a prop
for one of your new shows...
I'm asking myself,
what is a song and dance man
because that's what you do, huh?
Just a little song and dance,
and you put on a little show
doing with a.32 caliber
Smith & Wesson?
What? Hey!
What?
What, are you planning
to shoot your piano player?
Do you have a new
cowboy routine
in El Tropico now,
or something?
Any word from Ricardo?
No.
Why were you late
for dinner tonight?
Hmm?
I have enemies.
Cono.
And I have the right
to protect myself.
Cono.
Fellove, am I your enemy?
You weren't my enemy until
you killed my brother.
Luis Fellove, alias Peligro.
Not angel,
not the Virgin Mary
Peligro!
I swear,
I did not kill your brother.
Your brother attacked
the Presidential Palace
with the intent to kill
my President.
He committed suicide.
Believe me, you do not want
to disappoint me.
Trust me on this.
I can see
all you have is thirst for revenge.
Ah, I see.
You know what a zugzwang is?
It's a chess move.
Mm-hmm.
It is a chess move
that is no move at all.
It is actually a position
the position in which each player
will obtain a worse result
if it were his time to move
than if it were not.
Do you follow?
A double-bind.
A reciprocal situation.
All you have to do
is act accordingly.
Which means...
Do not act at all.
Go.
Ho ho ho!
Hey, hey!
Bravissimo, Fellove!
Bravissimo!
A showman to the end!
One more audition.
So just about any
clothes fit you, huh?
She's very lonely.
Ever since she moved in,
she won't go out at all.
Not even with her friends.
The memory of your brother,
and the fact that she
has not been able
to have a family of her own...
I hate to see her so sad.
It breaks my heart.
Why don't you ask her out?
She would like that.
It would do her good.
She needs you, and you need her.
Fico, talk to me.
Please.
You know the last thing
Luis said to me before he died?
What?
He made me promise...
that if anything ever happened to
him,
I would take care of you.
You've grown up in Havana all your
life,
and I bet there's parts of the
city you don't know at all.
I'm sure you know them well.
You know...
Havana's very much like a rose.
It has petals, and it has thorns.
So it depends on how you grab it.
But in the end,
it always grabs you.
Why don't you come out
with me tomorrow?
It'll do you good.
You ever see Beny Mor? Live?
Mmm.
Ah!
Have you been to
the Tropical Beer Gardens?
Ah!
It's good to see you smile.
Thank you.
Why are their handkerchiefs?
The handkerchiefs
are so there's no evidence.
Of what?
Of the intimacy they're sharing.
Beny! Beny!
Beny! Beny! Beny!
Where is he?
He's always late.
Beny! Beny! Beny!
Beny! Beny!
He likes to make an entrance.
There he is.
How many more are in the barracks?
Come on. Come on.
Fellove!
Let's move. Don't waste
any time with that.
Let's move.
You seem troubled, Fellove.
Is it about the captain we shot?
Listen to me very carefully.
In an insurrection,
the end justifies the means.
What is an insurrection?
Huh?
Armed struggle.
What is the end?
Revolution.
Which entails social, economic,
and political transformations.
Like I said?
The end justifies the means.
Hmm?
This is Havana.
Who said a woman
is like a flower?
A poet with a sense of smell.
May I join you?
Yes.
What was your name again?
My name again is no name.
What do you mean?
I don't mean nothing!
Names don't mean, people do.
But you are people, aren't you?
That... nobody can deny.
So what's your name, then?
I have no name.
I already told you that.
Everybody has a name.
Mm-hmm.
Everybody but me.
Why not?
I don't know.
Ask him.
Leave me out of your puns.
You're the strangest man
I ever met.
Thank you.
Okay, Emilio.
Your moneys no good here.
Thank you, Emilio.
I'll see you at the club.
When I grow up,
I wanna be just like him.
Why?
Because...
he never pays.
we interrupt
this program with a special news report.
The University of Havana was
closed by the government today,
as a direct result
of the ongoing riots.
President Fulgencio Batista,
who is under intense pressure
to resign,
declared publicly today
that the government
will not tolerate the disgracing
of the sacred grounds
of the university's Plaza Cadena,
which he claims the professional
agitators were using
for their selfish acts of anarchy.
She wants to talk to you.
It's okay.
El tiempo no estacon ustedes.
What did she say?
Time is not on our side.