oh God,
God grant me the serenity
to accept the things
I cannot change
why did you fight it so hard, Earl?
courage to change the
things that I can...
come one!
you have been a good boy for a long time
you know you wanna do this
and the wisdom...
...wisdom to know the difference
Taking, as He did, This sinful world
as it is, Not as I would have it
Trusting that He will make all things
right, If I surrender to His will,
that I may be reasonably
happy in this life
And supremely happy with
Him forever and next.
Amen
I could go on and on
about what a great guy here he is
how he give us so freely
his time and his money
even how he, uh, beliving
how he cuts his toenails
let's get him here and speak for himself
ladies and gentlemen
I'll give you a business man,
philanthropist, a very dear friend
and the Portland Chambers Commerce
Man of the Year
Mr. Earl Brooks
thank you all
very much
uhm...
first thing i'd like
to say is that I, uh...
i don't even know how i cut my toenails
20... years ago
when I started the brook's box factory
i never dream that i will...
I never dream that one
day i'll be standing here
subsbusters. blogspot.
com proudly presents
did you.. did you just
see Sis Wallace's dress?
you can see her nipples
at that age!
wow, she cannot keep those things hidden
the only thing that would have
made this evening more perfect...
if is Jane had been here
Emma, she called to
congratulate me, right?
she has mid terms coming up
I think she's dropping out
let's see
nothing she does is
wrong with you, is it?
well...
she missed a good party
it's not like it's not set up
you already know I don't
like pesty and lambs
you know i don't pick the lox
no
you are the fucking man of the year
you deserve a treat
no, Marshall, I said no
I heard you...
but you don't mean no
what's wrong?
nothing
you are flauting
I'm thinking about what
I didn't say in the speech
oh...
honey
you were so... moving
you made us all laugh
i don't think anybody fold left down
they have their dance class tonight
you can just drive by...
...and look at them
there's not harming,
and just having a look
no, means no, Marshall
please...
put it, please
I though the food tonight was very good
but I was not crazy about the dessert
would you like to stop somewhere
and get something sweet?
Ok
norad is an adorable small dog
the labrador is supposed to be brave
Goltys, when he goes into
the trailer is very happy...
don't let me do this,
don't let me do this, please
I don't wanna start again
you promised to, you promised to
please... please
why did you figth it so hard, Earl?
I'm going to stay up a while
maybe going to the studio
or play with some glaciers
ok
I'm gonna read... and If I'm not
awake, wake me when you come back
anyway?
I though you were
wonderful tonight Mrs Brooks
thank you Mr. Brooks
oh, I love the road my
boy! I' have missed this...
we are going to have so much fun
this is the last time Marshall,
Understand me? It's the very last time!
don't you dare, going
on your business, shut up
I wanna see what they are doing
hello
what the fuck!
be quiet!
set up!
uh, Earl
what the fuck is this?
these fucking pigs like to
do with the curtains open
You should have know now this
is a big mistake for you, Earl
almost like a wanted
get caught on, Marshall
I don't fucking do that
I don't think either what a joy is to spend the
rest of your life on death row or a lethal injection
Yes, Sir
please, forgive me
you are fucked hard,
Earl. I don't give you that
don't even think about it
you know the rules
now upstairs, make love
with your beautiful wife
can we have the room, please?
thank you
there's just a thumbprint, right there
one his, one hers?
that was really nice
this guy has not been
acting for over 2 years
he always rearranges the bodies
but this is weird, I care of dare
usually he is much more romantic
arms around each other, kissing...
mouths open, tongues touching
bullets from straight of the victims
killer would covered this a lot
these were open or
closed when you got here?
closed
could it be the work of a copycat?
that's never been or viewed to the
public that the killer will treat his logs
Jesus, I was hoping
this guy was out or dead
or in jail or in some other charge
we checked all neighbourhood,
but so far nobody saw a thing
maybe he don't like this... he must to
be really angry at them for some reason
where do they keep their vacuum cleaner?
So I bet you 100 bucks, Hawkins,
there is not bag in this vacuum cleaner
I have not idea of what
the hell you are look for
he vacuums the house... and took the bag
what if he kills somebody that
did never get a vacuum cleaner?
he won't do that!
Our best hope is if someone
in there saw something
detective Tracy Atwood?
- Yes
- this is for you
you've been served
You, fucking asshole
- I am in the middle of a fucking murdering investigation
- Listen lady
- i'm just a messanger, here
- Hawkins,
what's the deal? I don't know it
get his ass out of here!
what it is?
assume to be, my ex husband
scumbag lawyer's trying to show me,
just how painful she can make my life
if i don't give them what they want
other any new members?
hello my name Voine
I am alcoholic, and I haven't
had a drink in 10 months
hi, my name is Earl, and...
I am an addict
anyone else?
you are...
such a fuck hypocrite
if you run and you step up there and say Hi,
I'm Ear and I've killed two people last night
I really got off on it but
I need your help, to be cured
I'm different Marshall, i
won't argue that with you
this it is the only place that as ever
helped me be normal, and i've been straight up
untill last night...
for the past 2 years
I not going to kill again
and I am not going to quit
coming here because it upsets you
we need a clean up crew
for afterwords, so..
we need some volunteers for the...
oh, thank you Earl, I appreciate that
there's time for requirements,
this is our first to tempt
"Mr. Brooks, your daughter is
waiting for you in your office"
Well I hope this is what
you have in mind, if not...
we would love to work with
you, further on the design
always find the challenge on machines
now if you uh, gentlemen, will you excuse me
i need to see how much this is going to cost me
understand
daughter cost money, me too
I believe you do understand
Uh, Matt Johnson, wants to schedule,
lauch for friday, contact him...
- Sunday, did...
- Can you hold this for a second?
did Jane call to say she was coming?
Uh, nobody gave me
that message Mr. Brooks
- she is...
- yeah, she is, and...
she has some boxes and suitcases downstairs
and she didn't have any money for the cab
and you paid for that
thank you
welcome
ah, hold my calls
sure
I told you
when it's appropriate
you let me know
Ehy, can I've some water?
hello gorgeous
what are you doing here?
I'm sorry daddy
please, don't be angry with me
I can guess what you've done
but why don't you tell
me then I'll decide
I've dropped out the school
oh Jane
ok
uh... have you told your mother?
no, I wanted to talk to you first
Well, you gonna have to
tell her, Jane All right?
I'm not gonna do that for you
why can't you...
sit!
and then,
together, the three of us, we decide
where it goes from here
Well, I tought a lot all about this?
college is a waste of time for me
All this...
All this... how somebody know that,
half way through their freshmen year?
you did even go to college
daddy and you are successful
I wanna come work for you
she is not telling you
everything, she is hiding something
hell no!
I am not hiring right now, sweetheart
ok, but just listen to me for one second
all right?
look! what happen to the business if, God
forbid, something wouldn't happen to you?
ok
mom would probably have
to sell the strangers
look, I willing to start from the bottom
you can treat me like a regular employee
I just wanna learn everything there is
to know about welling the box business
then, when the time comes...
i can stay in the family
all that's sweet, honey, but
you are not talking about business, you
are talking about emotions, now get up...
infact, Your mother and I, came...
this close to selling out last year
what?
that's right, and hadn't will
been offered a little more money
and still, may come back to us...
we would sell
what would you do without business?
yes?
I'm sorry. The man outside insisted
that I'll give this to you, he claims
that you'll find what's
inside, very interesting
what is he, Sunday? is he a salesman?
No, I've never seen him before
I'll just give him back
and I'll tell him to call
No, Sunday, Sunday, here...
Thank you
Jane
to give yourself a chance to...
uh, find out...
who you are
and what you wanna do
I'll talk to mom
but I not going back to school
and where would you live?
saved money, i'll look back home
but new rules, I wanna
be treated as adult
would you pay for rent?
would you pay for food?
no dad, you are a very welfy man
I think you can effort to keep me
Sunday, would you escort the
gentleman who gave you the envelop...
into the conference room and
tell him i would meet him there?
no problem, Mr Brooks
and, uh...
what happen to the BMW, Jane?
a friend is gonna drive it up
but he will be here week-end
and get Jane a cab
call your mother
are you gonna gimme a job?
if you were up to me and I think your
mother will agree with this, I, uh...
I think you should go back to school
you see that Marshall?
that's why I didn't wanna
do that damned couple
stop with fucking widing your own
you enjoyed doing that couple just as
as much I did and look at the right side
he cames to us, he didn't go to the cops
if he's trying to shake us
down, we kill him, period.
we make it fun but we'll kill him
end of the story
what can I do for you, Mister...
Let's say... Smith
Ok Mr. Smith
before you get the wrong impression, Mr
Brooks, I'm not here to shake you down
I hope this is the only copies of
these photos and you have no others
no
I have other copies and other photos
and if anything happens to me...
how did you find me Mr. Smith?
you are the man of the year, Mr. Brooks
your picture is in the paper
and if it had not been... I don't know,
I don't know what I would have done
lucky me
what is it that I can help you with?
I've been watching
that couple for months
yeah, they liked to make
love with the blinds opened
sometimes I would... take pictures
visual aids, for later
is a great way to get
off, I tell you that
was fun, I though
until I saw you killed them
and I have never
ever felt out that... rush!
like that, ever
I know you are the thumbprint killer
you have done this before
what I want?
it's for you, to take me with
you next time you kills someone
and I'd like that to be soon
and you were worried this
was going to be unpleasant?
the answer is simple
Just tell Mr. Smith that you
have decided never to kill again
and you're going away
you enjoy watching me suffer, don't you?
in a word, yes
where do you think he
has the other pictures?
he put it in a safety deposit box
but I bet the box is in the banks
where he keeps his checking account
and the key...
it's on his key chain
he really wants us to do this
he is not going to the cops
we have a deal?
for the angle of these pictures...
you live at the 3rd floor at apartment building
across the alley, front of the couple house
uh
yes or no, Mr. Smith?
yes
what time did you get home from work?
6.30
7, depending of the traffic
you can't never come here again
you can't never call me
do you understand that?
yes
tomorrow night
not tonight, tomorrow night at 8 o'clock
leave your apartment
building and walk east
I will pick you up there
if you are thinking
about doing anything...
for both to aware the rules, Mr. Smith
but I feel I must warn you
if it turns out that you enjoy killing
you can become very addicted
it can ruins your life
I wanna do this
have I covered everything?
I can't think of anything else
then I'll see you
tomorrow night Mr. Smith
we've talked to our client and in common we put here
what we figure out, we feel this is more than fair
we can have a check for that
amount in your office by 6pm o'clock
oh, we told you at the
beginning what we wanted
and it hasn't changed
we feel our offer is more than generous
I paid for everything,
when we were together
and now I'm been asked
to give this guy a bonus?
for spending time with me, time that
I've already paid for in the first place?
you know as well as I do, counselor,
you're not gonna get a million five
oh, I - don't -
know that, no, I...
well, infact, this is the
front page of yesterday's paper
"Hangman escapes"
after torturing his victims
Thorton Meeks
well, hide him in public places,
church steeple, balconies,
freeways over passes...
where this is going?
Well, your client captures Mr. Meeks
Come on Tracy, this is
not a lot of money for you
and we both know how afraid that I was after Meeks
says that he was gonna escape and come back to kill you
let me ask again
what is your point?
Our point is that Meeks,
or someone like Meeks
make hurt after my client
in order to hurt your client
that is very imaginative, counsellor
but it's not based in reality at all
Jesse
let's just handle this, please
- Tracy
- Jesse
you know what will make me
feel really safe right now?
if you got hit by a truck...
and die
well, that's it?
Mr. Vialo and I, are leaving
you are threatening the safety of my client,
we are going after to get a straight order
we see in court
you hit by a truck and die?
fuck it, I felt good
what was here it's not
here, that's interesting
I hate the number, I'll say that
this people been killed by a ghost
the autopsy said there was a little tiny
piece of plastic in the female victim's brain
it's a dead end, the bag with the gun, he puts one
gallon plastic foresinc bag over his hand to his wrist
little bit of plastic comes out, when the
first one is gonna shots, it goes in the bag
are you looking for me?
I've received the subpena from
your husband for your works records
where you worked, date and
time, for the past two years
he just tries to blackmail me, do you remember?
my lawyers assure me that I'll never go to court
I can't take that chance
almost three courts of
your cases is a current
so, until you'll set your divorce
i'm gonna have to put you on the desk
that's also blackmail
do you have any idea what
this guy has done to me?
while we're married, while
i was paying for everything
he was just out and fuck every
woman he can gets his hands on
he fucked my friends,
he fucked my cousin
he made me look as an idiot
- and?
- and what?
get over it!
you can't roll there's a woman wanna
have this one blousy man in your life
well, I made him an offer and I
won't goin to give him a dime more
did you hear that Meeks escaped?
yeah
you get gonna looking for him,
you want me yo put a detail on you?
I think I can take care of myself
it's one of your biggest problem,
Tracy you don't know how to ask for help
what the fuck, what the fuck, what...
don't worry, if I were here to
kill you, you were already be dead
after you left today, I realize that our
friendship was a little one side of it
so, tomorrow night when we meet,
would you be so kind us to bring
all the pictures and the
memory card from your camera
that way we can like each
other simply for who we are
if you don't show up
I will presume that you have gone
to the police and I will kill you
even if I'll go to jail because of you Mr
Smith, someone will find you, wherever you are...
and they will kill you
Mr. Brooks
WoW
it's nice to have you home
hello, hello. You have to explain this
to me 'cause i'm your mother, that's why!
what's wrong, girls?
I asked your daughter what's the
real reason she dropped out the school
I told you, it's not the real reason
honey...
you wanted to go to college
you have good grades, your father put
in favours to get you in that school
if this is not the reason...
please, Dear God, tell me the reason
what is your mother thinking
even dropped you out the school?
I'm pregnant
but that's not the reason I dropped out
being pregnant wouldn't keep me
for going to school if I wanted to
who is the father?
some guy a was seeing
some, some guy, does he knows?
what he knows Dad?
he is married, he got two kids,
I want nothing to do with me
oh, honey
I'm not gonna go throw with it
there is nothing to be upset about
I mean, I was even
not gonna tell you guys
then would be
no abortion, jane
no Dad, you're not gonna
tell me what to do, ok?
it's my body and I'll
do what I want with it
I'm sorry, you're right. i said it wrong
I wasn't trying to tell
you what to do when I was...
what I was trying to say is that...
a grandchild would be a wonderful gift
for your mother and me
would you really wanna have a
grandchild? even if I'm not married?
yes
a child is what's important
we would... we would love him and
cheer him completely and we would...
we would help you raise him
if it means that much to
you, I will think about it
I'm gonna have to start getting
up little earlier, uh, honey?
well, we were right
she was hiding something
pregnancy is not of all of it,
she's hiding something bigger
something much bigger
you think so?
I know so
and so do you
it's darker tonight
than it was on your night
but still...
how did you managed to not
bumping into the furniture?
was the light on?
or did you turn it on?
because I know you and you
won't risk a shot in the dark
where have you been?
did you miss the thrill of killing?
what if these are stayed closed
because you yanked them closed
which would mean...
they were open...
...when you came into the room
thank you, I appreciate your time
ops, sorry, i'm sorry
no, I'm sorry
I was just about to knock
I'm detective Atwood, portland police
hey, do you wanna see me?
fine
you are a photographer
Mr... Bafford?
- No
- No?
thank you
no,
uh, actually it's...
a hobby i just started
well, do you know, there was a murder?
yes, in the house, close the way
You didn't happen to see something
unusual or suspicious that night, did you?
no, I wondered that
when it happened, but
no
I'm sorry, i'm supposed
to be meeting somebody
and I don't want to be late
uh, well, here is my card
if you did hear something
or remember anything
uh, i wish I could be
more helped, but,uh,sorry!
he looks clean
looks like he's alone
no,i tell you, he
really wants to do that
maybe I should plow
with him... pick him up
no, just honk
maybe he get killed crossing the street
and save us the mess he's doing up
almost
it's coming down hard
they said would be sunny tomorrow
I never trust those guys
they say it's gonna be clear, then rains
and they say it's gonna
rains and it's... sunny
I believe this is what you asked for
the pictures in the memory card...
all here
both
you and I both know that not
all the pictures are in here
and you made a copy of the
memory card, as an asshole
but, you understand my position?
yes, I do
but it's my hope you want to get to know me
better you feel confortable in giving me everything
that I've asked you for
sounds fair
maybe you'll be interested in this
this is the police woman,
who is looking for you
wow, we never know anyone
was looking for us before
you have to find everything
there is to know about this...
woman
this is close, Marshall
this is to damn close
so...
what's the plan?
where do we, uh, what
are we doing here tonight?
we'll drive around until we
see someone we think we might
enjoy killing
really?
you don't have have somebody... in mind?
I don't enjoy this Mr. Smith, I do it
because I am addicted to it
before you're in in my life I
had that I would never kill again
so, this is... your part
you can choose anyone you
want and we will do it together
can i pick somebody that I know?
no
you'll never kill someone you know
it's the easiest way to get caught
- ok?
- yeah
locked up?
you look a little bit like that...
E.T. guy
remember that movie? when
he flies on that bike?
- yeah, yeah
- yeah
I like that movie
Jesus Christ
fuck him
this is fault, he is an asshole
fuck you
maybe Mr Smith would like to kill
the driver of the pick up
what about the driver of the pick up?
what if we kill him?
yes
yes, I always wanted to fucking kill
somebody fucking to be in traffic
well, if you want to
kill the driver of pick up
I'll give you the honor
ehy, maybe not be the same
driver
ok
well, driver I am, to will give
a good looking at him or her
any problem to kill a woman?
no, no. an asshole is an asshole
I wasn't in town that night
my roommate was, maybe he saw something
Uh, may I speak to him?
he is in on his way to Tokyo right
now, he is also a flight attendant
did the victims ever leave
their bedroom curtains open?
all the time
I don't know if we can see them doing it and
that's why you are asking but they didn't care
well, here is my card
if you can have your roommate call me
and people of this number know how to
reach me at everytime, day and night
I won't be here, but
I will leave him a note
ok great, thank you
sure
would recognize him if you saw
his driving licence picture?
yeah
I'll memorize the licence
number, you write it down
I got it
wow
well, when you get
home, go on the Internet
find everything you
can... about this guy
we are gonna kill him tonight?
no
we could, but then we
won't be under control
we can leave lose ends but we
both know the danger of that
ok, I will do
what are... we... doing?
what are you doing?
look at me!
- look at me!
- why?
- close your eyes
close
what's the licence plate number?
shit
P4...
no
2, uh
I know I tore, then
because of the tree?
don't feel bad
I've been doing this a
long time. pen and paper
look out the window and write it down
how is your first time like?
you really don't wanna know
that much about me, Mr. Smith
no, I don't think it was right, go back
ok, we are in
for all the taxes we pay you think
they'll make it more difficult
to hack into the police personnel file
the father is John Atwood, why...
why does that ring a bell?
somebody you got business with?
someone we...
killed
no, no somebody we killed
let me see here, MBA
and married, she has
been a cop for 12 years
married Dr. Carlson
divorced Dr. Carlson
married at Jesse Vialo
and so two are separated,
from Jesse Vialo sue
...for support by Jesse Vialo seems
uhm, seem a shrimp
because of Jesse Vialo
who, who, who
she has caught a lot of people
and look here, this is not her first
time she has been looking for us
ok, here we are
Jesse Vialo, good looking,
a little younger than she is
younger, rest of all to her
she married him in a
rebound from the doctor
and the boy has married her
for money and connections
just because the old men
that doesn't mean she is rich
maybe is one of the kind of guys
ready to give her to the oprah
and than to his kids
what does she have to declare?
any outside and coming holdings?
oh, you are a...
you are a genius
the oprah didn't get much
why would a woman, worth
60 plus million dollars...
and probably more to come...
wanna be a cop?
I like that about her
you are a such a fucking snob, Earl
you like her because she is rich
no, i like her because she
founds something that's hers,
is not the family business,
and she is good at it
I'd like Jane to find
something it's... hers
and than she can be good at it
That's exactly why I would
scare the shit out of me
she's a cop who doesn't
need the money...
and she is looking for us.
that's one fucking dangerous human being
the fact you are not wrong
just not making me me admire her
any less
hey Nancy!
hi Tracy,
thank you for meeting me here
I got your latte
you wanna be walk and talk
while I hear your big idea?
oh, sure
you really wanna settle this?
If I can
I'd like to use your father
no
my father does nothing for nothing
Tracy, I understand but your
father has a lot of political massed
his poll won't make everything go away
but it would be a tremendous help
absolutely not
you're right
we could have done this one on the phone
if you will wanna play the game
right on the desk for a year
- i'm sure we can settle it
at 1,25- 1,5... - uff, I...
I'm not sit on a desk
an the only other option is your father
or money
1,5 and that's it
ok
I'll call them today
I just need to get this
done as soon as possible
that's what Jesse is counting on
I'll call you when I have something
oh, Tracy
your husband said there's a picture of him
holding some trophy, that you still have?
what picture? he has everything
he claims it's his favourite picture
and you put it up when
you store your suitcases
I'll look
I Know?
petty, you are going to divorce
thanks for the latte
I told you I was coming back to get you
how do you find the place
where i'm gonna hang you?
first
I'm gonna watch her
have some fun with you
then she is gonna watch
me, have some fun with you
you know...
don't fucking move!
shoot me!
come on, shoot me, motherfucker