I am General Wilkins,
and this is the
McArthur Outreach Survival Camp.
If any of you gentlemen
are in the habit of running,
well, good luck.
There are no fences here,
no barbed wire,
only 70 miles of rugged desert
in all directions.
Perfect, don't you think?
I think there has been a mistake.
Um... I am supposed to be
at the First Baptist Bible Camp.
No, no, son.
There is no mistake.
You're in the right place,
and I am your personal savior.
Gentlemen, you get caught
outside the perimeter,
you earn a day in the pipe.
Steal water,
Be late for a meal,
you get the pipe.
Next time you come up,
don't forget the eggs.
You use a four-letter word,
you're gonna get one long day
in the pipe.
Stone, what is the current
temperature in the pipe?
One hundred and forty degrees, sir.
One hundred and forty.
Any questions?
Wouldn't that be considered
cruel and unusual punishment?
Cruel... maybe.
Unusual... yeah.
Yeah, absolutely!
I say you're breaking the law.
Let's get one thing straight,
gentlemen.
I AM THE LAW!
Now, do we have any more
stupid questions?
You'll find your uniforms
at your assigned bunks.
Put them on!
Keep them on!
DISMISSED!
MOVE IT!
Go! Go!
Kinda cruel, huh?
What, what, what was that?
The guard said he sleeps in his truck
just on the other side of that hill.
Let's go.
What a dream.
This thing is a piece of crap!
Just take it easy with it, okay?
Man, this thing better not die on us.
# They say I gotta
a learn a lesson today #
# Yeah! #
# Hey, hey, hey! #
# They say I need
a good punch in the face #
# Yeah! #
# Hey, hey, hey! #
# They say
I started something up #
# I got mad at you #
# And I revved you up #
# But yeah, hey, hey ##
Yes?
Senator Boxwell?
Speaking.
General Wilkins.
It is about your son, Justin.
He's AWOL.
Where are we, man?
I am looking...
I'm looking.
Seventy miles into the Mojave Desert
and you lose him?
What would you like us
to do, Senator?
Talk to me!
Turn right onto Highway 6.
Are you sure?
National Geographic thinks so!
Are we tracking them yet?
Satellites are coming in.
You think they're back there?
If they are not, they will be.
Senator, I need an answer.
Find him, quietly.
You understand me?
Yes sir,
I'll uh, see to this personally.
You have my word.
Where is Highway 6?
Apparently the map
is older than the truck.
I don't get it.
According to this
they are right behind us.
Where did you place
the tracking devices?
Inside their hats, sir.
So much for technology, Stone!
Idiot!
It's gotta be the same road.
Go right.
We went right last time.
Elder Johnson and Elder Talbot,
this is President Andrews.
Your new assignment is to serve
in the town of New Harmony.
It's been two years
since the last missionaries
were transferred out...
This tape will self-destruct
in six seconds...
...so, you will need to be
on your best behavior.
That is funny!
Remember the mission...
And of course,
should you be captured
and tortured
by squirrel monkeys,
this office will deny
this mission ever existed.
Bishop Hollister has already...
Squirrel monkeys?
Yeah, squirrel monkeys.
...so, you'll be teaching...
They exist!
I've seen pictures.
You'll be doing a great work
in this town, Elders.
I look forward to hearing from you
after you have gotten settled.
- What was that?
- Are you crazy?
God speed, Elders.
There was a squirrel monkey
in the road.
It is a good thing
my cat-like reflexes
and quick instincts kicked in.
Elder, we have been
together long enough
for me to know that there
is nothing quick about you.
Hey Elder, I was kidding!
Want to see what blessings
have been bestowed?
Oh, absolutely!
Hooo, haha, haah!
Oooho! Yeah!
Oooho!
Yeah!
Wow!
Man, you've got
one amazing girlfriend.
It's from my sister.
Oh.
Is she writing anyone?
She's 12.
Well, when I'm 28.
Let it go, Elder!
Ha haa.
Catholic!
Disgusting!
Gluttony's a sin, Elder!
I will just assume you are
warming that one up for later.
Ha ha ha.
Which way are we going, General?
That's just great!
The carburetor
is completely clogged.
We got $300 dollars, okay?
That's good enough
for two bus tickets.
Do you see a bus station
around here?
We are in the middle
of the Mojave Desert.
So can't you fix it?
If I had a set of tools
and ten gallons
of carburetor cleaner.
I am just trying to help.
I'm just trying to think of a plan.
I just need to relax.
We're dead.
We're dead?
Why you gotta be so negative
all the time?
Open your eyes, T!
We are in the middle
of a very big desert.
You know what?
Our luck could change, man.
All right?
You know how I feel
about swearing, T?
Luck is a four-letter word,
and I'd prefer
you stop using it!
That's what I'm talkin' about,
all that negativity, man!
You need to chill out!
You sound more like
the General every day.
# Till we meet,
till we meet #
It's still a four-letter word.
# God, be with you
till we meet again ##
Be cool.
Hey, guys.
What's wrong with your friend?
Twinkies and this heat.
Bad combination.
What are you guys, salesmen?
Um, not exactly.
We're missionaries
for the Church of Jesus Christ
of Latter-day Saints,
you know, the Mormons?
I thought you guys rode bikes.
Do you know the purpose of life?
Do you?
Actually, yes, it's...
How old are you, Elder Johnson?
Nineteen.
You look 14.
Well, I, I'm not.
Elders have to be 19,
and sisters have to be 21
before we come out.
Come out?
To spread
the gospel of repentance,
and to brings souls to Christ.
- Look, Johnson...
- Elder Johnson.
Whatever.
Don't waste your time
on guys like us.
We are not good candidates
for the priesthood.
Oh, but you're wrong.
I mean, all you have to do
is open your hearts
and listen to the spirit.
I think one of those spirits
has got your friend.
If you have any questions,
uh, just call that number.
We'll send you a free video.
You can call
when you get to a phone,
and watch it
when you get to a VCR.
Elder, are you all right?
No, I am not all right.
Give me something, man!
Not another word, Elder.
Come on.
Shirt... pants... shoes...
Toothbrush?
Don't touch that thing.
You don't know where
that thing has been.
These guys must live
in their car, man!
What else is in there?
"Today was the most special
day of my life.
My mom cried when she
dropped me off at the MTC."
The MTC?
Oh, that must be
the Mormon Tabernacle Choir.
I'll betcha those guys
can really sing.
Hold on a minute, okay?
Ha ha!
Grrr! Grrr! Grrr!
Why'd you do that?
This isn't a time
to be playing around.
- Okay, be serious.
- I am serious.
Oh, yeah?
Well, what's the plan, huh?
Isn't it obvious?
The General is lookin'
for you and me right now.
Right?
But, nobody's looking
for two missionaries.
No.
Ha ha... yes!
Officer.
It took you guys
awhile to pull over.
Is something wrong
with the car?
Yes, as a matter of fact.
Elder Talbot, here,
fell on the shifter,
and it stuck in neutral.
I've been expecting you two
for quite some time.
Look officer,
we don't want any trouble.
Yeah.
Okay.
Hello, it's me.
I've got 'em.
Absolutely.
No problem.
All right, Elders, come with me.
I'll give you a ride into town.
Are you taking us into custody?
Yeah, right.
Good one, Elders.
Come on!
Maybe they just needed the car,
and they wanted to pay for it.
Maybe in their hurry
of stealing the car,
they forgot it.
Well, what are we going to do?
I am gettin' hungry.
Consider it manna from heaven.
I'd rather die!
Well, that is
a distinct possibility.
We'd better get going.
I, uh, I think we should
just stay right here.
Elder, we haven't seen
a single car all day.
That's because
it's been really hot, Elder.
Maybe the cool air
will bring the people out.
Oh!
Hey, everybody!
It's nice and cool now!
COME ON OUT!
I'm going.
I'm staying.
If you're staying here,
you're staying here all alone.
- Fine.
- Bye.
Look on the bright side, Elders.
Some people never get to ride
in a patrol car.
Some of us consider
it home, 'cuz I know I do.
Uh, what's that Elder?
Nothing, officer.
He is just, he's just a little tired.
Don't worry about the car.
We'll make sure it gets
to the repair shop.
You should have it soon.
Thank you, officer.
What's the plan now, smart guy?
Welcome to New Harmony, Elders.
Thank you, sir.
I am Bishop Hollister.
Hi. I am Elder Talbot, sir.
Yeah.
And, you must be Elder Johnson.
Yes, sir, I'm Elder Johnson.
I haven't heard so many sirs
since I was in the army.
Sorry... sir.
Where's your car?
It broke down.
That cop said he would
get it to us soon.
Ah, well, Brother Sorensen
is a good man.
How, uh, how are you fixed
for funds?
Elder Talbot
misplaced our stash.
Yeah, collection...
our congregational collection.
Uh, I'll tell you what.
Why don't you go inside
the diner, show 'em your badges,
and they'll, uh,
they'll put it on my tab.
In the meantime,
I'll put your bags in the truck.
Go on in.
He seems like a nice guy.
Have you ever met a mean Mormon?
# You said the other night #
# That we were through #
# But you keep coming over
like our love is new ##
Hello?
Anyone here?
I'll be right with you,
just take a seat.
You see that?
Lady Luck staring us
right in the face.
Gee, there must be a whole
nine bucks in there.
I hope that guy hurries.
I'm starvin'.
Sorry. We're back there
chopping up onions.
The real waitress will be with you
as soon as she can compose herself.
So, what'll it be?
Uh, a double cheeseburger,
and you can hold the onions.
Oh... well, thank you, brother!
Ha ha!
What are you two, salesmen?
No, man.
We're missionaries.
Read the nametag.
I'll be glad to read your nametag.
Elder "Talbot."
Hmmm... okay, ha ha.
So, let's move on.
Uh, can I get a, uh, club sandwich?
CLUB SANDWICH!
And a couple of Cokes.
AND A COUPLE OF COKES!
Fountain's down.
Fountain's down-- so water
is just going to have to do
for you fellas.
Okay.
Well, all right!
Hello, Sarah.
Oh, hey, Bishop.
Sorry to barge in so late.
I see you've met the missionaries.
Oh, I didn't know
they were the missionaries.
Well, come around and say, "Hi."
Elders, this is Sarah Covington.
She owns the diner.
Didn't you guys order Cokes?
Yeah, he said
that the fountain was down.
Mormons don't drink Coke.
Now, Sarah, you know
that's not altogether true.
Missionaries, on the other hand...
Elder Johnson, you're gonna
have to shake that Coke habit.
It's starting to create problems.
Gee, thanks, Elder Talbot.
Is there anything else
that I am not supposed drink?
Well, besides the Coca-Cola
products,
we Mormons don't drink coffee,
or beer, and uh,
we definitely don't smoke,
and no poker on Fridays.
Just follow the Word of Wisdom,
and you'll be fine, Elders.
That's right, wise words of wisdom.
Welcome to New Harmony, Elders.
- You boys ever been to Australia?
- No.
Don't go there.
They're mean as hell there.
My grandson, my great-grandson,
got shot at five times.
I thought they liked Americans.
They'd as soon shoot
a Mormon as listen to one.
Ahh, Sister Cutbank,
I'm sure there are a lot
of great people there.
Otherwise the Lord never would
have sent Timmy down there.
Ahhh, horse sh...
Apples?
Timmy is a pain in the butt,
and he deserves a little
hot lead in that same area.
Let's get in before we get drenched.
Well, Elders, this is it.
A place to sleep, a place to wash up.
Uh, this is very nice, Sister Cutbank.
Well, if you need anything
come by the main house.
And, oh... look out for Rusty.
Rusty?
The goat.
You have a pet goat?
I do for now.
It's more of a darn pain
than Timmy was.
Shall we pray?
That's a wonderful idea.
Elders?
Elder Talbot, I think that a prayer
would be very appropriate.
Oooh, uh, Bishop?
Would you like
to lead us this evening?
I'd be honored.
Dear Heavenly Father,
we are grateful
for our new elders' arrival
this day in safety...
Yes, truly grateful, Lord.
We hope this place will be
a sanctuary for them,
free from the powers of evil...
A sanctuary, Lord, no evil.
In the name of Jesus Christ, Amen.
Amen, ah, ha ha!
Man. Whew.
That's the way it outta be.
You seem to be very excited
about the work.
Uh, yeah, it's my Baptist
upbringing, sir.
Well, you boys
better get some sleep.
No rest for the righteous, son.
You've got a big day tomorrow.
What do you mean?
Uh, he means we better go to bed,
'cuz we gotta preach
come sun up.
Of course.
Bingo!
Uh, well, thank you so much,
Sister Cutbank,
for lettin' us stay.
Oh sure.
Now, don't be surprised
in the morning
if you hear Old Blossom choking.
She's just clearing her pipes.
I love this whole farm thing.
It's cool.
See you first thing.
I'd rather not.
Uh, bears or bunnies?
Bunnies.
Bears.
Yeah.
About time you got out here.
Don't start with me, Daren.
I'm tired, and how many times
have I told you to stay off my hood?
Hey, I stay out here all night
to make sure you make it out
to your car safely.
This is all I get?
Thanks, I'm safe.
Now get off.
Oh, who peed in your coffee?
Or, should I say, "Hot chocolate?"
Shut up.
No coffee?
No tea?
How about a little me?
We're not
boyfriend-girlfriend anymore.
Do I need to staple
a reminder to your forehead?
You used to be
remotely interesting
before you got all religious.
You are a mistake for any girl,
religious or not.
You know, I saw your two new
missionary dorks in there.
You are so observant.
I been thinking about
throwing a little welcoming party.
Don't.
Too late, sweet thing.
Already in the works.
I'll send you an invitation.
You're a jerk.
Fifteen, 16, 17, 18-- 18 bucks.
Gimme the two fives.
Gimme the two fives!
Look man, don't screw this up.
You got us covered, right?
Yes.
What do you think?
What do you think, huh?
Whew, you look like one sad cowboy.
I don't know why you waste
your time on her.
You see anybody else around here
that merits wasting time on?
You gotta be 21 to come in here.
Thanks for the reminder.
What'll it be?
I'll get a beer in the bottle?
I hate this game.
You next?
Um... sure.
What'll it be... 8 ball, 9 ball?
Uh, well, the only one I know
is Solids 'N Stripes.
We call that "Eight Ball."
You wanna light the break?
Light what?
I'll break.
I haven't seen you
around here before.
I haven't been around here before.
You be glad.
Just passin' through, huh?
Like a bad burrito.
Your turn, cowboy.
Name's Justin.
I'm Daren.
This is David.
You guys brothers?
Yeah, we got three more monkeys
just like him back home.
Must be somethin' in the water, huh?
Wait.
What?
Take the straight on the 12--
you'll be set up for the 10?
I think I like this one right here.
Oh, I didn't even see that.
Rack 'em.
What's that?
I lost.
In fact, you did.
But, I'll tell you what.
This one is on me,
but next one's $10.
You break it.
But, I just lost.
Well, let's just call it a little
New Harmony hospitality.
Well, you hit from there,
you're gonna scratch.
Shut up!
Is that good?
Huh?
Fifty-five, 60, 62 dollars!
They musta been pissed!
And... I got these!
Ooooh, okay.
Inside rear bumper.
Good work.
What are we waiting for?
Well, isn't it a little hot right now?
Those missionaries
are going to be here soon.
We gotta get outta here.
It's a long walk across the desert.
Maybe they got picked up
an' called the cops?
Hey, maybe.
For all they know, we went to Mexico.
The last place they'll look at
is New Harmony.
Yeah. Maybe.
Besides, dude, $62 won't get us far.
Yeah.
Ahhh.
Check this out.
Did you know that missionaries
aren't allowed to date?
Wow, that's a shocker.
Absolutely no contact
with members of the opposite sex.
Neat.
Turn out the lights.
One of us has to read mission rules
in this companionship,
so you need to relax.
Flirting or dating is not tolerated.
You are not to telephone, write to,
or accept calls or letters
from anyone of the opposite sex
living within
or near mission boundaries.
You check that out;
that's serious.
We're, uh, Senator, we're 140 miles
from the nearest town.
Yes, sir. I told you
I would personally find them,
and I will, Senator.
Good night, sir.
We didn't get very far.
It would have been nice for one of us
to remember water before taking off.
Well, the coffee can was a good idea.
We'll see ya in the morning.
Why'd you come on a mission,
Elder Johnson?
Prospects for marriage
are far greater
for returned missionaries,
and it was the right thing to do.
What about you?
Girlfriend.
Wow, she must be pretty special.
Ooooh yeah, real special.
She was fetchin' engaged
six weeks after I left...
Bummer!
to my brother.
Sorry. That hurts!
That hurts even worse!
It was like, my parents,
they were so excited about it.
They were?
How could they be?
Well, my brother is like 42.
They thought it'd get him
to move out.
He still lived at home?
Well, we shared a room.
C'mon baby... you can do it,
honey, ol' Blossom.
Rise and shine, Elders,
takin' the active runway.
Come on!
Weeeee! Ah ha ha hahaa!
Whew!
ORDER UP!
French toast, two short stacks,
over easy.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
How you holdin' up?
Oh, I'm as good as gold, darlin'.
Sorry it took so long, Elders.
There you go.
Anything else?
Uh, yeah, coffee, black.
Very funny.
This place is like a cash cow.
Are you always this busy?
Yes, and it usually runs
a little smoother.
You can smell the money
over the grease.
Then you should hire more help.
My mom handled crowds
for 20 years
without missing an order.
People waiting on their food.
Get a goin' now.
I better go.
Can't upset the cook!
Wow!
She looks a lot different.
You are so clueless, man.
What?
What did I do?
It's what you didn't do, man.
When a girl gives you an
opening that big, you take it!
What?
When?
Like the whole mom thing.
You shoulda been like,
"Your mom must be pretty special.
When can I meet her?"
That's not somethin' I'd ever say.
Oh, and what would you say, Romeo?
I'd ask her why her mom
wasn't here helpin' out?
Wrong.
What if she's sick
with some terrible disease?
Then she'd tell me she is sick
with some terrible disease.
Yeah, and then you say,
"I'm so sorry."
And then she'd know
how sensitive I am.
Then she'll start crying,
rushing to the back room.
Nice job, Johnson.
Why are we having this conversation?
We can't date!
OJ?
Is that a Coca-Cola product?
It's Minute Maid.
I'm tryin' to help Elder Johnson
keep his words of wisdom,
and I'm afraid it is.
What?
We'll have to pass.
Thank you!
Where're you from, Elder?
Uh, I'm uh, I'm from the South.
Oh yeah?
What part of the South?
California.
I grew up in the South,
and we never heard about California
bein' part of it.
Well, there's two parts
to California...
one is the North,
and one is the South.
And I'm from the South.
Should I be takin' notes, Romeo?
Our ride's here.
Those are the clowns
I hustled at the pool hall.
Can we please have it to go,
please?
Yeah, we were supposed to meet
the pastor ten minutes ago.
Here you go.
Sorry you're late.
Elders, wait.
Come on, I'll give you a ride
to Bishop Hollister's place.
No, that's okay, we can walk.
Don't be ridiculous.
It'll take you two hours
to get there walking.
Get in.
Is that guy a friend of yours?
What guy?
Daren?
How did you know his name?
I, uh, overheard the waitress.
Oh, so he's your boyfriend.
Daren Burnett is the biggest jerk
in three counties.
We grew up together.
He wouldn't stop asking me out,
so I went out with him.
He is unstable,
and I learned
I wanted more out of life
than football and beer parties.
So, that's where you found Jesus?
You know, you guys aren't like
typical missionaries.
You think this has traces
of coffee in it?
Even if there is,
the ox is in the mire,
wouldn't you say?
Oh yeah, sure.
I once I pretended to be sick
on Super Bowl Sunday
so my mom would take me
to the doctor's
so I could watch the game
in the waiting room.
She said,
"The ox was in the mire."
I still feel really bad about that.
That story makes no sense, Elder.
But I know what you mean.
I waited at your place
for more than an hour.
I am sorry, Bishop.
We completely lost track of time.
Where you been?
It was my fault, sir.
I was, I wanted to stop
at the diner.
I am sure Sarah is thankful
for the business,
but Sister Cooley
needed a blessing.
She is having a baby next week,
and she's not doing well.
It won't happen again, sir.
Elders, good missionaries
have dedication and commitment.
And this town needs
good missionaries.
Well, what would you like
us to do, Bishop?
Why don't you go back to town;
do some tracting?
Go where the spirit leads you, Elders.
Uh, right, that good ol'
spirit leadin' the way!
Say, Sarah, can we catch
a ride back to, uh, town.
Yeah.
Wrong spirit, Elder.
It is no big deal, Bishop.
I don't mind.
Elder Talbot, what is the rule
on riding in cars
with single sisters?
Are you talking
about attractive sisters
or unattractive sisters, Bishop?
We are not allowed to ride
in cars with single sisters.
I am sorry, Bishop,
I guess I didn't think about it.
It doesn't look too good
when two missionaries
are riding around
with a very attractive sister.
You guys know the way back?
We'll be fine.
All right, never enter a home
of a single sister.
When the father
is away from the home...
Man, tell me what we can do.
This place is worse than the camp.
Well at least we could drink a Coke,
or have a cup of Joe
and ride in cars with girls.
There were no girls
at our school.
Back up, back up, back up!
Back up!
Back up, back up!
Aaaaahhhh!
Okay. Okay.
All right.
Enough. Enough.
Six miles in under two hours.
Not bad.
Throwing lemons too.
You know, you can learn a lot
about a town
just by walkin' its roads.
Yeah, we saw lots of lemons.
Ha ha.
Come on.
I wanna show you something.
What about that tracting
you wanted us to do?
We'll get to that later.
Come on, get in.
Well, here we are.
Did you ride horses
when you were a kid?
Yeah, once.
That wasn't a horse;
that was a mule.
Fellas, come on in.
You've never ridden a horse?
Dude, how many black cowboys
have you seen?
Elders, I'd like you to meet
my good friend,
Reginald Steedman.
That's the first.
You guys ready for some work?
Work?
As in "work"
or are we talkin'
about the Lord's work?
Brother Steedman
and I have made a deal.
Every time you
clean out his stalls,
he'll listen to one
of the discussions.
That seemed pretty fair.
How many discussions are there?
You don't even want to know that.
Elders, I've never seen cleaner stalls.
Eight o'clock tonight.
What's at 8 o'clock?
You cleaned my stalls,
I'll let you teach me a lesson.
Great.
Eight o'clock.
That's less than two hours.
Okay, Elders, go ahead.
We had a deal.
Yeah, go ahead,
Elder Johnson.
It's your lesson.
Help a brother out.
Okay, just pick one of those lessons.
He's not going to know if it is right.
Uh, your body is a temple.
Yes, it's a very big temple.
No, no unclean thing
should be partaken of
to defile our body.
The Lord revealed to Jordan Smith
that we should refrain
from strong drink,
tobacco, and out-of-date meat.
Don't you mean Joseph Smith?
Exactly!
He always gets it wrong.
And, and, if you obey
these wise words of wisdom,
ye shall walk and not faint,
run and not fall down.
Isn't it, out-of-season meat?
Yes, but, uh,
it can be interpreted to mean
past the expiration date
shown on the packages
of the meats.
Yeah, what does strong drink mean?
Well, um, let's, let's, let's see.
Well?
Strong drinks:
"Not for the belly
but for washing of our bodies.
"And again, tobacco
is not good for man
"and is an herb for bruises
and sick cattle
to be used with judgment and skill."
Where does that come from?
Well, it says revelation given
to Joseph Smith, the prophet,
at Kirtland, Ohio,
February 27, 1833.
That's almost 200 years ago.
That's pretty forward thinking.
Uh, yeah, J. Smith
was no dummy, you know.
"Please help us.
We're heading west.
Elders Johnson and Talbot."
So, Elder Johnson, successful day?
Yeah, we uh, we did some preachin',
if that's whatcha mean.
Have you always been
a member of the church?
No. Why?
'Cuz you do some
of the strangest things.
Like ordering Coke
when I shouldn't have?
I have just noticed
there are things you do,
aren't typical
of the missionaries I've known.
Well, considering
where I've been in my life,
I think that I'm doin'
pretty good as a missionary.
Okay, that came out wrong.
I'm not judging you.
I just find it nice.
Nice?
Yeah, nice that you're different.
Do you realize
if my last name was Elder,
I'd be "Elder Elder."
And if I was a woman
I'd be "Sister Elder."
That's confusing, isn't it?
What is it with you
and bathrooms?
Every time you come out
you're like a genius.
But if I had an older sister
in the same mission,
you'd say,
"Sarah, this is Elder Elder,
"and this is Elder Elder's
eldest sister, Sister Elder.
Elder Elder, Sister Elder,
this is Sarah."
That's kinda cool, isn't it?
Why don't you be the dumb waitress
and leave the deep thinking to us?
Elder Elder.
Elder Elder, Sister Elder.
What was that supposed to mean?
What?
The "dumb waitress" bit?
I don't know,
I've met some pretty dumb waitresses
on the outside that is,
but, not you, of course.
My mom was a waitress
her entire life.
And I am sure she's probably
a very special person.
When can I meet her?
She is dead.
Sarah, wait...
I'm sorry, I didn't know.
Why don't you concentrate on being
the insensitive missionary,
and I'll concentrate
on being the dumb waitress.
Nice timing.
We gotta get outta here
before I go crazy.
Elders, I need your help.
Someone else have some stalls
that need cleanin'?
It's Brother Steedman.
There's been an accident.
He was unconscious
when they found him.
I don't understand.
We were just with him.
The first thing he said
when he woke up
was he wanted
to see the missionaries.
Now, do you have consecrated
oil with you?
What?
Consecrated oil,
that's why we're here.
I'd like to give
Brother Steedman a blessing.
No, we don't, Bishop.
We must have left it
in the car.
Well, I have some in my truck.
Uh, you two go inside.
A blessing?
Do you know what he is talking about?
Yes, and there is no way we can
bluff our way through it.
Brother Steedman.
Elders!
Well, I'm very glad you came.
What happened?
Well, I don't really know.
I was on the fence;
the next thing I remember
I was staring at the clouds.
So, what did the doctor say?
Well, they are doin'
a whole bunch of tests--
nothing so far.
Okay, that's a good thing then.
You know, I had a dream.
I saw some things that made
me think about you two.
It kinda scared me.
If it's that whole
out-of-date meat thing,
you know, we can review that whole...
Ever since I met you two,
something's a little, well...
Maybe some, you know,
some reading material...
will uh, help you clear your mind?
Ha ha, huh.
You two did a great job
taking care of my horses.
Please take care of my place
until I get back home.
Now, I know
it's a big responsibility,
but I am sure you two
can handle the job.
Tomorrow's feed day,
so you're gonna have
to take my truck
and go into town
and load up for the week.
No, but I'm afraid that
that is not gonna work.
Bishop Hollister's set up
a lot of appointments,
and we are sorta committed.
Well, I've already spoken to him.
He said he could work things out
as long as it's okay with you.
We'll do it.
I knew I could count on you two.
How are you?
I'm doin' okay.
You guys are going to have
to excuse me.
Uh, I have the consecrated oil.
What about the blessing?
Excuse me, I have to be
with my companion.
I'm sorry about that.
Look, you can't leave me here.
We're a team, remember?
Look, Elder.
Tyler...
We got wheels, we got cash,
and agreed to leave
when we had both.
So don't give me the guilt trip.
Are you comin' or not, huh?
We are supposed to stay together.
It's mission rules.
We're not missionaries!
We're delinquents, serial #43769.
Look, I think we are
somewhere in between.
The only reason why anybody
gives us attention
is because they think
that we are missionaries.
If they knew who we were,
they'd run us outta town.
Look, I just think it's time
we stopped running, Justin.
Hey, running's my life.
Why?
Well, let's see.
It started when my dad
didn't show up
to my championship
baseball game.
Yeah, I was seven.
According to my counselor,
I'm in desperate need
of some attention.
So, I run. I have to.
It's who I am.
It's not who you are;
it's what you do.
Blah, blah, blah.
What am I supposed to say?
Tell them that I got sick.
I had to go home.
The last missionaries up and left.
So, why can't we?
What am I supposed to tell Sarah?
No, don't do this man.
The children of Israel
wandered in the desert for 40 years
before they found
the promised land.
Is that supposed to motivate me?
Nah, it's just a little trivia is all.
Well, the tallest donut ever
was like over 30-foot high
and weighed almost 600 lbs.
It took ten guys
three days to eat it
Do you know that
because you were one of the ten?
Shouldn't we have
stayed at the rest stop?
Absolutely not.
This is going to make great material
for my homecoming talk.
Assuming we live.
Elder Johnson,
Yeah?
...if I die, you can eat me!
No thanks.
I hit my cholesterol max
with the Twinkies.
No, come on, really.
My parents would totally understand.
No. No, um, I'm uh, a vegetarian.
Good, the wolf will eat me then.
I realize we had burgers yesterday,
but as of right now I am a vegetarian.
Okay, that's cool.
Elder Johnson?
Is something wrong?
Where's Elder Talbot?
He is, uh, in the truck.
He's asleep.
That's the Steedman's truck.
Yeah, yeah, he, uh,
he asked us
to take care of his place
while he was in the hospital.
Well, what happened?
The doctors aren't sure.
They said not to worry.
I didn't want to bother you,
so I was just-I was just gonna
leave this note on your jeep.
What's it say?
Just that um,
we'll be at the Steedman place
if you need to get ahold of us.
It's a little weird seeing you
in normal clothes.
Yeah. Heh.
If feels kinda weird too.
It feels too much like home.
Listen, I'm sorry
about what I said earlier.
You mean about me
being a dumb waitress?
I didn't say that you were dumb.
We get it all the time.
People see the uniform,
but they don't see who's inside.
I guess waitresses and missionaries
have got a lot in common then.
Yeah, I guess we do.
So, do you like it here
in New Harmony?
What's not to like?
Everybody knows everybody.
It's quiet most of the time.
We're one big, big family.
Not a day goes by
that I don't think
about going someplace else.
There's a whole world out there
I know nothing about.
Yeah, well, most of it
isn't worth knowing.
I guess you see both sides
from being a missionary.
Yeah.
Yeah, I guess I do.
And I kinda like what
I see here in New Harmony.
Right.
Well, I uh,--I better go.
You know,
that whole opposite sex thing.
Elder Johnson?
Yeah?
Good night.
Beautiful Sunday morning,
and it's great to be alive!
Ha ha, ha ha!
Need some help?
Huh?
It was the girl, wasn't it?
No! Not even.
Yeah, right.
Not EVEN!
I came back to save you!
Yeah, right.
Remember the Donner Party?
Wrong season, Elder.
You must survive at all costs
to carry on my legacy.
I'm not eating you, Elder Talbot.
"And if you labor all your days
and save but one soul,
how great shall be your joy
in my Father's kingdom."
I'm still not eating you.
Ha ha ha ha!
Don't start without me, Bishop.
Brothers and sisters,
we've had a wonderful
meeting here today.
And in closing,
I'd like to invite Elder Talbot
and Elder Johnson,
our new missionaries,
to come up here
and introduce themselves to you
and to bear their testimonies.
Elders?
This oughta be interesting.
Good morning,
brothers and sisters.
Good morning, I'm Elder Johnson,
and my partner, Elder Talbot.
We are here straight from the MTC,
the Mormon Tabernacle Choir.
# Amazing grace #
But, it, it's good to be here,
in New Harmony.
# ...how sweet #
I'm from California,
and my companion
is from a small town in Idaho.
...where the nation vacations.
This is the Lord's work.
You saints of New Harmony
are awesome.
# swwweeeettt #
Uh, yeah, we're still,
we're still workin' on that.
Absolutely.
Can I get an amen?
Amen.
Amen!
# There are people
on this street #
# Who give us
somethin' to eat #
# Hey ya, hey ya #
# They could use some company #
# Have a laugh
or shoot the breeze #
# Hey ya, hey ya #
# And do you ever stop
to stare #
# Or take the time to care? #
# Hey ya, hey ya #
# And what about
the lonely man next door #
# Do you think he is tired
of bein' bored? #
# Come on,
come on #
# So many people
are reaching out #
# Looking for brighter days #
# When you help
someone in need #
# Get them back up
on their feet #
# Take a brother by the hand #
# He'll become a friend #
# Then there's a circle
without end #
# Turning strangers
into friends #
# With every kindness
you are blessed #
# Brings you real happiness #
# The circle of love,
# Comes back to you
the more you give it #
# Love ##
Oh dude, if I have to eat
one more scoop of mashed potatoes.
Today was the longest day
of my life.
Well, aside from my stomachache,
I thought it felt pretty good.
Definitely worth a journal entry,
ya know?
What are you doin'?
I'm writin' in my journal.
But it's not even your journal.
Why don't you worry
about going to sleep,
and I'll worry about writing
in my journal, okay?
That's it.
It's over.
So much for my legacy.
They've come for us!
You boys like a drink of water?
You got any yoohoo?
Milk?
Some skim milk?
Who are you guys anyway?
- We're missionaries.
- From the booklet...
Do you know the purpose of life?
'Cuz I do.
I definitely do.
Sorry to put you boys out,
but we're on official business.
Thanks for the ride.
Call the number on this card.
They'll send you a free video.
Let me know if you find out
the meaning of life.
Oh, but, we, we have!
That is... the point.
It's in the book.
I tried to tell...
Okay. Bye.
Ah... civilization.
So dramatic.
You make it sound like
we were gone for a month.
I'm starving.
Let's find a restaurant.
We still got some Twinkies.
Come on, delicious, tasty,
golden, delicious...
Okay, you're gonna
make me vomit.
...and it's got the filling
with the creaminess.
Come on, one Twinkie?
He is pretty cute.
In fact, they both are.
They are missionaries.
I've seen the way
you've been lookin' at him.
Don't be ridiculous.
What would you do
if he wasn't a missionary?
I'm not playin' your little game.
So, when are you going
to start dating again?
You know, I know four priests
who'd go out with you.
Stop this.
What?
It's true.
Come on, let me set you up
so you can have fun.
I'm not having
this conversation.
So, how many priests
are in this town?
About 15, but only 5 are active.
Eighteen teachers
and 21 deacons.
You're allowed to date priests?
They can date priests
but not deacons.
Teachers aren't supposed to,
but some do.
Ick, teachers are so immature.
Not as bad as some
of the elders I know.
I think I'm getting a headache.
With only one week
to election day,
polls are suggesting that
Senator Boxwell is a shoe-in.
The man can do no wrong.
It's come down...
Will you turn that up?
You guys aren't supposed
to watch TV.
Senator, what do you attribute
your last term's
incredible success to?
Well, aside from hard work,
I'd have to say a very loving
and supportive family.
Your daughters are adorable.
It's nice to see
such a strong family man
representing our great state.
Thank you very much.
And regardless of what happens
next week, Christine,
I know I'll always have
a loving and supportive family.
There you have it Bob,
Roy Boxwell,
a great senator and a great...
You all right, man?
Yeah, can I get Roy Boxwell,
please?
This is Justin.
Look, he knows who I am.
Yes, well put him through.
Justin, where are you?
I am in the middle of the desert,
right where you sent me.
What do you want... money?
I don't need your money.
Then what?
I saw your little TV interview today.
You're quite the family man
these days.
Justin, tell me where you
are so we can talk.
Nice try, Senator.
Justin, let me send someone for you.
You wanna send someone to get me?
Yes, I do.
Let me have your pen.
See you around, Roy.
Justin!
What?
Look, I'm on the last week
of my reelection campaign,
don't screw this up.
What was that all about?
Hello?
Yes, is Justin there?
No, nobody named Justin.
Tell me, where is this phone located?
It's a pay phone inside
the New Harmony Diner.
New Harmony?
Who is this?
All right, thank you very much.
Get General Wilkins
on the phone for me.
How did you know?
Half the camp knew you were
related to some politician.
Now I know which one.
Not a word, okay?
Please?
Why can't we get this in the open?
It's not a good idea.
What's the worst that can happen?
To him?
To him, probably nothin'!
He would claim he was helping
out some troubled kid
and walk away smelling like a rose.
Then why'd you call him?
I couldn't just sit back
and let him get away with all
that family-man crap, okay?
He's a liar.
Face it, man!
Okay, your dad's a politician.
He is not the ideal family man,
but so what, who cares?
You got your own life, man!
Justin, I mean that.
You got your own life, dude.
So then let's go.
It's you and me just like we planned.
Actually, I'm sorta likin'
what's happening around here, man.
Huh... you, you mean
this missionary stuff?
Yeah.
Yeah!
I mean, it's not my style,
but I just like it-- it's fun.
I guess I just like helping people,
you know?
Hey, you listen to me.
The fuse is lit, all right?
The real elders are coming.
I know, I know.
So let's go while we still can!
Come on!
Something's just telling me
we shouldn't.
Ha, ha, it's the cafe food talking',
all right?
I can't deny the way I feel, man.
We cannot stay here forever,
okay, Elder Talbot?
We'll leave when the time is right.
I swear!
I swear on the Bible
and the Book of Mormon.
You're so stupid.
Atta baby.
All right?
It's not our money.
Don't make me take it from you.
Try to take it from me
and I'll put you down.
I'm gonna count to three.
I'm warning you,
I am a trained martial artist.
One.
Two.
Two and a half.
All right buddy, snake eyes, okay?
Watch out for him, he's everywhere.
Ow.
Give it to me.
Right now.
Oh, man.
That really stings.
All right girls,
with the backpack you've got a deal.
Hey, I'm gonna get a hemorrhoid
from a seat that small.
They're going to be great;
the baskets are very nice.
And check this out...
Would you just hush up.
Bubbles!
Ahh, you know their names.
Perfect.
Yeah, but I'm not telling you
the other two.
So, ha!
Gentlemen, what are you thinking?
I mean you just leave the keys
in the ignition?
It's not real safe.
You never know
who's gonna pick 'em up.
I suppose you're not going
to give us back our keys?
Uh... no.
What's this all about?
This is about who stays
and who goes.
Oh, I get it.
This town isn't big enough
for both of us.
Showdown at the lemonade corral,
huh?
Come on, Daren, let's do this.
You boys get
two minutes' head start.
Last man without paint wins.
Wins what?
We win... you got ten minutes
to pack your stuff.
You're gonna run us outta town?
Yep... just like we did
with the last two dork missionaries.
If we win, we get our keys back.
We stay, and all you boys
have to attend church
for the next six months.
Come on, Daren,
let's get on with it.
Two minutes starts-- now.
Stay.
Elder Johnson,
spirit's telling me to move,
let's move, so let's move.
I ain't runnin' anymore.
What are you doin', man?
Elder Johnson,
what would Jesus do, okay?
Let's go.
Jesus?
Jesus wouldn't run
from a bunch of rednecks.
Heh.
Looks like these Bible boys
know how to play.
I've gotta work in a half hour.
Shut up, Dale.
Just me and you, huh,
preacher boy?
You first.
I'll take the rest of your crew, huh?
Come on, man,
you gotta make this interesting.
Come on, let's just go.
Let's just go.
I guess I'll see you boys
at church on Sunday.
# Sometimes you gotta take
one step back #
# To go two steps
forward #
# Sometimes you gotta
stop believing #
# And find the faith #
# What's done is done #
# Tomorrow has just begun... #
Hey, check this out.
Are you pushing me
off the road?
Hands up, come on.
Hey, nice day for a ride,
huh guys?
What the fetch!
Those are the guys
who stole our car!
Catch 'em.
Come on.
Pump.
Pump!
I'm tryin'.
You're on my wheel.
Lance Armstrong!
I can't do it, Elder.
I'm walking.
Elders, what's going on?
You know what, Bishop?
We just saw the...
Burnett Brothers.
Listen, I have a surprise
for you two.
Can you get yourselves
cleaned up?
We are sort of in a hurry.
Yeah, our laundry smells
really bad, sir.
Please.
It's only going to take
a couple of minutes.
Come on.
THREE BOGIES!
Hey, Bishop.
Hello, Sarah, how are you?
Good.
Hey, Elder.
Hey, Sarah.
Elders, come on over.
Oh, hey, you're out!
They couldn't find a thing.
Ha ha!
So, here I am.
I hate hospital food.
Looks like you're making up for it.
Please, sit down.
Elders, I know that things
have been kinda crazy
these past few days.
Yeah, they have.
I'm thinking about getting baptized.
Less than three days
and already you have a convert.
Are you sure we're not
rushing things a little bit?
What do you mean, Elder?
How do you know Brother Steedman
is thinking clearly?
He just got out of the hospital.
Reggie?
Well, I know it sounds crazy,
but, um, this feels right.
You Elders know what
that's like, don't you?
Yes, we do.
And I'd like you to be the one
to baptize me, Elder Johnson.
Me?
Would you do me the honor?
Can both of you excuse us
for a minute,
while I speak to Elder Johnson,
I mean Elder Talbot, in private?
Hey you!
Not so fast!
I know who you are.
What's going on?
We played pool together
two nights ago.
You must have me confused
with someone else.
I don't think so.
Daren, leave him alone.
He wore a cowboy hat, sunglasses.
Said he was passing through town
like a bad burrito?
There is obviously some mistake.
Missionaries don't play pool.
He ordered beer.
Yeah, well, missionaries
don't drink either.
You did.
You're a liar.
Shut up, Sarah.
Easy pal, or I'm going to be
introducing you to the ground.
Daren, stop!
So, shut up!
Back off, cowboy, all right?
Daren, stop it!
Easy boys, let's end this now.
I never forget a face,
especially an ugly one.
His name is Elder Johnson,
all right?
Look, we are missionaries, okay?
We don't want any trouble.
It's okay, Tyler.
You know, you're right.
I did play pool with you
the other night,
and I cleaned you out.
I told you.
See, I knew it!
He's been lying
to all of us.
He's a hustler.
My name is Tyler,
and we're not missionaries.
We are from a correctional camp
in the Mojave Desert.
The pickup we stole
broke down in the middle
of the desert.
So, we grabbed the first car
that came along.
I'm sorry.
I allowed you into my home.
I trusted you.
Is this true?
Yeah.
Shame on you.
- Sarah.
- Don't.
Senator.
I'm Bishop Hollister.
Bishop, it's a pleasure.
What are you doin' here?
I've come to get you, Justin.
I'm not going anywhere with you.
Justin.
Wait.
I'll take over from here, Senator.
Oh, it's all right, General.
I had a long talk
with Bishop Hollister here.
He's told me everything
that has been going on, Justin.
You know, in all the years
of military schools
and outreach programs,
I've never had such praise
for my son.
Did he mention car thief,
impostor, liar?
Like father, like son.
Right, Dad?
You lie to your people,
and I lie to mine.
Give him a chance.
He had his chance.
We're done.
Look, Justin,
come back with me, please?
We'll start over, I promise you.
Ah, that's nice.
Senator Boxwell welcomes back
his prodigal son.
That'll make quite the headline.
This isn't about headlines,
and you know that.
This is about you and me.
You're about 15 years late...
Dad.
It's better late than never.
I'd give a million dollars
to meet my father.
Hey, everybody,
we're the new missionaries!
What's your name, Elder?
- I'm Elder Talbot.
- And I'm Elder Johnson.
Sorry it took us so long,
but these flippin'...
These fetchin'...
We sorta got sidetracked.
I feel we already know you, Elders.
You guys look hungry.
Told you I lost weight.
It just didn't look like it to me.
Hey, that is a really nice tie!
Oh, thank you.
Does this belong to you?
Thank you, Elder Talbot.
And, uh, this belongs to you.
I'm sorry.
Uh, my name is Tyler,
and most people know me
as "Elder Talbot."
All right.
Get in the pipe!
# Who wants to go,
who wants to go to heaven? #
# Who needs to ask
or reason why? #
Come on!
Move it!
# Who wants to go,
who wants to go to heaven? ##
Remember the first time
we came here together?
Yeah, I do.
Almost two years ago.
Has it been that long?
Just a little somethin'
from all of us at the diner.
These are my travel books
from years ago.
You broke into my house?
Hello! I have a key!
Open it up.
# Who wants to go,
who wants to go to heaven? #
# Who needs to ask
or reason why? #
# Who wants to burn... ##
I can't accept this.
Well, it's not transferable
and nonrefundable.
Danielle!
Sarah!
You gotta stop thinkin'
about everyone else for once,
especially what's his name.
It would mean a lot
to all of us if you went.
I'm going to New York City.
It's pretty cool, huh?
# ...A chance to die,
to be reborn #
# With just one kiss...
just one kiss... #
# With just one kiss
and you're mine #
# Hold on #
Put 'em up.
Now, fill it back up.
# I lay my dream
down before you #
# A splendid tapestry,
it's so old #
# But tread so carefully,
for there is danger #
# You might just trample
on my dream #
# To never,
ever be forgiven #
ever wonder why #
# With just one kiss #
# A feat such as this #
# With just one
and you're mine ##
Steal water?
You earn a day in the pipe.
Any questions?
Speak up, son.
My um, my cousin told me
that two boys
died this past summer.
Earlier today we had 12 graduates,
a real success.
He said their eyes
were plucked out by vultures,
and their skin
was dried out like leather.
Well, let's just stick to the
mission at hand, shall we?
All right.
Can I come in?
You already did.
So, congratulations, man!
We did it!
We're done.
This is it.
Yeah, you too.
You all packed?
Uh, gettin' there.
So, have you heard from her?
No.
It's no big deal.
Huh... liar.
- No!
- Okay.
I'm okay.
Okay, ha ha.
I'm just gonna work
all summer... and...
forget all about her.
Sure.
What about you?
I haven't picked
a school yet.
Guess I'll wait and see where
the wind blows me, ya know?
Man, I'm so done with this place.
Yeah.
You're gonna be all right, man?
Elder.
I'm going to see
the Riveter, hoo hooo!
Yaaaa hahaha!
Wheee!
Okay, man, this is your space.
Don't you take
no crap from nobody!
Okay.
ORDER UP!
You are gettin' pretty fast
back there.
Bring it on, baby.
If you don't get back to work!
You see me awful busy in here.
I don't think
we've been properly introduced.
I'm Sarah,
and I own the diner in town.
I'm Justin.
I, uh, shovel... stuff,
all day long.
I understand
you give riding lessons.
Oh, Brother Steedman
gives the lessons.
I just sort of
make him look good.
Is he around?
No, he uh, he won't be back
until tomorrow.
Come here, I have something
I want to show you.
Look, Sarah,
I came back
to make things right.
And I don't expect
anything from you.
I know.
You, uh, might want to watch
where you're steppin'.
I'm glad you came back.
Now, come on!
I figured if you're
gonna be around awhile,
you oughta be properly introduced
to New Harmony.
Well, it puts a new perspective
on things, doesn't it?
It really does.
How about a barrel roll?
Wooohooo!
Whoa!
Load the barrel...
hahahahaha!
Whoa.
Help!
Sister Cutbank, stop!
Look what you're doing.
You two ever been to Australia?
No, Sister Cutbank, we haven't.
Why don't we just go
down under right now,
just the three of us?
It can't be more than
a couple of thousand miles.
We're a little low on fuel.
Ah, good point.
Get ahold of your stomach,
it's goin' into your butt!
Wooo!
Sister Cutbank!
I'm gonna be sick.
Hey, what's that boy?
He's turning a little green.
No!
Ha ha ha ha!
I'm finished.
I'm done, Sister Cutbank.
No more, please!
Ha hah haa!
Ahhhhh!
We oughta do this again!
(Love bites!)