( Narrator ) Deep in the mountainsm
secret ninja academies
train our future protectors.
Ancient scrolls told of three
who would be chosen above the others.
Three who would become...
# Go, Power Rangers!
Go, Ninja Storm! #
# Let's go! #
# The call is on
Their force is getting strong #
# They'll have to brave the weather #
# Ninja storm!
Stand together #
# The storm will grow
The waters flow #
# Power Ranger
Ninjas, go! #
# Power Rangers
Ninja storm is growing #
# It's growing! It's growing! #
# Go, Power Rangers!
Go, Ninja Storm! #
# Let's go! #
# At the speed of the wind, go!
And scream like thunder #
# Go, Power Rangers
Go, Ninja Storm! #
# Let's go, Power Rangers
# Let's go! #
( beeping )
( turns off )
( cheering )
- Hey, that was awesome, dude.
- Finally landed the back flip, man.
You wanna hit that new rail?
No, I can't. I gotta get to class.
- Class?
- Never mind, man. Catch you later, bro.
Not bad.
- Lag times are about two seconds off.
- I know, my bike's bugging on that uphill.
- What time is it?
- Five after, why?
Man, I am so busted!
- Dustin, where are you going?
- I'll call you later, okay? I gotta go.
TORI: Where are they?
Come on.
( grunts ) You miss me?
Dream on.
Where is Dustin?
Last, as usual.
Dude.
( door slides )
- 'Bout time.
- What's up, dude?
How can you guys
be late every single time?
I couldn't pull that off if I planned it.
Maybe that's because
you're the reliable one.
What does that mean, "the reliable one?"
In any group there are
different kinds of people.
Totally true, yeah.
Think about the Power Rangers.
Power Rangers?
You've got to be joking.
No. Okay, there's always
the mellow, reflective dude.
Then there's the risk taker.
The adrenaline guy.
- That would, of course, be me.
- Yeah, right.
And you, Tori, you're just...
You're the logical one.
You guys have to lay off
the comic books, seriously.
TORI: Power Rangers. Whatever.
This place always creeps me out.
- DUSTIN: I heard that, bro.
- TORI: You guys are so lame.
- Dustin, would you come on?
- I'm right here.
- SHANE: Sure is quiet out here.
- DUSTIN: Little too quiet.
Did you see that?
ALL: Ah!
He-ya!
Go!
Ah! Whoa!
DUSTIN: Not good.
( ninjas laugh )
Let go of me, man.
( squawking )
SHANE: Oh, man.
- That's enough for today.
- ALL: He-ya!
Tori.
Shane.
Dustin.
I am very disappointed.
I will expect a visit from you,
so that we may discuss
your lack of commitment
to your ninja training.
That wasn't so bad, huh?
What? Well, it wasn't.
Tell you what,
you guys can blame it all on me.
TORI: Don't worry, we will.
SENSEI: You have been students at
the Wind Ninja Academy for nearly a year.
And yet you fail to see
the importance of punctuality.
I would suggest you find a way
to change that before you return tomorrow.
Otherwise, I will have no choice
but to expel you.
Wait, you can't.
You all have great potential.
It would be a shame to waste it.
Now, go.
You must have other studies.
( men grunting )
I don't know why
you put up with them.
Well then, Cameron,
I suppose that's why I'm the sensei,
and you're the sensei's son.
( rumbling )
What's wrong, Dad?
( evil chuckling )
Cool!
Kicked up to 50/50.
That's what I got to learn for my video.
( alarm goes off )
Dustin?
Heads up!
You're not gonna leave me here
to clean up the shop.
Have I ever told you
what a cool boss you are?
Bye, Kelly!
( radio ) ...atmospheric disturbances
have the weather service baffled.
- Are we on time?
- We're early.
Hey, they look like they need help.
No way, Tori, we can't.
We can't leave them here.
What if something happens?
If we're late,
something will definitely happen to us.
And it won't involve
fun and fabulous prizes.
( thunder )
Lothor.
The dark energy is strong in you.
It's had time to grow.
It has been a while.
Armies take time.
And now is the time for revenge,
Zurgane, proceed.
As you wish, sir.
- It doesn't have to be this way.
- Why would now be any different?
ALL: Huh?
Kelzacs!
Ha, ha ha!
He-ya!
- Thank you very much.
- No problem. Bye.
Dude, what if his alarm clock didn't go off
and he doesn't even miss us?
He's a ninja master, Dustin.
- They don't oversleep.
- Really?
Ah!
Trash them all!
Now, Choobo!
Good-bye, Wind Ninja Academy!
Ha!
I can't feel a thing.
Where are we, man?
CHOOBO: Up, up, and away!
What's going on?
SHANE: Something's attacking the school!
TORI: Look out!
Whoa!
It's gone!
I don't know,
I'm thinking... earthquake?
When was the last time
you heard of an earthquake
sucking buildings
and people into the sky?
MARAH: Kapri, you said once Uncle
captured all the ninja schools,
- we'd divide Earth down the middle!
- KAPRI: No, what I said was,
once Earth's under Uncle's control, you'd
get the Arctic Circle and I'd get California.
Kapri, Marah, quiet!
Or I'll banish you back to your parents.
This is why you never
work with family.
BOTH: Sorry, Uncle. Bye-bye!
Now, where was I?
The final phase of your plan
to capture Earth, sir.
Of course.
Now that the last of the mighty ninja
academies has been silenced,
- the planet is ours!
- ( whispering )
( grunting )
Sir, it seems
there are three students
from the Wind Ninja Academy
still unaccounted for.
Why would I think anything
could be done right the first time?
- General Zurgane!
- Sir?
I want you to make certain
the zone is clear.
I want nothing left standing!
Nothing!
TORI: Who would do something like this?
Are we the only students left?
Who's that?
( grunting )
It's Cam!
Help me get him out.
TORI: We've got you, come on.
- ( coughing )
- Cam, are you okay?
Yeah, I'm fine.
ALL: Whoa!
No!
Come on, guys. This way.
Go!
- Cam, what is this place?
- Just follow me.
No way.
TORI: It's amazing.
Dude!
Don't ask any questions
because I can't answer them.
What, this is like
some big secret?
Yes, Shane, it's like some big secret.
And there are times when
secrets must be revealed, Cam.
Whoa! Hey, uh...
- that big rat sounds just like Sensei.
- Yeah, I know.
Doesn't really look like him, though.
I mean, except for the clothes.
My father is not a rat.
He's a guinea pig.
Dude, did he just explain why,
and I like... missed it?
He's stuck.
Stuck?
SENSEI: Yes, Shane. Stuck.
Observe.
Whoa-oh!
This is Lothor, once a great ninja.
He was banished from the Earth
when his hunger for power
turned him to the dark side.
When our energy fields collided,
I was transformed into
what you see before you.
Now he has returned,
and brought an army
that will do everything
to take our planet for their own.
Unless they are stopped!
Who is gonna be dumb enough
to try and stop them?
An excellent quiestion, Dustin.
The morphers, Cam.
Father, you're not serious.
- We have no choice.
- But these guys? I mean, them?
- They're, well, they're...
- We're what?
Yeah, I don't like
the way that sounded.
- Do you?
- Actually, dude, I'm kind of lost here.
Now, Cam.
These are your Power Ranger
Wind morphers.
Yeah, right.
Yes! See, I knew it, dude!
I was right.
Power Rangers are real!
Whatever.
No way.
SENSEI: Dustin, child of the earth,
true to your heart.
You will embody the powers
of the Yellow Wind Ranger.
Tori, fluid and graceful
like the water,
you will become the Blue Wind Ranger.
Shane, reaching for the stars,
you will command the powers
of the Red Wind Ranger.
From this point, you will be known
as the Wind Power Rangers,
protectors of the earth.
So, what exactly does this thing do?
Where's the switch?
- Does it have any games?
- No, it doesn't have games...
Ladies and gentlemen,
the defenders of the galaxy.
Quickly, Lothor's army is attacking.
You must intercept it.
Call on your powers
by saying "Ninja storm, Ranger form!"
Keep your eyes open.
( echoing ) Hey, looking for us?
It's them!
Okay.
Ninja storm...
- What is it again?
- Ninja storm, Ranger form.
It's Ranger form!
Dude, watch and learn.
Ninja Storm, Ranger Form!
Power of Earth!
Yeah, baby! Yeah!
I guess no one's laughing
at the comic book geek now,
are they?
BOTH: Ninja storm, Ranger form, hah!
Power of air!
Power of water!
ALL: He-ya!
Attack!
Wind Rangers, ninja sword!
# Go, Power Rangers,
Go, Ninja Storm! Let's go! #
He-ya!
All right, boys.
Step aside.
On your left!
Hyah! It's all in the wrist.
It's also a handy laser blaster.
What's wrong? Never seen a girl
in blue Spandex walk on water?
Yeah, it worked!
Ky-ah!
Good job, Dustin!
- Ky-ah!
- Power Rangers?
Nobody told me
there would be Power Rangers.
- Wind!
- Power!
- Rangers!
- You're impressive against our Kelzacs!
But you didn't think that
was all we had, did you?
ALL: Ah!
Guys, check me out!
This is what I call
getting some air.
- We've got you covered.
- On your wing.
I'm going in!
- No, put me down!
- You got it.
I'm afraid of heigh... ah!
- That's it!
- ALL: Hy-ah!
- Hawk blaster, fired up!
- Sonic fin, sound off!
Flying hammer, ready to roar!
Beat this, blue dude!
Ha!
Ready for a workout?
And one, and two...
and work those abs!
Work it!
Is it hot out here,
or is it just you?
Let's put 'em together, guys.
# Go, Power Rangers!
Go, Ninja Storm! #
ALL: Storm striker!
Oh, I'm so scared!
- Ready?
- Fire.
Ah!
- Later days!
- Oh, yeah!
Thanks for stopping by.
# Go, Power Rangers!
Go, Ninja Storm! Let's go! #
Yeah.
- That really just happened, right?
- I'm pretty sure it did.
Now, that... was awesome!
Whoo!
See, I told you guys.
I told you there were Power Rangers
and you're like, "No, you comic book geek.
It's an urban legend, man."
That wasn't me, that was miss fluid,
graceful water babe over here.
All right, that was me. But...
You did well this time, Rangers.
But understand that there will
be battles in the future.
Lothor will not rest until the earth
is completely under his command.
Or until he is destroyed.
The future is in your hands,
Power Rangers.
Captioned by Grantman Brown