Pencil!
Bye, Pencil.
Bye.
Good morning.
So much for my amazing self-control.
- Hi, Brenda.
- Hey.
- Is this a jelly?
- Yes, it is.
They're really good.
Three million in sales.
Almost three million. Around.
Let's round up.
Let's just say three million.
Seven percent. Ten percent is 300.
Five percent is 150.
Seven percent should be...
225, little under that.
About 215, around there.
This is definitely under...
It should be 7%. What is this?
But what a bonus. I mean, still...
Still nothing.
I mean, I know it's a lot of money to you,
but, I mean...
But you don't have my degrees.
- This isn't the only place I can work.
- Right.
It's not about whether
it's a lot of money or not,
it's about what's fair.
Jeff, he's always pushing
to get as much as he can.
Hey, Jerry. Hi, Jerry.
Hey.
Well, it's gotta be some kind of mistake.
I mean, everyone knows
how important you are to this company.
And you're here, like,
12 hours a day, at least.
You've been their number one seller.
Well, maybe not this year,
but not that long ago.
The last thing they would want
is to offend you, I am positive.
Then they need to start
prioritizing people over money,
because otherwise
you got a guy like me,
who is the bones of this place,
walking around feeling very gypped.
Very, very gypped.
May I ask who's calling?
Oh, yes, that's extension 3250.
I can transfer you.
Sit down.
Oh, babe, I can't.
We're meeting some vendors
over at Scarantino's.
Oh, lucky!
Well, bye.
Bye.
Don and I had a huge fight last night.
He started complaining about my nails.
Said it looks like I've been trying
to crawl my way out of a well.
Drives me crazy.
And then I wanted
to get a glass of wine,
you know, to calm my nerves,
so I went to the fridge, got a bottle out,
and I don't know what I was thinking,
but I pulled the cork out with my teeth
and chipped my freaking front tooth.
It looks fine.
That's because I ran to the bathroom
and stuck it back on with Krazy Glue.
Can you imagine the insults
if he saw me with a chipped tooth?
I gotta go to a dentist.
Every time I do that,
I can feel wind up my tooth.
And I'm scared to touch it
with my tongue,
so I'm talking like I got
a speech impediment.
I don't know,
I think he makes me insecure.
Layla, come on, you're so beautiful.
And you're sweet and funny.
You're a catch.
You shouldn't feel insecure.
That's crazy talk.
I just think if we were engaged,
I'd mellow out.
It's just, how many times
can you keep pointing out rings
in magazines and crap like that?
Smoked tri-tip
or the chicken quesadilla?
I feel the wind again.
Hey, sexy lady. What's your name?
Come here. Let me check that out.
Hey, sexy lady.
Come here. Get you over here.
What is this?
Oh, just a little something
that I got for Benjy.
You didn't have to do that!
- Auntie got you a present.
- Benjy got a little present.
He loves presents. Can I open it?
- Yeah.
- Well, we're hoping
that the allergies are under control.
He loves it!
I just wanna...
It seems neurotic, but I just...
Its fine, honey.
I just do a little sniff test now,
because we've got to check
for artificial fibers
because some of them
will set those allergies right off.
Here, here.
I want to get a picture with it.
God, this thing drives me crazy.
- I want it.
- Okay.
Lissie, share that with your brother.
Share that with Benjy. Lissie?
She just does not share.
As if the whole Halloween thing
wasn't nightmare enough
- with Benjy's asthma attack...
- It was crazy.
Last week we found out that Norali...
Norali has been doping Benjy
with Benadryl.
- What? That's awful.
- Yes.
We don't have proof.
You know, it's so obvious.
Every time I would come home,
she would say, "He slept all afternoon,"
or what have you,
which is weird, 'cause with me
he's practically spastic.
Energetic, very energetic boy.
I mean it in a sweet way.
But, one time we came back,
it was at night and he was...
He was, like, comatose.
Yeah. I mean, he would not wake up.
You know, it was...
It was terrifying.
And she had all these, like,
red stains on her shirt.
So I went upstairs
and I looked in the cabinet,
and the Benadryl was out,
and it was, like, almost gone.
Gone!
I just went, "Oh, my God. Oh, my God!"
"This woman has been
drugging my son!"
I can't believe it.
That's horrible. I mean, jeez.
We were really gonna do something.
But, I mean, this woman
has two young children of her own.
- So what are you gonna do?
- We need to do something!
What, throw her in jail? I mean...
Well... Hello.
I mean, maybe in some universe,
or third-world country, sorry,
that's what you do for a crying baby.
But I gotta tell you what. Not here.
Do you have to go tee-tee, Pencil?
Pencil!
Come on now, I mean it! Mommy's mad!
Oh, just stay out there.
Pencil!
- Yeah.
- Hi.
Listen, I am so sorry to bother you,
but my dog is missing,
and I hear him crying,
and I think he might be in your yard.
- Would you mind if...
- Yeah. Come in.
- Thank you.
- Just go through the patio door.
Pencil!
I think I hear him over there, yeah.
Pencil.
What happened?
It's okay, Pencil. It's okay.
Just hold on. We're almost there.
- Ma'am, I'll take him.
- Okay.
Somebody come look at this dog now!
Was he sick at all?
No.
What happened?
They said it was toxic poisoning.
He got into something. Ate something.
Boy...
This might be a good time for me to...
I was gonna wait
till closer to Christmas,
but I think you deserve a little boost.
I would've liked to give you more,
but since it's a percentage
of what they give me...
You deserve more,
but I'm still debating
what to do about that.
I'm just so sad.
Oh, no, don't cry.
Oh, I have just the thing for this.
It's nothing. Just a Xanax.
You won't even notice,
but it'll help calm you down.
No, I don't want that.
I know! Let's go see a crappy movie.
Let's go find
the stupidest movie we can find.
A stupid funny movie, yeah?
I know. Let's go out tonight
and get drunk.
Let's just get plastered.
You need to get laid.
When was the last time you got laid?
Oh, it's been a long time, huh?
I think we may have a dirty diaper.
Could you change that, Maria,
before dinner? Thank you.
Why is Aunt Peggy here again?
Because she needs some cheering up.
Oh, honey, could you get me
one of those serving dishes up top?
Yeah. Yeah.
So, two girls from Lissie's class
were sent home today with lice.
I had to spend an hour fastidiously
combing through poor Lissie's hair.
Thank God, she's clean.
Yay, Lissie!
Why does Aunt Peggy need
cheering up?
- You know what, sweetie?
- Because she's sad, honey. Okay?
- She's sad.
- Yeah.
Why is she sad?
Because Pencil died today.
Wow, that's a lot to process.
D- E-A-T-H.
It's natural, honey.
Oh, doesn't know
what that means. I'd rather...
- Just skip that one.
- Okay, okay.
We are gonna get ready for dinner!
Wash our hands. We'll be back.
Okay.
Peggy...
You know what?
Maybe we should go to San Francisco.
See my sister and do some shopping.
- That sounds like fun.
- Well, little girls' weekend.
My husband was concerned
because it was $59.95,
and that wasn't in the budget.
But when I told him
I could save $20, twice...
- Hey.
So, what happened with your dog?
He died.
Oh, nuts! Really?
I'm so sorry.
You know, I had a dog
when I was younger
and when she died, I was devastated.
I was just destroyed by it, so...
I'm really sorry.
It's so weird.
I feel like I should do something for you.
Bring you some food...
I'll be okay.
Can I take you out to dinner?
I mean, not tonight,
but another night when you're up for it?
Maybe Thursday?
Oh, okay. Sure.
He seemed like a real sweet little dog.
Thank you.
Take care.
Peggy, that is great!
That is exactly
what you should be doing.
You little vixen! Is he hot?
Um, no.
Do not let him take you
to some place gross.
Because if you guys get married,
then you'll always remember
your first date,
and you do not want it to be
in some stank, beefy BO burger place.
Go Italian. Go to Scarantino's.
Oh, I am so excited!
It might not even be a date, Layla.
I mean, he might just be being nice.
No, no! I believe in fate. Don't you?
I believe that there is somebody
on this planet for us all.
Even retarded cripple people
get married.
You just have to be open.
So, hey, maybe your dog died
so that your love life can live,
and you could find... What's-his-name.
- Al. Al.
- You could find Al.
Yes. Maybe this is all fate.
This is all for the best.
I really think so.
So I thought we'd go to Scarantino's.
You ever been there?
That's so...
No, I've never been there,
but it sounds great.
- Here, let me give you a hand.
- How do I go?
Oh.
Let me get your door.
Buckle up.
His name was Pencil.
'Cause when I got him,
he was thin as a pencil
and, you know, he was brown.
Sounds really cute.
Also, he did the sweetest little thing
with his paw.
He would wipe it
on the floor back and forth,
like he was trying to write
something to me.
He had a really unique personality.
Was he a water dog?
Not really.
So, you were saying you had a dog
who died when you were young?
Tessie. I loved that dog.
I had her since she was a puppy.
We did everything together.
She was my right-hand bitch.
Sorry. I mean in the dog way
of being a bitch.
Yeah, she died way too young.
She was only six.
Yeah.
How did she die?
I shot her in Wyoming.
You want some more wine?
Wait. What do you mean?
It was an accident. A hunting accident.
Oh.
I still feel terrible.
And what were you hunting?
Hunting moose. Mooses.
They got a lot of moose up there.
Don't worry about it.
- You ever been hunting?
- No.
It can be a rush.
But, you know, accidents do happen,
and, you know,
a gun is a very powerful weapon.
I learned that the hard way.
That's why I never
keep guns in my house.
- Well, that's good.
- Yeah.
Just knives. That's it.
Thank you. I had a nice time.
So, you ever been married?
No. No.
I mean, I was...
I had boyfriends, but I never, you know.
I guess I never...
That never happened, but...
You know, I think some people
just aren't as, you know...
I don't even know what I'm saying.
Just, you know, whatever, you know.
What are you gonna do?
And the whole dating thing is just
kind of... Yuck, no thank you, so...
Yeah, so that's basically
how I feel. Just, you know...
I don't know.
Just like that, I guess. But...
So you wanna get the tour?
It can be a real addiction.
You know, some people spend
all kinds of money traveling the world
just to find something to shoot
that's new and hard to find, you know?
Like leopards, rare birds and...
And they have tours in Africa
and Asia and India.
Even endangered species.
You know, so you can get one
before they're all gone.
This was a lucky shot.
Isn't it a beauty?
And those are my knives.
Can I see your garage?
My garage?
Sure. Yeah, right through here.
Was this open the other night?
What?
This garage door was open, wasn't it,
the night that Pencil got sick?
Yeah. Could be.
What are you looking for?
- Do you keep antifreeze in here?
- Yeah, I have.
I don't know if I have any now, but...
What about rat poison?
No.
No?
Why? You got a rat problem?
Are you looking for something?
Can I help you?
I like you.
What are you doing? Don't do that.
- What? I was just...
- Stay away from me.
- Don't do that.
- No, I was just...
Come on. I gotta go.
So, how was your date?
He's not my type.
Well, what is your type?
Do you have a type?
I kind of have
a lot of work to do right now.
Hello.
- Is this Miss Spade?
- Yes.
Hi, Miss Spade.
I'm Newt Erdrich at the SPCA L.A.
I'm a Client Services Manager.
I work in the adoption program
to place animals
to prevent them
from being euthanized by the city,
and I noticed that you were very upset
about losing your dog.
And my instinct is that you're
a very sensitive, caring pet owner,
and that is exactly
the kind of people that we're looking for.
And, well, we have a dog here
who needs a home.
And this dog, Valentine is his name,
has some behavioral issues,
and I just thought that maybe you might
fall in love with him.
It's a shot in the dark here,
but I'm just desperate
because I don't want to see him die.
But no pressure.
This is King.
He's diabetic, unfortunately.
Aren't you? Big goof.
- And this is Myrtle.
- Myrtle!
She came in
when I was first starting at the Center.
And who's this?
That's Buttons.
Oh, my God.
And of course, this is Valentine.
Now, I've kept him in the pen
because he still isn't
playing well with others.
Easy.
I brought him home because,
you know, he spoke to me.
And that happens sometimes.
But I can't keep him
because legally
you're only allowed three pets.
Animals are like us, they live for love.
And if you have too many of them,
then there's not enough love
to go around, right?
Valentine, say hello
to your new mommy.
Listen, he's been abused,
so you're really gonna
have to work with him.
But look at his eyes.
There's an old soul in there, I think.
I just love him so much already.
Well, if you need help training him,
I do that part-time on the weekends.
- And my methods are very positive.
- Okay.
It's about reward,
it's not about punishment.
Good boy. You like that...
Down, Valentine! Down, Valentine!
Down! Down!
Peggy.
Layla!
Oh, Layla!
I guess all my whining paid off.
Oh, my gosh!
I totally was not prepared.
We went to go see
the new Spider-Man... Superman...
No, no, no! Spider-Man.
Anyway, it was cute.
So then we went
to Greenstein's Deli. Not romantic.
And he's acting all weird and nervous,
and I'm like, "What is going on?"
And then, bam! He just pulls it out!
And I'm not even pregnant!
It's kind of a mellow engagement.
That's what Don's calling it.
But we'll see.
Guess what?
I have some good news, too.
Oh. What, what, what?
I got another dog.
It's a shelter dog,
and his name's Valentine.
Peggy, how are you ever
gonna find a boyfriend,
if you keep shacking up with dogs?
Do you have any soy milk?
- I'm sorry, I don't.
- That's okay. It's okay.
It's very political.
Because on the one hand
you have the city,
and they want to terminate every animal
they get their hands on.
- Yeah, they just have a killing routine.
- Wow.
And I know for a fact
that they have paper products
stored in those cages.
I could write an exposé.
It would explode like a bomb.
And on the other hand,
you have the animal activists,
who don't wanna see
even one animal die.
And we come under criticism
because we work with the city,
but there are 5,000 kittens that come
through the system each year.
You can't save them all, right?
Wow. That must be
so much pressure for you.
And I have nightmares, you know?
I had a nightmare last night
that I was being attacked
and raped by two bull mastiffs.
And... But what am
I supposed to do? Stop caring?
Oh, no. I mean, you can't stop caring.
This is your passion.
- Right.
- You know.
Makes sense to me.
You're right.
Good boy. Eyes to me.
Eyes to me. He knows.
And big ups. Big ups.
Okay.
No, no, no.
He needs to know
he can't play that part.
When I was little, we had a Lhasa Apso.
Valentine.
That's good. That's good.
You can just sign your name there.
You know,
I've always had better relationships
with animals than people.
I can relate.
Animals aren't petty, for one.
They don't backstab you.
So what about girlfriends
and that sort of thing?
Oh, I don't know.
That's very complicated.
I was raised in a very...
Culty...
Adults being...
Very... No boundaries.
I just used to go off by myself...
And I always had
this connection with animals.
And that's why I'm a vegan.
People say, "If you couldn't kill it,
you shouldn't eat it. "
And I could never kill an animal.
I understand.
I'm so excited to be eating here.
There's a couple of things
that are really amazing.
The seitan Sloppy Joe.
The tempeh BLT is good.
Tofu chop.
One of everything.
No, not really.
I think a veggie pizza.
What?
Nothing.
Do you sleep with your dogs?
Guilty.
- Three dogs?
- Yeah, it gets crowded.
King hogs the covers. Don't you, King?
Wipe that grin off your face.
You know, it's really nice
to finally meet someone who just...
I don't know,
I think we have a lot in common.
And you've really
opened my eyes to so many different...
- Oh, I think you're great.
- Yeah?
Yeah. Definitely.
Well, thanks.
- And you know what?
- What?
I'm gonna be a vegan.
Really?
Yeah?
I mean, after reading all those books,
how can I not? Absolutely.
Well, I think that's great.
Yeah.
It's been a while since I...
I'm just...
Well, we don't have to do anything.
Oh. Okay.
Cupcakes!
These look diabolical.
I just had a Croissan'Wich.
They're vegan.
They're what?
There's no milk, butter,
or any animal product in them.
No animal was harmed
in the making of those cupcakes.
Different.
No butter. That's weird.
Hey, Susan.
You gotta try this. It's a vegan cupcake.
Thank you, but I'm fine.
Oh, come on,
you gotta try it. It's delicious. There.
You know what happened, don't you?
They put me on the green team
with Greg and Paul.
Two of the oldest guys in this division.
I feel like
I've been put in with the dinosaurs.
What are you so happy about?
You know what
I was just thinking, Robin?
And you're probably gonna hate this.
But you should adopt a dog.
What?
You need something to come home to.
A little life in your house.
Something to love.
And I have the perfect dog for you.
It's a Maltese-poodle mix.
And I have a picture right here.
It's such a...
Peggy, no. Absolutely not.
I don't want a dog.
Get your head in the game here.
What are you doing?
Don't ever bring that up again.
Listen, I can't really talk right now
'cause my boss is getting
a little aggravated.
But guess what?
I got another one for you.
Yes, the receptionist
wants the dachshund.
Isn't that great?
No, it's fun. I feel great about it.
I know, making a difference.
Yeah. But listen, I really should go.
Yeah. I'll call you later.
Okay. Bye.
Peggy. What's going on?
Well,
I'm volunteering for this animal shelter
and I'm trying to get
all these dogs adopted.
But Robin doesn't want me
to be doing it during work,
so I'm just trying to keep it quiet.
Hey, but you know, now that you
and Don have moved in together,
you two should get a dog!
- I have the sweetest Maltese...
- No, Peggy.
You have been running around here
like Mary Pippin Poppins
Sunshine or something.
Have you met somebody?
What do you mean?
Come on,
don't bat your eyelashes at me!
Have you met someone?
Come here! Come here!
Tell me everything!
Have you slept together?
No.
Well, have you kissed?
You made out?
Well, kind of.
Peggy, you really like him, don't you?
He's a really nice person.
This is so exciting! Look at you!
I am liking this a lot.
Peggy's got a man. Peggy's got a man.
Babe! We don't have this one.
No, we don't.
There's pretty dramatic stuff in that one.
She's so sensitive. But you know what?
Maybe. Why not, huh? I think so.
Do you wanna say thank you
to Aunt Peggy?
Thank you, Aunt Peggy.
You're welcome, sweetie.
I'm gonna go watch it!
Okay.
I feel so sorry for her.
She has missed so much school
because of the lice.
She keeps getting re-exposed
because they can't coordinate
with the parents.
The kids need to get deloused
on the same one day.
We've been saying this
from the beginning...
There's no leadership.
It's kind of tearing
the first grade class apart.
The class? The community!
There's a No Nit Policy!
It's a total meltdown.
But enough about that.
You're so sweet.
You always bring
presents for the kids, Peggy.
Yeah. You really do.
You know, I was thinking,
for Christmas, maybe a dog.
- Yeah...
- I don't think that's such a good idea.
Benjy's still a little too young.
Well, we had a dog
when we were little, Pier. Little Tippy.
Yeah...
You know, even a small dog,
'cause I thought,
you know, a hypoallergenic dog,
maybe a toy poodle,
but, one bite for Benjy
and that's his entire finger.
We just have enough
going on over here as it is.
Oh, hey, stay for dinner!
You know, Maria made pasta
with spicy sausage.
You know what, that's okay.
I'm a vegan now, so...
Actually, there are so many things
that I can't eat.
Is that healthy, Peggy?
Oh, yeah, it's very healthy.
Actually, most people do it
for health reasons,
but I'm doing it for animal reasons.
The corporate farming in America
is awful. I read a book about it.
Oh, Peggy, you can buy free range,
did you not know that?
And organic.
Yeah, but it's still, you know, murder.
Well, it'll be interesting
to see how long that lasts.
Yep. Vegan.
It's nice to have a word
that can describe you.
I've never had that before.
Come on, Valentine!
- He knows. Up!
- Valentine.
Good boy.
Hey, how's it going?
Hi.
So, that dog can sure bark, huh?
Yeah.
It's good to get him accustomed
to being in the park
and seeing other dogs
before we take him off the leash.
But you have to watch,
because sometimes
they get more aggressive
when they're on the leash.
Hey, Newt.
What?
I like you.
I like you, too.
Yeah, but...
Do you know what I mean? Like in...
Peggy,
I'm not able to be in a relationship.
I mean, with a woman. Or a man.
Either, really.
I don't understand. You like men?
I'm celibate, basically,
anyway, so that's beside the point.
But...
I hope I haven't misled you.
Cody! Come here!
- Valentine!
- Get down!
- No!
Valentine!
- No! Get down!
- Valentine!
- I'm sorry.
- Get him away!
Valentine. I'm sorry, ma'am.
I'm so sorry.
- Crazy.
- Valentine, no! No!
Come on! What are you doing?
You know, I really do like you.
If you wanna find someone else
to train Valentine,
I totally understand.
But he really needs
someone that will build on my approach.
I've always been disappointed
by people.
So...
I've really only been able
to count on my pets.
I know it's pathetic, but...
Hey, it's not pathetic.
But it's enough.
It was enough last month and last week,
and it'll be enough next week.
Because of you,
I've really been able to
acknowledge that part of my life
in a deeper way, so...
So thank you.
And this just,
you know, confirms
what I already know, so...
Hey.
- Peggy.
- Valentine.
Come on.
Christmas is gonna be nuts.
Oh and I know
you're gonna be bummed,
but Don didn't go for the dog idea.
He said it just didn't fit into our lifestyle.
Sorry. So how's the guy you're seeing?
I don't wanna talk about it.
Why? What happened?
Okay.
That was a good meeting.
I mean, I know it's the meeting
that you wanted to have,
and everything's clear now.
Greg, would you get Vince
and Bob in here?
I wanna do a post-mortem
to make sure we're on the same page.
Okay. Vince and Bob.
Robin, hi.
First of all, I'm on my lunch break,
so this is my time.
I am not on the clock.
I've been doing some research,
and I've discovered
this science lab in Maryland
that's doing animal testing. It's evil.
So I am collecting signatures
for PETA to protest.
You gotta be kidding.
Would you sign it, please?
No.
How do you think we've made all
the medical breakthroughs
that we've made?
That's how you figure stuff out, Peggy.
You test it on animals
so people can live.
Well, what they're doing is torture.
People don't test stuff
on animals for fun.
They do it for a reason, for science,
and to help save lives.
And this isn't the forum
for political signature gathering, okay?
This is a business.
Not in the office!
Sorry.
I mean, come on.
Well, what are we talking,
like spring, summer, fall?
Don!
What? We're not thinking
anything, babe.
Look, we just got engaged. Relax.
I mean, we're young. What's the rush?
It's not like we're 40, right?
Anyway, I gotta go pee.
So, Layla says
you don't want to get a dog.
Doesn't fit into your lifestyle.
I'm never home.
Well. I think you should get a dog.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
It teaches responsibility.
Well, maybe
I don't want to be responsible.
Might keep you out of trouble.
Yeah? How's that?
I don't know. You're getting married.
You could...
You know, like go home
and walk the dog instead of,
I don't know, going to the mall
and meeting other women,
at Victoria's Secret, say?
That line was too long. I'll just go later.
Peggy, get a sorbet or something.
It's Christmas.
And Don and I are paying.
I'm okay.
Peggy.
Oh, my God, you scared me.
Guess what?
Don and I got to talking after lunch,
and we've come around
on the whole dog thing.
So when we get back from our trip,
we're gonna take one.
A small one.
Are you happy?
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah. Very much so.
See, we're nesting already.
Oh, it's great.
Okay.
Valentine!
Get out! Out!
- Hi.
- Hi. Oh.
Look, I have a friend over,
and we're trying to watch a DVD
and your dog is...
Do you think you could
get him to quiet down?
You know what? I don't know.
Well, do you think
you could at least bring him inside?
He's right under my window.
Well, maybe you shouldn't
have poisoned Pencil.
- Who?
- My other dog.
The one that died in your yard
after you left out whatever it was
he got into that killed him.
- Look, I did not poison your dog!
- Well, he was poisoned.
Toxic poisoning,
that's what the vet said.
Well, that's not my problem.
Well, now it is.
What is your deal?
It's a shawl.
I like it. Thank you, Bret.
- It's from me, too.
- Oh, thank you, Pier.
It's so pretty.
And I got something
really neat for all of you.
- Oh, thank you.
- There's one for everybody.
That's for you.
Pier, you can open Benjy's.
Benjy!
I found this really great place online.
It's an animal sanctuary
for discarded farm animals.
So I sponsored
different animals for each of you.
And they actually name
the animals after you.
They named a chicken Lissie
after you, Lissie.
- They did?
- Yeah. Isn't that neat?
She was rescued
from a slaughterhouse.
And now she's a very happy chicken
because you're sponsoring her.
- When do I get her?
- Well, you don't.
But she's living a very nice life
thanks to you.
But I want her here.
Well, you could go visit her.
She's only an hour away.
That would be fun, wouldn't it?
To go visit your chicken?
- That'll be fun.
- You named chickens after us?
Well, there's actually
a pig named after you.
A pig. That's good. That's good.
I know it seems funny,
but it's a really amazing organization.
I'm sure it is.
But it's not a joke.
It's really sweet, Peggy.
Pier, stop it!
- And what kind of animal is Bret?
- Oh, yeah.
A cow.
Stop it!
Robin Heaton's office.
Yes, may I tell him who's calling?
Mr. Heaton is in a meeting
in another city, actually.
But I know he really admires
your organization,
which is why
he made the donation, obviously.
Right. Yes.
But he is a very private person,
and I don't think he wants to be
on any mailing lists.
Yes, anything you wanna send,
you can send to me, okay?
I'm his assistant, Peggy. Right.
- Peggy.
Who was that?
That was just someone, you know,
asking about...
How was your Christmas?
Fine.
Asking about what?
What did you do?
Caught up on some stuff.
Please tell me you took the day off.
Well...
You know, I should've brought you
with me to my brother's.
I can't find the number
for Long, Green & Tessler.
Can you bring me their file, too?
Oh, look at the puppy! I just love you!
I just love you!
So cute!
Christmas was great.
Don's family loves me.
At least that's what he said.
They kept talking about
all the girlfriends he had in high school,
which really started to piss me off.
It's like, "Do you have to go there?"
And, evidently, he's still in touch
with some of these girlfriends.
And I am not down with that at all.
I just don't wanna come off
like a paranoid nag too soon.
Oh!
Peggy! He just peed on me!
This is my favorite sweat suit! Dang it!
Go on.
Thank you so much for doing this.
I really appreciate it.
I hate leaving him,
but my brother doesn't allow
dogs in his house, so...
He's one of those, huh?
Well, I think I need to alter
my approach with Valentine.
Maybe more firmer.
Okay. But you won't keep him in the pen
the whole time though, right?
No. No, no. It's just till he acclimates.
Good. Okay.
And maybe I can take you out for dinner
after as a thank you?
Oh, please, it's not necessary.
No, I know, but I would really like to.
- Okay. Good. That'd be great.
- Okay. Good.
- Happy New Year.
- Thank you. Happy New Year.
I'm gonna say bye to Valentine.
Bye, Valentine. Bye, Valentine.
Be good.
Thanks again.
Where are you going?
- Okay.
- We're gonna be late.
- Come on, we gotta go.
- I'm ready, I'm ready! I heard you.
We're good. We're good.
We've got everything.
Is that mink?
Oh, no, it's rabbit.
You know, Peggy,
when I first bought it,
the woman told me that it was faux,
because it kind of looks faux.
Do you think I'm horrible?
It's nice.
Okay.
If she likes it, we should go.
We have to go.
- Okay, let's go. Bye, guys.
- Bye, sweet boy. I love you.
I love you, honey.
I'm gonna keep my kiss
right here. See you later. Bye.
- Bye, Mommy. Bye, Daddy.
- I love you, honey.
- Bye, guys!
- Bye, sweetie.
Oh, listen. You know,
I'm gonna call you every hour.
Don't worry!
- Thank you. I love you! Bye, babies!
- Bye, guys.
Okay.
Where are we going?
I thought we could go visit your chicken.
Do you wanna go see Chicken Lissie?
Yeah!
Did you see Babe, Lissie?
Yeah.
- Well, did you like it?
- Yeah.
Well, we might see Babe today.
A real Babe.
Can I pet it?
I think you can.
At the place we're going,
they rescue pigs like Babe
and chickens like yours,
and they rescue goats and cows
so they don't have to be killed
and eaten.
Isn't that nice?
If the animals didn't get eaten,
what would they do?
Well...
Come on in.
Lissie is over there. Yeah, that one.
She and a few of the others here
fell off a truck
on the way to a chicken farm
about a mile up the road.
They fell out of a truck?
Yeah, and it's a good thing, too,
because they would've been
somebody's lunch.
Before she came here,
Lissie had never
touched the ground with her feet,
or felt the sun,
or even spread her wings.
Isn't that sad?
It's just...
Goodbye! Bye!
Wow.
That woman is a saint.
And this place, this place is heaven!
This is heaven.
And there is a hell
just one mile up the road, Lissie,
and we need to see it.
We need to see it.
Because there's a holocaust
going on there right now.
They're slaughtering chickens
up there right this second.
That's a reality, Lissie.
That's a reality, and we can't ignore it.
Life isn't like Babe.
You know,
they show movies like Babe to kids,
but then they don't tell you
what happens to Babe in real life.
But you need to know.
I don't wanna go.
I don't wanna see them
hurt the chickens.
I know, and I don't either
and we're not going to.
It's okay, it's okay, it's okay.
It's okay. It's okay. Okay.
Let's go home. We're going home now.
And since
everybody's looking up at that ball,
let's take a look at this year's addition.
It's made of Waterford crystal.
It weighs in at about 1,070 pounds
and is six feet in diameter.
It contains 696 lights
and 90 rotating pyramid mirrors,
all computer-controlled,
which enables the ball
to produce a state-of-the-art light show.
It's designed to dazzle the eyes
with all kinds of colorful patterns.
Kind of like a spectacular
kaleidoscope effect
on the top of One Times Square.
The theme of this year's design is
"Forward with Harmony. "
And everybody is waiting
for that ball to drop.
Think about it.
Very, very soon
it's gonna be a brand new year.
It's so exciting.
You can hear the energy, the voices...
Unbelievable.
Lissie.
Lissie? Are you awake?
Hi.
Do you wanna go see
the ball drop with Aunt Peggy?
You want to? Just the big girls, right?
Come on, let's go.
It's almost New Year's.
Don't wake Benjy.
It really is exciting.
And now we're down to 12 seconds...
Ten, nine, eight,
seven, six, five,
four, three, two, one.
Happy New Year!
There's our big celebration party
out in Hollywood,
and there's the sidewalks of New York,
teeming with people.
One million people,
all of them happy, smiling, laughing.
What do you think of these?
I think they're mean.
I think they're mean, too.
You're sweet.
- Thank you, sis. You're the best.
- I hope it wasn't too boring.
- We so appreciated a night away.
- Really appreciate it.
- What a hot night. Amazing night.
- We needed it.
I'll call you tomorrow, okay? Drive safe.
Bye.
Newt?
Newt.
Valentine killed Buttons.
What?
It happened so fast.
We were in the back,
and he...
Newt, I'm so sorry.
It's not your fault.
It's not your fault!
Oh, my God.
It's a mess back there!
Don't go back there!
I tried to call you, but I...
I don't know.
Poor Buttons.
I'm so sorry.
Newt, where's Valentine?
The city came and picked him up.
What?
I told them to put him down.
You...
You what?
It was the only thing to do,
and I knew you couldn't do it,
so I took it out of your hands,
so you wouldn't have to carry the burden
of making that decision.
- What?
- You have to put a dog like that down.
You...
I thought we could save him,
but we couldn't!
You...
It was a mistake.
He's not even supposed to be here.
It's okay. We'll find him.
While I'm looking him up,
you can walk back.
All the animals
that were brought in today
are in this first hall.
- Down there?
- Yeah.
Ma'am,
my records indicate
the dog was involved in a mauling.
He was euthanized a few hours ago.
This is terrible.
He shouldn't have died.
Come on! Come on, boy.
Come on.
Come on, boy!
Come on!
Take it easy.
Excuse me, sir.
Where are you taking that dog?
I want that dog.
What?
I want to adopt this dog right now,
so just give me the dog.
You want this dog? Right now?
I want this dog. Give me the dog.
Hold on.
Stay, boy.
Ma'am, you're gonna have to fill out
some paperwork.
Yeah, fine. I want this dog,
and I want every single dog
you're gonna euthanize tonight.
That's 15 dogs.
Fifteen. That's great.
Yes.
Ma'am, you can't adopt 15 dogs.
The limit is three.
Well, I work for the ASPCA L.A.
I work for Newt Erdrich.
He's a client services manager.
I happen to be in the adoption program,
and I will be taking all these dogs
and placing them in adoption situations,
so I think that should be fine, then,
thank you.
Get me the dogs. Great.
Come on, you two with me.
You two with me. In the house.
Quiet! I will be right back!
Big dogs out. Come on.
No, no, big dogs out.
Out, out, out, out, out.
No! Oh, no!
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Here's some water for you.
Oh, good boys.
No fighting!
Mommy's gotta go to work.
Okay. Be good.
Oh, no. Mommy's late. Mommy's late.
You be good. Be good. Be good.
Mommy's late for work.
Peggy! Robin's been
looking for you for an hour.
He seems pretty agitated.
- Where is he?
- He's in a meeting now with Jeff.
- Hello.
- Hey, Peg?
Why didn't you tell us
you took Lissie to some animal farm
and indoctrinated her?
Well, she wanted to see
her chicken, Pier.
I thought it would be nice.
No, it's not nice. She's traumatized.
Well, I'm sorry that you feel that way.
- Traumatized, Peggy!
- No, I don't think she's traumatized.
She will not even eat
a ham sandwich now.
Well, what's so important
about eating a ham sandwich, anyway?
If she doesn't want to eat it...
You know, Peggy,
you've completely betrayed our trust!
- The furs.
- Well, I'm sorry you feel that way.
- Yeah. And Bret can't find her furs.
- What?
What, you think I stole her furs?
- Peggy, where are they?
- I have no idea!
Look, I have to go right now. I'm at work.
She hung up.
Hey, Peggy, Robin's looking for you.
What happened to you? You okay?
Peggy, I know you're
gonna be disappointed,
but it's not working out with Snowball.
He keeps peeing all over the place
and chewing up all the furniture.
- And Don, he thinks that...
- Don?
Layla, do you understand that that dog
will be loyal to you his whole life?
Don's not even loyal to you now.
Don wants to keep it.
It's me.
What do you mean,
he's not loyal to me?
What, Peggy? Say it.
I didn't mean anything.
I gotta... I gotta go.
Robin's looking for me.
So, I just got a call this morning
from a woman named
Jocelyn Kleinhoffer.
She works for
the Animal Action something.
She wanted to thank me
for my generous contribution of $200
to help prevent
the clubbing of baby seals in Canada.
I trusted you
with the most valuable thing I have,
and you stole from me.
I thought we were
on the same team, but...
I trusted you.
So what were you thinking?
You're fired.
Effective immediately.
I have not slept 10 minutes in a week!
How many dogs do you have in there?
They need a home.
Well, get them one,
so I don't have to put up with this racket.
Not now!
And do you know
how much this house stinks?
You know what? You're a jerk.
I'm telling you,
you deal with this or I will.
- Hello.
- Peggy, it's Newt.
I haven't heard from you.
Are you still mad at me?
No, I'm not mad.
What's all that noise?
My dogs.
Oh, you got new dogs? That's great.
- Where did you get them?
- From the pound.
You sound weird, Peggy.
Is everything all right?
I was just thinking, you know, just now,
my house is full of love.
I have too much love in my life.
I've never had that before.
- Come here.
- Peggy? Peggy?
Well, I want them back! I don't care!
Well, what are you gonna do with them?
Well, you know what, ma'am?
That is not good enough!
I want a record
of every one of those dogs,
and if even one of those dogs is hurt,
I am hiring a lawyer!
Who called you?
Well, you know what?
You don't have to tell me who called
because my neighbor called!
Can I have your name please, ma'am?
Can I...
Don't hang up on me!
Hello!
You ever been hunting?
It can be a rush.
You gotta be real quiet,
so you can hear a twig snap.
After hours of waiting, sometimes,
up comes a moose
or a Rocky Mountain elk.
And there's nothing like the feeling like
something's gonna happen.
You know, but it don't know.
It's just another moment in its life,
but you know it's its last,
its last moment.
And you're gonna take it.
Yeah, so then she started to hang out
with that girl Linda and Kimmy.
You know,
the one with that thing in her lip.
Oh, yeah, that piercing.
And they just had her
partying like crazy.
Bad news.
So she left Jamie after that
and decided
she wanted to be with Dale.
But Dale was in the military.
That's why she divorced him.
Then she got with Darryl.
Half-Japanese, by the way.
And then they had a kid.
Al.
I think we've been robbed.
What? What do you mean?
I think you've been robbed!
Are you crazy!
- Call 911!
- Let go of me!
...can stay downstairs.
This bedroom needs to be
painted for her.
Kind of something soothing...
Hey, Lissie, sweetie,
it's night-night time.
The lawyer thinks because
she didn't actually hurt anybody,
it's gonna be all right.
And I talked to her boss for a long time.
He says,
because of their years together,
that if she gets help
and pays what she stole,
he's willing to give her job back.
Peggy, what were you thinking?
I just wanted him to know
what it felt like to...
What it felt like to what?
To be hunted.
Oh, Peggy.
We love you.
And we're so worried about you.
We're gonna get you the help you need.
We're here for you.
Lissie.
I'm so sorry.
Why?
You love animals,
don't you, Aunt Peggy?
So do I.
This one's mean and this one's nice.
Oh, welcome back, Peggy.
There she is.
Here, Peggy. Welcome back.
You look so pretty.
I had a talk with Jeff.
He moved us to the orange team
with Brad and Denise.
I just think that's a better fit.
Denise is great with people,
Brad's good with strategy,
and I'm the numbers guy.
Snowball! No!
You'll find this amusing.
Your friend Layla couldn't find anyone
to take her dog, so I took it.
I don't know what came over me.
Momentary lapse of reason.
I hate leaving him home all day,
so I sneak him in sometimes.
I don't really like the name,
but he answers to it.
Okay, Snowball. Down. There you go.
Stay over there.
Anyway.
So where were we? Oh, yeah.
The orange team.
Hey. Guess what?
We finally have a date. June 21st.
That's great, Layla.
Yeah, it took a lot of work,
that's for sure.
And I want you to be a bridesmaid.
You wanna go to lunch? Don has plans.
You know what? I can't.
I have a lot to catch up on.
I understand. I'll talk to you later, okay?
If you all didn't think I was crazy,
I'm sure you will now.
How do I explain the things
I've said and done?
How do I explain
the person I've become?
I know I've disappointed everyone,
and I'm sorry for that.
I wish I was a more articulate person.
I believe life is magical.
It is so precious.
And there are
so many kinds of life in this life.
So many things to love.
The love for a husband or a wife,
a boyfriend or girlfriend.
The love for children.
The love for yourself.
And even material things.
This is my love. It is mine.
And it fills me and it defines me.
And it compels me on.