[eerie whispers]
Traitor...
La Llorona...
No! No!
[child screaming]
No!
[child continues screaming]
Mama...
Careful.
It's deep.
[whisper]
Ryan...
[screams]
(Radio Announcer)
New York City continues its
reported missing
over the last three weeks,
with the most recent
disappearance reported
late last night
in Spanish Harlem.
Police have received a slew
of calls from individuals
claiming responsibility
for the abductions,
all of which have
proven to be pranks.
The NYPD is releasing
no further information
at this time.
Following the advice
of investigators--
[Latin music plays]
Say queso.
Check it out.
What is this?
You fired your maid?
Yeah.
He went on vacation.
Yo, what are you doing, man?
What?
What do you mean, what?
I gotta be ready
for something like that.
Like what?
Like, I gotta strike
a pose or something.
Damn, I'm good looking, huh?
Whooaa!
Carajo, man!
It's red!
What's with you?
Sorry.
Yo!
It's green man.
Hand me a coffee.
Is that it?
That's all you have
to say to me?
It's not like,
"Welcome back from vacation.
I'm sorry your trip
got cut short."
You're worse than Vanessa.
Which one's that?
Very fuckin' funny.
Montezuma's revenge?
No.
Castro's.
I tell you, every time
I go to that place.
Damn water.
You can't live with it,
you can't live without it.
[horn honks]
It's green, man.
So what's up?
You look like shit.
Number nine.
They said eight.
Yeah, well that was yesterday.
It's killing me.
Sisters...
You're like me...
Your fingers
will scrape the bottom
of the rivers
searching for your child...
La Llorona...
And you will
cry tears of blood.
Sing with me...
Dance wth me...
Cry with me.
[door slams]
About time.
You know we're closing today.
She's asleep.
Rose is late, again.
Be here at 9:30.
Take her...
[baby crying]
[whispers]
Cry with me...
Cry with me.
[telephone rings]
Mama, you scared Bruce.
Sorry, baby.
Tell Bruce I didn't mean to.
It's okay, Bruce.
Hello?
You're seeing them again,
aren't you?
Hola, ma.
Como estas?
Running to New York.
You think that's the answer?
Where's Tonio?
Donde esta, mi nieto?
He's with me everywhere.
All the time.
Maria, come home.
Get out of there.
At least here you're safe.
Tonio's safe.
Maria, por favor.
I can't help you if you're
a thousand miles away--
(Reporter)
Ryan has blond hair
and brown
eyes, and was
last seen wearing a green
T-shirt and tan, khaki shorts.
Today's abduction makes ten
in the last three weeks.
The mayor has issued another
statement asking parents
to vigilantly watch over their
children, and repeated that
task forces are working around
the clock to find the missing
children and to safely return
them to their parents.
- Maria, what's wrong?
- Nothing.
(Reporter)
I'm getting new information.
Diane Penn is at the 3rd
Precinct where she has
some breaking news.
Diane?
(Maria)
Look, ma, I gotta go now.
(female reporter)
...where a woman
in the drowning death
of her infant child.
Is there anything
you can tell us
about the murder this morning?
Another day, trying to protect
our fellow New Yorkers.
What would cause a mother to
commit such a heinous crime?
No comment.
And what about the
boy that was just
abducted in Central Park?
Why can't the cops stop it?
We're doing all we can.
As you can see, tensions
are running very high.
I'm Diane Penn, reporting live
outside the 3rd Precinct.
Back to you, Howard.
Thank you, Diane.
Meanwhile, police continue
their search for Ryan Weit,
who was reported missing
minutes ago in Central Park.
Ryan's disappearance
is the tenth occurrence
of a child missing without...
[phone rings]
Scott, Homicide.
OK.
Interrogation room.
Look, mama, that's me.
Oh...
Why's mama crying?
Because she loves me.
That doesn't
make mama sad.
Bruce says it will.
Mama's going to cry
just like that.
- What about counsel?
- She waived.
Mrs. Harwich,
I'm Detective Alex Scott.
This is my partner,
Sergio Perez.
I understand you're
prepared to make
a full confession.
Am I correct?
You're gonna have to speak.
Yes.
Mrs. Harwich,
we're going to be
videotaping this interview.
Are there any questions
before we begin?
No.
OK.
I'm Detective Alex Scott,
presently in the 3rd Precinct
with Assistant District
Attorney Tanin,
Detective Perez.
We're about to
interview Judy Harwich,
who has waived her
rights and consented to
speak with us at this time.
Mrs. Harwich.
There was an incident
that happened
at your house this morning.
Is that correct?
Yes.
The incident we're
about to discuss
involves the death
of your daughter.
Is that correct?
Yes.
How old was your daughter?
Nine months.
Where was your husband
at the time?
Work.
When did he leave?
Eight...
Eight-thirty...
Which one is it,
Mrs. Harwich?
I...was running.
And when you came back
after your run, what happened?
I went to the bathroom.
What did you do?
I filled the bathtub.
How far did you fill it?
Three, four inches.
And then what happened?
Drowned Lisa.
And for the record,
who is Lisa?
My baby.
Why did you drown Lisa?
I...had to.
Mrs. Harwich, why did you
have to drown your daughter?
I want them to cry.
Cry...
Make them cry.
Who cry?
Rachel knows.
Rachel?
Who's Rachel?
Rachel of Rama.
I know you.
You're like me.
You want what I want.
- Enough with the games.
- Our son.
Who are you?
Answer me!
Scott, back off.
He betrayed me...
Revenge...
Make it stop.
Mrs. Harwich.
Make what stop?
The voices.
Revenge...
Give me my baby.
I killed Lisa...
I killed my baby.
Perez, quit being a dick.
Perez?
[whisper]
It's your fault.
Daddy, don't leave.
You need some Pepto?
Listen up, Perez.
You get that partner
of yours under control
or he's going
to psych evaluation.
He's just a little stressed,
that's all.
Yeah?
Who isn't?
Hey, sweetheart.
How are you doin'?
I missed you.
I was gonna call you.
I just got back.
I missed you, too.
Your wife called.
Hey.
- You all right?
- I'm fine.
What's this bullshit,
you're fine?
I'm fine.
I thought you were gonna
ram that table down her throat.
And Tanin's about to ship
you to the funny farm.
This is what
I was talkin' about.
You gotta stay focused.
They're taking Harwich
to central booking now.
San Miguel, ayudame!
San Miguel?
I should've stayed in Cuba.
[screaming]
Everything you wanted to
know about sacrificial cults.
Happy reading.
Yo, Taylor.
What do you think?
[phone rings]
Scott, Homicide.
Look, for prank calls,
call the FBI.
I'm not...crazy.
That makes one of us.
I saw you this morning...
on the street,
then TV.
I don't give out autographs,
if that's what you want.
It's just...those kids...
The ones that are missing.
What about them?
I know who it is.
You do?
You don't get it.
I see them...
when it happens.
When what happens?
You can stop it.
Look, I don't have
time for this.
I see you.
I'm gonna need
a name and a number.
Another prank call?
Where's that coffee?
Baby...
Where's your magic spray?
[child weazing]
Alex.
Where is it?
What's crawling up his ass?
Been like that
since you left, man.
Why do you think
they called you back?
What's happening?
Gotta take care of your partner.
How am I supposed
to take care of my partner
if nobody tells me
what's going on, man?
He's cracked
all the biggies.
This one's cracking him.
You didn't get them from me.
Detective Vega,
Homicide.
Suit up, Taylor.
We got another body.
Later, Perez.
Later.
"Ms. Yates described
hearing voices."
Mrs. Harwich,
why did you have
to drown your daughter?
I want to make them cry.
Cry...
Make them cry.
"Todd Scott, a 4-year-old boy,
was found dead in his apartment
by his father, Alex Scott,
a Wall Street financial analyst.
Lisa Scott, the child's mother,
is being held for questioning."
Holy shit.
I know you.
You're like me.
You want what I want.
Alex.
I hear you crying.
You can't stop me.
Answer me!
Make it stop.
Where we going?
See a friend.
Don't worry, baby.
It's gonna be OK.
That's bullshit.
Look, man, this isn't procedure.
I gotta be there.
It's personal.
What isn't?
I don't want to
get into it.
You got to get into
something sometime.
Look...
I'm gonna see him myself, OK?
Fuck it.
I gotta find a bathroom anyway.
What's it been?
Seven...eight years?
Eight.
So why now?
Today...
a woman killed her kid.
She said Rachel knows.
There was this...
these voices....
this crying.
I just think they may
have something to do
with the missing kids.
You still haven't forgiven
yourself, have you?
Todd was my son.
And Lisa was his mother.
How could you know?
Rachel cries,
like any mother
who loses her child.
Like Lisa did after
she took Todd's life,
and before she took her own.
You know what's
going on, don't you?
It's simple.
Your demons are
staring you in the face.
What are you
going to do, Alex?
I want you to see
a friend of mine.
She knows things.
Knows things?
Things the Church condemns.
Ask her about La Llorona.
What's that?
The answer.
Fear...
It's everywhere.
You can smell it
in the streets.
We got a floater.
Father.
You still have that
medal I gave you
when you made your
First Communion?
Saint Michael, Archangel,
defend us in battle.
Thank you, Father.
And thrust into Hell,
Satan and the evil spirits
who prowl the world
for the ruin of souls.
(Father)
Amen.
Don't worry, baby.
We're almost there.
You did this.
You don't want to help me.
You're with her.
You ever heard
of La Loreena?
La what?
I don't know.
It's like, La Lorena.
La Yoh-roh-na.
Yeah, I heard of her.
These Mexican kids
where I grew up,
they were obsessed with her.
Her?
Yeah.
The crying woman.
La Llorona.
Yeah, well what's her story?
Some guy cheated on her,
or something like that.
So she lost it and then...
And then what?
She drowned her kids.
Because of that
she was cursed forever.
You know these
Mexicans, man.
Their parents used to
scare the shit of us.
They used to say stuff like,
"Don't go by the river
or she'll get you."
I don't get it.
What is she?
One angry bitch.
That's what she is.
I saw your name
on the ops order.
Thought you might
want a first look.
All right, so what
are we looking at?
Some guy walking
his dog found it.
The good news is the fish
population is back.
The bad news,
there's not much left.
Perez, I hope you
have an iron stomach.
Jesus Christ.
Can't be more than
9 or 10 years old.
[whisper]
He misses you.
[phone rings]
What do you think?
Hey, Scott.
What?
You all right?
Yeah.
I'm cool.
Is it yours?
Mine?
One of your MIAs?
Hard to tell.
It was a boy.
Look.
Looks like some kind
of braided branch?
Bag it for evidence.
Have them canvas the river
a quarter-mile down.
And tell the M.E.
I want DNA yesterday.
You got it.
Daddy...
Daddy!
Making breakfast.
Yeah.
Ice cream with fudge sauce.
She's asleep.
Mommy.
It's Daddy.
Mommy!
Hey, Wall Street.
Take care of yourself.
Wall Street?
Life before Owens.
We gotta make a stop.
What's this, man?
First a priest, now a curandera?
A curandera?
What's that?
She's like a witch.
Let me guess.
Witches make
your stomach upset.
Tonio.
[phone rings]
Scott, Homicide.
Leave a message.
Detective Scott.
Meet us at the park.
The angel.
You know, this morning,
in the interrogation room.
There was something strange
going on, don't you think?
Like, you guys knew
each other already,
or you knew something like her.
You know what?
Now that I think about it,
she reminds me of my mother.
Those eyes.
And that voice.
Jesus.
You know my mom.
What do you think?
I think we should
cut down Broadway.
Yeah.
It's probably faster.
Hey.
I know.
Know what?
About you and your kid.
We're partners, man.
You know, this morning,
when that reporter asked us
why would a woman
kill her own kid?
All that shit
they must go through.
Every breath they
take must feel like
a razor slashing
into their guts.
Maybe they're just
trying to breathe.
And you?
Are you trying to breathe?
Dead people don't breathe.
After you.
[La Llorona whispers]
[conversation in Spanish]
What'd she say?
She wants to know
what took us so long.
Sit down.
Padre Joe sent me.
Amigo.
Si.
Tienes problemas, hijo?
Muchos problemas.
Show her.
Mira.
Is that witchcraft?
Es brujeria?
No.
Eso no es brujeria.
[continues speaking Spanish]
She said
stop bullshitting her
and ask what you
came here to ask her.
La Llorona.
Ahhh...
What do you--
What does she know?
[interpreting]
La Llorona is a force who
carries the deepest pain
and most vicious rage
that ever existed...
In all eternity.
The Greek Medea,
the Jewish Lilith...
The Aztec Malinche,
Lamia, also Greek.
The Crying Winds from Africa.
Rachel of Rama.
She takes on many shapes.
What shapes?
She's like the Virgin Mary,
looking for her kid...
the only one that
can stop her pain.
She's a siren getting
revenge against men
that take advantage of women.
Men like the one
that betrayed her.
She's the monster that
puts the evil eye on mothers
because she wants to be
in the company of misery -
with other Lloronas like her.
Like Death,
La Llorona is everywhere.
In all places, at all times.
Why here?
Why now?
Uh...Por que ahora?
Her kid is here.
She's looking for him.
Her kid?
Reincarnated.
For 500 years I've cried...
How do we stop her?
The mothers
that see her face,
the face of the monster -
they need to take out
the evil eye.
Agua.
She gets her power
from water.
What about the children?
Los ninos?
Close to the mother's heart,
La Llorona can't take them.
She's close.
There's not much time.
What did she say?
She finally found what
she was looking for -
Her kid.
The angel.
In the park.
Mommy?
You abandoned him.
Daddy says to call.
Did you open a new jar?
Daddy said I could.
I'm the mother.
I'll put it back.
It's too late.
You're dirty.
Go wash.
[speaking Spanish]
Gracias.
I give life...
I take life.
Maria...
Walk with me.
See what I see.
Maria!
[screaming]
Aye, Maria!
[crying, speaking Spanish]
[answering machine beeps]
Detective Scott...
Meet us at the park...
the Angel.
I'll go this way.
[woman crying]
You have reached
the office of Alex Scott,
Senior Financial Analyst
at Green Brothers Capital.
Leave a message
at the tone or press pound
to reach Mr. Scott's assistant.
[machine beeps]
Daddy.
It's me.
Can you come early?
Something's wrong...
I think mommy's mad at me.
Come home daddy, OK?
- What are you doing?
- I got you, man.
- I could have shot you.
- But you didn't.
Let's get out of here.
There's nothing around here.
No, there's something
around here.
Like dead fish.
Look familiar?
Yeah...
It does.
[scream]
Alex...
Alex?
I don't wanna stay
with mommy.
Can I go over to grandma's?
Please.
I can take my bike.
Daddy...
Do you still love me?
Bye, daddy.
Yo!
Perez, there's a kid.
Ten-four.
Police!
Don't move!
I said don't move!
Are you OK?
I'm telling you man...
followed me around
for two days.
Two days...
Just gettin' closer
and closer.
So what'd you do?
Help me!
Please.
Hey.
What's wrong?
She's out--
Calm down.
- Let him take the boy.
- She's out there!
Nobody's out there.
Just breathe.
Breathe.
Nobody's gonna hurt ya.
No.
Please.
Just tell me how
to get out of here.
Just leave some for me.
Come back here you bitch!
What the hell...
[screams]
Alex...
I know you.
[boy screaming]
Baby?
He's mine...
Perez.
La Llorona.
Just hold on.
You're gonna be okay.
I'm gonna get help...
Just, stay there.
You're gonna be okay.
Ten-thirteen.
Officer down.
Underneath the...fuck!
Underneath the tunnel,
underneath East Park Drive.
Need assistance!
Perez.
Please!
Anyone!
Help!
I have my son!
Police!
Put the kid down!
Stop!
And put the kid down!
Help.
I can't help you
until you put the kid down!
Get your hands
off the kid!
No, she's here!
Let...him...go!
Help us.
It's okay, mama.
Let me go.
Don't move!
I have to hold him.
She can't hurt you
if you're not afraid.
Lady!
I said don't move!
You have to help him.
She's here.
Who's here?
She wants him - my baby.
What are you talking about?
She's real.
You know she's real.
He's mine.
- Who are you?
- I have to hold him.
Stop!
I said stop!!
Tonio?
Where is he!
Tonio!
Daddy...
Where is he?
Tell me!
You're like me...Cursed.
Don't listen.
[boy screams in distance]
Alex...
You killed him.
[man screaming]
Tonio!
Maria...
Cry with me.
Stop!
No! No!
[child screaming]
[Maria screaming]
[Tonio screams]
You're next!
Subtitles by LeapinLar