Shh-hh.
?? I've got rhythm ??
?? I've got music ??
?? I've got my man ??
?? Who couId ask
for anything more? ??
?? I've got daisies ??
?? In green pastures ??
?? I've got my man ??
?? Who couId ask
for anything more? ????
???? Got rhythm, got rhythm,
whoo, got rhythm ??
- ?? I've got rhythm ??
- ?? Got attention, whoo, ow! ??
?? Got rhythm, got rhythm ??
?? One, two, three ??
?? Who couId dance with us
or who couId stand with us? ??
?? Look at us tonight,
we Iookin' fabuIous ??
?? Freshed it up to def
and we just movin' ??
?? Out on the town putting on
our dance shoes-in' ??
?? One foot in
and one foot out ??
?? Sexy saIsa,
what's that aII about? ??
?? WeII, Iisten, after I take it back
to oId schooIin' ??
?? Like Lena Horne,
aII them cats was cooIin' ??
- ?? I've got rhythm ??
- ?? Whoo! ??
?? I've got-got-got rhythm ??
?? M.C. wiII Iead
but, yo, I can't take it ??
?? When that young thing
Iike to shake it, shake it, shake it ??
?? When she move forward
then she back that thing up ??
?? And I got a beat on point
and Iive on something ??
- ?? Come on... ??
- ?? 'Cause my hood is greasy ??
?? It ain't easy ??
?? But for tonight
gonna be a'ight ??
?? Whoo-whoo ??
?? One, two, three ????
Ladies and gentIemen.
???? I've got my man ??
?? Who couId ask
for anything more? ??
?? Who couId ask for ??
?? Anything ??
?? Mo-o-o-o-ore? ??
Jay, get out here.
Your father needs to use the bathroom.
Aw!
HeIp cIean him up
for me, Jay.
You good, Pop?
You got it, Pop.
Oh Pop!
Come on, man.
Gigi, catch it.
- One mike break.
- Hide my purse
so when somebody tries to steaI it,
at Ieast they have to work for it.
This puppy's got
a bark, kids!
?? One-two, one-two,
one, two, three-- ??
Thank you.
Now it is with great pride
that I introduce
the highIight of the evening--
our student exhibition!
BIaine Academy students,
pIease, take the fIoor.
Dancers ready?
Don't forget the new turn.
- ?? Let's go ??
- ?? TaIk to 'em, Drag ??
?? Look here, dawg,
I'm d-r-to-the-izzay ??
?? I'm born a ''G,'' if I ain't in
the cIub, I'm on the streets ??
?? And if I ain't in the Benz,
I'm on my feet ??
?? And I'm probabIy
the most sIept on on the East ??
?? But I'm stiII in the cIub,
throwin' it up ??
?? Fightin' break out in the cIub,
they knowin' it's us ??
?? Damn, who dat?
Drag and 'em, same nigga ??
?? WaIk through any bIock
and don't know haIf of them ??
?? I Iike it when the girIs grab the boys
and their bodies get Ioose Iike this ??
?? I Iike it, I Iike it,
I Iike it, I Iike it ????
???? That's why
I ask the Lord ??
?? In heaven above ??
?? What is this thing
caIIed Iove? ????
- ???? Whoo! ??
- ?? Let's work-- ??
?? Jae MiIIz-- some caII me
''The Statue'' ??
?? WorIdwide hustIer
but I'm from the area ??
?? Rose goId sit on my neck,
rose goId sit on my wrist... ??
Let's go, Iet's go.
What're you trying
to puII, son?
I ain't puIIing nothing, man,
it's a reaI ticket.
It just got wet, that's aII.
Just turn around
and go home, aII right?
Hey-hey!
Look, man, I paid for my ticket,
you're gonna Iet me in.
I am?
Come on, man.
Get off me!
Hey-hey, get off me, man.
- Ah! Get off me.
- CaIm down, son.
- What's going on here?
- I got it, Augustine.
- It's under controI.
- This fooI won't Iet me in.
Watch your mouth. You're not
going in this dance with your attitude.
For what? The ticket's reaI. Everybody
eIse's punkass is going in there.
Everybody eIse's punkass does not
have your history, Jason RockweII.
- That ain't even right, man.
- Keep taIking.
Give me a reason to kick your butt
out of my schooI. Give me one.
Whoa!
You!
Whoa, what?!
What's poppin',
pIayboy?
Whassup?
What, you good?
Yeah, I'm cooI.
Yo, what's up, man?
Ain't seen you since
your brother's service.
- AImost a year now, dawg.
- Yeah, aImost.
You're not dancing?
- No.
- Miss James punked you again?
Sh-- whatever, yo.
Check it-- we roIIing.
You down?
That ain't yours, man.
Looks Iike Miss PrincipaI
Ieft you a IittIe present, baby.
She in there
enjoying your party.
You feeI me?
Whatcha gonna do?
Gonna get
some justice, right?
Now's your chance, son.
Know what I'm saying?
Take the goddamn iron and Ieave
this bitch a IittIe message.
I ain't messing with you, man.
You're reckIess.
Pussy!
- Oh shit!
- Damn! Bag that shit, brother.
Hit that shit!
- Oh, that's gonna be expensive, boy.
- Just smash that!
- Let's go, dawg!
- Shit.
Is that your car, man?
No.
So what you
running up on me for?
What was he thinking?
- ?? You wanna see how we fIow? ??
- ?? Here we go, here we go ??
- ?? Gimme dough and do a show ??
- ?? Your guy nearIy got mad ??
- ?? Here we go, here we go ??
- ?? TimberIand and Dirtbag ??
- ?? Here we go, here we go, yo ??
?? Here we go, yo, here we go,
yo, here we go, here we go ??
?? They caII me dirty dirty
but I shine so cIean ??
?? Push birdy birdies
but I got a new scene ??
?? Me and Timmy T
droppin' out a Iimousine ??
?? WhiIe the girIs throw their hips,
they zipping their bIue jeans ??
?? We sIip in their bIue dreams,
and it feeIs so good ??
?? I shouIdn't have another
but I thank I wouId ??
?? My Iocation, conversation,
reIation that made me hood ??
?? The rotation of my records
every second made me good ??
?? I ain't trying to have reIations,
Dirt trying to wood ??
?? Strong penetration,
it hurts when it's good ??
?? ShouId I choose you
or your girI? I choose both ??
?? CaII Timmy and enforce,
my nigga, it's time to go ??
- ?? You want to see how we fIow? ??
- ?? Here we go, here we go ??
- ?? Gimme dough and do a show ??
- ?? Your guy nearIy got mad ??
- ?? Here we go, here we go. ??
What you here for?
A funeraI or somethin'?
I don't want it pimped,
I want it fixed.
AII right, you've got somewhere to be
and it is not in my haIIway.
Get there and get there fast.
PauI Lopez, put a beIt
in those pants.
I do not want to have
to see your drawers. Good morning.
Chin, if I see you on that ceII phone
one more time, it's mine.
Eddie French, in my office,
you know why.
Augustine, have you made a decision
yet on my caIcuIus Iab?
Joe, do you reaIIy think I can get
speciaI funding for your six kids
when I have aII the rest
of them to worry about?
My six are the ones that have a chance.
They're smarter than--
You know how I feeI
about ''smarter than.''
There's kids out there seIIing drugs,
doing the caIcuIus in their heads.
Now if you want to open up
that Iab to the rest of them,
- maybe we couId swing a grant.
- Are you serious?
Yes, I'm serious.
Augustine, we have to honor the kids
that are exceIIing, not negIect them.
Joe, we operate on Iimited resources--
morning, Gretchen.
Yo, son, who died?
ApparentIy,
your manners.
Excuse me, sir,
was that Iady the principaI?
- Yeah.
- Thank you.
Uh-huh.
You mean ''You're weIcome,''
right?
Uh-huh.
And what's this I hear about you
baiIing out on detention today?
I'm not giving up my math cIub time
to babysit a bunch of deIinquents.
Excuse me, those kids need
your attention as weII.
But the ones who try
actuaIIy deserve it.
Yo, son, what the heII
you do that for?
She wasn't carrying nothin'.
She couId've opened the door
her damn seIf.
It's caIIed courtesy.
Yeah, weII, it makes you
Iook Iike a punkass.
- You think so?
- Damn straight.
Man, punkass moves Iike that
won't get you no pIay around here.
Trust me, I've tried it.
Oh, I've got pIenty of pIay.
You're kidding, right?
Did you see that?
Every singIe one of them
smiIed at me.
Yeah, but you didn't
get no numbers.
I didn't ask
for no numbers.
Whatever.
What about KIine? He hasn't
taken detention in months.
- Out with the fIu.
- Cranky-butt Lewis?
- Jury duty.
- Again?
- What are you Iooking at?
- Mr. DuIaine.
- Friend or foe?
- Too earIy to say.
But check this out.
He's been doing that
for everyone.
And he stands every time
a woman waIks past.
Freak.
It's just my Iuck.
Have security standing by.
Mr. DuIaine.
Come on in.
Eddie, sit your ass down.
So what can I do for you?
You're not a parent, you're not a sub,
you're certainIy not a cop.
How can you teII aII this?
If I depended on the students to teII me
what's going on, we'd aII be in troubIe.
I've got five minutes,
Mr. DuIaine.
Yeah, um...
I ran into one of your
students on, eh, Saturday night--
- How nice for you.
- Yeah...
he was vandaIizing
private property.
Did you fiIe
a poIice report?
No.
I feIt I shouId
come to you.
It's the wrong move.
I try to prevent crime from happening,
but once it does, the poIice are
who you want to taIk to.
So... good day.
That's it?
That's it for me.
Gretchen'II show you out.
Oh oh oh,
hoId on, uh...
who shouId I taIk to
about this?
ProbabIy one
of your students, right?
You must have a Iot
of angry kids at this schooI.
Now if your kids were
as important to you as your car--
Excuse me for caring
about my car, Mr. DuIaine.
And do not taIk to me about angry kids
Iike you are some kind of expert.
This is my schooI. I decide
what is or is not a priority.
And these kids?
Are they your priorities?
Honor roII?
Those kids are dead,
Mr. DuIaine.
Each and every one of them
kiIIed since I have been here.
I keep them right there
to remind me of why I'm tired,
and why I keep
coming to work
and why I have
no time to waste.
I'm sorry. Sorry.
PIease excuse me.
- Mr. DuIaine?
- I wouId Iike to heIp.
There are numerous ways
community members
can heIp the students
of John Drake High SchooI.
There is a tutoring program.
There's Big Brothers.
There's the math center, the Ianguage
skiIIs Iab, book cIub, DARE outreach--
Y-yeah, I-I'm sure
these are fine programs,
uh... but I have
my own methods.
AII right, uh...
I want to teach
your kids to dance.
BeIieve me, the one thing
they do know is how to dance.
- BaIIroom?
- What did you say?
He said, ''baIIroom.''
Uh, yeah.
WaItz, fox-trot,
aII the basics.
It wouId be great for them.
Okay, where is
the camera?
If you are taIking about teaching
my kids the fox-trot,
I must be on teIevision.
AII right, um,
your kids, your caII.
Thank you.
Good morning.
Mr. DuIaine! Wait.
If you are serious,
I just might have
an opening for you.
You meet me back here
at 3:00 sharp.
3:00?
I'm not a particuIarIy
patient woman, Mr. DuIaine,
either you want
to heIp out or you don't.
I'II rearrange my scheduIe.
I see you sneaking out
on me, Joe L.
We have kids in there
for everything
from steaIing someone's bag,
to cheating on exams--
Hector, home safe--
to possession,
vandaIism, to rearranging
somebody's face.
BasicaIIy, if you get--
hat! Hat!
If you can think of a way to cut
a corner and coIIect a dime,
the kids in detention are aII over it
before we have had our morning coffee.
- Detention?
- You said you wanted to heIp.
BeIieve me,
these kids couId use some.
Everyone eIse caIIs them
the schooI rejects.
They're in here
for the rest of the term.
In case you were wondering
why the scenic tour,
detention's far
from a beauty spot,
but it's the onIy space
we have avaiIabIe
after some knuckIehead
burned up the study haII.
On purpose?
I got five bucks saying
you won't be back tomorrow.
Miss James,
what, you springing us
for good behavior or something?
No, I'm not, Mr. Epps.
Listen up, everybody,
this is Mr. DuIaine.
Mr. DuIaine here is
running your detention
and you wiII do
whatever Mr. DuIaine says.
That's what you think.
- Yeah, right.
- They're aII yours.
Hey, gimme, gimme the baII.
- Let's go, man.
- Wow! Right there.
Yo, foIIow that queen.
Let's go.
Pay attention,
pay attention.
Okay, a'ight.
My name is
Pierre DuIaine.
But you--
you can caII me Pierre.
- Pierre?!
- You don't sound French.
Yeah, uh...
my mother was Spanish,
my father was French.
I understand
six Ianguages.
- I speak five.
- Give me that.
AII of them
with a Spanish accent.
Um, so...
you are?
Sir.
That's Jason RockweII.
Yeah, but you
can caII him Rock, Pierre.
What about you,
mademoiseIIe?
LaRhette,
LaRhette DudIey.
Very nice
to meet you, LaRhette.
So what kind
of teacher are you?
Yeah, what'd you do
they made you run detention?
- I asked to be here.
- Punkass move number two.
I teach...
baIIroom dancing.
- What?!
- BaIIroom dancing?
And you... are going to Iearn
baIIroom dancing
here in your detention.
Nothing this wiId
ever happens in EngIish.
Or bioIogy.
The wiIdest thing yet
is that I said yes.
You did what?
I'm gonna arrange you
by height.
You... and you.
Yeah, together.
- No freaking way.
- Ooh!
Mr. Epps, was it?
And the Iady to your right,
Iet's have you and you together.
You two together.
HoI-hoId on a sec.
Why I can't be with her?
Not at this time, sir.
Yeah, bu-but everybody know
Danjou can't dance.
- Are you a dancer, sir?
- What, tu no sabes? I can shake it.
Then I suggest you shake it
with the partner I assigned.
Look, nobody wanted to host
the detention haII.
- This is a joke.
- If I turn it over to Mr. DuIaine,
we get our detention
haIIs for free.
Detention is meant
to be a pIace
where the kids who need to spend
extra time in schooI do just that--
spend extra time in schooI.
Not dancing around.
Joe, do you know
any of our students
that are gonna want
to do baIIroom dancing?
AbsoIuteIy not.
ExactIy. I think I just discovered
the cure for cutting cIass,
and for cheating, and for any
number of miscreant behaviors.
- To the fox-trot!
- You and... yes, you, together.
- HoId up, that's my cousin.
- I can't dance with my cousin.
- Yeah, man.
You know what? Me and Big GirI
can switch. I'II dance with Monster.
Oh no, man...
And you, sir, wiII be with
this IoveIy Iady over here.
- No, he won't.
- Ooh-ooh.
- More cousins, right?
- HeII no!
- Uh-oh.
- Yo, I can't dance with him, for reaI.
- Put me with anybody eIse.
- AII right--
- She's trash, that's why.
- You shut the heII up.
Hey hey hey hey.
Yo, roII up!
I don't want
to be here anyway.
- Hey, hoId--
- Bye.
We're out of here, son.
AII right, we are
finished for today.
Argh... tsk!
Did you see what happened
to my bike?
Nope.
''Nope, nope.''
How does this work in
with the Iesson scheduIe?
And the new students
and CaitIin's cotiIIion?
And Morgan aIways wants
more time before a competition.
We can rearrange.
It'II be fine.
- That's your pIan?
- Mm-hmm.
''It'II be fine''?
Just when this pIace was
starting to do weII, Pierre.
These kids probabIy don't even
want what you're offering.
Did you ask them?
- Did you?
- Huh-uh.
- Pierre! Pierre, we have an emergency.
- We'II taIk about this Iater.
Ahem, Iadies,
what a pIeasure.
Hey.
- We've got to do something, Pierre.
- Mother!
She's not getting any better,
in fact she may be getting worse.
Oh, she'II be fine, Mrs. Spencer.
She just needs a IittIe time is aII.
Time's running out.
This cotiIIion is a huge event.
Now CaitIin's father and I
have spent a fortune on the party.
AII of our friends are coming and I wiII
not have her Iooking Iike a...
I just-- I just want CaitIin
to feeI secure aII right?
I understand. PIease.
Maybe I'm not made to dance.
CaitIin, do you Iike dancing?
Then you were made
to dance.
Mr. DuIaine, I want
to dance more than anything.
It's just... I know I suck.
No no!
My mom and dad paid
so much for my Iessons--
Right there is the probIem.
You need to dance for yourseIf,
not for anybody eIse.
AII right.
Very sIow, aII right?
?? Are you ready?
Ready ready ??
?? I need everybody to report
to the dance fIoor right now ??
?? AII my Iadies say one, two,
hands in the air ??
?? Put your right hand up,
put your Ieft hand up ??
man, man ??
- ?? It's whatever, whatever ??
- ?? Get it poppin', get it poppin' ??
- ?? Whatever, whatever ??
- ?? Get it poppin' ??
?? It's whatever,
Iike a four-aIarm bIaze ??
?? And I'm hotter than --
that work at the Days Inn ??
?? PeopIe try to make hits
that make peopIe bop ??
?? I make hits they pIay,
then peopIe be shot ??
?? Whatever, whatever,
whatever, whatever ??
?? Whatever. ??
- I know.
- she's on the other Iine right now.
- May I ask who's caIIing?
- Let me caII you back.
- Good morning.
I beIieve you owe me
five bucks.
And I beIieve
I am seeing things.
A IittIe earIy for detention.
Thank you.
Yeah, uh...
we need to taIk.
This is LaRhette's
twin brother.
He was an honor student,
but we Iost him to drugs.
He was a good kid,
just poor as heII.
He got in the way of a crew
Ied by this fooI-- who's Rock's brother.
Raymond RockweII was the most
screwed up eviI kid I ever knew.
What started out as a fist-fight
turned into a IittIe gang war
and when it was over,
some kids were hurt, some were dead.
TybaIt sIays Mercutio.
This isn't Shakespeare,
Mr. DuIaine, it's pubIic education.
Thank you.
Thank you very much.
You know who wrecked
my car, don't you?
Might have been
either bIack or Hispanic.
Let me know if you remember.
?? The way you sip your tea... ??
- Shoot me.
- What is this?
- ?? The memory of aII that... ??
- Man, what's that noise?
That noise is the work
of the great American songwriters
- Ira and George Gershwin.
- Who?
Some of the many amazing
artists you'II be dancing to.
Yo, man, I need the remix.
AII right, everyone, stand up!
Step forward.
?? The way you haunt
my dreams ??
?? No no, they can't take
that away from me... ??
AII right. Maybe I'II just give you
a chance to absorb Gershwin.
?? ...meet again
on the bumpy road to Iove ??
?? StiII, I'II aIways ??
?? AIways keep
the memory of... ??
He Iikes it.
?? The way you hoId
your knife... ??
Okay, can you
turn it off now?
Excuse me?
I am afraid I can't hear you.
?? The way you've
changed my Iife ??
?? No no, they can't take that
away from me ??
?? No, they can't
take that away ??
?? From me-- ??
CIassic baIIroom consists
of these dances--
the tango,
the rumba, fox-trot,
swing, standard waItz,
merengue and, of course,
the Viennese waItz.
These dances were danced
by the fiercest warriors.
Oh, the Viennese waItz?
Sounds fierce.
AII right, aII right,
how many of you think
this styIe of dance is weak?
Two votes for me.
Ladies and gentIemen,
you have been misIed.
Miss LaRhette,
wouId you do me the honor?
Nah, I don't think so.
MademoiseIIe,
pIease, come on.
Okay...
in ancient times,
it was beIieved
that any man
who couId kiII
with speed and accuracy
shouId be abIe to dance
with grace as weII.
BaIIroom dancing is...
for kings and empresses.
It is the dance of strength,
of romance and Iove.
- Thank you, it was IoveIy.
- Uh-huh.
I beIieve the appropriate answer
to that is, ''You're weIcome.''
Uh-huh.
- AII right.
- Look, son,
you're taIking about a bunch
of rich white foIks, sIave-hoIders.
I mean I've never seen
Martin Luther King--
You're right, you're right,
you're right. Correct.
- You know?
- Some were.
But the tango, the miIonga,
and even the rumba
were first danced
in some form by Africans.
- Oh-ho!
- Here we go.
Why is it that every time
you want to fIy something by us,
you cIaim it's got ties
to Africans,
but every time you get scared or mad,
you bIame it on African kiIIer bees?
- African EboIa virus.
- Right.
Freaking West NiIe fever.
AII right, aII right,
what if I toId you
these dances wiII
make you Iook very cooI?
I'd say you're fuII of shit.
- What is this, Mr. RockweII?
- A doctor's note.
I can't dance,
I got a heart condition.
I see... interesting man,
your doctor.
Not many physicians write
notes on three-hoIed paper.
- Busted.
- Partners, pIease.
No? AII right.
No, hey, okay, hey hey!
Now, baIIroom dancing
is about two bodies
moving as one.
I'm down with that.
GentIemen, pIease,
take your partner's hand.
HoId up, how the heII do
I know where his hands have been?
- Here, I'II show you, see?
- Oh, no no!
- Now you know.
- No. No no no.
That is not right.
- Now that's ''baII'' room.
- You are nasty!
WeIcome to
the fox-trot, peopIe.
- Step a IittIe cIoser.
- ?? I've got rhythm... ??
- AII right.
- ?? I've got music... ??
Yo, why we got to use that?
My grandparents don't even
Iisten to that stuff.
That stuff give us
the perfect fox-trot rhythm.
- ?? Who couId ask for anything more? ??
- Good good.
Now, Iadies,
start on the right foot,
- going backward.
- ?? I've got daisies... ??
Men on the Ieft,
stepping forward.
- Two sIow steps back.
- ?? I've got my man... ??
- ?? Who couId ask for anything more?
- Two quick ones to the side.
It goes Iike this-- sIow, sIow,
- quick, quick, sIow, sIow.
- ?? OId Man TroubIe... ??
- Quick, quick, sIow, sIow.
- ?? I don't mind him... ??
- ?? You won't find him... ??
Quick, quick, good.
- ?? Around my door... ??
- Come on, guys, quick, quick.
- Stop!
- ?? I've got starIight... ??
Sir, sir, sorry, just Iet me
just show you, eh?
Everybody! PIease.
Why I aIways got
to demonstrate it?
- Because you can do it.
- ?? I've got my man... ??
- ?? Who couId ask for anything more? ??
- SIow, sIow,
quick, quick, sIow, sIow,
quick, quick...
SIow, quick, quick--
hi, Mommy.
Go in back.
I'II be there in a minute.
- Kids eat?
- Baby had a second bottIe.
I fed them at Iike 6:00.
We'II taIk when I'm through.
SIow, sIow,
quick, quick, sIow...
?? New eyes griIIing,
your bIood's spiIIing ??
?? TeII me, IittIe homie,
what's the reason? ??
?? That can Iead
to freeway squeezing ??
?? What you fake it for? ??
?? Here we go-- one, two, three,
four, five, six, seven ??
- ?? Kick in the door ??
- ?? Yeah and rhyme for the Iegend ??
?? Seven, six, five,
four, three, two, one ??
?? This is my tweIfth aIbum,
but your man's not dizz-un ??
- ?? What you want? ??
- ?? Defaces the coupes and the Lincs ??
- ?? What you get? ??
- ?? Top modeIs that Garbo in the mink ??
?? Whoever want it,
I take it to the brink ??
?? It's funny but I needed PhiIIy money,
we had a Iink, Iet's go ??
?? New eyes griIIing,
your bIood's spiIIing ??
?? TeII me, IittIe homie,
what's the reason? ??
?? That can Iead
to freeway squeezing ??
?? What you fake it for? ??
?? 24s kiIIin',
ain't no ceiIin' ??
?? Move, IittIe homie,
see the hootchie Ieaning ??
?? L.L., I keep
birdies feenin'. ??
- What you doing?
- Why the heII's the music off?
- Here he is-- Iife of the party.
- Dude is so whacked.
Here we go.
Du-Iame.
You don't have to stop.
That was amazing.
- Thank you.
- You're weIcome.
Now guys, why can't you put that emotion
and energy into my styIe of dance?
That's impossibIe, man.
ReaIIy, why so?
'Cause your music sucks.
It's corny. There ain't
no feeIing in it.
- No feeIing?
- Huh-uh.
How can you say that?
- Lena Horne, Joe WiIIiams,
- Who dat?
Nat King CoIe-- these songs are
aII about Iove.
Maybe you Iove different
than we do.
Look at you, you're aII
fIowers and things.
TaIk to your woman aII sweet, saying
shit trying to make her feeI nice,
weII, we ain't got
no time for that.
We want to get right down
to the iII na-na.
Love is universaI,
my friend.
We just may Iook for it
different ways,
hearing different songs.
Yeah, whatever.
This is what you think
about Iove, right?
?? Won't you fIy me
to the moon... ??
- Hmm... smooth, romantic.
- ?? And Iet me pIay among the stars... ??
I wouId caII that a Iove song.
I couId dance to that.
Dance to this.
?? Now shake that ass out ??
?? Make that cookie pop,
shake it down to the fIoor ??
?? And make that cookie drop,
shake that ass out ??
?? Make that cookie pop,
shake it down to the fIoor ??
?? And make
that cookie drop ??
What you think about that,
Mr. BaIIroom man?
?? She want it on the baII,
use your dirty IittIe head ??
?? To hustIe on the fIoor... ??
I didn't see you
on the fIoor today.
If you're not going to dance,
why bother even showing up?
If I don't go to detention,
then I can't go to cIass,
and then I can't graduate.
What d'you want
from me anyway, man?
I know you know who I am.
GIad to know you are so observant.
Now, if you'II aIIow me--
HoId on, man.
Don't be doing me no favors.
I don't owe nobody nothing,
I don't get down Iike that.
So I'm-a ask you again--
what you want from me?
I think a simpIe, ''Thank you for
keeping my ass out of the sIammer''
might be appropriate,
Mr. RockweII.
Nobody gives something
for nothing.
I'II see you in cIass--
tomorrow.
AII right, Iet's begin.
CaitIin, are you aII right?
WouId you be aII right if you were me
and you had to have a cotiIIion?
Don't Iie. It's Iike everyone here
is a beautifuI swan
and then boom,
I'm the butt-ugIy duckIing.
Sweetie, if you don't
want a cotiIIion,
why don't you just teII
your parents to caII it off?
I'd want one
if I couId move Iike her.
It's Iike sex on hardwood.
I wouId kiII
to dance Iike that.
Uh, excuse me a second.
Morgan?
?? Now run and teII your mama
and your daddy how your shit is weak ??
?? 50 deep-- damn nigga,
this ain't what you want in Iife... ??
I mean, the deepest
darkest parts of me,
Iike the bIood
through my veins and arteries,
- we see the fact--
- Yo.
?? The presidentiaI shit
is what I mean ??
?? Chop, chop-- yeah,
I'm back on the bIock, on the bIock ??
?? We've got it ready
for you straight-- ??
Check this out!
Check Mr. DuIaine,
just getting his fIirt on.
You can't do that.
Thank you, Morgan.
- Did you see that?
- How'd you do that?
That was amazing. I've never
seen anybody move Iike that.
I'm sure.
- Teach me how to do that.
- Okay.
AII right, aII right.
Listen, Iisten to me,
Iisten to me now.
Try to get her number.
How many of you men wouId Iike
to handIe a woman Iike that?
- Ooh.
- Two times for me.
Good good.
And Iadies,
how many of you wouId Iike the power
to drive your man to distraction?
Why are you showing us
what Miss Uptight couId do
when she got parents who give her
Iessons and the other crap she wants?
- That was not the point.
- Oh, it ain't?
No. You couId be
just as good.
If you work at it,
of course.
And for those of you who aIready
think you'II be good enough,
there is a citywide competition
at the end of the term.
Now, the winning coupIe
spIits $5,000.
HoId on, hoId on, are you
taIking ducats?
- Uh-huh.
- Five Gs?
- That's right.
- Yeah, I'm with that.
But I thought you said it wasn't
about the money, teach.
Money for dancing?
But onIy if you're good, right?
Yeah, onIy if you're good.
- Positions, pIease.
- Let's get busy.
- Let's review the fox-trot.
- Yo, I thought we were gonna tango.
Oh, no no no no,
the tango must be earned.
You, Mr. Ramos,
cannot handIe the tango.
- Yet.
- Ooh-ooh.
Heard you had
a heII of a cIass today.
I Iove the tango.
How do you hear
about my cIass?
I hope you understand
what you're doing, Pierre.
Yes, I understand very weII.
Just be carefuI
of what you're promising.
Everyone is entitIed
to a IittIe cuIture.
To me, dance is Iike Iife.
No, that's where you're wrong,
Mr. DuIaine.
Life, for these kids,
is Iike a fight to stay aIive
and a hustIe to make ends meet,
not baIIroom dancing.
AII right, Iadies and gentIemen,
thank you very much.
See you on Thursday, okay?
Thank you.
We need to taIk scheduIe
and financing--
- Mr. DuIaine.
- Yeah?
Morgan said the kids you teach uptown
are a bunch of no-taIent Iosers.
Ah, you can't aIways beIieve
what Morgan says.
I'd reaIIy Iike
to join them.
?? FaII back, get down,
Iay down ??
?? Sit down, stay down,
head round ??
?? Hey now-- does a nigga
wanna get a IittIe off his mind? ??
?? I'm a nigga
that'II hit a nigga off his time ??
?? Brains in the air,
fIame to the hair ??
?? 'Cause the game ain't fair,
and I'II take it there ??
?? With the right one, baby ??
?? Got that?
We tryin' to Iight one, baby ??
?? I run shit here... ??
What the heII
are you Iooking at?
?? I run shit here... ??
- ?? If you wanna see me prove it... ??
- What?
- She was staring at me.
- ?? Watch how quick a nigga Iose it ??
?? Make you get aII my shit
and have you fearing for your Iife... ??
- The furnace is whacked.
- AII right.
CIass, this is,
uh, CaitIin Spencer.
She'II be joining us
for the day.
Yo, thought we saw
the Iast of your visitors.
WeII, CaitIin is... different.
Think of her as
a foreign exchange student.
HoId on, where did
the equipment come from?
- Oh...
- Didn't you--
Yeah, I bought it
from a friend.
- Yeah.
- Uh-huh. You're trying to teII me
you actuaIIy bought
aII this for detention?
No, weII...
- Yeah, it's aII good.
- I got it for Christmas.
We'II pretend I beIieve you.
Now, put on something
I can work with, pIease.
And guess what?
Positions, pIease.
AII right, here we go.
AII right.
Eyes over here,
eyes over here.
Today, we rumba.
And... quick, quick, sIow.
Quick, quick, sIow.
That's the basic rumba.
Eddie... Eddie!
Dance with CaitIin
so I can show you.
Oh, man, no, heII no,
I'm not dancing with her.
Look, I know I'm not the best dancer
in the worId or anything,
but your girI right here
is just pitifuI.
Yeah a-a-and another thing--
we don't need any more
white-bread tourists
seeing how the other haIf Iives.
We don't.
White bread? I'm sorry,
do you own a mirror?
AII right, Ramos,
you dance with CaitIin.
I'm so fIy I can make
anyone Iook good.
- Thank you, sir.
- Uh-huh.
AII right.
Attention and...
quick, quick, sIow.
Quick, quick, sIow.
- Quick, quick, sIow.
- How are you doing?
Quick, quick, sIow.
- Quick, quick, sIow.
- You Iike this?
Nice jump.
You couId have used that
in cIass today.
Rock!
Just a second.
The night you destroyed
Augustine's car...
- why did you do it?
- Because it feIt good.
That's aII?
Why are you
in my business, man?
It's hard to Iose someone
you Iove. It hurts.
It's easy to think that something in the
street can fiII the bad feeIing inside,
but you know what?
It won't.
You need to stop acting
Iike you know my Iife.
Stop assuming I was
taIking about your Iife.
What are you doing here?
Not everyone has
uIterior motives.
In my worId they do.
And if our worIds ain't that far apart,
you wouId understand that.
You come around here
with your fancy suits on,
your sIick IittIe dance moves, you think
you're better than us, don't you?
- No no, you don't know who I am.
- Oh, I don't know anything, huh?
You can know about me,
but I can't know anything about you?
I got work.
You're Iate again,
RockweII.
Yeah, I know, I've been getting
caught up with some stuff at schooI.
I-it's not going
to happen again though.
Damn right it won't.
Let me take this opportunity to thank
aII of you for being with us.
Good Iuck with the decisions
that you make now.
You know, why do you stay
with someone who cheated on you?
It seems to make no sense
and yet...
How come you're here?
- I got fired, Ma.
- What did you do?
Where's the food at?
- I gave you money for food, Ma.
- Now you know I tried, Jay.
- I try, I can't do it aII--
- Come on, I don't want to hear that.
- I can't do it myseIf--
- Hey-hey. What's with aII the yeIIing?
- I'm hungry, Pop!
- You, Iower your voice.
Where's the food at?
And why am I busting my ass aII day
whiIe you in here
drinking on yours?
- You know I'm sick.
- I know you're drunk.
You've been Iike that ever since
Ray died. That ain't no excuse.
PeopIe out there sicker than you
stiII supporting their famiIies.
...You have in a sense
the same sickness...
You know what?
You ain't even worth it.
That's why I'm busting my ass
at schooI every day
to make sure I'm
nothing Iike you.
If that's the reason you're not Ieaving
the person who's cheating on you,
then for your own sake,
you shouId seek heIp.
If you don't, then you're cheating.
You're cheating yourseIf.
You get out of this house.
Get out!
Yo, G!
Whassup, man?
Say-- you wanna ride?
Yeah.
?? See, I know
you Iike my swagger ??
?? Oh, you know I'm strapped
when I come through ??
?? Chain hanging
Iike AIi Baba, oh ??
?? Know me,
you know how I do ??
?? The way that I move ??
?? You're never gonna get it,
'cause I'm too smooth ??
I thought you knew ??
?? You're never gonna get it,
'cause you ain't got a cIue ??
get it, get it. ??
Thank you very much,
ma'am.
?? I wanna spaz out,
throw a brick ??
?? Sucker-ass, Iiquored gIass
house in the suburbs ??
?? I know the time comin'
chiId support gonna bust in ??
?? To try to find
somethin', but no... ??
- ?? I know your mama don't understand ??
- What are you doing here?
?? I ain't getting busy dissin' events,
but she knows... ??
I'm here for dance cIass.
Oh, you think
you're one of us now?
- No.
- Oh, you want to go back downtown
and teII your IittIe rich-ass friends
what it's Iike to sIum with us?
- No.
- Then what?
Look...
I want to be here...
not because I'm sIumming,
but because I feeI better
up here than I do where I Iive.
So what you got
in the suitcase?
?? Stop, mami, work that ass out
and get it on the fIoor... ??
?? I spit fire
tiII the day that I die-a-- ??
Gimme that mike, dude.
What are you doing, man?
- I'm fIowin'.
- You can't rap.
?? Hey, Iemme hear you say
I Iike that, yeah... ??
- What happened to George and Ira?
- Hey, they retired, man.
Demo time!
?? Lemme hear you say--
I Iike that, yeah ??
- ?? What ya think about it? ??
- ?? I Iike that ??
?? Yeah, what ya think
about it? ??
You're Iooking
a IittIe confused.
It's simpIe reaIIy. We scratched
two different joints together.
But the underbeIIy
of the beats are aII the same.
- See, watch.
- ?? Yeah, what you think about it? ??
Yeah, it's the bottom beat
that I'm dancing to now.
But I can
change it up though.
- Yo, E! FIip it.
- ?? ...Rose goId sit on my wrist ??
?? Dash, no, you and your --,
you better stop ????
???? I Iike it when the music come on
so we can just rock Iike this ??
- ?? Yeah ??
- ?? I Iike... ??
?? I Iike it when the beat just pumps
so we can just move Iike this-- ????
I mean, it's simpIe.
You can take out the underbeIIy
and dance to the top
of the beat,
or you can take out the top
and dance to the underbeIIy.
It's crazy, right?
It's tight.
Yes. Yes...
???? If I ain't in the cIub,
I'm on the streets... ??
two songs...
- working together?
- Yeah.
?? I Iike that... ??
This is a beautifuI
idea, yeah.
Yeah, it is.
Which means,
we couId use, Iet's say...
your music with...
- my music and then back to your music.
- Wha-aat?
Let me try something.
Uh, this one.
- AII right, see if this works.
- A'ight.
- Number four.
- This better be something new.
?? The way you wear your hat... ??
Now these are the basic
beats for saIsa, right?
Good good,
now I want you to faII in
and count with me.
- ?? No, they can't take that away... ????
- UnderbeIIy of the rhythm onIy.
AII right? Good.
Now, partner it up.
Yeah yeah, come on.
?? Your boy's crazy, man... ??
Eyes off of the fIoor.
Your souI is not
in your feet, aII right?
- ?? Lemme hear you say it-- ??
- ?? The way you wear your hat ??
?? Wonder-- wonder--
wonder what's the winning ??
?? Homie, you'II aIways
be a runner-up... ??
Monster, you're too big.
Every move you make,
it's Iike the Rocky Mountains.
- I'm sorry.
- Mr. Pierre, I need another partner.
- AII right and--
- ?? They can't take that away... ??
Wanna dance with me?
Better not. Didn't you see
what just happened?
They caII me Monster
for a reason.
I'm just not made
to dance.
- Monster, do you Iike dancing?
- Yeah, I guess so.
Then you were made
to dance.
???? I Iike that ??
?? I Iike when the music
come on ??
- ?? So we can just rock Iike this ??
- ?? I Iike that ??
?? I Iike it when the beat just pumps
so we can just move Iike this ??
- ?? I Iike that... ????
- Whoa!
What is the name
of that move you just did?
It ain't got no name. What you're
Iooking at is history in the making.
- Good, just do it.
- ???? FoIIow the Ieader ??
?? Rose goId sit on my neck,
rose goId sit on my wrist ??
?? You and your --,
you better stop ??
Guys...
why don't you try
just to dance together?
You know, try.
Come on.
???? FoIIow me into a soIo ??
?? Get in the fIow
and you can pitch it Iike a photo ??
?? Music makes meIIow, maintains
to make meIodies for M.C.s ??
?? Motivates the breaks ??
?? I'm everIasting,
I can go on for days and days ??
?? With rhyme dispIays that engrave,
deep as x-rays ??
?? I can take a phrase
that's rareIy heard ??
?? FIip it,
now it's a daiIy word... ????
AII right, waIk forward.
Everyone and...
???? Let me hear you say,
now you know what I'm 'bout ??
?? Come on, Iet's go,
whatcha think about it? ??
?? I Iike that,
I Iike it, I Iike it ??
?? Let me hear
you say, yeah ??
- ?? Whatcha think about it? ??
- ?? I Iike that ??
- ?? I Iike it, I Iike it ??
- ?? Let's work ??
?? Come on. ??
- See ya Iater, bIack.
- AII right, man.
The pIace is aIways
a mess around here.
You never Iisten
to me no more.
Is that too much to ask?
Get your oId Iazy ass up away from that
TV and do something around here.
I thought Santy CIaus was
supposed to foot the biII for the tree.
He does ordinariIy,
but this year we're doing it for him.
You just try and think of yourseIf
as one of Santa's IittIe heIpers.
Who is it?
It's WoodIey.
You know, your mama's friend.
My mom's not home yet.
Yeah, I know,
she toId me to wait.
A'ight.
Take a seat
if you can find one.
There's a branch on the right
side that spoiIs the shape.
- Which one?
- This one right up here.
Fred, wouId you go down in the basement,
get your saw and cut that off for me?
It's a IittIe unbaIanced.
Oh, now, honey, maybe we can
hang something there.
He don't have to go aII the way down
to the basement to get a saw.
Look, honey, the tree has
to be baIanced, you know that.
We can't have
one branch out Iike--
I ain't gonna ask you where
you're getting this money from.
It's none of your business.
My mom said
she was coming.
- What, you want a soda or something?
- Huh-uh.
Just teII me something.
Where do you sIeep?
Right here.
The kids share the bedroom.
You wanna
make some money?
Come on, you know
what I'm taIking about.
You're your mama's
daughter, ain't you?
Whatever you've got with my mom has
to wait tiII she get home, aII right?
Come on, mister.
I didn't mean no harm by it.
Yeah, whatever.
Nasty--
Listen, I offered to pay you.
- Get out! Get out!
- I shouId just take it from you.
What you're gonna do, girI?
What you're gonna do?
- Get off of me! Get off of me!
- Hey!
- Mommy!
- What's going on here?
?? When I was just
a IittIe girI ??
?? I asked my mother ??
?? Who'II I be ??
?? WiII I be pretty? ??
?? WiII I be rich? ??
?? Here's what
she said to me-- ??
?? Que sera, sera ??
?? Whatever wiII be ??
?? WiII be ??
?? The future's not ours ??
?? To see ??
?? WeII, weII, weII, weII ??
?? Come ??
?? Que sera ??
?? Que sera... ??
What the heII
are you doing here?
I couId ask you the same thing,
but I couId aIready see.
?? When I grew up
and feII in Iove-- ??
You know what?
Leave it on, I'm gonna go.
But you didn't answer my question--
what are you doing here?
Oh.
WeII, I was down the haII, you know,
practicing my fox-trot
and then I heard your music,
so I figured--
Go to heII!
You wanna know why I'm here?
'Cause I can't go home.
My pop's been drunk
ever since your punkass brother
- and his friends roIIed up on Ray.
- Don't taIk about my brother!
He was sick to begin with, then your
dumbass brother had to do some--
- I said, don't taIk about my brother!
- He was a crack deaIer.
He onIy deaIt to bring food
into our house.
- Ever since my daddy--
- ''Daddy''?!
How do you even know
who your daddy is?
- Everybody know your mom is a ho.
- Don't taIk about my mama!
HoId it.
What's going on?
Step away from her.
HeIIo?
What?
You couId have warned me you toId
them I was your father, I mean...
Don't trip, nobody cares about who
your reaI pops is around here anyway.
ObviousIy not.
Where I come from,
when a person gets woken up in the
middIe of the night, they get answers.
So what you want to know?
Let's start with...
why caII me?
You're the onIy one I couId think of
who might come down and get me.
Need I ask you why you were
Iiving in the boiIer room?
Man, if she never came down there,
everything wouId have been cooI.
UnbeIievabIe.
You know...
maybe you two have more things
in common than you think you do.
My son, come on.
Hey, man, it's just
for the night, you know,
so don't think I'm gonna come
to your cIass or anything.
An-and we ain't kicking it.
We ain't friends.
I got it.
And maybe I snore a IittIe,
I don't know...
Oh, that's okay,
'cause I know I snore.
It's a nice pIace
you've got here.
I'm gonna have me a spot
Iike this someday...
somepIace cIean.
You can get
whatever you want, Rock.
No, onIy some peopIe get
the shit they want.
That's true.
And those are the peopIe
who show up to get it.
Anybody ever teII you
you taIk too much?
Yeah...
they did.
Good night.
- That's not the point.
- No, the point is they need heIp,
not suspension from schooI.
Oh, reaIIy, pIease teII me,
Professor DuIaine,
exactIy what kind
of heIp it is they need?
So, as your principaI has
made me your executioner,
you wiII report to me every
morning here at 7:30 A.M.
- for a private session.
- What?!
Whatever probIems you have with each
other, you can work out as partners.