In 1944, a demon was summoned
to Earth to wage war.
But the child of Hell was rescued
by good men who taught him honour,
kindness and a sense of right.
The scientists and researchers
who gathered around the boy
became the Bureau of Paranormal
Research and Defence,
an international organisation
that protects the world
from occult and supernatural threats.
There are things
that go bump in the night.
They are the ones
who bump back.
(Coughs)
- Are you all right?
- You know, water isn't really my element.
We must be somewhere
under the temple complex.
Hmm, so the sun worshippers
forced the bat guys underground?
Quite literally, it would seem.
- All set?
- Sure.
Can't wait.
Ugh.
Slime.
Do you feel air movement?
(Coughs)
Yeah. And something dead.
Very dead.
Well, we know what happened
to Agent Hamilton.
Mystery solved, I guess.
Did you know him?
No. But I understand he has family.
I guess we should... Oh.
Cute.
So, what do you think
we're looking for?
Ohh, I hope not.
Yeah, so where is Hellboy, anyway?
Unh!
Agh!
(Groans)
(Roars)
Oh, crap.
(Bays)
Unh! Agh!
- Well, this shouldn't be too hard.
- Yeah, right.
(Creatures moan)
Uhh, screw this.
(Roars)
Fine, have it your way!
Liz! This isn't working!
We can do this!
- Liz!
- OK, OK.
(Snorts, growls)
(Roars)
(Plaintive roar)
(Growled lament)
Pull it back, Liz!
Pull it back!
Liz.
Liz. Liz!
It's me, kiddo.
You did good. It's over.
So, what'd I miss?
Urrh!
Uh!
Beautiful!
So beautiful!
As for this,
it is something which happened.
The brothers of the dragons,
Thunder and Lightning,
brought their wrath upon the lands
of a powerful Daimyo,
smashing them
with their terrible weapons.
The war hammer of Thunder
made mountains crumble
and the forests tremble in fear.
His brother, Lightning,
wielded a flashing spear of white fire
which scorched the earth
and boiled the sea.
The Daimyo was helpless
before these monsters.
To save his lands, he offered them
what was most precious to him:
His daughter,
a fragile flower,
as pale as the moon,
and as beautiful as the stars.
But the Daimyo had
a brave samurai in his service
who loved the daughter.
Knowing the Daimyo's plan
was to sacrifice the girl,
the samurai sent her
to a shrine deep in the woods
where she would
be hidden from the monsters.
So when the demons
came to collect their prize,
they found not the beautiful daughter,
but a samurai warrior
ready to protect his love.
Thunder and Lightning
split the sky with their anger.
Pounding rain fell like daggers
upon the samurai.
But he did not weaken.
(Gasps)
Aagh! Urgh! Argh!
It seemed the demons
could not be stopped.
They would break
the samurai into pieces.
But the samurai sword
had been inscribed with ancient words
of great enchantment.
The samurai sword drank deeply
of the blood of the storm demons.
Its magic trapped them
in its blade forever.
The monsters were gone from his land
but the Daimyo was angered
by the samurai's trick.
His promise to the demons
had been broken.
No matter how onerous the bargain,
the Daimyo had given his word.
And the samurai had broken it.
The samurai left to join his love at the shrine
and never return.
The dishonour to the Daimyo's house
could not be undone.
There could only be retribution.
The Daimyo beseeched the gods
to ease his shame,
and the gods answered.
(Knocking)
Professor Sakai?
- Hiramatsu...
- Professor!
Just rest a moment,
and I'll fetch you some tea.
Thank you, Toshiro.
I can be foolish sometimes.
I get lost in my work.
It's too late. I can come back.
Nonsense, Professor.
You are here
and so are my swords.
You academics,
drawing strength
from your studies of artefacts.
Sifting through the rice sacks of folklore
after a single grain of truth.
I'm sure I know
the sword you want to see.
Right here. I was just polishing it.
A late 16th-century blade
that I believe was owned
by Musashi Miyamoto.
Please, Professor Sakai.
Fingerprints!
Uhh! Uh!
Uh!
Huh?
Unh!
(Neck cracks)
Sorry 'bout the turbulence, guys.
It seems like there's a storm building
to the east. Wasn't in the forecast.
Should be settin' down at the Bureau
in about 20 minutes.
Hey, kiddo. How you doin'?
Great, for a walking napalm strike.
You saved our lives, Liz.
I practically torched you.
Not to mention a couple of dozen Mayans.
- Sorry about the burns.
- Barely a sunburn.
Come on, they were mummies.
And they were trying to kill ya.
Trust me, there's no upside
to cutting the undead any slack.
You did what you had to do.
I lost control is what I did.
If you hadn't stopped me,
I would have melted the place,
and probably the two of you.
I can handle the little stuff fine,
but when I try anything big...
God, the Bureau should lock me up!
I'm the real monster.
Hm. (Chuckles)
(Both laugh)
OK, OK. I get it.
No, no. You're the monster, all right.
Me and Abe, we...
I mean, you're lucky
we let you be seen with us.
It's true. You do cramp our style.
The world needs what we can do.
That makes us good guys.
That's enough for me.
Katie, good to see ya!
I'd hug ya, but, hey,
bat-god saliva. It's the pits.
Thanks for your restraint.
I thought you were in Prague.
All finished. We discovered
the wolf apparitions were actually
the hounds of King Vold,
the flying huntsman!
And they weren't wolves at all, but the
transformed ghosts of berserker Vikings!
There's nothing in the literature
that hints at it.
I can't wait to start my paper on it.
Sounds wonderful, Kate.
Can't wait to read it.
Sorry.
- You OK?
- Sure.
Had to flambé a dozen mummies,
but you know the walking dead,
can't say no to a party.
- We'll talk when we get back.
- Back?
Another mission. Seems a folklore expert
turned agent is considered indispensable.
Well, stay safe.
That's too bad.
Me? I'm headed for a two-hour shower
and a sauna.
- Take care of yourself.
- Sorry, Red. Orders.
- You're with me.
- (Groans)
Come on.
We're going to Japan.
Tuesday, 11:30am,
Japanese standard time,
Special Agent Russell Thorne, BPRD.
Predictions, impressions,
and psychic resonances.
Yes, yes. Something is...
Beware the umbrella!
It seems friendly, but really isn't!
And I sense there was
a sudden release of energy here,
yes, very powerful.
You're good.
I've worked with psychics before,
but you're really something.
And I thought it was just bad feng shui.
- I hate psychics.
- I know, I know.
But we have to use them.
Come on, sometimes they help.
Yeah, but it's always too little, too damn late.
Excuse me, Agent Corrigan.
This disc from my security cameras
will be a much better witness than I.
That's Sakai-san, all right.
- You know that guy?
- Yes.
Professor Mitsuyasu Sakai.
I met him at the lpswich Conference
when I delivered a paper.
"Global Interpretations
of Troll Legends."
Gosh, Kate.
I feel just terrible luring you away
from your exciting career of
combing through rotting manuscripts.
I mean, you used to research trolls.
That's OK.
Now I get to work with one.
Hm. The past two days, he's had
a teaching assistant handle his classes.
- (lnhales sharply)
- What?
Here. Let me freeze it.
OK. That's never good.
Take your hands off of me!
Get... Let go of that.
I need that! Let go,
it's mine to use...
Oh, for Pete's sake.
Russell! What are you doing?
Agent Corrigan,
please instruct this person
to stop smearing his dirty fingers
all over my antique katanas!
It's him, Kate.
His disruptive chi
is ruining a delicate psychic inquiry!
All right, all right.
Both of you, calm down.
I'm sure Mr Hiramatsu
wants to get to the bottom of this, too.
After all, his beautiful
home was damaged,
and he'll need our help
to file an insurance claim.
Oh, I got something!
Um, never mind.
Something I can do for ya?
You there! Watch where you're stepping,
my collection cannot be replaced!
(Kate) I appreciate
your situation, Mr Hiramatsu,
but Russell is one of our best agents,
and he'll take great care
with your collection.
Hey, can I get a translator over...
Ah, crap.
Hellboy?
- (Creaking)
- Unh.
You're not a normal fox.
(Woman's voice)
And you are not a normal man.
Really?
What gave it away?
Any idea why I'm here?
Do I look like a philosopher?
Nice.
You carry the Sword of Storms.
And it has tasted the blood of demons.
That is all you need to know, for now.
Sure, 'cause that's just
so much to absorb all at once.
Don't cut yourself.
(Distressed whimpering)
My love! My love!
(Sobs)
My love!
Why did you not come?
Excuse me?
You sent me here
while you faced
those terrible demons.
And when the storms ended,
I knew I had been rescued
from my father's pledge.
I made ready to receive you
and I waited.
But you never came.
Once, I thought I heard you...
but I was mistaken.
My father spoke of duty and shame,
and death.
Even then, I thought,
"Any moment, my love will arrive.
And he will save me."
(Blade chinks)
(Weeps)
Why did you not come?
I'm sorry, but you got the wrong guy.
(Sighs)
You have been placed on a dangerous path.
Protect the sword
and keep moving east
toward the rising sun.
Great. Which way is east?
Hungry people are losing their heads. I...
Excuse me!
I sense something
that starts with an "S."
Maybe a "J."
Look, he disappeared, literally,
practically in front of me.
- I'm worried about that umbrella.
- Shut up, Russell.
Tell me you have him
on the satellite display.
They're still running the scan routines.
Just a moment.
- What the hell is taking so long?
- Agent Sherman,
we're doing everything we can.
Guys, get this crap pile working
before I melt it.
Liz...
I can do the little stuff.
It is working, Agent Sherman.
It's just his tracking beacon
is nowhere on the grid.
(Sighs) So he's not on the planet.
This has happened before?
There was the Marrakech thing.
Oh, jeez. Do you really think
it's something like that?
- How about Prague?
- Bombay, March 1993.
Istanbul, '89.
And that Marrakech thing?
Hm?
Oh, Hellboy disappeared
and turned up eight weeks later
near Glacier Bay,
frozen in a block of ice.
Yeah. He wasn't too pleased about that.
You just made the newbie face.
Well, if he gets out of this with nothing
worse than a case of frostbite, I'll be happy.
- Kate, he's not on the planet.
- Great.
Anything new on your professor friend?
Well, his study of the origins
of the supernatural
is highly regarded
in academic circles,
but his research seems to have led him
into some very hazardous territory.
Some of these artefacts
are potentially dangerous,
nothing too serious,
just enough to get him into trouble.
Hold it! I need to see that.
I'll have to call you back, Abe.
- Ma'am, you'll need these.
- Mm-hm.
Ma'am...
Why don't you boys take a break?
What is it? Kate!
This is one of the 18 scrolls
of the lost monks.
Tokugawa ordered them burned,
but every so often
you run across one,
and it's always bad.
It's always a problem.
I knew something
in here carried a charge.
These seem like innocent little fables,
but allegedly,
arcane secrets and rituals
are hidden in the prose.
Here! A samurai imprisoned
two demons in his sword.
Thunder and Lightning
are destined to bring their brothers,
the dragons, into this world.
According to Mr Hiramatsu, that's the sword
that went missing with Hellboy.
- Here.
- (Makes panicked noises)
(Sighs)
From what I saw
on the security cameras,
we're talking about
demonic possession.
If Professor Sakai
has been possessed,
then he went after that sword
to release the demons.
Is Sakai hosting these things voluntarily?
I mean, are we to consider him
a villain or a victim?
Take your pick.
Either way, he's connected
to Hellboy's disappearance.
And we are going to find him.
(Distant siren)
Hey, old man!
I don't care what your problem is,
stay the hell away from my garbage.
(Wheezes)
Get outta here
before I teach you a lesson.
(Frightened cries)
Damn.
(Screeching)
Figure it out in the morning.
(Yawns)
(Man) Hellboy.
Jeez. What's your problem, pal?
I was sleepin'.
You can't sleep here.
Too dangerous.
- Why?
- Bad things in these woods at night.
You come and stay at my house, OK?
Sure. Why not?
I have other guests tonight.
They will be happy to see you.
Uh, I don't wanna be any trouble.
No trouble.
Big house, lots of room.
(Gentle laughter)
(Chuckling)
(Man) That was great. I loved that.
(Woman) I'd like another.
Someone's here.
He's a big one.
Don't mind her.
It's the sake talking.
(Laughter)
Just travellers, like you.
Good people.
- Mr Lu here tells very funny stories.
- (Man) I love the stories.
Uh, don't let me interrupt.
Maybe you know this one.
A farmer met a ghost woman
and she gave him a golden box.
She said, "You must never open this box."
So this fellow, he took it home
and hid it from his wife.
But one day, she found it and looked inside.
And what do you suppose
was in the box?
It was full of gouged-out human eyes!
(Laughter)
And at the very moment
she saw them,
the farmer dropped dead
in his field! (Chuckles)
And the wife went mad
and lived the rest of her days
like an animal. The end.
(Laughs)
- (Laughs)
- Wow,
that is a funny story.
You know, I just realised I'm awfully tired.
- You guys have fun.
- (Chuckling)
This way.
(Giggles)
Sleep well. Very safe.
Yeah, I bet.
Huh.
Clean as a whistle.
Not a spot of blood anywhere.
Where the hell are your heads?
(Man) He must be asleep by now.
(2nd Man) Yes.
(3rd Man) Good. I am starving.
(Woman) A fine meal they've sent us
for the price of a broken sword.
But it is the Sword of Storms
that holds the brothers of the dragons.
For that, we deserve a feast like him.
(Man shouts)
He's gone, and he's taken our bodies!
What? Our bodies?
He has hidden them.
Find him!
Look around. He can't have gone far.
- Boo.
- Agh!
- Ugh!
- Get him!
You guys were gonna eat me?
Ow!
Jeez.
Make him talk.
What have you done with our bodies?
Talk! We're wasting time.
Tell us!
I've had about enough of this crap. Uh!
- Where are they?
- Guess.
Oh, please!
What have you done with our bodies?
Damn heads.
(Whimpers)
Appreciate the batting practice, but...
the sun's comin' up.
Where did you hide them?
I dropped 'em in the lake.
You guys didn't look too hard.
Where?
Bet that hurts.
(Seethes)
(Liz) Great. Suppose the roof leaks, too.
(Abe) It's all right.
The scanning array and computer
are on a different grid than the lights.
I suppose we can't consider the sudden
appearance of these storms a coincidence?
Maybe if we wish real hard.
Agent Sherman,
we've got something else.
Uh-oh.
Let's hear it.
We're picking up tectonic anomalies.
They're localised earthquakes, very intense,
but not on any known fault lines.
I can't see how they could
be related to the storms,
but I thought I should mention them.
But... I don't think they're connected.
When have we ever been that lucky?
With Hellboy gone,
Kate could be in way over her head.
We have to go to Japan.
Because we're the good guys.
Right.
- Nuh!
- (Screeching)
Ohh, you're just in time.
I was about to play
one of my own compositions.
- Lucky you.
- (Chuckles)
I am, now that you've fallen into my lap.
But you look tired.
A pleasant tune
will ease your burdens.
Sit with me and we will enjoy ourselves.
Mm, don't think so.
I got somewhere to go.
Listen to the tone of this koto.
I made the strings from my finest silk.
Is it not beautiful?
OK, then. Huh?
(Hellboy) Hey!
Urh?!
(Laughs maniacally)
Jeez.
(Continues to cackle)
I'm sorry I couldn't share
my music with you.
All the same, a mother
must feed her children.
Screw you!
(Screeches)
(Screams)
I don't have time for this.
Man!
(Screeches)
(Wheezes)
Air Force 916, suggest you divert
and return to Honolulu.
No can do. Got a couple of heavyweights
that have to get to Tokyo.
Can we go around?
Negative. The storm front
is spreading too fast.
We see it, Honolulu.
Air Force 916 out.
Holy Mother! Look at the size of that thing!
The radar's picking up
hurricane-force winds.
- Can we climb over it?
- I don't know if we can fly that high.
Strap in. This isn't gonna be smooth.
We definitely need a new travel agent.
I'm tired of flying economy.
It's not much better in first class.
It's going to be rough.
No surprise there.
Son of a...
Not my element.
(Muffled attempts to communicate)
(Pants)
Thanks... Abe.
Not a problem.
Er, let's move away from the shore.
Right. Right.
Problem is, there's more shore
than anything else.
(Sighs)
- So...
- (Gasps)
You gonna turn into a monster
and try to eat me?
No, no!
The monster is in that lake.
And you're feedin' it.
He has already eaten many of my family.
But, if I write the names
of those of us left
on these cucumbers,
the kappa takes the vegetables
and leaves us alone
for a year.
He really likes cucumbers.
I could carve one for you.
No, thanks, I...
Uh!
What is your name?
Too late.
(Hellboy) Ooh!
(Hellboy) Yah!
(Man) Spill his water!
Spill his water!
Got it.
Come here, turtle boy.
I'll give you something to chew on.
(Growls)
(Screeches)
(Makes belch-like sound)
That takes care of you.
Ask it a question.
You have beaten it.
It must answer your questions.
Why is the sword important?
It holds the demons.
It is your way home.
How do I get home?
Break the sword and return home.
Break the sword and free the demons.
(Laughs)
(Chokes)
How do I stop the demons?
Hey!
Jerk.
Here.
Keep him away from water.
Ugh.
- Can you believe this?
- At least we're out of the rain.
- I thought you liked rain.
- Not this.
This feels... wrong.
(Thunder)
Underwater... that, um, giving me air thing?
That was... um...
I didn't know you could do that.
I wasn't sure it would work either. But I have
burped excess air before,
- so I thought I might...
- Ugh!
I was breathing your burps?!
Ugh! I mean...
ah, thanks.
Good.
- Good to know.
- You know, it wasn't actually...
- a burp...
- (Bleeping)
- Sapien.
- (Pilot) Good to hear you.
We just picked up your telemetry.
What happened?
The plane was hit by lightning.
We lost the pilots.
Agent Sherman and I are OK.
Rough. It's happening all over.
The storms are off the charts.
All commercial air traffic is grounded.
OK.
There's a US sub
near your coordinates.
We can divert it to pick you up.
Have there been any more
of those earthquake anomalies?
Let me check.
Yeah, one at every storm centre.
Say, there was one right near you.
You feel it?
Saw it. Tell Manning to send agents
to check for weird crap
wherever there's been a quake.
And have them take guns.
Big ones.
Sherman and Sapien out.
Here. What?
In Japanese mythology,
a fox is considered
a mystical creature.
Japan. Hellboy.
Then I guess it's here for us.
Come here.
Come here!
Come here... foxy.
Great. I guess we follow.
Why doesn't it look wet?
Yeah, yeah, we're coming.
It's a cave.
At least it's dry.
Yeah. One mummy and I'm outta here.
Could you give us some light?
- Thank you.
- That's not me.
Oh. Then never mind.
- See the fox?
- Someone else.
Come closer.
Do not worry about your friend.
He walks a path of fate's choosing.
Much depends on his success.
Our friend?
The red one.
OK, didn't want to assume.
Two demons, sons of the storm,
seek entrance to this world.
They are Thunder and Lightning.
Their spirits are already here.
These storms.
But the storms are nothing.
Once they walk the earth,
the demons will wake their brothers,
the dragons.
And when they wake,
- the time of man will be at its end.
- (Baby cries)
They are already stirring.
(Gasps) The baby!
(Baby screams)
(Continues screaming)
(Man) Please be careful!
The steps are slippery!
Do not rush!
Head for the bus.
I am sure the rain will pass soon.
Or maybe we head back to town.
(Prolonged sinister female whisper)
Hello.
(Playful) Hello.
(Giggling)
(Laughing)
- Good morning, swordsman.
- We have something to tell you.
(Both laugh)
Please, come closer...
it is a private matter.
That sword does not belong to you.
(Giggles)
Why don't you give it to us?
I don't know. I like it.
It's a great souvenir.
Come, now.
There are other ways
of remembering a journey.
Perhaps a memorable evening
with charming company.
No, thanks. I got places to be.
- Ohh... Don't go!
- Don't go!
If you break the sword,
you'll return to your friends.
What?
Try it and see.
Break the sword.
Go ahead. Break the sword.
Then we can have some fun.
(All giggle)
I said, no thanks!
(All) Ohhh!
Uhh.
Oh, crap.
They've cleared everybody within an 8-block
radius, but there's no stopping that thing.
And they're not having any luck
in Guatemala, either.
(Sighs) Luckily, there's nothing
but jungle around it.
- How did Agent Sherman know?
- You got me.
We can't raise them on the radio
and we lost their signal a half-hour ago.
Your friend wanders through lands
where you cannot walk.
You have your own challenges to face.
The dragon you have seen
is not fully awakened.
You must not let him
join his demon brothers.
(Sighs)
Any hints on how we might do that?
How does Hellboy put up with this crap?
Russell, I'm running out of time
and patience as well.
I don't want to hear
about talking animals
or hungry heads or spiders!
I need you to just sit there,
close your eyes,
and concentrate on finding
Professor Sakai.
Professor Corrigan, please,
I'm not some sort of TV remote
that you can just click off and on.
My powers are...
Where... is... he?
Too close.
What the hell kind of answer is that?
Very close.
Amazingly, unbearably close.
- We should get out of here.
- Not until you find...
Uh!
- (Screams)
- Calm down.
They're called Tsukumogami,
artefact spirits. They're harmless.
Just supernatural fallout
from what the professor's been doing.
Not you.
- Mh...
- It's like being in a cartoon!
Konichiwa! Ogenki-desuka?
Chase these things into the closet
or something.
We have to find the professor.
Mmm!
Uh! Agh!
Ah!
Agh!
(Woman sobbing)
We cannot leave until you come for me.
Why do you stay away?
She will wait for eternity
until the unfinished business is settled.
It's all about the demons. I take care of
them, everybody can go home happy.
Perhaps so.
It won't be long now.
All the actors are here.
The play will begin again.
Take care of the sword.
Only the sword carrier can break it.
Yeah, yeah. Can't break the sword
without freeing the demons.
So, how do I get back?
Big help.
Very big.
Zurich big?
- Or the thing in Cameroon big?
- Big enough.
Damn. Anything we can use?
It likes to eat.
That hardly ever helps.
It's fairly lethargic
except around food.
I really don't wanna see it awake.
Maybe it won't wake up.
Maybe Hellboy will do
what he needs to,
and we can just wait
here for a pick-up.
He... could.
So, any plan? In case I'm wrong.
Not one that doesn't involve fire.
(Sighs)
At least the rain stopped.
Then I just have to lure it up here
so you can go to work.
Oh, sure, take the easy job.
Abe?
No big chances.
Liz! Run!
(Roars)
That's lethargic?
Wow.
(Growls)
Oh, here we go.
(Birds screech)
(Groans)
This is just getting better and better.
(Growls)
Ahh!
(Growl)
(Screeches)
No way it was that easy.
This isn't working.
We should hide in the cave.
No. No hiding.
Anything?
He's gone to the shrine.
The one from the folk tale.
(Low moaning)
Felt that, didn't ya?
(Roars)
- (Roars)
- Crap.
(Roars)
(Cries out)
At least you're solid.
(Roars)
Agh!
(Bellows)
(Grunts)
Serves ya right.
(Low grunt)
(Woman's voice)
Only the sword carrier can break it.
Muhh...
(Kate) Hellboy!
Japan. I can handle that.
You look awful.
I'll live.
Where's the Sword of Storms?
That's not good.
(Bizarre struggling noises)
(Roars)
Free!
(Gasps)
(Laughs)
The land will be dark.
(They cackle)
Do you feel them?
Our brothers are calling.
Then we should wake them
and bring an end
to this puny world of men!
(Hellboy) Think again, dumbass...
cos now... l'm pissed.
(They laugh)
We only feared one weapon.
And you destroyed it!
Ha!
Stupid, ugly monkey demon.
Me ugly?
(Hellboy) Come and get it!
Aaaghh!
(Roars)
He's starting to look better.
I know you.
Katherine.
The one with the trolls.
Sakai-san, listen.
How have you been?
Listen, you've been possessed.
Excuse me?
(Wild growling)
Big mistake.
(Snorting)
Just go get it.
(Roars)
Don't stay under the tree!
It's common sense.
Ha-ha!
Agh!
Hurts, doesn't it?
Aaaghh!
Eagh! Uh!
(Cackles)
Nnh. Nhh.
(Growls)
(Gasps)
Ah! Uh!
I guess we need a new definition of, uh...
little stuff.
(Screeches)
Agh!
(Cackles)
Aaaghh!
Uhh! Uh!
(Cackles)
(Sighs)
That worked.
I have a feeling Hellboy is back.
There ya go.
What the hell is that?
Oh, I feel so...
(Gasps)
(Woman) The play has begun.
After the samurai imprisoned
those demons in his sword,
he never returned
for the Daimyo's daughter.
He wasn't there to save her.
Unfinished business.
Kate!
Ah!
My love!
Lady, I keep tellin' ya,
you got the wrong... Oh.
Hey, you can stop this now.
Use your head.
You just have to forgive them
or else we'll end up
doing this all over again
and you're never gonna win.
O-Oh. Ow.
I'm gettin' myself some aspirin
and some breakfast.
Who's comin'?