Kaaaate?
You ready?
Should I say, "This
chapter is so boring,
my begonia committed suicide
when I read it out loud,"
or, "Let's talk"?
I like the first one.
Yeah, me too.
Oh, God, we're never
gonna make it.
So we're just gonna get
the 6 to Grand Central?
Well, I thought that
we would take the N here
and then transfer.
Heh.
Right.
Ta-da!
Wow!
Yeah.
I mean, I know it's
little and it's dark
and the hallways
smell like cabbage...
And it's in Brooklyn.
But it's mine!
There's--
there's no roommate,
there's no cigarette butts
in the coffee cups,
no-- no toenails
in the sink.
Ew!
You're glowing.
I'm happy.
No, I mean it.
You got this weird glow.
So, whaddaya think?
Oh! And, uh, they
fixed up the kitchen.
What are you gonna do
with a kitchen?
I'm cooking.
Mm-hmm.
Friday, as a matter
of fact, for Matt.
It's a special meal.
What's special?
Oh, it's mine,
it's mine!
It's all mine!
Thanks for coming!
Matt? Whaddaya think?
Forget the packing boxes
and I'm gonna get
some more furniture.
Well, I have a bed.
And just because I never cook
doesn't mean I can't.
It just means it's a pain
to cook for one person.
Mmm. Mmm.
Matt?
Well, I hope you like
what I'm making.
It's a special meal because
it's a very special night.
I said, it's a special meal
because it's a special night.
I have a present for you.
I can't do it.
Of course
the watering schedules
could be inserted
into the paragraph.
I'm not suggesting it's
a physical impossibility.
Esthetically,
it's a train wreck,
but it can be done.
You could also decide
to use italics
if you want to complete
the destruction.
What's wrong?
It's something
I said, isn't it?
My wicked tongue.
No.
Alright, mea culpa.
I wanted a different editor;
I admit it.
But let me come right out
and say you've done
an excellent job...
for a young woman.
Thanks.
"Dear Kate,
I honestly did think
"it could work between us
"and it is completely
my fault that it couldn't.
"You did nothing wrong
except ask me to lunch.
"If you've got
the heart to read this,
"it will explain everything
better than I could.
"Be warned, though.
"There are parts that will be
hard to get through.
"'Sorry' is too weak a word.
Matt."
Who?
Eighteen months ago.
"Dear Nicholas...
"as I write the first
entry in this diary,
you were not yet born,
but I know you will be..."
So, I've decided
to keep a record
of your childhood
for you to look back on
when you grow up.
It's important to know
where you came from, Nicky.
Gives you roots.
So I'm gonna begin
before the beginning,
before I even met
your father.
I was still a doctor
in Boston.
Dr. Brunik,
report to the neuro ICU.
Suzanne.
Michael.
See you
at the house, okay?
You got it.
Ugh.
Are you alright, miss?
I'm a doctor.
I think I'm...
gonna have
a heart attack.
Oh, my God!
I'm only 33.
Calm, Suzanne.
Yes, calm.
You had a double bypass,
not botox.
But I'm only 33, Phil.
With a family history
of heart disease.
Which doesn't seem
to be here in your record.
Hmm.
I forgot.
Uh-huh.
Well, I can tell you
that at auction
a piece of depression glass
in this condition--
You're late again.
Michael, I am so bored.
Will you please take me
out to dinner?
Please, please, please?
I want something fat
and I want something greasy
and I want...
Uh-oh.
Suzanne, how long have
we been seeing each other?
Six months?
And did you consider our
relationship a serious one?
Don't use the professor voice,
Michael, please.
It drives me insane.
Fine, regular voice.
Why the hell
didn't you tell me
you had a heart problem?
God, I can't--
Just one last time.
There was no problem.
There was a history.
Well, there was history
of measles too, Michael.
And you put that
in your medical record.
I took a look at your workup,
Suzanne; it isn't good.
There's damage
to your heart.
It isn't life-threatening,
but it is limiting.
And one of the limitations--
now I consulted
with cardio on this,
so don't shoot
the messenger--
Just...
Okay.
I'm afraid we've come
to the conclusion
that a pregnancy would pose
a real risk to your health.
You know I want
children, Suzanne.
You know it's one
of the most important--
I know.
If you'd just told me.
Wait a minute.
Wait, let me--
let me get this straight.
Are you saying that
because my family
has a history of heart disease,
that I don't have
the right to--
to fall in love?
Or-- or to have a relationship
or to get married?
I mean,
is this what you're--
is this what
you're saying, Michael?
Huh?
I'm sorry.
Bastard.
Did you read
the last page?
What?
No.
But you're
going to, right?
Why should I?
Maybe Michael dies
at the end or something.
I don't know.
Well, I know.
See, Matt's
the rebound guy.
Suzanne found him
and they're together right now
living happily ever after.
And that's all
I need to know.
What did you have?
Half of yours.
Weak. Weak.
He walked out with his art
and his antiques...
and my whole life.
I had nothing left.
No lover, no child,
no plans.
I needed a change, Nicky.
Not just a small change;
a sea change.
Until I began college,
I had spent every summer
on Martha's Vineyard.
And I remembered
it was the last
best place in the world.
So, with all of my savings,
I bought the practice
of a retiring GP
who was headed back to Boston.
We were switching lives.
I told him I felt that
I'd gotten the better deal.
And when I stood there
in that house that was mine,
everything snapped
into place.
I knew that I had made
the right decision.
By some extraordinary
twist of luck,
I had found
my perfect place.
You the doc?
Uh, yeah.
Something wrong?
No, I'm from
across the road.
Oh.
Yeah. I said to Carl,
my husband Carl,
I said, somebody
went and did it.
Couldn't be a local.
No, no, I'm from Boston--
Then he said it's a doc
from the city.
And I said, well,
that's a blessing,
'cause when we lost
old Doc MacLaren,
I thought we were just
outta luck down here.
And me with two
little ones.
You know, I have
a family practice--
And then Carl says,
does he know
what she's getting
herself into?
And I said, well,
I don't expect old Doc
give her the grand tour.
He could barely walk,
ya know?
He had this thing
with his hip?
You got a minute?
Um...
Take a whiff.
Think it's low tide,
don't ya?
Septic tank.
Oh, well,
that's not good.
Don't worry; there's six
more layers under that.
Watch.
But hey,
I'm the glass-half-empty girl,
ya know?
It's a beautiful place.
Well, it could be.
Anyway, we're happy
to have you here.
Welcome to the Vineyard.
I'm Melanie Boom.
Oh, Suzanne--
Bedford, yeah.
And don't worry
about a thing.
I know this great
handyman-painter type.
Better than Picasso.
I'll get him out here,
no problem.
Hello?
Hell--
Uh...
Picasso?
You've been talkin'
to Melanie.
Yeah.
You-- you started already?
Yeah. You owe me
140 bucks so far.
I'm just kiddin'.
I'm checkin',
makin' some notes.
I'll be right down.
Did Melanie, uh,
show you around?
Yes, she-- she gave me
the grand tour.
She tell you
about the roof?
No.
Uh, the shingles?
The, um...
Don't worry.
Yeah, that's--
that's what Melanie said.
I'll have it done
by the millennium.
But the millennium
was two years ago.
The next millennium.
Oh.
Do you know your way
around the island?
I could, uh,
show you around sometime.
Oh, um...
No, I, uh...
Or I could just
fix your house and shut up.
No, it's-- it's--
It's not that I don't--
It--
It's just a bad time.
No problem.
Ah...
The doctor in, Miss?
Uh, yeah,
I'm the doctor.
Ah...
Uh...
Do I need
an appointment?
I, uh, think
I can squeeze you in.
Why don't you
have a seat?
So what seems
to be the problem?
What ain't?
Okay.
I had a heart attack.
You did? When?
Last week.
You had a heart attack
last week?
It sure felt like one.
Well, did you see
a doctor?
Seein' one now.
Ah, okay.
Do you have any
other complaints, Mr., uh...
Earl'll do.
Earl.
Well, since you're askin',
I got the gout.
Pretty sore.
Swelled up foot.
How'd you get your shoe on?
Oh, it wasn't easy.
Alright, is there
anything else?
I got a list.
Uh...
Excuse me.
Sorry.
Hi.
Come on over.
I write.
Pardon?
Oh, you got that look.
What look?
Why is he
a house painter?
No, I don't.
Yes, you do.
Well, I'll tell ya
if you wanna know.
Okay.
I'm an open book.
Okay, if you're gonna
beat it outta me...
I went to work
at my old man's company
after I graduated
from Brown.
My father was proud of me,
which was important, I guess.
So I worked there
through most of my 20's,
and then my father
passed away,
and I realized
that I had nobody left
to prove myself to,
and that... I hated it.
And I drank too much
and I did too many drugs
and hated the city and...
I knew I had to make
a sea change.
Thank you.
See, the thing is,
at Brown I wrote.
And I had this one
great professor
who told me that
I'd be a writer.
He had, uh--
he had faith in me.
So I went back to him
and I asked,
"Is this stupid?"
And he said,
"It's never stupid
to do what you want."
Which I realize now
is a crock.
But at the time,
it's what I wanted to hear.
So, um, I moved back
to the only place
that I ever loved
and I began.
That was about
eight years ago and...
so far, I've sold...
almost one story.
The handyman thing
is how I support myself.
I write.
I write every single day.
Doesn't matter
if anyone reads it
or doesn't read it.
I write.
Only thing
I'm serious about.
I didn't know doctors
ate this kind of food.
A Sam's clamburger?
Ah, well, bad days,
small comfort.
Here you go, Matt.
Thank you.
Oh, no, no, no.
You don't have to--
No, I'm runnin' the bill up
on this new lady in town.
So, if your last name
is Picasso,
what's your first name?
Matthew.
Matthew "Picasso" Harrelson.
Welcome to the Vineyard.
Thank you.
Oh, God.
Oh, God, that's the--
She made it up!
That's not Matt at all!
That's not him.
Mr. Harrelson, hi.
I'm Kate Wilkes.
It's so good
to finally meet you.
Well, please come in.
Sit down.
Um, here.
Can I first say that...
I love your stories,
especially the ones
that you've written
most recently.
They show a dramatic
improvement.
Um, they're tougher,
more honestly emotional.
They made me cry.
Um...
Well, as you know,
ten stories
have been chosen
for your book.
Might I suggest that
we meet once a week
for the next ten weeks
and tackle one story at a time.
How does that sound?
That's fine.
Fine. Good.
So, uh, if this
is a good time,
then, why, let's say,
uh, every Friday at noon.
Yes.
Okay.
Why don't we get
to work, then?
Alright, Doc.
What was your secret?
What did you do for him?
Hey.
Ugh.
Long day?
No, it was a good day.
Finally have
some patients.
And that's not
counting Earl.
Like who?
Oh, I can't tell you that.
That's doctor-client
confidentiality.
Well, I saw Doris Latham
get rolled in.
She's dead.
Did you figure that out?
Oh, no.
She's only 92.
Who else?
I can't.
Oh, what could happen
if you told me?
Oh, jeez!
Oh!
Whoa.
Here.
I got it.
That's good.
Alright.
Got it?
Yeah.
Ho.
I-- I was just gonna
fix some dinner.
You wanna stay?
I'd love to.
Voila!
This is it?
Oh, come on,
don't insult
the Suzanne.
Oh, dear.
Okay.
Madam.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Watch your head.
Ready?
Does it even run?
On and off.
Ha ha!
Oh.
Like to take the helm?
Should I?
Come on.
Okay.
Just steering, right?
I don't have to
do anything fancy?
I just hold on
to this thing.
Okay.
Yes.
Ready?
Okay, yes.
Okay.
Hi.
Hey.
Matt.
Hey, hold on a minute.
Hey, Doc.
What?
Dance?
No...
It's not really
a dancing place,
I don't think.
Okay, okay,
stop, stop, stop.
What?
What's wrong?
Nothing.
Hi.
You look, uh--
So, um,
you know what?
I didn't have any
breakfast this morning.
I'm starving.
Sorry?
No, I mean that
we could, uh--
we could go out
to lunch now,
on the company.
And, you know, it would,
uh, we-- we would work there.
It'd be like a--
a working lunch,
but, um--
Mmm.
Okay.
Thank you.
It's where we take
our most important clients.
Yeah, it's a little fancy,
but, uh, good food.
The, um-- They have
a fish special every day
that's not on the menu.
You like fish?
No.
No? I thought, um--
Isn't fishing,
like, a big deal
on Martha's Vineyard?
Yes, it is.
Yeah!
With the whaling and--
That's Nantucket.
Right, 'cause that's
the main--
You know, they make guacamole
right at the table.
Really?
Yeah. They, uh,
bring over the avocados
and then they mush 'em up,
and, um, you know,
they just put the rest
of the stuff in, and, um...
Well--
Then they light it.
Yeah. It's their
specialty here.
Flaming guacamole.
Personally, I like
the fish better.
Well, it's a small town
about 50 miles
outside of Raleigh.
Tobaccy country.
It's got one main road,
one school.
Did you smoke?
Hmm?
Tobaccy country.
Oh.
Yeah, well...
everybody smoked.
Um, my first boyfriend
rolled a homemade for me,
which he could do
with one hand
by the time he was 11.
He dared me to inhale.
I passed out cold,
right into a patch
of poison sumac.
Oh, boy.
I came up with sores
that were so bad,
I truly believed that I had
a visitation from the Lord.
No, but I like it here.
Well, I do wish that my roommate
would get a job in Alaska.
And I wish that
the crazy guy
would stop following me
to work every day.
But we had a crazy guy
in Bethel, too.
Delbert O'Dell.
He would always hang out
in front of the Ben Franklin.
But it was different,
because when I was younger,
I could say, "Hey, Del,
it's time for you
to go home now,"
and I knew that he wasn't
gonna rape me or--
Del O'Dell?
Yeah.
Older brother of Mel.
But what about you?
I mean, what, uh--
When did you have
your first cigarette?
And do you have
a crazy guy in your town?
Are those
your nicest shoes?
Uh, are you, um...
married?
No.
Okay. Um...
So, uh,
on page 24...
24?
Yeah, small typo.
What did you give me?
Sleepy Time?
You give me Sleepy Time
at 10:00 in the morning?
Listen--
You know who's coming in
today, Bernard Faber.
Laurie--
The Amphibians Make
Good Pets guy.
Laurie...
I'm gonna be asleep--
Shut up!
I think...
I think it's serious.
What, you mean with the--
Okay.
No, it's getting serious.
Is that better?
No, I didn't mean--
Okay, okay.
It's moving
in the direction
of serious.
Ah...
It's serious.
I think he's gonna
ask me, ya know?
Oh, I know.
You know?
How would you know?
Alright, now take
a deep breath, okay?
It's an island.
Again.
Okay.
Well, that's
a good thing, right?
Good thing?
The best thing that
ever happened to me.
There's just this one...
Well.
Kid, I think
you're gonna live.
So who came in today?
Uh, Earl was in.
Earl.
What did he have
this time?
He had left-side
weakness, a lumbago.
Lumbago?
Mm-hmm.
I want
a lumbago.
No.
I can't clean your
septic system today,
Mr. Schwartz.
My lumbago
is acting up.
Listen, Matt, I...
What?
You know, you know
that I was, uh--
I lived in Boston
for six years, right?
You goin' back?
No, no.
No, not a chance
in hell.
I just-- There were
a lot of reasons
that I had to leave there,
and one of the reasons--
You-- you had
a heart attack
and then your
boyfriend left you.
No, no.
Yeah, but--
And you wanted
a change, I know.
Yeah, but, Matt,
you don't know
why he left me.
Alright? Michael left me
because he wanted to have...
because he wanted
to have children.
And because
of my heart disease,
pregnancy for me
is a risk.
And I-- I know
I should've
told you that,
and I didn't tell you that
because I was afraid to
and-- and I'm sorry.
How much of a risk?
Enough.
Okay.
Then that's just
the way it is.
You don't care?
You don't want kids?
Come on, Mr. Open Book,
you told me yourself
that the only thing
that you want in this life
is to have a family.
I want you.
I want you more.
And don't know
if I can give you--
I want you more.
So is that
your only problem?
Yeah, I guess
just, uh--
- one little thing.
Okay.
What's that?
It's a rock.
I don't think
it's a rock.
No, it's a rock.
Look, it's a rock.
Look.
You're right;
it is a rock.
Will you marry me?
Yes.
Careful, I might
have a heart attack!
This is Vineyard Home Services.
Matt isn't here right now.
If you leave a message,
he'll get back to you
as soon as he can, thanks.
I just--
I just wanted to say...
I'm reading it.
Okay, alright,
that wasn't easy.
Ready?
Put me down.
Oh, whoa!
Uh.
What does that say?
"Paramada junkie?"
Oh, well, um...
I thought that the--
Oh, "paragraph."
Right.
Uh, it's just
a bit--
Chunky.
Well, long.
Um, you can cut it...
from here...
all the way to here.
Ouch.
What if we just
cut it to, uh, there?
Yeah, uh,
it could work.
I suppose.
I'll try.
Good.
Good. That's-- that's--
that's good.
In here!
Oh...
It's beautiful.
Not bad.
My little corner.
I love it.
Yeah, so I could waste
my time as usual,
but, uh, at least
I got a great view doing it.
You're not wasting your time.
Seven years of rejections.
"Thank you very much
for your submission."
"We're lying when
we say we liked it.
"Actually, we didn't
like it at all
"and we think you should
get a real job
and stop wasting your time."
No.
Yes.
I feel guilty about it.
I hadn't felt guilty
about anything
since I left
my father's business.
Look at me.
I'm-- I'm living
in your house.
We could have
lived in yours.
Oh, yeah, my room
above Sulucy's Hair and Nails?
That would have been ideal.
I can't support you...
in any kind of style.
Wait a minute.
What is it, 1954?
I can support myself
just fine, thanks.
No, I don't--
I don't mean--
I'm not contributing.
And that bothers me.
And if you want me
to stop,
if you want me
to grow the hell up
and do something
with my life,
just say the word.
Thanks.
Matt... if I wanted
some corporate suit type,
I would've stayed
in Boston
and hung out
at singles bars.
Really?
No.
I don't want you
to change.
You're my van Gogh;
you're not--
you're not
my Donald Trump.
And another thing,
my sweet, sweet man,
I do not want you
to grow the hell up.
I'll try not to.
Page 37, para 2,
I think this reveal
happens too early.
I could be wrong.
No.
Where would you
move it to?
What?
I said, uh, where
would you move it to?
I was thinkin' about
the-- the end here.
Um, maybe,
uh, page 40?
Before Norman leaves?
It's only a suggestion.
If you don't want to...
I don't.
I don't want to.
Mmm.
Are you alright?
Yeah, sure.
Good.
You just look...
It doesn't
make you happy?
What?
What? Sex.
Oh, that.
Do you have
an ethical problem?
You know, me being
your editor,
that kind of thing?
No.
Because it won't
affect our work.
I know.
I mean, they're two
separate things.
I know.
I'm a professional.
Kate...
I like the sex.
I like you.
Everything's fine, okay?
Oh, I'm so sorry.
I don't nag.
Usually.
I just, um...
You don't talk
about your life.
At all.
And so, I think...
I think something
happened to you
and maybe if you
told me about it--
You know, I mean,
I can-- I can shut up.
But I can listen, really.
Um, I'm a very good...
listener.
Hey!
Suzanne?
You okay?
Yeah, honey, it's--
it's nothing.
Nothing?
There's all
those sick people
you touch every day
and I don't like it.
Suzanne?
Well, that's what
doctors do, sweetie,
they treat sick people.
Yeah, well,
it's an outrage.
You stay in bed today.
You let Earl
torture someone else.
No, sweetie.
Look, I finally have
a full waiting room.
Just let me go
to work, alright?
Well, then, you should
eat something.
Oh, yeah, right.
I could fry you
some eggs...
in butter.
I can fry 'em up
in bacon fat for ya.
That-- that'll be--
Yeah, hysterical.
Sorry, I got home
too late to cook.
You don't cook.
Okay, so,
everybody, dig in.
Uh, pan fried noodles,
they're my favorite.
I'm on low-carbs.
Oh.
I'll take the noodles.
Mmm.
So, uh, it's great
that we could all do this.
Um, Laurie has read
your stories too.
I love the one about
the country doctor.
Thank you.
Is it from life?
Someone I knew.
Where?
Martha's Vineyard.
You know he's from
Martha's Vineyard, Laurie.
Oh, I love the Vineyard.
What do you do there?
He's a writer, Stephen.
No, I mean for a livin'.
I should put
some music on.
Are you a native
of the Vineyard?
No.
It's wall-to-wall
celebrities there.
Tea? Everybody want tea?
I saw Carly Simon there once.
Do you know her?
No.
She has a big mouth.
Like, a huge mouth.
Where are you from then?
Laurie!
Uh, can you
help me, please?
Do you know any celebrities?
Put water in a kettle
and turn it on high.
Matt, do you know
any celebrities?
I installed a toilet
for Walter Cronkite once.
No kidding.
You know Walter Cronkite.
Huh.
What?
You told me that you
couldn't get pregnant.
No, I told you that there
might be some risks--
You never said "might be."
You said "would be."
Oh, Matt.
You said there would be.
Look, no one
really knows.
I mean, I could have
the easiest pregnancy
in the world
or I could have
some complications.
That makes me feel
a lot better.
Honey... we're gonna
have a baby!
I mean, aren't you happy?
I'd be happy if you go see
those doctors in Boston.
Why?
'Cause all the doctors
on this island are hicks.
Except this one lady doctor
with great boobs.
Oh.
Didn't expect
the Spanish Inquisition.
Alright, um...
The stress test doesn't
look that good to us.
There's weakness
in two of your valves.
And we, uh, discussed it
and we think it would be...
prudent for you
to terminate the pregnancy.
No.
Suzanne...
Look, I didn't just fall
off the truck, Phil.
I'm a doctor too.
I know what the risks are.
I also know that
if the three of you help me,
I can have this baby.
Am I wrong?
I don't know.
Is that your
medical opinion?
Alright, tough guy, we can,
um, give it some time,
see what happens.
Thank you.
Yeah.
Oh, be careful.
Look, if they
don't think
you should have
the baby, Suzanne--
No, I want
the baby, Matt.
We can adopt.
No, I wanna have
our baby.
Honey, I know that this
is gonna work out. Okay?
So three hot-shot doctors
are wrong and you're right.
Look, they agreed
to help, so--
And you gave 'em
a choice?
Well, it's my body.
Oh, so that makes
suicide, alright.
Suicide?
If you kill yourself
for this baby,
I call it suicide.
Oh, God, you--
What?
You don't--
You have no idea
what you're talking about.
What, the house painter
can't have an opinion?
No, not about medicine. No!
It's not about medicine.
It's about you
risking your life!
And I can have
an opinion about that!
I can have an opinion
about the-- the one woman
in this world
that I love!
That I will not
live without!
Okay, okay, okay.
It's okay to worry, honey.
It's okay to worry.
You got-- you gotta
trust me on this, Matt.
Alright? I'm not gonna
put myself in danger.
I promise you that.
I love you too much.
I'm not gonna leave you.
Just, please, don't give up
on this baby, okay?
I can stay.
All weekend?
I think Walter Cronkite'll
muddle through.
You know, I-- I know
that it's hard for you.
I mean, I could--
I could come up
to the Vineyard
one weekend.
I can take the ferry over
and you could pick me up
and drive me around.
Or no, we, uh--
we could rent bikes
and then ride around,
you know, if it's nice out.
And then you could show me
all the local spots.
And then you could
show me your house.
Then you could
show me your bed.
No.
What?
No what?
Nothing. Let's just go
back to the table.
You don't want me
in your bed?
Is that it?
Don't, please.
Don't what?
Don't say anything
that might disturb you?
Well, I'm sorry,
but I just don't know
what will disturb you
because you won't tell me.
I have to go.
Oh, no you don't.
Cabby!
Wait one damn minute!
I don't wanna talk
about it, Kate.
Well, too bad!
Kate!
I have had it, buddy!
I'm so sick of tip-toeing
around here!
You have problems?
Well, boo hoo!
I have problems too!
Yeah, so I've heard.
Yeah!
Because when two people
sleep together,
they're supposed to share
more than just sex.
I am what I am.
Take it or leave it.
That is not
how it works!
Then it doesn't work!
Stop!
Cabby!
You will deal
with this!
Cabby!
You coward!
You're just a coward!
Coward! Coward!
Coward!
No!
Ready?
I'm not goin' anywhere.
Oh...
That's beautiful.
Now watch.
Oh...
For little Herman.
His name is Nicholas.
Kate?
I'm sorry.
Okay...
Once, there was
an ordinary man
who lived
on a special island
full of celebrities.
One night,
he went to Sam's Clams
and his life changed
for the good.
Then it changed again
for the bad.
Then it changed again.
He sold a book
of short stories.
After many years
of trying and failing,
it should have brought him
more pleasure than it did,
but what brought him
pleasure was the...
smart and beautiful editor
they assigned him.
So they agreed
to a lunch date,
even though the restaurant
wasn't as good as Sam's Clams.
And she talked...
and listened.
And before
the crme brle came...
he knew that she'd
change his life again.
That's it;
that's the best
I can do.
That's good enough.
Hey, sweetheart!
There's nothin' to eat.
Could you come down
and fix me something?
Well, if you're hungry,
then I'll just haul
my ten-ton butt
outta bed
and make you
a bologna sandwich,
because you're a man,
and you couldn't possibly
put two pieces
of bread together--
Happy birthday!
I love you, honey.
Hi.
Did you get it?
What did you get me?
See ya.
Oh, God!
She got me
a black thong.
Honey, she got me
a thong.
I'll never be able
to wear that again.
Okay.
What? Is-- is this
my gift?
Oh...
Oh, you have a bow.
You've got a bow,
huh, huh?
Wanna dance
with a house?
You sure?
One slow dance.
Did you see me
holding Julia's baby?
You're a natural.
Yes, I am.
I mean, I know that
I'm a great doctor,
but I'm going to be
a fabulous mother.
Hmm. You are.
And I'm going to be
a great father.
Okay, you know what?
Enough dancing.
Let's go inside.
Alright.
Whoops.
Suzanne?
Matt...
Suzanne, I'm right here.
Suzanne...
Connie?
I'm sorry.
The Kind and I
at the playhouse.
I was Anna.
The baby, the baby...
Yes, we have a heartbeat.
But we're more concerned
about you right now.
The baby...
Suzanne, Suzanne...
The baby okay?
Hey, baby.
Suzanne...
Suzanne?
Better?
Oh, I'm really dry.
Here.
Oh, that's cold.
Okay.
We've got your BP
under control.
Your bloods are improving,
but I want to keep you here
just for tonight.
I gotta go call Melanie.
Everyone's waitin' to hear.
They're still awake?
I'll be right back.
Okay.
Matt, Matt, her stats
just dropped off the cliff.
She's shutting down.
We have to take
the baby right now.
Please, do not
get in my way.
It's 183.
Give it gas.
Here, put this on.
Suzanne,
I'm right here,
alright?
It's okay, baby.
It's gonna be okay.
Give me a 10 blade
and separators on the field.
Got it.
I'm right here, Suzanne.
Infuse three grams
of magnesium sulfate.
I've got my O2 at 100%.
O2 stat's at 93.
I'm right here, baby.
It's okay.
It's gonna be alright.
We're gonna need
separators--
It'll be okay.
Baby not responsive.
He's not moving.
Respiratory's down--
Get me suction.
I need a bag.
He's not moving.
Right here,
I gotta give it suction.
Turn it up to a hundred.
Great, I think
I got something.
Pressure's holding,
130 over 69.
Monitor is steady.
Here we go.
Let's move that up.
Uh-huh.
We're gonna need
a monitor and an EPG.
It's okay.
He won't break.
There you go.
I will never forget
that moment, Nicky.
I got to hold you in my arms
before they took you away.
I got to whisper
for the first time ever,
"I love you,
Nicholas the warrior."
Matt?
Whaddaya think?
I mean, forget
the packing boxes.
And I'm-- I'm gonna get
some more furniture.
Well, I have a bed.
And just because I never cook
doesn't mean I can't.
It just means it's a pain
to cook for one person.
I hope you like
what I'm making.
It's a special meal because
it's a very special night.
I said,
it's a special meal
because it's a very
special night.
I have a present
for you.
I can't do it.
I thought I could.
I wanted to.
And it doesn't
help you any.
I wish--
I just--
I can't.
Oh, wait.
I have a present for you.
See?
It's a rattle.
I'm pregnant,
you son of a bitch!
Ah, Ms. Wilkes.
How are you today?
Knocked up.
Congratulations.
You are most
definitely pregnant.
Great.
I, uh, I have a friend
who's been trying
to get pregnant
for the past year.
I miss one pill,
and bang.
As it were.
How did you miss
your pill?
Oh, you know...
I-- I thought it was gonna
work out with this guy...
I understand.
Well, the, uh, pregnancy's
at a very early stage.
At this point we can
terminate it
with a simple DNC.
Good.
Good. Um, let me just
check my week, um...
crying
Oh, my God.
No.
Suzanne, that's enough!
Honey, I'm supposed
to exercise.
Ask my 15 doctors.
Suzanne?
What?
He misses you.
He told me.
Ugh, Suzanne!
Okay.
Come on.
Hey!
I wanna get there.
Before it gets
too cold!
Hey!
Come on!
Whoohoo!
So?
There you go.
Yeah?
Not all pale and sick?
The patients don't wanna
see a sick doctor.
I don't blame 'em.
Okay.
Come in.
Aw...
Show him off.
Aw, isn't he a cutie?
That it?
That's him.
He the runt
of the litter?
Shut up, Earl.
Okay, let me say "good-bye"
to my little boy.
Okay, alright.
Bye, Mel.
Thank you so much.
Okay, who's first?
As if I didn't know.
Well, that's pretty typical.
I thought your numbness
was on the left side, Earl.
Shifted.
That was more
than half a day.
What was I supposed
to do, sweetie?
Tell Mrs. Garner
to take her walker
and get outta there?
You said half a day,
Connie said half a day.
How's the baby?
Scared you weren't
comin' back.
I'm not kiddin',
Suzanne.
Yeah, I know;
that's the scary thing.
Alright, up to bed.
I'm gonna get you something--
Matt.
--to eat.
Protein.
Matt, Matt,
Matt, Matt.
You've gotta stop.
Okay?
You have to stop
hovering and worrying,
and worrying
and hovering.
I know.
You're really starting
to become a gigantic
pain in the ass.
I know.
I'm fine.
Alright?
The doctor said
I'm fine.
And not just
the hick doctors.
I know.
I promise to be
a smaller pain in the ass.
Sweetie, I take care
of these people, you know?
I owe them.
Now I'm gonna go
kiss my beautiful child
and go for a run
on the beach.
A walk on the beach.
So, what, you gonna
take it to work
with you every day?
I wouldn't be
the first.
Yeah? You gonna nurse it
in front of your authors?
Or, you could
keep it home,
get a nanny who makes
more money than you.
Shh!
Or, Kate, I know.
Just quit, move back home
with Ma and Pa,
get a job
at the Piggly Wiggly.
I am not calling him.
He's a decent guy.
He'll take
responsibility, Kate.
No, you're right.
If I call him, he'll come
and he would try
to make it right.
And tell his wife.
He would, yeah.
And then she would divorce him
and he would marry you,
and move to the city
and take care of the kid.
And he would hate me...
for the rest of his life.
You'd get alimony.
That's very funny.
That's great.
I am not calling him.
Ready?
No.
He's almost
four months old.
Oh, and he hasn't
been to college yet?
He loves it.
[baby crying
Shh, shh, shh.
Shh, shh.
Shh, it's okay.
It's okay, sweetheart
It's okay.
Mama's here.
Oh, oh...
Oh, no, no, no.
Shh, shh, shh.
It's alright.
It's okay, honey.
Don't be scared.
Mama's here.
I'll always be here.
My little boy.
I'm gonna start
full time.
Tomorrow.
What?
The New Yorker.
"Dear Mr. Harrelson,
we very much enjoyed
"your short story,
Nicholas the Warrior.
"And we are happy
to accept it for publication
in our December issue."
Matt...
Oh, Matt.
It only took me
seven years.
They want me to come
to their office.
They wanna bathe
in the author's light.
It's important.
It is?
The first story that
you write about our family
is the first story
you sell?
It's important.
Good things
to happen for us.
So should I wear
my blue suit?
Look what I found.
"Gordon Grey,
the best photographer
"on Martha's Vineyard:
weddings,
special occasions,
babies."
Hmm.
Gordo's a hack.
If you say so, my love.
You're not gonna
take Nicholas there
the minute
I walk away, right?
Bye.
Are you ready for
your close-up, baby doll?
Yeah? Are you?
You're not gonna tell
anybody about this, right?
Especially not Daddy.
It'll be our little secret.
Our little $147 secret.
Oh, yeah.
Looks good, though.
I could use some help.
Yeah, honey, I know, but I have
to go into town really quickly.
They're gonna be here
in an hour.
I know.
I just wanna grab--
We have everything we need.
I just better make sure--
Except the baby pictures.
Which I'm sure are classics.
Oh, honey.
He was so cute.
I'll be back
in plenty of time, okay?
The food's all ready.
Hello, my sweet Nicholas.
It's Daddy.
I have to write this.
I can't think of anything
now except that I have
to talk to you.
But this is so hard,
little boy.
This is the hardest
thing I've ever had to do.
Bye!
Love you.
I let her leave.
I didn't stop her.
I didn't even go to her.
I never even got to
kiss her goodbye, Nicky.
Because you see,
my sweet boy,
Mommy had a heart attack
on the way into town.
Her car went through
the guard rail at the cove.
The doctor said
she died before the crash.
He said she didn't
feel any pain at all.
I want to believe him.
I wind up your music box
and it begins to play.
I reach into your crib and
I touch your sweet cheek.
I place an index finger
in each of your little hands
and let you squeeze.
You're very strong.
But you're not
in your crib, are you.
Because you went
with Mommy that day.
She strapped you
into your car seat
and drove you to town.
She wanted you to be the
first to see your photographs.
Oh, my God.
This is Vineyard Home Services.
Matt isn't here right now,
if you leave a message,
he'll get back to you
as soon as he can. Thanks.
Matt.
I understand now.
And I can't begin to tell
you on this damn machine
how sorry I am.
God, I want to talk to you.
I just--
Wanna tell you
how I'm feeling,
that's all.
So, um, can you
call me back? Please.
So, then Steven's
mother makes a face.
Mmm.
She doesn't say anything,
she just takes one bite,
makes "the face",
and puts her fork down.
But the face says it all.
My daughter-in-law to be
is one step above a hooker.
What I had in mind was a vine,
curling around both sides
of the title,
as if springing from
the base of the book itself.
In a kind of...
paean to medieval illuminati.
I also think...
Um, excuse me--
The tour bus
is down Pleasant Street.
Oh, no. Actually
I'm looking for someone.
He comes in here quite often.
I thought you might
know where he lives.
Got a name?
Um... Matt Harrelson.
You take Water Street to the
Prospect Road straight on out.
Can't miss it.
Big yellow thing.
Thanks, Earl.
Matt!
Hello.
Matt.
Kate.
Yes.
Oh, I'm--
Melanie.
Across the road.
Yeah.
The door wasn't
locked, so I...
Oh, it's an island.
Yeah.
He, he told me about you.
He did?
Yeah.
Do you know when
he's gonna be back?
He's gone.
Gone?
Gone.
Off the island.
Matt.
I got your messages.
I just wanted to thank you
in person for your sympathy.
And for driving out to the
Vineyard, I just wanted you
to know that I appreciate it.
That I'm sorry I wasn't there.
I...
I drove up to Maine,
took the blue roads.
Didn't pay much
attention to anything.
Stopped when it got dark.
I thought about
the first time we met.
I didn't want to meet you.
I didn't want to see you.
I didn't want to start
anything with anyone.
I did my house painting
and I wrote
in my little corner.
And I went to sleep.
And when I couldn't sleep,
which is most of the time...
I talked to Suzanne.
In the dark it seemed
as though she was there.
And it worked.
I found a kind of peace
in that house.
And then I met you.
And my life changed.
Like I told you.
But it-- it wasn't--
it was more than that.
I...
I started to feel myself...
let go of Suzanne.
but I kept her close
to me for over a year.
I checked Nicholas' crib and...
...every single day.
I was faithful.
I couldn't stand
letting them go.
I blamed fate
for bringing me to you.
I blamed ambition.
But most of all I blamed you.
And I knew that was wrong.
Suzanne and Nicholas died,
and I couldn't know
they were gonna die.
And I couldn't
have saved them.
They're gone.
Both of them.
For whatever reason
I'm not...
I'm still here.
Because I'm still here...
I am required to carry on.
That's what I figured out
driving north.
That I'm required
to carry on.
That's just the way it is.
Matt. Um...
But wouldn't you like
another chance?
At what?
Everything.
Love and...
marriage.
Children.
Yes.
I lived four months
with Nicholas.
Four months was
not enough time.
I'm sorry. I didn't come
here to make you cry.
Matt.
What?
It'll keep.
Closed-Captioned By
J.R. Media Services, Inc.
Burbank, CA