Titanic sank in the Guile of April 15
Flight 800: 230 people died, explosion happened in the seats 23J and 23K
(names)... count 23 letters
On December 11, 1941, War was declared in Germany
Hitler committed suicide in April 1945
Cesar a total of 23 times was stabbed.
The Mayan believed that the end of the world would happen on December 23, 2012.
Charles Manson was born on November 12.
"although I walk for the it is worth of the shadow of the death..." Psalm 23
::: NUMBER 23 :::
--- Legends for C4M4RGO, have fun! ---
FEBRUARY 3
One week behind...
... everything that seemed out of the normal
and that was mine have a birthday
Meow
Pardon!
I am only bored.
Oh!
Unit 5 in the he/she listens?
Do you listen to me, Unit 5?
Clear... Actually, the things
they began before here...
How am I?
Honesty?
Do I seem a rock star, not?
You this great one!
What does Hey, happen with you?
Why this so strange one?
Using drugs? Smoking a cigarette? Hein? Hein?
Have fun!
Maggie!
Everything well?
- This sexy one...
- I thought you would not like...
As much as in the day
in that I met you
Hopefully it will be contagious
I could be immune
And the one what with the party happens?
Will he/she miss of me?
And the cake?
I Only want two words
in mine it cuts
IT IS "BEEN..."
AND if I had order the
do I plan for caralho?
This single one this night, Walter?
Actually not.
He/she walks, we go!
Why is not going with me
to the room of the female dogs?
AND IF it had been more...
And it would not go with you
there inside unless...
... it was the last female dog of the world.
... cautious"
Sparrow...
we have a visualization
no identified.
It only lacks one minute pras five, Jill!
Then you agree that still
this of service, not?
Clear...
He/she seems delicious!
Can I take for trip?
This well, this well...
He/she comes with the dad!
I want to hear his/her story
Yes, we will have fun...
It was once a dog
with a horror life
but he/she didn't fear anybody
he/she had some teeth
very sharp
and the full belly...
but with an empty heart
therefore he/she wanted to leave traveling
for a place a lot, very far
It ties that arrived one day
a wide stick...
With a ring in the tip
And he invited to enter
the dog was hypnotized
And on this night...
An enormous cloud of smoke
leave the chimney
but with
a horrible smell
because he/she will see
The man was from China
And in China
The dogs are eaten
Let us see who and his/her owner
Curse!
An easy work, hein?
Good Ta...
I can live with one
little of critic
I don't believe
Very well friend
Be quiet
Now the where you were?
I Destine
Maybe the word is big
too much for him
If it had been gentile with Cybill
she would not have ordering me behind of that dog
it is then I would not have me late
with Agatha this night
AND nothing of that would have happened
But I was late
and that was enough
He/she only looks
Yes, he/she tries not to vomit
Cursed dog of the hell
I go kill him/it.
It is will be like this a...
Damned dog killed of the hell.
He/she breathes bottom.
Everything will be well.
And remember that and yours has a birthday.
He/she had not thought about that.
Why have to see
do their friends in mine have a birthday?
Maybe because you don't have friends.
He/she makes sense.
Well, I am old, I am deformed,
and I have to live at the hell.
No.
And haul of that have you to stand.
Of face it is noticed that this very well
compared with other.
Well, I am also crazy.
I will wait for the film.
Didn't he/she forget of anything?
Of the one what?
The number 23.
A Story of Obsession, by Topsy Kretts.
I Entered in paranoia and I passed
for changes never before views.
Care with the dog in the door to the side.
To that...
Ta playing with me?
I will buy for you.
It swallows the candies.
February 3 makes me to be aquariano
The "experts" say that the
friends are extremely vital.
Hello
Hello.
He/she lets to give you a kiss.
I am an alive proof of the
lie of the Astrology.
Hello, as it goes?
Everything well...
he/she has to come more times
Bird...
Birds...
The Mister of the Flies.
All of the characters of this book are fictitious.
And any one similar to any
person lives or died...
... he/she should not continue to read.
It was good the party.
What does the one know?
What?
Let us be outside a little more.
Dear...
It will be romantic.
But also this cold.
He/she catches my coat.
I tie you!
Mom, dad... Hi for you!
He/she hoped he/she was sleeping,
it was not for being hearing anything.
Dad, I forgot to give you this.
I wrapped.
This getting better more and more.
Did you wrap him/it?
Clear...
Good, very well.
Filho...
Her and a good girl.
Guarantee that continues like this.
With certainty dad, good night...
Happy I have a birthday!
Thank you.
THE FATHER OF THE YEAR.
Chapter 1.
I can call myself of Fingerling.
No and my true name.
It comes from a book that I read when he/she was child.
Fingerlin in the zoo.
The leaves were consumed at times,
he/she had a green layer, with texture,
and it was probably
my first book.
Love, no longer I remember more
on what it was...
the only thing that I remember and the name.
Fingerling.
He/she always wanted that went mine.
It is now and.
February 4.
And his/her first fight?
With an animal, yes.
My wife and defender of the animals.
Talk me about that animal that you fought.
What would make if he/she found him/it again?
It would arise in my van and it accelerated
he/she ties to hear a "tugh."
He/she excuses, he/she was playing...
That was stupidity.
Mister, the rules of the animal control
they are that any official...
... that has been attacked by an animal owes
to have to help psychological for a period of 7 days...
... to revalue his/her mental state.
I served him my arm in a plate...
... I cannot be crazy for that.
I committed a mistake, he/she writes down there,
I know that committed a mistake.
And my fault.
And I eat when he/she said my wife that
she could choose the color of the walls of the room.
It was not a very intelligent idea.
Have a good morning, Mr. Sparrow
No, I think you and the person
more intelligent than I know.
But I am not sure.
He/she looks, I like the work and I am good in that.
It can already go.
Yes, but...
Don't worry.
No and that it is badly, I do for his/her good.
You no and dangerous for anybody.
Therefore it can go and to remove the day off.
Truth?
Clear.
Mr. Sparrow.
What did his/her color wife choose for the walls?
Red.
He/she chose red.
Chapter 2.
He/she imagines me is gotten.
In somebody that you already knew.
Somebody that you maybe have liked.
Or better...
Imagine like you.
When small it was the best of my class.
It was not because he/she liked to study.
But yes because I knew that to study
it was my best chance of leaving of there.
The stork dropped me off at a covered in dust town.
He/she didn't have wrong there.
Compared with other annoying towns,
we overcame her measured.
I had friends.
But it felt always alone.
Nobody never left.
But I would not die here.
No matter how much I love him,
he/she didn't want to seem in anything with my father.
He seemed always very distant, and sad.
The numbers were his/her life.
He was an accountant and he/she waited
that I continued his/her business.
But I had other plans.
My mother was happy
when I completed 8 years.
And I announced that he/she wanted to be a detective.
It was not like this with my father.
He was losing his/her master plan.
And that went increasing his/her hate for the
widow Dobkins, she lived to the side.
He/she seems strange, but it was for his/her dog,
Alfie, that I turned into detective.
The gram and always more green of the other
side of the fence, at least according to Alfie.
Therefore always it was in our garden,
and it was my work catch him/it.
But I never entered in the garden
of the widow Dobkins.
That era a rule of my father.
In my eighth I have a birthday...
... I broke the rule.
I admit that my solitude and obsession
with the detectives' stories...
... they had fed fantasies
and I am not sure of all the details.
Except one.
The widow Dobkins was dead.
He/she took one hour ties that medicate him/it arrived.
And for that hour,
my 8 year-old mind accelerated.
I decided that a crazy man
it had killed the widow Dobkins.
Crazy as our town
he/she had never seen.
Nobody would be safe,
nor their dear beings.
Mainly their dear beings.
Of course medicates him/it
he/she said that was suicide.
But I never believed.
My mind was open
for a new existence.
There it began a detective to be born.
Detective Fingerling.
That and... that and too much.
Here this. What this doing?
I will clean everything soon.
This with the head full of nonsenses?
Did he/she read this?
Almost everything, and very creative.
That Fingerling...
Yes, and a good name.
Yes? And that impression you had?
I was liking,
at least in the beginning.
Why in the beginning?
Well, the how much you read?
Two chapters.
Can it move that stairway? Right here.
He/she knows that Fingerling reminds me
of my life, and so strange...
And as my childhood, my memoirs...
Does it pass me the blue paint?
Take.
Fingerling doesn't seem anything with you.
No? He/she looks at this...
"Fingerling in the Zoo",
my mother read for me when child.
With certainty a lot of people he/she read
when he/she was child.
Did you read?
- No.
- Daaaaaaa...
But every time that I read a book,
and as if the author stole me
something that only I knew.
Some day I will write something
and that had happened with other.
I don't know wanted, and really eccentric.
Many neighborhoods exist with houses
as yours.
With streets as yours.
Yes, and with dogs to the side?
His/her neighbor had a dog, that unusual.
He/she didn't call himself Alfie, he/she calls himself Genius,
"Bad-tempered", my father called him/it.
He/she always escaped, for that
I work in the Control of Animals.
Fingerling and a detective.
I collected detectives' magazines.
The widow to the side? You Dobkins?
And as my mother.
He/she died in the day that completed 8 years.
He/she looks, he/she gets tied up ruffled...
Dear, continue reading.
Therefore descubrira that Fingerling doesn't have
anything similar to you.
Somebody wrote a book
on the dad?
- No.
- Yes.
Yes.
- How was the school?
- Horrible.
Am I in him?
If and on the dad,
I should have a spectacular paper.
Yes, you would owe, but you don't have.
Is it there, what do you think that means?
Gee.
- Who and that?
- Fabrizia.
Fabrizia.
Chapter 5
I know the blond suicide.
They informed me of the neighbors' surveillance.
I know that he/she wants to do some thing,
but it had not worked.
Arrive close and I kill myself.
I hope not,
today and mine has a birthday.
If you do that,
he/she will end up being the worst of all of the times.
You and pathetic.
I am making that of truth...
To hang and a painful thing.
Most that it is hung,
he/she puts an end to a permanent necklace.
A memory finds strange of
how miserable they are.
He/she goes, we will talk...
If it it continues depressed, I put you
a candy among the eyes.
I have good aim.
Is it true that and does yours have a birthday?
The blond suicide, told me that was already
a good person, but now...
... I am a bad person.
He/she didn't want to leave you angry.
You don't have that power.
You should see my former-boyfriend
I will show you.
And I was quiet for one moment.
But then she said:
- And this number, that cursed number.
23.
He dominates my world.
And my father's fault, he said that
it found a way of winning the number
That he had won,
that I was safe.
He/she said: dad you love.
He will make something to guarantee
that you don't inherit the curse.
He was wrong.
His/her warranty if it returned with
the blood with that I write.
I believe that dad didn't like me enough.
This everywhere.
Plates, you paginate of books,
it ties in the lights of the elevators.
This in my name and in the
words that I say.
Anything, anything and safe.
Because my favorite and pink color.
Do you know him/it what rose and?
Red 27.
White 65.
65 + 27 = 92
Rose has 4 letters, 92 divide for 4.
The porra of the 23!
For being sincere, I didn't understand anything.
I asked the only question
that I remembered.
Does he/she have more coffee?
THE STAIRWAYS FOR THE SKY
It was important that she continued speaking.
I told like this him/her a story.
I had an uncle that called her Charlie.
His/her horoscope said that he/she would fall in love
for a dressed woman of red.
Like this he left, it sought everyday
for a, it ties that he/she found.
Six months later, were married.
Lie.
Two years later the red wife got divorced
of my uncle. Everything diffused and it left.
Him this outside...
... at this time...
... it still looks for the dressed woman of red.
He/she believes that he/she found the wrong.
Was that for doing to feel better?
You seem smarter than my uncle Charlie.
She had a face done to smile.
And while I leave the building, it thought
I had one more work than it was well done.
The following day I sought the former-boyfriend
that the blond suicide mentioned.
To burn glasses of coffee
and an old trick policeman.
To eliminate the smell of the death in the scene of the crime.
But somebody had consumed
the whole coffee.
When I counted Fabrizia
on the suicidal loiria...
She asked me that took her/it to his/her apartment.
His/her reaction was Fabrizia purely.
Death and sex.
That aphrodisiac.
While you paginate them if they loosened of the walls...
... the reach of the obsession of the
blond suicide if it turned clear.
She had reduced everything to 23.
This everywhere, dates, hours.
Plates, you paginate of books,
it ties in the lights of the elevators.
This in my name.
And in the words that I speak.
When I discovered his/her name,
that was also fit in in the sum.
Maybe it only went a coincidence. I want to say...
... a name and only a name, and
a number and only a number.
No and?
Printed by him same, edited by him same...
... it is an author that I never heard to speak.
He/she seems that this Topsy no
he/she wrote anything nor before nor later.
Walter, that this doing?
He/she looks at this.
Walter Sparrow doesn't work,
but if I use my second name...
Walter.
5, 1, 1, 9, 7.
No and incredible?
What?
Everything and 23.
Mine has a birthday, driver's license,
number of safe social, everything.
I was born 11:12 in the night,
11 more 12
And as if he/she was imitating my life.
You cannot be speaking serialize.
The author knows a lot about me,
I feel that he/she chose me.
Did he/she do that all the day?
Did he/she finish the book?
Not yet.
He/she concentrates on small nuances and
you arrive crazy conclus.es.
And the fact that Fingerling sees a murderer? How many did you kill?
Wait.
Who does he kill?
He/she asks the Mr. Fingerling.
Pardon love.
Why this color?
Why did choose this color?
I don't know, you tell me.
Red number 5. R, and, d and 27
(red in English). Plus 5 and 32, that and...
This exaggerating.
Of course exists differences.
Fingerling and a detective,
I catch dogs.
- He met Fabrizia when he/she had 32, I met you with...
- 23
And that day we met each other?
September 14.
And 14 more 9 and?
23.
We got married on October 13,
13 more 10, 23.
He/she dominated the world of the blond suicide, it killed himself for that.
He/she surrendered Fingerling in the day that did 32: 23 to the I contradict.
Fingerling said that was destiny (fate). Does he/she know his/her value númerico? 32!
"I contain my case, meritíssimo."
I think this taking everything serializes her too much.
We lived in the 1814.
I say that 18 and more than 8 and it is equal to 9.
And 9 more 14 and equal to 23.
14 and 1 more 4 that of the 5.
- And 5 + 18 also and 23!
- My God!
Ok Robin, don't begin with that joke.
Nobody this of joke.
I say that 5 more 18 and 23.
Because if the book went 27 or 150, he/she could make the same.
18 + 14 and 32.
23 to the I contradict.
Frightening, hein?
Chapter 7.
The suicidal loiria provokes in Fabrizia an enthusiasm of new emoc.es.
I followed the life, but everything that I got to think was in a number.
Thank you.
Didn't he/she tell you that the clock behind the table indicated 9:14?
Fake that he/she has a knife. Fake that he/she has a knife.
I know that will be sorry.
He/she shuts up, furious!
Or you die.
Of course I would never hurt truth Fabrizia.
I loved her.
And it thought she loved me.
But I began to have horrible nightmares.
8. 9. 10, 11, 12, 13...
What this doing?
I am reading.
This crazy one?
FEBRUARY 6
Isaac?
In practical terms, and a box that accumulates organic energy.
We will speak about WIlbelm Reich
next week, thank you.
He/she seems a fascinating book.
They exist many few books
in that the protagonist plays Saxophone.
He/she didn't know that he/she played.
I don't play. No and that that matters...
And the number, I see him/it everywhere.
An aficcionado for a conspiracy...
For all, the world has a Ray of 23 degrees, when I say that 23,5 say that 5 and only 2 + 3.
23 and very good for this
I play in matter.
Game?
Yes! Paranoia.
A lot of literature exists on the Enigma of the 23.
Do exist?
23 axioms exist in the
geometry of Euclides.
The human body possesses 46 chromosomes,
23 of the father and 23 of the mother.
The blood takes 23 seconds to circulate.
The Mayan believed that the end of the world would happen
on December 23, 2012.
- 20 + 12 and?
- 23 to the I contradict. Or 20 + 1 + 2. Then, which and this... What and 23?
God...
2 divided by 3.
0,666.
666. The number of the devil.
Only 22 chapters exist in Apocalypse.
And all know as that finishes.
23 no and a gift, and a curse.
The truth and that a very select group of people exists...
... that he/she is delighted in perpetuating the infamy of a number.
The 7 of the luck.
The 13 of the bad luck.
The shoes of an old player's luck.
There are people that only prays because he/she believes that God angers to help.
That and a magic thought, without rational scientific.
Now that it seeks the 23, you always anger finds him/it.
Agatha thinks am crazy.
Finish the book.
If after reading everything still to believe
that the subject and you...
... the author knows you well and he will only be able to answer you.
And a good idea.
Meanwhile, I can speak to Agatha if he/she wants.
All of the nights it killed Fabrizia in my dreams.
I explained to the psychiatrist the sum of his/her name.
23. What does think that means?
I don't know, Miles.
Who knows should be a damned accountant.
The Dr. Phoenix recommends hurt me.
He/she should leave of you hurt.
As if the time got well.
The time and a gentile man.
The time and only a murderous system...
... with numbers with a composed meaning arrested to him.
In any way, I also prescribe myself some you hurt.
Emotional license.
Then no and one more detective.
Fabrizia no longer it was impressed.
I am a detective of you hurt.
Then you don't have a weapon.
I still have these.
Maybe should sleep this night.
The number was for all sides.
At this time I don't need to say how many equal of shoes she had.
What are these shoes making in the garbage can?
Did he/she know that you had 23 equal?
You this crazy one.
They threw the bomb in Hiroshima the 8:15.
8 + 15 = 23
Explos.es in Waco, Texas and in Oklahoma City they were on April 19.
4 + 19 = 23.
The Tropic of Cancer: 23,5 degrees north. Capricorn: 23,5 degrees south.
10886 and the number...
... that Al Capone used in his/her uniform of the prison.
They executed Ted Bundy on January 23.
Everything and 23.
She didn't understand.
What was not problem, since I didn't also understand.
He/she only knew that the number had followed the blond suicide.
Isabel Lydia Hunt.
Now it came behind me...
Can I speak to Fabrizia, if he/she wants?
I believe that he/she said him/it at this time with a certain innocence.
But thinking well.
Can I speak to Fabrizia, if he/she wants?
He/she wanted to have reacted different.
He/she should have given me bill of the truth.
I know that and absurdity.
But it ties the color of the tie betrays him.
Do you know him/it what and the pink color?
Red: 27, white: 65. 65 + 27 and 92.
Rose has 4 letters,
92 divided by 4.
23, caralho!
Meanwhile he/she could speak to Agatha, if he/she wants?
Paranoia.
23 and very good for this
I play in matter.
Paranoia.
Can I speak to Agatha?
2 divided by 3.
And 0,666.
When they say that and 23,5 and they say that 5 and 2 + 3.
You seek the 23.
CLOSED
Meanwhile he/she could speak to Agatha, if he/she wants?
Chapter 21
Oh, my God.
.Ag?
My God, My God.
And a nightmare. And a nightmare. And a nightmare.
Everything will be well.
Ag.
I don't want him to worry.
I only need one night to clear my head.
Please don't give up of me.
His/her husband that loves you and he/she catches dogs, Walter.
Why this street?
Why this hotel?
How was I selected?
Good morning.
In what I can help?
Well, I want...
... a room.
Sign the registration.
The 27 and the most silent.
And the 23?
We have been having plumbing problems with the 23.
Chapter 22.
He/she happened what I feared.
Playing damned games.
Plus 4 and 48, more 50.
Tropic of Capricorn.
It was not a very happy end.
It was not an end at all.
After the Chapter 22, there was not anything else haul of the question:
Did the number live for killing another day?
Was the number behind Fingerling?
It is now vineyard behind me.
You?
And everything his/her fault.
If he/she didn't have me late.
A place to rest in peace.
Yes.
I caught you, son of the prostitute.
He/she calms, he/she had wakened up in some hours just with a headache.
Now no this so ferocious one.
Filthy and evil dog.
L, M, N, 14.
THE, B, C, D, E.
Shit.
Ned, Ned.
I am priest Sebastian, I suppose that that has an explanation.
This sleeping. I work for the
Control of Animals. And his/her dog?
And of Barnaby, my gardener.
Don't worry Barnaby, he had been well, only this sleeping.
Why did call him/it of Ned?
I didn't go I, was lost and I adopted him/it, he likes cemeteries.
He/she sits down and it observes them cut as if it was protecting them.
I invented like this his/her nickname, "Guardian of the Deads."
Lately and this.
Been born on February 10, 1968.
Died on February 10, 1991.
No and possible.
What does happen he/she, son?
He/she died in the day that completed 23 years.
We can suppose like this.
What?
That he/she died.
They never found the body, and only one cuts.
- Where was it?
- In the library. No and a simple book.
It is true, the number leaves you crazy, he/she makes to do you things.
Terrible things.
And better I to go.
No, I want him to see this. All you.
They murdered a called university student Laura Tollins.
They never found his/her body, but his/her bed was full of blood.
This man killed her, Kyle Flinch.
They found his/her weapon, a butcher knife, with their digital impress.es.
Walter, that was to 15 years.
Ag, was not just his/her teacher
of psychology, they were lovers.
Everything that you/they did together - sexually -
it was as the characters of the book.
He said that the knife was her idea.
She wanted to fake an attack.
Kyle Flich.
And Topsy Kretts.
The book and yours.
Disturbed literary confession.
Agatha said that a dog told you this.
Ned, no and any dog, and the Guardian of the Deads.
What does happen with all these 23?
And his/her name, and the one of the other ones?
And everything a coincidence?
I don't know.
But I know who can tell me.
FEBRUARY 8
He/she arrived 2 days before.
You knew that I would come.
The reporters always come on the 10.
The day in that killed Laura Tollins.
The day that you/they removed her/it of me.
I am not a reporter, my name is Walter Sparrow.
I was born on February 3.
Late congratulations...
In February 3, 2-3.
Yes.
Don't fake that he/she doesn't understand, Topsy Kretts.
I Read his/her book.
Speak to me about the number.
And for that what did he kill her?
I need to know, you have to tell me.
What does he/she/you happen you?
I fear that is passing for me.
What me acontence?
Does he/she want to know the worst of being in the prison?
His/her family, his/her sister, their parents, all come to visit you.
With the time, they stop coming, and his/her sister stops coming entirely.
Therefore he/she notices that his/her mother doesn't look at you more in the eyes.
Therefore she had also stopped coming.
Finally his/her father says that his/her sister had a nervous collapse.
He/she didn't get to work with the fact of having a murderous brother.
He/she has tears in the eyes when it tells you that, but no this sad one.
This with rage.
That and the last time that he/she sees him/it.
I didn't kill Laura.
I loved her.
And I didn't write a book on a number.
You this lying.
I am arrested by a crime that I didn't commit, Mr. Sparrow.
But I believe that their problems are worse than mine.
You and a damned liar.
- No.
- Yes.
No.
If I had writing a book.
It would not use a ridiculous name like Topsy Kretts.
A Story of Obsession, by Topay Kretts.
It was very convincing on his/her innocence.
Well, murderers usually the healthy.
Their impress.es were in the knife,
her blood in his/her hand when he called for Police.
And innocent.
Why doesn't his/her name add 23?
The true murderer, the author, this loosens, I have that you find him/it.
Wait, I know how it can find him/it.
Yesterday the night, when he/she was reading the book.
I found the number of a Post office box in the end.
- Doesn't nothing want inside?
- Only the stuffing.
- When does he/she want that arrives?
- Tomorrow of guile.
- He/she will have to Be expressed.
- Everything well.
That and everything?
No... No... We want...
We want 23 of them.
I dreamed that I killed you, Ag.
Fingerling had the same dream on Fa...
I am going with you today.
And everything this will finish.
You would not hurt me, Walter.
He/she would not hurt anybody, never.
How does he/she know?
FEBRUARY 9
Here they are their boxes, garotao.
Now we will see if somebody appears.
It can be that is not the author, maybe nor be a name.
Well.
We will know soon.
- Walter, looks.
- What?
Somebody entered.
And he, has to be.
Do you find?
He/she looks for him, he/she has to be him.
He/she finished the game, Topsy Kretts.
You should be dead.
I will call the Police.
Stop, unfortunate, stop!
Who and you?
What does the number, mean?
I think you know.
Oh my God, an ambulance.
God of the sky.
He/she calls an ambulance, by God.
Don't dare to die.
Does he/she listen to me? Don't die.
Walter, please.
Only he can help us
to return to the normal.
No this helping, I want that you and Robin space home.
He needs a hospital, I will take care of that.
But he knows.
Take Robin and go home.
I said that will take care of that.
He knows.
Shit.
He/she had to liberate of me.
What?
And a madness.
What did he go mad?
And difficult.
Get rid of him.
The Institute.
Go there.
You will see.
Oh my God.
Agatha?
Walter, he didn't survive, I feel a lot.
Did something say?
No.
I feel a lot.
Who did you discover he was?
No. I will arrive home soon.
INSTITUTE NATHANIEL - CARE
PSYCHIATRIC
You
this
reading
Hell? ... this... waiting
Man Sparrow.
Oh, caralho!
They are me zoando...
Robin.
Each twentieth-third word of each twentieth-third paginates.
Visit Casanoca Spark. Marry under the stairways for the sky.
Who and Casanova Spark?
No and a person.
You adverto: "the hell you wait, Sparrow"
We have to go.
Dear Ag: We went
to the park Casanova
19 more 4 = 23
5 + 18
They are 23.
What did he go mad?
SPARROW
In case No. 85307
Does he/she want to bet that they are 23?
11, 12...
20, 21, 22...
Is he/she sure that he/she wants to do this?
Is it if the mom is right?
Is it if that man was not the author?
If it was alone his/her father or something like that?
I think that we have many "and if..."
Doesn't he/she mean that the true murderer still this the free?
Did he/she hear something?
This beginning to be similar to me, garotao.
Me of the the flashlight.
Me of the the flashlight!
Santo Deus...
We should go.
Me of the the flashlight, walks.
Me of the the flashlight!
We will leave of here.
There this a, soon there!
Be here.
911! Which and his/her emergency?
He/she has to order somebody
to the Parque Casanova.
By chance that and a joke?
This emptiness.
What?
He/she was...
He/she was there.
We are not crazy.
Each twentieth-third word of each twentieth-third paginates us said so that we came here.
And am I seeming totally crazy, ne?
They will sleep, we finished here.
10-23, we don't have anything.
Mom?
Oh, dear.
Are we going for house, good ta?
Yes.
A skeleton cannot be to put of foot like this and to flee.
You were right, that man was not the murderer...
The true murderer this loosens and he/she knows that dad the search.
The book had secret messages to each 23 paginate.
With certainty, to each 23 you paginate of the book.
Already I am enough the two.
Listen to me, 23 and only a number...
He/she doesn't have magic meaning, the people create that.
It doesn't import how many lunatics fantasized
on the number, but they make a mistake.
Any curse doesn't exist.
No there is none murder free.
And him.
That and Ned.
Filthy and evil dog,
and a dead dog.
Father!
Walter!
You
You were
You moved the skeleton
No knife that
How did he/she know?
Unless...
His/her unmarried woman last name and Rose
What does the one know and Rose?
Red and white. 92 divided by 4.
Some day I will write,
and that had happened with other.
My God!
Who wrote you knows well,
and he will only be able to answer you.
You wrote him/it.
Did Isacc know about that, not?
Walter, forgets that, please.
You and Topsy Kretts.
Maybe nor be a man.
- Don't force me to do this.
- Why Ag?
Why did make this?
With who this living?
So that this, Ag?
What will make with this?
I diffused to protect us...
... of who found in the mail.
Did he/she want to kill the poor man that published his/her book?
To protect his/her secret?
I will take charge of that.
He was alive when you ordered us away.
Robin had listened to you.
Don't we want that, truth?
That our son knows the horrible truth about the mother.
Mother, what does father, happen?
Her and Topsy Kretts.
She wrote the book.
No, no and truth.
Will his/her father loosen the knife, no and, Walter?
Tell him the truth.
Say how it took the skeleton.
Yes, Isacc and I moved the skeleton.
Truth?
And it would return her do him/it,
but I didn't write the book.
Don't lie. 13 years, Ag.
13 years of lies!
He/she ended.
No, no knife that with us, Walter!
Who wrote the book?
Say who wrote him/it.
Say!
You wrote the book, Walter.
SPARROW
In case No. 85307
I found this with the things of the old.
A Story of Obsession, by Topsy Kretts.
A Story of Obsession, by Walter Paul Sparrow
- You wrote my name there.
- No.
No, no, not.
Lie! This lying!
I didn't write that.
Then who was it?
You!
Were you two, you two the whole time, not?
What and that?
What this doing?
Father?
Father, what this happening?
Who killed the widow Dobkins?
Walter, let to help us.
The dressed woman of red.
That anger to do to feel better.
The case of the seductive Italian.
Curse!
Walter!
Naoooooo!
Leave!
We will catch his/her car.
We go, dear.
Chapter 23
They can call me of Fingerling.
But my true name and Walter.
Walter Paul Sparrow.
The one that you read ties here no and all the truth.
Most was changed to protect innocent.
And the criminal.
Once I read that the only philosophical question that matters...
... and to commit suicide or not.
I suppose that that makes me a philosopher.
He/she can one to say that and my decision.
After my mother's death...
... my father didn't get to tolerate...
... he/she didn't leave any ticket.
Only a number.
That number pursued me of adoptive house. it marries adoptive...
It ties the University, when I met her.
Laura Tollins.
I believed that she would help me to forget the number of my father.
It was a mistake to think that I would escape.
Press well.
Tell me that he/she has a knife.
I have a knife.
He/she cuts my blouse.
I will cut you more.
Cut.
I loved her.
And I believed that she loved me.
He/she has an obsession with the number 23.
And quite so has a power on him.
- And a type of madness?
- Yes.
It ties that the number of my father returned the look for me.
This crazy one?
That cursed number!
THE STAIRWAYS FOR THE SKY
When I marked each twentieth-third letter of his/her ticket...
Everything was clear.
The number came behind me.
It is now he wanted her.
Laura, you have to go, please.
I don't get to impede him/it!
What?
The number.
No.
He/she leaves me alone.
Does it think he/she has culhao for using that?
He/she is going ahead!
He/she kills me.
I love you!
I don't love you...
... I never loved you.
How would it be able to?
How could anybody make that?
You and pathetic.
Equal to his/her father.
Release!
I was right.
She was in danger.
Only that I didn't know that
the danger was me.
Laura?
What began as a suicidal ticket, it finished in something more.
In a lot, much more...
Curse, curse!
I see him/it everywhere!
More amusement and games.
Laura?
Shit!
Almost, I am close...
No and truth.
No, no, not.
I love you!
That imbecile!
Sign of admiration!
LAURA DIED
Does he/she remember that?
The number 23
A Story of Obsession, by Walter Paul Sparrow
I believe that was the fall.
You have a serious traumatism...
... something common in case of such severe les.es...
But it could recover the memory,
tomorrow or never again...
And necessary to consider the report of instability
mental of the family.
His/her own father tried to commit suicide.
But he/she didn't have success.
Once Laura's trauma seemed to be a fiction...
And that text?
Severe Grafomania,
result of a mind divagante.
Guilty conscience for survival mixed with an obsession by numerologia.
And something very complicated, Dr.
I will do what can.
Do look, can I be with the book?
Thank you.
My story, my confession.
My name and Dr. Nathaniel.
I will never return her see him/it.
Some hurt they heal in some time...
... some are too deep to recover.
Like this, I preferred to block that horrible thing which I had done...
And their reasons.
- Take care!
- I hope not to see you never again.
I wait like this.
Don't return.
Beauty.
Oh God!
I lament...
Oh not!
Agatha didn't know anything about my past.
Like this, we were two.
He/she was free for the time being.
But the number found a new victim.
The number left me alone
for 13 years...
It ties the night in that she found my book.
Or the book she found.
It was here that I wrote everything.
I went me.
I am a murderer.
I don't know what happened you,
but I know well about this...
... you no and a bad person that got better...
... you were a sick person that got well.
I killed Laura Tollins.
He/she has an innocent man arrested by my cause.
You and a wonderful husband.
And you and the best father
that a son can have.
What Robin would do without you?
But I let to suffer an innocent man.
For my horrible sin.
We were lost, Walter.
Does he/she remind that he/she told me that his/her life began when we met each other?
My life began that day also.
I didn't know who I was.
I want that it leaves, Ag.
You should go before...
Before the one what?
Before it kills me?
Curse, Walter!
Look!
This, this and who you were.
This no and who you and.
I am a murderer!
I killed somebody!
And it could return her do him/it...
Do you think he/she would make him/it again?
Then it takes this.
He/she is going ahead!
If you and a murderer, then kills me!
Look about of you, all those beautiful ones 23!
Don't you want disappoint them, does he/she want?
Knife!
I love you!
No, don't say that...
No, you are not able to...
Nobody can...
Father!
Destiny doesn't exist.
Only different decis.es exist.
It is just a number.
Some decis.es are easy.
Some not.
Those are the ones that matter really.
The ones that define us as people.
THE Mister and my Shepherd, and anything I had lacked...
to Lie down does at green pastures,
it guides me gently you water her calm...
13 years ago, I made a wrong decision.
He/she needed to correct her.
And not only for me.
To die there in the street would have been very easy.
But it would not be exactly.
At least not in the concept of justice
that a father teaches to a son.
They sentenced me in more or less one week.
The lawyer said that the judge will be
indulgent for me to have given me.
Maybe this is not the happiest end of all.
But and the right.
Some day they will give me probation.
And we can proceed with our lives.
And only a subject of time.
Of course the time and only a murderous system...
... with numbers with a composed meaning arrested to him.
Or not?
::: NUMBER 23 :::
--- Legends for H. Miraculous, I hope has liked! ---
"Be sure that yours
sin he had found!"