Mother?
What's going on? Mother?
Judith, where is my mother?
Where is my family?
I don't know. I
haven't seen anyone.
It's only the ninth hour, and
the day seems darker than the night.
Mother!
We are here-
To judge a woman
who is guilty of adultery...
with a foreigner, with a Roman!
Who accuses this woman?
I do. I.
What are you asking for your bride?
That she be punished according
to the full extent of the law!
So be it!
No! Father! Not
my mother, Father.
Father! No!
You must throw
the first stone, Nathan.
No!
I can't. I cannot.
Stone her! Stone her!
- No!
No. Don't. Have
pity. Have pity!
Stone her!
No! No!
Go away! Tabitha! Go away!
Forward... for Rome. Hey!
The Romans! The
Romans are here.
Wait. We'll
ask the priestess.
High priestess-
what does she say?
It's an earthquake!
Dismount! To the ground!
I've got their flag!
The flag!
Romans! With me! With me!
For Rome! For Rome!
Burn the priestess.
Stop!
Your gods are
also destined to die.
Long live the Roman Empire!
A battle has been won. But
one battle is not enough for Rome.
Rome wants to
win the war...
and for this to happen,
the emperor of Rome...
wants your leader- Segimerus.
No Roman is familiar
with his appearance...
but I know
he's amongst you.
Now, I could
crucify all of you...
to be sure I kill
Segimerus with the others.
But I'm offering him
the chance to act with honor.
Segimerus! Come forward...
and I will save the lives
of your companions.
I am Segimerus.
Is he Segimerus?
- Yes.
He is Segimerus.
With his lust for
power and glory...
this dog had led
us to our downfall!
Stop!
Segimerus.
You're finally
in the hands of Rome.
But you're to be executed
by one of your own men-
the one who
identified you.
And in exchange...
he will not only
receive his life...
but also freedom.
Come on. What
are you waiting for?
You will be a free man.
Segimerus! Segimerus!
Commander, how did you
realize he was Segimerus?
I'm well acquainted
with these people.
They are barbarians,
but they are loyal.
Not one of the royal guardsmen
would betray his king.
Each one of them
would rather die for him...
except one- himself.
Offer the prisoners the chance
to choose between joining the legion...
or being sold as slaves.
You I will keep
in my personal service.
What's your name?
- Brixos.
And you'll never have my loyalty,
unless I decide to give it to you.
Allow us to render
funeral honors to our king.
In exchange, I shall
use my sword at your service.
Oh, Father Segimerus.
I have a message
for Titus Valerios Taurus.
Titus Valerios Taurus.
Commander of the Seventh Gemina
Legion, at our emperor's service.
Our emperor requires your presence.
You're to be given the honor
of meeting him personally.
Hand command over to your
subordinate. Gather your things.
The emperor
is expecting you.
The emperor is expecting me.
Emperor Tiberius has taken up residence
on Capri for the past few years now.
Almost everyone calls him
"the man of the island. '"
Why did you bring me back
after so many years of exile?
I have decided to entrust you
with a missión that calls for all your talent.
It's a mystery that
cannot be solved byjust anybody.
One day, in April, at the
ninth hour, the sky clouded over.
Yes, in Germania too.
And during the battle, the earth trembled.
- Yes.
These mysterious signs were observed
in many countries of the worid...
from east to west,
from north to south.
And since then, I've had research conducted
in the entire empire...
because I wanted to know
whether there is a link...
between these
extraordinary events.
And I believe
I've found a clue.
Where?
- In the Tabularium in Rome.
The clerks in my
archives found it.
What is it?
It's the records from a trial
that came to a close with a death sentence.
There are hundreds of death
sentences every day in the empire.
What's so extraordinary
about this one?
It's all included
in my instructions.
Read them, carefully,
and then destroy them.
What is my destination?
Jerusalem, the
prefecture ofJudea.
Can I rely on our
local authorities there?
Of course. Just try to be
as independent as you can.
I understand.
- What do you know about the situation in Judea?
I know that the governor is a
man named, uh, Pontius Pilate...
and that the entire area
is a snake's nest- not much more.
Yes, that's-that's
about all you need to know.
I will obey your
orders, Emperor.
"Proceedings against
Jesus of Nazareth...
"the so-called king
of theJudeans...
by the praetorian ofJerusalem."
Welcome toJerusalem, strangers.
Do you want to
sleep with me tonight?
They're beautiful.
Shh, shh, shh.
Who is that stranger?
Come with me, my friend.
Welcome to town.
There's a quieter, more secluded
spot through that door.
The service is
better and quicker.
Did the man from
the island send you?
If the answer is yes, we can
speak more privately over there.
Bring some of your
best wine and some lamb.
First of all,
tell me what...
someone representing the emperor...
is doing in a
disreputable hole like this.
This is the perfect place...
to pick up interesting
bits of information...
for, uh, someone like me.
Barabbas. So,
how did it go?
We killed off a
lot of those dogs.
And one of them, before dying,
gave me the information I was looking for-
the identity of the traitor
who works as a spy for the Romans.
Is it him?
I'll take the
food to those two men.
Bolt the doors
from the outside.
Who are you?
- We are looking for the way.
Our lord Jesus has said the day is near.
- Come.
We must be ready for soon he
will return and change the worid.
My name is Stephen
and this is my brother David.
We welcome you here, sisters.
Is this your first visit?
Put it on the table.
Death to the traitor.
Brixos!
Friendly place.
- Very... friendly.
Let's leave now.
- Yes, master.
You traitor!
Oh, Barabbas! Remember
who you owe your life to.
Master!
Master. The Roman patrol.
You were about to tell me something.
Make an effort, my friend.
I need this last piece of information.
Your last service to the emperor.
You must find...
a man who lives...
outside the gates of the city.
- Where?
The house belongs to a man-
Judas Iscariot.
They call it... Aceldama.
Aceldama Field.
Take it all. Take it all.
Master. The patrol.
I don't want anyone
to know who we are yet.
Over here. Come, Brixos.
That's it.
Hurry, Brixos.
Hey. We saw them first.
Be on your way.
Oh, by the gods.
You are more beautiful than the
priestess at the temple of Ishtar.
The two of us will have
a good time together.
Leave her alone! She's the daughter
of a very prominent man.
Her father will make you pay dearly
if you touch a single hair on her head.
Oh, her father should keep her
locked up in the house...
like any other nice girl...
if he doesn't want
to have any trouble.
Oh, hold her still.
Disappear, you scoundrel.
Help! Help me, friend. Help!
They've gone.
You need worry no longer.
They won't bother
you again, believe me.
What's your name?
We've already met.
I see that you're not
familiar with our customs.
Do not be offended, stranger...
but my granddaughter cannot
take the hand of a pagan, ever.
The religion of our
forefathers forbids it.
Of course. You people are afraid
of being contaminated.
All right. Never mind the hand.
But does she have a tongue?
Or is she also afraid of, uh,
talking to an unclean stranger?
She is not afraid at all.
So? Tell me your name.
It is not suitable for a young girl
to tell her name to a stranger.
All right.
Can I at least take you home,
to avoid you being attacked again?
By the way, that fool
was right about one thing.
What are two good women like you
doing here at this time of night?
The streets ofJerusalem
would be safe...
if it weren't for those
foreigners who attacked us.
And foreigners like us who rescued you.
But you didn't answer my question.
What are you two doing out in
the streets at this late hour?
We cannot tell you.
I'm- I'm afraid you
cannot accompany us home.
It would be-
- Inconvenient? Hmm.
Is there anything I may do without compromising you?
- Yes.
I cannot tell
you my name...
but you can tell me yours
and you can say where you come from.
Thank the gods. I
thought you were a deaf-mute.
My name is Titus
Valerios Taurus. I come from Rome.
A Roman.
Thank you, Titus
Valerios Taurus.
I shall never forget
what you have done for me.
Yes, thank you,
but, uh, we have to go now...
before they discover
that we are missing at home.
Do not fear for us.
We live close by.
Good night, young lady
who cannot say her name.
Farewell, Titus
Valerios Taurus.
Master.
Master. Another patrol, master.
Master. Master. Quickly.
Hail to you,
Pontius Pilate.
I hope you have a good reason
to bother me at this time of night.
Has another revolt flared up?
I would never have bothered you
with such a trivial matter.
No. It's something
much more serious.
An imperial titulus.
I found it on the body
of a man who died...
during a fight with Barabbas
and some Zealots in a tavern.
I suspected him of being
a secret informer of the emperor.
But this titulus could
not have belonged to him.
Witnesses say that the informer was sitting
at a table with another man- a foreigner-
and that they were talking
in great secrecy.
An imperial envoy has
arrived in Jerusalem unannounced...
and the first thing he did was to
ask Tiberius's spy for information.
It is obvious. The emperor
has sent an inspector incognito.
Do you know where he is now?
- My men searched for him...
but lost track of him
in the alleyways of the old city.
Fine. Find him.
What shall we
do if we find him?
With the credentials he has,
he can give orders to anyone- even to you.
Aulos Fuscos.
I hope you're not tempted to disclose
confidential information...
about my administration
to this meddler.
Should I fall, so will you.
My mistakes are your
mistakes. Remember that.
You've never made any mistakes
that I recall, Prefect.
Of course. I've
never committed mistakes.
Aulos Fuscos.
When you find the man, tell him
that the prefect has invited him to dinner.
He certainly cannot refuse.
Excuse me. We were told
thatJudas Iscariot lives around here...
in a place called Aceldama Field.
Do you know where it is?
- I don't know anything about anyJudas...
but Aceldama Field is over there.
Thank you.
Judas is dead.
I bought his house.
Did Judas have any relatives,
friends? I want to speak to them.
Friends? He betrayed
their teacher, a certain Jesus.
His friends would kill him
like a dog if he were still alive.
Or maybe they wouldn't.
They might forgive him.
They're a strange folk.
I must meet them, even one
of them. It's very important.
I don't really
know any of them.
But I do know that someone
is doing his utmost to find them.
They say he's a
spy from the temple.
What's his name?
- Saul ofTarsus.
Where can I find him?
- He usually attends a rabbinical school...
close to the Mitzpah market,
just in front of the temple.
We've been here half a day
already, master. Nothing so far.
Patience, Brixos. The
key to this work is patience.
There. That's
Saul ofTarsus.
But don't tell anyone that I pointed him
out to you. He's a powerful man.
Out of the way!
Let Stephen go!
Let my brother go!
David, remember
the teachings ofJesus.
Come on, young
man. Defend your brother.
Come on.
Defend your brother!
No one will harm you if you do.
I give you my word.
Do not use hatred against hatred.
Come on. Love him,
defend him! Come on.
It is your duty
to defend your brother.
No! No!
Stop! You're
all under arrest.
Throw down your weapons.
Prefect will hear of
no brawling in the street...
especially over
stupid religious differences.
After him! After the boy!
Five men. Quickly!
Have no fear. I'm a friend.
Just want to ask you a question.
Promise you won't shout
if I let you speak?
Why didn't you
defend your brother?
Answer me!
Why didn't you defend
your brother? Are you a coward?
The rabbi.
The rabbi said so.
"Do not use hatred against hatred."
Who's the rabbi?
Who commanded him?
Jesus of Nazareth. Let me go.
Jesus of Nazareth? Did you meet him?
Let me go. They're coming!
There!
Who are you?
You are under
arrest! Commander!
It's all right, Brixos.
It's all right.
So.
I believe we've
already met- in a tavern.
I'm Titus Valerios Taurus
of the Seventh Gemina Legion...
a special envoy
for the emperor.
Welcome toJerusalem, Tribune.
We were aware of your presence here.
The prefect is expecting you
at Fort Antonia.
You're to be
his guests for dinner.
Thank you for
your very kind invitation.
It's an honor to be a guest
in your magnificent palace, Pontius Pilate.
You're welcome, Ambassador.
Claudia Procula.
- Welcome.
I've been told that you've had some
marvelous fabrics brought to you from Syria.
Welcome. We're honored to have
such a prominent guest.
I've never been invited
to dinner before...
by an armed squad
in full fighting trim.
I believe it was a necessary measure
to protect your security.
The streets ofJerusalem
are not safe for a Roman citizen.
Please be so kind
as to follow me for a moment.
Dinner will be
served in a while.
I don't fear the streets
ofJerusalem, Prefect.
I've spent 5 years- the past
5 years- fighting in Germania.
So I know how to
take care of myself.
The barbarians of the north
fight you out in the open.
Here, the enemy
can be hidden anywhere.
He strikes without warning
and then disappears just as quickly.
Remember what
happened to you in that tavern?
All I want to
do is help you...
once you tell me what the
object of your missión is.
Dinner is served.
My wife, Claudia Procula.
- Hail, Claudia.
Tribune.
- The tribune and I have urgent matters to discuss.
We will join you in a while.
But the guests are expecting you.
- Please.
Claudia. With that name, your wife
has to be a relative of the emperor.
A cousin, yes.
But that isn't the reason for my becoming
the governor of this province.
If that were the case, Tiberius would have
entrusted me with an easier task...
either Greece or Bithynia.
But you have not
answered my question.
What is the purpose of your missión?
Come, Tribune.
We must join our guests.
I'm looking for a body.
What? What did you say?
A body. A body
that has disappeared.
Are you trying to make a fool of me?
- Not at all.
It was theJudean rabbi who you
sentenced to death a short while ago.
I authorize so
many death sentences.
This is a turbulent town.
Who are you referring to?
A certain... Jesus.
From the town of Nazareth.
Jesus? I do not recall.
It is a very common name
in the area.
But why are you looking for his body?
- Because it's gone, vanished.
Or I should say resurrected,
as the word goes.
"Titus Valerios Taurus
to Tiberius Caesar Augustus.
"Hail, Emperor.
"Following your orders,
I am now in Judea, in the city ofJerusalem.
"As soon as I set foot
in this territory...
"despite traveling
incognito, I was attacked...
"and one of
our informers killed.
"At this moment, I am the reluctant guest
of your prefect, Pontius Pilate.
"He claims to know
nothing about theJudean rabbi...
"but allows the man's
followers to be persecuted...
"something of which
he is well aware.
Evidently, Jesus is
more dangerous dead than alive'"-
"...should he
really be dead...
something that I will
soon discover."
Your best informers
were not successful...
and they were well acquainted
with their surroundings.
Why do you think
he might succeed?
His pride will never let him
abandon his search for the truth-
not until he has found it.
Even though he's
well aware that-
that the truth may sometimes be
extremely dangerous.
Hmm. May I ask you something, Caesar?
- Yes?
I believe you
have sent him there...
to discover whether a man
can truly rise from the dead.
Is that not so?
I've always been curious
about the beyond, Austomedorif...
because I fear nothingness.
Where was Pilate?
- He was seated over there.
Sit there.
- But, Tribune-
I said sit there and read it.
"The senate and the people of Rome
againstJesus of Nazareth."
Who are you? Why have
they brought you here?
"Who are you? Why
have they brought you here?"
Why do you not speak?
Are you not aware
that I can save your life...
or choose to
give you death?
"And the prisoner replied,
"You would not have this power...
if it hadn't been
given to you by the Most High. "
My power has been
invested in me by the emperor.
And you are accused of
proclaiming yourself king of theJews.
This is a crime
of lese-majeste.
"There are no kings
other than the emperor."'
There are no kings
other than the emperor.
What is your answer? Are you
or are you not king of theJews?
My kingdom is
not of this worid.
He was crucified up there.
How long did
his agony last?
He died on his own
before the ninth hour.
Centurion, did you
examine him afterwards?
I'm a soldier.
I can recognize death.
Which one was Jesus' cross?
- That one.
Do you know that woman?
- She's his mother.
The mother ofJesus.
Who are those other women?
I don't know.
Lots of women followed Jesus.
They were the most faithful
of his disciples, as you can see.
They're faithful to him
even after his death.
Women are capable of being very faithful
to those who really love them-
until their death and even beyond.
They know what love is.
Elijah, before God,
I promise you my daughter.
The wedding will take place as
soon as the arrangements can be made.
Before God, I accept
the promise of your daughter.
I pledge to wed her
on the agreed date.
Help me, Grandmother. I can't.
I would rather die.
Oh!
I know where he is.
- Who?
Jesus of Nazareth. Follow me.
Where are we? I've never
seen such a desolate place.
It's called Gehenna.
Judeans consider it
the home of demons...
where the souls
of the damned are sent.
It's their hell.
This is where
theirJesus is hiding? In hell?
There they are- the followers ofJesus of
Nazareth, fleeing with what they treasure most.
The body ofJesus of Nazareth,
there on the cart below that sheet.
It is the proof of his death
without resurrection.
I don't expect any resistance. The followers
ofJesus are cowards. They won't fight.
But I fear they might
try to burn the corpse...
in order to eliminate
the proof of his death.
I will come down the trail
from the north with my men.
Another group, led by Fuscos, will move in
from the south to block their escape.
If they try to destroy the
body in the meantime, Tribune...
you take the point to lead
a frontal attack from here- agreed?
Romans.
He's setting the body on fire.
Come, Brixos. Hurry.
Come on!
Stop!
Don't kill us.
We are unarmed.
Master! Look out!
Hurry. The tribune is in danger.
Huh!
Are you all right, Taurus?
Is this Jesus?
Do you recognize him?
- His face is disfigured by death...
but his height
and body, yes.
It's him. I'm certain.
Look. Nail wounds...
on his hands and feet.
Brixos. I'm putting you in charge
of getting this body toJerusalem.
And you can take these Nazarenes
and the weapons too.
I want to examine them.
- Yes, master.
Why did you
summon me here, Tribune?
And why are you still bothering
with that dead body?
This is not the body
ofJesus of Nazareth.
What are you talking about?
How do you explain the nail holes?
Drove nails into these hands.
But the skin around
the holes didn't tear.
And there was no
bleeding either.
They have nothing in common
with the gaping gashes...
suffered by someone who was
hung from a cross for hours.
By all the gods.
What do you mean?
That these wounds were inflicted
on this body only recently...
after death, in order
to simulate crucifixion.
That this body is a fraud.
It's not the body of
someone who was crucified, Pilate.
This is notJesus of Nazareth.
Just suppositions, fantasies.
This is the body ofJesus.
The fraud was committed
by his disciples.
This is the official story,
and you'll stand by it, otherwise-
Regarding the official story,
I've also conducted an investigation into those...
Nazarenes.
Investigation? What
kind of investigation?
I've been thinking about
their method of fighting.
In battle, a man
shows how he was trained.
And the way they fought-
It reminded me of only one thing-
the arena.
What are you talking about?
- They were gladiators.
Very well-trained gladiators.
- And who do you think planned this trap?
Whoever might
have gained from it.
Surely you're not insinuating-
- I'm not insinuating anything... for the moment.
I don't have the proof.
But I've included my deductions
in a letter to the emperor.
Forgive my being so stubborn.
I can see now that
you're right, Tribune.
We will discover who is behind
this treacherous ambush.
I have no doubts.
And by the way, I have
to ask you for something...
that will cause you some problems
with yourJewish friends...
and their high priests at the temple.
- What?
You have visitors.
Mary.
- Stephen.
David.
- Brother.
Allowing that
follower ofJesus...
to receive visitors in prison
without our permissión...
is a deliberate offense to us.
I beg you...
to explain yourself.
Political reasons
of a superior entity.
DenyJesus?
Declare that he
was a false prophet?
Stephen, your
life is at stake.
No one is asking you
to sacrifice yourself.
Even Peter, the
nightJesus was arrested...
denied him three times.
Is Peter the one asking me this?
No. Only me.
They will kill you.
Are you not afraid?
Death... does
not exist, Mary...
and you know that
better than we do.
You metJesus.
You met him after
the resurrection.
He taught us to love life.
He would never
have thrown it away.
Guard, we're leaving.
Follow her.
Mary Magdalene
follows her heart...
but she's asking me too much.
Magdalene!
Thank you. And may
peace be with you.
May I speak
to you, Rabbi?
You know I'm not a rabbi.
You are one for me.
Your words are
full of wisdom.
How old are you?
Eighteen.
I'm only a year
older than you.
How could I be your teacher?
I know what you
want to ask me.
You want to
be released...
from the marriage promise
your father made to Elijah.
My father took that oath.
I did not.
But how can I
disobey my father?
You can't...
but you could
do something else.
You could speak
to your father...
as frankly as
you have spoken to me.
Sooner or later...
you will touch his heart.
What is it?
I don't want you
to die, Stephen.
Girl with no name.
- You.
I cannot speak to a
stranger on the street.
You can't speak, you
can't tell me your name...
but you can be kind and
affectionate with that man in prison.
How can you talk like that?
He fooled me in the beginning too,
with his saintly airs.
But now I realize
how he uses all that talk...
of resurrection,
universal love...
to enthrall naive giris like you.
How can you talk like that?
He is risking his life.
Stephen is worth,000 times more
than you, with all of your arrogance.
Please. Please.
Please.
Forgive me.
Perhaps l- I misunderstood.
Lord, why does he not realize
that I cannot speak to him?
But I have to
speak to you.
All right. All
right, all right.
Since I can't speak to
you, I will speak to the gods.
O gods...
make her realize that I
was just worried about her...
and just wanted to
advise her to be careful.
But if I made a
mistake due to my-
Why would she be talking to him?
- Irreverence...
I humbly ask her forgiveness.
And allow her, at least,
to tell me her name.
Lord, have the
Roman keep quiet...
before we are lapidated
due to his irreverence.
And above all, I beg
you to- to forgive me-
What's he saying?
- For making her cry.
Lord, please tell the Roman
that I have not cried at all.
And in any case...
certainly not
because of him.
Wh-What's she saying?
She doesn't want to admit
she's been crying?
Oh, yes, I realize
she's a very proud girl.
Oh, my God.
May all Romans
be struck by lightning.
Yes, but before
I'm struck by lightning...
please-
At least tell
me your name.
Why is it so important for you?
Because I can't go on
thinking about you...
without knowing your name.
My name is Miriam.
But everyone
has called me Tabitha...
since I was a child.
What does it mean?
Gazelle.
Hmm.
I see why they
called you that.
Now let me go,
before someone reports us.
One more thing. Wait.
Allow me to give
you some advice.
Don't be fooled by the followers
of theJesus of Nazareth.
Don't fill your
head with illusions.
You do not know
what you're talking about.
Lfhe has truly
resurrected from the dead...
where is he now,
and why is he hiding?
Jesus isn't hiding.
And anyway, I can't
tell you anything about it.
All right, Tabitha. Hmm.
Shalom, Titus
Valerios Taurus.
If you really want
to know aboutJesus...
you should go
out to Bethany.
There is a man there
who can help you.
He has two sisters.
His name is Lazarus.
Shalom, High Priest.
Nathan. I haven't
seen you in a while.
I have something to tell you.
Is there anyone here?
Lazarus is gone...
but not for good.
How can you say that, master?
Strange-
Place like this must
be worth a lot of money.
Although it's clearly
been abandoned...
no one has taken it over.
Perhaps people think
Lazarus will return.
No one wants this place.
It's cursed.
But follow us.
We have something to show you.
How did you know
we'd be coming here?
We have many friends.
I assume you also know what
happened to Lazarus and his sisters.
Nothing. They probably realized
they were no longer welcome here and left.
The stone was used to
cover the entrance of the tomb.
Lazarus was inside...
wrapped in a shroud.
ButJesus came here with
a small group of people...
and he performed a miracle.
Accept a goblet of wine.
It's from one of our best vineyards.
Go on, Saul. What happened?
Take away the stone.
His disciples rolled away the stone
that was sealing the tomb.
Then Jesus raised his arms,
called out loudly.
Lazarus.
Come out.
And Lazarus left the tomb,
still covered in his shroud...
after having lain there
for four days.
Did he... bring
him back to life?
Just before Pesach.
Is it not oddly appropriate
that this should happen...
right before the Nazarene ladies
returned toJerusalem?
He was thus preceded
by the reputation...
of being a man who could
bring the dead back to life.
Do you mean it
was... just a show?
A rehearsal. A dress
rehearsal for a show...
that would prove
to be even greater.
His own resurrection.
The goblet.
The wine- The
wine was poisoned.
Brixos!
- Master!
Master!
Titus Valerios Taurus.
I'm here.
Please-
Help me.
Titus Valerios Taurus...
come out.
Brixos.
Master.
Master- l-
I tried, master.
I trust that you
are well, noble Taurus.
When Pilate finds
out about this...
he will have you crucified.
I don't think so.
Please forgive
this little demonstration.
But you wouldn't
have believed it...
unless you'd
experienced it yourself.
You have died and
come back to life.
What are they saying?
- The wine they offered you was laced with a substance...
that produces a state
of apparent death...
lasting from several hours
to several days.
Your servant was able
to verify it himself.
You were dead for
three days and three nights.
It's true, master.
But you were not dead.
He was not dead...
just as your fellow townsman
Lazarus was not dead...
orJesus of Nazareth on the cross.
Before your eyes,
we have revealed a hoax-
an evil ploy perpetrated
by the followers ofJesus...
on a naive and
gullible people.
Go. Go and spread the word...
of what you have
witnessed here today.
Forgive us.
Sometimes our methods
are questionable...
but they're necessary.
Should they have been left the chance
to spread their madness...
the followers ofJesus
would have divided us.
Your inquiry might have
created such a división.
I believe I can safely
conclude that your inquiry...
is now over.
Longinus, unless
you answer my questions...
I'll be forced to arrest you.
- What are you accusing me of?
Of having allowed
Jesus of Nazareth...
to be given a drug that
caused his apparent death.
To make sure he was dead,
I stabbed him with this.
Let him speak, Brixos.
It went all the
way to his heart.
Can anyone confirm this?
- My soldiers were with me.
They'll witness what happened.
Tribune, this woman
insists on seeing you.
She says she has something
very important to tell you.
Who are you?
Tabitha.
- They have sentenced Stephen to death.
You are the only one
who can help him.
Stephen! Stephen!
Go away! Go!
Tabitha.
I'll go.
Master, there are
too many of them.
Silence!
- There's nothing we can do.
Today...
the Roman prefect authorized
that Stephen be stoned to death.
Lapidation.
Yes. Let us stone him to death.
Don't look. Come on.
Brixos, stay here.
Stephen.
I will not go
back to his house.
Where will you go?
I will look forJesus' followers.
Mary Magdalene told me that
many of them are in Galilee...
and that they live there
like brothers.
Do you still believe in the
fairy tales ofJesus of Nazareth?
How can you talk like that
after seeing Stephen's sacrifice?
Stephen acted in good faith.
He was a courageous man.
L- I judged him unfairly.
But I only believe
what my eyes can see...
and what my reason can explain.
And what does your reason
suggest to you?
LfJesus is still alive,
his disciples...
are playing on the hopes
of people like you- like Stephen.
For the time being,
they're gathering followers.
When the right opportunity arises,
they'll make their move...
and take whatever they want.
What?
- Power.
Money.
Like all men.
That is all that matters to you-
power, money.
You are a Roman.
You know nothing
about the power of love.
You're right.
I knew nothing about love...
before coming
to this country.
I've encountered love here.
I don't want you
to go to Galilee.
I wish you would
come to Rome with me.
I want to marry you.
I want to make you happy.
L- Give me your hand.
Give me your hand.
I have never even
touched a man's hand.
It is shameful.
It is forbidden.
I love you.
I love you too.
Where are you going?
Your cloak's stained with Stephen's blood.
- Uh-
Go back to your-
Go home and prepare.
Tomorrow is your wedding day.
Yes. It is my wedding day.
Mmm.
- You wanted it to be the unhappiest day of my life...
but it will be
the happiest...
because today I will be leaving
with the man I love.
What-What do you mean?
What are you-
Who is he?
- A Roman.
He will take me
with him, far away-
the farthest I
can get from here.
A Roman-Just like your mother!
Yes. I am like my mother,
and I am proud of that.
Be quiet.
- I love that man.
Be quiet!
- I love him.
Be silent! Silent!
Silent!
Be silent!
Silent! Silent!
Silent! Silent! Silent!
- No!
No! Nathan!
- Give me-
Tabitha!
Miriam! Tabitha!
Tabitha.
Tabitha!
- Tabitha.
Uh-Wake her up! Wake her up!
Tabitha! Tabitha!
Just-Just go! Go!
- What happened?
At the house. Go!
- Where's Tabitha?
Hurry. Hurry, please.
Hey! Hey!
Hey!
Open up!
Who are you?
- I'm the doctor.
Her wounds are very serious.
What's wrong with her? Speak up!
She was beaten
on the head repeatedly.
What does that mean?
It means she's dying.
And I was the
one who killed her.
I... and you.
You.
- You-
You- How dare you?
We both murdered her.
I wanted to keep her
and you wanted to take her away.
You wanted to change her.
And this is what happened.
Kill me.
Stop! What are you doing?
You're not helping her that way.
How can I help?
She only has a few
more hours to live.
Where is she?
- Upstairs.
Tabitha.
Am I dying?
- Shh.
What can I do, my love?
Bring the disciples ofJesus here.
Let them speak to me-
aboutJesus, about his kingdom.
Have them pray for me.
Promise me.
I am afraid.
It is so dark.
I promise you, my love.
You must promise to hold out-
to fight with
all your strength...
till I come back to you.
Promise me, Tabitha.
Be strong, my love.
Is this your promised land?
Even a place like this...
can be beautiful.
This is Galilee- the land ofJesus.
Hail to you, Mary.
My name is Titus
Valerios Taurus.
I'm a Roman, and I've come
a long way to meet your son.
The emperor dispatched
me here to find Jesus...
and to discover
if he was an impostor.
I no longer care
about all this...
because I have
another reason.
The woman I love is dying.
She believes in your son,
and now she needs him.
Please.
I beg you.
I beg you to help me.
Oh, yes.
Thank you very much.
Who are you?
My name is Simon,
but they call me Peter.
Why did you
steal the body ofJesus?
Jesus is resurrected.
He's alive.
- If he's alive, where is he now?
He has returned to
his father in heaven.
So he's alive, but in heaven.
Very convenient.
The woman I love is dying...
because she believes
in your wild ideas.
That's why I've come here-
to ask you to come
toJerusalem for her.
For Tabitha.
LfJesus really has left you
with the task of governing his disciples...
you must come
and speak to her...
about his kingdom- about him.
Tell her the fairy tales
you preach to the poor.
Let her die under the illusión
that a new worid is awaiting her...
instead of darkness.
- I cannot.
Why?
- There are persecutions all overJerusalem.
You're just a coward.
- No.
I was told that even
on the day he was crucified...
you denied him three times.
True.
But things are
different now.
I am responsible
for all my brethren.
I cannot leave all of them
to comfort only one.
Charlatans.
You are nothing
but charlatans.
Your people are
similar to mine.
They teach us not to fear
our own death.
It's the destiny
of every warrior.
But there's no remedy
against the death of those you love.
Have you ever lost
someone you loved, Brixos?
I had a wife and son.
The plague
came to our forests.
That was a battle
I could not fight.
I took them...
and ran away to the
shores of Hyperborea.
But I...
did not run fast enough.
So you have nothing to go back to.
Just like me.
I have a friend...
master.
I have no other friend
as good as you, Brixos.
Perhaps this isn't the
right moment to tell you...
but I have already deposited,
in the prefect's archives...
a deed...
of your release from service.
You are a free
man, my friend.
Thank you, Titus
Valerios Taurus.
But I've always
been a free man.
That's true, Brixos.
I do not like this place.
- What are you afraid of, Brixos?
There's no danger here.
Drink.
Brixos!
Brixos, my friend.
Tell your emperor...
It's not worth the effort...
Looking for the answer.
We shall all find out-
Brixos.
Sooner or later.
My friend.
Yes, my friend?
Friend.
My friend.
Last night the doctor said that her soul
was hovering between life and death...
but this morning
she didn't seem too-
You came alone.
You didn't manage to-
I haven't kept my promise.
Forgive me, Tabitha.
Forgive me.
You-You're so
cold, my-my love.
A doctor- Call
a doctor. Hurry.
It's too late.
No.
Tabitha. Tabitha.
Roman, you must be strong.
- Tabitha. Tabitha.
Tabitha's soul
is watching over us...
from above.
Master, a man has arrived.
Who is it?
- He comes from Galilee.
He is one of those followers
ofJesus of Nazareth.
I told him that this
is the home of a Pharisee...
that it is
prohibited by law.
Let him in.
- But, master, he is a follower-
Shh. Shh.
Let him in.
My love.
It's me.
Peter.
Is this Tabitha?
- Yes.
It's too late.
You've come too late.
It's too late. She's dead.
Leave me alone with her.
And pray.
Come. Let's do what he says.
Come.
I have to go.
The Pharisee informers...
must have already
reported my arrival here.
Thank you for
your faith, Roman.
I have no faith.
So you say, but you
have demonstrated...
more faith than many of those
who shout it out in the temple.
Farewell, Taurus.
Now go to her.
Taurus.
Is it you?
Tabitha.
"The missión you
have entrusted me with...
"has succeeded.
"I am now fully convinced
thatJesus of Nazareth rose from the dead.
"He lives today,
and I have witnessed his power.
"My inquiry has proven
that the words ofJesus...
"have the power to change
those who listen.
"We Romans
dominate the worid in fear...
"but here I've discovered
the beginning of another worid-
"of another kingdom-
"where men don't live
according to fear...
but according to love. '"
Are we ready to leave?
Yes, Uncle.
Everything's ready.
Forgive me, but I must insist
on dissuading you.
Consider your state of health,
to travel all the way to Rome.
I want to surprise our senators.
The matter I want to submit
to them is much too important.
We leave tomorrow as planned.
"And perhaps the teachings
of this little-known teacher...
"really do change
the hearts of men...
"and steer them
towards peace rather than war.
"I will let you judge
if whether or not...
this is positive or
negative for the empire. '"
Caligula. The physician says
that the emperor was almost dying...
and now has regained consciousness.
But he'll never reach Rome
in his condition.
We have to stop this journey.
Mmm.
- Hail.
The worst is over.
- Go.
Uh-
I've prepared the report
for the senate.
May I know the
subject, Uncle?
"I, Tiberius Caesar,
Emperor of Rome...
"return to the
senate today...
"in order to submit an important matter
to the fathers of Rome.
"It regards a new cult...
"that has sprung up
in the prefecture ofJudea...
"and which preaches
peace and harmony...
"and I propose that you
publicly recognize it...
as the new religion of the empire."
But the cult ofJesus...
denies the emperor's divinity.
Does this old ruin look
like the body of a god?
How can you foster a religion
that states that all men are equal?
The free and the slaves,
the Romans and the barbarians...
men and women alike?
Reconsider, Uncle.
My decisión is final.
So be it.
Go now.
- So be it, Uncle.
Do you want to be crucified
for what you have seen...
or do you want
to swear allegiance...
to the new emperor?
Hail to you,
Gaius Caesar Caligula...
emperor of the Romans.
You will take the
tragic news to the senate.
May he be granted
all the honors...
that he deserves...
and be proclaimed a god,
as, no doubt...
shall be done for
myself too, one day.
Regarding his proposal
for this Judean god-
burn it.
I want an order
to be sent toJudea.
Titus Valerios Taurus is...
to be put to death.
Destroy every document
that regards his inquiry.
As you command, Emperor.
No one will rob me
of my immortality...
Uncle.
Soldier!
It's urgent- for
the prefecture ofJudea.
It's a death sentence. Go.
"It is my duty to
end my letter to you...
"by informing you that,
as for myself...
"I shall never
return to Rome...
"but I will always remain loyal
to the Roman Empire...
and its emperor. '"
Hail.
- Hail.
I'm looking for a tribune-
a certain Titus Valerios Taurus.
Do you know him?
- No. I've never heard of him.
Hail.
- Hail.
"I have decided to live
amongst the followers ofJesus...
"in the hope that I might gain a
place for myself in the new worid...
"which I am certain
is being prepared.
"So farewell.
"Don't search for me, because
no one will find me where I am going.
"This is my last letter.
"From Titus Valerios Taurus, once
commander of the Seventh Gemina Legion...
to Tiberius Caesar Augustus,
emperor of the Romans. '"