Ready?
Ready. Red car.
He is in there?
Yeah. Pretty sure it's him.
Oh, you're pretty sure.
Is he in there or not?
Now, I'm getting tired of this, man.
You need to be sure, for sure.
It's him. I'm sure. I'm sure, all right?
Last time, you fucked up.
Red car, right?
Relax. At least it's not Charlotte.
I'm not playing.
All right. Turn left.
Okay. I can't be perfect.
- I'm doing the best I can.
We need you fucking perfect.
Shut the fuck up!
I shouldn't even be here, man.
I shouldn't even be here.
Shit.
Hey, Tarkey.
Where's that, um, alcohol-lotion stuff?
Hey, don't use too much.
That stuff is expensive.
Yeah.
And then at 11 he cries and...
I don't know, it's, like, every two hours.
I don't know how much more
we can take.
How long do you think
this diaper duty is gonna last?
Everything's gonna be okay.
Just get that baby puke off of your shirt.
Yeah.
Benny.
Officer Steadman.
Ten-sixty-six.
- So how long you think you...?
- I told Mom I'm staying at Lisa's.
Okay. Don't shoot the messenger.
Thanks.
Here you go. Have a good one.
Something wrong with your stepdad?
- Yeah. He hates you, Benny.
- Uh-huh.
- All right. Here we go.
How'd you get it?
Hit it. Mask on.
I'm ready.
Get your mask on.
- Ready? Here we go.
Move!
- Hastings Market. December 20th.
Are you okay? What do you want?
What do you think?
Benny?
Yeah. What, Tarkey?
Don called in sick.
Do you wanna stock tonight?
Oh, I've been here since 3.
It's a $ 1.10 more an hour. But, hey,
if you're so rich, you don't need to work...
...that's fine.
- No, it's fine.
All right, go see Manny in back.
Yeah.
Attention, Hastings shoppers.
The store is now closed. Thank you.
- Hey, Benny.
- Hey, Officer Chambers.
Hey, where's your flypaper?
Oh, it's in the bottom,
right-hand side over there.
- Thanks, man. Be good.
- No problem.
Benny.
Down on the ground.
Okay.
Don't fucking move.
Don't you fucking move.
Get down.
No buttons, no phones.
No buttons or fucking phones.
Take it easy. Whatever you want,
you can have it. Just take it easy, okay?
- Whatever you want, whatever you want...
Eyes on me.
Okay. Okay. Okay. We're good.
- We're good.
Come on. Come on.
Okay.
Eyes.
- Okay.
Lady, let go of the tree. Crazy?
Stop. Don't move. Turn around. Keep quiet.
Please.
No. It's not him.
- Wait here.
Check there, Spooky.
Get down on your knees.
On your knees. On your knees.
No, get down.
Aisle 5!
Attention,
Hastings shoppers. This is a robbery.
The front and back doors
have been chained.
We're monitoring all cell-phone activity.
Anyone caught using their cell phone
will be shot.
Do not, I repeat, do not try to be a hero.
If you cooperate and do as we say...
...this will all be over in a few minutes.
Thank you.
Here are the keys to the safe.
There's not much in there.
Go!
Keep the hostages separated.
I'm at Aisle 3. I got one to look at.
Copy that.
Whatever you need, man, it's cool, okay?
Shut the fuck up and don't move.
- Okay. Whatever you need, okay?
- Keep quiet.
Okay. Okay.
Get him.
Oh, please. Don't do it. Don't!
Yo, bag him over here, baby.
Yo, Spooky, where you at?
I need you to come check this one
right now.
What did they shoot Mark for?
These are bandidos, man.
Shouldn't we get him to the hospital?
Shut up. Did I say you could talk?
God.
Shh. Move.
Move.
Okay. Okay.
We're in Aisle 7. Keep sweeping.
And be careful.
They know we're here.
Please, what are you doing?
- Just stop.
Turn right here.
Just let me go home.
My daughter's sick.
- Spooky, Spooky, check her real quick.
- Please!
Is she it?
- No! No!
Move out of the way!
- She's one.
Move!
Shit.
All right, you come here.
Be one. I've got a good feeling
about this one, Spooky.
No.
No, no. He's fine. He's fine.
I almost blew your head off there.
- Don't hurt me.
I said shut up.
Okay. Don't shoot me.
- Where are you, guys?
- Don't shoot me.
Ulrich, what's your status?
Ulrich, respond.
Anyone seen Ulrich's last position?
Hastings Market two shooters,
possibly more.
Three shooters.
You okay?
Yeah.
- All right, keep them quiet.
Stay the fuck down!
He's dead.
Police Department. Drop your weapon.
Drop your weapon. Police Department.
Lady, get out of the way.
Get out of the way!
Put the weapon down. Put it down.
Everybody, stay where they are.
I can't believe this is happening.
Boo.
Come on.
Ken, are you there? Please respond.
Shit.
- Ken, are you okay?
Ken, please answer me.
Ken, the units are on the way.
Yo, Ulrich is down, and this one over here
is a cop and he called it in.
- We gotta get out of here.
Ritter?
We need Spooky
to look at these guys in back.
Spooky is dying.
I am?
Yeah, Spook.
You are.
Goddamn.
What's going on up there?
Spooky's dead.
- We gotta get out of here.
- That's not an option.
Let's put the ones we cleared up front.
What?
Ritter, the cops are coming right now.
If we don't get out of here,
we are going down.
- We haven't gotten the one we came for.
That's my point.
Fuck the needle. Let's burn this haystack,
you know what I'm saying?
- You said you'd play by my rules.
- They're fucking changing.
Nothing's changed.
Spooky said it was here.
We leave, we gotta start again.
I'm not doing that.
You wanna go? You go.
I'm staying till we're sure we got it.
What the fuck?
Logan, you in?
Yeah.
Sterling?
The cops are on their way.
You still in?
Spooky said it was here. I'm in.
Copy that.
You with us?
We need you.
Oh, see? That's fucked up.
You gotta get all sentimental and shit.
Yeah, I'm in, man. Shit.
Take the manager
and the girl back to Sterling.
You two, come on. Let's move.
- Let's move!
Okay. Okay.
Take it easy.
I hope you know what you're doing.
Yeah.
So do I.
Please just take what you want
and let us go.
Relax. Let's go.
Come on.
Oh, here comes the cavalry.
Yeah, well, this should keep them occupied
for a while.
No talking. Heads down!
Do not move until I tell you to.
Single file.
Kane?
We're gonna need to tape up
the ones we haven't cleared.
We're gonna be here for a while.
Who would've thought
it'd come down like this?
Yeah, well, this is where it started.
This is where it's gonna end.
Go ahead.
Come on, move. Go. Now! Hurry.
Come on. Let's go.
Everybody, get back.
Everybody get through. Move. Move.
Move. Move. Cover them.
Keep going. Keep going.
I got it.
Jesus. Fuck.
Circus come to town early this year.
Oh, Jesus.
Specimen appears to be
approximately eight years gestation.
- Hey. Move out of the way.
- No, don't. I want Ritter to see this.
What are you talking about?
That's a stupid idea.
You know what? Just take it easy.
You know what? You got
one more time to tell me to take it easy.
Jeez.
Asshole.
Yo, put him down.
Not right there.
You take him away from them.
You should have a little bit more respect.
He's heavy.
- I don't care if he's heavy.
And you, skinny boy, why don't you grab
that box right there and break that lock?
- Why?
- I'm the one with the gun, that's why.
See how you dance without that gun,
asshole.
- What did you say?
- Nothing.
Cover him up with some plastic.
All right, let's get out of here.
Move it.
Are you guys all right?
The cops are still busy debriefing
the hostages that we released.
So, what now?
Plan B.
They shot this woman.
I don't know
why they didn't shoot us too.
So how many shooters was that?
Two.
Three.
- It was a slaughterhouse.
- Hey, Seth's here.
We got a hostage situation here,
Chicago.
What are you talking about? I just left
here. Let's get this lady out of the way.
This is kind of a new territory
for us here.
Are you kidding me?
My wife's daughter is in there.
The hostages.
Okay.
All right, move it, everybody.
Everybody, move it to the back! Let's go!
- Move it!
- I don't know.
- These guys...
- Just do what they say.
Things get too complicated...
...it gets hard real fast.
They got us in the back, too, surrounded.
Well, how many?
It doesn't matter
how many people are there.
We need to take care of this situation
at hand.
That's exactly my point, Ritter.
We don't have enough people
to complete the situation at hand.
- We bring in a new spotter.
- What?
Who's gonna walk in here
even if the cops would let him?
Charlotte.
Oh, my God, Charlotte?
After what happened in Scottsdale?
- That was an accident.
- Was it?
It doesn't matter.
We don't have a choice.
Unless somebody else has a better idea,
that's what we're doing.
- What are you gonna do to us?
- Hey.
You got one more time to open up
your mouth! Do you want this?
Just make yourselves comfortable, okay?
Okay, all right.
All right.
In the meantime until she gets here...
...we do the snip test.
What if we already killed him?
According to Spooky, we didn't.
There are some younger kids back there.
I know that. But if this thing gets out,
it's gonna get a helluva lot worse.
No, it's all right.
All right. I need bandages, tape, peroxide,
Tupperware containers, lots of ice.
Something that will make a clean cut.
Markers.
You know, that's real considerate of you.
Okay. Okay. Aisle 4 and 6. I'm on it.
Sterling?
Take care of the cell phones.
Check the other bodies.
See which ones have been infected.
Make sure Logan videotapes everything.
That may be all there's left
once this thing's over.
All right.
So, what, Ritter,
you gonna call K.C. Or what?
I'll go get the milk.
- Take care of the lights first.
- Yeah, I'll get the lights first.
Tell these guys to kick their high beams on
so they're as blind as we are.
Chambers said he took down two.
- How many dead?
- One confirmed the 911 call.
We don't know about the second.
Did you call Jennifer?
Phone's off.
She don't wanna wake the baby.
It's probably best she doesn't know
what's going on.
- I need to hear those tapes.
- We're getting it now.
Yeah. How many hostages?
Manager says five or so employees. Cars
in the lot give us four or five shoppers.
Maybe more, maybe less.
We're running plates and getting names.
Look, keep their friends and family
on a perimeter.
I need to set up a triage as well,
in case we get any more wounded out here.
Keep an ambulance on the ready.
I'm assuming there may be a television
or a radio on the inside...
...so we're gonna need to get somebody out
here on the media, keep them in control.
Just where exactly do you think
you're living these days?
Look, scratch that. Let's just get somebody
to talk to the family and friends...
...and find out if there's any health issues
with regards to the hostages, okay?
- Will do.
- Thank you.
So I guess you're used to this, huh?
No, you never get used to this.
See you later, Spook.
Well, I thought they'd bring
their big guns.
Well, this is Buck Lake.
These are their big guns.
We need to cut all the phone lines
at the front of the store.
I'm so sorry.
I can't keep another drop of anything down.
Finish it.
Don't fucking talk down to us, asshole.
I can have you killed.
- What did you say?
- Nothing.
Yeah, that's what I thought.
Big boy...
...don't get too comfortable, all right?
You're first.
- Uh, first?
- First for what?
Now, you know what for, don't you?
What?
The first one is ready. Come and get him.
Who are these guys?
Terrorists.
Like in that TV show.
They wanna kill all of us.
Tarkey's gonna die.
- What?
Shh, shh, shh.
The dead cop,
I saw a gun strapped to his ankle.
- Are you sure?
- Cop that's in the freezer?
One of us has to go back there.
Whitney, don't be a douche bag, okay?
- You're a douche bag.
Stop it.
Listen, they came in, started shooting.
They didn't try to negotiate.
They're gonna kill us all.
You don't know that.
Yeah, yeah. You don't...
My stepdad was a hostage negotiator
in Chicago.
I'm telling you,
the only way we're gonna get out of this...
...is if we save ourselves.
- That's what they did in that TV show.
- Manny...
...I swear, if you don't shut up,
I'm gonna kill you myself.
Uh-uh.
It could be rigged.
Then maybe you should stand back then.
Is this a robbery or is this a siege?
It's a picture of the stock boy.
What do we have on this guy?
The van is registered
to an Aaron Ritter, 43...
...widowed. Wife is dead.
Apparently, he used to work at JPL.
- JPL?
- It stands for Jet Propulsion...
- Jet Propulsion Laboratories. I know.
- Yeah.
What do you mean "used to"?
Either he quit or was fired a few years
back. We're still getting details on it.
Let's get a phone line in,
see if we can talk to this guy.
The lines in front are cut.
- There's no other lines in?
- We're checking on it.
Let's get on it.
My name's Aaron Ritter.
This is Sherry Sterling...
...our medic.
Over here is Logan...
...he's our technician.
This is Kane.
- Notice they don't say what he does.
- Shh.
We are no happier about this situation
than you are.
But it is what it is...
...and we're gonna have to deal with it.
Look, uh...
These two?
They're just kids. You don't need them.
Why don't you let them go? Their parents
are gonna be worried about them.
I'm sure you all have
people out there who are worried...
...and we are gonna do our best...
...to figure out which of you are cleared
to go home as soon as possible.
Cleared? What do you mean cleared?
We know for a fact that one of you has
been infected with a dangerous substance.
And we've traced the origin
of that substance to Buck Lake.
Our spotter's dead.
Now he's the only one that could tell us
which of you had been exposed.
We're gonna have to rely on a backup
method to figure out which of you...
...are carriers.
Logan.
Come on.
- Whoa! What are you gonna do?
What are you gonna...?
Okay. Okay. Okay.
- Relax. Relax.
- Okay. Okay.
Look...
...we're gonna do a test.
This milk has altered your pH.
It'll cause a reaction in the carrier.
Now if you haven't been infected,
you will be cleared.
- What if we have been infected?
- Then you're dead already.
Look, let's just take it one step at a time.
All right?
Ho, ho, ho. Come on. 'Tis the season.
Okay.
Write your last name on the lid there.
- What?
- Just write your fucking name on it.
I already biopsied half the specimens.
What did you find?
They are twice as big
as anything we've seen.
So far, they're all female.
All fertile.
All right. Let's get to it.
Tarkey, are you married?
- What?
- Are you married?
No. Yeah. No.
I'm divorced.
I want you to look at my fingers.
Do you see a red line?
Uh...
No red line.
- Which finger?
- Pinky, your left.
- Pinky.
- When did you get divorced?
Um...
There was this other guy at work.
He was in the Sales Department.
I didn't ask you why. I asked you when.
When did you get divorced?
Um...
Just take a deep breath.
Calm down.
Answer the question.
It was...
...three years ago.
You dating anyone?
Why? Uh...
I mean, um...
No. I mean, there's some online serv...
No! Don't touch me! No, no, no!
- Stop moving! Don't move!
- All right, calm down! Calm down!
I got money. I got money.
You can have it. You can have it.
Look, look. Here.
- Slow.
- Okay. Okay.
I got... I got money. Look.
- Where did that come from?
- Where do you think?
Not in his ass.
Looks like Mr. Tarkey's a thief.
Look, look. It's, like, $2000 there.
You can just have it.
- Sit.
- And you can go.
- You can just take...
- Sit the fuck down!
Take them.
All right.
If anybody goes to get that gun,
it's gonna be me.
Oh, yeah, old man?
What, are you out of your mind?
Manny the Man's gonna get that gun.
- Then I'm gonna take all these fools out.
- Don't be stupid.
Listen.
I've had a lot of weapons training.
I'm an expert marksman.
Are you military or something?
I teach a shop class
at the public high school.
Fucking teacher?
- Okay.
- Oh, man.
You come in firing,
we'll tackle him from behind.
There's...
There's a backdoor
at the end of the corridor.
It'll take you to the meat counter
where the freezer is.
Shh, shh.
All right, I can make it.
- I can't believe this is happening.
- Hey!
Some of us have to piss, eh?
Man, it's a free country.
Go let loose, all right?
Yeah, órale to you too.
All right, the box cutter.
Give me the box cutter.
Yeah.
This is Detective Seth Steadman.
I'm in charge of the negotiations.
Am I speaking to an Aaron Ritter?
That's right.
Okay, Aaron.
I thought you should know
we found your van.
- I figured.
- I wanna help, okay?
But I can only do that
if you tell me what you need.
Why don't you tell me
what's going on in there?
- Lf I told you, you wouldn't believe me.
- Yeah, well.
I've had some pretty
crazy rides myself.
- Why don't you try?
- I'm a little busy right now.
Well, it must be pretty big.
You're a long way from home.
I go where the work is.
That means you're a hardworking man.
Got a lot of respect for that.
Tell me. Is it anything that your daughter,
K.C., would understand?
There's a lot of people
in there that we're worried about, okay?
There's a lot
of worried mothers and fathers.
I want you to bring me a woman
named Charlotte Breen.
Charlotte Breen.
Okay, that's a start. I like that.
Tell me if there's anybody else there
that's hurt. Give me some name...
Charlotte Breen.
You'll find her at Phoenix Station 508.
Arrested on drunk and disorderly
and possession two weeks ago.
I'd have bailed her out myself,
but I've been preoccupied.
Okay. Okay.
What about the other hostages?
If you wanna contact me in the future,
the number's 709-555-4823. Got it?
And Seth, the longer it takes you
to bring me Miss Breen...
...the uglier it's gonna get in here,
you understand?
Yeah.
Whoa, wait! Just wait a minute.
Wait a minute. You guess... What?
Just a minute, you guys need to get
to Charlotte, we can get that done. No!
- Ahh!
Jesus.
What the hell?
Hey, what are you doing to him?
- Shh. Quiet.
- What are you doing?
You know exactly what we're doing, okay?
We're conducting a test.
Do you realize all you guys
are going to jail?
You hurt us, they're just gonna put
you away for that much longer.
Yeah, it seems likely.
You know, you give yourself up now
and they're gonna go a lot easier on you.
Yeah, my dad's friend, he's a real
good lawyer. I'm sure he'd help you out.
Well, if he's from Buck Lake,
I'm not interested.
Oh, God. I just wanted a bottle of wine.
I should've opened a can of beer.
- What kind of test you doing?
- Well, do you wanna find out, huh?
Do you wanna find out?
Oh, it's been two minutes. He's clear.
I could have sworn it was him.
Kane...
...it's not the manager.
You have to stop wriggling around.
The organism has a biology
used to heat...
...so freezing is the only sure-fire way
to kill it.
And that process can take hours.
Fertility is directly tied to maturity,
as you can see:
Each of these nodules contain a larva.
The larva itself is nearly indestructible.
Did she say it came from a meteor?
I think she said "a meteor-like object. "
But that means what I think it means,
right?
Charlotte Breen is on her way.
Get here in next 20 minutes.
Rap sheet is a mile long.
Crack, heroin, meth, you name it.
This is what came up on Ritter.
Left the JPL shortly after he was acquitted
of involuntary manslaughter.
- Manslaughter?
Yeah. Oh, it gets better.
All the circled ones
quit the JPL at the same time.
According to Ritter's in-laws, they started
some club and started buying guns.
And one more thing, you're gonna love this.
The rest of the people in the picture?
All dead.
Someone...
Psst. You got your hands free yet?
Nice.
If you get in there...
...don't let the door close behind you
or else you'll be locked inside.
Yeah.
Oh, my God.
- What did they do to you?
- They cut my finger off.
What?
I know it looks bad but trust me.
We have your best interests at heart here.
Let me know if you need some more ice
for that.
I'm not gonna need another reason
to hate the holidays.
All right. Come on.
- What? No.
You're next.
- What are you doing?
- Look, shut up!
All right, come on. Let's go.
We can blow your foot off
just to see what happens.
- Ready to go?
- Dude, just...
Am I talking to you? Am I talking to you?
You wanna take her place?
Is that what you wanna do?
Okay. Well, then shut up.
- Come on, let's go.
- My dad is Seth Steadman. He is a cop.
What the hell's going on in here?
It seems like our cashier here
has high connections.
Her father is a cop.
The name is Seth Steadman.
Stepdad.
Seth is your stepfather?
Pick who you're gonna pick.
Let's get going.
- That's what I'm talking about. Let's go.
- Fuck.
Wait, wait.
Just take me, okay?
- Let's go.
Somebody get him...
Come on.
- Fine.
Hey.
Asshole.
I need my glasses.
They must want you pretty bad
over at Buck Lake, huh?
Can I have my sunglasses, please?
They wanna know why you and some guy
named Ritter had a falling out.
I fucked up, that's why.
Fucked up, how?
I was supposed to help out
with something...
...but a friend of mine hooked me up
with some TMAs...
...some real high-grade stuff.
Have you ever tried that shit?
What were you supposed to be
helping with?
Oh, fuck.
I told you.
I help out that guy, he gets me into shit.
These handcuffs are too tight.
They're too tight.
You should go ahead and sit back.
We're almost there now.
I'm done talking to you.
So I'm supposed to see a red line?
I don't know.
Do you?
Is there an answer that's gonna keep you
from cutting off my finger?
I can't tell you that.
No?
Tell me something.
Why did you stick up for that cashier?
Uh...
She...
What's gonna keep you from doing this?
I'm sorry.
Are you?
Yes, I am.
Very.
Fuck. Fuck! Run!
Get down.
- Get down. Get down.
I don't know. I don't know.
- Okay, where is it? Where the fuck is it?
Fuck, here it comes. Here it comes.
Let's go. Where the fuck is it?
Where the fuck is it?
It's chasing Fred...
- Where did it go?
- Who are these people?
What the fuck is he doing?
You're a pretty tough kid.
I'm impressed. Don't move.
Shut up.
Oh, God. I feel terrible.
Oh, God. I thought being drunk
would make it kind of easier.
All right. How many we got left?
Three.
We don't need Charlotte...
...which is a good thing considering
every time she fucks up, people die.
She's a junkie. What do you want?
We're not leaving till we verify we got him.
And we're gonna need her to do that.
- You are losing control of the situation.
- I'm aware of the situation. Thank you.
- Do something about it.
- I will.
Jesus! Quiet.
Bingo!
Shit.
Fuck it.
Guys, she's cracking out!
Oh. What the fuck was that?
I don't know.
Yo, what's going on out there?
You read me?
Hey, go. Go.
- Are you doing okay?
- Don't start now.
- Let me see.
- Don't.
Yeah.
What the hell was that?
Yo, is that you guys in there?
No, it wasn't.
Why the hell do we not know
what's going on in there yet?
Hang tight, everybody.
Would you check that out?
This place is crawling.
You're taking way too much time.
Where's Charlotte Breen?
Hey, hey, hey.
Who are you shooting in there?
We haven't shot your stepdaughter,
if that's what you're wondering.
Look...
...just tell me she's safe.
Yeah, she's safe, for now.
All I'm asking is that you
stay cool in there, okay?
I mean...
...if you start shooting in there again...
...I'm coming in there.
Do you understand me?
No, you bring me Charlotte Breen
or else I think you know who's next.
She's only 10 minutes away, man.
Give me 10 minutes, okay?
We're not gonna make it, are we?
I don't know.
But we're gonna finish this.
What are you doing here?
- What are you doing there?
Well, the sentinel sucker tried
to infect Sterling.
- How mature was it?
- Very. He's unlike anyone I've seen before.
Murphy's Law, man.
Where did the old guy go?
Where did he go?
Oh, you all wanna play?
Stand up.
You tell me where he went
or I'm gonna blow your head off.
He's in the freezer.
Good boy.
Ritter, Sterling,
you guys need to come in here right now.
We're on, boys.
- I'm looking for a Seth Steadman.
- That'd be me.
I got something for you.
Let's do it.
Charlotte Breen.
Thank you, Lord.
Where I come from,
you break your hands to get out of those.
I did.
All right, you come out right now
or we start firing.
Shit!
What?
Cover my back.
Oh, did you hear that?
- No.
Jes...!
Christ!
- What the fuck?
- What?
Give me a warning next time.
I can't hear a thing now.
Stop being a pussy.
He wasn't gonna make it anyway.
Whoa!
Yo, see that?
You see someone there?
He's right there!
- Jesus Christ.
- They're not coming back.
You don't know that.
Stay here. They could be right outside.
- Let's just make a run for it.
- No.
- Whitney, shut up.
They left.
If they were gonna kill us, they
would've done it. Just sit down! Wait...
- Ritter.
- Hey, I got Charlotte Breen.
I'll call you back.
The fucker hung up on me again.
Would you mind telling me
what's going on here?
Why don't you get me something
to make it worth my while?
- Jesus Christ.
- John has some OxyContin for his knee.
Get it.
Kane, Logan, you read me?
Stay here and watch them.
Kane, you read me?
Not yet. Almost. But not yet.
Jesus Christ, Kane, what happened?
Yeah, well, Logan is dead, man.
Yeah.
It's the cop.
Sterling didn't check him.
You think it's a king?
Yeah.
That's some powerful motherfucker, man.
It's the most powerful one I've seen yet.
God, that body was all dead
and it just came back to life.
All right.
- Hang in there. You're gonna be all right.
- No, man. No.
No.
It was all acting all cracked up and...
Stung me.
He stung me, Ritter.
But, you know, I hurt it...
...busted a couple of times,
couple of bullets, man.
It was frozen for a second.
It's all confused.
Oh, ain't this some shit?
Just try to relax.
Oh, man.
Man, Ritter,
I know we had some differences.
I don't regret none of them shit so...
You understand what I'm saying?
Yeah.
Don't you dick around with this thing.
You go out there
and you kill that motherfucker.
You end it right here, right now.
So...
...should you do the honors or should I?
Come on now. You can only kill people
that you were married to?
I'm sorry, Kane.
Yeah, I'm sorry too, motherfucker.
Do it.
Do it!
Killing?
Yes.
Aliens?
Case in point.
- What happened?
- Kane found it.
It was the cop.
It got him.
Kane's gone.
Look, luckily it's cracked out, so
it won't take the chance of going outside.
Wh... What about Logan?
What happened?
Look, I'm gonna have to go after it.
What about them?
I need you to stay here and protect them,
all right?
Okay.
Just be careful.
I don't have all night.
Why don't you start
by telling me just how you fit into this?
Okay, I'm a spotter.
- A spotter.
- Yeah. I can see them.
I was infected.
- You were infected?
- Yeah.
Didn't take. Too much "better living through
chemistry" screws them up real good.
The only problem is you gotta keep using
to keep them from taking over.
That's the best druggie excuse I've heard.
Jesus Christ.
Get ready.
This is a bad idea.
Shh.
Now, Benny. Go, go, go. Go, Benny.
Hold on. Hold on.
- Whoa, hold on, just wait. Wait, wait.
- Fuck.
Let it go. Let it go.
Crazy bitch!
I got it. I got it!
Who's in charge now?
Manny the Man.
He's right behind me. Get ready!
Do we have a location on those shots?
What the fuck was that?
Goddamn it. He's not picking up.
Are we ready around back?
I wouldn't do that if I were you.
Your friend is not leaving me
much choice.
You go in there now,
everyone in there dies.
You saw it, Benny, with your own eyes.
Shut up.
Come on, Benny. Let's get out of here.
Let's go.
Look, it's loose. It's loose out there.
Now you go out there, it's gonna kill you.
Plain and simple.
You wanna survive this,
you're gonna have to trust us.
You cut my fucking finger off.
We did what we had to do.
Don't listen to him, Benny.
Shut up!
Now lookit, Benny.
We think it's the king, all right?
We've killed all the other ones...
...but this is the king.
We get it and it's over, done with.
But we're gonna need your help to do it,
all right?
What the fuck's the hold up?
Just give me a second.
Look, Benny, they're calling me.
They brought in a new spotter.
Her name's Charlotte.
- She can verify it's the king.
- Come on, Benny.
Do you want Whitney
to get her finger cut off?
Shut up.
Okay, Benny.
You can see this is important, can't you?
Give me Charlotte for 10 minutes.
That's all I'm asking, 10 minutes.
Fine. Just bring her in.
Benny.
- Come on. Come on. All right, give me that.
Back the fuck up, Tarkey!
You fucking stiff us for two months.
Fuck, it's our overtime.
Now it's a fucking karmic dildo
just fucking you in your ass.
Just go sit down!
You are so fired.
Benny, I'm putting my weapon down...
...and I'm answering the phone, all right?
- Ritter.
- Hey, what the fuck is going on in there?
- You got Charlotte?
- Yeah, she's right here.
All right. Look, you give me Charlotte,
you get one hostage.
Give me 10 minutes,
you get the rest of the hostages.
No, no, no. I want Whitney.
Come on. You and I know she is the reason
you haven't stormed this place already.
One hostage, 10
minutes, you get Whitney and the rest.
What's that noise we keep hearing?
Seth...
...if I were you,
I'd get my family out of Buck Lake.
Put Charlotte on the phone.
Hey, Ritter.
I'm sorry.
Charlotte, tell me something.
The cop, is he clean?
Hey.
Yeah. Yeah, he's clear.
Good. All right.
Look, let him bring you in for the exchange.
We got a problem in here.
Let me take care of it.
I'll call you back...
...let you know which door to use.
- Ritter?
I'm scared, Benny.
No.
Now listen, I'm gonna protect you.
I don't trust these guys.
A spotter...
...that can see kings.
Look, all I know is what I saw.
These guys...
These guys know what they're doing,
okay?
If they say that this guy is a king...
...then we have to kill him.
Hey, why don't we just stay here
and wait for the cops?
Be quiet.
Just shut up, Tarkey.
Looks like we're taking
the long way around.
All right, cover the rear.
Both of you, to the right side of the door.
I thought you're gonna give them time.
Ten minutes.
But forgive me if I prepare for the worst.
Oh, shit.
We're gonna have to use the front door.
Front door. Got it.
Why aren't we going in?
Nobody goes in until I say so.
Are you doing this for those hostages?
Or are you doing this for your family?
I'm doing this for all of us.
And I said nobody goes in there
until I say so. You got that?
Did you see something?
I don't know.
Please tell me this thing
is not trying to trap us?
Tarkey...
...that thing is not trying to trap us.
What's this thing doing, stalking us?
I don't think it knows what it's doing.
It's only as smart as its host.
That brain must be half dead by now.
All right, come on.
I see flashlights.
But why the hell are they moving
so damn slow?
Always getting me into shit.
What's taking so long?
Goddamn it, Moody.
Would you give me a few more minutes?
- I lost my finger.
- Shh.
Tarkey!
What the fuck?
Oh, Jesus Christ.
All right, look, we need to get them
some place safe.
Take them back to the manager's office.
Stash them there. Go! Go! Go!
Let's go fast.
What's taking so long?
Give me a few more minutes, Moody.
Seth.
Seth!
Okay, wait.
Okay. Come on.
Stay down. Stay down.
Where's my hostage?
Charlotte.
I'm not handing Charlotte over
until I get my hostage.
Ritter, what's going on?
The king is loose in there.
The king? The first one's in here?
What the hell is he talking about?
I'm gonna say this one more time.
Where is my hostage?
Your hostage is dead.
- What was that?
- Look, Seth.
I know it's crazy. I don't have the time
to explain it to you right now.
But your stepdaughter is still alive.
I'm trying to keep it that way.
But to do that, I'm gonna need your help.
- You're telling me Whitney is alive.
- Yes, sir, she is.
Now what's it gonna be?
Charlotte, lock the door.
- What happened to Spooky?
- He's dead. So is Ulrich.
- What else we got?
- Females.
All fertile, bigger than we found before.
- Pick anything out?
- Yeah, it's powerful. Very powerful.
I shot it six times.
What the hell was that? Was that Ken?
Define Ken.
Oh, shit.
I told you so.
- Where's Whitney?
- I hid her in the office with Benny.
Ritter. Ritter, it's looking for something.
Oh, shit. The kids.
All right, look.
Let's circle around back. Come on.
Be quiet. Just stay quiet.
- We've gotta make a run for the doors.
- No.
No, it will kill us.
I'll run for it. I'll distract it, okay?
When it gets far enough...
...that's when I want you to run.
Benny?
I'm not leaving here without you.
You fought for me today.
That's all I've ever wanted you to do
is to fight for me.
Okay.
Wait a minute, goddamn it. Now
where the fuck is the manager's office?
Because I'm not taking another step
until I get my daughter...
...and get her the fuck out of here.
Period.
Okay, fine.
It's in the northwest corner
of the building.
We'll create a distraction. You circle
around, get the kids and get them out.
- Just tell me when.
- Wait a second.
You'll promise me, if we do this...
...you'll give us time
to finish what we came in here to do.
Done.
We'll draw it towards us
then you take off.
How the hell are you gonna do that?
It sounds like a personal problem.
After this, you and me are even.
Fine.
- Ahh!
- Hey!
Whoa, whoa. It's just me.
Hey. Come here, baby.
Come here. Come here. Come here.
Hey, are you okay, huh?
Oh, God. Listen. I'm gonna get you
out of here, okay?
- Okay.
- Okay?
Okay.
It's coming.
Don't shoot. We're coming out.
All right, go, go, go!
- Wait a minute. Wait a minute.
- Goddamn it. I said, wait a minute.
- We're not waiting any longer.
Put them in the car.
- What the fuck is happening?
- I have no fucking idea.
I'm going back in. Listen, you two let
nobody come in or out this door.
Freeze!
Drop the gun.
- Put it down.
Shut up!
- Put it down!
Drop the gun!
- Shut up! Drop the gun!
I'm putting it down.
- I need to talk to Detective Steadman.
- Shut up!
Chambers!
What the fuck is it?
Seth, shoot it!
Seth, shoot this fucking...
Oh, God. No.
No, no, no!
God, Ritter!
Charlotte.
Is...? Is it...?
Call an ambulance!
We need to get a medic in here.
Get a medic here now.
This is it.
- No.
Sterling. Sterling.
Do it.
Oh, no.
No.
He had seen it from the beginning.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, whatever.
Listen! Listen! There are females loose
and they can't spread with the king dead.
They can't spread with the king dead,
but somebody has to finish this. Listen!
You listen to me. Right now,
that is the least of your worries, okay?
If what happened here,
what you said happened here today...
...verifies and checks out, I will promise
that I will do whatever I can, all right?
You got my word on that.
Let's go.
Seth. This crackhead
won't let us near this thing.
- She's up to her elbows in it.
- She's verifying.
- She's what?
- Verifying.
She's verifying.
Just let her do her thing.
Oh, no.
What?
- Give me your goddamn radio.
- Hey!
Sterling, it's not it!
Not it! It's not the king!
Oh, Jesus. One of the kids.
It's that kid. Whitney, get out of the car.
It wasn't the king. It's the boy.
Whitney?
No.
I always loved you, Benny.
www.opensubtitles.org