Should we go shopping?
Azim, please.
Who the fuck's that?
Maybe somebody sent your dad a hooker for Christmas
Move!
See you.
Goodbye, Anna.
Calm down.
Be calm.
Slowly
Come on.
Pederast!
You too.
Wait...
This is the best spot to get rid of a corpse.
Let's go.
One...
Two...
Three...
Come on, Kirill
Get Out.
Get up, Kirill
We're partners now, man.
Yeah, yeah.
You know?
I think he's had enough.
Allow me.
That's an order.
What's the matter with you?
That's enough, Kirill.
Enough?
Siberian ox...
Psycho.
So, which one is it going to be?
Thank you, brother.
What's your last name?
Tell me your last name
Kirilenko
Where are you from?
Ukraine
Which village? Which town?
Irpen
Outside kiev
Stay alive a little longer.
Understand?
I dealt with the vory v zakone when
I worked for the KGB
I was an auxiliary!
What are you saying?
Azim's nephew slit Soyka's throat
Kirill paid him to do it.
Shut your fucking mouth!
Your dad always knows the truth.
Kirill did the right thing.
He did a good thing for our people.
They will appreciate that.
Ok, ok.
When I was in the KGB,
we knew how to deal with scum like you.
And you did what there?
Calm down.
Devil!
Motherfucker!
It was nothing important.
My only son.
I met him.
Yes, yes.
Do you understand me?
Yes.
For my brother...
Nikolai, come on
What's she talking about?
I didn't catch it
What did she say?
I don't know.
Shut up, bitch!
Fuck her, Kirill!
Forget her
That's an order!
I don't know
I don't know either
She is one hundred years old.
Yes
It's time you joined us.
Thank you...
Papa.
You, my dear friend...
... don't think ill of me.
In this wilderness...
... simply bury me.
My dad swapped a little girl from Georgia for this shit.
Let's drink to the little Georgian girl.
Yes, yes Kirill.
Hey...
I am a vor by birth.
I know.
Don't you forget it
Beautiful building..
Good evening
Is everything alright?
Yes, everything's fine.
We can see that you were in prison in Siberia...
...and that you were a thief.
My father was a government worker.
He fixed the cars of officials.
I began by selling the spare parts
when I was fifteen.
You have no forced tattoos?
None.
You were not cooperative?
I spent two years in the punishment block.
You went through the Crosses in St. Petersburg?
I was in solitary confinement a dozen times.
I was called "The Stump" because
they couldn't shaft me.
Your father was a bitch and a weak fucker
for working for the Government.
Right?
That's right.
He means nothing to me.
My mother...
You have no mother.
She was a whore anyway.
Yes.
I have no mother and no father...
There is only the code,
The vory v zakone...
... which I have always followed
That is why there is an empty space
above your heart...
... where the stars will go.
And an empty space
on your knees.
I am dead already
I died when I was fifteen
Now I live in the zone all the time
Kirill is in there...
... there, there..
Are you ok?
Finish him off.
You didn't come here to give me flowers...
You have gone beyond what was agreed.
What are you looking at, baby?
You..
Sorry.
You're either with him or with me...
With him... or with me...
I know, Kirill...
Give her to me...
Your father's going away.
The family business will be yours.
It's our time.
Let's go
Come on!
That's an order!
Bless you.
Goodbye, Anna Ivanovna.
My little russian doll...
My muffin.