Coming!
Who is it?
Hello?
Stop fuckin' around!
Whoever's screwing around
out there better quit it
or I'll come and kick
the shit out of you!
Asshole.
Who the fuck keeps
knocking on the door?
Who's there?
Hey, guys, wait up.
Come on, Curt! Ha ha!
Not waiting today.
People to do,
things to see.
You guys see the play
that Shawn made this weekend?
- No.
- Oh my God, amazing.
I wish you would stop
playing though. Terrible.
He is not terrible.
- Speaking of sucking...
- Thanks.
Hey, Uggi,
tell your dad after all
our parents reelect him,
he better hook us up
with some easy summer jobs.
Yeah, sure thing.
Yeah, me and Nicole
can be lifeguards at the pool.
We could just hang out
all day in the sun,
driving all
the old men crazy.
Pool? Uh... you're gonna
be working in the library.
The library?
Okay then.
We'll have all the bookworms
beating off
in the corner.
- Get out...
- That's disgusting.
Hey, Nik, what was your grandfather
doing outside school before?
My mom told him to stay
away from the house.
Why?
I mean, you've just never
talked about him before.
He was a city cop
his whole life.
He even missed
my father's funeral
because of some case
that he was working on.
- That sucks.
- Yeah.
And now after all these years
he wants to get to know me.
He seems
like a cool guy.
Then you get
to know him, Tom.
Hey, did you guys hear about that
girl that got robbed in Jeffersonville?
- She went to grammar school here.
- Who cares?
Did you know her?
No, she was a little
younger than us.
Her dad's a general
contractor though.
He owns, uh, that big
boarding company, SIPCO.
Yeah, I know him.
Our dads were friends.
They used to play
football here.
Yeah, well, I heard
her house was broken into
and she was...
What?
Well, my dad won't tell me,
but I know she's... dead.
Uh, there's a reason
why your dad won't tell.
You're a burnout!
Look who's talking, bitch!
Oh, God, Cindy,
that's disgusting.
Will you two get a room?
Can I help you?
Can I give youse
a ride home?
- No.
- Come on, Nicole.
Can't Grandpa
do anything for you?
I don't need
a grandfather now.
I just wanna talk.
Please.
Just stop harassing me,
all right?
Just... just leave me alone.
Just leave me alone.
Please. Nicole, please.
The beginning
to another great season...
for the Glass County Lions!
Like before
in the years past...
like when
I was on the team...
we're gonna bring
home that trophy!
And when we do
bring home that trophy...
...best party ever!
Thank you and good night!
Okay, why are you talking
with your mouthpiece in?
Why do you have a mouthpiece
in, anyway? It's a pep rally.
I'm trying to get
ready for the season.
Why? You're not gonna
need it on the bench.
- Whoa! Ooh!
- Oh, snap.
Yo, why don't you
bench these?
- At least I made the team.
- 'Cause he fits into the small uniform.
Hey, Uggi, maybe you
should take a picture.
I mean, I hear
they last longer.
- Oh, good idea.
- Get out of here!
Leave him alone, Billy.
"Leave him alone, Billy."
Mickey Masturbator
over here.
I hear he freakin' whacks off
every night to the thoughts of my girl.
What the hell are you
talking about?
What?
Seems as though you have
a staring problem yourself.
- Don't worry, Uggi, you have me.
- Aww.
All right, down, Uggi.
Down! Down!
Hey, but your old man
really did get us
- fired up tonight, man.
- Yeah, the way Uggi looks,
so did your girlfriend.
Yeehaw! Whoo!
Oh! Shit! No!
Knock knock.
Who's there?
Oh my God! No!
Good evening, Billie.
Now what brings you
all the way out here tonight?
Miss being around you, Deputy.
My God.
Didn't think anything like
this made it out of the city.
What do you have?
Jerome Peters.
His mother says there
was a knock at the door.
She opened it,
she saw nobody.
She opened it some more.
She saw her son
hanging on the door.
So far we have no clues,
no motive,
no witnesses... nothing.
- Where's the mother now?
- She's in the den with the husband.
Get him down
as soon as you can.
Hey. Hey!
Turn up the TV.
...in Glass County,
a gruesome murder took place.
Glass County Sheriff's office
believe that
the Jerome Peters murder
was the direct result
of a high-school prank
gone very very wrong...
Gee, who... who would do
a prank like that?
That was no prank.
- Hey, they said...
- Who's "they"?
Who said?
Your police?
They wouldn't know a murderer
if he handed them their business card.
Well, here's mine. And it looks
like you've had enough for one night.
Wow, Detective Billie Vega.
High voice for a guy.
She ain't built like
any guy I know, Mick.
Yeah,
well, I seen better.
Hank, have you
seen Cutter?
Uh, Billie,
no, not yet.
Thanks.
That was no prank.
Eat it...
eat it right up.
- Hey, where you been, man?
- Yeah, we just ordered.
I stopped by
Coach Sully's office.
He said Jerome was
killed with ice picks.
All right, guys, here we go.
Cheeseburger, yours.
Sweet, nice.
Got a side salad order
and you guys are splitting
the B.L.T. How about you?
- Can I get you something?
- No, thanks.
He said he was literally
stuck to the door.
Ice picks?
What's up with that?
I heard they were
actually after his brother
and mistakenly
killed Jerome.
No way.
Jerome's brother's
older and much bigger.
Dude, my little
brother's bigger.
Billy, what's wrong
with you?
Your friend gets
killed by a lunatic
and all you can do
is sit here and make fun?
Uggi, what's...
what's your father think?
I don't know.
I haven't seen him.
He's been down
at Town Hall all night.
I heard him on the news,
though, saying it was a prank.
A prank?
Come on.
It was a black thing.
You know how they are.
You're really screwed up.
No, the person who
did this is screwed up.
Look!
At what?
- Did you see him?
- See who?
There was a guy just standing
out there staring at me.
Was he cute?
No, he was this...
this big scary-looking guy.
And he... he was
just looking at me.
Ooh-hoo-hoo!
A big scary-looking guy!
- Boo-hoo-hoo, everyone!
- Cut it out, Billy!
He was just standing there.
Dude, come on,
quarters down.
Seriously, could you
spit more food out at me?
So, Uggi, have you heard
from Jules tonight?
Yeah, she said she had
to back to her father's shop
and give him a hand
with some stuff.
With what, a motor job?
Billy,
Nik was really freaked out
over that guy.
Oh my gosh!
What guy?
There was no one around.
Wait... did you see anyone?
She looked like she'd
seen a ghost, a big one.
Okay, well, let's go inside
and I'll show you a big one.
Billy, is that all
you ever think about?
Oh, come on.
And you don't?
No, not right now.
Hey, Billy.
l... um...
hey, hi... Toni.
Hi, T-Toni.
You know...
my sister's hot, but...
she's... just not
hot like this.
I...
would fucking tear...
you... up.
But then...
I don't think you'd
be able to function,
no less play football.
Hey, Cin, I'm gonna go spend
the weekend at Brad's house.
Billy, baby...
wipe your drool.
Billy, what are you doing?
Come upstairs!
Yeah.
Hike! Go! Go!
What? I thought
you could run faster.
You know, I'm better off
just throwing to the pothead.
What, were you scared,
you little bitch?
What?
What, Nik?
Nik... hey... hey...
what... what happened?
- It was him.
- Who, Nik?
- It was that guy.
- What...
what guy, Nik?
There's nobody around here.
It was the guy standing
in the window.
He's... he's following me.
There's no one here, Nik.
He was... he was so big.
- And his face was...
- Hey hey.
Okay, what did
he look like?
Burned.
Come on, Nicole.
I think it was just your imagination.
It was real!
I walked right into him!
Guys, I'm not crazy!
It was real.
All right, come on.
Let's get you home.
Oh-ho-ho.
Oh, that is beautiful...
if I do say so myself.
Troy! What's wrong
with the lights?
Troy, do you hear me?
Who's at the door?!
Well... who is it?
- Mrs. Olen?
- Yes?
Mrs. Olen, I'm Detective Vega.
I think you know Sheriff Cutter.
- Mrs. Olen.
- Hello.
Knock knock.
Who's there?
Knock knock. Who's there?
Knock knock.
Who's there?
Knock knock. Who's there?
Knock knock.
Who's there?
Knock knock...
Is your son Troy home?
Is... is he in some
kind of trouble?
We just need to ask him
a few questions, Mrs. Olen.
Is there something wrong
with your lights, Mrs. Olen?
Must be some kind
of a power surge or something.
Uh, please,
just wait right here.
- I'll... I'll go get Troy.
- Thank you.
Troy...
what have you done?
Nothing, Ma. Nothing.
Look at this place.
This place hasn't
changed in over 20 years.
You've been here?
Once or twice
when we were kids.
Jeez.
They're taking awhile.
Let's go take a look.
Nothin', Ma.
I did nothing.
Well, then why is
there a detective
and... and that
Cutter boy in my house
wantin' to talk to you?
I don't know.
I don't know, Ma.
Well...
Mrs. Olen,
is everything okay?
Yes.
Why shouldn't it be?
- Hello, Troy.
- Hello.
Troy, some of the kids
we spoke to
said they saw you looking at them
when they left the pep rally.
Please, Ma,
don't let them take me.
- Please.
- Why would we want to take you, Troy?
Did you do something
wrong?
Please don't
hurt my boy.
Please!
I didn't do anything.
No, not me,
Then who, Troy?
Who did something?
Tell us, Troy.
I didn't do nothin'!
I didn't do anything.
Leave him alone!
He didn't do nothing!
He knows more
than he's telling us.
I don't know.
I mean, even in high school,
I just thought
he was a weirdo.
Cutter, that's what
they said about Ted Bundy.
What did I tell you
about being a bad boy, Tommy?
You don't listen, do you?
Well, we've got special
plans for you, Tommy.
Aw, you might as well
say bye-bye, Tommy.
Bye-bye.
Silly boy.
There you go.
Oh, Nicole.
So beautiful.
You look pretty today.
But you didn't tell me
you missed me yet.
Why don't you ever
tell me you miss me?
I miss you. I do.
Honestly, I do.
How you doing?
Well, I'm sweepin'.
God, it is hot
in here.
Who won the football game?
Dad, you know by now, I don't
go to those games to watch.
I just go to... hang out.
- Do you need some help?
- Nah.
Dad!
What?!
Julie!
What's the matter?
Nothing, Dad.
Nothing.
Nothing, I'm... I'm fine.
Okay.
I want to go
test drive this baby.
Yeah, all right, Dad.
I'll pick up some dinner on the way
back.
- Chicken?
- Okay.
Make sure
it's extra crispy,
not like last time.
Oh, God.
Julie! No!
Please, no.
Please!
No! No no!
Julie, no!
No no no no!
No! Julie! No!
God, no!
No! No!
Please! No!
No, please!
No! No!
Please! Don't leave me.
- Please.
- Who's there?
No!
# The shadows arise,
consuming freedom to them #
# 1,000 years vast will end
retrieving our prize #
# Out from the forest,
I'll be your picture #
# A lonely town
and bad ass #
# Under control,
sicken and wither... #
Kids, I promise...
it'll only be
for a little while.
Just try to be home
by dark if you can.
Walk in groups, please.
All right?
Pay attention to surroundings.
Hey, Frank.
Good seeing you.
Don't forget to vote,
all right?
Thanks a lot.
Take care.
Try to be home
by dark if you can.
- See you around, man.
- No doubt.
- Look at this shit.
- What?
They want us
off the street by dark.
Or walking
with a large group.
Yeah, right.
- Oh... ah!
- And one.
I didn't touch... whatever.
A football team
is a large group.
It is.
Curt! When you're
done getting dressed
I need to see you
in my office.
Okay, Coach!
Hey, why don't you meet me in Coach
Sully's office when you're ready?
All right, cool.
It'll take a minute though.
Yeah, I know.
Yeah, right.
Come on, Curt.
Stop fuckin' around!
Your son Shawn looks
real good in practice.
He's really gonna
light them up this year.
Yeah. I keep telling him
he's gotta stay focused,
keep working.
Game's getting
faster all the time.
It sure is,
I'll tell you.
Can't keep up
with it myself.
What the...
Knock knock.
"Knock knock"?
What the hell kinda prank
are they playing on me today?
Knock knock.
Who's there?
Knock knock. Who's there?
Knock knock.
Who's there?
Knock knock. Who's there?
Knock knock.
Who's there?
No-oh-oh!
No! No! No! No!
- No!
- Holy shit.
No!
Knock knock.
Who's there?
- Where you taking me, man?
- Shut up!
I didn't do anything.
Where... where you taking me?
Please, where are
you taking me?
- Come on! Quiet!
- What is this?
Come on, Troy, tell me:
Why did you kill Shawn Rae Jr?
Look at me, Troy!
Was it jealousy?
I didn't kill anybody,
not me. No, not me.
Didn't I tell you
to look at me?
Do you think this is funny?
I'll smack that fucking
smile right off your face.
Why did you kill
Shawn Rae, Troy?
I didn't kill anybody.
Oh! She has a little
tiger in her, huh?
I love that
in a woman.
We got our killer?
We charging him?
What do you
think, Mike?
This guy's
not your killer.
What do you mean
he's not our killer?
Dean, please.
Why do you
think that?
Charlie, look at him.
He's small, weak.
Besides, this guy's
left-handed.
The coroner says your
guy's gotta be 6'2", 6'3".
Most of all, Charlie,
your killer's right-handed.
The coroner?
He stops for a cocktail
at The Abbey once in a while.
Innocent people
are being killed.
There are pictures
of kids in this book.
Start fucking talking, Troy.
The ice pick incisions
in the Jerome kid
all came from
the right side.
Julie Papas,
she was smacked around
on the left side of her face.
And, Charlie, I'm telling you,
I'll bet you anything,
something on Shawn Rae
is gonna lead you
to a right-handed killer.
You are good.
What can I tell ya?
I think you're
both fuckin' crazy.
We need a killer
and we need him now.
So Vega's smacking around
an innocent guy?
I didn't say
he's innocent,
but he's not
your killer.
Let her get her
frustrations out anyway.
Maybe it's that time
of month or something.
Besides, it might soften
this prick up a little bit.
Well, you better
get out of here
before she sees you
and softens you up a little.
Hey, you know
I might like that too.
Hey, Charlie,
where's this guy's mother?
Out in the waiting area.
Do me a favor...
hold 'em here.
I want to do
a little snooping around.
We searched the house
and his room.
And that's why I'm going.
You think
he knows something?
Oh, he knows.
He knows a lot.
Believe me.
Hey, Mike, you've seen
a lot of shit in your day,
being on the job.
What do you think of that Shawn kid
being killed like that?
And then in his
father's place too.
What do you mean
"too," Hank?
That Julie Papas...
she was killed in her
father's shop too. Right?
You know, you're right.
What do you know
about this Rico Volpe?
Father or son?
- Both.
- Hey, now you're going back.
Father...
local funeral director.
Nice dresser and all.
Good customer too.
His place burnt down,
almost killed his son.
What happened?
The son, Rico Jr...
loner, had no friends.
Mother left,
father falls behind
on the mortgage.
They say he
torched the place...
...to collect
the insurance money...
with his son in it!
- Shit.
- Nice guy, huh?
- Real nice guy.
- Uh-oh.
Find anything, Mick?
I don't know what
you're talking about.
You know damn well
what I'm talking about.
Maybe they didn't use warrants
in New York,
but here we do things
by the book.
Like tonight, when you
smacked around that mamaluke?
Is that by the book?
Stay out of my way
or I'll fuckin' smack you around.
I might like that.
Billy, I'll be down
in just a minute!
Don't go anywhere.
Billy, quit trying to scare me.
You're so predictable.
Quit fucking around, asshole.
Billy?
Billy, are you out there?
Excuse me.
Could you help me
a minute, please?
Hold on one second,
I'll be happy to help you.
I'm sorry to bother you.
I left my glasses home... again.
I was hoping you could
help me read this article.
It's kind of important.
Don't even think about it.
That's what I'm here for.
Thank you.
Excuse me.
That's... quite all right.
Okay, what do
we have here?
Okay.
"Yesterday, in Glass County
Superior Court,
Rico Volpe Sr.
was found guilty
of attempted murder
and arson
after deliberately starting
a fire in his funeral home
to recoup insurance money.
Mr. Volpe maintained
his innocence,
stating that he left his son
and his son's friend in their home
when he left
to go on an errand.
Firemen found Rico Jr.
locked in a casket,
still alive,
but badly burned.
No other body was found.
Sources say defense attorneys
had tried to argue
that Rico Jr. was responsible
for starting the fire,
but Volpe
refused to reveal
the identity
of the alleged accomplice.
Rico Volpe Sr. was sentenced
to life in prison."
He didn't do it. He could
never do anything like that.
How would you know that?
I know him.
He had a thing for me...
if you know
what I mean.
I don't blame him.
Thank you.
I know one thing,
I know he adored his kids.
Kids?
Oh, he has
a daughter named Rachel.
She runs a bar called Dylan's
on the outskirt of Wayne.
What is she,
the barmaid?
She's the bouncer.
If you've had one too many,
you find yourself
staring at the sidewalk
when you wake up.
She's a real tough one.
Why don't we have a drink?
I'd love to, sugar.
But like I told you,
she's a real tough one.
And she don't
like me very much.
Maybe next time?
Maybe.
- What can I get ya?
- Let me get a Scotch,
tall glass,
a lot of ice, please.
You got some body.
You work out?
No.
You look like you do.
Yeah, well,
I get my workout
throwing annoying guys like you
out on their asses.
What happened
to your wrist?
Well, some guy annoyed me,
so I knocked him
the fuck out...
with one shot.
- Nice. Very nice.
- That's $5.50.
Keep the change.
You are Rachel Volpe, right?
- Who the fuck are you?
- My name's Mike Soato.
Yo, hold up.
What are you doing?
How many times
do I have to tell you
they go in
the walk-in box.
So what are you, a cop?
Used to be.
No more.
So then,
what do you want here?
I'd like to find out a little more
about your brother Rico.
Why? You like being nosy?
What, that's a cop
thing, right?
No. I think what
happened to him that day
has a lot to do
with what's going on now.
What, those kid murders?
Well, fuck them.
What does it have
to do with my brother?
I was hoping
you could tell me.
How about I knock
your fuckin' lights out?
Jesus Christ.
What is it with me and women?
All youse wanna do
is hit me.
I wonder why. Listen.
They put my father away for life
and they committed my brother.
End of story.
What about your mother?
Don't know, don't care.
Bitch is dead to me.
Like I said:
end of story.
How's your brother Rico?
Hello.
Marcus, look.
You're the mayor.
If you want to continue
to be the fuckin' mayor,
you gotta find out
what's happening.
Our kid's are dying here!
Look, I just
walked in the house.
Dean, I'll talk
to you tomorrow.
Cindy!
Knock knock.
Who's there?
Cindy!
God, no! Cindy!
God!
Cindy! Oh my God!
Cindy! No!
Cindy!
Knock Knock.
Who's there?
Knock knock. Who's there?
No!
Knock knock.
Who's there?
Knock knock. Who's there?
Knock knock.
Who's there?
Knock knock. Who's there?
Knock knock.
Who's there?
Okay, Vega,
what do you got?
I don't know anymore.
This guy is just killing at random.
He has no motive.
Try starting
with revenge.
- What did you say?
- Captain, may I?
Yeah, what do you got?
The killer's getting some kind
of work-related revenge.
What?
Julie Papas...
she was killed
at her father's workshop.
Shawn Rae,
and today,
this kid Billy...
also killed in the father's
workshop.
What about
Cindy and Jerome?
They were both
killed in their homes.
Cindy was butchered
like a deer.
So? What does that have
to do with anything?
Cindy's dad owns
Drake's Meat.
Jerome's father
is an iceman.
What do we do?
We can tell
their friends.
That would take
too much of our manpower
that we don't have.
You could try to see what
the fathers have in common.
What do you think?
Find out who's next.
Nobody knows that.
He does.
Who are you?
Knock knock.
Who's there?
Knock knock. Who's there?
What do you want?!
Knock knock.
- Knock knock.
- What have I done to you?
- Who's there?
- Why are you doing this to me?!
Why are you
doing this to me?!
Why-why... why are you
Oh my God! No!
# I look forward... #
What are you
gonna do with that?
It ain't safe
out there, Mick.
So me and Suzie here
are gonna have
to put a stop to it.
You're not gonna stop
anything with that.
Then how do we?
We?
We can start
by having a drink together.
- What can I get you, Billie?
- Jack, straight up, please.
What's the matter?
You look like
a martini girl to me.
Martinis are
for next time.
Here's to the next time.
Get me another one
and her one.
Are you okay, Cindy?
You hurt Cindy, Rick.
You hurt Cindy.
I promise he won't do it
to you again, Cindy.
Because if you do...
You look so beautiful.
You know I love you,
don't you?
Is it true you once dressed
as a woman to make a bust?
- Yeah. Scary, huh?
- It's hilarious.
You think that's funny,
you should've seen the time
they made me go
undercover in a gay bar.
You've seen a lot
of shit in your day.
How about you?
Biggest things
I ever had before this
were shoplifters, bootleggers
and some domestic violence cases.
Usually the same people too.
How come they
named you Billie?
Father wanted a boy,
I guess.
Is that why you got
that chip on your shoulder?
My father wasn't
nice to me growing up.
I never told anybody this,
but he should've had a boy.
Is that why you
joined the force?
I was homecoming queen,
Miss Teen-everything.
My father was livid.
At least you have
the equipment for it.
Thanks.
Listen, I'm really sorry about
the way I've been treating you.
Listen to me, Billie.
Listen to me.
Don't let this job take
your life like it took mine.
I gave my entire life
to this job.
Even when my wife
was dying of cancer,
I didn't even
have time for her.
And after she died,
I sent my only son up here
to live with his aunt.
Why?
Because I didn't
have the time to raise him.
And then just when I thought
I'd get to know him...
he goes and dies
in a car crash on me.
Now I'm trying to get
to know my granddaughter...
his daughter Nikki.
And she don't want
nothing to do with me.
And you know what, Billie?
I don't even blame her.
I'm really sorry.
Give her a little
more time.
Time?
Oh, and another thing...
- There's more?
- Oh, there's more.
Don't ever ever tell
your commanding officer
you don't know.
Even when you don't know...
you know.
I guess I have
a lot to learn.
Hey, I got time.
Knock knock. Who's there?
Knock knock.
Who's there?
Knock knock. Who's there?
Knock knock.
Who's there?
Oh God, no!
Pick up, Mike.
- Hello.
- Mike, it's Vega.
There's been another murder.
Meet me at the skateboard park on
Morris Boulevard near the highway.
Get here as soon
as you can.
I'll be there
in a little while. Bye.
So what's up?
I told you they were
bad for your health.
So are you?
Look, Mike, you said
I have a lot to learn, right?
- That's right.
- Well, school's in.
It's bad.
Come on.
What do you got?
His name was
Rick Cohen, 16.
Decapitated...
every limb cut off.
- Oh my God.
- I've never seen anything like this,
not even
in the movies.
This kid's out of the circle
of the other murder victims.
He goes
to a private school.
No connection.
What does
his father do?
He's a doctor.
What do you think?
It's definitely
the same killer.
The patterns all match.
The coroner was right.
This guy's extremely
fuckin' strong.
And like I said,
he's right-handed.
You see how
the right side limbs...
the cuts are much cleaner?
If the killer was holding up the
body with his left hand,
to cut the right side limbs
wouldn't be a problem.
Otherwise, he'd have to
reach over his outstretched arm,
making it very difficult
to cut the left side.
And remember, he's still
holding the kid up...
by his hair.
What happened to him?
He said Rick was doing
his thing in the ring
when he saw a shadow
come up behind him.
He turned,
next thing he knows,
he's being brought to
by the E.M.T.
Why not kill 'em both?
He didn't want both.
- Cutter, what's up?
- I just got back from Clark's Gym.
Tommy Clark's body was thrown
through the front window.
Every bone in his body
looked broken.
His face was
barely recognizable.
What kind of doctor was
this Cohen kid's father?
Plastic surgeon.
This Cohen kid's father,
he wasn't even
on the football team.
Excuse me, Mr. Mayor, but what do these
killings have to do with football?
Well, I mean,
all the other fathers,
they... they played football.
Did you know that?
No.
l... I played
high-school ball with them.
- Yes.
- Come on, Billie. Come on.
I realize it's bad.
The Clark boy too. Uh-huh.
Where are we going?
First we go by the Tommy
Clark crime scene.
Then after school, we're gonna
go see your friend Troy.
Think we could
get him to talk?
If not, you're gonna
need a whole lot more
of this yellow tape.
Hey, what do you
make of the mayor
knowing all the fathers
of the victims played football?
Coincidence?
I don't believe
in coincidence.
How do we play Troy?
You're the beauty
pageant winner.
We're gonna use
these good looks
for the sake of the job.
Leave the jacket
in the car.
Come here.
Come over here.
Act nice.
Be a little bit more seductive.
Come on.
There he is.
Hey!
Please! Please don't...
don't hit me!
Calm down, Troy.
I'm not gonna hurt you.
- Please don't.
- Troy, listen.
We just need help with a little
something. Ain't that right, Billie?
That's right.
Will you do that
for me, Troy?
Please?
Good. What can you tell
me about your friend?
You know, Troy,
the one you're always talking to.
Oh, I don't know.
I don't know what
you're talking about.
Come on, Troy.
Please tell Billie.
Tell Billie all
about him and I promise
no one's gonna hurt you.
Knock knock. Who's there?
Knock knock.
Who's there?
Knock knock. Who's there?
Knock knock.
Who's there?
Knock knock. Who's there?
- Stop that! Get off!
- Who's there?
- Please stop it! Stop!
- Knock knock. Who's there?
You had your turn!
Listen to me,
you fuckin' idiot!
You ain't as dumb as you look!
Please!
Go away!
Stop that!
Don't do that!
- Go away!
- Knock, knock.
- Mike!
- Mike what? You had your turn!
Listen to me,
you fuckin' idiot.
I know you ain't as dumb
as you look. Please what?!
Knock knock. Who's there?
Where's Rico Volpe?
Tell me about Rico Volpe!
Tell me about him.
The guy you've been
talking to... where is he?
Look at it! This is the guy
you've been talking to.
Don't look at her,
look at me!
What happened...
Tell me about the fire.
How did the fire start?
I'm talking to you!
Listen to me, you fucking idiot.
What happened to Rico?
You were with him.
You were with him, Troy.
- Knock knock. Who's there?
- What happened to Rico Volpe?
Knock knock. Who's there?
You were the friend that was
with him. Ain't that right?
Knock knock. Who's there?
Did you start the fire?
Knock knock.
Who's there?
Listen to me, Troy.
Please listen to me.
There are innocent
children being slaughtered.
They are just kids.
Kids. You understand?
- Kids!
- So were we!
We were just kids too.
What happened, Troy?
Please tell us.
We were just playing army
in our foxhole.
You and Rico
were playing army?
Then what happened, Troy?
Rico and I would always
play together after school.
He's my best friend.
That's good. Real good.
After school, me and Rico would help
his father clean up the funeral home.
And then you know,
Mr. Volpe,
he would let us play
in the basement.
That's where
our foxhole was.
Ha ha!
I'm killing all your guys!
- What do you think of that?
- Not all my guys.
What about my sniper?
We had so much fun.
- That's good.
- Then what happened, Troy?
Did you two by accident
start the fire?
No. No.
We didn't start the fire.
- They did!
- Who, Troy?
Who are they?
My bazooka guy's
getting all your people.
Here comes my sergeant.
Me and Rico were
playing in the basement
when we heard
them upstairs.
- Who's that?
- I don't know.
Rico!
- Shh! Quiet.
- You think it's burglars?
I don't know.
Hey!
- What's going on, Rico?
- What are you guys doing?
What's going on? Hey...
What are you guys doing here?
We're closed...
Lookie what we got here.
Where's your
retard friend, huh?
Hey, what are you guys
doing here? We're closed.
Oh, you are? Hey, guys,
he says they're closed!
Go home.
Hey you, get off
my father's stuff.
Get him.
Get him guys! Come on!
Get him down.
Hold him down!
- I got his legs.
- What are you guys doing?
Hold him down!
You'll see what we're doing.
No!
What are
you doing to me?
- No!
- Oh, you'll see what we're gonna do.
- Come on.
What are you guys doing?!
Hold still!
Come on, guys!
Hurry up!
Come on, damn it!
Open to the casket! Get it open.
What are you guys
doing to me?! No!
- Shut up! Shut up!
- No!
Stop! What are
you guys doing?!
- Quiet!
- Come on, shut him up.
Let me out!
Knock knock.
Who's there?
It's Rico!
Knock knock.
Who's there?
It's Rico!
Knock knock.
Who's there?
It's Rico!
Knock knock.
Who's there?
It's Rico!
Shh!
Knock knock.
Who's there?
It's Rico!
Knock knock!
All right, hey,
it's enough. Just let him out.
Dean, we're just
having a little fun.
Knock knock.
Who's there?
- It's Rico!
- I said cut it out!
Who the fuck do you
think you're talking to?
I don't know we even hang out
with this little sissy punk.
Come on!
Knock knock. Who's there?
Knock knock.
Who's there?
Knock knock. Who's there?
Knock knock.
Who's there?
- Fire!
- Put it out!
Get it open!
- I can't! It's stuck!
- Come on!
- Get him out!
- What did you do?!
- He's gonna fucking die.
- Rico.
Are you kidding me?
Guys, come on!
No, we're all
gonna die, man!
Oh, Rico, I'm sorry.
Rico!
Rico! Are you okay?
Can you hear me?
I'll get you out, Rico!
Rico! Rico!
Rico, I'm gonna
get you out, Rico!
Rico! Rico!
- Rico!
- No!
They left him
there to die!
I wanted to help...
but I couldn't.
I couldn't
open the casket.
I let my
best friend burn.
Troy, oh my...
Troy, if you could've,
you would've.
You can help him now.
Tell me who
did this to him.
Tell me.
Please, Troy.
Please, Troy, tell us.
I'll make sure
no one hurts you.
Come on, Troy.
What do you want to show us?
Shawn Rae,
Tony Papas,
Billy Smith,
Jerome Peters...
They were the ones
that did it, Troy?
The football players.
Football here
is so important
they'd even cover up
attempted murder?
I'm sure they didn't
intend to start that fire.
They were probably just bullies
out having some fun.
That casket door jammed
and they panicked.
The Cohen kid...
he had to be the ballboy.
That's how
he fits in.
He had a car.
They were friends with him
because he had a car.
Some things never
fuckin' change.
The last one
is Fred Hunter.
His kid's
gotta be next.
His was first.
Holly Hunter was
killed a few weeks ago
in Jefferson County.
Is that it, Troy?
Is that all of them?
That's all the circles, Troy.
Who else was there?
It's okay.
Michael Reynolds?
Billie, that's my son.
When he came up here,
he moved in with his aunt.
He took her last name to fit in.
Knock knock. Who's there?
Your son was the one that locked
Rico in the coffin.
My granddaughter Nikki.
That son of a bitch saved her
for last! Let's go!
Knock knock.
Who's there?
Please don't hurt him!
Please don't hurt him again!
He's my friend!
#... you borrowed from me
just expired #
# You never loved me #
# Like I love you #
# Many many times #
# I tried to walk away #
- # Can't no one love you... #
# Like I love you #
# You pick me up to break
me down and kiss the... #
This is Detective
Billie Vega.
I need all available units to meet me
at... Mike, what's the address?
- There's no answer.
- Mike?
- 926 Willow.
- 926 Willow Street.
Possible 10-13 in progress.
Okay, so Rico gets
out of the institution,
comes back for revenge.
Instead of taking it out
on the guys that did it to him,
he kills their kids.
In a way that relates
to their father's job.
Just like they did to him.
What'd your son do
before the accident?
Nothing. He killed himself
soon after he got married.
- You said it was an accident.
- I always thought it was...
until now.
We'll find Rico
and stop him.
We will?
His sister said he died
two weeks ago in the institution.
- Sister?
- Don't ask.
Knock knock.
Why... why are you
doing this to me?
Why are you
doing this? Help!
Nicole!
- Mrs. Reynolds!
- Ruth!
- Nicole!
Nikki!
Nicole! Ruth!
Nicole!
Ruth!
Help!
Why are you
doing this to me?
Why are you doing this?!
- Who's there?
- Please!
Please!
Why are you doing this?
Why?
Wait! Wait!
Who's there?
It's Rico! Knock knock.
It's Rico!
Knock knock.
Who's there?
It's Rico!
Shit.
I'll go around back.
Shit!
Ruth.
Ruth!
Shit.
Nicole!
I'm sorry, Nicole.
I should've figured
this out sooner.
- I could've protected you from it.
- You saved my life, Grandpa.
Who... who is he?
Supposedly, a dead man.
Grandpa!
No!
- Grandpa, please.
- I'm so sorry, Nicole.
I wasn't there
for you or your father.
No no no. You were here
when I needed you the most.
Grandpa, please. Grandpa, please,
I need you now.
Somebody!
Somebody, help!
Grandpa!
Grandpa, please!
- Who did this, Billie?
- He did.
- Who?
- Rico, I shot him.
He was right there
and now he's gone.
# Knock knock #
# Who's there? #
- Who's there?
- Me.
Knock knock.
Who's there?
# You never change #
# Yeah #
# Oh here we go again #
# For the thousandth time #
# I shouldn't have to teach you
how to treat me right #
# All I do is give #
# I can't take no more #
# All the time you borrowed
from me just expired #
# You never loved me #
# Like I love you #
# Many many times #
# I tried to walk away #
# Can't no one love you #
# Like I love you #
# You pick me up
to break me down #
# And kiss the tears you make #
# Sometimes I feel
I am the only one #
# That cannot see through #
# The lies,
the stories #
# And the shady things
you always do #
# Just when you trick me into
thinking that you'll change your ways #
- # Never change #
- # You just mess up again #
# And bring me back
to all my pain #
# So much pain #
# Baby baby #
# You could save me #
# Please say that you
love me tell me you need me #
# Why can't you say
how you feel? #
# It hurts so bad #
# My heart is breaking #
# How many tears
should I cry? #
# 'Cause I'm dying inside,
you're killing me #
# You never loved me #
# Like I love you #
# Many many times #
# I tried to walk away #
# Can't no one love you #
# Like I love you #
# You pick me up
to break me down #
# And kiss
the tears you make #
# Sometimes I feel
I am the only one #
# That cannot see through #
# The lies,
the stories #
# And the shady things
you always do #
# Just when you trick me into thinking
that you'll change your ways #
- # Never change #
- # You just mess up again #
# And bring me back
to all my pain #
# So much pain #
# All I want from you
are smiles #
# You're the only one #
# Who makes me cry #
# And I'm holding
onto you so tight #
# I just can't let you go #
# No no #
# You never loved me #
# Like I loved you #
# Can't no one love you #
# Sometimes I feel
I am the only one #
# That cannot see through #
# The lies,
the stories #
# And the shady things
you always do #
# Just when you trick me into
thinking that you'll change your ways #
- # Never change #
- # You just mess up again #
# And bring me back
to all my pain #
# So much pain. #
Knock knock.
Subtitles by LeapinLar