STARCROSSED
Out of pool, boys!
Connor, use the legs, damn it!
Fabulous facility...
Where have your damn legs?
Good job, man.
Dad...
Please!
Dare not help him!
He can do it self!
Do it self!
Hey, what happened?
Connor, you know...
Daddy says those things to us
that we can succeed.
Succeed at what we wants
to succeed at.
I don't wanna be,
who he wants me to be.
He doesn't even care
about anything I'm good at.
He never has.
That's not true.
Yes, it is.
Hey...
Come here.
Come, come on.
It's OK.
Let's see.
I wish I was more like you.
You are like me.
Connor, what the fuck was that?
- It wasn't anything.
- No, what the hell was that?
It was nothing.
I was just kidding.
You don't gotta be all serious.
It was just a joke.
Let's...
Let's go already meet the girls.
OK?
Hello ladies,
throw your coats on the floor...
Ah, Veronica, this is Brad.
Excellent!
Did you girls bring your partying slippers?
"Dear diary, I want to kill...
and you have to believe it's for more
than just selfish reasons,
more than just a spoke in my menstrual cycle.
You have to believe me."
It's so great to be able to talk to a girl
and not have to ask "What's your major?"
I hate that.
So, when you go to college,
what subjects do you think you'll study?
Come on, David. Shouldn't we get
back to the party?
We will.
It's just you're so hot tonight.
I can't control myself.
Oh Christ, I can't explain it,
but I'm allowed an understanding
that my parents and these Remington University
assholes have chosen to ignore.
Hey, Connor...?
Yeah?
What's happening?
I don't know.
What's wrong with us?
Wrong?
And I don't...
not like others view, so...
something has to be wrong with us.
Are you scared?
Yeah.
Showers!
- Darren!
- Hi...
- You're just gonna walk pass me?
- No, I'm sorry. I didn't see you.
- Why haven't you return any of my calls?
- I know. I'm sorry. I've been little busy.
- You used to call me every night.
- I know. I'm sorry. Look, I gotta go.
- Did I do something wrong?
- No!
I'll call you tonight, OK?
I promise.
Connor...
Yeah?
How long do you think we could keep this all?
I don't know.
What if we get torn apart?
I won't let that happen.
Connor?
Mom!
Take him...
they cannot see each other again.
- Where are we going?
- I don't know. Just drive!
Darren!
This isn't gonna end good, is it?
No.
I got here a stolen car.
I don't wanna live,
if I'm not with you.
I love you.
No one's here.
Are you ready?
Yes.
Subtitles by FOX
f-ox@post.cz