(Trey) She's hot. She's hot.
(Vince)
Ooh, man.
(Trey)
Hey, now, look.
506 Castle Drive.
That's definitely
the jackpot, man.
So look, we need
to set this up quick
and just melt in.
Don't we need an invite to get
up in here, man?
Ooh, thickness.
Thickness.
(Trey) Look, man,
this is our invite.
This.
Come on, man.
(Vince) I don't want
to get no damn barbecue.
I want to get a thickness.
[people chatting]
See you in a minute.
I gotta go.
(Trey) Vince, man, where you going?
I need help with this.
Vince!
(Vince)
Trey.
Trey, I just came
from the hot tub.
There's girls
in there, man.
They naked.
Titty city.
It's the real thing.
(Trey)
Yeah, right.
(Vince) No, no, no. Trey, Trey.
Put the food down.
Put the ribs down, man.
Come with me, man.
I got two first-class tickets
to Titty City.
(Trey)
No, look, look, man.
I got this food delivery man.
(Vince)
The food?
I'm telling you
about some titties,
and you
talking about ribs.
[hip-hop music playing]
Do you see this?
I'm going to the Titty City.
[man rapping]
Gonna make you clap.
Make you clap.
Yeah, yeah.
Girl, shake.
Pop left,
right, with it.
[girls laughing]
(Vince)
Hell yeah, boy.
This is what
I'm talking about.
Fantastic.
What are you doing?
Well, I noticed
that you lovely young ladies
are missing one key thing
in this hot tub.
That's a man.
It's me.
(girl)
Uh, hold up.
(Dedra)
Hey.
(Katherine)
I promise you,
if these kids tear up
my house, I'm gonna-
(Dedra)
You gonna what?
(Candace) You ain't
gonna do nothing.
Katherine, you need to stop
living vicariously
through your sorors.
(Katherine)
Shut up, Candace.
Look, all I'm saying is,
this is the last year I'm giving these kids
my house to do this.
I'll promise you, D.
Keily does not know what to do
with that man of hers.
(Dedra) Okay, you need to
stop looking at my niece's man.
Ooh, but look at him.
Hey, baby.
(Candace)
Hey, hey, hey, shh, shh.
Both of you,
will you please stop flirting
with these college boys?
(Dedra) And, "Why?"
would be my question.
(Candace) Uh, number one,
because they're young.
Number two,
you both have men.
(Katherine)
Separated.
Divorcing.
(Candace)
You haven't even filed yet.
And, oh, my God.
Wow, I would
buy him an Xbox.
[Katherine laughs]
(Dedra)
I might as well file.
My husband has a different woman
in every city he plays in.
(Candace)
That's hearsay.
(Katherine) I told you
not to marry a pro athlete.
They're all whores.
I just thought baseball players
were different, you know?
But he's gonna slip up,
and when he do,
I'm gonna catch him.
(Katherine) I'm going
to go pay this caterer.
I'll be right back.
(Candace)
Ooh, and I'm going to go see
if he has the new Madden.
(Katherine)
Hey!
Are you, um,
from Southside Barbecue and...
(Trey) And Check Cashing, African
Artifacts, and Laundroland.
(Katherine) Oh, thanks for
finishing that up for me.
I'm Katherine.
How you doing?
I'm Trey.
Hey, your food
is right over there.
(Katherine)
Oh, thanks.
Looks like
it's all there.
I thought you were
one of the college kids.
(Trey)
Huh?
(Katherine) I thought you
were one of the college kids.
(Trey) No, no, I'm just one of
the regular old delivery guys.
Yeah, you know, it's so loud in here,
I can barely hear you.
I'm sorry.
(Katherine)
This is for you.
(Trey)
Okay.
Well, thank you,
and I hope you enjoy your food.
And thank you
for your business.
(Vince)
Wait a minute.
Seem like you the only one
that's trippin'.
I don't care.
You're not getting in here with us.
Oh, it's like that?
What are you,
stupid or something?
Wait a minute, shorty.
You ain't even seen
what I got to offer yet.
Let me show you...
what's really going on.
[laughing]
What, I miss the joke
or something?
What happened?
- Is my thing out? What's happening?
- Rubber duckies?
[laughs]
Quack.
You know his mama
picked them out for him.
You ain't gotta
like my rubber duckies.
(girl)
Quack, quack.
(Vince)
Forget y'all!
Excuse me.
Could you get me
that towel over there, please?
(Trey)
There you go.
(Keily)
Thank you.
(Trey)
Sure. No problem.
Hey, I'm Trey.
(Keily)
Oh, nice to meet you.
(Carlton)
Honey, we have a problem?
(Trey)
No, there is no problem.
(Carlton)
Is your name Honey?
(Keily) Carlton, he was
just giving me a towel, okay?
(Carlton)
I'm right over here.
Look, you can't be
talking to dudes-
(Keily) You are
always embarrassing me.
(Carlton)
I'm embarrassing you?
(Keily) Excuse me.
I'm so sorry about this.
(Trey)
That's okay.
(Carlton) Why are you
apologizing to him?
He's the help.
(Keily)
Stop being rude, Carlton.
You are always
doing this.
(Carlton) All right, look, look.
Trey, is it?
(Trey)
Yeah, Trey it is.
(Carlton)
Do me a favor.
Why don't you get me and my girl
a plate of ribs, some chicken-
(Keily)
Carlton.
(Carlton)
He brought them.
He's the rib dude.
He's supposed to serve it too,
ain't he?
Hey, yo, Trey,
no potato salad for me, man.
Bad on the indigestion.
What?
What did I say?
(girl #1)
I'm gonna tell your mama.
[girls laughing]
(girl #2)
I know. Did you see those?
His mommy pick them out
for him this morning.
(girl #1)
Gotta love your mama.
[girls laughing]
(girl #2)
I thought he was about to dive in.
[girls chatting and laughing]
(Carlton) Baby, he
works at that ghetto spot
where they got, like,
eight businesses in one.
(Keily)
So?
That gives you no right
to be rude.
(Carlton)
I think it does.
(Trey)
Excuse me.
Here's my
business card/menu.
(Carlton)
Oops.
(Vince) Excuse me, big man.
Hey, Trey,
we got to go, man.
We got a problem.
(Trey)
What is you doing?
(Vince)
Man, come on!
(Trey)
All right.
(Carlton)
Oh!
[water splashing]
That's right.
You better run.
It's your ass
when I see you next time!
[upbeat R&B music]
[Tamia singing] What
happened to the roses
and the little phone calls
we made throughout the day?
And the silly little games
we played?
Somehow things have changed
How I miss the old.
Got my feelings thrown.
We barely holding on
Why can't we,
you and me, be happy?
Why can't we
just be so happy?
Why can't we just chill
and be happy?
Why can't we
just be so happy?
The arguing
seems to win over lovin'.
Use to be huggin',
kissin', and rubbin'.
Now every day
is something new
separating me and you.
I thought that we could
get through anything.
Why can't we,
you and me, be happy?
Why can't we
just be so happy?
So happy, baby.
Why can't we
just chill and be happy?
Why can't we just
be so happy?
(Mr. Vickers)
Glad you enjoyed it.
Vince, put the magazine down.
Get to work.
You don't stand a chance
with none of them shorts.
(Vince)
It's shorties, Dad.
(Mr. Vickers)
Shorties? Got you.
(Mrs. Vickers) I thought you had
a buyer for that spear, Cinque?
(Cinque) Couple of
crackers came in yesterday.
Said they'd come back
this morning and buy one.
Never showed up.
You know how
white folks are.
(Mrs. Vickers)
Yes, I do.
Don't sweat it, Cin.
(Cinque)
Yeah.
All I'm saying is,
the peckerwood could've told me
he wasn't interested
instead of wasting my time.
(Mrs. Vickers)
Let it go, Cin.
You know they got
that elitist attitude.
(Cinque) Yeah, they
think they better than us.
(Mrs. Vickers)
Exactly.
Unbelievable.
Well, hello.
What can you do for me?
(girl)
What?
(Vince)
I mean, uh...
what can I do for you?
(No Doubt)
I will get your dog.
[record scratching]
Your dog.
Get your dog.
Krispy Kreme.
The pumping of the bass.
The color
of your hair, dude.
(Mack)
Hey.
That's it for today, boys.
What's up, Trey?
Hey, Unc,
brought you some food.
(Mack)
Aw, thanks, man.
(No Doubt) Yo, Trey,
that's the hit right there.
Ya heard me?
Hey, we going to the top
with this one, baby.
(K-3)
Ugh.
Trying to tell you, man,
when this single
hits the streets,
it's going to be game over.
(Mack) You boys
are really talented.
[chuckles]
(K-3)
Yeah, fo' sho, fo' sho.
Hey, look here,
Mack, man.
About that money
we owe you this week,
we gonna be coming up
a little bit short.
So, you know,
all we got is, like, $50.
So I figured-
that's good?
(Mack)
Yeah, man, that's cool.
That's all right.
Yeah.
Yeah, just hit me
when you got it.
[cell phone playing music]
Studio.
Look, man, the answer's
the same as it was yesterday.
No.
[sighs]
The developers again?
Yeah.
(Trey) Then why you keep
letting them guys slide?
(Mack) Oh, man, it's okay.
(Trey) You can't keep letting
them guys get away without paying.
All right, they gonna run you
straight out of business.
That's why you haven't been able
to upgrade the studio now.
(Mack) Look, Trey, some
of these kids have talent.
They just
ain't got the money.
It's just my way
of helping out.
(Trey)
That's it.
That's a reel to reel
right there.
That's a cassette recorder.
Everything nowadays
is digital.
Once people figure out how
to do this on their laptops,
you gonna be done.
(Trey) How much I
owe you for the food?
(Trey)
Why you tuning me out?
Why don't you
just sell this place, man,
and cash out?
(Mack) Me and your father put
our blood, sweat, and tears
into this place.
You see all these stars
on this wall here?
They all
did their albums here.
(Trey)
That's it.
They not coming back.
You got a 16-track board
and only 9 of the tracks work.
They not coming back.
(Mack)
I'm not selling.
If your father was here-
He would
tell you to sell.
(Mack)
No, he wouldn't.
(Trey) Look, you got 75K
in arrears, all right?
I saw the notice.
(Mack) You looking
through my mail now?
(Trey)
I'm not looking at your mail, all right?
You got 35 days left
until they
foreclose on this property.
All right, and you're
not getting nothing for it.
(Mack) They trying to
tear this place down
and turn it
into a strip mall, man.
I'm not gonna let that happen.
(Trey)
Oh, you ain't got no choice.
You ain't got no money.
(Mack)
I'll get the money.
(Trey)
From where?
(Vince) Why you so
angry all the time?
(Cinque)
You want to know why?
Because the conservative
white right wing of America
is trying to take us
back to the '50s.
And I'm not going.
(Mrs. Vickers)
Word.
Oh, hell no.
Ma, why do you
always keep feeding
into his hostile attitude?
(Mrs. Vickers) Well, I'll stop when
you quit running up my credit cards
on those
meet-a-freak websites.
[laughter]
(Vince)
That's real funny.
Yeah, you know
I'm doing a research project.
(Mrs. Vickers)
Okay.
(Cinque)
In what class?
Don't you have to be
enrolled in college
to take classes?
(Vince) Hey, man, why your boy
always trying to put me on glass?
(Trey) Look, man, you
know you're an easy target.
You still looking at them girls
on the internet, huh?
(Vince)
Aw, man. Come on, man.
You trippin', man.
You know
I got the ladies.
(Trey)
Damn.
(Vince)
Hey, Ma, I got this one.
How y'all doing?
(Carlton) Hey, aren't
you that little bitch
that pushed me in the pool?
(Vince) No, I believe
you got me mistaken.
That actually was Trey.
Trey?
(Keily)
Carlton, let's just go.
Come on.
(Trey)
Thanks, Vin.
(Vince)
Hey, man, hey,
that is a starting all-American
middle linebacker, man,
from NCU.
He about 6'5", 250.
Now, you know
I'm half of that.
You know what I'm saying?
And you know
I'm into the self-preservation.
(Carlton)
Shut up, punk!
(Vince) Hey, man, Trey,
what's up with your boy?
(Carlton)
So it was you.
If I remember correctly,
I said the next time I saw you,
I was going to whoop your ass.
And I believe
this is next time.
(Trey) Well, it's pretty
obvious that philosophy
must be one
of your favorite subjects.
[Carlton scoffs]
(Vince)
Hey!
Hey, Trey,
get him.
(Carlton)
What you gonna do?
(Cinque)
You better get off me, homes.
(Carlton)
Or else what?
What you
gonna do about it?
Oh!
Ah, that hurts, man.
What's wrong with you?
Let my arm go.
(Vince)
Yeah. Yeah.
Mm-hmm.
(Carlton)
Get off me.
(Keily) Trey, Trey, please
accept my apologies, okay?
(Trey) Look, there's
no need to apologize.
I mean,
you're absolutely stunning.
(Mrs. Vickers) Vince, your dad
and I are fixing to roll out.
Can you hold it down
for about three hours?
(Vince)
Of course.
(Mrs. Vickers) Okay,
come on, honey, let's go.
[Keily whispers]
Those are his parents?
(Trey)
Yeah, he adopted.
(Carlton) Keily, get
your ass out here now!
(Trey)
Wow.
That's no way for a man
to talk to his woman.
You know you can
do better than that.
(Keily)
I gotta go.
(Trey) Well, it was
nice seeing you again.
(Keily)
Bye.
(Trey)
Why you do that, man?
(Vince) Hey, man, don't
touch me like that.
[both arguing]
(Trey) Thanks for having
my back down there.
(Vince)
No problem.
Check out this email.
"Hey, V-Double@fahoomail.com,
"haven't heard from you
in a long while.
"Please email me back
so we can get together.
Love, Bunni."
[laughing]
(Trey) V, how many times you gonna
have to respond to these emails
to realize it's going to be
another $39.95?
(Vince) No, see, that's
where you're wrong.
Okay, now,
this is real.
This whole situation
is real love.
This is Mary J. Blige.
It's real love.
(Trey) Yeah, you said that
about the last one, right?
What was her name?
Uh, uh, uh, Bab-
(Vince)
Bambi.
(Trey)
She got you for $300.
(Vince) What do you think,
I'm stupid or something?
You don't think I know an
internet scam when I see one?
I'm appalled at you.
Look, you're supposed
to be my boy?
(Trey)
I'm going to go ball.
(Vince)
And it wasn't $300.
It was $375.
It's just that with the tax,
it was $300.
[man rapping]
You see me
I got my head on TV
but you don't see
Haters looking mad
'cause my swag, like, ill.
Like ill.
Hey, y'all know
who I be.
These other dudes
might do it,
but they don't
do it like me.
It's my swag.
It's my stride.
(K-3)
Hey, yo, Trey.
Yo, you got
to check my man out, man.
Man, spit for him.
(No Doubt) Hot water, corn bread.
I said,
got popped by the feds.
Now I'm seeing red.
I peed in my bed.
I must be dead.
[makes record scratching sounds]
Yo, dog.
(K-3) You know where
we going with this.
(No Doubt)
Hey.
(K-3) Do you know where
we going with this?
(No Doubt)
Hey.
(K-3) Do you know where
we going with this?
(No Doubt)
Hey.
(K-3) Do you know where
we going with this?
(No Doubt)
Hey, all right.
(K-3) Do you even see
where he going with this?
(Trey)
Most definitely.
(K-3) Man, yo, can you
drop us off at your uncle's?
We got to lay this down today, man.
(Trey)
Yeah, hop in.
(K-3)
Aw, yeah.
My man.
[bass pumping]
[thumping hip-hop music]
(Trey) Miss Vickers
and Mr. Vickers.
All right.
(Sida)
A little possessive, but...
(Keily)
Tell me about it.
(Sida)
The boy does love you.
No, it's too much rabbit.
[laughing]
[Trey whispering]
Okay, okay, okay.
Hey.
Hey, what's up?
(Keily)
Oh, hey. How are you?
(Trey) Hey, I see you
not with your other half.
[cell phone ringing]
(Keily)
Help me out here.
(Sida) Ooh, I think it's this one.
(Keily)
Hello?
I tried to answer it.
You're breaking up.
[cell phone rings]
(Sida) Oh, okay, something
else ringing over here.
(Keily)
Here.
(Sida)
The red, the red, the red.
Hello?
I really couldn't hear you.
I'm not playing.
I'm not talking
with anyone.
I'm in a store with Sida.
A clothing store.
The one that
I always go to, yes.
You hang up first.
If I hang up,
you'll get mad at me, okay?
I'm going
to my aunt's house next.
All right,
are you going to hang up?
Love you too.
Wow.
How many phones
does he need?
(Keily) He just worries
about me a little bit, okay?
(Trey)
A little?
(Keily)
He just loves me a lot
(Trey)
If it works for you.
Well, look, I'd like
to hook up with you sometime.
(Sida)
Did you not hear her?
She said
she has a boyfriend.
(Keily)
Sida.
(Sida) You said you
have a boyfriend.
That's rude.
(Keily)
She's right.
I have a boyfriend,
and that just
wouldn't be appropriate.
(Trey) Look, I'm not trying
to get married or anything.
I just thought we could
be friends or something.
Look.
Here's my number again.
No strings attached.
If you ever want
to talk to me,
just call me
on one of your cell phones.
(Sida)
Snap out of it, okay?
He is not
on Carlton's level,
not even a little bit.
(Keily) And what exactly
is Carlton's level, Sida?
(Sida) You know I'm not
a big fan of Carlton,
but he is at least
a step up from him.
Goodness gracious.
[knocking at door]
(Trey)
Hello?
Southside Barbecue.
(Katherine)
The door's open.
Come on in.
I just came
out of the shower.
(Trey)
Oh, okay.
Place looks familiar.
Been here before.
This is real nice.
I like this.
(Katherine)
Hey.
(Trey)
(Katherine)
I know you.
(Trey) Yeah, I was
just looking around
and said I delivered
food here for you before.
(Katherine)
Yeah, it's not every day
that I get a cute young man
to deliver my food for me.
(Trey)
Me?
(Katherine)
Yeah.
Have a seat.
I got your money
right over here.
(Trey)
All right.
(Katherine)
Oh, sh-
This is a mess.
Oh.
Um, you didn't see that,
did you?
(Trey)
No, not all of it.
(Katherine)
I'm so embarrassed.
(Trey)
Don't be, ma'am.
I mean,
you have a nice body.
Please don't call me ma'am.
It makes me feel old.
Just call me Kat.
Kat, you have a nice body.
Kat, right?
(Katherine)
Mm-hmm.
What are you thinking?
(Trey) I don't know.
A lot of things.
(Katherine)
Like?
(Trey)
Like, I don't know.
(Katherine) Well, what do
you want to know about me?
(Trey)
Well, I know, every year,
you let the AKKs
throw a party at your house.
That's about it.
(Katherine)
Okay, well,
I'm sure that's not
the only thing you're thinking,
so let me just let you know
that I don't make it a habit
to sleep with men
five or six years my junior
who deliver ribs
to my house.
And, yes,
I'm married.
But I'm separated,
and it's going on two years now.
And, yes,
you were incredible.
(Trey)
Are you serious?
(Katherine)
Yeah.
Do you have a girlfriend?
(Trey) Nah, nah, not really.
(Katherine) It's usually a "yes" or
"no" answer that follows that question.
(Trey)
Well, not at the moment.
She kind of occupied
at the present time, you know,
so no.
(Katherine)
Can I ask you something?
(Trey)
Sure.
(Katherine) Can you
keep this between us?
I mean, you kind of caught me
at a weak moment.
(Trey)
Come on, girl.
You got my word.
I won't tell a soul.
[record scratching]
All she had
was just a robe on, man.
Next thing you know,
I'm trying to walk
all through it.
(Vince)
You lying.
(Trey)
What you mean, lying?
(Vince)
I don't believe that.
She got naked like that?
She got a big booty?
(Trey) Dog, the booty's so big,
I didn't know what to do with it.
I was looking everywhere,
you know what I'm saying?
Let me tell you-
let me tell you something.
Hey, you know
how I like booty.
You already know.
She made me work out more.
That's why
I'm working out right now.
(man) Hey, Mack, you
can't keep ignoring
the notices we sent you.
(Mack) Look, I told you last
week that I was going to try
to apply
for a second mortgage.
(man)
You couldn't even get the loan
for a Hot Wheels.
(Trey) Hey, man, you
ain't going to come in here
and talk to my uncle
like a little kid.
(Mack) Hey, Trey,
I can handle this.
Back up.
(man)
Take the offer, man.
(Mack)
I am not going to foreclose.
I'm going to get you
that $75,000.
(man)
Talk to your uncle.
(Trey)
Get up out of here, man.
(K-3)
Listen to this.
Three, two, wick-a-wick, one.
(No Doubt) Flip-a-tick,
talk the talk
like a clock
with a hole in my sock.
I could kiss a gnat
strapped with my gat.
I hit you with the word, y'all.
Like a ninja turtle,
I talks with the po-po.
And I flow
on the low-low.
(K-3) Can you see where
he's going with that?
I mean,
can you see it?
You see that?
It's fire right there.
He's hot.
Nobody's
talking like that.
Come on.
(Vince)
(Trey)
Hey, what's up, V?
(Vince)
Hey, what's up?
(Trey)
Hey, where your dad at?
(Vince) He's in the
back in the kitchen.
You okay?
(Trey) Yeah, I just need to
ask him something, that's all.
It's nothing.
(Vince)
Uh.
What the...
See, Vick?
This is the part of the pig
that whitey will let us eat.
Know what I'm saying?
And we turn it
into a delicacy,
'cause we creative,
you know what I'm saying?
(Mr. Vickers) I don't
understand why that was done.
I am so deeply troubled.
I am so ashamed.
To do that to another
human being, that's wrong.
I'm sorry, man.
It just really hurts me
to think about it.
(Cinque)
It's all right, Vick.
It's just a small microcosm
of what they did to break us down.
(Mr. Vickers) But why would
they do that to people?
(Cinque) 'Cause your
people is wrong, Vick.
(Mr. Vickers) Yeah, but why
would they do that to everybody?
(Trey)
Excuse me.
I didn't mean
to interrupt,
but I need to talk to you,
Mr. Vickers.
(Mr. Vickers)
We'll continue this later.
(Cinque)
Yeah, you all right, Vick?
I'll holler at you.
I'm gonna be
right over here.
(Mr. Vickers)
What's up?
Well, I've been working here
for almost two years now, sir.
And I need
some more money, so...
(Mr. Vickers)
Oh, Trey...
(Trey) Think I could
get a raise, sir?
(Mr. Vickers)
I wish I could.
We're on a very strict budget here.
I just bought
a bunch of radio time.
We're pinching pennies.
(Trey) Well, I'll work
overtime, whatever it takes.
(Mr. Vickers) Trey, I cannot
afford to pay you overtime.
Son, you know
how hard it is
to run a black business
in this town?
And white people are not exactly
busting my door down
for the ribs
and the African artifacts.
It's just not making it,
all right?
I hope you understand that.
Do you?
(Trey)
Yes, sir.
I understand.
(Vince)
Mm, mm, mm.
I just love it
when you come here.
You can wash clothes for free
any time you want.
You hear me?
Hey, hey.
What's up, dog?
Where you going?
(Trey) Man, your dad
won't give me no raise.
[Vince laughing]
I could've told you
that wasn't gonna happen.
Hey, but I got
some other news, though.
Remember old girl
I was telling you about?
I've been talking to her
over the internet.
(Trey)
Yeah.
(Vince) Me and baby
about to link up.
(Trey) Man, how much
you spend so far?
(Vince)
Hey, man.
Now, you done known me
since we was kids, man.
Why you keep insulting me
with questions like that?
What me and this girl got
is real, man.
I mean, I'm offended that you
would even think otherwise.
(Trey)
How much?
(Vince) Man, I told
you what we got is real.
But it's about $700.
About, yeah,
roughly $700.
But I'm telling you, man,
what we got is real.
We about to walk down
the aisle.
We gonna two-step,
jump over the broom.
We got the reception planned.
Got ribs and chicken
for the reception.
It's gonna be
off the chain.
(Trey) Look, man, we got to
go watch the front, so come on.
(Vince)
Hey, hold on.
And it's not $700 anymore.
It's $698.50.
Mm, mm, mm.
I'm telling you.
Hey, do you want
potato salad with that?
Okay.
506 Castle Drive.
Got it.
All right,
see you in 30.
Thank you.
(Trey)
506 Castle Drive?
(Vince)
Yeah.
(Trey)
Oh, damn.
(Vince) Oh, snap,
is that- is that the-
Hold on,
I got it.
(Trey)
No, no, no, no, no.
Let me take this.
I got to go apologize
for what happened.
Don't worry about it.
(Vince)
Apologize for...
(Trey)
To go, please. To go!
506.
(Vince)
Blockin'.
(Trey) Girl, be
looking at me like that.
You know you wild.
[laughs]
Mm, mm, mm.
(Katherine)
Here.
(Trey)
What's this?
(Katherine) Just a little
something to show my appreciation.
(Trey) There's, like,
over $1,000 in here.
(Katherine)
Yeah, I know.
(Trey)
Nah, I can't take that.
(Katherine) Yes, you
can, and you will.
(Trey)
Nah, I can't take that.
I'm sorry.
I can't.
This?
No, I can't do that.
I can't do that.
I got to go.
[doorbell rings]
Oh, shit.
[whispering indistinctly]
(Katherine)
Come on.
It's just my friends.
Yeah, yeah. Yeah.
(Dedra)
Hey.
(Katherine) Um, hey,
thank you for the ribs,
and, you know,
I forgot your tip.
(Trey)
You know what?
Don't even worry
about that.
And have a good night.
And, ladies,
y'all look real nice.
Have a good night.
Good lot of food
back there.
I'll see you.
(Dedra) I know you
ain't forget his tip.
[laughing]
Ribs.
(Candace)
Kind of young, Kat.
(Katherine)
He's the delivery boy.
(Candace)
Mm-hmm.
Cute robe.
(Katherine)
I'll get the wine.
Y'all make a plate.
(Vince)
So what happened?
(Trey)
She gave me $1,000.
(Vince) Oh, she done
turned you into a trick.
(Trey)
No, that makes me the pimp.
(Vince)
No, she would be the pimp.
(Trey) No, that makes her the John.
(Vince)
So that makes you the ho.
- No.
- Yes.
(Trey)
Whatever, man.
She gave me a grand,
all right?
What you saying?
(Vince)
It's all right.
I'm just hating anyhow,
but it's cool, though,
because when Bunni gets here,
the script is gonna be flipped.
[laughing]
(Trey) I'm really happy
for you, man, for real, man.
(Vince)
Oh, no, no, no.
I'm happy.
Let me show you
what I'm doing to this room.
how I sexed this room up.
Check this out.
[smooth R&B music playing]
[giggling]
[clears throat]
That was, uh-
That was pretty cool, huh?
[humming uncomfortably]
(Trey) Man, what's with all
the white spots on everything?
(Vince)
Hm?
(Trey) Anyway, Vin,
on the real, man,
I got to jet.
I'm going to holler at you,
all right?
(Vince)
You ain't got to do all that.
(Trey)
I love you, man.
You need a sock
or something.
Damn!
[brakes squeak]
(Sida)
Oh, great.
It's the pest.
(Trey) Look, I wouldn't
say I'm the best,
but I'm pretty close to it.
How you doing, Keily?
(Keily) Good. How are you?
(Trey)
I'm doing great.
Think I could talk to you
for a minute?
(Sida) No, actually,
Keily, we got to go.
(Keily)
I got a minute.
(Sida)
Oh, you do?
(Trey)
All right.
Um, so where's the man?
(Keily)
He's at football practice.
(Trey)
Kind of figured that.
None of your cell phones
are ringing.
(Keily)
Funny.
(Trey) So you mean to tell
me, out of three phones,
you couldn't
give me a call?
(Keily) Trey, I have been with
Carlton for over six years.
And I care for him deeply,
okay?
(Trey)
Aha.
(Keily)
What?
(Trey) You never
said you loved him.
(Keily)
I do love him.
(Trey)
Are you in love with him?
(Keily) Don't you
think you're asking
some awful personal
questions here?
I got to go.
(Trey)
Wait, Keily.
Look, just give me
one chance, all right?
Can we just
meet up once?
Have sodas
or something?
(Keily)
Seriously?
You know,
Carlton would have a fit
if I did something
like that.
(Trey)
He don't have to know.
I just can't.
(Trey)
Keily.
Just once, all right?
I promise
I won't bug you anymore.
What exactly
do you want from me?
(Trey)
Well, I don't know.
Just think about it,
all right?
I'll think about it.
I got to go.
(Sida)
Are you crazy?
You know Carlton has spies
all over this place.
(Keily)
Sida, stop trippin'.
(Sida) What do you
see in him anyway?
He delivers ribs.
Oh, now,
there's a bright future.
(No Doubt) Hot water,
corn bread, I said.
Got popped by the feds.
Now I'm seeing red.
I peed in my bed.
I must be dead.
Flip-a-tick,
talk the talk
like a clock
with a hole in my sock.
(K-3)
We 'bout to get so paid.
(No Doubt)
I hit you with the word, y'all.
Like a ninja turtle.
I talk with the po-po,
but I flow
on the low-low.
(Trey) Now, when you
gonna be honest with them?
(Mack)
Trey, I build dreams.
I don't tear them down.
(Trey) Look, now, we got
three weeks left to get 75K.
(Mack) I know that. I know that.
(No Doubt)
All right, from the top, baby.
I'm coming in.
(K-3) Let's do this
bonfires right now.
(No Doubt)
Yo, dog.
Yeah.
[Mack chuckles]
(Trey)
Here, have this.
(Mack)
What's this?
Hey.
Hey, I can't take this.
Man, this is your savings.
(Trey) You need
that more than I do.
Plus, I owe you.
You my nephew, man.
You don't owe me nothing.
(Trey)
Look, Unc,
you didn't have to take me
when my dad died, all right?
But you did.
And I'm grateful
to have you in my life.
Plus, I know how important it was
for you and my dad
to keep this studio
up and running.
This studio's more than just
a place to make music.
It's a diversion
for the youth in the community.
Look, I see the big picture,
all right?
So take that.
I know it's not much.
I'm going to come up
with something.
Trey.
(Trey)
Yeah?
(Mack)
I love you, man.
(Trey)
I love you too, Unc.
Gosh, it's really slow today.
(Cinque)
Yeah.
But anyway,
like I was saying, right?
The white woman puts the change
on the counter
instead of in my hand.
Know what I'm saying?
So I say to her politely-
I wasn't rude.
I said to her politely,
I said, "That's not how
I gave you my money.
I placed my money
in your hand."
(Mrs. Vickers)
Oh, what a bitch.
(Cinque)
That's herway...
of making me feel
like I'm not human.
You got
to understand something.
White people don't see us
as equal,
which, in turn, makes us feel
unwanted in this society.
(Mr. Vickers)
No, you are wanted.
And you are accepted.
And why do white people
treat people with such disdain?
(Trey)
What's up, everybody?
(Vince)
Hey, what's up, boy?
(Trey)
What's-
Nah. Cool.
What's up?
Why you crying, Mr. Vickers?
(Carlton) I told you to
stay away from my girl.
(Vince)
Hey, man.
(Cinque)
Stop it before I break it.
(Carlton)
All right, all right, all right.
(Cinque) This is the second time I
had to remove you from the premises.
Get out.
(Carlton)
I'm leaving.
You been warned, Trey.
Stay your ass
away from Keily.
(Vince) Hey, man, I
don't know your girl,
but I'm going
to sit down with Trey,
and we gonna
come up with something
where we can work it out.
(Carlton)
Shut your ass up!
(Vince) What the hell
is wrong with him?
You hitting her?
[mouthing words]
(Katherine)
Oh, thank you so much.
I mean, look,
I'm not in love.
It's just...
this young man
is just so passionate.
(Dedra)
To get passion,
much is required.
I call it the three C's.
Comfortability,
consistency-
(Candace)
And "C" Batteries.
[laughing]
(Dedra)
And commitment.
(Katherine)
Look, you guys,
it's not even that serious.
I mean, it just feels so good
to feel wanted again.
You know what I mean?
Being wanted
and feeling wanted just,
it makes you
want to be wanted
while wanting
to want something.
You know what I'm saying?
(Katherine)
No.
(Dedra) Actually, girl,
I like them young too.
That way, you can mold them
into whatever you want them
to be, like Play-Doh.
I just hope that my sorers
can keep my business to themselves.
Why are y'all
looking at me?
I do not have
a big mouth.
I didn't tell about you
getting caught stealing.
I didn't tell her
about that.
(Dedra) Okay, why you got to
bring that up in front of her?
(K-3)
Try and be late this time.
[buzzer sounds]
Come on, man.
(K-3)
Come on.
Yo, who is it?
(K-3)
Yo, it's K-3 and-
No Doubt.
(K-3)
Yeah, how'd you know?
Man, what you guys want, man?
(K-3) Yo, I got some
fire for you, man.
(man) For two years, twice a week,
y'all talking about,
y'all got some fire for me.
And y'all
haven't delivered nothing
even remotely close to that.
Matter of fact-
Y'all, hold on right quick.
Yo, it's 97.3,
hip-hop and R&B.
Listen, I got these fools
outside of my door right now
that are trying to get me
to listen to their demo.
(No Doubt) Hey, man, he
talking about us on the radio.
(K-3)
Yeah, shh.
Yo, and if you think
I'm going to let them in,
you're absolutely crazy.
What I'm gonna do is,
I'm going to put this microphone
up to the intercom,
and we gonna see what fire
these dudes have been talking about.
K-3, can you hear me?
(K-3)
Yes, I can.
No Doubt,
you there?
(No Doubt)
Yes, sir.
(man) Now, I know you got
that little boom box out there.
Matter of fact, go ahead
and play a sample of that fire.
(No Doubt) Oh, okay. Okay.
[hip-hop music playing]
[both singing] Do you know
where we going with this?
Do you know
(man)
Now, that was some booty.
(K-3)
Man, are you kidding me, man?
That was ill, man.
Yeah, I think
I am getting sick.
[laughs]
(No Doubt)
Hold up, man.
You ain't even
give us a chance, dog.
You making us play our song
through the intercom, homes.
Hey, man, this thing needs to be
live on the air, man.
They can't even
hear the beat.
(man)
I'll tell you what.
Here's what
I'm gonna do right now.
I'm in a nice mood.
I'm gonna take some calls,
and I'm gonna find out
what the people think.
97.3, what up?
What do you think of that new
K-3/No Doubt record?
(man) Son, on the real,
son, that song, son...
that song is hot, son.
(man)
Really?
Keep playing that song, son.
(man)
Huh.
Hey, thanks for the call.
Hey, K-3,
your cousin just called.
Let's take another call.
What you think?
(woman) You are crazy
if you don't like that song.
That song was hot.
Can you tell me
where I can get it?
Is it out yet?
(man)
You can't be serious.
(No Doubt)
Yeah, boy!
Hey!
Hey, you heard 'em?
(K-3)
Yo, they feelin' it, man.
They feelin' it.
(No Doubt) Hey, man,
we got a hit, dog.
(woman)
Yo, you gotta let them in.
I want to hear
the whole song.
(No Doubt) Hey, man, open
this mother[...] door.
[hip-hop music playing]
[K-3 and No Doubt singing]
Do you know where we going with this?
Do you know
where we going with this?
(Carlton) You damn right
I had to punish him.
I just
can't have everybody
trying to come
and get with my woman.
(Keily)
You don't own me.
All you do is just treat me
like I'm a piece of property.
(Carlton)
I told you, I don't like that dude.
And what do you do?
You publicly humiliate me
by talking to him in public.
Just what were you thinking?
(Sida) Okay, I'm
gonna get out this car
if y'all
about to start trippin'.
(Carlton)
Peace.
(Sida) I'll see you
in the house, Keily.
(Keily) So I'm supposed
to check with you first
before I speak to someone?
(Carlton) All I'm saying is, why do I
have to hear it in the streets first?
(Keily)
That's probably, what,
the second time
I've even spoken to him.
Why are you
so threatened by him?
(Carlton)
Please, threatened?
Girl, he's a delivery boy.
He's beneath me
and you.
(Keily) What an incredibly
arrogant thing to say.
(Dedra)
Hey.
(Sida)
What's up, girl?
(Dedra) What's going on over there?
(Sida)
Arguing, as always.
(Dedra) I don't know why she
won't break up with that fool.
Big, old country bumpkin.
Girl, he don't know
who I am.
(Keily)
Well, you know what?
That makes two of us.
(Carlton) I wasn't
done talking to you.
(Keily)
Can I go?
(Carlton)
Look, I'm sorry, okay?
It's just that
I love you more than anything.
I can't stand the thought
of another man looking at you,
let alone talking to you.
(Keily)
Carlton, can I go?
(Carlton) Do you accept my apology?
Keily?
(Keily)
I accept your apology.
Can I go?
(Dedra)
What's wrong with y'all?
(Keily)
Nothing's wrong.
What are you all doing?
(Dedra) Well, I have
your uncle's SIM card
from his cell phone.
(Sida) You took your husband's
SIM card out his cell phone?
You know that's fowl, right?
(Dedra) Well, technically,
it's my SIM card,
'cause I bought it
and put it in his phone.
His dumb ass don't even know
what a SIM card is.
(Sida) Okay, and how
did you pull that off?
(Dedra) Well, I went
to see him play in DC.
And then after I put it on him,
he fell asleep,
and I switched
the SIM cards.
So let's see what's new
in Jason's life.
Oh, now, this one right here
looks nothing like me.
(Sida)
Nice boob job, though.
She has a natural
little teardrop shape to it.
It looks good.
Ugh.
Look at her.
She needs a wax.
(Sida) She needs a hatchet
or a weed whacker, something.
Ew, that's nasty.
[all laughing]
[all sigh]
(Keily)
Y'all are crazy.
(Dedra) Oh, I think
I know this one.
I believe he told me
it was his cousin from L.A.
Well, let's just see who that is
near her mouth, shall we?
Let's zoom in.
Bingo.
I'd recognize
those genitals anywhere.
You see that mole
shaped like a cockroach?
(Sida)
Unfortunately.
(Dedra)
Yeah, yeah.
That's your uncle's
scrotum sac, baby, mm-hmm.
And you see
that angle?
He must've
taken that one himself.
(Sida) Yeah, yeah, that's
definitely a POV shot.
(Dedra)
Mm-hmm.
(Sida)
Definitely.
(Keily) Okay, Aunty, look,
I think you've had enough.
You're getting
a little upset here,
so why don't we
just close it?
(Dedra) Upset? Who's getting upset?
Dedra is fine.
Dedra is not upset, okay?
I am fine.
I am just getting started.
I am not upset.
Oh, okay, now,
this one is upsetting.
(Sida)
Why?
(Dedra)
'Cause that's a girl-rilla.
Oh, I can't believe
I slept after that.
Oh, my God,
call the clinic.
(Cinque)
Trey.
Hey, Trey.
(Trey) What? I'm in the back.
This order been sitting out here
for about 25 minutes.
Come on, son.
(Trey)
Where is it?
(Cinque)
Right there.
(Trey)
Where's it going?
(Cinque)
North side.
I can't see that
without my glasses.
There you go.
North side,
506 Castle.
(Trey)
Oh, my God.
(Cinque)
Uh!
Walk in blackness,
my brother.
Power to the people.
[speaks foreign language]
Stay strong,
black man.
[K-3 and No Doubt singing on radio]
(DJ)
97.3 hip-hop and R&B.
Now, that's
the new K-3 with No Doubt,
song number 2
on the top 9 at 9:00.
Now, as y'all know...
[cell phone playing music]
(Trey)
Hello?
Uncle Mack.
Hey, man, guess who
I just heard on the radio.
(Mack)
K-3 and No Doubt.
(Trey)
You knew?
(Mack)
Yeah, I knew.
I just mixed that song
this morning.
They've been playing it
on the radio all day.
They must've went down
to the radio station or something.
(Trey) Well, why you
don't sound too happy?
(Mack)
No, I'm happy for them.
You know, people giving them
all kind of love, you know?
Ain't nobody
flowing me no love.
(Trey)
So what, have you talked to them?
(Mack)
Yeah, you know, I called them.
I left a message.
They ain't called me back.
I guess they busy,
you know?
(Trey)
Really?
(Mack)
Yep.
(Trey) Well, look,
I'm going to go ahead
and give them a call,
all right?
(Mack)
Hey, no, don't do that.
(Trey)
Why?
(Mack) 'Cause you can't
force people to give you love.
You know
what I'm saying?
(Trey) But, Unc, you bankroll
damn near half their studio time.
(Mack)
I ain't trippin' on that.
(Trey)
I'm gone.
I gotta go, man.
Hey, K-3, No Doubt.
What's up?
This is Trey.
Hey, man,
congrats on the record, man.
I really um...
I dig it.
Um, give me a call
when y'all get this message.
I really appreciate it.
All right.
[knocking on door]
(Katherine) I didn't think
you were ever gonna get here.
[Trey sighs]
[moaning and giggling]
[phone ringing]
(Katherine) I know you're not
about to answer that phone.
(Trey)
Hello?
(Keily)
Trey?
(Trey)
Who is it?
(Keily)
It's Keily.
(Trey)
Hey, how you doing?
(Keily) Did I catch
you at a bad time?
(Trey)
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Is it okay if I call you back
at this number?
(Keily)
Yeah, sure.
Okay, I'll call you back.
(Keily)
All right, bye-bye.
(Trey)
Bye.
Uh...
Yeah.
(Katherine) I can't believe
you just did that, Trey.
(Trey) What?
It was an important call.
(Katherine)
It was a girl's voice.
Look, I'm not stupid,
all right?
If there's anything
that I don't like, it's liars.
(Trey)
Look, nobody lying to you.
I told you I had to take
an important call.
It was an important call.
If it was a girl that called,
she took the call.
This ain't-
it was-
It was important.
I don't make
the lie to you.
What you talking about?
(Katherine)
I think you need to go.
(Trey)
I need to go?
(Katherine)
Yeah, I think you do.
Be gone.
(Trey)
All right, Katherine.
[phone rings]
(Keily)
Hi, Trey.
(Trey) Look, Keily, I want to
see you face-to-face, all right?
If that's
all right with you.
At least just give me
five minutes.
[phone beeping]
Hey, look, look, look.
Before you say no, all right,
just hold on one second, okay?
Hold on.
[phone beeps]
Yes?
(Katherine)
Come back over here, Trey.
(Trey)
For what, Katherine, huh?
(Katherine)
For me.