All those who wish to accept
Jesus Christ as their Lord and Savior,
Please, come to the railing
and be comforted.
The Lord be with you.
...Like it's the most natural thing
in the world. Nobody looks at me funny.
Nobody even gives it a second thought.
I mean, I have this dream all the time.
There's never any sense
of sin or shame in it.
Don't you just love being naked?
Uh, look, I know we just met
and everything
but would you like to go out on a date
with me on Saturday night,
Norma Jean?.
My uncle,
Ted Lewis is opening a show...
The Ted Lewis?.
Yeah.
Ted Lewis is your uncle!?.
Oh wow! God, Eddie, I'd love to go!
Really?.
Yeah! Oh, my heart is beating so fast.
Can you feel it?.
God!
It's like having
our own private swimming pool.
And to think they pay you for this.
Yep. Eighty dollars a week just to sit
in that life guard's tower over there.
The best part, by far,
is that Miss Emmeline Snively's
Blue Book
Modeling Agency is located right
in the lobby.
Well, I'll tell you a secret,
Mr. Edward Jordon.
I don't intend to be
a bathing suit model
for too much longer.
In fact, a year from now,
I'm going to be a very famous actress.
Sure, sure, sure.
I mean, bigger than Betty Grable
and Jean Harlow put together.
I'm going to be so damn famous, Eddie,
nobody'll be able to touch me.
Of course,
my husband has always discouraged me.
He says
there are a thousand beautiful girls
in Hollywood who can act
and they're all looking for work.
Uh, where is your uh...
husband, Norma Jean?.
Over seas - where he belongs.
He was recalled to duty in the Pacific.
Well, he's okay and all but
I don't really feel anything for him.
I suppose I'll have to do something
about it one of these days.
God,
I want this feeling to last forever.
Is everybody happy?.!
Eddie, that's Errol Flynn!
Look, over there! He's standing up.
Oh, it is...
It's really him.
He is so dreamy.
Let me borrow your pen
for a sec, will ya?.
Oh my, that's gotta be Orson Welles!
Where?.
Over there, by the exit.
That's not Orson Welles.
Eddie, I am having a wonderful time.
And I just love your uncle.
He reminds me of you.
He's so commanding.
He's so sexy!
Well, he's a great entertainer, sure.
But sexy?.
The man's fifty-eight years old.
You know how you said
you'd introduce me?.
Yeah. The next time he's in the area,
we'll go out on the town.
We'll make an evening of it.
Well, why don't we go back stage
and talk to him after the show?.
I just wanna shake his hand.
I wanna finally meet a real star, Eddie
I don't know, Norma Jean.
I mean, there's usually
a lot of commotion back there.
A lot of weird people hangin' around -
it's not the best way
to get to know someone.
Do I embarrassyou, Eddie?.
God, no. No.
Mr. Lewis, I am so thrilled.
You are my favorite enter-
tainer of all time!
And I just wanted to tell you how much
I admire you for dancing
with a negro in your act.
I don't know how long you're gonna be
in town, Uncle Ted. But,
I'm in a play at the Cast Theatre.
It's " A wake and Sing,"
by Clifford Odets?.
It's a greatplay. It's very political.
Actually, I got the second lead
and I was wondering
if maybe you could...
Sure, Eddie. Sure.
If I have a chance, I'll stop by.
Here you go, kid.
It can be real tough
starting out in show bizz.
Hell, I aughta know.
That's not necessary.
Ah, come on.
A big town, a gorgeous girl...
You need a little dough
to have a good time.
Am I right, huh?.
Am I right, boychick?.
There.
Is everybody happy?.
You know what, Eddie?.
I got my final divorce papers
in the mail today.
I am officially a free woman!
Free, white and twenty-one!
I can't help myself --
I feel like celebrating.
Yeah, well... And
then we both got somethin' to celebrate
You're pregnant?.
Nope. I have just signed a seven year
optional contract
with Twentieth Century Fox!
When were you gonna tell me?.
At dinner. Over a bottle of champagne.
It's up for renewal every six months
at their discretion.
Seventy-five dollars a week to start
with but then it keeps climbing, right,
every time they renew.
So, if they keep me around
for the full seven years
then I'm gonna get somethin'
like fifteen hundred a week.
I mean, Jesus, Can you imagine?.
You'll be able to say you knew me when.
Wow, Eddie. That's great.
That's really terrific.
Of course the minute I signed
that made me eligible to join
the Screen Actor's Guild,
So now I have my SAG card, too.
And I'm already up for my first part.
Well, I mean, it's not much of a part,
it's just two lines.
But it's a Dana Andrews movie
and I think it could be...
Well, fuck your contract, Eddie!
Fuck your contract, fuck your SAG card,
fuck Dana Andrews and fuck you, too!
What the hell is the matter with you?.
Let me tell you something.
I don't have a guild card
and I don't have a studio contract
but I know
there's only one way to get them - -
I'm gonna be in the goddamn movies
if I have to fuck Bela Lugosi
to get there!
You know,
you always talk about being an actress
but you never done
a goddamn thing about it.
You wanna be an actress?. Okay, so act!
It's work, Norma Jean.
Get into an acting class,
do your scene work,
Iearn the craft,
work your way up like I did!
Oh, you think girls get movie contracts
because somebody respects their talent,
Eddie?.
I'll tell you
how girls get movie contracts,
they fuck the right people, that's how.
And that's exactly what I'm gonna do.
And I'm gonna be rich and famous
and powerful and you'll be able to say
you knew me when.
Oh, God, Eddie,
I really screwed it up, huh?.
I said some pretty awful things.
God, I'm sorry.
I'm so upset I can't sleep.
You're not really mad at me, are you?.
I don't think
I could take it if you were.
Say you're not mad at me... Eddie?.
I'm not... really mad at you.
It...It's just that sometimes you're...
you're like, you're like...
What am I like?.
I don't know.
You're like two different people.
Both of us love you.
Don't just Bitch me, Eddie.
Please, don't. Don't.
I won't. I'm not. I uh...
I love you.
Alright, Ladies.
Brown and Bigelow have asked us to find
a fresh face for their 1947 calendar.
They want a girl who embodies
the spirit of the post-war woman.
No professional modeling
experience necessary.
The job pays 250 dollars.
Your name, please.
I'm Adrian Wallingford.
And no, I've neverdone any former
modeling before,
but I do have work experience.
Really?.
That's right.
I was electrical supervisor at Locheed,
on the Liberator Bomber series.
My unit made...
Hi. Oh, I hope I ' m not late.
I ' m Norma Jean Dougherty.
From the the Blue Book Modeling Agency?.
I was so afraid I was going to be late.
Could you...
Would...Would you mind zipping me up,
please?.
Sure.
Thanks. You're sweet.
Would you mind standing under
the light, Miss...
Dougherty. Norma Jean Dougherty. Sure.
Is this how you want me?.
Mr. Jasgur usually lets us listen to
Jack Benny when we work Sundays.
Great, isn't he?.
We presentthe Jack Benny show
starring Barry Livingston,
Dennis Day Rodchester, and your host...
The one and only... Mr. Jack Benny!
Oh, look at that.
Oh, yes. Oh, it's a beauty.
Gladys?. Gladys?. Honey?.
You'll find another job real soon.
I hear
they're hiring neg cutters over at PKO.
Leave me alone!!!
Jesus loves me, this I know,
'cause the Bible tells me so.
Norma Jean?. Norma Jean?.
Look at me for a second.
Your mama's sick, honey.
She's going to have to stay
in the hospital a little while.
So how's about you come
and live with Doc and me?.
Juust till she's better.
Why can't I go live with my daddy?.
Do you know about your daddy,
Norma Jean?.
Uh-huh. I have his picture.
His name's Stanely.
Stanely Gifford, and he lives in dairy.
Ma says
he's just about the handsomest man
she's ever seen in her life.
Ma says if you squint your eyes,
you'd swear he was Clark Gable.
And you know that your daddy's very,
very busy right now, don't you?.
Why doesn't he every come to see me?.
He would't have to bring me candy
or toys or anything.
Just come say hello.
Come on now, little lady.
We're gonna have a good ol' time.
Just you and me and Gracie.
Come on. Up!
What do you say
we go pick up your things?.
And then,
what does Harlow say to Ben Lyon?.
She says,
"I wanna be free, be gay, have fun!
Life's short,
but I want to live when I'm alive."
And "Dinner at Eight."
What does she say in "Dinner at Eight?. "
Um, to Marie Dresser?.
Dress -- ler.
She says, "Do you know
machinery's going to take the place
of every profession?. "
And then, what does Marie Dressler say?.
"Oh, my dear, that is something
you need never worry about. "
Oh, that is so good. That is perfect!
Just perfect!
Baby, your mama's here.
Can you say hello?.
Gladys?.
Alright, here we go.
Oh, oh...Oh, my God.
Easy, Gladys. That's alright.
It's alright. It'll be alright.
Now,
we'll just set you down right there.
Oh, my back.
It's okay. It's okay.
Isn't she pretty, Gladys?.
Tell your mama what'ch you're gonna be
when you're all grown up.
Say, "A movie star, baby."
Tell her you're gonna be a movie star.
Gonna be our own Norma Jean Swanson.
Or maybe we'll call you
Norma Jean Stanwick!
How'd that be?.
Let's face it girls.
That wonderful guy in your house
and in mine is building your happiness
and the opportunities that
will come to your children.
Split-level homes may be in style,
but there is simply no roomfor split-
level thinking.
So when my Jimcomes home
from a hard day at the office,
our Family Room
brings us closer together...
Is there more?.
What was your name again, Miss?.
Dougherty. Norma Jean Dougherty.
And who sent you to us, Miss Dougherty?.
The Blue Book Modeling Agency.
Have you ever auditioned
for radio work before?.
No. Not before. No, never. No.
Well, Miss Dougherty,
you are to go back to
the Blue Book Modeling Agency
and tell them they should send you out
for print ads, and print ads only.
Under no circumstances
should they put you up for any job
that entails reading, speaking,
moving or anything
that might vaguely be construded
as acting because you do not have even
the slightest aptitude for it.
What?.
Blonde hair photographs better.
It can be made to look light, medium,
or dark just by controlling the light.
That's why my biggest demand is
for blondes.
If you wanna go places, honey,
you've got to bleach.
But Emmeline, it won't look natural.
What's so great about natural?.
The good Lord spreads it around, child.
You've already lost the hair lottery.
It's going to look gorgeous.
You'll see.
You'll feel like a different person.
You know,
some women really look better blonde.
There. Now, you just sit there
and relax for a few minutes, okay?.
And I'll...
Would you like something to drink maybe
Sure.
I've got some Coke,
or some Tasty Oragne.
You should work at a hospital.
Doc's a funny name for a cowboy.
Come on, little lady, let's ride!
Now, this is the way
the gentleman rides:
gallop, gallop, gallop, gallop!
And this is the way the lady rides:
trot, trot, trot, trot,
trot, trot, trot!
And this is the way the farmer rides:
gallop-deloy, gallop-deloy.
Oh! Come on, honey,
give your old Doc a kiiisssss!
My God, you're pretty.
No.
Aw, Gracie, honey, we were just playin'
Norma Jean, this is Mrs. Dewey.
She's very nice,
I think you're really gonna like her.
But, I'm not an orphan.
Hello, dear.
I...I think it's for the best.
Just for a little while.
Just till Doc
and me can work things out.
Come inside, Norma Jean...
I don't belong here!
Meet the other girls!
Let go of me!
Don't leave me! No! Grace!
Aunt Grace! Aunt... Ow!
Hello?.
May I speak to Stanley Gifford, please?.
Who's calling?.
This is Miss Norma Jean Baker,
his daughter.
Um...Gladys Baker's girl.
Uh...just a moment.
He doesn't want to speak to you.
He says if you have any questions
you should call his lawyer
in Los Angeles.
I'll give you the number.
Do you have a pencil?.
Bless you! Blesssss you!
I'm Mary Louise Gifford, you...
Your father's wife, your stepmother.
I've travelled all the way
from Hemet to beg you --
your father's in the hospital.
He's dying.
His last wish was to see his daughter
just one time before he meets his maker
Tell him to call my lawyer.
Do you have a pencil?.
Absolutely perfect!
You look like a whole new woman!
Hey, Eddie! Eddie,
take it easy over there!
Somebody help him!
The two of you dancing together,
you looked like some kind of
burlesque skit!
I'm not seeing him because of
the way he looks, Eddie.
Yeah, no kidding!
So, who the hell is he?.
Johnny Hyde.
He's a very influential agent.
In fact, he's Vice President of
the William Morris Agency.
Yeah, I've heard of him.
Johnny's the one
who discovered Lana Turner.
He also repressents Bob Hope
and Rita Hayworth
Not to mention my Uncle Ted.
That's right, I didn't know
if you knew that.
Ted's the one who introduced us.
You have been seeing Uncle Ted!?.
Well, sure. When he's in town.
Why are you getting so upset?.
Why?. Why?.
Because he's married, that's why!
To my aunt! And I'm gonna kill him!
Listen, Eddie,
I don't give a fuck about your uncle.
But if he wants to help me out
and all he wants in exchange is for me
to spend some time with him,
and to be nice to him.
How nice?. Huh?.
Eddie.
You used Uncle Ted
to get to Johnny Hyde.
Oh, who are you to talk?.
Are you trying to tell me
you didn't use your uncle to help you
get your SAG card
and your studio contract?.
Oh, yeah, sure...
He mighta made a couple calls for me.
Yeah,
but I didn't have to sleep with him!
Oh, and I did.
So big deal.
Johnny Hyde is going to be
the best thing
that ever happened to mein this town.
I mean, after you. Eddie...
What we have is real.
You know you're the only one I love.
Johnny, I can't believe
I just saw Eleanor Powell
and Loretta Young!
I'm having lunch
next to the most famous stars
in Hollywood!
Well, baby, you're gonna be bigger
than all of 'em put together.
Ah, thank you.
Whoa-whoa-whoa! Mmmm.
Who's that?.
The goyish-looking one is Darryl Zanuck
he's chief of production at Fox.
Started off as a writer
at Warner Brothers,
used to write Rin Tin Tin movies.
And the Greek guy sitting
next to him, that's Spyros Skouras.
He's out here from New York.
He's the chairman of the Board at Fox.
So, this guy grew up
in a little village in Greece,
his family raised sheep
and now he's Zanuck's boss.
So what we have hear
is a guy who used write
for a German Shepherd sucking up
to a guy who used to be a shepherd.
See, everybody's beholden
to somebody else.
Don't ever forget that.
Can I meet them?.
You listen to me.
Right now, you're the mystery woman.
You see, everybody in this room
is dying to know who you are.
And I want to keep it exactly like that
So just trust me.
I do. You know I trust you, Johnny.
You're the finest man I ever met.
Well...I have ulterior motives.
So do I.
What are those?.
Nembutals.
Can't seem to get to sleep
without them anymore.
And these are Benzedrine.
One to go up and one to go down.
I hope your doctor knows
what he's doin'.
That stuff's really dangerous.
Actually, your uncle sends them to me.
You're crazy! You wanna kill yourself?.
I know what I'm doing,
and I know exactly what I need.
You're just gonna
have to take me the way I am, Eddie.
Take me the way I am
or don't take me at all.
Most of the gals who pose
for us are actresses or models.
Usually the don't like to give
their real name.
So you can make up any name you like.
How about Margaret Tuman?.
Or what about Judy Garland?.
Oh, honey, I could tell you stories,
believe me.
Okay, Norma Jean. Get ready.
Great. Mmm, good.
Very good.
Okay, here we go.
Get in position. Yes. Oohhh.
I like that. Oh, beautiful.
Right in the camera.
And...
Yeah.
Nice.
This girl's gonna be a major star,
Darryl.
Just look at these fairways, will you?.
Like velvet and right
in the middle of the desert.
Hillcrest is a goat track compared
to this place.
I'll tell you something,
she has real flesh appeal.
Oh, yeah?.
I promise you,
you haven't seen anything
like this since Harlow.
Harlow was never Miss September.
Yeah but...
Has she got any film on her?.
Not until you authorize the screen test
Eh. Will you look at that!
On in one and then I three putt!
Hmmm. Daryll, I understand that
Henry Hathaway needs more prep time
on "Northside 777."
Actually I could call Jimmy Stewart
and get him to agree to
a two week delay.
It won't cost you a nickel.
Alriught, Johnny.
Shoot your screen test --
black and white.
Color.
Deal.
Johnny?. They called me at Hillcrest.
I came as soon as I heard...Johnny?.
I'd be lost without you, Johnny.
You have to get better.
You have to.
Besides, I know what you need.
What?.
This.
Oh. Come here.
Johnny?.
Oh, oh, oh, oh...
I've fallen for her, Mozelle.
Oh, Johnny,
you've fallen for every blonde starlet
you've ever represented, including me.
But you've never made a fool
of yourself like this before.
The entire Morris office
is talking about it.
Abe Lastfogel says
you act like she's your only client!
So, is this going to be
some kind of ongoing thing?.
I'm sorry, Mozelle.
I love her. I want to marry her.
Well, maybe she'll let you.
She's ambitious enough.
But she doesn't love you, Johnny.
I don't care.
Then you deserve each-other!
She's a bimbo, John.
She's a one-line telephone operator...
She's a walk-away funny waitress.
Come on, Darryl,
you've been wrong before.
Who hasn't?.
She's a star.
From the neck down she's a star,
but the girl has no chin to speak of.
She's got a nose like a baked potato.
Let's have a blade.
After this, we redefine the chin,
you'll hardly recognize yourself.
All contract players
at Twentieth Century Fox
are required to study
at the actor's lab Monday,
Wednesday and Friday mornings.
You'll need a singing coach.
You'll be paid
seventy-five dollars per week.
I know. I know.
Then let's start with your name.
"Norma Jean Dougherty"
is not a movie star name,
and that is the sad fact of it...
You remind me of someone.
Ever hear of Marilyn Miller?.
No.
She was a great musical comedy star
on Broadway in the 20's.
Funny...Sexy as hell.
God, I was crazy about her.
Marilyn Dougherty?.
What do you like?.
Any-one you particularly admire?.
How about Lincoln?.
Too many "lins."
Besides it should be a literative.
Maybe we should stay
with American Presidents...
Marilyn Madison?.
Mmmmm, no.
"Marilyn Monroe."
Has a nice round tone to it.
What do you think?.
Norma Jean?.
Who?.
Then long live Marilyn Monroe!
You never really loved me.
You just thought it would be fun
to be in love with me, that's all.
It's true... Torvald.
Um, when I lived at home with Papa,
he always told me
what he thought about everything.
So I never had any ideas of my own.
Oh, dear. No. No, no, no, no, no.
What comes next?. Um...
You never really loved me Orville...
Oh, I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to...I'm...I'm...
I don't belong here. I'm...I'm sorry.
You okay, Norma Jean?.
Don't call me that. I'm Marilyn.
Look, it's alright.
Everybody's gone, you can come out now.
Oh, god, I was hathetic out there.
Everybody else has talent,
it's easy for them.
Oh, you're wrong, okay?.
It's not easy for anybody.
But, they can all get up there
and do it, Eddie.
They can all get up there and perform,
same as you can.
I'll never be an actress.
No, listen.
All you need is some coaching.
Okay?. Every time you perform
you're gonna improve.
I'll work with you.
We can rehearse together.
We'll do scenes together.
You're great!
You're gonna be great.
Promise?.
Guarantee it.
Mmmm. Hey! I bet Johnny knows
all the best coaches in town!
Diction! Diction! Diction!
You speak with your mouth closed!
I-did-not-want-to-pet-the-dear-soft-cat
I didn't want to pet the quick...
I ' m sorr--
Oh, it's not it, is it?.
You have to know your lines backwards
and forwards
so you can throw away the words
and speak the soul!
If you arrive on the set unprepared,
you are guaranteed to fail!
And if you fail, I will be crucified.
I'm sorry, Natasha.
I am trying to love you, but sometimes
you make it so difficult.
You don't have to love me, Natasha.
Just teach me.
When you left you broke my heart.
Because I never thought we'd part.
Every hour in the day,
you will hear me say,
"Baby won't you please come home?. "
Your vocal range is tiny,
your volume is small
and your phrasing is...is trite.
Altogether it's pretty terrible.
But not hopeless.
Is isn't?.
No. You can... You can carry a tune.
Not...
not very far but you can carry one.
And the sound engineers can bring up
your volume when you record.
And you do manage to create
the illusion that
you actually know how to sing.
I do?.
Yes. Uh...
So, let's take the last verse again.
Try and slow it down a little bit,
alright?.
Play with the rhythms.
Like this...Uh...
"Every hour in the day,
you will hear me say Baaaabeeee,
won't you pul-eeze come hommmmme?. "
It's...it's uh...It's called phrasing.
Have some fun with it Alright?.
Got it?.
"When you left you broke my he-art.
Because I never thought we'd part.
Every hour in the day,
you will hear me say...Baby! "
Big finish now.
"Won't you pleeease...come..."
You um...
You move well.
This is the allegro vivace.
Can you hear it?.
It comes very gently, but it builds...
and it builds...
Good morning.
Hi.
Well, how was the concert?.
Inspiring.
I waited up all night for you.
Oh, no, Johnny. You need your rest.
I'll get my rest when I'm dead,
which is gonna be sooner rather
than later. You know that, Marilyn.
I don't want to hear that kinda talk,
I won't listen!
How can yoiu be so cruel?.
Becuaes you let me.
I'm going upstairs. You coming?.
Marry me, baby. I'm crazzy about you.
I know you are, Johnny.
I wish I could feel
the same way about you.
I mean, I love you,
but I've never been in love with you.
I never said I was.
Yeah, but millions of women marry men
they're not in love with.
Millions?. Really?.
I had no idea.
Is that just counting L.A.?.
No, don't joke with me, Marilyn.
Now marriage is based
on a lot of other things,
you know, it can be based
on mutual repspect, trust.
That wouldn't be fair to you, Johnny
Besides, I'd be even more of a joke
than I am right now.
Good night, Johnny.
Good night.
Ah, feeling better, my dear?.
Sure. Just like the English Ch...
Oh, no. Not again!
Cut!
I'm sorry.
Alright, we'll try it again after lunch
After lunch everybody!
Ah, thank you, dear.
Miss Davis, would you mind
if I got some publicity stills
before lunch?.
Not at all.
Um, Miss Davis?.
I just wanted to say that
I think I'm screwing up out ofnerves -
working with you and all.
I uh, mean I've seen all of your movies
and I think you're such a talent.
I mean, I must have seen
"Now Voyager" at least ten times.
And when I was a kid I...
I remember going with
my Aunt Grace to see "Jezebel."
I musta seen that movie a dozen times,
and afterwards I 'd go home
and I 'd do all of your monologues.
I mean, not as well as you did them,
of course, but...
I mean,
I knew all of your lines by heart.
What I mean to say is,
it's just an honor
to be on the same set with you.
Thank you, dear.
Now get the fuck out of my shot.
I don't know where I ever got the idea
I could turn you into an actress.
You don't have it.
You'll never have it.
Who the hell was I kidding?.
You know,
I've mae up hundreds of actresses
but I've never experienced
a metamorphosis quite like yours.
I gotta tell you,
I get goose bumps every time.
Go get 'em, kid.
Gentlemen,
in just a few moments Miss Baxter
will be available
for photo-graphs outside the...
Hey, what's the name
of the chest that just walked in?.
Now, listen to me, Darryl.
I want you to consider using her
for "Blondes." I hear she sings.
Sings?. She barely speaks.
No, we've decided to go
with an established musical performer.
What?. Opposite Jane Russel?.
She ain't exactly Ethel Merman, y'know.
Skouras,
this girl's talent is...slight.
Then how come she gets four thousand
fan letters a week?.
That's more than Darnell
and Hayward together.
How come she's on the screen
for two minutes,
the audience stages a riot
in te theatre?.
And how come we put on
a test screening of "All About Eve,"
she doesn't even get a screen credit --
we get three hundred comment cards back
one hundred and fifty of
them wanted to know who is the blonde
with George Sanders.
Tell me, how come?.
Sweetheart?. Darling?.
Sweetheart, over here.
No, no. Over here. Come sit next to me.
Don't do this.
Take a walk, kid. Amscray!
Yes, sir. Right away.
Oh, you look magnificent this evening.
Thank you.
Doll, do you have a picture comin' up?.
Why, I don't know.
You'll have to ask Mr. Skouras here.
How about a big smile?.
Well, I mean, I think
it's time for us to renegotiate.
Yeah, well, Russel's getting a $ 100,000
and we're still capped off
at five hundred a week.
Yeah, but Jane Russel's
a well known star
with an established track record.
Well, maybe so,
but the name of the picture is
"Gentlemen prefer Blondes"
and she is definitely not the blonde.
So, we want a large dressing room with
Donna, get Dr. Prinzmetal...
What was that?.
Hey, what's going on?.
Johnny?. Johnny?.
Oh, Johnny.
Johnny, Johnny, please wake up. Please.
Told you she was a lousy actress.
I want you to go to his house,
round up all her slutty clothes,
dump 'em in the backyard
and light a match.
Then call someone
and have all the locks changed.
But first, get her outta here,
I don't care if you have to drag her.
We're just like a little family now.
Aren't we, Natasha?.
But what if I don't want it to be over.
I'm in love with you, Fred.
You cry too easily.
It's because your brain isn't developed
Compared to your bosom, it's embryonic.
What does that mean?.
Look it up!
You mind is...is inert.
You never think about anything.
You just float through life
on that pair of waterwings.
You would be a terrible example
for my children.
It wouldn't be right for them
to be raised by a woman like you.
But you're the only man I've ever loved
Well, Marilyn,
given your extensive history,
I'm sorry to heart that.
Was I supposed to love you?.
A man can't love a woman
he feels no respect for!
Freddy!
You couldn't handle a family
if you had one.
And raise children?. Forget it!
You can barely drag your ass out of bed
and make it to the set before noon.
Shut up.
What makes you think you're fit
to be any-body's mother?.
Shut up! Shut up! Shut up! Shut up!
No man will ever love me, Johnny.
You're wrong, kid.
Once you learn to harness your power,
every man in the world will adore you
Just not the ones
who know you personally.
Marilyn?. Marilyn?. Marilyn?. Marilyn?.
Marilyn?. Marilyn?. Over here.
Marilyn?. Marilyn?. Marilyn?.
Marilyn?. Marilyn?.
Marilyn?. Marilyn!?. Marilyn!?.
Marilyn?. What have you done?.
Oh, you foolish, foolish girl!
Oh, I am far too old for this.
I guess that's why she really needs
someone like I to educate her.
They are coarsening you.
They are making you into a buffoon!
It repudiates all the fine work
we have done together.
It's a famous play, Natasha.
Carol Channing originated
the role on Broadway.
Lorelei Lee is a great part.
Medea is a great part!
Lorelei Lee is a vacuous moron!
You are an actress!
You should be playing Gretchen
in "Faustus."
You should be playing Portia.
You should be playing Ophelia...
No, I refuse to set foot on the lot.
I will not be party to this profanity!
Oh, please. Please, Natasha.
Please don't speak that way.
I do. I do want to play
those roles someday, and Grushenka, too
Gru-shenka.
Accent on the first syllable, please.
I have to be more established first.
I'm so scared.
You don't know how scared I am.
I have these voices in my head
and some days
I feel like I'm about to explode.
I can't do it without you.
I need you to be there.
I'll do anything you want.
Just tell me.
Tell me what you want me to do.
Don't you know that a man being rich
is like a girl being pretty?.
You might not want to marry a girl
just because she was pretty,
but my goodness, doesn't it help?.
And if your daughter wanted to marry
a poor man...
Cut!!!
What?.
No, no, no. You don't yell cut
because you are not the director.
She botched the line.
And do not take that tone with me,
Mr. Hawks, I studied with Reinhardt!
Really?. Well you must of flunked.
I want you off my set
and don't come back.
Howard, if she isn't here,
then neither am I.
You know,
maybe that's not such a bad idea.
I know a hundred actresses
who could play this part.
Every single one of
them would shoe up on time,
know her lines and sing, dance and
act a damn sight better than you can.
Now look what you have done.
Well, there are no broken bones,
but she needs to stay off her feet
for several days.
How many days?.
Don't... Don't it hurts.
Can you do something?.
I can give her something that' ll help,
sure.
Oh, please. Please.
So where is she?. It's eight thirty.
Marilyn sometimes runs
a little late, Joe.
Two hours!?.
It takes a lot of work to look like
Marilyn Monroe --
even if you are Marilyn Monroe.
And speak of the devil!
You look terrific, honey.
Thank you.
Say hello to Joe DiMaggio.
How do you do, Mr. DiMaggio?.
It's always a pleasure to meet one of
David's friends.
He's the best publicist in town.
Well...
So, are yoou in show business, too?.
Marilyn, you're kidding?.
He's only the greatest baseball player
since the Babe.
Oh...Who's the Babe?.
What a kidder.
Huh. Joe?.
Uh...Gee, Sil...Look at the time.
Um...You know, we're gonna leave you
two kids alone.
Get acquainted, okay?.
And uh, don't worry about the check,
alright?.
It's all taken care of.
Uh, the Veal Marsala's great,
by the way. Enjoy!
Cheers.
Oh, this guy's elec-trifying.
Does he speak?.
I'm afraid I don't know
very much about baseball.
Well, you wear baggy pants,
chew tobacco and hit a ball
with a stick, okay?.
Marry me.
I'll teach you all about it.
You just met her three minutes ago,
you moron.
Why, Mr. DiMaggio,
I've only just met you.
Well, in that case,
have dinner with me tomorrow night.
Well, why don't we start
with dinner tonight, Joe?.
Surely you cannot be serious
about this person.
I am certain he has never read a book
in his entire life!
Joe is very sweet, Natasha.
He makes me feel safe.
He takes care of me.
And he's very good with his hands.
I take care of you!
Natasha...sometimes you sound just like
a jealous boyfriend.
Mrs. DiMaggio, where will you live?.
Anywhere my husband wants.
Marriage is my main career now.
Ohh-ho-ho. Are you planning a family?.
Of course. Manhood means many things
but womenhood means only one.
I'd love to have six children,
God willing.
I won't let you ruin us, Marilyn!
You can't do this!
Will you keep house for your husband?.
She's a movie star!
I'm looking forward to it.
I'm learning how to cook all of
Joe's favorite foods,
Iike steak and lasagna. Right?.
No! No! No! No! No! Noooo!
Well, I can see
you have a real aptitude for this.
You're a regular Mama Leone.
Cannot wait to watch you scrub
the toilet bowl.
Oh, will you lookit fuckin' Woodling?.
He's dumb as an Irish Setter!
He can catch a ball
like a frog zappin' a fly,
after he got it,
he don't know what to do with it.
Rookie's Lefty.
Are you crazy?.
We're tryin' to watch a ball game here!
Hey! Hey!
Here comes the Neanderthal.
Hey Joe, you gotta see this!
Rizzuto just took
a line drive to the nuts!
What's wrong, Marilyn?.
What could possibly be wrong?.
You are burying us alive,
that's what's wrong! We are cooped up
in this house all day watching
"Hopalong Cassidy"
and "Father Knows Best."
You don't even talk to us!
All you care about is hanging out
with your dimwit pals,
sitting around burping and farting
and scratching their balls!
Are you sure you're okay?.
Of course we're not okay, you blockhead
We need some room to breath!
We need to work!
We need to feel the crowds and the fans
and we need to be in a city
with a pulse!
I'm fine.
Okay. Good. Listen, uh,
just forget about the lasagna.
Just make some spaghetti, okay?.
The fellahs are hungry.
Lunch is served!
Alright. Marilyn, Tom... All set?.
Now, darling Marilyn,
when you get to the...
What you call it?. Crating...
Watch it with your heel. Alright?.
And roll sound!
Rolling!
Mark it.
And...action!
You know... The sense of being in love.
That's a very interesting point of view.
Oh, do you feel the breeze
from the subway?.
Oh...
Marilyn! Marilyn!
Billy?. Billy?.
What is it?.
Um, I don't know... The...
The panties are really sheer.
Even up on the crane I could still see
the dark pubes.
Jesus.
Marjorie. Marjorie?. Please.
Eh, could we put another pair
of panties over those panties?.
Thank you.
In the space of a single day,
I believe we have increased Marilyn's
wardrobe of underthings by 200 percent.
Joe, Joe. Hey, what do you think of
Marilyn showin' off...
I had no idea they didn't renew
your contract.
What a lousy break.
Yep. I've been thinkin' about
gettin' back to the city for awhile now
and try my hand at Broadway --
where they appreciate real talent.
Hey, am I distrubing you, Marilyn?.
Do you realize that
you haven't taken your eyes off
your goddamn reflection since
I've been here?.
Well, gee, Eddie,
I hate to break it to you,
but what do you think actresses do
in their dressing rooms?.
I don't know.
I guess it depends
on how self-absorbed they are.
He's back?. The life-guard?.
Don't let him insult you like that.
Get out of here.
Sure. I was just leaving.
No, no! Not you, Eddie.
It was just a line that
I was working on.
Could you please sit down?. I'm sorry.
Please.
Well, you delivered it well.
Like he would know?.
You know, sometimes I have to look
in the mirror to see who's there.
Know what I mean?.
Nope.
Much better.
I see you're mixin' booze
with your downers now, huh?.
What booze, Eddie?. It's Champagne.
It's still booze
and the combination can kill you.
What?. You're gonna lecture me now?.
Am I...Am I the only person
that tells you this stuff?.
What about your husband, huh?.
And what about your...
Your...Your friends?.
I mean, for chrissake,
don't you have any friends?.
Well, of course I have friends,
Eddie. Ha!
But see these here are my best friends.
They're the only ones
who are completely loyal.
The only ones
that never try to change me.
They shake me see, and some-times
they get very nasty and they yell,
"Hey, bitch! Get the fuck outta bed! "
Oh, yes. Sometimes,
when I feel my clock running down
and I'm dead on my feet
and I can't dance another step,
the run all over my body
and turn all my switches back on..
They make me alive again.
The way they lined up to see me
in New York.
Don't let it go to your head.
The same folks line up to see
the fat lady and the two headed calf.
They love a good freak show.
You seemed to enjoy it.
You think I'm fat?.
You're a little prky around the middle
if you want to know.
I didn't ask.
You know, Zanuck says he thinks
"The Seven Year Itch"
is gonna make him a bundle.
He says it's my best role ever.
Well, you've had enough practice.
It's the same role you always play --
cheap, dim-witted floozie.
He says I'm really incredibly good
in the picture.
Then why is he sending us this crap?.
Have you looked at these master-pieces?.
"The Girl in the Red Velvet Swing,"
you play a rich old man's mistress.
"The Revolt of Mamie Stovere,"
you play a hooker in Honolulu.
Oh, and here's an art movie,
"How To Be Very, Very Popular,
Starring Marilyn Monroe
as Curly Flagg."
You should be working with Burton,
with Brando with Olivier!
But what if I'm, you know,
not that good of an actress?.
I mean, what if I just don't have
that kind of talent?.
Then you'll just have to develop
that kind of talent.
You'll just have to march
into Zanuck's office
and remind him that he would lose
about a million dollars a year
without you.
You'll just have to tell him
you want to do serious roles
in serious films
with serious directors you select.
And then what?.
Then will you be happy?.
Will that be good enough for you?.
Will anything ever be good enough
for you?.
No, dear.
Movie stars don't choose
their own pictures.
I choose their pictures.
That's how they get to be movie stars.
Understand me?. You are a movie star
because I made you a movie star.
You could send me your sister
from Phily or your aunt Josephine
from Minneapolis...
If I wanted to,
I could do the same thing for them.
No. If I am a star, it's the public
that has made me a star...
No studio... No director... The public.
Is that so?.
Well, all the public
wants to see you do is sing
and dance and wiggle your ass!
Who do you think you are --
Katherine Hepburn?.
You wanna play Shakespeare?.
You wanna play
"The Brothers Karamazov?. "
Not the Brothers. Grushenka.
Huh?.
She's a girl, Mr. Zanuck.
All right. Let's defer this discussion.
We'll talk about it after
"The Seven Year Itch" is released.
Well, now I think
you need my help to promote that movie.
So that gives me more...
What was that word
that Johnny used to use?.
I know...Leverage.
We're here today with Marilyn Monroe,
the first woman in the history of show
business who successfully negotiate her
own independent production deal.
I'm Sidney Skolsky and I love Hollywood
Marilyn, I understand that under
the terms of your new deal
you'll be developing screen properties
to produce yourself out of your office
in New York. Now, uh...
Why New York, Marilyn?.
Well, Sidney, I believe
it's a better atmosphere
for me to find good materia,
and for me to learn to use myself
more fully as an actress.
You will never find
anyone who loves you like I do.
You cannot even recognize sincere love
when it is offered to you --
you ungrateful brat!
I took you in when you were nothing.
I breathed live into you!
I made you into a star!
Yeah, you and apparently everybody else
in Hollywood.
You would have thrown away your career
for a moron --
for a cretin!
I am the one who saved you!
Yeah, well,
Joe isn't my husband anymore, Natash.
And neither are you!
Make it real. Make it honest.
You are angry. Juliette is angry.
The nurse is dilatory.
You want to yell. You want to scream.
So...do it. Go ahead. Come on, yell.
I can't.
You can't?. Then get out of the business
What are you feeling now?.
You're frustrated now?. You're angry?.
Then Yell, goddamn you!
God, I'd die if he screamed at me
like like that.
That's better. Now...
Listen if a doctor gives you good stuff
and it works,
you don't have to like him, do you?.
This torture should be brought
in dismal hell.
Did Romeo slay himself?.
Mr. Strasberg?.
I really enjoyed your class today.
You're so brilliant with actors.
I have...
Well, I've been wanting to extend
my range as an actress.
And I've always dreamed of studying
at the Actor's Studio.
It takes a lot of courage
for those who are already functioning
professionally to come to work here.
Unfortunately,
you have already acquired
many odd habits and mannerisms
which you now have to unlearn.
I recommend private lessons
in my study perhaps three times a week.
You might even like to stay
for dinner afterwards.
Thank you.
We've met before.
Elia Kazan introduced us years ago.
I don't know if you remember.
Why of course I remember, Art.
I was just a very unimportant starlet
then and you just won
the Pulitzer Prize
for "Death of a Salesman."
I'm prepping a new play, uh...
"A View From the Bridge."
We open next month at the Coronet.
Uh...perhaps you'd like to stop by
and watch a rehearsal with me sometime
maybe make a few suggestions.
They'll say,
"If Arthur Miller's interested in her,
she must be more intelligent
than we thought.
She must have hidden dimensions
we never even suspected."
They'll probably say,
"If Arthur Miller's interested in her,
he must be desperate to get laid."
Didn't you figure it out last time?.
So now, instead of
trying to cook spaghetti,
you're gonna try to make matzo balls...
They're harder, you idiot!
You're not meant for love
and marriage -- you're not built for it.
Stick with what you're good at.
Nothing if I listen to you!
He's old enough to be your father!
And then there's this voice in my head,
"Do this. Don't do that."
It never ever stops.
You know, some days...
Well, a lot of days actually --
like even today...
I uh, think I'm about one step away
from becoming a raving shit throwing
lunatic just like my mother
and my grandmother... You know?.
'Cause it's in my blood.
It's in my brain.
I...I don't...
I don't want to end up a zombie.
I don't...I don't want to end up
lead around by some nurse
Iike some kind of
a wind-up doll on wheels.
See, every morning I wake up
and I worry about whether
I'm gonna end up in some hospital,
strapped to my bed and crapping
in my clothes -- screaming gibberish.
Am I gonna end up like my mother,
Dr. Kris?.
The science of the mind has progressed
a great deal in the last twenty years,
Marilyn.
We are not as quick to hospitalize
as we once were.
there are new therapies,
new medications.
Tell me something, Dr. Kris.
What would you think if I became a Jew?.
But I think it should be a serious name
don't you?.
Like Isadora -- for your father.
Isadora?. The kid'll probably hate us
for the rest of his life.
Oh, no. I know!
What about Abe?. Abraham Miller.
Well, what about Sarah, or Hanna...
or Rachel?.
Oh, no, Papi.
I got a boy in here...
And I'm gonna paint his room blue
and not a pastel blue, either,
more like a robin's egg blue.
Oh, Papi,
we're gonna be just like normal people,
aren't we?.
Oh, do you think
he'll be as happy to see me
as I'll be to see him?.
Two guys dressed as women,
you think that's funny?.
It's been the basis of
theatrical comedy
from Shakespeare to Feydeau.
I think it's silly.
Well, that's the point.
Plus, he wants to shoot it
in black and white.
My contract expressly guarantees that
I will always be shot in technicolor.
Then turn it down.
Well, somebody has to bring
in some money around here.
So, I guess it might
as well be the pregnant wife.
I can't count on you to do it.
I seem to remember that
you used to be a writer.
So what have you written lately, Arthur
You turned out to be a full time job.
Well, that's right.
Just get up and walk away
like a fucking milquetoast!
Why don't you write
about getting a stupid job!
Oh, Arthur...Arthur...Arthur.
How are you?.
Alive. Lucky me.
There's something wrong inside me,
Arthur...
Some defect...Some evil.
God doesn't want me to have babies.
We're gonna have lots of babies.
We're gonna watch them grow big
and prosperous and dignified.
They better take after you.
Sorry.
I'll get the doctor.
No. Pleaes don't go. Please.
I'll be right back.
Okay.
Eh...Well, you must be very happy.
No.
Liar. Come on...
Tell me how babies
would just stretch my belly
and make my tits tag.
Go ahead, this is your chance.
This is your opportunity.
Tell me
how I would have ended up fatter
and flabbier than I am already.
God, you're awful quiet today.
Never when I want you to.
What's the matter?.
This is one of your greatest days.
Don't you know I love you, Marilyn?.
Action!
Where is that... bon-bon?.
Cut!
And...Action!
Cut.
I have an aunt in Vienna --
also an actress -- her name,
I believe, is Mildered Lachenfarber.
She always comes to the set on time,
she knows her lines perfectly,
she never gives anyone
the slightest trouble.
And at the box office,
she's worth about fourteen cents.
You get my point.
What good is being Marilyn Monroe if
I can't have a normal life and family?.
A family...
I'd settle for just one baby.
Why does everything have to turn out
to be so shitty?.
Maybe God
is trying to tell me something.
I'd probably be a kooky mother,
I'd probably love my child to death.
Stop it! Stop it! Stop it!!!
Did you hear her?. That voice.
That noise.
It never goes away.
Please make it stop, Dr. Kris.
Oh, plese, just turn it off.
I'm going to prescribe something
for your nerves.
Oh, go ahead. Eat the whole bottle --
then they'll be reeeally sorry.
Oh, go straight to hell.
How can you have so little respect
for yourself when I love you so?.
There. There we go.
Papa?. How come you never talk to me
in those beautiful flowery sentences
like you write?.
When the movie's over, I'll be better.
I'll be a good wife to you, Papa.
Acting tears me up inside.
The first time I ever saw you,
you were so beautiful
and so angelic that you almost made me
believe in God again.
And now?.
We're losin' the light Mr. Clift.
I'm on my way.
I hate you, Arthur.
Really?. Why is that, Marilyn?.
Well, you're so smart,
why don't you figure it out?.
You told me you were going to write me
the best role of my career.
This is the best you could do?.
The character is passive and stupid --
she just wonders around all day long
feeling sorry for herself.
Is this the way you see me?.
Is this the way I inspire you?.
"The Misfits!?. "
You're the misfit, Arthur.
You don't know
the first goddamn thing about darma!
And after all you've taught me.
You're a lousy writer, Arthur!
And you're a lousy husband!
They need you in the bleachers now,
Miss Monroe.
And hey, kill that motor, will you?.
We're ready for a take.
No. Go on. Just drive. Go. Go! Just go!
Just get outta here, goddamn it!!!
Get out of here!
Which is it, communism or freedom?.
We'll triumph
in the next five or ten years.
That's what should concern us.
God, he's brilliant...
Absolutely magnificent.
I think he's gonna be another Lincoln.
No, no, no. Don't do it that way.
Wait. I'll show you.
This works much faster, believe me.
Weeeee!
Sometimes, I open them up
and I let the granules dissolve
on my tongue, like communion.
But mostly, I mix it with stuff.
I like Nembutal with gin.
But Dexamyl's good with champagne
'cause it bubbles see...
It's really the best combination.
Unless you can get your hands
on some Mandrax.
I once almost lost a whole bottle of
Mandrax on an airplane.
It happened a couple of years ago.
I was flying to Louisville to shoot
"Raintree County"
and I went to the john
and I managed to drop a hundred
and fifty randy Mandies down
into the TWA crapper.
What did you do?.
Well, I had to go in and fish 'em out.
My right arm turned...turned...
turned blue all the way up to my elbow!
It itched like a sonuva -
bitch for like three weeks.
Ohhh...
That's what I love about you, Monty.
You're the only one
I know who's more fucked up than me.
What?.
Arthur's never coming back, is he?.
Well then
he's the biggest fool God ever made.
I haven't washed my hair in days.
I haven't slept in a week.
"Something's Got To Give"
starts shooting in nine days.
I have a wardrobe test on Monday,
and I look like somebody
who's been buried and dug up again.
So, what can you give me to bring me
back to human?.
What do you usually take?.
Nembutal, Seconal...Chloral Hydrate...
Phenobarbital...
Amytal, Dexamyl...Demerol sometimes.
You take the Amytal
and the Demerol intravenously?.
Mmmmmm, usually.
Self-administered?.
I know some doctors...
I like the "professional touch."
From now on, I'd like you
to restrict yourself to one doctor.
For the time being,
I'm going to allow
the Chloral Hydrate --
it's fast acting and I think
it's going to help to wean you off of
the other barbiturates.
But...
...No more IV drugs.
Now do you understand?.
Party pooper.
Thank you.
Mmmmhmmm. Oh...Marilyn?.
This is my son, Danny.
Hi.
Oh, go ahead. I'll see you tomorrow.
Walk her out, Dan?.
Oh, sure.
He doesn't have to.
Hey, Danny...What are you studying?.
contemporary American Government.
Really?. Can I ask you something?.
Uh, I hope I can answer.
If you were going to meet
the President of the United States,
what would you talk about?.
Of course, if you like sports, uh,
we usually have a pick-up game of uh,
touch football on Saturdays --
usually quite fun.
It is fun.
Excellent Brandy.
Mr. President?.
Yes?.
Isn't the massive build up of U.S. Aid
and the dispatch of thousands of
"advisors" into South Vietnam
a direct violation
of the Geneva accords?.
Well, the uh trouble is we...
we are violating the Geneva agreement.
Uh, not as much as North Vietnamese are
but violating them never-theless.
So, whatever we do has to be done
with a certain amount of uh... secrecy.
And of course
there's always an element of uh...
danger in that, isn't there?.
Thanks, Mr. President,
for the things you've done...
Battles that you've won.
The way you deal with...
What's the matter, honey?.
You're wearing my dress.
That dress costs
twelve thousand dollars, you bitch!
Is that the sort of language
a First Lady uses?.
I don't think so.
But first Ladies don't look like whores
they don't act like whores
and they don't stink like whores.
Stop it! Stop it!
Can't you see that
you're just going to ruin everything
if you go out there looking
like a high priced slut!
You have to wear something simple.
Something elegant.
Something befitting the wife
of a President.
Jack likes me to look sexy.
He says it gets rid
of the pain in his back.
Yeah, right.
This is better on me, anyway.
You're too fat to wear it.
Haven't you read,
Jackie only weighs twelve pounds...
Oh, I'm sorry, I forgot.
You only read Dostoyevski
or is it tolstoy?.
Can't you forget about Jackie?.!
It's just a political marriage.
He doesn't love her.
He never sticks his band up her dress
like he does to me!
You think you are so grand.
The President's whore!
How many women do you think he has?.
Isn't this what you wanted?.
You're the one who wanted
the nice clothes
and the money and the power.
I did this for you.
Bullshit!
You've never done anything for me.
But I'm gonna do something for you...
ohhhh...
What the hell is going on here?.
Marilyn, you were supposed
to be on stage an hour ago.
What did you take?.
What did you take!?.
I didn't take anything, Peter.
Nothing, I swear, that's the problem.
Okay.
I'll take care of it.
Thank you! Oh, Happy Birthday,
Mr. President!
Happy Birhtday to you!
Say, how'd you all like
to hear another one, huh?.
Honey, what on earth
did you do to this dress?.
I've had to sew
a whole new seam way up the fornt!
And it was plenty tight to begin with.
You know, I may have to open up a slit
in the back, just so you can walk.
I'm sorry, Hazel.
I can't find Sidney Guilaroff anywhere.
Somebody said he left
about a half an hour ago.
He's probably half way
to Idlewild by now.
The only hairstylist
still hanging around back stage
is Mickey Song.
He's the guy who does the Kennedy's.
Oooh, well, I sure
as hell don't want to look like Jackie.
You ask him to come in.
Hey, you tell him
I wanna look just like Jackie.
In the history of show business,
in fact,
there has been no one female who
has meant so much,
who's done more...What?.
Mr. President...
The late Marilyn Monroe.
Happy Birthday to you...
Happy Birthday, Mr. President...
The President's concerned.
We're all concerned,
in fact, that uh...
your involvement with him
has become a little too public
for comfort.
Especially since your performance
at the Birthday Gala.
But you were the one who asked me
to sing Happy Birthday to him.
And you...you telephone the President
from your dressing room
when other people are present.
And you put these phone calls through
the FOX switch-board.
Now, the family cannot,
and will not tolerate this level
of indiscretion.
He's going to marry me, Bobby.
No.
I don't believe
the President ever gave you
any reason to think that.
So now I have to ask you
not to attempt to contact him
in any way.
Now, he believes
it's the best thing for him,
and it's the best thing for America.
And personally, I...
I think he's crazy.
Listen, I'd uh...I'd like to give you
my private phone number.
This'll put you right through
to my desk at the Justice Department.
But they can't fire me.
I've never been fired before in my life
I had to promise them
that you'd be on the set on time
every morning.
Well, you've worked exactly four
of the last twenty-one days.
Every man woman and child in America
saw you singing Happy Birthday
to the President
when you to me you were home sick
with a virus!
Ah, honey, you're all out of chances.
But I was ill. You know know that I was
So Liz Taylor can get sick and I can't,
is that it?.
Every time she sneezes
they spend four million dollars
to break down the set
and move 'em to a warmer climate.
And her arms are fat.
Oh, Henry, her arms are so fat.
I make millions for them
and this is how they treat me!?.
Fucking Weinstein --
fucking bastard -- Judas!
No, he's out to get me.
They're all out to get me!
Especially that stupid, no talent,
over-the-hill washed up Cukor.
What do you mean?. Of course you can!
You're the Attorney General
of the United Staes,
for chrissakes,
you could do whatever you want!
No! You can! You can!
No, you could!
If you wanted to you could put them
in jail.
You...you could,
you could audit their taxes,
you could deport them.
You can have them assassinated!
Oh, no. Oh...Bobby. Bobby...Oh...
God, Eddie, wouldn't you know it,
I'd get a dog with depression.
Uh...it's a beautiful house, Marilyn.
I'm impressed. I am.
Thanks.
You know, I've been planning
a trip to Mexico to pick some tiles
and furniture and stuff,
I'm actually gonna leave on Thursday.
It sounds great.
Did I tell you?.
I've been renegotiating my deal at FOX?.
They're gonna hire me
back at twice my old salary.
I don't even wanna ask.
You know, Eddie...
Being with you, is like old times.
Rmember the Ambassador?.
Yeah, I do.
You used to love me then.
You know, Eddie.
When I was little, nobody loved me.
Nobody at all.
But then when I grew up,
I learned that I could make anyone fall
in love with me...
Just by taking off my dress.
Well, I guess
I've gotten smarter since then,
so...I'm gonna say goodnight.
You're leaving Eddie?.
Yeah, I have to get back.
Hey, did I tell you?.
I made a settlement with FOX.
They're gonna pay me five times
my old salary.
I'm gonna start to work next Thursday.
What happened to Mexico?.
After I get back from Mexico.
Have a safe trip.
There are eighty-eight tiles around
the rim of the swimming pool.
There are three-hundred-sixty-seven
flagstones in the walkway.
There are one thousand,
eight hundred seventy-four tiles...
on the roof...
No! I told you, you have to walk
at least three steps behind me!
There are eighty-eight tiles around
the rim of the swimming pool.
There are three hundred sixty seven
flagstones on the walkway.
There are one thousand...
Hello, sweetheart.
Oh, yes! Yes!
You are happy, aren't you?.
Aren't you happy?.
Oh, yes, you are!
You are.
Robert Kennedy residence.
Hi. It's Marilyn.
Could I talk to Bobby, please?.
Just a moment, Miss Monroe.
Angel?.
Mr. Kennedy's unavailable
to speak to you.
He is accepting no more calls
until further notice.
Please, don't attempt to make contact.
Thank you.
What are you doing?.
Sometimes I have to hurt myself,
just to see if I can still feel.
Get out of my house! I hate you!
It's all your fault.
He dumped you as fast as he could
because you're a cheap piece of trash.
You're ignorant and you have no class.
No. That's you. I'm Marilyn.
You're only good for one thing.
That's why every man you've ever known
has walked out on you.
They've all walked out on you.
Even your daddy.
Freddy, Johnny, Joe.
I won't listen. I won't.
Arthur, Bobby. Even your fans.
They all left you.
We could have had it all!
But you had to go and wreck it,
like everything else in your life.
I'll make you go away.
Thirty-six years old
and your tits are sagging faster
than your ass.
No. I'll make you go...
I'll make you go away.
Your mind is gone.
You're just a drunk and a pill head.
No wonder everybody left you.
It's too late. Everybody hates you.
Never work again.
The world will be better off
without you.
Jesus loves me, this I know.
For the Bible tells me so...