My sister...
was just-
Oh, God.
What happened?
What happened to her?
... regional safe zones.
This is not a test.
- Justine?
- Repeat. This is not a test.
Justine!
Justine, where are you?
Justine, it's me.
It's Mommy.
Hello?
Hello? Is anyone there?
Hello? Please.
I'm your neighbor from 431. Please.
Please, I need some help.
I can't find my daughter.
Hello! Hello!
Please open the door!
Please.
Please help me.
Open the door!
Help me, please. Help me.
Oh, my God.
It's a plague.
Michelle?
Oh, my- Oh, my God.
E-Excuse me. Something terrible's
happened, and I can't find my daughter.
I-I've lost my little girl.
Please. Can you tell
me what's going on here?
Why would I do that?
I- I'm sorry?
- Go on like this.
- I don't understand.
It hurts.
It- It hurts so bad.
What hurts?
What's wrong with you?
You wouldn't understand.
I mean, how- how could you really?
- You're right. I-I'm sorry. I don't.
- Lisa. Lisa, answer me.
- Tell me where you are.
- Oh, God. I'm sorry. I- I thought-
It's not enough to.
Can I just have a moment of your time,
please? I've lost my little girl.
I wanna die.
I just wanna die.
Lisa, it's time to
get you help.
But I don't know how.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
I can help you.
Just tell me where you are.
I'm sorry. I have to find my little girl.
I'm sorry.
All you have to do
is tell me where you are.
I've looked everywhere.
Good-bye, David.
No. Don't hang up.
Stay on the line.
- Good-bye.
- Lisa, where are you?
What do you want, Michelle?
Aunt Carmen. Oh, God.
I thought you and Uncle Pete were-
- Carmen?
- You shouldn't be out at this hour.
Something terrible is happening.
- Everywhere you look-
- I know.
Justine's gone.
And- Well, I thought, um-
I thought maybe I left her with you.
No. She's- She's-
She's not-
I don't- No.
She's not here.
- Are you all right?
- Yes.
- Are you sure?
- I think so. You?
- I don't know.
I- I just don't know anymore.
I'm scared, Carmen.
I'm scared, and, um-
People are dying
from some horrible disease...
and others are killing themselves,
and... I'm scared.
I'm- I'm scared.
TV's not workin'.
Radio either.
Um...
where's Uncle Pete?
- Is he-
- Pete- Pete-
Pete's in the back bedroom.
Can I talk to him?
Well, I don't know if that's
a really good idea right now.
- Why not?
- He's-
I don't know.
Let's go and talk to him, okay?
Can we do that?
- Please.
- Well, all right.
Uh, I- I'm just-
I'm just not sure he wants to
talk to anyone right now.
He really hasn't
been himself lately.
He has Mr. - Mr. Peppers
in there with him. He-
Um- Um- Pete?
Peter pie.
Uncle Pete?
Uncle Pete, it's me.
It's Michelle.
It's your niece, Michelle.
Is there a key?
The door doesn't lock.
Never has.
Then why haven't you gone inside?
I don't know.
- No, don't. Don't go in there.
- Why?
That's-
That's not my husband.
Not anymore.
Pete?
Oh, my God, Michelle.
What have you done?
Justine?
Justine, honey.
Is that you?
It's me.
It's Mommy.
What's wrong, baby?
Are you sick?
Is that it?
It's okay.
Everything's okay.
I promise.
Can I see your face?
Can you do that for me?
Can you show Mommy your face?
- It's been out here all night.
- What?
Why didn't you tell me?
It's been watching me
since the sun went down.
Stop saying "it."
I- I- I thought it was
Justine, too, at first.
But I tried talking to it.
It never says a word,
never shows its face.
I think you need to get away from it,
Michelle. Now.
What are-What are you saying?
Is she-
I think- I think, if you touch it...
you-you'll die.
- No.
- You'll get the infection, and you'll die.
I don't believe you.
You don't know what you're saying.
Get away from it.
Come on, baby.
Let's go home.
Oh, wait. Please wait.
Oh, God have mercy on us all.
God have mercy on us all.
No, no, no.
No, wait, please.
Justine.
Justine, come back.
Please!
Come back, please, Justine!
Justine!
July 6. I talked to the school psych.
Justine is acting out at school.
This tension between me and
Stephen is affecting our child now.
- This has got to stop.
- [Chimes]
July 15.
Stephen is more and more remote.
He is no longer hostile,
but he won't talk about us...
and he won't try family counseling.
July 24.
I think Stephen is having an affair.
August 2...
Stephen wants a divorce.
Says I share the blame.
How am I to blame
for his infidelities?
August 3.
He moved out today.
Claims he's going to stay
at the cabin.
Liar.
He's living with her.
I know it.
September 14.
Forty-three days single.
Teri signed me up
with a dating service.
All losers.
I just want you back, Stephen.
September 20.
I'm spending all my time in chat rooms.
I can't eat.
I can't sleep.
It's a sick world out there,
especially at night.
September 23.
I found a strange Web site.
People actually seem to be killing
themselves in front of their webcams.
Once I got over the horror of it...
I realized there was something
almost welcoming in their despair.
A kind of shared pain nobody
else could possibly understand.
September 24. I must get these
dark thoughts out of my head.
I must think of Justine.
My sweet little angel.
October 5.
The day I thought would never come.
Stephen won custody
of our daughter...
and I was ruled an unfit mother
for neglecting my child.
How could this happen?
How could you do this to me?
I hate you.
October 7.
I can't bear the thought...
of leaving Justine with you
and that woman.
I would rather see my baby dead.
October 8.
Decision made.
FirstJustine...
then me.
Good-bye, my love.
I'll be with you soon.
Justine?
Justine! Justine!
Justine! Justine, thank God!
You all right, sweetheart?
You okay?
Huh? You okay?
Christ, I've been worried
sick about you.
I called all the neighbors. I called 911.
I called your mom.
I called Aunt Carmen and Uncle Pete.
Oh!
Sweetie...
where's Mommy?
Huh? Do you know where she is?
Did- Did she- Did she get sick?
Huh?
Oh, come here. It's okay, squirt.
Daddy's here. There's my big girl.
We're together.
Nothing's gonna change that.
You understand? Nothing.
Come on.
That's my daughter.
That's my girl.
All right. Sit back.
Stephen. Stephen!
Justine.
Hey, squirt.
You want to buckle up for me?
Here.
I'll give you a hand.
That-a-girl.
Oh, no.
Don't look, okay?
Just don't look.
Hold on. I'm gonna
try and get past him.
Is that Justine?
You had us all
praying for a miracle.
And praise the Lord,
it finally paid off.
So what's going on?
You turning people away now?
Residents and family only.
That's the rule.
Otherwise it's gonna be chaos,
just like down in the city.
There's gotta be something we can do.
I'm sorry. I know how it sounds,
but that's the way it's gotta be.
Now, uh-
I'm gonna have to ask you both
to step out of the car.
- What?
- Uh, it- it's just a precaution.
Uh, uh, anybody who leaves, don't matter
for how long, we just gotta be sure.
- What's this about, Hutch?
- It's just a precaution.
Come on.
You gotta be kidding me.
All right. If y'all would just step out
the front of the truck here.
Take your jackets off.
All we need to see is
your arms and your legs.
And, Steve, if you'd just go over there.
All right, sweetheart.
It's only Hutch, okay?
It's all right.
Come on.
Let me see your arm.
All right. Now show me
the other arm.
- Now your arm.
- Now check the leg.
And the other one.
There. What's that?
- I see it. On her shoulder.
- What is that?
- It's dirt. It's just dirt.
- What is it, Steve?
- Steve, step back.
- Christ, Hutch.
- Just step aside!
- Hutch, it's just dirt!
- Goddamn it, Steve! Step aside!
- See? You see?
- It's just dirt!
- Okay.
- It's just dirt, goddamn it!
- Just calm down, Steve. All right.
- Okay.
- You're good to go.
It's good, Steve.
It's good.
Do you think you'd
like to talk about Mommy?
I don't know.
Can you tell me what happened?
Take your time.
She was in my room...
crying.
- Did she say why?
- Sh-Sh-
She said she wanted to die.
She had that stuff all over her.
What stuff?
That black stuff
that looks like mold.
She wanted me to come-
She wanted me to come closer...
but I was too scared to.
Come here, baby.
Mommy just wants to hold you.
I love you so much.
It's just 'cause I love you so much.
It's okay.
It's okay, baby.
Come on.
It's okay.
Everything's gonna be okay.
# Hush, little baby #
# Don't say a word #
# Mama's gonna buy you #
#A mockingbird #
# If that mockingbird
don't sing #
# Mama's gonna buy you
a diamond ring #
# If that diamond ring
don't shine ##
All the pain will be gone soon.
Very soon.
And then we can fly away from here.
Fly away from-
Mom?
What did you do after that?
Did you run away?
I went to Aunt Carmen's
and Uncle Pete's.
I couldn't remember
how to get there.
But then I saw the big church...
and I remembered where it was.
Were they home?
I think Uncle Pete was.
But he stayed in his bedroom
and wouldn't come out.
So I went out back and sat on a swing
and waited for him.
For how long?
- Till Mommy came.
- But you-
You said Mommy came
to Aunt Carmen's.
Is that what you said?
I think so.
What do you mean you think so?
Sorry. I didn't mean
to raise my voice.
Was she, um-
Come on, squirt.
Let's get you cleaned up and into bed.
Good night, squirt.
Who is it?
Who do you think,  Stephen?
Had to remind those gun-humping
mongoloids I was still your girlfriend.
Three days I'm stuck in hell central,
and you're where?
- I was looking for my daughter.
- Oh, I get that.
- But what about me?
- Could you just take it down a notch?
I thought I was gonna die, Stephen.
I've never been so scared
in all my life.
I had to steal some poor
dead fucker's car...
with his fucking ashes still in it,
thank you very much.
Drive myself up here,
alone, hoping and praying...
that one of those vigilante alcoholics
you call neighbors...
will have the simple human
decency to let me through.
God, I need a drink!
Wine, Drano.
Anything.
I think I have some cooking sherry.
Well, you know how to party.
Glass? Dixie cup?
Forget it.
I'll rough it.
I know you're out there.
You can't fool me.
I don't know who you are,
but you are not my wife.
You hear me?
You are not my wife!
But you-you can't get me.
You can't get me. Huh?
You can't get me!
Oh.
Oh. Oh. Oh. Oh, God. Oh, God.
My pills. My pills.
Carmen. Carmen. My pills.
Car-
Carmen?
My pills. Carmen.
Carmen. Carmen.
Who-Who-
Who are you?
Do you believe that shit
they're saying about the red tape-
that it keeps you safe somehow?
I'm not sure
what to believe anymore.
Well, I am not sealing myself
up in my own tomb.
That is just too fucked-up
for words.
Speaking of words, do me a favor.
I have a six-year-old upstairs...
who's been through something
no child should ever have to face.
Could you please just drop
a few less F-bombs?
God, I hardly even notice anymore.
Sorry.
By the way...
- I know what you're thinking.
- Really?
What am I thinking?
You're thinking how much
further that food would go...
with two mouths instead of three.
Funny, I never pegged you
for a psychic.
You know, I could
make myself useful.
And how are you gonna do that?
I know how to relax you,
better than anybody.
Oh, please. No.
Don't do this. Not now.
Don't do what?
- Don't!
- What?
Isn't this how celebretards
get out of taxicabs?
- I mean it, Marta.
- No, you don't.
You never do.
Remember the first time we did it?
Standing-
on your boss's back porch
while dear, sweet Michelle...
was inside boring everyone to tears
about global warming.
Wow, the ice is melting, all right.
It's trickling right down my thigh.
Okay, did you turn that on?
Are you kidding? No way.
Don't you know you're
not even supposed to
have those things
around anymore?
It wasn't even plugged in.
I guess you forgot to pull
the battery, now, didn't you?
Well, fine.
Be my guest.
I'm not touching it.
I had two of my friends kill themselves
after touching their computers.
- You had friends?
- Okay, "F" you, sweetheart.
Jesus! Do something.
Calm down. All right?
It's a computer.
You can't get infected by a computer.
Those are just rumors.
Mass hysteria.
Well, then you turn it off.
Fine. I will.
- No, don't!
- What?
Just don't touch it.
- What-What are you doing?
- Killing it.
Wait!
Oh, God.
It's Michelle.
These are all from Friday.
There's even more from Saturday.
Jesus.
This session's over.
Squirt, I need to
ask you a question.
It's very important that you answer me
as honestly and as clearly as you can.
Is Mommy alive?
Was she dead?
You have to tell me, Justine.
The last time you saw her,
she was alive, right?
When she came to Aunt Carmen's,
she was alive.
No. She was dead.
Daddy!
Justine!
Marta, get up!
- We gotta get out-
- What, Stephen?
- Come on, Marta! Marta, get out now.
- Stephen!
Stephen!
Come on! Marta!
Marta! Marta!
All right, wait here.
Marta!
I didn't mean to hurt you. It wasn't me.
It was- Stephen seduced me.
- Marta.
- Stephen, help me.
Move, goddamn it!
Does Mommy want to hurt us?
I think she, um-
I think she misses you very much.
I miss her too.
Even when I'm afraid.
I know you do, squirt.
I know you do.
Can we go around it?
Jesus. Open the door!
- Open it!
- Okay!
Scoot over, Tinker Bell.
I left you a gap on the right.
You can just squeeze through.
I'm not going anywhere
till you tell me what you want.
We can wait for that
gas tank to explode,
or you can get the
hell out of here!
- Me, I'd choose the latter.
- Get that gun out of my daughter's face!
- Just go.
- Okay.
Okay, honey, it's okay.
Uh, I- I thought-
I-I-I-I mean-
I-I-I didn't think
anybody was, uh-
there was anybody, uh-
Don't go.
I'm sorry.
Uh, I-I-I should be going.
I never knew before...
what they feel.
- So alone.
- They?
L-Look, ma'am,
I don't know what I can-
Oh, God.
- U-U-Uh, ma'am-
- Touch me.
No. Uh-
No, m-ma'am.
I-I-I'm a- I'm a-
You don't want to feel me?
Is that it?
Yes- I mean, no.
I-I-It's not that I don't.
I do. I-It's just-
You think it's catching?
It's not.
You don't get it from us.
You get it from them.
Maybe. I- I don't know.
I don't-A-A-All I know-
You know nothing.
You don't know what she took from me.
You don't know.
Oh- Oh, I'm so cold.
So cold.
Hold me.
Please just hold me.
I'm so cold.
Yeah.
You just-just hold me.
Please.
Oh, I'm so cold.
Please just hold me.
So, we're gonna go
on a little shopping trip.
Then I'm out of your hair
for good. How's that?
Everything of value
was looted days ago.
- Not what I'm looking for.
- Which is what, exactly?
Let's just say that I have a plan...
that can save the world...
or end it a whole lot sooner.
- Just tell me what you need me for.
- Wheels, man.
You're planning on saving
the world but can't find a car?
I don't drive. I never have.
It's my bit for the environment.
All right, then, knock yourself out.
No, dude, I'm not
going in there. You are.
I'll be sitting right here with
little, uh-What's your name?
- Chatty Cathy.
- No. That is not acceptable.
Get out.
Okay, tell me... exactly what it is
I'm looking for.
It's your basic multi-use
infrared microprocessor.
A few aisles down on the left,
as I recall.
Very important-you want IR-245-F.
IR-245-F. Okay.
- Sweetie, sweetie, sweetie-
- Giddyap.
Okay, honey.
It's gonna be okay.
You be good.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
IR-245-F!
Nothing else will do!
Daddy!
Daddy.
You gotta be kidding me.
Coming when?
Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
IR-245-F.
IR-245-F. IR-245-F.
Where are you?
Oh, shit.
What? Come on. What-
"C."
"D." "E."
Goddamn it! Where?
All right, here-There! Right there!
Come on!
No!
Get away from me!
Get over, sweetheart.
Did you get it?
- Yeah.
- Come here.
Right on.
I saw my ex-wife last night.
- What a joy.
- My dead ex-wife.
So you want to know...
where she's been, why she's back...
and if it's really even her.
All right. Imagine you're out there
floating in some black, empty void.
Suddenly there's a way back
to this plane of existence...
a way back to life.
You'd grab onto it, wouldn't you?
Even if that life wasn't your own?
The problem is, in this little
passion play you're still not alive.
And that's gotta hurt.
That's gotta really suck...
to know that you made it
all the way back...
only to find out,
beyond a shadow of a doubt...
that you're still fuckin' dead.
Here. Take it. Red's the one frequency
they can't penetrate.
Yeah, I kinda got that impression.
So what am I supposed
to do with this?
When the time comes,
you'll think of something.
- Dad.
- Stay in the car.
Stay in the car.
Be right back.
Excuse me?
I'd like to buy some gas.
Sir?
I'm on pump four.
I'm just g-
I'm just stepping inside.
I'm just gonna-
I'm just gonna reach past you...
over your shoulder.
That's it. That's all.
I'll, uh-
I'll leave the cash on top of the pump,
if that's all right with you.
Pop the gas cap.
You know where it is, right?
Never mind.
I got it.
There.
I-I-I had no intention
of stealing your gas.
It's full service only.
Oh. Right.
Uh-
Hey, that works for me.
No problem.
Uh, premium's all I got left.
Fine. Uh, p-p-premium's-
premium's fine.
It's b- better than fine.
You have no idea how grateful I am.
I was, uh, practically on fumes.
Move over, squirt.
Do you happen to know anything
about any kind of relief center?
Emergency services,
anything like that?
There's a- a refugee camp
being set up along 306.
It's about 20 miles south
of Chillicothe.
It's where the cell signals
won't reach.
Thanks. I'll try
heading down that way.
Hey, did you hear that, squirt?
It's only four or five
hours' drive from here.
Not that it'll do you
a damn bit of good.
I'm hungry.
I'm sure they got food
and a place to sleep.
I bet they even have
other kids your age.
What about Mommy?
I'm sure that she would
want you to be okay...
before she'd ever want you
worrying about her.
That's just the way mommies are.
I know it's hard,
but... try to-
Hey. Hey!
Wait. Wait.
Oh, shit.
Damn it.
I'm sorry.
What do we do now?
Someone will come along to help us.
We just have to sit tight.
I haven't seen anybody else.
Have you?
Not for a long time.
Look, by tomorrow morning
we'll be back on the road.
We just have to find
this refugee camp.
It's- It's only a-
It's only a couple of hours away.
What's a refugee?
It's, um-
It's someone who, um-
Well, who likes to camp.
You know what?
We should try to
get some sleep, squirt.
I'm too scared to sleep.
Oh, come on.
Just like last summer.
King's Canyon?
When it rained so hard
on the tent...
you wanted to go sleep in the car.
It's just like that.
- Okay?
- Okay.
That's my girl.
What is it?
What do you see?
It's nothing.
I'm just, um-
You know, just-just thinking.
You know what?
I got an idea.
Here.
- Fix that up there.
- Okay.
- Up here.
- Hmm?
- There.
That's it.
- What are we doing?
- We are making a tent.
You're trying to
keep us safe, aren't you?
That's right.
- From Mommy?
- From...
whatever.
There.
How's that for a tent?
Marta said the last
thing she would ever do
was seal herself
up in her own tomb.
Yeah.
- Well, it's not like that.
- Why not?
Because it's not.
Ah-
Go on to sleep, all right?
Okay?
Good night, squirt.
Justine.
Dad?
Dad.
Hmm?
What is it?
Go back to sleep, squirt.
Dad.
It's nothing, Justine.
It's just the wind.
Justine.
Mommy?
I miss you.
I miss you so much.
Justine!
Justine, can you hear me?
Justine, get back here!
Justine, shout if you can hear me!
Justine!
Mommy?
Honey, can you hear me?
Justine!
No, don't! Don't!
Th-That is not your mother, Justine!
Oh, Jesus! Come here!
Come on, Justine!
Mommy! I want my mommy!
I want my mommy!
Stay put!
No! Let me out!
Justine- Please, Justine!
Let me out! Let me out!
I hate you! I hate you!
Please, Justine!
Justine, please! Listen!
I hate you!
- It's your fault! You killed Mommy!
- That is not your mommy!
- Shut up! Please! Please! Justine!
- You killed Mommy!
- Shut up! Shut up!
- I hate you!
Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
Oh, my- Oh, my God!
Hey. Hey, hey, hey. I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Justine, please! Please!
Oh, God. Oh, God, squirt.
I'm sorry.
Squirt, I didn't mean that.
I didn't mean that.
I didn't mean to do that.
Okay? I'm sorry.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry, okay?
Daddy's really sorry.
I will never-
If I went with her...
she wouldn't be so sad...
would she?
You killed her.
No, Justine.
Yes, you did.
Your fault.
What's that?
Come here.
I'm so sorry.
I love you so much.
Justine, wake up.
Come on, stop!
Please, please, please.
Oh, my God.
Attention. You will be
transferred to a secure location...
outside existing
cellular coverage zones.
All transferees will be supplied food,
shelter and necessary provisions...
till the crisis is past.
Hey, squirt, come here.
Squirt, there is a bus out there.
It is our ticket out of here. Okay?
When I give you the word,
I need you to run straight for the bus.
You can do that?
- Mm-hmm.
- Good girl.
Come on. Come over here.
Daddy's got you.
Okay, run. Run!
Justine, keep going!
Come on, squirt! Run!
Run! Come on!
You can do it. You can do it, kid.
Come on.
Come on. Come on.
- Justine, come on!
- She needs me.
No. Justine.
She is dead, and there's nothing
that we can do that can change that.
Come on.
Justine, look at me.
I will make this right.
I promise I will make this right.
Y-You have to believe in me.
C-Can you do that?
Then I need you to run
straight to the bus.
And whatever you do,
never look back.
Okay?
I love you with all my heart.
I love you too, Daddy.
Okay.
Now go.
I'll be right behind you.
I'm right behind you.
I love you...
always.
Daddy! Daddy!
Daddy!
- Hold on, little soldier! Not so fast.
- Let me go!
- No, no. You're coming with us!
- You're coming with us, sweetie.
No!
I know you'll never stop, Michelle.
And there's no
place that I can take
our daughter where she
won't try to find you...
and you her.
So if you feel that you need
to punish me for what
it is that I've done...
or if you just want someone
to share the loneliness...
then...
I'll come with you.
You can take me.
But please take me alone.
- I'm begging you. For Justine.
- Daddy!
Daddy!
Dad!
- Daddy!
- For your daughter.
For our- For our little girl.
Please.
- You'll be okay with us. I promise.
- No! No. No.
- Gonna take you-
- No! No!
You'll be okay.
We'll take care of you. I promise you.
- No!
- I got her. I got her.
I always loved you, Michelle.
Always and forever.
Thank you.
Ah.
It hurts now,
sweetheart.
It won't always.
Subtitles by LeapinLar