# S.P.D. Emergency! #
# Power Rangers S.P.D.
Power Rangers to the resuce #
# Heroes on your side
Heroes for all time #
# Out to save the universe #
# No matter where you are
if it's near or far #
# You can always call out #
# Space Patrol
Space Patrol #
Space Patrol Delta!
# Go, go
Go, go #
# Power Rangers, go #
# Power Rangers S.P.D.
Power Rangers to the resuce #
# Go, go, S.P.D. #
MAN: We have taken all we can
from Nelandia.
The life-forms have fled,
and the planet is useless to me.
Destroy it.
( Maniacal Laughter )
( Male Narrator )
In the not too distant future,
Earth has become a haven
for all alien races
who come from the fathest reaches
of the galaxy to live in peace.
Ninety-nine percent
of the newcomers live in harmony.
But for the one percent who can't...
Ah!
( Screaming, Gruntung )
...there is Space Patrol Delta.
The new breed of police
to bring them in.
MAN: You can hide, monster...
Well, actually, you can't really hide.
Perp at two o'clock.
- That's nine o'clock, Syd.
- Got it!
Fist of Iron!
Yah!
( Grunting )
Let's go!
Ha! Ah!
( Screaming )
( Groaning )
Sky Tate reporting in.
Mission complete. Please advise.
Well done, cadets.
Your training progresses nicely.
Uh, Kat... Ah...
I mean... Ma'am?
I mean... Miss Manx?
We were all wondering...
We know there's A Squad Power
Rangers, and we're B Squad cadets...
Not that there's anything wrong
with being B Squad,
- or C Squad or D Squad...
- SYD: Let me translate.
I speak fluent Bridge.
He wants to know
when we're getting designer suits.
Kat, I've told them, it's not about
the suits or the weapons.
It's about helping people
and upholding the tradition
of being a Power Ranger.
That's up to Commander Cruger.
Not me.
Dismissed.
( Groaning )
( Shrieking )
( Panting )
Best cadets ever, Kat.
Agreed.
And you, Boom, my eager assistant,
job well done.
- Get those charts.
- Yes, sir.
Right here. Great.
MAN: Coordinate 993 confirmed.
Commander Cruger,
we have a problem in the...
Ninth Quadrant. I am aware.
Nelandia has been destroyed.
There is not a lot of time
and much to be done.
He is coming.
Beware, Earth.
Your end has begun.
( Video Game Effects )
- Boom, did we do that?
- No.
You guys just dislocated my shoulder.
I popped it back in,
and it's good as gold. See? Ahh!
Anyway,
this is Kat's new arm cast laser.
Cool, huh?
Anyway, I got to go, so bye.
Aah! Ah!
- ( Crashing )
- Oh!
Boom! Clean up your mess.
Yes, sir. Sir... which mess?
Start with the last one you made
and work backwards.
Yes, sir.
Lighten up, Sky.
Boom's a great guy.
A little weird, but a great guy.
Yeah, well, some day our lives
may depend on that great guy,
and then what?
I know. I know.
Then our lives will depend on him.
Commander Cruger wants to see us. Now!
CRUGER: Listen carefully, A Squad.
Preparation is the key
to any tactical defence.
Report to Delta Air Base
for last-minute simulation instruction.
- Earth depends on you. Dismissed.
- ALL: Yes, sir!
CRUGER: Good luck, A Squad.
ALL: Hut! Hut! Hut!
Attention!
Ahh!
SKY: That is who I want to be.
I'm gonna be the Red Ranger.
Jeez, did you see the size of them?
Even the girls are massive.
What's wrong, Bridge?
I don't know.
Their energy, their colours...
something's off.
Cadets, I trust you've enjoyed
your training here at S.P.D. Academy.
Fluorescent lighting
gives me a bit of a headache...
( Growls )
Yes, sir.
CRUGER: Not that your training's ended,
or will it ever and while you're here,
but as your commander,
I must now call opon B Squad
to step up
and take on new responsibilities.
Yes!
I thought new responsibilities meant
kicking intergalactic freakazoid butt.
The data device says to
bring in Parkington Market thieves.
It's code, no doubt.
What do you think it means?
Bring in the Parkington Market thieves.
You know, Sky, you are good.
MAN: Stop, thieves!
Out of the way.
We don't want to hurt you.
- Hurt us? That's a good one.
- ( Groaning )
- S.P.D. We'll take it from here.
- Thank you.
You may not be coming in peacefully,
but you're coming in.
- What about me?
- Huh? Yah!
It's a hologram. It's not real.
Ah! Uh! OK, she's real.
Ha-ha.
Let's get 'em.
Got ya!
Aaah!
Huh?
There you are!
SKY: We got him.
Say good night, friend.
BOTH: Whoa!
( All Groaning )
I'm sorry we can't stay and play,
but we got to run. ( Laughs )
That went well.
CRUGER: You underestimated your
opponent and were soundly defeated.
We are so not ready to be Rangers.
I'm ready.
So it must have been Syd and I
who let those two get away then.
CRUGER: Listen to yourselves.
There is no team here.
This is the issue you have to overcome
before you can become a Power Ranger.
Oh, I get it, we have to stop blaming,
criticising and judging each other?
- Forgot failing to bring in suspects.
- Right.
Let's see, that puts us right
on schedule to be Rangers around...
...never!
You will meet those two again.
Sir, the civilians, they were different.
They had special abilities like we do.
Yes, I know.
Cadet Tate, come with me.
- Thank you.
Jack...
We've been on the streets
a long time together.
You're my best friend.
You're like my brother.
And, brother,
after five years of doing this,
I say we change careers.
I'm tired of playing Robin Hood.
( Cooing )
Oh, ah... I'm sorry.
We don't have anything else
to give out. Maybe tomorrow.
( Sighing )
Wait! Wait.
Oh! ( Cooing )
What? She needed it.
Maybe her husband did. Or her child.
OK. OK, you're right.
We got to do something else.
- OK.
- But after we do one more job.
Jack, do you think
some more food and some clothes
are gonna make a difference?
If we're gonna make a change, we
have to be part of something bigger.
Yeah, well, when you find
something bigger, let me know.
- Why Red Ranger, cadet?
- Lots of reasons, sir.
I'm top on B Squad in test scores,
weaponry and in fighting.
As you know, sir,
my father was the Red Ranger.
Ever since I was a kid,
I've trained for the day
I become like my dad...
the next Red Ranger.
Your father was the best
of the best of Rangers.
If you're anything like him,
we will all benefit by your service.
- Dismissed.
- Thank you, sir.
Cadet, if I was
to appoint Syd as Red Ranger,
would you follow her into battle?
Sir, she's a girl.
Or Bridge?
I like Bridge, but in all honesty,
sir, he's not a leader.
I see.
Thank you for your honesty, cadet.
That will be all.
Sir.
Hmm.
MAN: A Sirian space web.
Anubis Doggie Cruger is still alive.
The web is strong.
I need a Proton Accelerator
to move my ship through it.
I have a contact on the Earth planet
who will be able to get me one.
My ship may not
be able to get through now,
but a robot can.
Get me what I ask,
and let no one stop you.
Yes, master.
I told you this would be a great score.
Good work, Z.
You know, Z, if we put
all of yourselves together,
we could get unlimited amounts
of food and clothes...
No, Jack! This is my last job
for me and all myselves,
or we're packing up
and doing it alone. You got it?
MAN: Help me!
Take this! And don't let them have it!
The future of the planet
depends on it! Hide it!
Ah... Ohh!
( Screaming )
( Both Laughing )
Why do the nuts of the world
always seem to find you?
Just lucky, I guess.
Yes!
Fifty-five times in a row! ( Cheering )
OK, enough!
I'm officially bored to tears.
We get called to report
an hour ago, to who?
- Whom?
- Never correct me again!
I'm sorry.
I'm just tense watching Walk-a-thon
Boy wear a path in the floor.
If you have a problem with it,
Sydney, make me stop.
OK. I may be a girl
and I may be cute, but no one...
I trust you're using this time
to bond as a team?
- ALL: Yes, sir!
- Good. Come this way.
Without going into details,
Earth's survival dictates
that I elevate your team
to active status. Any questions?
Um... Yeah, just one.
Did you say ultimate survival,
as in, Earth may be destroyed?
I did.
Cadets, you have spent the last
two years in simulated training.
But this time, the game is real.
S.P.D. morphers.
They are, without a doubt,
your best friend.
They are also judgement scanners.
They will assess
the guilt or innocence
of those you take into custody.
Boom,
guilty or innocent of eating
the last slice of cake today?
BOOM: Me? I...
I... ( Giggling )
No. No, no, I didn't.
The scanner reads body temperature,
pulse and electrical impulses,
then renders a verdict. Guilty.
- But...
- KAT: And it does not make mistakes.
OK. I'm guilty.
But it was a just a piece of cake!
BOOM: OK. Time to let Boom out now.
This makes transportation
of the detainee a non-issue.
- BOOM: Kat?
- You are trained and now equipped.
You are the new B Squad Power
Rangers. Congratulations.
- Yes!
- Celebration can come later.
I need immediate assistance
on an urgent matter.
- ALL: Yes, sir.
- Follow me.
BOOM: Hello? Kat! Hello?
I will never eat chocolate cake again!
CRUGER: Coordinates
of the street thieves' location
is locked into
your vehicle's computers.
( Siren Sounding )
- Thank you.
- This is all that's left.
If you can't eat it or wear it,
it has no value.
Ha!
Did you see how much those people
appreciated what we gave them?
Yeah. Kind of gave me that warm
and fuzzy feeling that I hate so much.
And no, I didn't change my mind
about wanting to do something bigger.
Nice to see you two again.
I told you we should have quit
while we were ahead.
Don't worry. I'll take care of this,
and we'll be on our way.
Jack!
Guess what?
You're not the only one with tricks.
- Jack, let's get out of here.
- Can't do that.
We need to finish this here and now,
or these clowns will bug us forever.
Listen, I think we should go about this
in the smoothest
and most repectful way,
each valuing each others'
humanity and dignity and...
Or not.
Hiya!
( Grunting, Panting )
We're not doing as well as before, bro.
Any suggestions?
Run?
Huh?
You're accused of stealing
and distributing stolen goods.
- Can you prove it?
- Actually, yes, we can.
- BRIDGE: Guilty.
- Any chance of going two out of three?
Didn't think so.
- Wait!
- What is it?
- What are you gonna do with us?
- It's quite fascinating.
We're going to blast you
with anti-matter fusion
which reduces you to
approximately this big and this thin.
Simultaneously, you're inserted
into a confinement card
where you're shipped off
for filing until... your time is served.
You had to ask, Z.
You do the crime, you pay the time.
- I always wanted to say that.
- Enough with the small talk.
( Gasps )
( Growls )
- Huh?
- ( Robotic Whirring )
That's OK.
A few extra friends won't bother us.
Hate to break it to you,
but these aren't our friends.
So with our deepest apologies,
we'll take this opportunity
to be on our way.
Good luck. Let's go, Z.
Captioned by Grantman Brown