This is the story
of a time long ago.
A time of myth and legend,
when the earth
was still young.
The ancient gods
were petty and cruel,
and they played mankind
for their sport.
Aaaagh!
Plaguing them with suffering,
besieging them with terrors.
( laughing )
For centuries, the people
had nowhere to turn,
no one to look to for help.
Until... he arrived.
He was man
like no other.
Born of a beautiful
mortal woman,
but fathered by Zeus,
king of the gods.
Hercules possessed strength
the world had never seen,
a strength surpassed
only by the power of his heart.
But everywhere he went he was
tormented by his stepmother,
Hera, the all-powerful
queen of the gods.
Hera's eternal obsession
was to destroy Hercules,
for he was the constant
living reminder of Zeus' infidelity.
No matter the obstacle,
as long as there were people
crying for help,
there was one man
who would never rest:
Hercules.
( Panting )
You came searching
for Hercules...
- but instead you found your death!
- ( Yells )
( Gurgling )
Hera killed him!
It's only us now!
We must find Hercules
before it's too late!
We're almost there.
You're the last!
It's up to you!
( Groans )
( Thundering Footsteps )
( Footsteps Continue )
( Screams )
( Cow Mooing )
( Chickens Squawking )
There's a giant coming!
- There's a giant coming!
- Where is that water I sent you to get?
- I've told you before: You don't work,
you don't eat!     - But it's true!
I saw him! He's huge!
The ground started to shake--
- "The ground started to shake." What, like this?
- ( Footsteps Approaching )
No, like that!
( Footsteps Continue )
MAN: It can't be.
Shut the door!
Here! Right away!
( Footsteps Continue )
- ( Giant Growling )
- ( Woman Screams )
( Giant Growling )
Please. Anything you want.
I want Hercules!
MAN: Hercules?
There's no Hercules here.
What would Hercules be doing
in a crummy place like this?
- Then I kill everybody.
- ( Crowd Protesting )
MAN: Please!
( Giant Growling )
I'm Hercules.
What can I do for you?
( Laughing ) You are Hercules?
I didn't come all this way
to kill something as small as you.
- Fine by me.
( Giant Grumbles )
Look, why don't you sit down,
have some stew.
First, you.
Then, stew.
Come on, little man.
( Crowd Chattering )
Be careful.
You know,
this really isn't necessary.
- Oh, yes, it is.
- ( Crowd Gasps )
( Grunting, Laughing )
- ( Continues Laughing )
- Look!
You don't have to do this--
( Giant Grunting, Laughing )
( Growd Groans )
Looks like Hercules has
finally met this match.
I beg your pardon, sir.
I don't think so.
- What do you know, old man?
- Oh, I know about these things.
- ( Laughing )
- Maybe we do have to do this.
( Giant Growling )
( Laughing )
( Crowd Gasps )
( Groaning )
( Giant Groaning )
( Continues Groaning )
( Groaning Continues )
Now I kill you!
- ( Giant Gasps )
- ( Crowd Cheering )
( Cheering )
Huh?
Here's to Hercules,
slayer of giants!
( Crowd Cheering )
Bravo!
Our little village will be famous
forever. To show our appreciation...
- we're going to build a shrine to you, Hercules!
- ( Crowd Cheering )
No shrine, thanks.
I wouldn't know
what to do with one.
- ( Chuckles )
- But you must want something.
- All the gods want something.
- I'm not a god.
I don't want anything.
I just want to finish my meal.
( Panting, Gasps )
Hercules, look.
( Gasping )
Are you Hercules?
- A hundred of us were sent to find you.
- Bring him water.
You're safe here.
Where are the rest?
Dead. All dead.
Killed by the queen
of the gods.
She didn't want us to find you.
- Hera.
- Hercules...
you have to help us.
We've been driven
from our city...
and all our best warriors killed.
We've done nothing wrong...
and still the goddess punishes us.
Please, take our side.
Help us.
- What city is this, my friend?
- The lost city of Troy.
Troy? Troy?
- I'll find it.
- But you can't.
It's lost in the mist.
Only I can lead you back.
Then you will.
Now drink and rest.
( Gasping )
( Gasping Continues )
( Crowd Gasping )
( Thunder Rumbling )
- WOMAN: What has happened?
- MAN: Stay away from Troy.
Hey, wait a mintue.
- Where do you think you're going?
- ( Chuckles )
- You were great with that giant.
- Forget about the giant.
- How do I find Troy?
- Hercules, don't get involved.
Involved? Hera killed
that messenger in my arms.
She does strange things.
She's the queen of the gods.
- You're supposed to be king.
- Who says I'm not?
Hercules, if you were only
nice to your stepmother.
I mean, if you went into one of
her temples and did a small sacrifice.
- You've got to be kidding.
- Then you'll never find Troy.
She's vanished it.
So you're not gonna
help me, again.
Oh, how can I explain?
I can't.
Fine. Thanks, Father.
- Hey, w-wait a second.
Wait a second.
I probably shouldn't tell you this...
but you must find
the one, true compass.
It points directly to Troy.
King Omphale had it last.
( Thunder Rumbling )
I can't tell you any more.
You'll have to find it yourself.
Why don't you come with me?
Oh, if I were only
a thousand years younger...
and single.
##( Chanting )##
##( Drumming, Chanting )##
##( Natives Continue Chanting )##
- Excuse me. Excuse me, sir.
- ##( Chanting Continues )##
- Whose shrine is this?
- The shrine of the water god.
He withholds the rain,
and we have nothing to eat.
##( Continues )##
Eat this stuff
before it goes bad.
No, no! This is for the water god,
in case he gets hungry while waiting.
- What's he waiting for?
- The virgin.
She's going to fall
to her death in honor of him.
Sir, human sacrifices don't work.
I'm going to bring her
down from there.
##( Chanting Continues )##
##( Continues )##
What are you doing?
Go away.
You're interrupting
a religious ceremony.
Yeah, well, if you're sacrificing
yourself to the water god...
he's not home.
You're wasting your time.
- ( Screams )
- See? What did I tell you?
That was close.
You almost fell.
( Grunts ) I was supposed
to fall, you idiot!
Didn't you ever
see a sacrifice?
A maiden at the height of her fertility
is the only thing that can save the crops.
( Gasps )
So you're a maiden
at the height of her fertility?
You've spoiled it.
It took all morning
for the rope to burn through.
You have no right to interfere
with my destiny with the gods.
Take my word for it.
The gods don't care about your destiny.
- And who are you that you know so much?
- I'm Hercules.
Your parents named you after Hercules?
What a laugh.
I don't have time for this.
I have to get to Troy.
No! Put me down!
This is between me and the gods.
Would you stop squirming
or we'll both fall.
What's the matter
with your people?
She said her destiny
is to be with the gods.
The gods don't care
about her or you.
My own father's one.
I wouldn't trust him with my sister...
- if I had a sister.
- Which I hope you don't.
Which I'm glad I don't.
Forget the gods.
You can get along without them.
If it doesn't rain, irrigate.
I wouldn't stay here
if I were you.
Hey!
If you really are Hercules...
then, obviously, I wasn't meant
to drown in that mud hole...
which is why you came along.
You're part of my destiny...
- which means you're working for me.
- Look, kid...
I've already got
something important to do.
There's a whole city
waiting for my help.
Unfortunately, it's a lost city,
which makes it harder to find.
But you must have been sent to help me,
whether you know it or not.
I've decided the best thing to do
is to travel together.
- Is that right?
- That's right.
Until the gods show me a sign.
If you're gonna follow me,
you better keep up with me.
I can keep up with you.
- What's your name?
- Deianeira.
Well, Deianeira...
when was the last time you ate?
I never eat.
Food's a luxury I don't have time for.
So, of course, it was only natural
I'd give my life over to public service.
See, my father was
this really handsome king...
who loved me more than
anything in the world.
But then when his kingdom
was threatened...
he sent me away
for my own good.
I think he made quite
a sacrifice, don't you?
That's a well-known fairy tale,
Deianeira.
My mother used to tell it to me.
Who told it to you?
I told it to myself, all right?
- You don't think orphans need fairy tales too?
- Sure I do.
- We all do.
- What do you know about it? Your father's a god.
Well, he wasn't home much,
I can tell you that.
Yeah, well...
my father is this really
homesome king...
who love me more than
anything in the world.
Sweet dreams, kid.
Who are you?
Why do you follow me?
If you're protecting me, here I am.
I could use protecting.
Wait!
- Who are you talking to?
- Nobody.
I heard you--
DEIANERIA: Don't just stand there.
You're blocking the road!
Will you get out of my way,
you mountain of meat?
- No one passes today.
- I've come to speak to the king.
- The king is dead.
- The king's dead?
- That's right.
- I was sent by Zeus himself.
There must be someone I can see.
It's very important. Come on.
Too bad. You and Zeus are
six years late.
- And no one passes today.
- Do you know who you're talking to?
This is Hercules.
You better get out of our way.
Or he'll crush your skull like a
bird egg and make all the gooop run out.
Please.
Well, who's in charge of the kingdom?
I have to see him.
Our queen sees no one.
She appears in public...
- only once a year at the great slave market.
- Which is today.
The slave market?
That's outrageous.
How'd you like to be a slave?
But I guess you already are.
Slaves to the slave market.
Does she belong to you?
- You could teach her some manners.
- She belongs to no one.
Twin half- wits, huh?
Mom and Dad must be really proud.
Come here! We can get more for her at
the market after I cut out her tongue.
- This will just take a moment.
- Yeah, I know.
- ( Yells )
- ( Grunting )
Wow.
From now on, be quiet.
I'll do the talking.
I was only trying to help.
- I don't need your help.
- You're so ungrateful.
- You don't thank me. All you do is tell me
what to do. - Remember what I told you.
- Let you do the talking.
- That's right.
Greetings.
I'm here to see the queen.
- I was sent by the king of the gods.
- How did you pass the brothers?
Stop him, Brothers!
Prepare to die, trespasser!
( Both Grunting )
Don't let him get away!
- ( Grunts )
- ( Yelling, Groans )
I love this.
I'm glad you're enjoying yourself.
How many of you brothers
are there?
We are the 48 sons of Martinus,
guardians of the gate.
On the blood of my brothers,
now you will die!
- ( Yells )
- And now you will die!
( Brother Growling )
- ( Brothers Gasp )
- Only 42 more to go.
- Not that way.
- What?
- How'd I ever get mixed up with you anyway?
- Oh, that's great.
Why are we sneaking in?
We were doing great.
I have to talk to the queen
about a compass...
not leave a trail of bodies
48-brothers long.
Surely there must be
as easier way than this.
- ( Deianeira Screams )
- ( Chickens Squawking )
( Groaning )
What did you push me for?
- I didn't push you. You fell.
- No, you pushed me.
Now, listen, behave yourself.
This is a big city,
so keep your mouth shut.
Don't tell me what to do.
I've been in a big city before.
( Crowd Chattering, Sheep Bleating )
( Chattering Continues )
Tomatoes, sweet and beautiful.
Hey, hey, try my rabbit.
Try it.
- Hungry?
- Yeah.
- How much?
- For you, nothing.
Tell your friends.
Tell them, tell them!
This rabbit tastes funny.
That's because it's possum.
- ( Spits, Gagging )
- MAN: Welcome!
Welcome, everyone,
to the queen's slave market!
For our first item today, we have this
attractive former princess of Thessaly.
Still listed as a virgin...
and with excellent references
up and down the country.
She's anxious to find
a domestic position...
and she can start immediately.
Now what am I bid?
Who can--
( Gong Sounds )
( Crowd Murmuring )
( Murmuring Continues )
How are you gonna get
to meet her?
( Crowd Murmuring )
( Murmuring Continues )
I'll think of something.
So, you're calling him Hercules, huh?
It might work.
He is Hercules.
Look at him.
Ouch.
You convinced me, kid.
Like to come this way,
uh, Hercules.
And here we have Hercules,
son of Zeus!
Available today only,
for one day...
to clear fields,
move heavy objects...
of you name the labor.
At ten dinar,
who'll open the bidding?
( Crowd Shouting Bids )
( Bidding Continues )
( Crowd Continues Bidding )
( Gond Sounds,
Bidding Continues )
- ( Bidding Continues )
- Sold to Her Highness, Queen Omphale.
( Bidders Groaning )
May Her Majesty find
much pleasure in him!
Your Highness.
- I'll take this to him.
- As you wish.
Thank you, Waylin.
( Doors Close )
- Are you comfortable?
- Too much so.
Queen Omphale,
I put myself up for sale...
because it was the only way
I could get to see you.
I'm on journey
to the lost city of Troy.
Zeus told me your husband has the only
compass that could lead me to it.
There's plenty of time for that
when you're completed your work here.
- ( Sets Down Drink )
- Of course.
- What is it you want of me?
- Hercules, the best thing about being queen...
is that I can make a holiday
whenever I want.
I've decided no one will work
in my kingdom today.
So rest here,
and tomorrow we'll see.
Apologies, My Queen.
You only have me for the day.
But I paid for a thousand days.
- ( Coins Clink )
- But this is way too much for one day's work.
( Shushing ) If you find
any more Hercules like that...
you just bring them to me.
- Is someone hitting his door--
- With a rock?
Yeah, me.
Where's Hercules?
I need to talk to him.
This door is over
a thousand years old...
and, in five minutes,
you've made dents in it.
Excuse me, eunuch. I just gave you
a message to give to Hercules.
Hercules is unavailable
for the foreseeable future.
- I'm not a eunuch, I'm a slave.
- What's the difference?
( Scoffs ) Uh--
I'll tell you
when you grow up.
Lovely kumquats,
two for a dinar.
- I hate kumquats.
- I make a bargain.
- ( Groaning )
- ( Dog Barking )
- Guards.
- ( Gasps )
( Chattering, Indistinct )
( Laughing )
You're a funny man, Waylin.
( Patrons Chattering )
( Chattering Continues )
- Hey! Watch it!
- Excuse me.
- ( Growls )
- WOMAN: Welcome, slave.
Do I look like a slave?
Just give me the menu.
- I'll be back in a minute.
DEIANEIRA: I'll have the wild chicken.
- And to drink?
- She doesn't like slaves.
- That--   - You can be frank here,
even tyrannical, if you want.
- She's a master?
- Look, can I get some service or what?
Why don't you come to my table, huh?
The wild chicken's gonna take a while.
First, you gotta chase 'em,
then you gotta catch 'em.
- These girls work for the government too.
- Mm-hmm.
- You're all slave? Happy slaves?
- We have financial security...
steady work and no chance
of being fired.
- You're miserable, and you don't even know it.
- ( Laughing )
You should be fighting to be free,
fighting to the death.
- Appetizer.
- Food.
When was the last time you ate?
We get three squares a day working for the
government and a roof over our heads.
- Mm-hmm.
- A toast to Queen Omphale.
Salute.
You call this a chicken?
It's small and tough because it had
to make it on its own.
No offense.
( Patrons Chattering )
- WAYLIN: Oh, no, it's Melus.
- ( Gasps )
You don't pay your protection money...
how we gonna protect you?
Just a moment, you.
I am Princess Deianeira
of Thessalonia...
and these slaves belong
to the royal household.
It's just business, miss.
How much do they owe?
Ten dinars a week,
three weeks behind.
( Puts Down Coins )
Very sensible...
Princess.
Don't be smug with me,
you arrogant bucket of slop.
( Patrons Gasp, Murmur )
Very well.
And know that if my men find any
impersonators to your royal family...
we'll honor you
by slitting their throats.
( Door Opens, Closes )
Whatever you paid him,
he'll just want double next week.
Unless you really are a princess.
You slept well, I trust.
You must be hungry.
I've no right to rest like this.
- My journey is urgent.
- Eat something. You need your strength.
What I need is the compass
that points me to Troy.
OMPHALE: These are my late husband's
navigational instruments.
With them, he traversed the world.
They can guide you
to where you want to go.
Take what you want of them.
They mean nothing to me.
Thank you, Queen Omphale.
I know this will take me to Troy.
Don't-- Hey, listen,
I know Hercules is in there.
You're squashing my foot!
Tell Hercules his friend,
Deianeria's waiting...
and if doesn't come out soon,
she might not be waiting anymore.
( Gasping, Groans )
( Door Closes )
Princess Sayonara of Thessalonia.
Do I have it right? Or is it, by any
chance, Princess Dead Squirrel Meat?
Kill everything, except her tongue.
Bring that to me.
I want to watch it flap in the dirt.
- ( Grunting )
- ( Men Groaning )
Get her!
Out of the way!
- ( Panting )
- ( Chuckling )
- We got her.
- That was easy.
( Screaming )
Hercules?
Hercules, wait.
it's you. You saved me.
I must go.
But you've been following me
since I was a kid.
I want to know why.
Hey, I'm talking to you.
As you follow your destiny,
I follow you.
Follow my destiny?
What is my destiny? Tell me!
Are you ready to travel? Or maybe
you need another couple of days in bed.
This will get us to Troy.
The queen was very generous.
( Scoffs ) Of course,
you couldn't say no.
Let's go, Deianeira.
Time's wasting.
Not so fast.
I made plans for lunch.
Come on.
( Patrons Chattering, Gasping )
You paid last time,
so you can pay again.
- WOMAN: I didn't. I couldn't.
- Excuse me.
Is there a problem?
Not if you got 30 dinars, slave.
Why don't you just
leave people alone?
Mm-hmm, yeah, sure.
( Women Screaming )
( Grunts, Screaming )
( Screaming )
- ( Grunts )
- Huh?
( Screams, Groans )
- MAN: Look out!
- ( Groans )
( Screaming )
DEIANERIA: Sorry.
Good-bye, Waylin.
Master, every cringing cur
in the kingdom owes you obedience.
I thank you from the bottom
of my servile soul for saving my life.
It's no problem.
I enjoyed it.
Bye, Waylin.
Don't be a slave all your life.
I have no choice.
Can I try?
Sure.
Get back here.
This way.
( Bird Screeching )
DEIANERIA: How far is this Troy anyway?
Hercules, something's
been bothering me.
If you are a god,
then you could answer it.
What bothers you?
I wonder if maybe I am one.
- A god?
- Mm-hmm.
- Don't be a god.
- It's not up to me, is it?
- Be a girl, and then a woman.
- Just a woman?
My mother's "just a woman,"
and everyone loves her.
Which is why Hera hates my guts.
Look, I know the gods,
and most of them are bums.
They kick people around
because they're bored...
or because some other god
tweaked their nose.
They live forever.
It makes them crazy and mean.
- What about you? Are you immortal?
- You want to know?
- Mm-hmm.
- So do I.
All I can tell you
is when the sun's out...
I'm gonna live forever.
Then at night...
when I can't sleep
and the worries come creeping in...
the next monster's
gonna get me for sure.
- ( Rustling )
- You said somebody's been following you?
Yes, since I was a kid.
Stay here.
( Owl Hooting )
( Hooting Continues )
( Strange Snort )
( Snoring )
( Gasps ) Hello.
HERCULES: I don't need
a slave, Waylin.
I appreciate the offer,
but it just wouldn't work out.
You saved my life
back at the bar.
I've decided to devote the rest
of my time to your service.
- Don't you want to be free?
- I can serve as a free man.
- I don't need a free man either.
- I don't think you realize...
how truly useful
an obsequious person can be.
( Brushing )
You worm! Haven't you got
any self-respect? Look at yourself!
Hey, what do you want?
I'm a professional slave.
It's what I do,
and I do it well.
You have to admire a man
who knows what he's good at.
I await your command.
All right. Here's my command.
Return directly
to Omphale's kingdom...
and serve her
for the rest of your life.
Is that what you really want?
Yes!
Then I must obey.
You'll never see me again,
either of you.
But know this, master:
Whomever I serve in the future...
I dedicate my servitude to you.
Waylin--
Thank you.
Great.
We come all this way...
and now your one, true compass
is pointing to nowhere.
( Scoffs )
I suppose it's broken now.
It's not broken.
Well, my destiny
doesn't stop here.
Somebody's did.
Look at this boneyard.
Troy must be on the other side
of this ocean.
How are we going to get across?
We don't have a boat.
Rise.
Rise, Blue Serpent...
and to the work
that Hera asks of you.
Hercules, I feel
something happening.
HERCULES: Who is that? Is that
the man who's been following you?
It's my protector,
Hercules. ( Gasps )
Some protector.
- ( Roaring )
- ( Deianeira Screams )
( Screaming )
Did you see that?
It came straight for me.
- I noticed.
- I told you my place was with the gods.
Deianeira, I don't think
the gods hang out in here.
But they accepted me.
That's all that matters.
I don't know why you're excited.
We're about to be digested.
Don't you understand?
This is supposed to happen.
No, that's what's supposed to happen.
That's the wrong way out.
This way.
( Heart Beating )
Stay here.
( Beating Continues )
- ( Gasps )
- Hold on. I'll come back for you.
- ( Screeching )
- ( Deianeira Gasps )
( Whimpering )
( Gasping, Screaming )
( Deianeira Screams )
Hercules, there's something in here!
( Heart Beating )
( Continues Beating )
( Screams )
- ( Screeching )
- No!
- ( Heart Beating )
- ( Grunting )
( Serpent Groaning )
- ( Screams )
- ( Screeching )
Did you kill it? Did you kill it?
Is it dead? Is it dead?
It's dead!
We've got to get outta here!
- ( Panting )
- Give me your hand.
( Gulls Screeching )
( Screeching Continues )
It's Troy, Hercules.
HERCULES: How do you know?
I remember now.
It's where I'm from.
Why are you stopping now?
We're almost there?
HERCULES: Something's not right.
We could be walking into a trap.
Hercules, you still don't believe
my whole life's been a journey here.
Whatever the gods intend...
- I will fulfill, with or without you.
- I'm pretty sure it's a trap.
Then without you, and fine by me.
( Yells )
( Struggling )
( Sighs ) Of course,
I could be wrong.
Will you get me down?
Get me down, Hercules!
I've already killed you, spy,
but for information to please my king...
- I may loan you back your life.
- Kill him, Hercules!
( Sighs )
- We're your prisoners. We won't resist.
- The hell we are!
- I'll die right here before you keep me from my city.
- Your city?
The city is ours, and though
we may live in the woods now...
the people of Troy will one day retake
their homes and be exiles no more.
Take us to your king.
Hercules, you want us to be captured?
I bow to no king.
- ( Strikes Sword )
- ( Deianeira Gasps )
You will bow
to the King of Troy...
who knew you landed the instant
your foot touched our shore.
( Indistinct Chattering )
( Child Chattering )
( Sheep Bleating )
( Chattering Continues )
CAPTOR: Up the stairs.
( Bleating Continues )
( Dog Barking )
( People Murmuring )
- You found her.
- As you predicted, My King.
- An easy snare.
- Hey, what's going on here?
Tell me your name, young woman.
- Deianeira.
I don't understand.
I thought they were spies.
Will you leave us, my friends?
Are you my father?
Yes.
Yeah, but I gotta
figure this out.
You're king.
The king of what?
The King of Troy?
How come you live in the woods?
Your words still spill out.
Deianeira, I did a terrible thing...
which I've kept hidden
all these years.
You were such a beautiful child...
that Hera demanded
I sacrifice you...
to her sea monster.
I couldn't do it.
I sent away,
across the sea.
Yes, I saved you...
but Hera was angry.
She sent Blue Priest
to drive us out of the city...
to live in the forest as exiles.
And only I knew why.
Because of me.
I loved you too much.
I sacrificed all of Troy...
for one, tiny girl.
No, you sacrificed your own heart
to keep me alive.
I found my way back,
as you knew I would.
I will never leave you again.
I'm glad I waited.
The people need you, my daughter.
Lead them well.
( Gasps )
- Father?
- I have what I want.
The rest is yours.
Father?
( Crying )
Please don't go, Father.
Father.
( Chattering )
( Chattering Continues )
The King, my father, is dead.
- CROWD: No.
- He taught us how to live...
when we were driven
from Troy...
and that the spirit
of our people cannot be broken.
We must never forget him
and the city that he loved.
- This is Hercules.
- CROWD: Hercules.
He can teach us how to fight
and win back our homes.
( Crowd Chattering )
Yes. Yes.
( Chattering Continues )
Let's charge the city right now,
Hercules, and see...
how many each one of us
kills before he dies.
There must be a better way
than a frontal attack.
That would be the coward's way.
Well, we certainly wouldn't want to take
the coward's way, would we, Telamon?
Because that way some of us
might get out of this alive.
I think we should go back now.
The girl is here.
I can feel her presence.
She will not escape me this time.
- Prepare the sacrificial chamber.
- It shall be done.
( Swords Clanking )
( All Yell )
Come out!
Come out, spy!
I'm not a spy!
Whoa! I'm a slave!
Well, the people of Troy
do not allow slaves.
That's all right.
I'm used to prejudice.
- You're coming with me. Come on!
- Careful, it's a thin cloth.
Go on! Get a move on.
Move, move.
- After you.
- Straight up the hill.
- Oh.
- Come on.
Ooh, Zeus, it's a nice day.
No. Face the target
at a right angle.
Don't square off, okay?
You want to grip
the bow in the middle.
Hold onto it like you have
a bird in your hand.
Maybe we should find
a different weapon for you.
- Use your back more when you draw back.
- All right.
Deianeira, you have to get
yourself into a rhythm,
You notch...
draw..
aim...
release.
That's good.
You have steady hands.
You can make them tremble.
Uh, next time,
bend your left elbow a little more.
Pull back on that more,
using your back. Good.
You shoot well.
So why do we need him?
( Chuckles )
He's Hercules.
WAYLIN: Ow! I work a lot better
without a knife in my back!
- Just get on there.
- Excuse me. What's your name?
- Just keep moving!
- "Just keep moving"? Is that a first name or a last?
- Just keep moving.
- DEIANEIRA: Waylin!
- How did you find us?
- Oh, it wasn't easy. I wore the wrong shoes.
Waylin, what are you doing here?
Hercules, you know,
the more I thought about it...
the more I think
you're making a big mistake.
You need me as a slave,
a good slave...
a slave who knows
how to be obedient...
- even if it means being a pain in the ass.
- "Obedient"?
I ordered you home,
and you've disobeyed me.
That's a good point.
But what I'm trying to tell you,
without being obsequious...
is that my place
is here with you.
Yeah.
Give me that.
Come with me.
Can we get something to eat?
MAN: What do you think, Hercules?
Do we stand a chance?
I've watched you training.
There's nothing wrong
with your swords or your bows...
but the enemy has them too.
It's difficult to be a warrior.
It's not easy to kill.
You have to make yourself hard.
I want every fighter to find
his own rock and study it.
You have weapons
for your hands already.
Make a rock your weapon within...
because a rock has no mind or heart...
or hope or fear.
If you're to succeed in battle, you must
rid yourselves of all of that...
and be hard.
If we have to be hard like rocks...
to win our city back...
then we'll be rocks.
You'll see. Won't we?
( Crowd Cheering )
Yes! Won't we!
( Cheering Continues )
The people know
that you're behind us.
It means everything
to them, Hercules.
Thank you.
They still have to fight.
They just don't get
the idea of combat.
They think too much.
They've memorized how to shoot an arrow.
If you memorized how to walk,
you'd never get across a room.
Why don't you ever look at me?
Huh?
Soon I may be dead,
and you never look at me.
I've changed.
Can you see it?
Deianeira, beauty's not important.
It's your spirit everybody likes.
- You don't think I'm beautiful?
- Sure. That's not what I mean.
Would you ever want to kiss me?
I don't think so.
How about now?
Now?
No.
Deianeira, wait!
I think...
you're a born leader.
I mean, you're
doing a great job.
Don't make it worse, Hercules.
Quit following me
everywhere I go!
I'm not.
It's a great city, isn't it?
Yes, it is.
And you plan to attack it?
I don't think it's a good idea.
Hera likes the Blue Cult.
- Yeah, she would.
- Can't talk you out of it?
No.
Troy belongs to these people, not Hera.
Why don't you join us?
We'd be side-by-side for once,
fighting for a good cause.
I haven't been in a real war
for... years.
- Still got it in you?
- What a question.
( Laughs )
Of course I have, son.
Did you see that?
That means Zeus himself is on our side!
( Cheering )
- That's a nice shot...
- ( Cheering Continues )
but are you going
to help us or not?
I've got things to do.
I'll lead them myself.
We'll fight our way in
and keep fighting.
- If--
- HERCULES: Good, you're together.
We attack at dawn.
Dawn? Why don't we
attack tonight?
Because we attack at dawn.
The truth is, I didn't think
we could do it before.
I thought I'd just be leading
our people to certain death.
But with the thunderbolt, I know we'll
win because the gods are on our side.
There's not going to be
any more thunderbolts.
But I saw it.
- Zeus is your father. He'll help us.
- Forget about Zeus.
Dawn's in a few hours.
The fighting will be bloody,
so you better be prepared.
DEIANEIRA: I must do something
or they'll all be killed.
Priest, where are you?
I can't let this happen.
Come to me, Deianeira.
Fulfill your true destiny.
Hera will open her arms to you.
Deianeira, it's dawn.
Time to go.
She's not here.
What are you doing here?
Where's Deianeira?
- I thought she was with you.
- That was hours ago.
Waylin, have you seen Deianeira?
She passed me in the middle of the night.
I thought she came back to her hut.
I saw her go into the woods
to ward the city.
Hercules, she must have gone.
And, by the gods, she's gone alone.
- All right, you stay here. I'm going after her myself.
- So am I.
- I'm going as well.
- Me too! Who's game for the attack?
- ( Crowd Yelling )
- Let's get Deianeira and take the city back!
No. No!
There'll be no attack!
- I'm going alone!
- I'm going, and you can't stop me.
But you'll both be killed.
There must be another way.
I refuse to take
the coward's way.
I'm going, not you.
Telamon, just so you know,
I don't need you to tell me...
How there's a hero's way
and a coward's way.
Coward's way.
You're right.
The cowherd's way.
Why didn't I think of it?
- What, now you?
- Not "coward's way." " Cowherd's way. "
I remember before we left the city...
the men who herded the cows didn't like
to use the main gate.
It took too long to get down to the
oasture. They had a shortcut, a tunnel.
- That's right.
- It got them to the pasture quicker.
We called it
the cowherd's way.
- You mean there's a tunnel to the city?
- Yeah.
- Where exactly is this cowherd's way?
- It's down in the brush.
It's all grown over.
Nobody's used it for years.
- Show me.
- Yeah, come on!
Here it is.
MAN: That's it, Hercules.
Remember your training now.
Stay alert.
Shh!
Quiet.
WAYLIN: There's nobody here.
Well, what happened?
It's a little run-down
for a big city. It's too quiet.
I don't like ot so quiet. I like
it better when people are talking.
- Waylin!
- Yes, master.
Stay here.
I'm going alone.
- We came to fight.
- Look around you.
The doors were open.
There's nothing to see.
You can't fight
what you can't see.
You're in charge now, Telamon.
Keep them here.
Hercules worries too much.
There's nobody here.
If there were somebody here,
they'd come out, wouldn't they?
Otherwise, what's to stop us
from coming in?
( Gates Rumbling, Latch )
I'm Telamon, warrior of Troy!
Are these empty walls
my only challenge?
( Yelling )
( Monks Yelling )
( Continue Yelling )
Deianeira!
WAYLIN: Telamon, no!
( Gasps, Groans )
Get up, Telamon!
Don't quit!
Waylin, are you crazy?
Telamon's dead!
We'll all be dead
without Hercules!
- ( Monks Chanting )
- Deianeira!
Go away, Hercules.
You'll spoil everything.
Deianeira... come to me.
( Yells )
We don't need Hercules.
I've got Hercules in here.
( Woman Shouts )
Come on, fish face.
I'm not afraid of you!
Don't be afraid!
If you stand up to them,
they don't exist!
( Shouting )
Wait! I want to make sure.
If I go through with this,
my people won't be killed...
and they'll get
their city back, right?
You were always meant
to die for Hera.
It's what you were born for.
- But my people--
- ( Thunder Rumbling )
( Rumbling Continues )
Look. Hera is coming for you.
She's all around us.
Feel her power.
( Unsheathes Sword )
This is your destiny.
- Embrace it.
- But I thought--
- It doesn't matter what you thought!
- ( Thunder Rumbling )
- ( Thunder Continues )
- You know, I'm getting tired of this.
- She belongs to Hera. It is her destiny.
- I don't think so.
We'll see.
( Thunder Rumbling )
( Grunting )
- ( Gasps )
- ( Thunderclap )
( Groaning )
( Gasps )
No more labors for you, Hercules.
( Thunder Rumbling )
I don't think
it would be this easy.
- ( Grunting )
- No!
Stop! If you want me to sacrifice
myself to Hera, I will!
Good. First I'll kill him,
and then I'll kill you.
( Gasps )
( Thunderclap )
( Hercules Straining )
( Deianeira Whimpering )
Hera, I offer you
this small life.
May it give you pleasure.
( Straining, Whimpering )
( Gasps )
Guess it wasn't so easy
after all, was it?
- ( Thunder Crashing )
- ( Gasping )
Why did you come here?
What did you think you were doing?
I thought it was the only way
I could save my people.
- ( Deianeira Gasps )
- ( Priest Screeches )
- ( Grunts )
- ( Priest Screaming )
( Sighs )
( Yelling )
( Warriors Fighting )
( Thunder Rumbling, Crashes )
He said it was my destiny.
You followed your destiny,
and you found it.
But it wasn't
to sacrifice yourself.
It was to follow in your father's
footsteps and lead your people.
- Will you rule them with me?
- You don't need me.
Son... this isn't
what's supposed to happen.
- What are you talking about?
- I can justify your saving the city...
but...
Hera wants the girl.
- Why does she get the girl?
- ( Sighs )
You expect me to explain Hera?
( Sighs ) Hera's a goddess.
- ( Thunderclap )
- ( Deianeira Gasping )
Hercules, help me!
Hercules!
( Yelling )
Hera, you don't control our destiny!
We find it for ourselves!
Hercules! No!
( Yelling )
He's gone.
She won't hurt him.
She doesn't dare.
- But I love him.
- So do I.
But his work is done here,
and he has to move on.
I'll never forget Hercules.
Don't forget what
he told you about the gods.
They are jealous and petty.
Now... listen.
You must follow your own destiny.
You are his father, aren't you?
You see the resemblance?
( Laughs )
No, no, no, no.
He looks like his mother.
She's only mortal,
but she's exquisite.
Well, I have to go,
and you've got things to do.
( Crowd Cheering )
( Cheering )
( Cheering Continues )
You're alive. ( Sighs )
Hercules saved you
when I couldn't.
- You're hurt.
- It's nothing.
The people are waiting for you.
The city is truly ours
once more.
We're home, Deianeira.
Thank you.
You were very brave.
Deianeira, did you see us fight?
We were superb.
You father would have been proud.
Yes, he would have.
Princess, I know Hercules
ordered us not to attack...
but after Telamon got wounded,
I ordered myself to attack.
And being a good slave,
I obeyed without hesitation.
- Waylin, you're free.
- I think I showed--
Now you can work
for the cause of Troy.
I appoint you Minister of Defense.
Minister of Defense.
I like the sound of that.
( Crowd Chattering )
WOMAN: We must build him a shrine!
- MAN: Yes, a shrine for Hercules!
- No shrines.
He wouldn't want that.
Hercules' labor is done here.
I know that wherever he is...
he would want us to look
to ourselves now...
to believe in ourselves...
and always to remember him.
Long live Queen Deianeira!
( Crowd Cheering )
( Continues Cheering )
( Cheering Continues )
( Grunts, Moaning )
OLD MAN: Hercules. Hercules.
Well, they said you cam his way.
You've got to help us.
- There's a monster, a fire-breather.
- A fire-breather?
Yeah, and we've sacrificed
everything we have.
Sacrifices don't work.
Lead me to him.
I'll see what I can do.
Captioned by Grantman Brown