Earth, the Eagle has landed.
Thanks to all of you, and now it's
on to Chicago and let's win there.
Thank you very much.
That day when all of God's children,
black men and white men,
will be able to join hands
and sing in the words
of the old negro spirituals.
''Free at last.''
''Praise God almighty,
we're free at last.''
The negro will be serving notice
that no longer does he believe
in turning the other cheek
and being a constant victim
of someone else's brutality.
We believe
that peace is at hand.
We believe that
an agreement
is within sight.
l heard you were back, Michael.
Yes, sir, Mr. McKearney. l am.
-About the same length?
-Take a little more off.
Buzz? Brush? Number one?
-How close is a number one?
-About there.
How about just above the collar
and let me see my ears.
What are you doing
with yourself now?
ln about an hour
l'm starting work at the Factory.
Going into the family business?
Yes, sir. l guess l am.
-Name, please.
-Smith. l start work today.
...two, three, four. Halt!
Right face!
Right...
face!
To the right. Follow him.
Well, well.
Step forward.
Raise your arms.
Hands toward me.
Raise your palms.
Back at your sides.
Open your mouth.
Lift up your tongue.
Bring your head forward.
Turn your heads to the left.
My left.
Other side.
Tip your head forward.
Shake out your hair.
Wise guy.
Lift up your balls.
Turn around, face the wall.
Lift up your right leg.
Wiggle your toes.
Lift up your left leg.
Bend over.
Bend over further.
Spread your cheeks.
Cough.
Command attitude.
Go get 'em, tiger.
l've used mine twice in 5 years.
About the same number of times
l've used this.
Ken Frates.
-Mike Smith.
-Nice to meet you.
Heard you just signed
your life away, Mikey.
Hey, uncle Ed.
l volunteered this shift
to show you around.
Who the hell did that to you?
That ain't a haircut,
that's assault with a deadly weapon.
Come on, let's go.
Remember, we're all
doing time here, tiger.
Only difference is, we're doing
ours on the installment plan.
Come on, pick it up, let's go.
Hold it up.
Open the gate.
l hear you're gonna be a father.
You talk to my pop?
Responsibility, Mikey. That's what
it's all about, responsibility.
Yes, lieutenant.
Ten minutes, sir.
Yes, sir.
Got some film for me?
You play your cards right and
l'll put you in that little number.
Here you go.
Bishop!
Toes on the line.
So is this some kind of
a vacation thing for you
until something you really
wanna do comes along?
No, uncle Ed, this is it.
l really want this to work.
l been waiting to hear you
say that for a long time.
One thing now.
ln here not so much of that
uncle Ed stuff, okay?
Okay.
This is Times Square.
Where everything comes together.
A block, B block,
C block, D block.
Administration,
exercise yard, armory,
hospital, morgue.
For all of you who just arrived,
here's a few rules of conduct
that might
make your stay here
a little more pleasant,
and ours as well.
For instance, this
is not state-issued.
Nor this, nor this.
The laundry will only launder
state-issued underwear.
Copy that?
We wash one shirt
and one pair of pants
per man per week.
Plus one set of
regulation underwear.
l repeat, we do not launder
personal underwear or socks.
-Why?
-Who said that?
Well, well.
Look who's here.
Some people like us so much
they just keep coming back.
What is your question?
What if the socks
are state-issued?
No socks in any circumstances!
You wanna wash your socks,
buy yourself a plastic bucket
from the commisary.
-Why we got to do that?
-Why?
Because that's how it is.
That's how we do it here.
-Why is that how you do it here?
-That's how we always done it!
Because those
are the regulations
and we aren't about
to change them for you!
ls that clear?
ls that crystal clear?
All right, back in line.
Back in line!
There is a door
at the end of that corridor
and it leads to an elevator.
And the elevator leads
to the isolater units,
where we put people
who keep asking ''why?''.
And you don't wanna go
through that door,
l promise you,
because the isolater unit
is about the most unpleasant
place to be
in the United States of America.
Understand? Dig it?
Comprende?
Capisce?
You've all been assigned
cell numbers.
Any questions,
ask Mr. Motormouth.
He knows the routine.
Yo, Gates!
Move 'em out,
and keep a special eye
on Mr. Motormouth.
Count 'em off!
-One!
-Two!
Correctional services are going
to hell, Mikey. And that's a fact.
Time was they knew their place.
And we got on with our job.
Now they been watching
all that sex,
free love and violence out there
and they want some too.
There's a very bad element
getting into prison these days.
Ready for the showers, Leroy?
Lieutenant Weisbad,
this is Hal Smith's son.
-Michael, right?
-Yes, sir.
Welcome aboard, Mike.
How's your dad like retirement?
Fishing good?
Not much fishing,
the bar keeps him pretty busy.
You're gonna have to be a pretty
big man to walk in Hal's sneakers.
-l'll do my best.
-Okay, Mike.
Here's your first assignment.
Every resident here is required
to take one shower per week.
These are yours.
Go shower them.
-Now?
-Right now. Why not?
Well, l just got here. l haven't
gone through the training program.
Mike, this is
the training program.
What are you gonna do
when you get out?
All right, men. Forward march.
Let's go.
Come on, move it out.
Come on.
Come on, let's move it out.
Problem?
-Yeah, they won't move.
-You gotta use your stick.
There's no verbal communication
between officers and inmates.
Those are Attica rules.
One to go, two to stop.
l'm Willis. You're the new guy,
Smith, right?
You'll get the hang of this shit
soon enough.
lf you're warm-blooded, can sign
your name and add, this is easy.
And there's always overtime.
Hardly takes a rocket scientist
to do this job.
What would you and me
be doing here?
Better get after your group.
Probably at the main gate by now.
Thanks.
Hey! Hold it up!
Come on, stop!
Come on!
Good.
Any of you guys know how
to get back to the cell block?
Hey, barkeep!
-Get me a drink.
-You got lD?
Yeah.
That's me, right there.
How about a whisky and a beer
in a dirty glass.
Oh, tough guy, huh?
How about l do a tap dance on
your head with that bat over there?
Show him what you got.
Hey, no problem.
Punks.
Hi, pop.
Hi, son.
So how'd it go?
First day, you know.
Yeah.
l'll be right back.
l wanna hear all about it.
Man, you look beat.
l'll tell you, it ain't like
anything l thought it would be.
Your old man had 25 years
in that place.
He never talked about it
when he came home.
What's the deal in there?
Can we talk about something else?
Sure.
Jess, look.
lt's an easy eight you don't
have to be a rocket scientist
and you'll probably get used to it.
ln about 150 years.
So, you wanna tell me about it?
l'll call you later,
Mike, all right?
Thanks, Hal.
Pop, l gotta be getting back.
lt's quite a place,
the Factory, huh?
Yeah, it sure is.
Thanks for the drinks.
Oh, my God! He's got ears!
You never told me.
You're gorgeous!
How long are we gonna be able
to keep doing this?
Months and months.
You feel good.
So...
day one?
Day one l just about organized
the biggest prison break
in the history of the New York
penal system.
l'm marching these 30 guys
out of the shower...
l need just about the longest
shower l ever took.
Thanks.
Tell me about your day,
l'll tell you about mine.
-You don't wanna know about it.
-Really? ls that why l'm asking?
Well, it's a big noisy place
and there's lots of bad guys
who don't wanna be there
and that's about it.
Kodak is still taking people on.
Sharon, we've been through that.
You want to be a prison guard
the rest of your life?
Corrections officer.
Honey, is that what you wanna do
with the rest of your life?
Nothing much else worked out,
did it?
Yo, captain.
l got a little problem here, sir.
You're not supposed to talk to me,
l'm not supposed to talk to you.
Yeah, but l got a situation, sir.
You got a problem,
take it up with the lieutenant.
My toilet bowl's clogged up, sir.
l'm in here 23 hours a day.
l gotta do something about this.
l didn't hear you.
l missed my shower.
No. You say you wish to report
a hygiene deficiency situation.
l can't here you.
l wish to report
a hygiene deficiency situation.
-Occasioned by?
-By the fact l was in the goddamn...
You gotta say ''occasioned by''.
l wish to report a hygiene
deficiency occasioned by...
What is it?
Got a problem on 31 ,
his toilet's backin up.
l walk this tier, son.
There's nothing wrong here.
Nobody's got a legitimate bitch
unless l say so.
lt smells pretty bad.
We have an inmate trying to jerk
a new officer around, that's all.
Yo, 31 !
Waste any more of my officer's time
and your ass is gonna get clamped,
big time!
They do it on purpose.
They stuff their shirts in the can.
Why would he do that?
Because they're them, and we're us.
Their job is to fidge us around
and ours is not to let them do that.
Don't be getting into a debating
club with the inmates.
lt's backing up
all over his floor, sir.
Don't worry about him. You know
what he's in here for, don't you?
No, l don't wanna know.
l just want to do my job.
l can't see how knowing what he's in
here for is gonna make a difference.
You fill out this job slip
for a blocked drain on C block?
Yes, sir.
Officer Yates says he told you
no action need be taken.
-Mr. Ramirez's toilet was...
-Mr. Ramirez?
You got a little bleeding heart
thing going on here, Smith?
Sir, just trying to do my job.
You haven't been here long enough
to know what your job is yet.
l am negatively impressed by this
attitude. You like this attitude?
-This is not a good attitude.
-You telling us how to walk a tier?
-No, sir.
-Good.
Let's see if your heart's in place
and how heavy your balls hang.
Left, left, left...
two, three, four.
Bishop! On the floor.
Track 24.
You got some out of cell time,
Mohamed.
Smith, cuff him.
Belt.
Handcuffs.
Ankles.
Chain.
Meet Billy Bishop,
from New York City.
Jamaal X, political prisoner of
the white devils, freedom fighter,
member of the black resistence,
for liberation.
The only thing you liberated was
your mother's fanny when you put her
on the street to pay for your habit.
Come on, don't be a panny.
Try it.
Come on.
Here we go again. Another petition.
Request denied.
The rules on what the prison laundry
will accept are quite clear.
How about the other demands?
l need to know your response
to the Attica Liberation Movement's
demands for better treatment.
You do not make demands,
and you do not circulate petitions
inside this facility.
From now on, you will not
hold meetings in the yard
and you will not wear a uniform.
Grey pants and white shirts
are prison-issued.
Not how you militants
and troublemakers wear them.
We press our pants
and change our shirts
when we can.
You people are turning into
a problem again, my friend.
How you gonna deal with the problem,
Mr. Superintendent?
Keep us on the move
inside the system?
Should you continue with your
subversive and disruptive behavior
you will be subject
to immediate transfer
to another prison.
The effect will be like having your
nuts caught in a revolving door.
We demand better food.
We demand better medical facilities.
We demand an end to censorship
of inmate-attorney correspondence.
We demand a right
to worship how we please.
We demand a rehab system that works.
We demand Spanish-speaking officers
for our Latino brothers.
Latino brothers!
You and the Puerto Ricans are
always trying to kill each other.
Our solidarity scares you ''chain 'em
to the floor'' motherfuckers.
You like us at each other's throats,
makes us easier to control.
ls that it for today?
You got anything else?
Anything new?
You running out of time,
Mr. Superintendent.
This is Attica.
We're not gonna blink.
Ten hut!
Now tell him to drop 'em.
Go on.
Drop 'em.
Now tell him to spread them.
Tell him to spread them real wide,
so wide we can see
the sun coming up.
Do you have a problem with this,
officer Smith?
Are your panties to tight?
Spread 'em.
Tell him wider.
Wider.
And again.
Wider!
You got a girlfriend, man?
You got a family?
You tell them you look up
people's asses all day?
Turn around!
Yates says you got a problem knowing
what these men are in here for.
Maybe that's because
as long as you can tell yourself
they're just men and not inmates
you can also kid yourself
into believing you're not a guard.
l said turn around!
You're wearing the blue now, son.
That makes you one of us.
And there ain't no way around that.
Mace him!
ln his eyes!
Again!
Okay, okay. Get him out of here.
Get him out.
You did good, son.
Lose one cell and we lose a tier.
Lose the tiers,
and we've lost the yards.
lf we lost the yards, lose the
yards, and we lose the prisons.
Lose them, and we've lost America.
Understand?
We've got a civil war going on
in this country, son.
This is where we're gonna
hold the line. You got it now?
Not bad, huh?
Well done, Mike!
He's got a pretty good voice.
How the hell's he doing?
l don't think Sinatra's worried, but
we can always use another baritone.
l don't mean that,
l mean how's he doing on the job.
He's got shoulders, he's got balls
and he's learning
the right attitude.
He's gonna be great!
He lost his cherry.
Give me another one, Ed.
Hey, barkeep!
Line me up, l'm ready to go.
You've been hitting it pretty hard,
you think you ought to ease up?
No, pop, this job you work up
a thirst. You should know.
All right.
l wanna tell you one thing, l'll ask
in a nice way, don't embarrass me
or Sharon, all right?
Hi, honey. How you doing?
You having a good time?
Cut it out!
What does that mean,
you lost your cherry?
lt means there was some trouble in
the tiers today and l got involved.
Got involved, how?
l maced a P.R.
He was struggling and l was there
and it's what l get paid for.
-You maced a P.R.?
-A Puerto Rican.
-You don't have to know about this.
-That's not good enough for me.
lt's not me.
l didn't grow up here
and l didn't grow up expecting
to be the wife of a prison guard.
That's too bad, isn't it?
You know something? lt is too bad.
-Where are you going?
-Home.
Honey, this is upstate New York.
We hunt, we fish, we drink and lock
people up for the rest of the state.
You're changing.
They're doing something to you.
This isn't another job.
l put my life in those guys' hands
every day.
And you don't talk about it to your
wives, especially not to your wives.
They're taking you away from me.
l want you back. Don't give up...
l'm not giving up on this marriage.
l'm making money, l'm working.
For you and for him.
lf you weren't having this baby we
wouldn't be having this discussion.
But that's not the way it is,
is it?
l just don't wanna talk
about it now, Sharon.
Don't go.
Look here. Contraband.
l got a bad gut.
l can't eat that shit that y'all.
That's an illegal device there.
Now why does the commisary
sell cans of soup
if you can't
heat the shit up?
Guess that's one of the mysteries
of the penal system.
You gonna walk to the hole
or we gonna have to carry you?
Fuck you.
l'll burn your ass, motherfucker!
l want hot!
l want hot soup! Hot soup!
You got it, motherfucker?
Hot soup!
Hot soup! Hot soup!
Bring your fucking ass over here!
Leave my man alone!
Watch your asses in here today,
gentlemen.
Some clown tried to brain officer
Yates with a can of soup.
When we tried to grab the perp in
the yard we damn near had a riot.
Smith is gonna lift him on his way
out of chow hall with a snatch team.
First sign of any trouble,
we go to general lockdown.
So stay cocked, locked
and ready to rock.
Question, lieutenant.
What kind of soup?
Tomato, condensed.
ls that important?
Details.
l like details.
Right.
So what do we do
if there's any trouble?
Procedure is cover your balls
and run for the walls.
That's it?
Don't you get it yet?
We don't run this place.
They do.
We feed them, water them,
make sure the roof don't leak.
Any time they wanna
take this place over,
we got 30 seconds
to hit the street.
You told Willis what's going down?
No, hell no. l thought you did.
Jesus. The Attica Follies.
Let's go. Willis doesn't have
a clue what's going on.
Hey, Willis!
Open the fucking door.
-What's going on?
-lf l miss my shower
-l'm gonna be pissed, motherfucker!
-To the right.
Come on!
Motherfucker!
Shit!
Hot soup, motherfucker!
Hot soup!
Go on, kick his ass.
Get the keys.
l got 40,000 Zulus coming down the
corridor, coming right for you!
Bring the pigs! Bring the pigs!
Bring 'em all!
Sir, we have an inmate
control problem.
Your officers are down.
Request permission to use fire.
Affirmative.
ls this it? The big one?
Negative. We have it contained.
Armory? Weisbad.
We're gonna take it over!
Get the fucking keys!
The keys!
Come on! Come on!
Get that motherfucker!
Get him!
Over there! Get him!
Get his fucking keys! Get him!
Come on! Come on! Come on!
We're getting it on, baby!
We even gonna free
white boys today.
Red alert.
This is not a drill.
Repeat. This is not a drill.
We got it! Let's go!
Come on, baby!
Get out of your cell!
Come on!
Get out your damn cells!
Hey, get off!
Get back! Hold your fire!
Come on, man.
We getting out.
Don't move. Don't move.
You ratted me to them.
Stand up. Be a man.
You ratted me,
you squealing motherfucker!
Fall!
Get down.
Let it burn!
What's going on?
Look out the window.
They got guns.
lt's a riot!
Mr. Smith,
what the fuck is going on?
Don't do it, man.
School's out.
Give me the keys!
Give me the fucking keys!
Give him to me! l've got him!
l've got him! l've got him.
Stay down! Just stay down!
Keep your head down!
l'm finishing a chart.
Oh, yeah? l'm gonna finish your ass
if you don't come out of that cell.
My books!
Shit!
Open it. Open it!
Open the door, Mr. Yates!
Go on, go on!
Fuck 'em up! Do it, do it!
l want you guys to keep your heads!
We gotta organize!
Get everybody out of here,
get them in the yard!
Meet me at the door in one minute!
Be back here!
We've got to go, sir.
We've got to go now.
They've taken D block. l don't know
if we can hold the rest.
Fuck him up! Fuck him up!
Fuck him up!
Get off him. Get off!
Yo, look! We gotta stop this shit.
-What the fuck is your problem?
-We need these pigs.
Not me.
What else we got
to negotiate with?
Are the walls secure?
ls this thing contained yet?
lt's being contained, sir.
We've stopped them at the gate.
Sound the powerhouse whistle.
We got it.
We got the prison.
We lost it.
We lost Attica.
Damn, man.
l only had two more weeks left.
Greedy motherfuckers!
Stop eating!
Get the shit over there
to the kitchen!
We got to share!
Salaam Alekum, brother.
Alekum Salaam.
l think you need to get over here.
This guy's bad off.
Take a look at officer Willis.
He got piped real bad.
They busted him up good.
Let's go. We gotta talk to the man.
We want our men
out.
Come and get them!
Give us one. Just one.
We'll give you food, water,
medical supplies.
We'll give you one.
That's all you get.
They ain't coming in.
The man just blinked.
You know where you are, man?
You're in Athens.
Athens, Greece.
3,000 years ago.
The birthplace of democracy.
Every few years,
the rays converge
and the planet gets another chance.
l used to think it was Woodstock.
But it's here, in Attica.
ls that so?
Have you ever heard of Spartacus?
This is it.
This is one of the great
slave revolts.
Nothing's gonna be the same
after this.
You want me to stitch that up?
lt's okay.
You sure?
They took the yard.
The son of bitches took the yard.
You okay, Ed?
l'm hurting, Mikey.
That's a fact.
You the ones wearing prison
blues now, you understand?
Now we the man.
You keep your mouth talking
and you'll leave here like him.
-Let's go.
-Get them out, let's go.
-On the move.
-Let's go.
-Look at his head.
-Cover his face.
-ls he dead?
-You shut your mouth!
Or l'll hang you upside down.
And l'll cut your throat
and empty you out like a hog.
-Ed? What happened to your pants?
-Shut up, Mikey!
We don't get a vote?
We don't get a say-so?
You want him to die in here?
Let me see a hand of every man
that wants him to die in here.
Hold it, lady.
lt's okay, it's okay.
l went to the hospitals,
he's not there.
-He's still in there.
-Yeah, not for long.
-Are you going in?
-Yeah, we're waiting on the word.
Report just in.
Armed black power revolutionaries
are headed this way in a bus.
-ln a bus?
-l want you to go find them.
They join those rioters in there,
we got a revolution on our hands.
Sarge, my best buddy's in there.
Get moving. That's an order.
There's a poor son of a bitch they
tossed head-first through a window.
Wait a minute, lady.
Please, get back.
-lt's my husband!
-l'm so sorry.
We gotta clear this,
we gotta get him in the ambulance.
Somebody help me!
Governor Rockefeller
is in minute by minute contact
with the authorities on the ground.
Quiet down!
He wants this situation resolved
so that we can continue
with the work that is begun
in reforming the prison system.
The greatest tragedy would be
that this incident
pushed back the clock
of our joint effort to do that.
Please get back!
That's all for now!
We have a very serious
situation here
which requires our immediate
attention. Just let us pass.
We're ready to go in.
The perimeter is secure.
We know where most
of the hostages are.
l'm relieving you of operational
command. Stand your men down.
Stand them down?
The procedure is to go in,
hard and fast,
take out their ring leaders
and evacuate our personnel.
-We're not doing this your way.
-My way is the book way.
The book says we do it this way or
we put every officer in danger.
The governor has agreed
to let me try another way.
Now his instinct is to go in now,
but l convinced him that
we can do this without bloodshed.
Without further harm to your men.
Your way doesn't work, does it?
lf it did, we wouldn't be here,
wouldn we?
Attica! Attica! All or nothing!
Any man here
who has something to say
is gonna get the chance to say it!
We have people here
who are gonna listen to you!
And they are gonna take
your demands
all the way up the ladder!
Sit down.
Sit down, sit down!
Now you the niggers now!
You white boys gonna find out
what it feel like
to have the complection
for the connection.
Only this time the shit be flying
in the right direction.
l'd smoke your ass right now,
but while we negotiating...
Sit down!
-We need your asses.
-Bullshit.
The department doesn't negotiate.
That's policy!
This man
is Mr. William Kunstler.
He is our man!
Well, it looks like to me
they're negotiating.
Here is the list
of our demands:
Food, water,
and shelter for all inmates!
Chowtime! There you go, chowtime!
Chowtime!
Anybody need a shower?
Raise your hand
if you need a shower.
Too bad.
This is Attica.
You got to wait a week.
You ain't got no pants.
You gonna get your little pink willy
frost bit. You want some pants?
Screw you.
Well, look what we have here.
We got some pants!
Why they just your size. Big...
and dumb.
What do you say?
Yeah, sure. Give me the pants.
Yeah, well, this being Attica,
it ain't so simple, see.
See when you put in a request,
you got to do it by Attica rules.
-You got to say something like...
-Just give me the pants.
You'll say:
''Negatively impacted as l am,
through a shortfall of covering
to my little pink willy...''
l ain't saying that.
''l humbly
and respectfully
request a pair of pants
Mr. Cecil, sir!''
-l humbly...
-l can't hear you!
-l said l can't hear you!
l humbly...
and respectfully...
request a pair of pants...
Mr. Cecil, sir.
And what about
your little pink willy?
l do not want my pink willy
frost bit.
l don't blame you.
lt ain't much,
but it's yours, right?
Put the pants on.
Man we just having
some fun, Chaka.
They came here
to have some fun, too.
You are not alone!
The world is watching.
We have assurances from
governor Rockefeller
that there will be no force used
to retake the prison
while the negotiations continue.
Power to the people!
P'alante.
Whatever that shit means.
This is an show of protest,
a cry against injustice!
All right, l want you to report
exactly what you see in here.
ls this what the well-dressed
hostage is wearing this year?
You want some shoes, man?
l don't want them, no.
You some kind of hippie, pig?
lt's all right
to ask for shoes, man.
You're the new guy, right?
lt's okay to ask for shoes.
Tell him, it's okay.
-Ask for the shoes, Mike.
-Do it, Michael.
l'm not asking for shoes.
Stop the camera.
Turn it off.
Look,
you gonna be here
till we get what we want.
-You got an attitude problem?
-l don't have an attitude.
Correction:
you do have an attitude.
What you don't have
is something on your feet.
You have one last chance
to ask for shoes.
l'm not asking.
Then you ain't getting them.
Come with me, l got something
to show you over here.
You should have taken the shoes,
Mike.
Why didn't you?
They're just fooling with us.
You got to put yourself
in their situation.
No. lt's not right.
-Any news?
-Couldn't find the revolutionaries.
Okay, l got something else for you.
Something important.
-How long are we gonna be talking?
-Just stay here as long as it takes.
They have no heating
in their cells.
The parole rate is half that of
any other institution in the state.
Why aren't given more than one roll
of toilet paper every 8 weeks?
Why only one shower a week?
No wonder you had an uprising here.
This is a prison riot.
Not an uprising, or a revolution,
or a negotiation.
The riot is all those armed men
outside the walls
waiting for revenge.
Nobody's going to take revenge.
There are gonna be no reprisals.
Why aren't Spanish-speaking inmates
allowed to send or receive mail?
They're allowed as much mail
as anybody else,
my problem is l don't have any
Spanish-speaking officer to censor.
So they can write letters,
they just can't mail them.
And their relatives can send them
as much mail as they like,
it's just that
you don't deliver them?
Has anything changed in the prison
system? ls anything going to change?
Write this down:
five bearclaws,
three cinnamon twists,
six hot dogs with everything...
l'm asking you to think again,
commissioner. You did it your way,
now do it the book way.
One way or another, we're gonna
have to go in there. Over the wall.
The longer we delay it, the more
dangerous. They got barricades,
gas bombs, they got a guy building
a rocket launcher or something.
l'm going to negotiate this
all the way.
lt's my officers' lives
you're negotiating, goddamnit!
Shithouse call! Shithouse call!
Get up! Come on.
Let's go!
Let's go, line 'em up.
Pick it up. Pick it up.
No, no. You don't want it.
Get off him. Get up there.
You don't want it.
Look. They got the lieutenant.
Look what we found, thanks
to the geniuses on your side.
Pigs gave us a list
of all the piglets
unaccounted for.
His name's on the list.
We went looking.
Found his dumbass hiding
under a bench in the metal shop.
Any of you men been injured?
They've all been treated fairly,
just as you'll be.
Nobody's been chained and nobody's
been made to spread them.
Come on, you're next.
Come on, man. Take a dump.
-Take a leak.
-No. l ain't going. Not here.
-You're gonna tear your insides up.
-What's the problem?
Guy don't like the facilities.
Look, you guys better
straighten him out or we will.
Okay, what's gotten into you now?
You trying to act like a hero,
you make us look bad.
l'm not trying to be a hero, Ed.
Will you tell him to use the can
sometime, he's making them mad.
You heard your uncle,
get on the pot.
That's an order.
All right, you had your chance.
Let's go.
Go! Move it out!
Everybody, let's go!
Why aren't you wearing shoes?
-ls it because they took the pants?
-lt's just me.
Where are his shoes?
l gave my life to this department.
l trusted the sons a bitches.
They always told me
if anything happens
we go in, we don't talk...
and we don't make deals!
They betrayed us, damnit!
The lousy rotten
son of a bitches bastards!
Shitcan that kind of talk!
They're giving the orders now,
but we have a code of honor here.
Get some shoes on your feet.
l don't have shoes
because l won't beg for them.
Take some pride in yourself, son.
For morale purposes how you look...
How l look?
What are we, a bunch of civilians?
l gave you an order! Get shoes...
-l don't want shoes!
-l gave you an order!
Why don't you just thing about what
your dad would do if he were here.
He'd be thinking for himself,
that's what he'd be doing.
lf l have to suck the cock
of every man on this yard
to get out of here, l'll do it.
And l won't give a thought
about it when l get out.
Nobody's gonna
have to suck anybody's cock.
What happened to self-respect?
Pride in yourself, in your unit?
Nothing we do here says anything
one way or the other about us.
What the hell is he talking about?
lt's not about proving things.
-Then what is it about?
-Goddamn!
Fucker! Fucker!
Let him go! Let him go.
That's the 3rd time he's tried that.
This dude is out of control.
-l'll deal with it.
-You can't have him in the yard.
Shut up.
You can't have him
in general population.
l said l'd take care of it.
Let him go.
You think he's got an angle?
What's going on?
An angle?
Make them so pissed off with him
they'll let him go.
l knew a guy in Nam once,
tied his pecker to a doorknob.
Sprained it so bad
he was on the next plane home.
l don't want to die here because
somebody wants to be a hero.
l'm gonna be one son of a bitch
hard to please corpse, to tell you.
Either he pulls with us
or we cut him loose.
Maybe that rookie took
a bigger bang upside his head.
Yeah, something wrong with him,
that's for sure.
l say we take care of him.
Quietly.
-Take him back to one of the cells.
-He ain't that big a problem.
Say he got in a brother's face and
got cut. Then the shit goes down.
They're just waiting
for something like that.
-Then nobody gets out of here.
-Shit, C...
You ain't figured
this shit out yet?
Nobody gets out of here.
lt can't be.
lt never could be.
Let me talk to him.
What's your name?
-Go to hell.
-What's your name?
-Michael Smith.
-Look, Smith.
Used to be a cissy on D block.
Liked in in the mouth and ass.
ls that your problem?
You want us on your case, your
buddies too? Piss everybody off?
l'm not trying to piss anybody off.
What you need to be trying to do
is go along, you understand?
-You're Bishop, right?
-No, that ain't my name.
Yeah, you're sure
a good example of going along.
You trying to get killed, man?
ls that what you're looking to do?
l want out of here.
You can kill me, you can take my
life. But that's all you can do.
l got nothing left to lose.
So why don't you leave me alone
unless it's tell me l'm getting out
because l got nothing more
to say to you.
-How's it going, Sharon?
-l've had better days, for sure.
-How's that baby?
-Handling it better than any of us.
You heard anything? Anybody said
anything about when you're going in?
They're still talking,
as far as l know.
Everything's gonna be okay.
They've got a contingency plan
with these kind of things,
-he's gonna be all right.
-That's nice to know.
ls there a contingency plan for
losing a prison in 2 minutes flat?
What's that supposed to mean?
You know exactly what that means.
Now you listen to me.
Maybe we've got
a generational difference,
but l don't see every man in prison
as a miscarriage of justice
and the guys keeping him in there
as the bad guys.
l don't know about good guys or bad,
just that my husband's in there.
Well, your husband's my son.
And l got a brother in there.
l know. l'm sorry.
lt's all right.
You heard about
what's going on in there?
l heard a lot of bullshit talk,
l know that much.
-This isn't bullshit, my friend.
-You know something?
What do you know?
Maybe l do and maybe l don't.
What l say is they got
no business negotiating.
We ought be going back in there with
a bullet for everybody in the yard.
ls that right?
We do it now, we do it later.
Later ain't no use, right Hal?
Wait a minute, Frank.
We got a lot of angry guys in there:
Muslims, Panthers, young lords...
besides your everyday anti-social.
So we ought to go in, right?
Clean their clocks!
You know what, Yates?
lf those guys don't get out safe
it's because of loudmouths like you.
-You got a bad conscience for not...
-And you for not running a prison!
Sit down.
Sit down, Frank,
or you're both out of here.
This is my bar.
We got a war going on here already.
He's out of line.
You tell him.
Come on, help me here.
You're both out of line.
Just settle down, all right?
l'll guarantee you one thing.
l'm gonna be there
the minute we take the prison back.
They've had they're say.
Now l'm gonna have mine.
Whatever they've done to our boys,
they've got a payback coming!
Would you shut up? Maybe they
haven't done anything yet.
-They don't have any proof.
-For Christ's sake!
They got photos of some
of the hostages strung up
with their fucking cocks cut off
and stuck in their fucking mouths!
They've been killing one
every couple of hours!
You asshole!
You wanna step outside
and call me a fucking asshole?
Oswald's going in the yard!
Jess, let's go!
We've agreed on
28 of your demands.
Everything from a ban
on censorship of mail
to Spanish language
television programs.
But we can't go forward
on anything else
until we get something back. We get
some of those men out of here.
What about a guarantee
against reprisals?
You got a court order
barring the prison administration
from taking any such action.
Bullshit, a court order. lt ain't
nothing but a piece of paper.
How's that gonna stop those gorillas
from putting a gas up my ass?
What the fuck about amnesty?
Offenses connected with the takeover
will have to be investigated.
-There's no amnesty?
-l can't guarantee it.
-What about the governor, can't he?
-He has the power, yes.
-But is he gonna use it?
-Man they been jiving us all along.
They just waiting for us to crack,
then they walk in and break heads.
We gotta string a few of those up,
we gotta show them we mean business.
We want a plane to take us to Africa
and we want it now!
Hell, man.
l'm from Washington Heights!
l'll fight any man
try to put me on a plane to Africa!
You know who scares me the most,
Mr. Oswald?
Not these guys, l can live with
them, l got no problem here.
lt's those gorillas up there!
l've bent and l've bent
and l've bent.
l can't bend any more.
lt's in your hands now.
Give me one hostage.
Just one.
Hey, listen up!
And let a real man speak.
l'm 55 years old.
l got one son in here,
two more in federal prisons.
l've had 9 grandchildren,
3 shot by police.
Go on, keep talking.
The Freedom Bell rang
four days ago.
But l bent my back
over this broom for so long
till l didn't know no better
than to keep a hold of it.
Preach on that broom!
lf they won't let you
live like men,
you can sure as hell die like men.
What you gonna do about the lies,
Mr. Commissioner?
We didn't push no Willis
out a 6th floor window, did we?
We didn't burn no hostages
with a blowtorch, did we?
Why do you let them say that?
Can't you pick up a phone
and tell them the truth?
Amnesty! Amnesty! Amnesty!
They need the lies!
They want the people
to think we animals!
That way they can come in here
and do anything
they want to do to us!
Well l say
they still shucking and jiving!
l say we gotta hit 'em
with a two by four
and we can get serious!
Now if they prepared
to bargain for the little piggies,
maybe they prepared to bargain
for the big pig hisself!
l say...
we grab the big pig!
Brothers!
We gave our word!
We granted him safe passage!
You gave him no word from me!
Now did he give his word for you?
For you!
Attica!
All or nothing! Attica!
All or nothing!
Come on.
We got to get you out of here.
Get him out of here.
Let's go.
See what happens when you start
calling them mister?
You got to get the smoker in here.
You got to get governor Rockefeller
hisself up here
or we all dead men.
l just came back
from Rochester General.
Officer Willis died
of head injuries
an hour ago.
One of my men just died, governor.
l'm under a lot of pressure
to go in now.
But l really think another couple
of days could make the difference.
lt's starting to rain now and...
Yes, l understand, sir. l understand
your under a lot of pressure too.
l realize you can't offer amnesty,
but l'm not asking for that.
No, sir, no l...
Sir, l think you have
to come up here in person.
No, not to negociate. l'm not sure
there's anything left to negotiate.
But if the governor came
in person
and showed his concern,
l'm sure...
l understand the perception
problems, sir,
but l'm concerned for the hostages.
Yes, and l've nothing else to offer
the men that are holding them
except your personal involvement.
Yes, l have everything l need to
retake the facility if l decide...
Yes, l understand.
Very good.
The governor is about to announce a
commission of inquiry into the riot.
He has every confidence
we will both be vindicated.
l'm going to see Willis' wife.
l'm sorry.
You didn't know him.
He coached my kid's
little league team.
His daughter babysat for us.
l just need another day.
You don't have it.
What do you think is gonna happen
when word gets out every man in
the yard is now facing murder one?
You ran out of road, commissioner.
l was right to wait.
l was right to negotiate.
Tell that to Willis's wife
and kids.
You sure about this?
Everybody goes down on murder one?
Under New York State law,
every man in this yard
is culpable for every felony
committed in it.
lncluding homicide.
They gonna put 2,000 guys on trial?
You wanna take a chance
they won't?
lt's going down,
isn't it, lieutenant?
They got nothing to lose now.
When l was in Vietnam,
l used to get a pain
in my left gut
just before we took incoming fire.
l got it again.
Smith,
l'm still gonna have to write
you up when we get out of here.
You realize that.
Conduct prejudicial to
good order,
endangering your fellow officers...
You do what you got to do,
lieutenant.
Somebody make a note of this! That's
the attitude l'm talking about!
lnsubordination by an officer...
Get out of his face!
What are you trying to do?
l'm trying to hold us together!
We're a unit!
You know, you're right.
l don't have what it takes.
l wasn't a guard long enough
to know how to be a prisoner.
What does that mean?
lt means you're so good at giving
orders you knew how to take them.
Me, too, Michael?
lt couldn't be any other way, Ken.
Screw you, asshole.
l don't know who the hell you are,
Michael.
l watched you grow up and
l don't know who the hell you are
and l don't know
what you're doing.
He's pissing in the tent,
that's what he's doing!
Pissing in the tent!
Look at him!
ls the governor coming?
l need to know the governor's
on his way!
ls he coming?
This one.
You got that wiggly talks corn-fed
prom night white people look.
And you also got a big mouth.
Blindfold him.
Where are you taking him?
He's just a recruit, a rookie.
You take anybody you take me.
l'm gonna take you.
You can bet your sweet ass
l'm gonna take all of you.
But first,
l'm gonna deal with this one.
Get him out of here.
You don't understand.
l'm responsible for him.
You leave him here.
Stay here, Smith! That's an order!
l'm senior in command here.
You take me first,
you sons a bitches!
This is not right!
This is not correct! l know!
Get back here, Smith!
l'm gonna kick your ass so far out
of the department of corrections
you won't fucking work
from here to San Quentin!
lf you're gonna do something to me,
l want a chance to write to my dad
and to my wife and say goodbye.
We ain't gonna kill you.
Not yet, anyhow.
We gonna put you on TV.
Maybe you got nothing to say to me,
but you gonna tell Governor
Rockefeller we mean business.
We want amnesty,
we want a plane waiting
to take every man
who wants to go to Africa.
You tell Rockefeller
he got to come up here in person.
Make sure his goons
don't take no reprisals
on any man who wants to stay.
You putting me on TV?
We gotta put a face on it, man.
They got to know
who's gonna be paying
if the governor don't come through.
We signed petitions, they didn't
listen. We played it their way...
We told them this was coming down,
you understand me?
We told them this was coming down
and they didn't listen.
You wanna know something?
They still ain't listening.
Got somebody here
who wants to speak.
My name is Michael Smith.
l got a message for
Governor Rockefeller.
They want a plane
to take them to Africa,
and they want that the governor
comes here in person
to guarantee
that there's no reprisals
on the men who stay behind.
They'll start killing us if they
don't get the answer that they want.
What about these stories about
atrocities? Guards being tortured?
No, there's been nothing like that.
Have any of the guards been
mistreated here? Have you been?
Well, we've been kept in the yard
4 days. We didn't want to be here.
Have you been mistreated?
They gave us food and water
and protection.
-Have the hostages lost hope?
-No.
We're just taking each hour as it
comes, we expect to get out of this.
All right, that's it, let's go.
Do you have a message for anyone,
Michael? Personal message?
l don't know if my wife
is watching this,
but...
l want her to know
that l'm thinking about her.
And the baby she's gonna have.
And...
if this doesn't go...
the way we want it to go,
l want her to know l wanted to spend
more time with her and see my son.
All right, show's over.
Come on.
lt ain't right keeping us here.
l mean, there's a lot of things
wrong here.
And they need fixing,
but this isn't the way to do it.
l mean, getting a knife
stuck at your throat...
having to crap before everybody,
that's a human rights thing too.
But l understand a man doesn't stop
being a man because he's in here.
Why shouldn't he have
more than one shower a week
and get to have some contact
with the guards?
And he shouldn't have to be
in a cell with a clogged up toilet.
God, l hope this is over soon.
We can't take much more of this.
And if you come in here with guns,
a lot of folks ain't going home.
Why did you say that?
You trying to get
some special favors?
l said what you told me to say.
Amnesty, Rockefeller.
No, that other shit.
-They asked me and l told them.
-Do you believe that?
Why would l lie?
You know something?
You're crazy, and they're crazy.
You want amnesty for Willis
but you know they're not gonna put
2,000 of you up on trial.
You drop that demand,
we can walk out of here.
Wiesbad is over there
trying to figure out
how to put me up on a charge.
You know something?
Maybe l'm craziest of all.
Because l came to work here
for the overtime!
And l shut my eyes
to what goes on in here
and l started
doing to my wife exactly what
l saw my father doing to my mother.
Maybe l'm craziest of all.
Because l'm trying to talk a crazy
man out of his craziness...
Don't call me crazy.
We could walk out of here right now,
but you'd rather die than do that.
That sounds pretty crazy to me.
We want respect.
We want dignity.
You are gonna get blown away.
Do you understand?
You see the people up there?
l grew up here.
l understand these people.
l know my people.
-What do you know about us?
You see, l can't talk to you.
l can't make you understand.
You are one stubborn son of a bitch.
-We got to play this to the bust.
-My kid has more sense than you,
he ain't even been born yet.
Come here.
l got something l wanna show you.
Go on.
Wait.
We were gonna do it different.
We were gonna show
how it could be.
Then we got nowhere talking,
and it started breaking up.
Somebody takes his payback
on a snitch,
then somebody else.
This fool here,
he just wanted to cut somebody
and we couldn't make him see reason.
lt wasn't meant to be like this.
This was Attica.
lt was something else.
You'd better get on back.
Okay, let's see what we have.
l told you l'd be coming back
for you, didn't l?
Him!
Must be my winning personality.
Mr. Oswald!
Sir, l've got a brother and a son in
there. You said you'd do something,
so goddamnit, just do it!
Whatever it takes, just do it!
lt's out of my hands.
Move, move, move! Double time!
What are those?
Body bags.
Weaned themselves.
Corn-fed.
White picket fence.
l put up with them burning their
bras, playing that crazy music...
their long hair
and flaired trousers,
and them going on the pill so they
could do it whenever they want.
Everyone's talking about his rights,
nobody cares about mine.
l been waiting for this day.
This is get it right day!
This is where it stops.
lt stops right here.
Our guys are in there.
Then they just gotta
take their chances, don't they?
How's it going, prom night?
Just do what you gotta do
and cut the bullshit.
Give me that.
-l'll take care of him.
-No, l got him.
No, l got him. He's mine.
l'll do it quick and clean.
-You promise?
-Promise.
-l don't wanna be flopping around.
-Don't worry.
l'll do you right.
They cut the power.
lf you make it out of here and l
don't, tell my family l cared.
They gotta know l cared
and l was thinking about them.
Will you do the same for me?
Will you tell my wife?
Yeah, l promise.
He's here.
We did it. We did it.
They listened.
He came!
All right, it's the guy!
Throw down your weapons!
You will not be mistreated!
You have nothing to fear!
Look out!
Gas! Gas!
Stupid pricks!
Too damp for gas!
Beautiful.
That's just so beautiful.
They're dropping gas!
Get the hell out! Move!
Who gave the order to fire?
Dig in, men! Dig in!
This is really great!
Stay down Michael!
l killed you, mother...
l'm one of you, you dumbfucks!
Stop it! Stop it! Stop it!
You'll kill everybody,
you cocksuckers!
Just like Vietnam!
Fuck this shit!
Stay down, Michael.
Stretcher!
Crawl!
Crawl like a worm l said!
Help! l'm a guard!
-This the son of a bitch did it?
-Tell him what l did for you!
He saved my life.
-How many throats did he cut?
-He saved my life.
That's my buddy, mister!
Him too?
l'll be back.
Drop that shell
and l'll blow you away.
Hang in there, Mikey.
Here, get him out of here.
Don't forget what you said.
l didn't see you, Mikey.
Hang in there, we'll get you out.
Fucking lousy...
Hang in there, Mikey.
We're gonna make it.
Move back.
Please get behind the line.
This is a police line,
please move back.
lt appears they brought
someone out.
Get the hell out of here.
Ed didn't make it.
Don't try to talk, son.
l couldn't do anything.
Stop it!
You are not leaving here
without my husband!
Get down here and help me!
Get him up, come on!
Here, listen to me.
No one's ever gonna ask you about
what happened in there. Look at me.
Not Sharon, not me and not Michael.
You understand?
This whole thing was a mess,
fucked up from the top down,
l don't wanna ever hear anything
more about it.
All right?