(Lou, Russian accent)
Doctor Breuer.
I must see
you on a matter
of life or death.
Meet me at nine
tomorrow morning
at the Cafe Rousse.
[violin music]
(Breuer)
A matter of life
or death! Hmpf!
[exchange of greetings]
Doctor Breuer?
Lou Salome.
How do you do?
May I?
Would you like
a coffee?
Yes, café latte.
Waiter, café
latte, please,
My friend
is preparing
to kill himself,
This man's
death would have
momentous consequences
for me, for you,
for all of the world.
Who is
this friend?
The philosopher
Friedrich Nietzsche.
Nietzsche?
Should I
know of him?
Not yet, but in time
we shall all
know of him.
(Nietzsche)
How do
we confirm
a truth that has arrived
through disbelief
and skepticism
and not through some
childlike wishing
something were so.
It is hard to be
in God's hands.
It's not truth.
It is a child's wish
for the everlasting
blow to the nipple.
We have
evolutionary theory,
Evolutionary theory
scientifically demonstrates
God's redundancy.
So Darwin himself
had not the courage
to follow
his evidence
to its true
conclusion. So--
where are we?
Surely you must
all realize we
have created God--
and all
of us together
have killed him.
God--
is dead.
My friend is sick.
What is the nature
of his illness?
Headaches.
Tormenting headaches,
My dear lady,
I will see
your friend.
I'm a physician.
I know you can cure
his physical condition,
That is not
why I am here.
Nietzsche suffers
from the deepest despair,
That is what
I ask you to heal.
I cannot
cure despair.
Ah, but you
can, doctor.
I have a spy.
My brother,
a medical student,
attended the class in
which you described
a new technique.
The talking cure.
Now I can arrange
to steer Nietzsche
to your office
but he must believe
you're treating only
his headaches.
Tell me, is yours
a Russian accent?
It is.
Well, perhaps
the people in Russia
believe in sorcerers
but sorry, fraulein,
I am Austrian.
I have no magic
to offer you.
(Lou)
May I walk you
back to your hotel?
I would enjoy
that but--
my wife will be watching
from the window.
I have a duty.
A duty?
It is my duty
to be free
of duty.
Doctor, save Nietzsche.
(Breuer)
I am sorry.
I had hoped
it was hepatitis,
(patient)
How long--
do I have?
It is best
you put your
affairs in order.
Please, doctor.
How long?
(woman)
Please.
Tell us.
Three to
six months.
(frau Becker)
Are you
alright, doctor?
Make sure the Pfeiffers
are never billed again.
Of course.
Cancel all
their outstanding
debts to me.
Of course.
A Fraulein Salome
has suddenly arrived.
A very grand
young woman.
Show her in.
But Frau Reinhardt
has been waiting
for hours.
Frau Becker!
Fraulein Salome!
Doctor Breuer.
I see you like
to do things
for yourself,
Doesn't that deprive
men the pleasure
of serving you?
We both know that
some of the services
men provide are
not necessarily
good for women.
The habits
of a lifetime
are not easily
extinguished, my dear.
Your future
husband will need
extensive retraining.
No husband
for me. Ever.
I would not
do that to
a man.
If then or ever
you use this
new technique,
do not attempt to use
this mesmerism method
with Nietzsche.
Our patient would
refuse to engage
in any process
he perceives
as surrendering
his power to another.
And are you
responsible for
"our" patient's despair?
He believes
I am.
Where has
God gone?
I shall tell you.
God is dead.
We all have
killed him,
You, you,
you and I.
(priest)
God will throw
you in hell!
After the death
of Buddha,
his shadow was shown
for centuries in caves.
A gruesome,
gruesome shadow,
God will
punish you!
You are Satan!
Given the way
of people
[slam]
in the caves,
thank you,
for thousands of years,
in which God's shadow
will still be shown.
Vanquish the shadow
within yourself!
(man)
Friedrich. Friedrich.
Meet Lou Salome.
A brilliant poet
from Russia.
Fascinating lecture
to fall on so
few ears.
Why are people
so afraid of
you, professor?
Oh, truth is
a fearsome thing.
Why do you say
God is dead?
And not that
he never existed?
What you think?
That God has ceased
to be a reckoning force
in people's lives.
An interesting
interpretation.
But if God
is dead,
then everything
is permitted.
No morals,
no rules.
Without God, who
will organize
our society?
What is the
solution to your
godless proposition?
From what stars
have we dropped down
to each other here?
auf Wiedersehen.
(Lou)
I was immediately
attracted to him.
Seduced by
his intellect.
We could say so much
to each other with
half sentences.
Mere gestures,
He became obsessed,
proposing marriage
after our first meeting,
I was attracted
to him.
But not romantically.
I wanted to learn.
Not to submit.
Stop it!
My refusal
turned his love
into hatred.
He wrote me
these crazed
insulting letters.
Then he wrote about
killing himself.
So if I understand
you correctly,
you want me
to persuade Nietzsche
that his life
is worth living.
But I must accomplish
this without him
knowing it.
You are the
only doctor qualified
for this
psychological treatment.
frau Reinhardt
is still waiting.
And still suffering.
(Lou)
One more thing,
You must read
his books,
I shall do
everything I can
to help your friend.
Good night,
Dr. Breuer.
(Breuer)
Good night,
Straight home,
fishman.
[gasping and sobbing]
(Breuer)
Siegmund?
Where are you
racing to?
The most charming woman
in Vienna invited
me for dinner.
Her more charming
husband is
on his way home
this very minute.
Jump in, Siggy.
I diagnosed a liver
cancer today.
I never get used
to my patients dying.
Well, get used
to it, young
Dr. Freud.
The children
are eating.
Say hello to them.
Daddy!
My little chickens.
See what I
mean, Siggy?
He hardly
talks to me.
[soft piano music]
Oh, by the way
I've taken on
a new patient.
I haven't
met him yet,
Suicidal tendencies,
As always,
it starts
with a woman.
But Josef,
love sickness is not
a medical condition.
The story gets
even better.
Because the woman
feels guilty,
she wants me to sneak
in a cure for his
psychological distress.
While at the same
time, I address his
physical ailments,
Surely, you're not
going to attempt this.
[sigh]
I have
already agreed.
Why?
I don't even
know myself.
Perhaps I need
a challenge like this.
You cannot say
no to this woman.
She could persuade
a horse to lay eggs.
(Lou)
Our plan
is working.
Dr. Oberbach
has persuaded
Nietzsche to consult you,
Neither I
nor Nietzsche
shall ever forget
your kindness,
The professor
is here.
(Breuer)
Send him in,
Good day,
Herr Professor.
Please. Please,
have a seat.
Tell me about
your illness.
Would it be
more efficient
to review my
previous consultations?
I'm sure they're
excellent physicians,
thank you.
But I make
my own diagnosis
before reviewing
those of my colleagues,
Just as I prefer
to see a play before
reading the reviews,
Tell me, professor,
to what extent--
has melancholia
accompanied these
migraine attacks?
I have my black
periods but who
does not?
Speak not of me
tell me of
my illness.
What it
might be?
A life dominated
by black periods
is a breeding
ground for despair.
Despair?
No.
Perhaps once
but not now.
No.
I'm just pregnant.
Here.
My headaches are
the labor pains for
my new book.
What book?
[sings loud]
(Nietzsche3
Zarathustra!
A young prophet,
bursting with wisdom
and courage
and truthfulness
decides to
enlighten the people,
I teach you
the Ubermensch.
Man is something
that must be overcome.
What have you done
to overcome man?
What is
the ape
to man?
[laughter]
A laughingstock,
but I feel
no shame.
lust that,
man shall be
to the Ubermensch!
People refused
to understand
those words.
The prophet,
realizing he has
come too soon
returns to
his solitude,
So--like--
Zarathustra,
I come
too soon.
I must ask you
a personal question.
Physical wellbeing
is not separable
from social and
psychological wellbeing.
Is there someone
with whom you have--
You referring
to sex... Doctor?
Well--
I have found
that a flash
of bestial pleasure
is followed by hours
of self-loathing, so,
such herd pleasures
are not for me.
But is there
a Woman
in your life?
Every time I have
attempted to build
a footbridge to others,
I have been betrayed.
first, there was
the composer,
Richard Wagner,
I have suffered
because of him,
and later,
my best friend--
with that--woman.
Tell me more
about that--woman.
And why?
It's connected
to your illness,
Trust me
on this.
I cannot afford
to--trust--again.
Then I believe,
Herr Professor,
that we can proceed
no further.
(Breuer)
Have a safe journey
home, Herr Professor.
[horse neighs]
(driver)
Stupid animal!
(Nietzsche)
Hey, out! Leave
the horse alone!
Leave it!
Leave it,
I tell you!
[thud and gasp]
(Breuer)
Are you alright?
[neigh and shh]
[heavy breathing]
Can we meet--again?
[panting]
Friday afternoon,
same time?
Good night.
(Breuer)
Breathe deeply,
Bertha.
Did you have
any dreams
last night?
Yes. I dreamt
you were making
love to me.
Really?
Yes.
I'm just going
to examine you,
don't worry.
It's perfectly normal,
What are you
doing? No!
I want you!
You are mine!
[laughter]
(female voice)
No, Josef!
How could you?!
(Breuer)
Mathilde!
What are
you doing?!
That is horrible!
Horrible!!
Dr. Breuer!
You are now
a free man.
Go back,
you syphilitic
whore! He's mine!
No!
He's mine!
Mine!
He is mine!
He's mine!
No!
[shouts
and grunts]
[music plays]
[gasp]
(Breuer)
"There was a time
in our lives
"when we were
so close
"that nothing
seemed to obstruct
our friendship.
"When only
a footprint
separated us.
"I asked you, 'Do
you want to cross
the footbridge to me?'
But you did
not want to."
What do you make
of it, Siggy?
I'm not sure.
Let's reason it out.
The first man can no
longer cross because
he feels he is
submitting his power
to the other person.
Yes. Yes.
You're right.
He interprets
any expression
of positive sentiment
as a bid
for power.
It makes it
almost impossible
to get close to him!
It's all here.
May I see it?
And reveal
his identity?
And why not?
Perhaps if you lend
this book to Siggy
you won't hide
in your study all
night reading it.
Mathilde, stop.
What am I to do
when I watch you
withdraw more and
more from me
and the children?
First that woman!
Now this Nietzsche!
Friedrich Nietzsche?
To this day I
regret listening
to you.
The transfer
of Bertha to
another doctor
remains one of
the great shames
of my life!
Excellent books.
Very few copies
of them sold.
Then your
publisher is
a fool
for not championing
these with his
life's blood.
You're writing
in short and
brief sentences.
It is my ambition
to say in
ten sentences
what others
say in a whole book,
Hm.
As to
your migraines,
I believe their
fundamental cause
lies in stress,
Due to upsetting
events in your work,
your family,
your personal
relationships.
I've given
up teaching.
I have no home
to look after,
no wife to
quarrel with,
no children
to discipline.
I have
no obligations
to anyone.
I have no stress.
Your extreme isolation
is stressing itself,
Great thinkers choose
their own company, no?
Undisturbed by
the mob.
Consider Thoreau,
Spinoza, Buddha.
Professor.
Stress is
our enemy.
My task is to help you
reduce stress in
your life.
I propose that
you enter my
Lauzon clinic
for one month
of observation
and treatment.
We have
new medications
for migraine.
I will visit
you daily.
I'm unable to pay--
for such services.
Money doesn't
matter to me.
It will be free.
And why
are you
doing this?
You came to
me for help.
I offer it.
I'm a doctor.
Far too simple.
Human motivation
is far more complex.
What is
your motive?
Why are
you here?
Because of pressure
from my friends and
my headaches,
I ask again.
What is
your motive
if you don't
request payment
for such services.
One practices
one's profession.
A cobbler cobbles.
A baker bakes.
A doctor doctors.
Why do you write?
Why philosophize?
You want nothing
from your work.
I do not claim
I philosophize
for you.
Whereas you, doctor,
continue to pretend
that your motive
is to serve me.
Such claims have
nothing to do with
human motivation.
Now what
are your motives?
My motives?
Yes!
My motives?!
Who can answer
such a question?
I believe you
are destined
to become
a great philosopher.
My mission is to aid
you in becoming
who you are.
So you as my savior
can become
even greater?
I did not
say that!
Do you know
my patients
are the leading
scientists and
musicians in Vienna?
Yes, and at this moment
you use their eminence
to enhance your
authority with me!
I will never
exploit your name.
I will still
be used
by you!
Nonsense!
Your charity,
your techniques
to help me?
To manage me!
All of these
with you stronger
at my expense!
This is a perfect
example of why
you cannot dissect
your own psyche!
Your vision is
blurred, Professor!
You need help!
You are
about to make
a mistake!
Then go
already!
You crazed
deluded creature!
Shabbat Shalom.
[all repeat softly]
[cheerful piano music]
[screaming]
Come here!
[laughs]
[banging]
The old Bishop,
Nietzsche,
he's dying
in my hotel!
[driver coaxing horse]
Get me
some ice!
Dear God!
Bring me
some blankets!
[moan]
Herr Professor.
[gasp]
Professor Nietzsche.
friedrich!
[gasp]
Take the pain.
Take the pain in.
You will
feel better.
[gasping]
Help me.
[gasp]
That much chlorine
is a poison
in the sleeping juice
so you could
have died.
Oh, living, dying,
who cares?
I shall be in
your office tomorrow
with what I owe.
Before my train
leaves for Basel.
Basel?
Yes.
Not until
this crisis
is over.
I'm leaving tomorrow.
[waltz music]
You know,
part of me
holds some--
strange hope that
by helping this
bizarre creature
overcome his
own suffering,
I might
defeat my own,
Defeat your suffering?
You're the envy
of every doctor
in Vienna.
One feels
things at 4O
that one cannot
possibly know
at 25.
I must stop him
from leaving.
There must
be a way.
Perhaps if you'd
fully disclosed
yourself to Nietzsche,
you might have
engaged him.
Once you
gain his trust,
he might
open up like
a steamed clam.
I think I know
a way, Siggy.
I think
I know
a way.
Your documents
and receipts,
Herr Professor.
Auf Wiedersehen.
[door opens]
Professor Nietzsche.
May I have a word
before you leave?
I have a proposition
to make, Professor,
Perhaps never before
made by a doctor
to his patient.
I propose a
professional exchange.
for one month,
I will act as
physician to your body,
if you will act
as physician
to my mind.
What do
you mean?
That you doctor me
and I teach
you philosophy?
No, no, no.
Not teach me.
Heal me.
Of what?
Despair.
I see
no despair.
Not on
the surface.
But underneath,
my mind is invaded
by alien thoughts.
I've lost sight
of why I live.
I'm terrified
of death, yet--
I often think
of ending my life.
I cannot help
you with this.
I've no training.
Who is trained?
Such healing
is not a part of
the medical discipline.
What do
I know
of this?
You know more
than any man alive.
Aren't your books
entire treaties
on despair?
I can't cure despair.
I only know how
to tolerate it.
Then teach me
how to tolerate
a life
of despair.
You were right that
your mission is
to save humankind
from illusion
and aimlessness.
To create
a new code
of behavior.
A new morality
free of superstition.
It's all there.
In your books.
This is my offer.
You enter
my clinic
for 30 days.
I will observe and treat
your medical illness daily.
In return,
you become
my physician,
and help
me talk about
my life's concerns.
Look.
I'm indebted
to you--
more than
any man.
You saved
my life.
I'm just
a writer.
I'm not
a doctor.
You can pay
your debt by
saving my life.
The way I
saved yours,
So what?
I do this
for you to--
relieve my debt?
My motivation--
is entirely
self-serving.
I want
to save
my life,
but are you
strong enough
to do this?
(Breuer)
I will persuade him
that he is
the only one
who can help me.
And then what?
Then I will
reverse the roles.
He will once again
be the patient
and I will be
the physician.
And what happens
when Nietzsche
turns to you
to cure his despair?
Siggy, I'm convinced
there's something
healing in unburdening.
Look at
the Catholics.
Their priests have been
offering confessions
for centuries.
Nietzsche is
a solitary man.
Yet a few
nights ago
he opened up
to me.
A real plea
for help.
Help me.
What you saw were
his unconscious desires.
Those that if they
were liberated
could scream
for help
in daylight.
The goal of
my talking cure
is to liberate those
buried desires,
to allow the patient
to ask for
help--openly.
(Sigmund)
But is "liberation Integration"
the right term?
Isn't it "integration"
that we are after?
Integration of
the unconscious
with the conscious.
Yes!
Yes, Sigmund!
Very good.
Take a seat.
Remove your stethoscope.
And your coat.
As well.
I made a list
of your complaints,
One, you have a
general unhappiness.
Two, you're besieged
by alien thoughts,
Three, self-hatred.
four, fear of aging,
five, fear of death,
Six, urges
toward suicide,
Anything else?
I feel--
completely--
remote and distant
from my wife.
Trapped in a world
not of my
own choosing,
And is that
One more
problem or two?
You make me
feel uncomfortable.
It is my task
to make you
feel comfortless.
No, no, no.
Your approach
is all wrong.
Mr. Breuer,
we made
an agreement.
"Mr." Breuer?
Do you want
us to proceed,
Mr. Breuer?
You've mentioned
your wife last,
Which tells me
it begins there.
What initiated
this change--
in your feelings
toward her?
[gentle thunder]
[clears throat]
Two years ago
I took on the case
of a young woman.
This patient
--I gave her the
pseudonym Anna O. --
suffers from what
we doctors call
hysterical behavior,
[screams]
Try to stay calm!
(Breuer)
During our daily
meetings, she--
opened up to me,
She had the details
of every disturbing event
of the last 24 hours.
She called
these confessions
"chimney-sweeping."
[clears throat]
I prefer to call it--
the talking cure.
Unfortunately,
the course
of treatment
was terminated
by its insane ending,
How?
I fell in love
with my patient.
She and her mother
were friendly
with my wife.
[heavy breathing]
Bertha.
What's wrong?
Stop it, Bertha!
I'm pregnant!
I'm pregnant with
your husband's baby!
(mother)
Bertha!
(Bertha)
Here comes Dr. Breuer's
little baby!
Bertha!
No!
Stop it!
Bertha!
It was her delirium
speaking, of course,
her illness.
But my wife
forbade me
to see her again,
What did
you do?
I'm sorry, my dear.
I cannot be your
doctor anymore,
But I've done
nothing wrong.
Of course
you haven't.
I will refer you
to a colleague
of mine.
He will take
good care
of you.
Please don't
let me go.
I have no choice.
You will always be
the only man in
my life. Always.
Can you imagine
how terrible it was
to hear those words?
They were evidence
of the damage
I had done.
I left her weakened.
Crippled.
You are responsible
for all of your thoughts
and deeds.
But she, by virtue
of the so-called illness,
she is exonerated.
from everything.
Who has
damaged whom?
weakened whom?
Doesn't this cripple
Bertha, as you
call her--
have greater power
over you?
An excellent beginning.
He even developed
a list of my problems,
Breuer is
a curious mix,
Intelligent yet blind.
Sincere but devious,
Let him continue
to think that this
is what we are doing,
He's possessed
by a woman who
shreds him to pieces,
[chuckles]
And he licks
her bloody fangs,
[Nietzsche,
laughing hard]
I love it, Josef.
What do you love?
Tchaikovsky!
Why?
Swan Lake!
[bells ringing]
[Breuer screams
and Nietzsche laughs]
Josef, look!
We're running
out of time!
[thunder]
Backwards!
Look at the time!
Faster, Josef!
Pedal faster!
[Swan Lake ballet, playing]
Take me, Josef.
Take me!
Throw away
your shackles!
Sticks and stones
may break my bones,
but death will
never hurt me!
[Swan Lake, playing
and thunder]
[gasping
(Breuer)
I feared that after
yesterday's confessions,
you would
think less of me.
Do not worry
about what others
think of you.
I suspect you find
sex disagreeable.
I do
not object
to sex.
What I hate
is the man
who begs for it.
He surrenders himself
to some crafty woman
who turns his lust
into her strings.
Lust is part
of life!
And nothing must
interfere with
the development
of the hero
which is
inside you!
And if lust stands
in the way, lust
must be overcome!
(Breuer)
Be more practical.
All you give me
are quotes from
your books!
first time I've attempted
to put my philosophy
to practical use,
Choose between comfort
and the truth.
Are they
mutually exclusive?
If you want to choose
the pleasure of growth,
prepare yourself
for some pain.
Less pain, shrink.
Go. Be part
of the herd.
[soft playing]
[abrupt loud notes]
Look at
this tree.
It requires
stormy weather
if it is to attain
its proud height.
Learn, creativity
and discovery,
But they
come in pain!
(Breuer)
I wish for
simple things.
To sleep
without nightmares
[sigh]
to live
without tension.
Lie down.
Why?
It's the
best inducement
for recalling memories.
Lie down, please.
Close your eyes,
Let us
imagine
An icy
mountain peak,
And we see
this little man
trudging to the top.
He's looking
into the horror
of his existence.
He is encountering
times that are endured.
[thunder]
But he sees
too much.
This insignificance,
this mere
little speck
that he is.
[loud thunder]
And now his fear
becomes so raw,
that he welcomes
lust into his mind.
And he starts looking
into this castle.
He begins to spend
his time recollecting
these miracles,
How his little
crippled Bertha
moves her legs,
Her lips.
And her arms.
And her breasts.
And his mind
which was filled
with the noblest
of ideas
becomes clogged
now with trash.
And that is how
he is today,
He's just rummaging
through the rubbish.
Of Bertha.
As if it contained
the answer
to his prayers,
Well, what do
you think
of this man?
Josef, open
your eyes.
Open your eyes,
Talk to me,
Josef.
This is
my way.
Where is yours?
[cheerful piano music]
He asked you to lie
on the couch? Why?
He said it
was the best way
for recalling memories.
Interesting.
He is honoring
his contract,
but offers
no support,
My confessions
have failed
to produce
even the slightest
admission of his
own obsession.
Is your frustration rooted
in your competition
with him?
Not at all.
I'm a physician,
Siggy.
I do not meet with
my patient for
my pleasure.
But Josef,
I've read
his books.
He has more
penetrating knowledge
of mankind
than any other person.
I think, he may
be, perhaps
the greatest psychologist
who has ever lived.
You can best
help him by letting
him help you.
[soft piano music]
[woman sings
in foreign language]
[heavy rain
and thunder]
Josef?
[pigeons cooing]
[crashing thunder]
Josef? It's
after midnight.
Are you coming
to bed?
Soon.
(distant female voice)
Dr. Breuer!
Where is
my wife?
Your wife--
is in the house!
Mathilde!
(Bertha)
You'll always be
the only man in my life.
Always,
(Bertha)
You'll never regret
it, Josef. Never.
You will never
regret it, Josef.
Never.
[ship siren]
[crashing thunder]
I feel healthy.
I wish to waste
none of our
precious time
on these physical
exams, hm?
Uh, before
we begin,
the last time we met
you called me "Josef."
I like that.
Should we use
first names?
Friedrich or--?
Fritz.
Friedrich.
My best friend
at school was
called Friedrich.
He used
to call me the lad
of infinite promise.
What happened
to the lad?
He became
a successful doctor.
And respected,
And rich,
Then you have
fulfilled your goals.
You are satisfied?
I have fulfilled
my goals, yes.
Am I satisfied?
No.
How did you
choose your goals?
No, don't--
don't think.
lust chimney-sweep,
Hm.
Goals are
part of my culture.
They're in the air.
You breathe
them in.
Like every
young Jewish boy,
I wanted to climb
out of the ghetto
to succeed.
My father was
the great teacher
of my life.
No, Papa.
No, Josef.
I won't encourage
bad habits.
But I never
chose goals.
They were
just there, like--
like an accident.
And yet not
to take possession
of your goals
is just that,
let your life
be an accident.
What is
wrong, Josef?
I've had a sudden
and painful understanding
of the obvious.
Time is irreversible,
The sands of my life
are running out,
I'm in lockstep
with all people
marching towards my death.
So you see clear
vision as a wound,
Knowing that as
my death approaches,
I'm impotent and
insignificant, yes.
That does not mean
that existence has
no purpose.
On the contrary,
As death
creeps closer,
the value
of life increases.
You must learn
to say "Yes, " Josef,
But say "yes"
to every minute
of life.
Be passionate.
Be a free
thinking spirit.
Rise above
your limitations.
Be the Ubermensch.
Hm? Please.
Please, Fraulein.
Will you take
a seat?
The Russian
is here.
Let her wait.
[chiming]
Good afternoon,
Frau Pettik. Please
take a seat.
Herr Schubert,
hello.
Take a seat. The doctor
will be with you shortly.
Please, understand,
I'm very sorry.
Please, the doctor
will see you,
frau Pettik,
the doctor
can see you now.
What a pleasure.
I had forgotten,
Then look
more carefully
this time.
I'm distressed
at having so little
time to offer you.
The price
of success,
Dr. Breuer.
You like to
live dangerously.
Tell me, why
didn't you write
so that I could
arrange a proper
time for you?
I am concerned
about our patient.
Our patient?
Have you graduated
from medical school
since our
last meeting?
You must read
these letters
Nietzsche sent me.
He writes
as if to punish me.
"You are a woman
without sensitivity
or spirit,
incapable of love,
a predator clothed
as a house cat."
Why does he
regard me as
such a monster?
I deserve to know
the outcome
of my efforts.
The outcome
of your experiment.
It's been lovely
to see you,
but I must
return to
my work.
Where is he?
I cannot tell you.
Or the state
of his condition.
You turn
your back
to me.
I cannot violate
my patient's--privacy.
[slam]
(Sigmund)
Perhaps you are
not capable
of being hypnotized.
Perhaps,
I didn't tell you she
left some of Nietzsche's
letters with me.
Hm. And?
He berates me
for feeding at
the trough of lust,
and all the while,
he himself,
just like me,
is rummaging
through the trash
of his own mind.
You think he
should answer
for his falsifications,
may I remind you
of your own.
Of the deceptive premise
of your arrangement
with him.
Of the two patients
in this relationship,
I have become
the more urgent case.
(male voice)
General.
What are you
doing, soldier?
Trying to kill
myself, sir.
Carry on, soldier.
Yes, sir.
[gun cocks]
[cocks again]
General, help
me please!
The interesting thing
is that in my dream
the general
was you.
And why me?
A symbol of
your unwillingness
to join me
in a down-to-earth
manner perhaps?
Be open
with me.
I presume that,
like all men,
you've suffered
from love-sickness.
Have you ever tasted
the pain of love?
Yes.
And?
I must know.
Let me remind you
of Goethe's words.
"Be a man.
Do not follow me,
but yourself, "
Teaching philosophy
and using it
in the real world
are Very
different undertakings.
You wish for something
to soothe you now.
Then go, suckle
on the teat
of superstition,
Whatever you do,
don't go to reason,
Unfortunately, the
theatrical director
of my mind,
the one who stages
all these scenes
with Bertha
is unaffected
by reason.
Of course not.
for what reason
will a man
could love
such a cripple?
Oh, stop it!
Bertha is intelligent,
beautiful, loving!
Loving?
How?
She tried
to seduce you
into adultery.
She almost
destroyed you,
You are too
hard on her.
Well, next time
you go to her,
don't forget
to bring your whip.
Yes. I think to love
such a woman
is to hate life.
Bertha is
a fine woman.
May I remind you
she became ill
because of her
father's death?
And may I remind
you all fathers die?
I think the time
for excuses is over.
[happy laughter]
(Bertha)
You will always be
the only man in my life.
(Breuer)
friedrich, I need
your help.
Attack my obsession,
It's ruining me!
Do you want war?
Yes!
You will follow
my directives
without question.
Absolutely.
Sit.
Please.
Close your eyes.
[sigh]
Imagine--your life--
with Bertha.
But I don't
want to!
Please, Josef.
Relax.
Now, you're
starting your day.
You're having
your breakfast,
with Anna O.
I want you to compose
a list of 1 O insults
and I want you
to hurl them
at her.
To her face?!
Yes.
What?
Like "ugly?"
Precisely.
Ugly, yes.
Ugly.
Scream it out!
Ugly!
Stupid!
Cow!
Whore!
Sow!
Cross-eyed!
Monster!
Cripple!
That's nine.
One more.
Idiot!!
Good. How is
she responding?
I love you.
Banish the tranquil idea
you've composed.
See Bertha as she
would be now
each morning,
Spasms, her arms
and legs in spasms,
Cross-eyed,
Mutant.
Hallucinating.
Suffering!
[screaming]
See her as the infant
she longs to revert to.
[rattle and giggling]
See her as an adult,
sitting on the toilet
as she does
each day,
Ooh.
Hi, Josef.
[farts]
If you are alone
and you begin
to think of her,
tell her "Go away,
I hate you!" as
loud as you can.
You pinch yourself
as hard as you can!
Say it!
Go away!
Pinch yourself!
Pinch yourself
as hard as
you can!
Go away!
I hate you!
Listen. If you're
ever alone
and you begin to think
about her, shout
"Go away, I hate you"
as loud as you can.
Say it. I hate you.
I hate you!!
I hate you!
Louder!
Say it.
I hate you,
Say it! Josef, if you are
ever alone, you begin
to think of her,
you shout "Go away,
I hate you" as loud
as you can. Say it.
As loud as you can.
Say it. I hate you.
Go--away!!
I hate you!!
I love you,
(Breuer)
Go away!
I hate you!
What are
we waiting
for, Fishman?
(fishman)
Yeah, ho!
Hm.
Your heart
is strong.
But mine
is close
to bursting.
After yesterday,
I feel like a bear
being trained to dance,
It's true.
I've lowered you.
And myself.
And a teacher
should be
a raiser of men.
We are
missing something.
Yes, we've neglected
to understand
the meaning
behind your obsession.
How can we
discover the
meaning of something
that I myself
have concealed?
By talking
about it.
What would your
life be if there
was no Bertha?
Life without Bertha--
would be
a colorless one.
Everything would
be decided.
This medical bag,
these black clothes.
I'm a scientist.
Yet science has
no color.
I need passion!
I need magic!
That's what
Bertha represents.
Life without passion,
without mystery?
Who can live
such a life?
But he is
expecting me.
You're lured to mystery.
You're lured to danger.
But I hate danger.
I live my
life safely.
Living safely
is what's dangerous.
is dangerous?
Nietzsche, there is
no Professor
Nietzsche here.
Check again.
There is
no Professor
Nietzsche here.
Perhaps Bertha
represents my
desire to escape
my deadly safe life,
the trap of time.
Time is our
burden, Josef.
The greatest challenge
is to live in
spite of it.
I hate women
with lips.
Why do you
show me this?
Because she has
a combination
of lips,
eyes and breasts--
that give her almost
superhuman powers.
Powers to
do what?
When I'm
with her,
I feel that
I'm in the center
of an orderly,
tranquil universe.
An intensely
beautiful place
where there
are no questions
about life or purpose.
Like walking
on clouds.
Where do your
thoughts go now?
Her eyes--
they glisten,
She doesn't speak,
yet she talks
to me.
And what does
she say?
She says--
"Josef,
you are adorable."
And in
that moment,
I am.
When she told me
one day that she
dreamed of us
making love,
I was ecstatic.
What a victory,
To enter a place
where no man
has ever been.
Have you ever known
a Bertha, Frederich?
friedrich,
I once knew
a woman who could
not be denied. Yes.
Tell me more
about this woman.
What was
her name?
Do you still
love her?
We are more
in love with desire,
than the desired.
[opera music]
(Breuer)
Si99y.
These sessions
with Nietzsche
have become
the center
of my day.
Why?
The relief
of disclosure.
Perhaps in 5O years
this talking cure
might develop into
a precise science.
I thought
I could
help him.
No longer.
He has everything
to offer me.
I'm wondering
if part of this
talking cure
involves learning with
the patient transfers
to his doctor.
Shh.
What would it
be to live as
Nietzsche lives?
No house.
No obligations,
No wife.
No responsibilities.
(Lou)
"Goodbye, my
dear Lou.
" I won't see
you again,
"You've caused damage.
You've done harm.
And not only to me,
but to all people
who loved me."
(Nietzsche3
"And this sword
hangs over you,
But I hope
you will make
good to Henry,
what you couldn't
make good to me,
(Nietzsche)
Yes!
You make music sick.
You are sick!
[taps rhythmically with foot]
[orchestra begins to play]
Wagner.
The first requiems.
You make music sick!
You tyrant!
You antisemite!
I hate you!
[loud music]
[Nietzsche,
shouting,
no music]
Wagner,
You make
music sick,
[music]
Hate.
[gasping]
Fritz.
[music]
late.
Fritz!
Hate!
Look at me!
Talk to my animals.
Fritz!
late.
(Breuer)
I visit my parents'
grave once a month,
Would you like
to come with
me today?
It's less than
one hour's ride
from the city,
Why didn't you tell
me your mother's
name was Bertha?
She died
when I
was three.
I have very few
memories of her.
No conscious memories.
Are you suggesting
I love Bertha
because she and
my mother shared
the same name?
[thunder]
My mother
is hardly
real to me.
Bertha Pappenheim
is the most real
thing in my life.
I think
your obsession
with Bertha
has never been
about Bertha.
A year after
my father died,
I had a dream.
This grave opens,
and my father
rises up,
and he runs
to this church.
It's where
he preached,
And he grabbed
this small child,
and he climbed back--
into the grave,
I always believed
that this dream
predicted my
brother's death, but
I suspect it
was my own--
it was my
own fear.
I was
that boy.
[thunder]
In my
father's arms.
And fear is expressed
in your dream
where you--
plunge towards
the closed coffin.
Who is inside
the coffin?
I don't remember.
Who is the one
who stops you
from falling
to your death?
Your crippled Bertha?
Or perhaps
your mother?
The real Bertha.
Who, Josef?
Who is inside
the coffin?
I can still
see her face.
She's smiling
at me.
Hm.
Your mother?
How could she
leave me?
[trembling breaths]
I never really
let her go.
Perhaps adult figures
enter a child's mind
and refuse to leave.
But you must be
as frightened as
I am of death--
and godlessness.
We must die.
But at the
right time.
Death only loses
its terror when
one has
consummated one's life.
Have you
consummated
your life?
I have achieved
a great deal.
But have you
lived your life?
Or have you
been lived
by it?
You stand outside
your life, grieving,
for some life
that you--
you never lived.
I cannot change
my life!
I have my family,
my patients!
Students.
It's too late.
I cannot tell
you how to
live differently.
If I did,
you'd still be living
by some other's design,
but perhaps
I could give you
a gift, Josef.
Maybe I could give
you a thought.
What if some demon
were to say to you
that this life,
as you now live it,
have lived it
in the past,
you would have to live
once more but--
innumerable times more.
There will
be nothing
new in it.
Every pain, every joy,
every unutterably small
or great thing
in your life would
just return to you.
The same succession,
the same sequence,
again and again,
like an hourglass
of time.
Imagine infinity.
Consider the possibility
that every action
you choose, Josef,
you choose
for all time.
Then all--unlived life
would remain--
inside you.
Unlived,
Throughout eternity,
You like
this idea?
Do you
hate it?
Which?
I hate it!
Why?
The only thing
I love about my life
is the thought
that I have fulfilled
my duties to my wife
and children.
Duty?
Your duty
is a sham.
It's the curtain
you hide behind.
To truly build
your children,
you build
yourself. First.
And as for your wife,
let her break out from
this prison you share.
And be
broken by it.
Hm?
(Sigmund)
Are you sure
about this?
To continue
with the sense
that I have not lived.
That I have not
tasted freedom.
The idea fills
me with horror.
Help me, Siggy.
Fly! Fly!
Fly!
You're free!
And you too
are free.
(Mathilde)
free them?
This is madness,
Suddenly I find
that I am old.
I am facing death
without having
lived my life!
Since when is there
your life and
my life?
We made a covenant
to share our lives.
Leave if you want!
But not until I tell
you about the cruel
joke of freedom.
I wish I had
your freedom.
Freedom of a man
to obtain
an education.
To choose
a profession.
I wish I had
the vocabulary,
the logic
to express
just how foolish
you sound!
Mathilde, if I
am able to
find my life
we will both
be better off.
Perhaps I will
come back
to this life.
But it must be
my choice!
Have you forgotten
about the choice you
made in marrying me?
What choices
does a deserted
wife have?
You are young,
rich, attractive!
You will be
as free
as I am!
We have
three children!
Mathilde, I should
have been I before
I became we!
Words! Words!
You cannot live
in words!
I choose
my life, too.
And I choose
to tell you
you cannot return
to this house
because it will
no longer be
your home!
Once you leave,
I will no longer
be your wife!
Mama!
Say goodbye
to your father,
children.
Forever.
Please, Papa,
don't leave.
[weeping]
Get out there.
Leave, if that's
what you want.
Robert, I'm still
your father.
No, you're not
my father anymore.
Robert.
Goodbye, my
little chickens.
I only have
one life!
(Breuer)
Nietzsche is right.
My freedom has been here
all along for the taking.
Now is my last chance,
This is my one
and only life.
I'm looking for
Bertha Pappenheim,
She's in the garden
with the doctor.
Should I inform her
you are here?
No, thank you,
I shall wait.
Please, wait for
her upstairs.
Thank you.
I love you.
You will always be
the only man in
my life.
Josef!
How are you?
Papa, don't leave,
(Nietzsche)
Having doubts, Josef?
How could I
have given
up everything?
You'd given up
everything long
before you met me.
Yes, but now
I have nothing!
And nothing
is everything.
In order to grow
strong, you
must first
sink your roots deep
into nothingness,
But learn to
face your
loneliest loneliness,
[weeping]
My wife.
My children.
How could I
have left them?
You must be ready
to burn yourself
in your own flame,
How could you
become new,
if you would not
first become ashes?
Waiter.
Josef?
Dr. Breuer?
Josef!
Where are
you going?!
What a ridiculous man.
(Sigmund)
Josef, come back?
Josef!
Look out!
Come back!
Josef!
Josef, listen
to me.
[choking]
Eight,
Seven,
Six,
five,
four,
three,
One,
[gasping]
You're wide
awake now.
Where am I?
Everything's alright,
Josef.
Siggy--
what's happening
to me?
You are in
your house.
It'll all come
back to you.
I did exactly
as you instructed.
I hypnotized you
using your watch
as a pendulum.
Here it is, Josef,
on your desk.
Yes.
Yes, I remember.
How long
was I under?
Nearly an hour.
You wept,
you looked frightened,
I asked you
if you wanted
to stop,
[gasps]
Now I know
what it would
be like--
to live differently.
Max and Rachel
have arrived
for dinner.
Mathilde.
You complain
you don't see
enough of me.
Yet, when
I'm here,
you want
to desert me?
I've been
away, my dear.
But now
I am back.
I'm glad
you're here.
Dr. Freud,
my husband
needs a doctor.
To your health,
my boy.
And to you, Max.
(Max)
And to
you, Josef.
Cheers.
Oh!
[whistle and chuckle]
Mmm.
My boy, my boy.
Excuse me.
[trembling breaths]
[breathes in
sharply]
Have I made
you cry?
It's a good cry.
It's sad too.
When I think
how long it's been-
Marry me, Mathilde.
Please.
I think we did this
15 years ago.
And I choose
to do it again.
Today.
And every day
for the rest
of our lives.
(Nietzsche)
So, tell me, how
did you cast her out?
Well, I was terrified
by aging and death.
I fought back
but blindly.
In desperation,
I attacked my wife
and sought rescue
in the arms of one
who had
no rescue
to give!
In a certain sense,
I've betrayed you,
I have been
so dishonest
with you.
Completely.
I was
myself involved
with a woman.
A few months ago.
Her name
was Lou.
Not so unlike
your Bertha.
Beautiful girl.
I fell in love.
She just appeared
to be my twin brain.
My soul's mate,
And she led me
on to believe
that I was the man
to whom she was
destined and--
I believed her,
And when I offered
myself to her,
she spurned me--
in favor of
my best friend--
in the world.
[thunder]
I must tell you
that there
is not--
not one day
that goes by--
not even an hour,
where I do
not think
of that woman.
She is your Bertha.
But you see?
You've been doing
double work here.
Yours and mine.
I'm like the most
cowardly of women.
And I crouch behind
your back here,
letting you face
all the dangers
all alone.
You have courage.
Friedrich, there is
something I must
tell you.
Dr. Breuer?
How do you do?
You must read these
letters Nietzsche
has sent me.
These are
my private letters.
You did see
her then?
Yes, but I
refused her.
So all of this
was just
a pretense.
I made a promise
to help you.
I never betrayed
that promise.
What did she do?
She took you
by the arm?
Told you she had
to spend more
time with you?
I shared one,
one holy moment
with her,
it's the only
holy moment
I've ever known.
No one fell
in love with
me, ever. Ever.
Friedrich, it may
have been a holy
moment for you,
but not for her.
What are
you saying?
She never mentioned
the water?
No.
I feel such
a loss.
Hm.
I don't know.
I think I've
lost Lou.
And you.
Everything, I lose.
I could have
[indistinct]
from your mind.
And you
have a family.
You have your family
and I have
my pretenses.
My secret little
ways of tolerating
my aloneness.
But I glorify it,
don't I?
And I just don't
want to die alone.
I don't want my body
just to be discovered.
By its stench.
Lou softened that fear
for me for a while.
But you're right.
It's just
an illusion.
Friedrich.
It's such
an illusion.
friedrich,
She does care
about you,
She went
to extremes
to help you.
If your tears
had a voice,
what would they say?
I feel so ashamed.
Tell me.
My tears
would say
we're free.
You never
let us out,
until Dr. Breuer
opened the gate.
And what about
the sadness
behind those tears?
It's not sadness.
It's such a relief.
It's such
a relief!
It's the first time
I'm revealing
my loneliness.
It's melting.
It's melting away.
It's a paradox,
Isolation exists
only in isolation.
Once shared,
it evaporates.
My dear friend.
We are friends.
I like saying that.
No one ever said
this to me.
I like it.
We are friends.
Friedrich.
It's good.
Stay with us tonight.
Have supper
with me and
my family.
No, it would mean
to abandon
my mission.
It's time
we went
our ways.
"We'll have friends,
and have become
strangers to each other,
"This is as
it ought to be.
"We do not want either
to conceal or obscure
the fact
"as if we had
to be ashamed
of it.
We are two ships,
each of which has
its goal and its course."
And finally, Dr. Breuer,
"We have to become
strangers to one another
because it's the law
to which we
are subject."
Have a safe journey.
My dear friend.