Ash, put the fucking gun down
Put it the fuck down!
Get in the car Ash?
Ash?
... considered armed
and dangerous.
All units, all units stand...
She's dumb, too
Shut up
Hey, Taylor
Hey, Ashley
Hi, Cathy
You guys skipped class again
Yeah, we had stuff to do
So, what
are you doing tomorrow?
Maybe guitar lessons
Ah
I'll just
hang outwith him
Yeah, why?
He's a friend
Yeah
Ow! Knock it off, Ashley
You jerk!
- Are you okay?
- I'm fine
I hate your friend I don't know
why you hang outwith him
I gotta go
Are you gonna be
in school tomorrow?
I don't know Maybe
Hope so
See ya
You know she's going
to that other school next year
Who cares?
No matter what happens,
we're best friends forever
The Raskins: # Find that look
still inyour eyes #
# What can I say? #
# Holding back the kid
inside of you #
# Feelings left with no disguise #
# Can't hide away #
# All we've shared I thought
would get us through #
# What we have to change #
# It's clear we're not the same #
# The trouble we uncovered #
# Hopeless dreams #
# So far away, girl, you and I #
# Cried so hard
till nothin'we could do #
# All that's left from yesterday #
# Excuses why #
# The road's too long #
# It's time for something new#
# What we have to change #
# It's clear
we're not the same #
# The trouble we uncovered #
# What we had to change #
# We are not to blame #
# Stop fighting with each other #
# And what we had to change #
# It's clear we're not the same #
# The trouble we uncovered #
# What we had to change #
# We are not to blame #
# Stop fighting with each other #
# And what we had to change #
# It's clear we're not the same #
# The trouble we uncovered #
# And what we had to change #
# We are not to blame #
# Stop fighting with each other #
# Na na na na na #
The guy might
be on to something,
lizards notwithstanding
What are you talkin' about?
The lizards
The shape-shifters
The alien?
You're not fucking
listening to me, are you?
No, I'm not listening
Well, if you're not interested,
just fucking say so
I'm not going to bat
for the lizard people
I just think it's kinda odd
that 38 out of the 45 presidents
have all been related by blood
Yeah, it's odd
What about this?
What do I look like,
a hairdresser?
It's good
It's discreet, uh...
- It's gay
- You're gay
No, we need something
tough, with balls
Like this
Yeah, the OJ escape vehicle
"The Beef State"
The Beef State it is
So, uh
Why Connecticut?
Why here?
'Cause Dickson said so
Said the air is plum
Since when
do we take his advice?
Since now
He says he wants us
to meet some jewel guy
Fast Bobby
Fast Bobby?
That's so cliché "Fast Bobby"
You ever think about the kind
of people that live in these places?
Heck yes
This is Fairfield County,
one of the richest communities
in America
Guyworks so fuckin' hard
to get a house like this
Big fuckin' house
Beautiful wife, kids
Pool Car
Guyworks so fuckin' hard,
the poor bastard
never gets to see his family
Theyjust end up resenting him
That's the American Dream, man
Heck yeah Exactly
Shit Just got an idea
So, let me get this straight...
I pick one of them up,
go to her place in her car,
you follow in the truck...
You unlock the door,
I sneak in while
you're hittin' it upstairs...
Oh, wait, hold on
How do you know
there's an upstairs?
I doubt she lives
in a split-level ranch
So, you let me in...
No, no
You wait outside,
I'll case the joint,
see what's portable,
meet you later
Well, what am I supposed to do?
I don't know
Read a book
Think Oedipus
Think you could do it?
Yeah, be like bangin' your mother
I don't know
What do you think?
I think they're sauced
Agreed
No, well, listen,
I picked up three...
Hello
Ladies
Oh, my God
I'm so sorry
We didn't see you
standing there Um...
Joy, Constance,
another round of cosmos?
I'm ready
Oh, and can you
get us fresh lime juice, please?
Thank you
- Um
I'll go get you those
Extra dirty
- Okay
Come on, don't...
Well, we have to engage the
enemy on their own territory
Blend in
All right, think of a place
where they travel in packs
Parks
Malls
AA, Al-Anon
Little League or soccer games
It's the middle of March
All right
Hockey moms
Hey, man, my business
Go get her, tiger
Hey, which one's yours?
Come on, Josh!
Mine's 14
On the other team
Those little bastards,
tough as nails
You look awfully young
to have a pee-wee
Well, so do you
I was, uh,
20 when Joeywas born
Then hismother died
Tragically
Oh, I'm so sorry
Can I help you?
Ohyour kid
He's good
Real solid
Well, thanks,
butwhich one's yours?
Uh, he's on the green team
Ah, no kidding
Well, what's his number?
Because I know
all the kids on Josh's team
You knowwhat?
I forgot Joey's,
uh, medications
Asthma
Excuse me, uh
Leave him alone
Hi
Hello
Which one's yours?
Oh, no, um
I don't have any
I'm here with a friend
She has two
You?
Um
I'm sorry
Karen
Hey, Taylor
Nice to meet you
I haven't seen you
around here before
Yeah, no, I'm just
visiting my uncle
I'm, uh
I'm a hockey fan
Oh
Well, what's so funny?
It's... it's cold in here
Yeah, it's an ice rink
Yeah, I know, it's just colder
in here than it is outside
It's so funny howtwo strangers
manage to talk
about the weather,
even when they're indoors
It's absurd, isn't it?
No, it's not absurd
It's just typical
Do you want to grab
a cup of coffee?
Yeah
Whoa, easy there, chief
Sorry
Nice stick you got here
Yeah, I know
Smart-ass
Coach Bradley
doesn't like itwhen we're late
Coach Bradley, huh?
Please can I get my stick?
Here you go
Get out of here
What are you doing here?
Me? Just a hockey fan
- Fan?
- Yeah
Go Penguins
Now get in there
Give 'em hell
Who?
I don't know
Whoever you're playing against
You got skills, don't ya?
Well, Coach Bradley
doesn't think so
Coach Bradley's an idiot
Look, how old are you?
I'm 11
May 13th
Right
So, if Coach Bradley
really knowss dick about hockey,
what's he doing coaching
a bunch of 10-year-olds?
I don't know
Does he ever
put you in the games?
Never
And who does he
put in every single game?
Evan
Evan who?
Evan Bradley
Yeah
I know Coach Bradley
I know all the Coach Bradleys
Wait
Do you really think
I've got skills?
Fuck yeah
What's your name?
Ashley You?
Tracy
Sweet
Bet you got a lot of shit for that
back in school, huh?
Have a seat
So, what do you do?
I'm in school
Well, I was in school
Columbia
Takin' a break
In... in Connecticut?
Well, my uncle's here,
and he works for the airlines,
so, uh, I get to travel a lot
God, I used to love to travel
I, uh... I went to Italy
a couple of years ago
Not Florence...
I was... I was in Tuscany
Um
but Florence
is in Tuscany, no?
Yeahso stupid
I was, uh...
I was down south
Oh
Great place
Great pasta
Uh-huh
You're not some kind
of child molester, are you?
If I was a child molester,
would I tell you about it?
Good point
Mightwant to keep your eye
on Coach Bradley, though
Care to join me?
My mom says
cigarettes are bad for you
It's not a cigarette
It's not?
Nope
Well, I don't know
My mom says that...
"My mom says ehh..."
No peer pressure, man
If you don'twant it,
no big deal
Well, if it's not a cigarette
Attaboy
Hit itjust like this
And hold it in
Nice try
Why didn't you give yourself
a fuckin' PhD while you're at it?
Columbia
What a dick
She was cool, man
Who cares?
Give me the details
I'm just sayin',
l... I liked her
We... we clicked
She was cool
I'm very fuckin' happy for ya
- Details
- Look, there are no...
There are no details
S-s-she had to go
She got a call
Some kid went nuts
Started getting into all these
fights at the hockey rink
Well, can't you fight in hockey?
They're kids
Kids don't have to learn
howto fight?
Well, when are you
gonna see her again?
Tomorrow night
Hi
Hey
Hey, umlhi
Hi
- Um...
- Just stop
You look fuckin' hot
Thank you
Thanks
From... from now on,
you should, um,
probably come in
through the... through the back
I'm... I'm just afraid
the neighbors
lt... I always keep
the door unlocked
Right
Is that safe?
Oh, absolutely,
around here Yeah
So, um, do you like mojitos?
Sounds tasty
Good, good
So, make yourself comfortable
Um, put on some music
if you'd like
Hey
Where are you going?
I gotta get up early tomorrow
See my uncle
Will I see you again?
Yeah
I hope so
It's so wrong
It's wrong
I just
You know
Jerry
Mmm
I mean, Jerry
Jerry
He can be...
A prick?
Actually, I was
going to say "detached"
Oh, yeah
There's that
Oh, God
What am I defending him for?
It's his fault
Well, I say enjoy it
And I
I justwanted to feel something,
you know, anything
Jesus, Karen, when's
the last time you had sex?
Emma, everything with you
has to go back to sex
Well
I wanted to feel
close to someone
A month?
Two months?
Emma
Look, I'm not rationalizing this
It's cheating,
and I feel awful about it
I do
Oh, my God, have I
become that desperate?
Six months?
- Maybe more
- Oh, my God
And I'm sure it hasn't been
that long for Jerry, though
No, I'm sure it hasn't
So, tell me
When, how, where?
Welll told him
That I would
leave the light on for him
- The light?
- You know
To let him know
that Jerry's away and
And he can come in
All right, if you could live
anywhere in the world,
where would it be?
Paris You?
Tijuana
Cheap booze
If you could only eat one kind of food,
whatwould it be?
Uh...
Like Italian,
Japanese, Chinese...
Burgers
- American?
- Yeah
- Huh, interesting
- You?
Japanese
I don't like that
Rawfish?
I mean, fish is meant to be cooked
I think I'm getting nicely drunk
I think after we leave here
we should, like, go to the beach
or something, you know?
Go jet-skiing
and paragliding and
you know,
shrimp cocktails and stuff
Ta-da!
What do you think?
Don'twe look special!
Thank you
Think we can do
some actual work tonight?
We?
Uh, yeah, okay
Don't forget to hit that shit
Hey, boy
So how's your uncle?
He's good
Where did you say he lived again?
Uh
I didn't
Ah
But, uhhe lives close
And is your friend staying with you?
My friend?
From the other day at the ice rink
Yeah, Ashley
Ashley, right
Yep
Hmm
So, uh
Where's your husband?
He's away on business
Right
What's he do?
He's an investment banker
Wow Cool
Mm-hmm I guess
Any kids?
Just one
Mm, mm, mm
Taylor?
Yeah?
Yeah, I'm just going
to get some water
Would you get me some, too?
What the fuck
are you doin' here, man?
Gettin' somethin' to eat
This is crazy Come on
How'd it go?
This is dog shit
I got it out of the bottom
of her jewelry box
It's stuff she wouldn't miss right away
Where's the Winston,
the Yurman, the Bulgari?
That's Ripka
This is Ripka, too
It's the Armani Exchange
of Armani
At least she got some real pearls
Although those synthetics
they make nowadays are almost exact
Did you know
that pearls dissolve in wine?
That's wine, Hamlet
It's cold
I was in the middle
of an anecdote
Yeah You always are
You two seem to be doing
just fine for yourselves
We certainly are
Yeah, this town
was ready to get tapped
- Yeah
- What did I tell you, Taylor?
- You told us
- I told you
Taylor even got a girlfriend
out of the whole deal
Oh, fuck you
No, he's fuckin' crazy about this bitch
For real
It's all part of the scam
- Yeah, right
- Oh, yeah
- Fuck you, too
- So sensitive
All right, enough
Where we goin'?
- Can't fuckin' take it
- In here
Hey
Whoa, nice place, Dicky!
- I know
- All right, so, uh
what's the deal
with unloading this shit?
Fast Bobby,
Taylor, Fast Bobby
- Yo! Fast Bobby!
- Fast Bobby!
Okay, look, if you guys want
immediate cash, it's gotta be Fast Bobby
- Period
- Okay, okay, just don't fuck us
Yeah, don'tworry
You knowwhat, you guys just relax
Let's have a couple drinks,
do a couple of lines
It's all gonna be okay
Pass the bottle
Jesus Christ
Hey, Dickson
Boys
Fast Bobby
Wait a minute
You're Fast Bobby?
Whatwere you expecting?
Pfft, I don't know
Something with a dick
Sorry, don't listen to him
Uh, just not somebody
as attractive as yourself
It's an honor to meet you
Likewise
Let's just get on with it
I know about your scam
lmpressive
Dangerous
And so boring
Whoa, whoa, whoa,
it's not as easy as it sounds
Hockey moms are toughbaby
What did you call me?
Baby
Fuck this Take it to a pawn shop
and get your usual ten percent
All right, all right!
Cool it guys, can we just
can we get this over with, please?
He's a smarter one
Well, fuck this shit
We're not amateurs,
we're professional thieves
Sit down Just listen
I'm all you have
Yeah, can we just,
can we do this, please?
Let's have a look
This is it?
This is shit
What the fuck is it
with bitches and jewelry?
Baby
What'd she say to me?
It's not good
Way to go
Fucked this up, too
Good for you for looking out
for yourself for once
I know, it's just
I'm not
Like me?
That's not fair
What's not fair?
I don't care It's fine
It's just sex
For me, maybe not for you
Give me one of those
What? You quit
Emma, Jesus Christ, it's the least
of my problems right now
Okay
So what about his friend
from the hockey rink?
What's his name?
Emma!
What?
What, you have the monopoly
on being lonely, now, Karen?
What's his name?
Ashley
Ashley?
Sounds, uh, artistic
Apparently, he hangs out
downtown at the café
- Really?
- Mm-hmm
What? What's wrong?
I don't know how long
I can keep this up
So leave the light off
Hmm
Just a couple more minutes, man
What the fuck for?
She's not gonna turn on
your precious little light
Probably fucked
some sense into her
Fine, go
- What?
- Go!
Oh, really? All right
Go party by myself
Have fun walking home
Nice Lap dances?
I'm next
Dicksonam I chach?
You better square with her
before you deal with me
I don't generally kiss ass, but
I justwanna apologize
Now, when I first met you,
I know I came off as, like, a jerk
It's just that you're so beautiful
I guess I was intimidated
Come on, what d'you say?
Please?
You're lucky
Never get the second chance with me
Well, I appreciate it
Now
Can I please have some cocaine?
Now, how you plannin' on
payin' for this?
Relax, we got some ladies lined up
They got more jewels
than the Queen Mother
I haven't done this since, um
I haven't done this sincecollege
I'm sure it hasn't changed much
Since way back then
Oh, fuck you
If I remember correctly
Ah, yes
Not that good
Mmm Ew
What's that one?
It's a dragon
Oh, yeah?
- Yeah
I'm a dragon
I'm a fire-breathing dragon
Mm
There are two of them
That's my partner
My friend
Taylor
We've known each other forever
andit's a longstory
There you are
Hey
So, uh, th-that must be your daughter
Yeah
April
How old is she?
Nineteen
Wow
You were young
when you had her
I was 18
Where's your first husband now?
He's dead
Oh, I'm sorry
ltwas a long time ago
I don'twanna talk about it
Where is she now?
She's in school
Any more questions?
Sorry
I'm justtryin' to make conversation
I'm tired
Hey, can I justgo?
Do what you want
Oh, shit
That little stoner Tracy
scored two goals lastweek
I think I got frostbite, you fucker
Sorry, buddy
I, uh, had to take care of something
Next time, you should walk
Where were you?
Had a date
With Fast Bobby?
No, with your, uh, old lady's friend
from the hockey rink
Think that's a good idea?
Who cares?
Well, hey
Least you got laid
It's been a couple months
Easy
Now, listen, I, uh
was thinking a couple more days,
and then we hit the road
What do you think?
Sure
Then we can clean 'em both out
Wake up!
Get up!
What the fuck?
Hey, I got you some coffee
Here
What the fuck, bro?
Come on, get up!
Let's go fuck around, man,
have a good time
- For real?
- Yeah
Whoa, whoa!
Check this shit out, bro
Oh! I got it
# All the cuts and the scars #
- # Of passion I sweat #
- Here we go
- # Generates thoughts in our minds #
- Check it out
- # See everyw here we go #
- Ow, fuck!
# Voices in my head #
- That fuckin' hurt!
- # Get on one crazy long ride #
# Nowwe're holding all the cards #
# Rolling right along #
# Realize howwe can run free #
# Foroced a smile onyourface #
# Today we'll have fun#
# Laughing so hard we can't see #
# For I can't help myself
'cause I burn deep inside #
# You look down
on things that I've done #
# Asking why you can't stay #
# It won't be long #
# As I reach for the moon in the sky #
# Searoching the crowd #
# No little hold #
# Remember howfar we have come #
# For without you I'm lost #
# Those lonely days cold #
# Shined upon me...
you're my sun#
# Now I'm floating in the wind #
# Towns we roll through #
# Fame is a hard hill to climb #
# For with you I can share
so much to lose #
# Dreams I hope one day we'll find #
# For I can't help myself
cause I burn deep inside #
# You look down
on things that I've done #
# Asking why you can't stay #
# It won't be long #
# As I reach for the moon in the sky #
Yeah
This place is fucking crazy, you know?
Fuckin' creep built this
Huwah!
Oh, shit
Uh, Taylor, this is Satan
Satan, this is Taylor
Hey, nice to meet you
Pleasure's all mine
Oh, shit
Fuck
Ooh
Ow
They should be fuckin' thankin' us,
kissin' our fuckin' asses
Who needs that fuckin' shit?
You know, why'd he
wanna fuckin' live like that,
fuckin' walking around
on the streets all fuckin' dirty
Shut up
What?
- Who are you?
- I'm sorry, I thought...
What are you doing here?
You want money, right?
- I'll give you whatever you want
- I don'twant any money
- Don't hurt me No, no, no!
- No, wait! April!
How do you know my name?
Oh
You're him, right?
Who's him?
The guywho'sbanging my mom
What are you, like25?
I'm 30
That'spathetic
Look, it's a long story
You wouldn't understand
Explain it to me
I don't have to explain myself to you
Y-yeah, you do
You entered my house uninvited
Okay I'll call the cops
No you won't
You won't do anything
April, we're back
April, did you leave the backdoor open?
Uh
Yeah, I guess I did
I'm sorry
Sweetie, are you... you okay?
Yeah
Okay
We got Chinese vegetarian for you
Thanks
Okay
So where are you from, darling?
My mother's vagina
Ew, gross!
No
- No, seriously
So how you guys know Dickson?
The three of us
go way back
All the way back
to Devonwood
That sounds fancy
If you like guards and dogs
and bars and stuff
We were on the polo team
Devonwood was a reform school
So, are... are you two like brothers?
Yeah, more like lovers
Fuck you
Fuck you!
No, fuck you
We've got a Jacuzzi in our room
Back the hell up
Hey, get out of here!
Nice try
What's goin' on here?
Who the fuck are you?
- Well, I'm the fuckin' DJ here
- Oh
Well, then get l-l-lost
Dickson, can you do me a favor
and get these two fuckwads outta here?
Theywere hittin' on my girl
Uh! Your girl?
Take a walk
I'm spinnin' tonight
Oh, you're spinning
Aw, jeez I guess we gotta find
someone else to press play, don'twe?
Get the fuck out of here
Who's your dog?
Who is that guy?
That's my boyfriend
I'm serious
Lucky guy
How do you have
that much energy?
Uh, Energizer Bunny
Ready for the Jacuzzi?
- I am so ready for the Jacuzzi
Oh
Yo!
W-w-what up now, fuckwads?
Yo, yo, yo Calm down, man
Don't do anything stupid Listen...
- Don't fuckin' embarrass me!
- Jesus!
No, no, no You knowwhat?
You're right, man
I know how you feel
I was out of line... she's your girl
It's happened to me
You should go with him
Come on,
let's get out of here, Taylor
Stop it!
- Motherfuck!
- Ow!
Ah! Fuck!
What the fuck!
Fuckin' gun!
Are you fucking crazy?
All right, all right, enough!
I'm fuckin' sorry
Fuck you!
- Oh
- He's got a fucking gun!
Get off of him!
Get off!
Ash, get the fuck off!
Fuck
Oh, baby, I'm sorry
- Get the fuck outta here! Right now!
- I'm sorry Okay
- Come on
- I'm sorry, man
- Get the fuck outta here
- Fuck you
- Fuck you, get away
- You're not coming with us?
- No!
- Psycho!
Fuck you!
Fuckin' bitches
- I'm sorry
- Get the fuck outta my face!
- Let's just go
- Oh, God
Fuck
Slow down, bro
Taylor!
Taylor, what's wrong, man?
Yo, what's fuckin' wrong, bro?
You're what's wrong!
What are you talking about, man?
That motherfucker started this...
It's not him!
It's everywhere we fucking go!
Yo, you're fuckin' trippin', bro
- What's you fuckin' problem?
- I'm fuckin' tired of this!
It's everywhere, it's everything,
and every time, I get caught
in the fucking middle
It's like you against
the whole fucking world, right?
Nah
It's us against the whole fucking world
Come on, man
You're just trippin', dude
Come on
It's cool
Fuck it
Dickson!
What the fuck is going on?
Where's your head?
You're smarter than this
You see what they did
to my DJ?
Enough with this dog and pig show
Pony
It's "dog and pony show"
Just fix this
Look, consequences, okay?
That's all I'm saying
Aw, just because I
fucked up some punk-ass DJ?
It's notjust that, okay
I mean, you can't be running red lights
when you're robbing banks
What the fuck is that supposed to mean?
Look, I asked you guys to come east,
make a little money, okay,
maybe even eventually go legit
Okay, butwhat do you do?
You fuck it up and throw it back in my face
- Bullshit
- No, it's not bullshit, okay
You're reckless
You're damn straight
Hey, Mom
Hi
Can I borrowthe car?
Where are you going?
Just out for coffee
Would you like some company?
Well, I'm
kinda meeting someone
A boy?
Yeah
So when do we get to meet him?
We're not quite
thereyet
# Days that pass
now I can't sleep #
# You're always on my mind #
# So in love
my world just doesn't move #
# Wrap my arms around the one
I know I'll neverfind #
# A pretty little angel
such as you #
# Hold me now#
# The ocean's getting high #
# Each day that passes
I want you more and more#
# Spin me around
all these feelings deep inside #
# I hope in the end
we'll finally share them all #
we will finally share them all #
# I hope in the end
Hello?
Hi.
Who is this?
Oh, I think you knowwho it is.
Your timing's a bit off
Mama Bear's not in right now
I wasn't calling for her.
I was calling for you.
What do you want?
Not sure, but uh...
I think I want to see you.
Why?
I don't know. Why not?
Wow, that's a wonderful argument
Uh, I'll think about it
Mmm
Shit
I took those right out of her fuckin' ears
Mmm
Look what the cat dragged in
Where's your partner?
He's, uh
He's not here
I can see
I thought you were a team
We are
Maybe someone needs
to start looking for a new partner
I think someone needs
to mind their own fucking business
What do you have for me?
Now I'm happy
Very happy
I'll be happy too once I get paid
I'm thinking9,000 for all of it
Ten
Okay
Nine it is
Thank you, very much
You're welcome
Oh, hell yeah!
So
What are we doing?
Takin' a walk
Yeah?
Andwhat about my mom?
Yeah, uh
You gonna tell her?
Tell her what?
I mean there's nothing to tell
What are you gonna tell her?
Nothing for me to tell anymore either
Oh
So
What do you do?
I uh
I steal stuff
- And that's it?
- Yeah
That and get busted for it
Pretty cool, huh?
Oh, yeah
I stole something once
Got busted for it
ll've been here before
I knowthat bridge
Yeah, it's pretty old
I think itwas built in, like, 1911
by an architect from, uh, Prague
Yeah, I saw a picture once
from when theywere just building it,
you know, and
everything around it looked so
justwild anduntouched
ltwas kind of haunting, really
Nothing looks like that anymore,
you know
It's all developed
Not everywhere
Yeah, I guess
So where'd you grow up?
All over the place
Hmm
I've never been there
You should go
Yeah
Maybe I'll stop by
No!
Up there...
Got a little surprise for you
Ready?
He's cute
Taylor
This is Candice
Hmm All right
I doubt that's her real name
Huh, bro?
Just like old times
That's the Jacuzzi I told you about
Hot!
What do you say, dog?
So
We gonna party?
Taylor?
What's up, bro?
We gonna party?
Shut the fuck up
You knowwhat?
Here
Take this fucking money
Pssh!
Yeah, you guys have fun together
Go! Fucking
Dude, what's wrong with you?
Yeah, you'd rather
watch fucking cartoons, dude?
This fucking
moody shit's getting a little old
That cunt's clouding your judgment
How's it going, man?
Hey
Nice barn
What are you doing here?
I'm workin'
Working?
Workin' on what?
Your golf swing?
No, I, uh
met Karen's daughter
She's got some rich friends
I thoughtwe could hit them,
too, you know?
I like the way you think
Regular entrepreneur
Taylor?
Ashley But I'm sure my esteemed
colleague has told you all about me
He's told me all about you
Well, I better run
You two lovebirds have a swell time
Been a pleasure meeting you, April
You certainly are
a lovely young woman
Who was that?
Just an old friend
Nobody
Yeah
Wow
This is cool
Yeah
It's my favorite spot
What's so funny?
Nothing
So, uh
What do we do now?
I haven't really
thought that far ahead
Which is funny,
'cause usually that's all I do
Think ahead
I try not to think at all
Well, look where it got me
In the barn,
with my mother's "lovah"
I guess I'm just starting to feel
Stuck, you know?
Why? This
This is great
Look around you
I mean, seriously,
look at everyone
They're slaving away
for houses, cars, stock options
They're completely
dying inside, and for what?
In 30, 40 years,
what's the sun gonna set on?
This
It's... it's like a mundane lockdown
You're startin' to sound like my friend
I don't think I'm
too keen on your friend
Yeah
I don't blame you
I don't really like him sometimes, either
So why you with him?
He's all I got
That's sad
You're sad
So what happened to you?
What happened to me
Let's see
Well, I never knew my dad
Didn't really know my mom
She was a hippie
They fucked, they had me,
and they never gave a shit about me
And she dropped me on my head
when I was six months old
I know, fuckin' ridiculous
I got a dent, right here
It's flat Feel it
And I'm a thief
And I fuck people over
How's thatworkin' out for ya?
Pretty good, I guess
Yeah?
Brought you here?
For what?
Just tryin' to get by
When can I see you again?
I'm sure you'll find me
I don't think she liked me
No, I don't think
she liked you, either
You're gonna fuckin'
blowthis for us, man
What are you...
what are you talkin' about?
Fuckin' show in there
Big fuckin' deal
We gotta get outta here anyway, man
People are gettin' suspicious
This town is fuckin' bullshit
Just drive
Calm down, pal
Let's go up to Westchester County
There's fuckin' rich people
out the ass up there
Or Miami
Whatever, man
Just, can we go?
Jesus Christ
So what's
the deal with Ashley?
He's my best friend We
We grew up together
Went into foster care
People we knew
from the neighborhood
Whatwas that like?
Let's see, eight kids
in a one-bedroom apartment
fighting over scraps
I mean, we lived off
of leftover Greek food
from this diner they owned
That's extraordinarily fucked up
Yeah, that's, uh
that's not the half of it
What's the other half?
Ashley's dad gave him this
German shepherd when he was alive
After his dad died, they let us
keep the dog at the foster home
That dog was so cool
and so smart
He sensed that our new
ma and pop, Frank and Sally,
you know, they
weren't stand-up people
So, after years of the dog
hating them, growling at 'em,
and trying to bite them,
they said enough was enough
So one night at dinner,
good old Frank says, "Hey, Ashley!
What do you think of the stew?"
Ashley said,
"For a chef, it tastes like shit"
Frank said, "Well, it should,
'cause it's dog meat"
Then he threw
the dog collar at Ashley
We beat his ass that night
Put him in the hospital for a month
Ashley crippled his hands
He used the door as a vise
He wanted it to be a constant reminder
Every time he looked at those hands
he would remember what he did
Don't do that
Do what?
Pity him He... he hates it
I wasn't
So, where in NewYork did you live?
Brooklyn
I always wanted to live there
I've always wanted
to move back
You wanna go?
Yeah, okay
Yeah?
J-j, yeah, j-just like that
Yeah, just like that
O-o-okay
Well, uh, give me
a couple days to sort some shit out
You'd better make it fast
I might change my mind
I will
I wanna bring her with us
Who, Pollyanna?
April
- You gotta be fuckin' kidding...
- Quit fuckin' around
You can't be fuckin' serious
Oh, I'm serious
Oh, I get it
She read about guys like us
in her little beat-poetry
feministworkshop
Huh? The tortured rebel
with the heart of gold?
You done?
How's she gonna react
when she finds outwhat you really do?
What you're really like?
That you steal fuckin' cars,
you rob houses, you do drugs...
She knowss
- Really?
- Yeah
She doesn't give a shit?
No, she doesn't
Fuck
A bad little rich girl
Shit, fuck it, man
She can come with us
What are you doing?
Just
you know, thinking
Go on
You can say it...
I deserve it
Deserve what?
You were right
You're always right
How did you
get to be so smart, huh?
I'm so sorry, April
It's all right
You got it out of your system
Mm, no
No, for all of it
For everything
I miss Dad
I miss him, too
God, I miss him so much
I tried, you know
ltjust all went by so fast, and
Oh, whatwas I thinking,
trying to replace him
Hey, you did the best you could
You were always so strong
I feel like I'm losing you
You're not losing me
I'm right here
Been here
Don't end up like me
Okay?
You need to get out of here
Well, let's go, come on Yeah
Let's get out of here is right!
Come on!
I can't I can't
Why not?
One day you're gonna understand
I-I don't think
I can go alone
Oh
Yes, you can
You have it in you
You're so strong
Maybe I don'twanna
Well, sometimes, you know,
it's not aboutwhatwe want
It's aboutwhatwe need
Coming!
I'll get it
Thanks, sweetie
- Hey
- What are you doing here?
I need to talk to you
Okay, go around the back
Yeah, no Thanks
Who's that?
Jehovah's Witness
Oh
Do I have time
for a walk before we eat?
Sure lt'll wait
Cool
Well, thatwas a brilliant move
Whatwere you gonna say
when my mom answered the door?
I don't care
No?
No
I love you
Really?
Well that's, uh, that's intense
Yeah I love you
I love her!
I don't think she cares
Let's go
Let's get you outta here
Mm Butwhere?
Anywhere
I love you
I love your smile
I'll come back and get you
Okay
Ash!
Hey, April
Hi
Oh, um
Aston, right?
Ashley
Taylor's friend
Ashley, yeah
Uhwhat's up?
Apparently, your stepdad
found out about
what's going on
with Taylor and your mom and
he's pissed
Really?
Shit
We're supposed to meet Taylor
at this diner
He's tying up some loose ends
Butwe gotta hurry
Uh, yeah
Oh, okay, let me just stop by home first
I'll see you there
Taylor didn't think that
was a good idea
Uh
Do you mind driving?
Uhyeah o-okay
Come on, we gotta hurry
April!
Excuse me, can I help you?
Yeah, where is she?
Honey, do you knowthis kid?
Is he a friend of April's?
I-I guess he must be
Is she here?
No, she's not here right now
What the fuck was that?
I have no idea
He's gone now
You should really eat something
You're too skinny
Not all guys want to date
15-year-old anorexic models
It's kinda gross
So where's Taylor,
'cause you did say he was here
Personally, I like girls
with a little curve
- Thank you
- You're welcome
So tell me about yourself, April
I reallywant to get to know you
I justwanna get to knowthe girl
that my best friend's fallen for
Is he coming?
Think I'll have a little smoke
Don'tworry
I'm not gonna hurt you
What kinda person
do you think I am?
You sure are pretty
You can't smoke in here
You wanna take that to go?
No
We're done Thank you
- You okay?
- We're fine, thank you
Just the check, please
That'll do it
Thank you Huh?
Where are my manners?
No thanks, I don't smoke
Never?
Not even socially?
Not even for me?
My dad died of cancer
Bummer
Mm-hm
You fuckin' think you love him?
You fuckin' love him?
You shouldn't play games with people
I haven't
You gave him hope
I have hope
Well, it must be nice
You're his soul mate
You're soul mates, is that it?
What's your soul look like, April?
Is it like your name?
All spring and flowers?
I don't know
What's yours look like, Ash?
What does it look like?
He loved you
I know
At least you fuckin' had him!
Taylor!
What the fuck's going on?
You tell me
what the fuck's going on here!
What the fuck is going on here?
Did he touch you?
Did you fucking touch her?
- Is it?
- Put it down!
Is thatwhat?
What the fuck's going on here?
- What happened?
- He's just
II
Put the gun down
What's going on here?
Do you remember
when I picked you up
when you got out?
And we got in that car
Let's go
Let's get the fuck outta here
I can't
I can't!
Ash, put the fucking gun down
They're coming
I didn't call them
Oh, shit
It hurts too fucking much,
and I can't fucking take it anymore
Ash, put the fucking gun down
Put the gun down!
No! No! This is
how I fucking want it!
I love you!
I loveyou
Get in the car! Ash!
Ash!
# I go away #
# To a place #
# My peace of mind I find #
# I lie my head #
# I close my eyes #
# And trap the love #
# No matter what they wanna
think of ya #
# You gotta look 'em in the eye
and say Brotha #
# You're never gonna be
more than another broken soul #
# No matter what they wanna
think of ya #
# You gotta look 'em in the eye
and say Brotha #
# Brotha, brotha #
# You're just a lonely soul #
# I go away #
# Lose my place #
# This world it just stands still #
# The way in line,
lose their minds #
# For the sake of love and loss #
# No matter what they wanna
think of ya #
# You gotta look 'em in the eye
and say Brotha #
# You're never gonna be
more than another broken soul #
# No matter what they
wanna think of ya #
# You gotta look 'em in the eye
and say Brotha #
# Brotha, brotha #
# You gotta walk with me... ##