there are many, many centuries,
in old China,
a very beautiful youth lived,
called Kwan Yin.
In a moment of passion, she was
pregnant still before marrying.
When the father discovered
such transgression,
it felt the bastard son's shame.
In a fit of anger, he perforated him/her
the eyes and it tore him/her the womb.
He believed that would annihilate like this
his/her body and his/her soul.
When dying, the youth pressed in the hand
a mysterious jade amulet
and it intoned a secret prayer.
When they buried her, still
it pressed in the hands the amulet.
According to the legend, the prayer allowed
. his/her soul to continue to live
and the amulet
it checked him/her can magic.
in the course of time, they were
raised temples in his/her memory.
most of their followers,
they worshipped her for the purity
that she had maintained in life.
But some adored her
for the power that she had in the death.
they Believed that who controlled
the amulet, would obtain a secret power.
they Believed to obtain the immortality,
if a pure soul was sacrificed
at the same time that if it intoned
Kwan Yin's prayer.
THE amulet was the key of everything.
20 years ago, the epic demand
for the secret grave
it reached the end.
MOUNTAINOUS CHAIN OF QINLING
SOUTH OF CHINA
PORTO OF SANTA ELENA
CALIFÓRNIA CENTRAL
Ancestral spirit of Kwan Yin,
he/she lets to immolate us these bodies and souls.
I give you my body and my soul.
I am Kwan Yin, died before time.
My heart and my soul
they are pure.
My body is dead,
but my soul lives.
I am Kwan Yin, died before time.
My heart and my soul
they are pure.
My body is dead,
but my soul lives.
You have to submit!
Your soul, I need your soul.
You will use her power in your advantage
and not for anything of pure.
I don't give you my soul!
No ta give.
No!
You will never have our souls.
Yours not.
I will wait
that your daughter Mindy grows.
Mindy?
CLUB OF CULT
Argument
Production
Accomplishment
UNIVERSITY OF FULLFORD
PRESENT
In the first half of the semester
we ended that Abraham, Jesus and Mohammed,
the three great illustrations of the monotheism,
they were worshipped.
What more they had them in common?
You won't say that had all
beard and they lived in the Medium East, Alex!
It is me to sand the whole jokes.
- You don't have joke...
- Remain silent, this can be important.
They were expelled of the breast...
- Are Mindy, well?
- Yes.
...that can give them
the so desired interior peace.
- I have a question.
- Say.
He/she is to try to compare the génese
of great world religions
with the sect idea?
Of course no. The sects
they are something totally different.
They end for perverting the own base
in that you/they were founded.
See what the followers have to do,
for if they maintain in the good thanks.
Some give the savings
of a life.
Others submit. mutilation
of the body.
And there are still the ones that arrive,
and allow me the cliché,
to go behind the maralha, so to speak.
I reformulate the original question.
What is that main religions of the
does world have in common with the sects?
- The district.
- Exactly.
They already heard to say that the terror of one
can man be the freedom of other?
A man's sect,
it can be the religion of other.
And for today, it arrives.
Remember that these final projects
they are worth 25% of your note.
Alex, Mindy, Cassandra,
Bailey and Morgan.
Be with me one more minutes.
I want to discuss your project.
I hope is fast.
I have training.
You are the mascot, mine!
Just because you have a spirit
depressing academic,
he/she doesn't have to unload in me.
Cover me the retreat.
Fork, Bears! Bears!
Bears will win...
- Where is Morgan?
- He/she is sick.
I think he/she had an infection, but I go
to be with her in the library, this night.
Very well, I was to review
the proposals of the projects
and, to be frank,
your it worries me.
But it is a radical research.
Do Massacre him/it of Kwan Yin's Temple?
That is almost a baseboard note
in the history Taoist and, still for top,
it is an open wound in this community.
But it is not that our function
of investigators?
To diffuse in the baseboard notes
and to do of them chapters of the History.
Because, what badly is that can have?
They can discover things
very disturbing.
As well as Jesus' scene
to be preached?
It is not only disturbing,
because we are already habituated. Right?
All of religions have yours
more shameful moments.
He/she is well, I don't only want
that you/they are enthusiastic of more.
Don't worry. We will maintain the
laziness and the indifference of the habit.
He/she is well, they can go.
- Good-bye.
- Are you well?
- Yes.
- Of certainty?
- Clear.
I thought that were to shake.
He/she walks here.
We see in the more afternoon.
Do I appear, ok?
Mindy, as it is that convinced them
to be so enthusiastic?
I don't know about what is to speak.
He/she told them that he/she was his/her student
favorite and that we would always have an A.
This project
he/she is going against my will.
Come to speak with me,
if they find some thing that...
That...
If they find some thing.
What is that he/she will happen with Mindy?
- That great intuition yours.
- Didn't you notice?
It was beside her, and she is mine
friend. What is that find?
- Do you want even to go thereabout?
- If you want.
Because it is that you don't enjoy
be we him together, Cassandra?
They are alone three years. Because it is that
do you have to be always so difficult?
I don't know.
"Mindy?"
"Who are you?"
"Your friend Bailey."
"Hello."
"How is it that he/she runs the study in group?"
"There is no group. I am alone me.
Morgan was frustrated."
I am not me to complain.
I Think are. Apposed that nor
you left the residence the whole day.
I was about 45 minutes in the crosswalk,
to do exercise.
Because yes. You will bring that ember
of your room friend. party?
I don't know if she goes.
He/she had a discussion with the father
today of guile and he/she left to cry.
Morgan?
"Are Bailey, oh?"
I gave cable of my whole work this
night and I have the inflamed throat.
That should be of my enormous one...
It is not anything of that.
You are really disgusting.
"Yes?"
"He/she will have with me to the patio, now!"
You are with luck, the parties of the
republic is only worthwhile after 11 o'clock.
he/she Sees there if your room friend
he/she appears .
Because yes.
it Goes there, it liked that tanned
the three. Do you align, right?
Then, we will forget the party.
I will have the house there.
He/she stops being stupid!
- it Seeks me when there you arrive.
- Combined.
- can you go well boazona?
- You can have faith.
I am now to enter in he/she douches him,
therefore he/she sees there if you are a dear one
and don't pull the autoclismo, until me to leave.
- Is he/she well?
- Excuse.
Who was that?
It was only a hideous fufa
to arm in goat.
- What was?
- I tell you for the road, he/she walks.
Now, Mindy, are the sure that
was the image of the book Morgan?
He/she resembled her.
If it is like this, she runs danger.
is there anybody?
Yes?
We walked. it seeks of Morgan.
Did you see her?
I didn't see her/it in the whole day.
- Do you make idea where she can be from?
- Because ray there was me of knowing?
If it suits, for beings the room friend!
Shit!
Mindy, walks here.
He/she walks here.
It was one of my students.
- Did she seem him/her disturbed?
- Quite distant and absentee... yes.
If he/she has more quest.es,
I enter in contact get.
- Right. Thank you.
- Thank you.
The Police judge
that Morgan committed suicide,
but I think her death
he/she makes to remind that of Kwan Yin.
She was not more involved
in the projecto than us.
You knew that she took
antidepressive?
No. We were not like this so arrivals,
but...
I find same that owed
to diffuse in another projecto.
Or then, I postpone the period
of the projecto if you...
No. I want to continue.
You don't want at least
to ask to the other ones?
It is not necessary.
Are you well?
He/she thought that had already gone you away.
And I went, but later I decided to wait for you.
So that?
He/she wanted to have the certainty
that were well.
Because it is that had to be?
- Already nothing of what sees myself surprises.
- How like this?
- Was it like this, your whole life?
- More or less.
Not always they were like this
strange or violent,
but from small that I see things
that I don't know how to explain.
- What type of things?
- I know there.
My mother's face to smile.
It is good, but it is strange.
She died when I had one year.
I don't know how it is that can remember.
That has to do with your visual cortex.
Then, there are things that I see
and that remove me the sleep.
A lot of things remind me that
of Kwan Yin's temple, that people.
Mindy, because it is that you didn't do
the alone investigation?
Because it is that dragged us?
I think he/she wanted somebody to lean on.
And you have.
I am.
Does he/she give me my teacup of coffee?
- Can you pick me in the work?
- Yes.
- it is that I dislike to go alone home .
- Everything well.
Yes?
You order a  and - mail  to the rest of the group
on the meeting tomorrow, right?
- Yes. It is .s two.
- Exacto.
You know that plus, Mindy, think if
we spoke to the Prof. Eastbrook,
she put us in a different projecto...
No. He/she wants to say, already falámos,
and she said for us to continue.
- Are you good with computers?
- I am an aselha.
- Because, because...
- Seriously.
You could research some thing
on Kwan Yin's temple.
Clear.
This explains everything.
Yes?
Who is there he/she?
Of the other times
he/she didn't also have grace.
He/she calms there, Kournikova.
- Did they return you to annoy today?
- Because it was.
When he/she meets, I give you a squeeze
that you never again straighten.
What is that happened you today
in the classes, small?
Anything. He/she was only tired.
If it suits have to go with more calm
in this projecto.
No, it is everything well.
.s times, when they grow,
the people relax a little.
Thank you, I know about that.
I won't meet as
encontrámos Morgan, yes?
No.
You already know that can count on me,
if you need of some thing.
Because it is that everyone
does he/she say the same?
Because? Because we adored you.
- Because yes.
- And you are a goat.
If you do want go see
the such temple marado,
you know that I align.
Fasten.
He/she walks here.
We see each other later.
Among.
Does he/she happen some thing?
No longer I know what is real and what is one
myth between this history and Morgan.
Mindy, learned if some thing
in my chair,
you know that everything is a myth.
The religion bases on the faith.
Then, and Morgan?
How is it that explains that?
She was with a depression.
She could have committed suicide her,
he/she wants was in the projecto or not.
I will tell you a thing,
but you cannot say anybody.
It is secret.
Morgan was pregnant.
Then the depression.
You are too involved in this.
You have of relativizar the things.
- Hello.
He/she signs here.
Here you have.
Are you well?
Do you feel well?
Yes, excuse.
I am only a little tense.
It should be some "caught."
How is it that are going those potatoes?
A delicacy.
And the funniest
it is that me nor I prove.
The funniest
it is that nor you try to be humble.
- Mindy.
- Yes. Hello, father.
- What is that he/she happens?
- Teacher Eastbrook.
Did you know the girl that was died?
The rumors here for the kitchen
they say that she walked put
in a sect with drugs.
They are same coscuvilheiros. Nobody
he/she takes her malts of the kitchen seriously.
You want to put in cause the moral carácter
of the people that make your food?
You are right. But I knew her, yes.
We were not arrived.
We had a chair committees, only that.
- Are you well?
- I am.
I only walk a little concerned.
Do you know him/it what should do soon?
A family dinner.
He/she doesn't please to see me you to eat
these refeic.es all alone one.
Soon.
- Good-bye.
- I adore you, filhota.
I think are to hide him/her
a lot of thing. She doesn't know about anything.
I feel a lot. He/she doesn't compete to me.
She is not my daughter.
Hello, everything well?
How is it going that?
I already made the research, and I found
very frightening scenes.
What is that you discovered?
He/she has to do with the leader of the sect,
twenty years ago.
- Yes, I already know about his existence.
- But do you know like him entered in the country?
Which do know his aspect is?
How is it going that?
I wait that the meeting of to speak
of what it happened. Morgan yesterday.
Personal, I have to dispatch me.
The boss will be harmed with me
for being me to neglect so much.
I ended for finding some
informac.es on this leader.
Good! Who is?
This type here. See.
Owen Quinlin.
He/she has a strange aspect.
Were you. does he/she wait that? Of the winner
of a beauty contest?
He/she waited a type of Chinese Christ.
Quinlin passed some time in China,
but it disappeared there are about 20 years.
Because?
Was he where?
Nobody knows for sure, but the type
he/she appeared in American soil again.
Here, in our town.
- Is it later?
- It was how Eastbrook said.
"A man's sect,
it can be the religion of other."
He began to seek followers.
Women. Young pure like Kwan Yin
and ready for if they give him/her.
I don't notice because it is that he would gather
followers to imitate Kwan Yin.
Because, alegadamente,
she had a god's power.
He should want to capture that power.
It is that Kwan Yin became pregnant
before marrying.
The father had her forbidden of loving one
lower class man.
When he/she discovered
that she will give. light a bastard son
he/she was so rioted by his/her only daughter
to stain the good name of the family,
that perforated him/her the eyes
and it tore him/her the womb
to kill him/her the body, the soul and the son.
Just as Morgan.
Morgan committed suicide because of one
sect disappeared 20 years ago?
That abnormal!
This can seem strange,
but he/she walked to research in a book
on Kwan Yin and I found the drawing
of a girl to be died.
He/she was Morgan.
- What?
- No. That is impossible.
Do you find?
- He/she lets to see me. Am I also there?
- I wait albeit yes. We will see.
I want to show you a thing.
That is frightening.
Did you receive that, like this for mail?
If to cassette he/she has same material
fasten, we will have the best presentation.
For speaking in that... Me .s times I am one
little nervous to speak in public.
- We have to solve that.
- He/she hears there...
All of the weeks you walk to the jumps
. front of a thousand of people.
That is very different.
That is not my face.
There, I am masked.
I am the Urso Saltitao.
Remain silent, I will begin this to run.
Ok, fork.
I already watched a porn film
that began like this.
What does he be to say?
All are dead.
They committed suicide all!
Massacre him/it happened even.
Because?
I don't know.
But I think were to try
to arrive to something higher.
He/she wants to say... it is the foundation
of all of religi.es, right?
We approximate ourselves of God
or of that that we adored.
They were to adore
the statue of a dead Chinese.
I think are us
to approximate of any thing.
How like this?
To approach that?
- I don't know... of the truth.
- The truth? On the one what?
We should go to the temple.
That is a very nice ranch
to serve as stage to a massacre.
- That is enormous.
- He/she is quiet.
There is no reason to laugh of Kwan Yin.
It was the agony and no the laughter
that he/she had room in this sacred ground.
Excuse.
That scene more marada.
If you don't know how to behave as adult,
he/she is outside, as the dogs.
What is that he/she brings you
to Kwan Yin's temple?
We are to do research
for a work.
- And who are you?
- I am the monk Gee Ming.
I am the guardian and protector
of the souls that wander for the temple.
- Beautiful job.
- He/she is quiet.
Because it is that they need
of proteccao?
Because there are people that wants to abuse
of Kwan Yin's power.
Is he/she to refer Owen Quinlin?
Mine, he is dead.
Us vimo-Io to die in the cassette.
The death is a revolving door.
Kwan Yin proved quite so.
Accompany me.
This is to be
a strange little bit.
Quinlin judged that if it sacrificed him/her
his/her people, she would give him/her his/her power.
It will be that was for that
what did Morgan die?
Good. Then, did he return?
That doesn't scare me.
Quinlin judged that he/she had obtained
the power, but something ran badly.
It is now he is sanded,
and we are home of him.
Personal, what is that?
What ray is that?
There is still more to learn.
My beautiful geisha...
I will take this to show.
She got scared...
The acolytes' spirits
they are arrested here.
The death arrested them
instead of freeing.
Alex, uses your machine
and ribbon some pictures.
You think he gets
to feel the spirits?
He doesn't seat anything.
Get.
And I think also get.
Feel...
Ribbon .quilo.
He/she photographs a thing of those.
They go. front. It is a lot fastens.
P.e-you under her!
Because it is that seek
the answer the these quest.es?
To discover the truth.
Which truth?
The one of Quinlin or your?
Of the one what is it that is to speak?
Some thing invoked of turn
the evil spirits.
He is still thirsty
for Kwan Yin's power.
He/she waits there...
How is it that we see each other free from him?
He is to hide some thing.
- Do you find?
- Let us go.
Personal!
Personal, this doesn't have grace.
Your involvement
it is not coincidence,
and your presence became dangerous.
They should leave
and never again here to return.
Wait. What is that there is there?
The Past and the Future.
The conflict and the resolution.
I have to go.
His power is more and more strong.
They are going walking that I already pick you.
My lady...
...is it true?
Release me!
What ray?
Shit!
Help!
Help! Let to do!
My God, we were also here.
- Let to do!
- Alex, is going to the right.
- He/she goes until. door.
Alex, walks here. He/she gives me your hand.
He/she gives me your hands. We go, it jumps!
- Are you well?
- My God, my God...
We go for here. We go for here.
- This place is too strange.
- What is that he/she happened?
Hallelujah!
It seems that passed there hours.
Mindy?
Are Mindy, well?
I am.
That rich projecto. Fork, Bears.
- What ray is that happened there inside?
- Of the one what is it that are to speak?
Mindy, know very well
of what it is that am to speak...
- No. I don't know.
- Are you to hide some thing?
Hear well, Gee Ming said
that what was exhumed
he/she cannot return.
Yes, that I noticed.
Quinlin returned.
Do you know him/it what? I think he counts
the same tretas
to any one that will beat him/her. door.
He/she was Morgan.
When she committed suicide,
he/she opened him/her the door for him to return.
- She became pregnant out of the marriage.
- I am to see. Just as Kwan Yin.
Now, he comes to try to finish
that that began 20 years ago.
That this scene is sanded. "Scooby Donate."
Even if leads. chair,
I have more important things
to do in the life.
I think Mindy is right.
"I think Mindy is right."
Didn't you hear?
- I am out!
- Alex, and our work?
That the work is sanded.
Make him/it without me.
They will complain about me. Eastbrook,
do what understand. He/she finished.
All are scared, Alex.
But we are not to flee.
- Then, they are all some idiots.
- He/she sees there as speeches.
I see him/it that, his/her idiot,
pretentious and fake?
He/she goes but it is to drink your soy milk,
p.e a music in the iPod
and it will start there the day to order
messages. girlfriend.
"Oh my love, taste so much of you."
What was?
Not even you arrive for her!
What is that you will do,
does he/she tell me, his/her son of the mother?
He/she will sand you, Alex.
He/she has pity. I should be the only
that you still didn't eat.
Stop with that, boys.
Stop.
You can do what to please.
Eastbrook won't annoy us
therefore.
But I will extricate this.
It is exactly like that.
He/she flees while it is time.
He/she will seek you!
Fork Bears!
Hello Urso Bradley.
Did you miss?
Today not.
They are bedtimes.
Thank you.
I am the Saltatory Bear.
He wants you to be with him.
No lho give.
He is the instrument of the death.
It is the return of the evil.
- Excuse.
- You nailed me a death fright.
Do you have time to speak?
It is on Morgan.
He/she didn't know more with whom speaks
on this without seeming crazy.
It is not worthwhile to doubt
of the mental sanity of the other ones.
I found this in Morgan's things.
Is Morgan, right?
Yes.
You saw her
in the day in what that happened?
Yes, she was strange.
He/she was very calm.
He/she had the red eyes,
as if he/she had state to cry.
I thought that was for her to be depressed.
- Her father is an idiot.
- What is that you want to say with that?
He told him/her that he/she was embarrassed
of being her father.
Such and which like Kwan Yin.
Rejected by the father.
It was the opportunity of Quinlin.
He/she excuses...
He/she forgets what I said.
I also found this.
Where?
In the box of her bijutarias.
The mother called and she asked me
that arranged her things.
I saw this and...
...he/she knew that didn't belong to Morgan.
But as it is that you know
what did have to do with her death?
That followed me for the room.
What?
He/she judged that he/she had kept him/it,
and that appeared in my pocket.
I made the same again,
and he/she appeared in my neck.
I threw him/it for the window and it went back to me.
I will see what get to discover.
- Yes?
- Hello, Fetish.
- Hello, Mrs. Farrell.
- As you are?
- I am well.
- fortunately.
I already have her things
almost arranged.
We want to bury her with
her necklace. Did you already arrange him/it?
I didn't see him/it.
please, he/she sees if you find him/it.
It is very important for us.
I will see what get to do.
Enter.
Hello.
He/she wanted to speak with you the alone ones.
It is because of the projecto, Mindy.
I think are to exaggerate.
What do you be to say?
There are people to die.
Exacto, Mindy. And I don't want
that happens to us.
I think didn't owe
to take this forward.
He/she has grace.
You said that supported me.
I support you.
If you want to go, it goes.
He/she disappears, it goes!
What do want you to say with that?
He/she is going to another group,
because I will move forward with this.
- We see each other thereabout.
- Yes, maybe.
Fetish! Fetish, are you there?
He/she opens the door!
I only wanted the truth.
I think deserve that.
You make idea of the one that is increase
without anything to know of my mother?
Of the one what do you be to speak?
Of your wife.
I know about Kwan Yin.
I know that she was part of the sect.
Did you think that I will feel?
I didn't have him/it done.
But now I can do-Io,
because you disappointed me.
- He/she was only to try to protect you.
- That? Of my mother?
- How is it that you discovered?
- In the chair of the Prof. Eastbrook.
I made a work
on him it massacres of Kwan Yin.
He/she seemed that some thing pulled me.
Now, I already know because.
What?
I am going to the end with this, alone.
I am very close, father.
It is for some to happen thing
very bad and I can avoid her.
I think was that that the mother
he/she was to do or to try.
How is it that she died?
How?
- It was stabbed itself own.
- Where?
In the throat.
I have to go.
- Because it is that you didn't tell me?
- I thought didn't compete me.
Besides, you didn't get to impede her.
Because it is that you judge that I get?
Mindy, wait.
Mindy, please waits.
Did he/she also know about my mother, it is not?
He/she could have told me.
Do you think that left you satisfied?
Don't try to make a mistake.
You are not the person type that gives up,
just because they tell you for doing.
Somebody should have myself statement some thing,
don't find?
Like this, there would not be people to die.
Mindy, if you go with this forward
the close can be you.
He/she judged that was everything a myth.
I was to try to refrain the imagination
of an entrepreneur.
There are things that one can study,
to understand the religion.
But he/she believes, there are things
in that nor we should play.
He/she should have impeded me
of beginning this projecto.
He/she could not stop.
He is part of your family history.
Well, that means that am me
that I have to stop Quinlin.
- Then?
- We have that to help.
He/she gives me time
to investigate Kwan Yin
and he/she comes to have with me to my cabinet
in half hour.
Hello, I have to close the house.
Can you pick me in one hour?
I am not able to, Cassie. You can arrange
another person to accompany you?
He/she hears... I know that we have to talk
on some things.
AND I adored to hear, but...
he/she did Want to speak to you
of some things.
I Have to treat of some things
for the classes.
does he/she Have to be now?
This night?
- Yes.
- Ok. Do you tie me later?
- Ok.
- it is well.
Do you have one second?
You don't need to give more explicac.es.
This is really a madness.
All have the nerves in bang.
I think I know in a way of stopping.
I discovered that he/she was my mother
that was in the center of the circle.
In that cassette.
She didn't submit because he/she knew something
that the another didn't know.
It was for that that Quinlin
he/she didn't have success.
- Because... but she committed suicide.
- Yes, but it was not for him.
Her faith-Io to impede
that something bad happened.
Therefore, I have a plan.
- Did you end there in the machine of the yogurts?
- Yes.
- Did you restore the palhinhas?
It is that you always forget.
Then, it tells me as they ran
the things with Bailey.
- Good night.
Is there anybody?
I don't think so there are like this so much people
disposed to commit suicide.
It is not necessary. An is enough...
...and I think I know
as to bring of turn.
Shit!
- Cassie?
- Cassandra?
He/she releases me!
Still no terminámos.
- Cassandra?
- Cassie?
- Bailey.
- What is that?
It is a long history,
but this is not good.
You are the sure that you know
what are to do?
"To invoke Kwan Yin's spirit,
it is necessary the sacrifice of the souls.
"A pure soul that follows the steps
of Kwan Yin to the hell
"and return as a god.
"But that person should possess
Kwan Yin's old amulet.
"In agreement with the sacred book..."
I have state. he/she waits of Mindy.
- Cassie! Cassie, where are you?
- He/she waits, we won't seek at random.
What do suggest?
We have to find Gee Ming.
He knows any thing.
You remember the room
what didn't he want to show us?
I felt that there was there something.
He/she waits there, Mindy,
do you sit down or do you know?
I saw. I know. I saw me own
to pull my eyes.
- Balls. And do we want there to return?
- We have that finding. Walk.
Diane? Diane! My God,
what is that happened?
- Mindy...
- What does she have?
She will sacrifice him.
But without the sacred prayer,
everything is in vain.
The sacred book...
He/she saved Kwan Yin.
He can save Mindy...
...and to kill the spirit of Quinlin.
P.e end to this.
Mindy.
Alex is dead.
All died. The Fetish, Morgan,
Teacher Eastbrook...
- And Cassandra?
- I didn't see her.
Does he now walk behind us, it is not?
- Only of me.
- No.
Died before time.
My heart and my soul
they are pure.
My body is dead,
but my soul lives.
Don't let to die her.
Not without the sacred book.
Bailey?
No!
Cassie! Cassie! Cassie!
Cassie, you are well.
I think so.
What was?
- I think he will kill myself.
- Who?
We go, we got.
Calm.
We only have to do one more thing.
Gee Ming, is arrived the hour.
Here you are you.
He/she moves me that tail, mine!
- Do you seat the energy?
- That that is sanded.
To me no longer you deceive me. He/she gets up then
the tail and it takes me to the sacred books!
Mindy!
The pages are all burned.
Mindy, cannot be to speak seriously.
We leave of here.
Let us go.
This puts an end to everything.
It is alone one more sacrifice Kwan Yin.
I think your plan won't result.
What is that you want to say with that?
We only needed Kwan Yin's prayer.
Quinlin burned the sacred books.
- What?
- We are sanded.
- Mindy! Mindy!
- He/she is my father.
Father, Teacher Eastbrook is dead.
- He/she brought this of her cabinet.
- What is this?
- It is Kwan Yin's prayer.
- What does this mean?
We have to recreate the sacrifice.
We will use the corpses,
as in the cassette.
If it sacrifices me, I can snatch
the power of Kwan Yin to Quinlin.
That that if it sacrifices
and to read Kwan Yin's prayer
it will follow their steps to the hell
and he/she will return as a god.
We will make this,
before it lacks us the courage.
That person has to have the amulet.
Wait... we needed the amulet.
He/she is at the other room,
where I saw you before.
I go buscá-Io.
Was it of this amulet that you needed?
My God! Cassie! No!
What are you to do her?
Mindy, what do we do?
Cassie!
He/she says the prayer, Mindy.
Cassie, have to say these words.
He/she repeats mentally.
My body is dead,
but my soul lives.
I am Kwan Yin, died before time.
You are to give beginning
to a world totally new.
Cassie, says the ray of the words!
"My heart and my soul
they are pure." He/she repeats, Cassie.
- Please...
- Cassie, repeats!
- Cassie, speech.
- He/she will sand you!
No!
Cassie!
- I don't submit.
- I force you.
It is not worthwhile.
Before I want to die as the other ones
and to be here prey for the eternity.
Then, just as Kwan Yin,
you will die your father's .s hands.
Kwan Yin's heart
it was pure as yours.
But with this amulet, I obtain
the power that your mother denied me.
Mindy. Mindy.
I Lament so much
to have left you alone.
I saw you.
All my life saw these moments.
it is always wanted to tell you
that feel your lack.
I Adore you.
AND it is for that that you will live.
Kwan Yin's amulet
it saved your soul that is pure.
your body will live, thanks
. your delivery and to your sacrifice.
- He/she excuses, father.
- Because?
My God...
Bailey.
Bailey?
Cassie...
it finishes Like this one more chapter
of Kwan Yin's legend.
instead of losing,
one more life survived.
But the last book
it is still for writing
because the natural human tendency
to do ligac.es to the past
he/she will never stop existing.
Translation and legendagem:
Edit Raposo - TRADUVÁRIUS