Huangshi's Kid
How about playing basketball later?
Are you nuts?
Maybe.
I used to be on a boat
I'm sympathetic to you, man
but I have to stay healthy
I'm marrying on Tuesday
Congratulations
So, I have to be back
to Nanjing on time
I'm the driver of
the Red Cross
Really?
You are going to Nanjing
Yeah, I'll start two days
before the wedding
Let's have a drink together
Great
I have a good idea
ok
I told you,
journalists can't
go to Nanjing
So just ask the Japanese
They are the master now
Bath, this is my best friend,
Endilis, he came here
to visit his love
I'm Jiashlong
Hello
This is Captain Lujibath,
the bitch of British consular
I met Mr. Fet before
Excuse me, help yourselves
His girlfriend,
they will get married Tuesday.
He won't come back on Tuesday
He would go to
hill tomorrow morning
You son of a bitch, you are the
one who gave him the passport.
Fuck you, how long we
have been friends?
Please forgive me, Mr. Aps
He is not a journalist.
He is a member of Red Cross,
so he could get the passport.
We need the passport to Anji
since we are the member
of Red Cross.
We can finally go to
Nanjing, Baers.
Trust me
I'm Endis, you are Felibaks.
We are drivers for the Red Cross.
You send the
medicine to Nanjing.
For this,
Endis wants to get married.
If you do this, we
can help all of them.
God, are you crazy.
shit.
Eide.
Eide is over there.
Who's that?
I know who he is.
Why'd he come here?
He's going to Nanjing as well.
Just keep your watch
one hours ahead.
Now we should use
the Tokyo zone.
Do you know what
Tokyo speak in Japanese?
They are here to help Chinese.
They said that Chinese
is disordered.
Ride, military, and the fight.
They came here
to help you Chinese.
Nonsense.
They are not against China.
I told you why they
do not try to straight a war
if they don't do that
they can capture
Chinese people as they wish
and they can do anything
without be blamed
Japanese are not barbarians
But they thought others are
See
So many people
They are coming from Nanjing
World War II begins
but we don't know that
Parking
park over there
our identity were Americans
so just speak in English
got it, captain
We are Red Cross
the materials in the car
is sending from Britain
we must check the car
guys
get into the car
hey, all of you
sorry, captain
These substances are
disinfect drugs
Can you
just be careful
when you check these things
as they are very precious
ok
go
if you don't come
back before nine
I have to go alone
ok
good luck
you two, that way
hurry up
I'm trapped in a building
which is bombed down
there are many Japanese
soldiers outside
the city is so quiet
keep in line
go go
ready
check
there is one
Tokyo impress me very well
I've been there for
three months
and I met so many
good guys there
and I think there
are very good
China
so many things to painted
but I don't paint very good
do you want more tea?
no, thank you
go, hurry up
give me the cigarettes
now, we are safe
what's your name
where are you come from
British
who do you know
no one would wear like
this but janelist
brother, look there,
the street over there
where is here
Who are you
this is the
Commissioner of Tax
my first name is Chen
Chen Haisheng
Chen Haisheng you can
tell me Haisheng
why they want to kill you
they don't capture British
I saw something
should not be seen
really?
I took pictures, and
they found me
No wonder
Perhaps I should not be asked
but why you hide here
they are killing
people outside
we are not many staff
and their weapon are
more powerful then ours
so we have to wait
Hold this
we intend to bomb
several houses before we leave
we want to teach Japanese
just let they know
we are not shit
ok, get out, hurry
Thank you
just wait me over there
We try to go to British
Consulate
maybe they can get
you out of Nanjing
You must leave
you must tell the whole
world, what is happening here
This is my favorite
hurry up
your friend should be here
who are you
slowly, man
who are you, I have
the passport
in my pocket
shoot
it's not time to kill people
keep calm
hand your passport to me
who is that
don't let him go
stop
fire, fire fire
you hurt badly
I can't feel pain
maybe it's too cold to feel pain
your bleed too much
but, you still survived
you should thank
him, he save your life
thank you very much
he told me
right, Liu
now, you are in the hospital
and you speak a lot
while you are in a commer
and you
you speak English very good, and
you must not learn it from text book
I learn it in military
academy
I thought you are a
member of Communist Party
yes, I am
surprise?
This only shows that you are still
not understanding China very well
I do not think that
you love helping others
as lease, you won't help a man
I can't leave him alone
he said you have to
wait at least for a month
I can't take him
back to Shanghai
Miss Sears
Please tell me what should I do
to help this guy
Haishan, did you know a
place called Hauangshi
I came here to teach building
but now I teach the
farmer how to bomb
actually, I think
that would be fun
Really?
of course, ti have armed organization
in the basement of Japanese
I have to go tomorrow
I'll go with you
I am going to report what
happened in the front line
to the whole word
I'm not worrying
about you
I am worried about those
who have to take care of you
but there's a
place called Huangshi
in the west
you can get some information
while you get yourself cured
and you can improve
your Chinese
and then go to the front line
let me introduce myself
I'm Nangua
Very good
You understand?
Of course
you said let me introduce myself
I'm a pig
This area is the place
Communist Party get controlled
This area is our
brothers in the KMT
keep heading west
Along this railway
Huangshi probably here
Huangshi
the place you want
to go to Huangshi
get down
what happened
They are not Japanese
yeah, they are not
they are the army
of Jangjieshi
The KMT, yes
I thought they
are your brothers
sometimes we are brothers,
don't you fight Japanese together
that depends
and I think they are not
at this time
and they can't be
what are they doing
they are capturing
strong man to be their soldier
they are come from south
and far away soldiers
and they can't run away
as they are trapped
sir, do you need cigarettes
do you want cigarettes
cigarettes
hello
is anyone here
who's here in charge
please give this to your master
I told you
this is for your master
dear sir, I'd like to introduce
Well-known university
academics Niujin
George pig
I'm the master here
Mr. Pig
The letter said pig
you know how to write
I'm not like those farmers
My name is bovine Kai Shi my
father is a government official
what is he looking for
Probably looking for food
are you kidding me
Hello
you think I have food
just because I have a pan
come and look
they want food, but I
have nothing
see
I have rice with pest
sir, where's teachers,
where are they
they have gone, all of them
do you have rice
what are they doing
I don't know
get up, hurry
come on
hurry up
Who's there
Ms Li
the kids want to hurt sir
Stop
if you touch him
I will leave here
and I would never come back
He is to frighten you
just tell me, Sikai
why I do that
why are they acting
like monsters
How long have you
been to China
5 weeks
how about you
Five years
come here, let me have a look
you are that nurse Li
Phillips
Hello, My name is George
I know who you are
Let you come here is my idea
Children haven't had such
a good m for a long time
Outstanding Niujin
university academics
Haisheng introduce you to us
but, he call you Mr Pig
that is not funny
here it is
out of my way, what are you doing
that kid is very thin
he is very impressive
He saw his father was beheaded
Sister and mother were raped
And then beheaded
Japanese drive him and many people
rushed to the edge of mass graves
Ready to kill them
He had escaped by
pretending to be dead
ok, don't say that
I've been there while
these happened
Hansheng told me, so
he told you to come here
and give you a Chinese name
so the kid can remember you
my name is Heke
stop that, I won't stay here
I came here
not to be the
babysitter for these kids
OK
tell me how to go to
the front line, I can go myself
as you wish
why they help you
everyday, people die of cold
Arbitrary or breaking cold
I would tell them
if they keep running
maybe you just feel inch first
but you would have a
fever next day
if you don't care
your bone would pain
and you can't open your mouth
and you teeth would hold
tight, and you would die slowly
I have the bag with
the Royal anti-drug needles
if I go, they
don't have the medicine
so who would play with me
so, why don't
they close the school
just let the kids
go back to home
This is not a school
It seemed like a schools
This is an orphanage
every child here has
the experience as Kai Shi
don't you want to collect
information on the war?
we got all the
information you want
they don't need a teacher
but one who take care for them
Bed is full of lice
so do the kids
they are so lovely
Those who have
lice infection typhoid
ok
they should be disinfected
How to disinfect them
by hot water
Good idea
Louse powder, they don't
want to use that
But the problem is let them
know that this will not pain
You can find a way
Heke has lice
Grasp
These lice let him sick
See this louse
powder to kill lice
But he will not hurt
Laugh
Very happy Heke
take off your clothes
why are you
embracing, hurry up
what is he doing, hurry up
Hand
don't go
slowly
Beat him
we won't cut your hairs
off if you have no louse
Can you guarantee that?
Not so vain, Mr Pig
I'm not
what's this
Coffee
drike
this is the first couple of
coffee when I left Shanghai
why you came to China
as China is in trouble
Everybody is waiting for the
arrival of voice upstairs blood
Waiting for the next war
Like it was in a cellar
waiting for the arrival of storm
I went to the United
States first
Take two cars across
the United States
Americans hided in their bed
the British were even worse
War
What kind of war, sir
the Great Depression comes
Later, I went to japan,
where I learned Japanese
Japanese tell you they want war
if you don't believe
me, just ask them
Then to the Nanjing
it was horrible
I killed people just for
help some innocent people
I never know that I
have so much hatred
Everyone would hate
them, don't blame yourself
But, we shouldn't
My whole family are pacifists
They are not as
good as you thought
Not really
They are famous
Handi together with
my mother drinks tea
My father in the war
when peace Zunguo prison
He is the bravest men
Now I think they are wrong.
Sometimes I think
we must use force
In the war at
the expense of others
I can be and
typewriters Zuoban
Now, even typewriters are lost
you save George Today,
Although you would
not look like a hero
and you cannot feel it either
but, what you done
is very remarkable
Not slept well
me too
A child diarrhea
Make dirty
You can keep this first mule
you want leave
I have to go to
several health posts
I wait here just want
to leave you these food
I estimate that
would enough for three weeks
and then you have
to think by yourself
I could only do this for you
When do you come back
May
it is March now
the kids here is
just like others
they need food
clothes and warm
if you can do that
you are great
wait, listen to me, I
won't stay here
just find someone else
there's no one
You have to stay here George
Son of a bitch
come here
here you are
Rain the Fast Fast
Wind up on a sheet of paper
will not be pegged to come in the
break that
All the torn tear
Can you help me?
yeah, you
wait wait
Stone stone
come come
Hege Hege
Heke My name is Heke
Jingling
Letter letter
I am writing now
I'll tell you later
Letter
Ink ink
Hey, you do
Table
what's wrong with you, kid
TABE is TABE
TABE... very good
maybe it's me
I'm looking for Boss Wang
I'm Heke
On the front to
the point forward Thank you
Hello
I'm Heke
I'm looking for Boss Wang
glad to see you, Mr Heke
our house is nearly broken
Because of war
There are also gambling
revolutionary war drugs
so many ways to spend money
but we gain for nothing
I have to receive
hard currency
if you can pay in
the Chinese current
sorry, the price have to redouble
I would like to
pay by vegetables
Chinese cabbage is
also a kind of hard currency
British humor
You give us food
and seeds first
We plant, when we harvest
you can take your part
Harvest is not guaranteed, Heke
what's that
the rice from the last year
it won't grow very well
in the climatic conditions
done
thank you, Mr Heke
give my best wishes
for Miss Purs
thank you, I will
I'm working, Yulin
it won't grow like that,
you are just waste seeds
pray to god that god
would bless us
hope that we could
have a harvest
nothing, what
thank you, Ms Luo
This time you will be happy
Weeping
Reading is in English DOG
DOG DOG DOG
DOG DOG
And not be afraid of,
read it together
DOG...
why the lights gone
Kai Shi
don't expect that I
can convince him
We can only minimize
the damage he
I'm just nervous
You never told me
why you come here
for freedom
I can only stay in Narita
result of this temporary clinics
surgery in the candlelight
You are surgeon
the people who die will
not mind if you have some titles
No one helps you
you have to do it by
yourself alone
I am not a nurse
Just as you, you are not a
teacher either
In China, we would become another
personal Therefore, we come here
I was a soldier Malila's wife
But I did not participate
in the wedding
Life is ridiculous
what's this
My Collectibles
Will it dancing?
no
you will come, right
Very glad to see you
You will stay?
I will
For a period of time,
what about you
I think so,
Ms Luo
he's hungry
I do not cook for
small pig offal
Thank you
you know nothing
Your stupid farmers in Gansu
let me see
your eyes are a
little bit inflammation
just look at me
horrible, it is so horrible
You have to brush
their teeth every day
look up
I also have bad teeth
this is for you
this is his
He will be very pleased
Here
do we need flowers
Although I kept four day search
Heke
although I have to climb all days
But I will trace her
kiss her
Pulling up her hand
go with her in to the bushes
Xiaoqing
it's ok
it's ok, no one would hurt you
Goats
are you crazy, how
many have they eat
it is used to clear the lawn
My mother is a good gardening
she uses the goats
listen, Heke
don't touch my things
Sorry, I hope you
can live in comfortable
I don't like that
where are you going
ok, I don't ask, but
when do you come back
don't ask that
you can't go like this
Lee
how's Uncle Qi today
He aggravated the tumor
he needs more pain medicine
it will kill him
that is not too bad
Today, I heard that solution of the
KMT have been made is little bit problem
all of them will be ahead
I heard that too
all those who drugs
and that criminal
Japanese to chop your
head because you are Chinese
what can I do
for you, Miss Puers
I thought you had
the Wang on-powder
No one use Wong On-powder
Even the Japanese don't
Your friend must
be very depressed
no one want to play with him
He must be very lonely
I think he would be fine
Because you never lonely
if you think so, you can visit him
I don't want to wash time
on someone who don't need me
Do you have something
similar to morphine?
Only these?
yes, I have
You are not the
only customer of mine
just replace with this
You know how they evaluate this
You still feel pain
But he could not have hurt you
Six months ago
they were a hungry and dirty
Sick completely useless waste
Now I really admire you
Heke, I did not
expect you will be successful
I must confess
that my wife Wang
I did not expect
I hope you receive this gift
Oh God this is the English
where are you get these
when I was young, a
paders give me
Because I was a good boy
Silk Road
It is 2,000 years of the link
connecting the East and the West
it suits you
Thank you
It witnessed our friendship
ok
I beg you, please tell
me where I come from
Mineyasu
We have gone for two days
Hate ghosts aircraft
Do not fear, their will past
tell me what's he's name
Laosi
Let me guess
Second third honests
and four boss
I'm back
Who are they?
Sleep sleep
no, no
let it go, Laosi
Xiaoqing, he is too young
He also too small
good night