Okay now, take your time.
There you go. [Rumbles in the sky]
Dad, Dad, it's up here.
Slow down Sam, slowdown.
Wow!
- We must show this to the sheriff.
Come on, let's go, go!
Move, go, go, go!
Sam, you're all right?
I'm scared!
Wuh? wa...
Watch out!
How're you doing Dallas?
Eddie.
Come on, I'll give you a ride.
I usually ride in the back.
It seems you remember you're being with me
a couple of those times.
You've got work lined up?
Why? You hiring?
I had enough trouble convincing people I belonged
in the job, but I'll ask around town for you.
I appreciate it.
You, uh, seen my brother?
Actually, I've been seeing him too much.
You gotta wear the hat.
Drew, the only reason you make us wear a hat is because
the manager made you wear a hat when you were drunk.
Look, the only reason you got this job,
is because the guidance counsellor begged me to give it to you
Yes, I'm sure the fact that she is hot has nothing to do with that huh.
14-27 Watercross.
I can' make that delivery, I can' do it.
This is no democracy.
Make the run or you are fired.
And wear the hat!
[Indistinct radio chatter]
[Radio chatter: Copy that, R31D]
Harry, we keep telling you guys to stay out of here and you keep coming back.
I hate to do this , but I'm gonna have to take you in.
Let me just get my dog.
Butch!
Come on boy, what is that?
Jesus.
Sheriff, Sheriff.
Hey, Ricky.
-- Hi, Jesse.
Come on in
Can we get you something to drink?
I'm good, thanks.
Cute outfit, Rick.
-- Yes, isn't Halloween in October?
Yes now I know who's ordered the "Sausage Lovers" (pizza).
My purse is in the kitchen.
I'm sorry.
He is such an a**hole.
Yeah, well, you always know how to pick 'em, Jess.
Well now you and I have a little secret...
I am getting ready to fire him.
Fire him. That's funny.
So what do I owe you?
Err, USD 53.50
Keep it.
Thanks.
I'll see you later.
Come on
-- Dale, Dale, stop it
Was that laugh you've got worth it?
Huh, no answer?
-- Dale, leave him alone!
Gives me my keys.
Find them in 30 minutes or less, a**hole.
Let's go. bitch!
Let's go Jesse.
Ray, you find anything?
Nothing. Anyone parked at the turn-out?
Only Ben's truck.
Jesus, Eddie.
He usually go out with his kid.
Dad?
Hey, I missed you so much.
She's so big,
-- Yes I know
Hi.
-- I can't believe that you're at home.
It has been so long.
Do you want some help?
Is this for me?
You don't like them?
Are you kidding me, these are so cool!
I'll show you how they work later, ok.
Well.
You've got problem with the door?
When did you get back?
-- Today.
What happened to your face?
We'll talk about that latter
-- Ricky.
We'll talk about that later.
-- No let's talk about that right now
Get your hands off me, get your ****ing hands off
-- What happened to your face?
Dale Collins and his friends jolted me.
And threw my keys in the sewer.
All right, give me the bat!
What're do you doing here.
Ricky I'm not gonna ask you again, give me the ****ing bat!
Come on, I'll help you find your keys.
Butch, shut up!
Barry, you better save some for me.
Mom.
-- Sorry, it's bed time, honey.
I am not sleepy yet.
Molly, put those away.
It's time for bed.
I love you.
I want Dad to read it.
See you in the morning.
Do you remember all those times you told me,
how you missed your mom.
It's OK to tell Mommy that.
Ok.
Hurry up.
You want to do it?
-- You're the convict in the family.
Very funny.
Help me with this, okay?
Why don't we climb down where they threw
your keys.
So that Jessie can see me climb out
covered in shit? No, thanks.
Amazing. We're gonna be covered in shit?
Take this.
It's gross down here.
-- No, I could think of worse places.
I guess nobody's home
-- Is that a couch?
Yeah, it's nicer than ours.
What the hell?
It smells like something died down here.
Are you sure this is the right way?
It should be right up here.
That's the drainage.
- Check down there.
They're your keys a**hole.
You got hands.
- Yes, and I'm not sticking it in that shit.
You can do it.
Knock yourself up.
Tel me about this girl.
- What girl?
The one you got your ass kicked over.
- She's the girl.
Nobody goes around digging in shit just for
a girl, okay.
What the hell was that?
- Relax, just a rat.
F***ing rat.
Check that drain.
I got them.
Let's go.
Sam!
-- Ray, head towards the bridge.
Sam, where you?
Buddy?
-- Buddy?
Sam.
Sally, bring them in.
Where are you Buddy?
We won't stop looking for you, Sam.
Thank you guys.
Pay attention please?
Eddie.
We will start up again first thing tomorrow.
My son and my husband
are out here, somewhere.
They wouldn't stop looking for me.
Do you think that...something happened?
- I dunno.
Why don't you go home and get some rest.
You'll need your strength.
OK.
[Indistinct radio chatter]
Ray, anything?
Negative, I'll run again
along the ridge.
All right, keep in touch.
Otherwise, I'll see you in the morning.
.
MISSING
Sam and Buddy Benson
Excuse me, Sir.
Have you seen my husband and my son?
Thanks you.
Pardon me, can give you read this.
This is my husband and my son.
Keep an eye?
- Of course.
How is the job hunt going?
Is "breaking and entering" a special skill?
Do you have a suggestion?
I hear the bank is hiring.
Any word on Buddy and his kid?
Carrie, coffee please.
You were there all night huh?
No, we called it off at 2am.
Ray didn't come home?
- Eddy, I thought he was with you.
I've tried his cellphone.
- Carrie, listen to me.
Ray tried real hard.
I'm sure he's still looking.
Ray, you down there?
I cannot believe that this is Ray.
I do not wanna believe it either.
Do you know what it takes for someone to do this?
For osmeone to skin a human being?
There were no tracks.
Nothing.
Eddie, you're in over your head.
What are you gonna do?
I'll let you know when I figure it out.
Hey.
- Hey, Jessie. Hi.
You know, you looked at me the same way
in class.
Yeah, well, the clock's  behind you.
- What?
Tomorrow when you're in class, turn around.
Yes, I know its there, but
we both know that not what you're looking at.
You know, you never were a good liar.
Do you want to go swimming tonight?
- Swimming?
Where?
- At school.
Come on, it will be like old times.
Old time like before you had a boyfriend?
Yeah, and he's ex-boyfriend actually.
He's been fired?
So, tonight, around 10pm.
See you tonight.
We're closing now.
- I'll see you whan you get here.
You're all right?
If you want talk.
It's OK.
You're welcomed to stay with me and Cathy tonight
Darcy's coming by to pick me up.
I'll sleep at hers.
I'll see you tomorrow.
We found Ray's body in the woods.
It was odd.
He was skinned alive.
Do you think it's got something to do with
Buddy and his kid disappearing?
I think this kind of thing doesn't happen here.
[Radio} Sheriff, we have report of a small gas explosion
in the sewer on 16th Street, do you copy?
Roger dispatch, notify the Fire Dept.
I will meet them there.
[Radio] Right away, Sheriff. Dispatch out.
Do you need some help?
- I don't know Dallas.
Come on, I'll ride in the back.
So...
How do we get in?
I've taped up the lock, after class.
I couldn't decide on which suit
I wanted to wear, so...
Now, you tell me...
Are you looking at me or the clock?
Come here.
What do you think you're doing, Jess?
- Dale, get out of here.
Just remember, Ricky.
I taught this s**t everything she knows.
No, Ricky, stop it!
Stop it. Dale, stop it.
Stop it, he's drowning.
What the hell was that?
Oh my God, get out of the water.
Jess, go.
Go.
Get out of the pool.
Help me.
This side.
Is Ricky dead?
- Why don't you go back and find out.
Come, let's go.
- Go.
Window.
Come on.
Help me.
Go.
Daddy.
- What is it?
It was outside the window.
What?
- Some monster.
Come here.
When I was your age, I used to have
these awful nightmares.
I saw it.
It was real.
See. No monster.
Daddy!
We have to go. Come on.
-- Daddy!
The fire's spread to the whole plant.
We have to shut down the reactors manually.
Roger that.
Dispatch?
We have to evacuate the entire town.
Call the National Guard
in Colorado Springfield for assistance, over.
Copy that.
Jesus.
Sheriff.
- Yes?
I think you should hear about this...
Dallas.
- OK, thanks a lot.
I saw something came up to us,
I don't know what happened.
What do you mean something came up.
- Where were you?
Slow down, where were you?
- I don't know.
Where were you?
- We went to school.
Mark, he's dead.
I think they got Nick too.
What was it?
Ricky?
I don't know.
Call help.
Somebody's gota know about this.
Eddie.
Dispatch, where's our backup?
Dipatch, come in!
Dispatch, come in.
Let's go. Let's get the hell out of here.
Carrie, the power's out.
Help me!
I don't think the police station
is not such a hot idea.
What do you want me to do?
We do not know what we're dealing here.
Come on.
- Look out.
Sheriff.
Darcy? Darcy, what happened?
What are you doing?
Eddy, you must...
- What?
[Incoherent] Carrie are also here.
They're all covered in blood.
They're all gone.
She is dead.
Ricky, get her inside.
Get her in.
People are dying.
We need guns.
The National Guard will be here soon.
- Not soon enough.
I can't believe I'm letting you do this.
This plan is stupid.
Let's just leave town now.
We're not gonna make it without weapons.
You are too stupid to talk,
Dale, just shut up.
Where are the guns?
- Follow me.
Here they are.
Dale, get some bags.
Jessie, load them up.
Eddy, you got power on that thing?
Yes, I just need some light.
Go, go, go.
0-1, scout the area.
0-2 secure the perimeter....[indistinctive]
Roger.
0-6 out.
Move. Move.
What's your status
0-1 has the area secured.
0-2 has secured the perimeter.
This is Sheriff Morales, to the National Guard,
come in.
Repeat, Sheriff Morales, to the National Guard,
This is Lieutenant Wood, 89th Troop Commander
Colorado National Guard.
Go ahead, Sheriff.
What is your location, Lieutenant, over?
We are on Main Street.
Look, Lieutenant, I don't know what
your men is walking into.
But our situation is getting worse.
Lieutenant, come in.
Are you there?
We've a missing man.
- Hold on, sheriff.
We've got gunshots...[indistinct chatter]
We've been ambushed!
What the hell's going on out there?
Pull back.
I repeat, pull back.
Lieutenant.
Lieutenant, are you there?
[Static]
Lieutenant, come in.
Are you there?
We're not gonna make it are we?
Don't shoot, take what you want.
I'm not gonna get killed for USD 6.25 an hour.
We've been attacked.
- Terrorists had done this sir?
I told you they would, one day.
What you guys, stoned?
Do you see that?
Are you hurt?
Come on in.
It should be safe here.
Hold on.
No pulse and breathing.
Take him straight to intensive care.
When's the light going back on?
We are on emergency generators, until the
power's restored.
I think my water just broke.
Okay, I will find the doctor.
You two look pretty shaken up.
- Hasn't been an easy night for her.
And what about you?
I'll live.
We're leaving in 5 minutes.
Thank you.
Where is he?
Give me the gun.
Come on.
Mummy.
Turn back.
It's a trap.
Go.
-- Molly, come on, run. Run.
Come here.
- My God.
F**k this.
What is this f**king s**t?
What was that thing?
That's not possible.
Something's wrong.
Check the other room.
Straight ahead.
What the hell?
- This is our help?
What the f**k is going on, Eddie?
Where are all the bodies?
- They are gonna kill us all.
We are not dead yet.
There may be weapons we can still use.
Radio.
National Guard, come in.
Repeat, any National Guard unit,
come in.
This is Colonel Stevens, US Army.
Identify yourself.
Sheriff Eddie Morales,
in Colorado.
You must help us, Colonel.
We have here a kind of infestation.
And if we don't get help soon,
there won't be any of us left.
What's the Army's evacuation plan?
Colonel?
Colonel, we need immediate evac.
Sheriff, all ground routes have been compromised.
There is an airlift, in 30 minutes
from Gilliam Circle.
Confirmed. Airlift. Gilliam Circle.
We will be there in 20 minutes.
But that's right in the centre of town.
We will be there, Colonel.
What the f**k are you.
Everyone, get in the APC. I'll drive.
Do you think you can drive that thing?
I will get on the gun.
- Don't miss.
Don't crash.
Hold on.
Why are we stopping?
- It doesn't make any sense.
Gillian Circle is right in the centre of town.
We will be surrounded by those things.
Why are you saying?
- I think that the Colonel is lying.
But that is crazy.
The government doesn't never lie to people.
The army thinks about containment first.
They can't risk this getting worse.
But a few miles down that road,
there will be waiting for us.
If you don't wanna drive us there,
I will.
if she is right, then the only thing down that
road is more of these things.
You're not seriously considering this?
- I'm considering whatever keeps us alive.
Which means getting out of this town.
There are only two helicopters in town.
One is at the airport..
No, that's too far. We'll never make it there.
- The other is at the hospital.
The people at the hospital probably used
it to get out.
That's a chance we have to take.
If you have wrong and the helicopter
is gone, we're all dead.
If I am right, they'll die if they follow you.
There's a truck coming.
Dallas, what the hell are you doing in there?
- Never mind that.
You guys heading to the air lift?
- Yes.
Follow us.
We don't have much time.
Listen up.
Everybody's gotta choose right now.
We're going to the hospital with the tank.
We're going to the center of the town.
- That is right.
I'm going with my brother.
- I'll go along with you.
I'm going in the tank.
Dallas, don't do this.
She's wrong.
And brother or not, he's wrong.
You're gonna get them killed.
We are running out of time, Sheriff,
We gotta move now.
Hold on.
We're coming with you.
Wait.
Take care.
I hope we're both wrong.
Lets go.
I didn't help anybody.
I was too scared.
I just watched them die.
All right, put these on.
You too.
All right, listen.
Whatever happens inside, the only person
who can't get hurt is Kelly. We all protect Kelly.
What is this, the Titanic? Screw the
"women and children first", man.
Look, a**hole, unless you can
fly the helicopter, shut up.
Let's go, now.
Maybe they are all gone.
Shoot it!
Jesse, no wait.
- Move, now.
Jesse, wait.
Ricky, wait.
Mother...
Come on.
Come on, get up.
You're gonna make it.
We have to go.
Now.
Go. Go. Go. Go.
[Indistinct shouting]
Is this everybody?
- This is all that's left.
What have you heard?
- The air lift will be here soon.
Clear!
Come. Go go. You're all right?
- Yes.
Come here.
Go go.
Follow your mom.
Come on.
- Everyone, move.
Run Molly.
Dallas.
- I'm trying.
Are you going to use that thing?
- Hang on.
Lets go.
You got her?
Colonel Stevens? This is Gunnison County...
requesting status on your evac, over.
Colonel, where's the air lift.
Sheriff, we are still 10 miles out.
Hold your position, over.
Colonel, we're here over.
God help us all.
Okay, get out of here, now.
I will buy us some time.
I'm not leaving you.
- Get to the chopper.
You don't have to do this, Dallas.
Now. Go, go.
Come on, you motherf**kers.
Come, over here.
Come on.
OK, go.
Come on over here.
We're not leaving without him.
- We have to go.
He will make it.
Die.
Let's go.
Close your eyes.
Hang on.
- Mummy.
Hey, you're all right? Ricky?
- Press here, yes, hard.
Drop your weapons.
You killed the whole town.
- We're just following orders.
Put down your weapons.
We need a medic, for my brother.
Medivac is inbound.
Secure any weapons and let set up a
perimeter.
Go, move it.
I told you not to crash.
Mummy?
Are the monsters' gone?
They are gone.
The world isn't ready
for this technology.
But this isn't for our world, is it Miss Yutani?
[Subtitle edited by Halimi, 4 Jan 2008]