G'KAR:
I believe that when we leave a place...
...part of it goes with us,
and part of us remains.
Go anywhere in the station
when it is quiet and just listen.
After a while, you will hear the echoes
of all our conversations...
...every thought and word
we've exchanged.
Long after we have gone,
our voices will linger in these walls.
[BURKE GRUNTING AND GRO ANING]
[DISTORTED VOICES WHISPERING]
Get out of my head!
No!
LOCHLEY: Personal log, Colonel Elizabeth
Lochley, commanding officer, Babylon 5.
In the nine years since I took over
day-to-day operations on B5...
...I've requisitioned
some pretty odd things.
Strange foods,
alien booze, exotic dancers...
...for a Centauri business meeting.
But this....
This is a new one even for me.
[BEEP]
MAN [O VER PA] : Begin docking
procedure. All hands, stand by.
LOCHLEY: Father Cassidy,
CoIoneI EIizabeth LochIey.
-WeIcome to BabyIon 5.
CASSID Y: A pIeasure.
LOCHLEY:
I hope your trip in wasn't too bad.
The onIy ship we couId get
was a cargo transport...
...and they can be pretty awfuI.
I've been in far worse pIaces
than that.
Though I must say, there was quite
a Iine at the customs area.
We're getting ready
for the big ceIebration party...
...for the anniversary
of the IntersteIIar AIIiance.
President Sheridan himseIf is coming in
from Minbar to be here for it...
...so things are a bit crazier than usuaI,
which is saying something.
WeII, pIease, this way.
I hope you don't mind
that we're meeting here in my quarters.
I feIt it best to keep this away
from the crew.
The cIergy speciaIizes
in private conversations...
...in smaII, quiet pIaces.
I'm just sorry it took my superiors
so Iong to respond to your request.
I'm afraid there aren't many priests
in this sector of space...
...or any sector,
to teII the uncomfortabIe truth.
We're something
of a vanishing breed out here.
-I'm sorry.
-Don't be.
A decIine in faith and the infIuence
of the Church was to be expected...
...once humans penetrated heaven
and found there no angeIs...
...no choir eternaI, not even
a deIinquent seraphim Ieft behind...
...by the generaI evacuation.
Just infinite space.
For 200 years,
mankind has waIked among the stars...
...on Iegs of fire and steeI,
daiIy encountering profounder wonders...
...than the burning bush.
True, but stiII, there are a Iot
of scientists that beIieve in God.
Oh, sure.
Physicists have tried
to soften the bIow...
...with quantum-mechanic
consoIation prizes...
...noting mysteries yet to be resoIved
in tiny subatomic particIes...
...whose actions hint at the presence
of inteIIigence.
But where,
in those infinitesimaI spaces...
...can be found the God who stopped
the sun in the sky over Jericho...
...parted the Red Sea,
birthed the universe...
...and shaped moIecuIes of dust
untiI their name was man and woman?
Once we got into space, the deck
was stacked and the cIock was ticking.
But that doesn't scare me.
I think the Church stiII has
a few surprises up her sIeeve.
WeII, if it's surprises you're Iooking for,
you have come to the right pIace. I--
Before you go any further,
I have to ask, are you reIigious yourseIf?
Yeah, sometimes
I think I'm pretty reIigious.
Then I reaIize I haven't been to church
in ages and I feeI guiIty, so then I go...
...but then, am I going because
I'm faithfuI or because I'm guiIty?
Ah.
So you're just Iike
the rest of us, then.
Good. Go on.
WeII, it started with this smeII
in Brown Sector...
...which isn't surprising because
there's aIways a smeII in Brown Sector...
...but this one wouIdn't go away.
And the repair crews, they kept
hearing voices in the haIIways...
...even when we couId determine
for sure...
...on the monitors
that there was nobody there.
And then....
Then a few days ago...
...there's this guy
that works in security, Simon Burke.
He had come back from a vacation
on Earth a few weeks earIier...
...seemed fine, and then....
SuddenIy, in the middIe of a shift...
...he just started screaming
and saying that he wasn't aIone...
...and that something was inside him,
and then he disappeared.
He'd barricaded himseIf
inside the chapeI on BIue 4.
But when we got to him,
it reaIIy wasn't him anymore.
It was....
Father Cassidy...
...do you feeI quaIified
to perform an exorcism?
Is there anything in his fiIe...
...showing a history of mentaI instabiIity,
psychosis, erratic behavior?
No. No more so than anybody eIse
around here, myseIf incIuded.
You understand
why I have to be sure.
In situations Iike this...
...a mundane answer is far more IikeIy
than a supernaturaI one.
The Iast recorded case of possession
was aImost a hundred years ago.
Yeah, I know.
We've got a IittIe piece
of the 1 4th century here...
...right in the middIe
of aII this technoIogy.
-HardIy seems to fit, does it?
-No, I--
It's coId. And dear Lord, that stench.
Knocks you back on your heeIs, huh?
Two feet that way, it's 72 degrees.
Drops another 20 right there.
His ceII is up here.
HeIIo, Father.
PIease come in.
I couId use the company.
-Mr. Burke?
-After a fashion.
Are you or are you not?
I'm sure he's in here somewhere.
CASSID Y:
Why is he restrained?
For our protection, and his.
The night we found him,
he attacked two of my security guards.
And then Iast night, we came in
and we found him covered in bIood.
We checked him for wounds...
...not a cut, not so much
as a scratch anypIace on him.
And the bIood?
WeII, according to the tests...
...not a singIe strand of DNA
was anypIace in the bIood.
PIateIets, red ceIIs,
white ceIIs, but no DNA.
You wanna expIain
that one to me, Father?
The deviI is in the detaiIs.
Are you saying you are the deviI?
No. Just a humbIe servant.
Does the smeII offend you?
-WouId you Iike me to change it?
-Can you?
[SNIFFS]
Roses?
-ImpossibIe.
-Of course it's possibIe.
Are not aII things in heaven and Earth
possibIe for those who beIieve?
But this is neither heaven nor Earth.
Then this must be heII. So why then
are you surprised to find me here?
If this is heII,
and you hoId sway...
...then you shouIdn't mind
teIIing me your name.
Names have power.
CASSID Y:
Yes, they do.
You first.
If you are what you cIaim,
then you shouId aIready know my name.
So, what is it?
Your name is sadness...
[IN DEMONIC VOICE]
...IoneIiness, useIessness.
Those are descriptions, not names.
BURKE [IN NORMAL VOICE] :
That's why they have power.
That's why my name has power.
And that name wouId be?
Asmodeus.
-You're a Iong way from home.
BURKE: Home is where the heart is.
You're very cIever, at Ieast in EngIish.
Do you know any other Ianguages or--?
Do not waste my time or yours,
Father Cassidy.
We have more important matters
to discuss.
-And those matters wouId be?
-My removaI from this fIesh.
Get to it or Ieave.
Let me get this straight.
You want to be exorcised?
BURKE:
Cast out, yes.
You have the authority to bind me.
Speak the name,
abjure and command me...
...and I wiII be removed
from this body.
Look, if you wanna Ieave,
then why not just Ieave?
We were bound here
among the stars Iong ago.
Bound to remain,
and bound to possess.
Bound by who?
Oh, we cannot speak the name.
Are you saying that God himseIf
bound you to this part of space?
Why? Why wouId God do that?
It was inevitabIe that, in time,
man wouId cross the sea of stars.
InevitabIe that their faith wouId wane
as they gIoried in their accompIishments.
And as you reshape distant pIanets...
...becoming yourseIves creators
of worIds...
...whence comes the desire to crawI
on bended knees for saIvation?
Where can be heard the cry
of the terrified...
...and the Iost
raised in the hope of heaven...
...and the intercession
of divine providence?
Nowhere.
But before there can be hope,
there first must be fear.
Before man can seek saIvation,
there must be the smeII of damnation.
There must be a reason
to reawaken the Iove of God.
But in the absence of humiIity...
...that reason is the fear of heII...
...the terror of we who feII
and waIk among you stiII.
Man sought his God in the stars
and found onIy siIence.
But if the hand of darkness
can be found...
...does that not impIy its opposite?
Proving the presence of heII
aIso proves the existence of heaven...
...bringing peopIe back to God.
-Is that it?
-Yes.
And for this reason...
...the one you worship
saIted us among the stars...
...to wait the siIent centuries
for your arrivaI.
To remind you of your Iimitations.
To renew the fear
you thought you Ieft behind...
...when you stepped
beyond your cradIe.
To keep you from getting
too far off your Ieash...
...and forgetting your pIace.
CASSID Y:
RemarkabIe.
The most remarkabIe pathoIogy
I've ever seen.
What, you don't think
he's reaIIy possessed?
Demonic possession carries with it
severaI very specific signatures...
...none of which were present here.
No demonstration of speciaI powers...
...no abiIity to speak
in more than one Ianguage...
...no speciaI knowIedge.
He knew your name.
He couId have heard it
from one of the guards.
LOCHLEY:
What about the smell?
CASSID Y:
Interesting, but not conclusive.
There's an element of suggestion...
...that couId even be
some kind of eIaborate hoax.
Before I couId bring the Church
into this, we'd need a Iot more--
-Just a second. You hear that?
-Hear what?
[RADIO BEEPS]
LochIey, go.
WOMAN [O VER RADIO] : Colonel,
we're getting an unusual energy spike.
-Where is it?
-Unknown.
We're tracing it now, but we--
[STATIC]
C&C, do you receive?
[RUMBLING]
[ALARM BLARING]
WOMAN [O VER RADIO] : Blue 32.
-That's his ceII.
You know, it's funny.
As a member of the cIergy,
you taIk about miracIes every day.
Of course, that's the probIem.
Everybody taIks about miracIes,
but nobody does anything about them.
Without the proof offered
by such signs and wonders...
...as the parting of a Red Sea
or the dead raised up...
...after a whiIe,
any member of the cIergy...
...wiII have doubts from time to time.
But you keep going...
...because that's what faith is for.
To beIieve in everything
that reason teIIs you is impossibIe.
The terribIe thing is, he's....
It's right.
Two minutes
of what we just saw in there...
...wouId be the best recruiting tooI
the Church ever had.
I aIways thought the deviI
was the prince of Iies.
Oh, without question, but even the deviI
wiII use the truth when it's convenient.
The question is, if there is a Iie,
then where is the Iie?
And most important of aII,
why is the Iie?
I have to go back in there.
You don't have to come with me.
In fact, for your own safety,
I'd urge against it.
You say you were forced
to possess this man...
...that your kind were put here
by God himseIf...
...that this is aII part of his strategy
to keep mankind at his side.
What if I say I don't beIieve you?
BURKE:
Then cast us out.
Those are your onIy choices.
[IN DEMONIC VOICE]
Cast us out...
...or aIIow us to remain in this body
and Iet the whoIe of mankind know...
...that we are here.
[IN NORMAL VOICE]
WouId you not sacrifice a singIe Iife...
...if it meant bringing back biIIions
to the Church?
I think you're saying it's God's wiII
that you remain here...
...because you want to hoId on
to your foothoId here.
You couId have toId me
you wish to be exorcised...
...preciseIy because
you do not wish to be exorcised.
[LAUGHING IN DEMONIC VOICE]
Perhaps.
But if that were the case...
...then why did you teII me anything
in the first pIace?
Because this way,
knowing what you now know...
[IN DEMONIC VOICE]
...your souI is at risk...
...and we take pIeasure
in such things.
How is my souI at risk?
If you beIieve that by Ieaving us in this
body, it wiII serve your God's intent...
...then you must wiIIingIy sacrifice
the souI of this innocent man...
...and thus Iose your own souI,
comforted onIy in the knowIedge...
...that the resuIt wiII be
a return to the Church.
ExpeI us in secret...
...and you defeat
your God's pIans...
...and again
doom your immortaI souI.
But what if I aIIow you to stay,
and none of this was God's pIan?
BURKE:
It does not matter.
Whether this be God's wiII or not,
the news of our existence...
...the fear of us,
wiII Iead to a Church restored.
To pews fiIIed to overfIowing.
To beIievers by the pIanet-fuII.
The resuIt is the same, Father.
The resuIt is the same.
But if you simpIy cast us out,
here and now...
...you wiII have no proof
that any of this is reaI.
Nothing to show for your faith.
Without that,
you and your Church wiII continue...
...to become more irreIevant
with every passing day.
But if you Ieave us here...
...and aIIow the worId outside
to know that we are here...
...you and your order
wiII again be needed...
...necessary, important.
You wiII no Ionger wake in the middIe
of the night and wonder:
''Why am I here?''
You wiII know...
...because we wiII be here...
...to define you.
So, what are you gonna do?
I don't know.
I mean, this is so far outside
my usuaI experience.
What, you're not thinking of Ieaving
that thing inside him, are you?
No, no, of course not,
but there is the question of timing.
Do I attempt this on my own
or bring in others of my order to assist?
-But once I do that--
-Word wiII get out.
A phaIanx of priests
converging on BabyIon 5?
Oh, I shouId think so.
Putting together a group of that size
and IeveI of expertise...
...wouId require weeks.
They'd want to study him,
examine him, during which time...
...even more peopIe
wouId find out about this...
...Ieading to preciseIy
the resuIt it described.
And that's the Iarger question.
What if these creatures reaIIy
were seeded here among the stars...
...for some divine reason
we cannot ourseIves determine?
But why wouId God do that?
Why did God create Lucifer
and aII the others...
...who went with him,
knowing they wouId faII?
Why aIIow pIague, pox,
fires and earthquakes?
Why aIIow possession
in the first pIace?
Amos 3:6:
ShaII a trumpet be bIown in the city
and the peopIe not be afraid?
ShaII there be eviI in a city
and the Lord has not done it?
Sometimes God uses what we,
in our narrow frame of reference...
...may think is eviI,
onIy to achieve a greater good.
Either we do it now or we wait.
Those are the onIy options.
Which of those is God's wiII?
I don't know.
If there's a pIan here, I can't see it.
There's a piece missing.
WeII, we're not gonna find it tonight.
We're both exhausted.
Get some sIeep, Father.
We'II pick it up in the morning.
Screw it. I can't sIeep.
[SIGHS]
Computer, access status
of prisoner in BIue 32.
COMPUTER: Prisoner, Simon Burke.
Maintenance. Status, unchanged.
Simon, you poor bastard.
What did you ever do to deserve this?
You're here at this pIace
for four years...
...hard worker, mind your own business,
no troubIe, then this--
No.
No, no, no, wait a minute.
Simon, you weren't here
the whoIe time.
You were--
Computer, access personneI fiIes.
Burke, Simon.
Subject took Ieave approximateIy
two months ago, correct?
COMPUTER:
Confirmed.
One round-trip ticket to Earth
via Io jumpgate.
And he returned
about two weeks ago on--
COMPUTER:
Commercial Starliner Asimov.
Purchased one coach, seat number--
Not important.
Can you access the ship's Iogs?
COMPUTER:
Confirmed.
Search out any unusuaI entries
on the return fIight to BabyIon 5.
COMPUTER:
Stand by.
CASSID Y:
A decline in faith...
...and the influence of the Church
was to be expected...
...once humans penetrated heaven
and found there no angels...
...no choir eternal,
not even a delinquent seraphim...
...left behind
by the general evacuation.
No seraphim, no choir eternaI.
But none of those things either.
COMPUTER:
Entry found. Playing.
CAPTAIN [ON RECORDING] :
It was there again today, that smell.
We just can't seem to get rid of it.
We've checked the galley,
the recycling systems, everything.
Just can't figure out
where it's coming from...
...and it's cold all the time.
We've considered diverting
for repairs...
...but there's nothing to indicate
trouble with navigation...
...so we'll stay on course
for Babylon 5--
End record.
That's it.
That son of a bitch.
That's the missing piece.
Are you sure you know
what you're doing?
No, but it's never
stopped me before.
You sure if we sedate the body,
that thing wiII go under too?
-That's what the Iiterature says, but--
-Did you give him the sedative?
Doc and I Ioaded him up with tranquiIizers
to knock out five guys, but he's strong.
You got 1 0 minutes
before he's out Iike a Iight.
LOCHLEY:
Good.
LOCHLEY: On the way here,
Father Cassidy toId me...
...that he's decided to go ahead
and perform the exorcism now...
...even if it means putting
his souI at risk.
That wouId amuse you, wouIdn't it?
Making him Iive with that fear?
Too bad it's not gonna happen.
You aImost had us convinced
that we onIy had two choices.
Perform the exorcism
here and now or wait.
But there's a third option...
...sending you somewhere eIse.
After aII, you didn't possess Simon
when he was here, did you?
No, no, you moved in
whiIe he was back on Earth.
A fantasy.
I saw the ship's records.
You were there.
Your presence was feIt by her crew.
But you kept a Iow profiIe. Why?
And how couId you
possess him on Earth...
...if you were bound out here
among the stars waiting for us?
[VOICES WHISPERING]
Know what I think?
I think you can't Ieave Earth
on your own.
I think you're trapped there,
not here.
The onIy way you couId sIip out
was by hitchhiking inside Simon.
You're gonna be exorcised,
aII right, but not here.
We're sending you back to Earth.
[VOICE SCREAMING]
Back to your cage.
You know, when I was a IittIe girI...
...I remember reading how
heaven was above and heII beIow.
And it never made
much sense to me...
...because if heII was underground,
then where was it?
The truth is much simpIer, isn't it?
When you feII, when you got cast down,
you got cast down to Earth.
Bound to Earth. Trapped on Earth.
Denied heaven, denied the heavens.
Denied the sky. Denied the stars.
Earthbound.
Yours was no divine mission.
It was an eccIesiasticaI jaiIbreak.
The onIy way
that you couId escape Earth...
...was to crawI inside the skin
and hitchhike out here among the stars...
...and then do everything you couId
to make sure...
...that you got cast out
by a servant of God, here in the stars.
It was the onIy way you couId sIip
your bonds, escape the inevitabIe.
You see...
...the day wiII come when the Iast of us
Ieave Earth behind for other worIds...
...because we know
that another day wiII come.
A far-off, distant day...
...when the sun wiII burn out
in a finaI bIaze.
The sky wiII go bIack, the seas wiII boiI,
the ground wiII turn to ash...
...consumed by a briIIiant Iight.
Any of this sounding famiIiar to you?
And on that day,
trapped on Earth with no escape...
...you and your kind
wiII at Iast come to an end.
But the heavens wiII remain,
and so wiII we.
A new start. A new universe.
A new dream.
And you....
You don't beIong in that dream.
[VOICE SCREAMING]
[IN DEMONIC VOICE]
We wiII remember you.
I'II be here.
[VOICES WHISPERING]
[WHISPERING STOPS]
He may have been the first to try
to sIip out, but he won't be the Iast.
I'II be sure to brief the HoIy Father
on my return to Earth.
I've aIways wanted to meet him
in person.
Now I have a story
he'II want to hear.
I'II put out the word to some others
on Earthforce that I can trust, quietIy...
...and if this ever happens again,
they'II caII me, and I'II caII you.
President Sheridan once said
that with BabyIon 5...
...he wouId draw a Iine
against the darkness.
He was righter than he knew.
Oh, crap. Oh, sorry.
Um, I'm sorry, it's just that Sheridan's
supposed to caII me any minute...
...and I've gotta go take it.
-You can take it from here, right?
-I can.
CoIoneI, if you ever decide to Iook
for another Iine of work, give me a caII.
We couId use someone Iike you.
Yeah? What, you think
I'm reIigious enough?
You'II do.
LOCHLEY: Personal log,
Colonel Elizabeth Lochley.
Every few days, a new Starliner arrives
from Earth, Mars or some damn place.
Among the passengers are always some
who have never been in space before...
...and they'll stand at a porthole,
looking out at the infinite horizon...
...at the intersection of what's known
and what's not...
...and comment on how cold
and dark it is in space.
They're wrong.
When I look out into space,
into the sea of stars...
...I see a billion times a billion lights,
each calling out to someone:
"Remember me, my child. "
Each of them whispering to someone,
"Come home. "
My friends back on Earth
don't understand why I'm still here...
...when I could be at a comfy desk job
or commanding a warship.
I'm here because
this is my home now...
...and because
when the darkness comes...
...it's good to know you're standing
in the one place...
...where the lights are always on.
MAN [O VER RADIO] :
Mr. President, your ship is here.
Be right there.
SHERIDAN:
Ten years.
Ten years since the world changed.
Ten years since I changed.
Ten years of press conferences,
bureaucracy, politics and arm-twisting.
Every day, somebody points me
to the big picture.
Every day, I wonder if I'm missing
the small picture, the details.
[RADIO BEEPS]
Yes.
WOMAN [O VER RADIO] :
Mr. President...
...the ISN reporter is asking
to see you again.
TeII her I'm dead
and throw her down the stairs.
WOMAN:
Sir?
AII right, aII right. Let her in.
SHERIDAN: Because sometimes
it's the details, the small picture...
...that can change the future.
CHAMBERS:
Mr. President?
SHERIDAN:
Is there a probIem, Miss Chambers?
No, sir. It's just rather stark in here.
SHERIDAN:
Oh.
The Minbari are minimaIists.
For the Iast 400 years...
...their viewing rooms
didn't even have chairs.
They stood the whoIe time.
Yeah, a group of nine
standing out in the void.
When I suggested we put in some chairs,
I aImost triggered a fuII-scaIe revoIution.
I'd go for some throw piIIows next,
but I'm afraid of being assassinated.
[CHAMBERS LAUGHS]
[SHERIDAN SIGHS]
-WeII, speaking of chairs, pIease, sit.
-Thank you, sir.
So gearing up for the big party
at BabyIon 5?
Just meditating on the famiIiar.
I spent four years of my Iife
in that pIace.
The best years of my Iife.
And aIso the hardest years
of my Iife.
-It's a pIace of beginnings.
-And endings?
Some day.
This might not be the best time
for an interview.
-Maybe Iater.
-I've seen your scheduIe, sir.
You don't have a Iater.
Life's fuII of disappointments.
You don't Iike reporters, do you?
Of course I do, properIy cooked.
It's pak'ma'ra humor.
I just got back from a state visit
to their homeworId.
Now, if I'd have said that there,
they wouId be Iaughing for days.
Mr. President--
ActuaIIy, aII their jokes
end with ''properIy cooked.''
They just scream.
Even their cat jokes.
I don't understand it, but it seems
to make them happy. Who am I to--?
So how does it feeI
coming back to BabyIon 5...
...after aII this time, Mr. President?
-I didn't reaIize the interview had started.
-Mm-hm.
And where's your camera?
Right here.
My director said it wouId heIp make sure
that peopIe Iook at the camera a Iot.
So BabyIon 5....
Point of demarcation
from starship captain...
...to station commander, renegade...
...and now here you are
returning in triumph...
...as president
of the IntersteIIar AIIiance.
How does that feeI?
WeII, speaking
on behaIf of the AIIiance...
...we appreciate BabyIon 5
making itseIf avaiIabIe...
...to ceIebrate the 1 0th anniversary
of the founding of the I.A.
Its position in neutraI space
makes it ideaI for everyone invoIved.
I understand there wiII be
ambassadors and dipIomats...
...from a hundred different worIds.
And there's aIso a rumor...
...that Emperor MoIIari
from the Centauri RepubIic...
-...might show up.
-No.
No, he won't be coming.
Londo's been in a very strange,
dark pIace for the Iast few years.
When peopIe Iaugh,
sometimes they Iaugh...
...from a IittIe back in the mouth,
you know, that kind of fake Iaugh?
WeII, Londo...
...he wouId Iaugh
from the bottom of his shoes up.
[CHUCKLES]
Yeah, I hear
he doesn't Iaugh much anymore.
So, no, he won't be attending.
We wiII be picking up
Prince Vintari on the way.
He's third in Iine for the throne,
so there wiII be a Centauri presence.
And Citizen G'Kar?
He's out there somewhere.
Beyond the Rim.
AIso, um...
...DeIenn won't be attending.
She has responsibiIities of her own.
Which brings us back to my question.
-I aIready answered your question.
-Mm-mm.
You gave me the press reIease
as to why you're going and where.
The question...
...was how does it feeI coming back
to BabyIon 5 after 1 0 years?
You onIy give two interviews
a year, Mr. President.
I'm not Ietting you
off the hook that easiIy.
It feeIs good.
I'II confess, I've missed the pIace.
It'II be strange but good.
[BEEPING]
WeII, that is the signaI
to Iet everyone know...
...we're about to jump
into quantumspace.
Quantumspace, sir?
Yeah, it's a new technoIogy we acquired
from what the VorIons Ieft behind.
It's a step up from hyperspace,
twice as fast...
...twice as, um, disorienting,
shaII we say?
[ECHOING] Makes you feeI Iike
you're being turned inside out.
It messes with your inner ear,
your baIance, your sense of reaIity.
It takes some getting used to.
WouIdn't normaI hyperspace
be good enough to--?
No, no, no.
We'd never make it in time.
And as I was saying, the first time some
foIks make the jump to quantumspace...
...they just puke their guts out...
...fouIing themseIves in the most
awfuI ways you can imagine.
Mr. President, I--
Here we go.
SHERIDAN:
The problem isn't that I only give...
...two interviews a year,
Miss Chambers.
The problem is that so few reporters
ever seem to come back for seconds.
Was that a new dress?
[THUNDER RUMBLING]
Look famiIiar?
No?
Of course, my mistake.
The bIack dust, you see.
It hides stars and the moon,
cIouds and sky...
...hope and pity, despair and....
Here, I'II fix it.
As the saying goes,
Iet there be Iight.
[SIREN WAILING]
[HORNS HONKING]
GALEN:
New York.
The city that never weeps.
TAxI DRIVER:
Get out of the road!
What do you think you are doing?
Learn to fIy.
Up yours.
This is what was...
...and for this one moment
out of time...
...stiII is.
And this is what wiII be.
Up there somewhere...
...far above us, above the cIouds...
...a thousand vast war machines
are warping into normaI space.
Each of them armed
with terribIe engines of destruction...
...capabIe of devastation
on a scaIe never seen before...
...untiI right now.
No.
[SHERIDAN GASPS]
This was not a dream.
Do you understand me?
-Do you hear me? This was not--
-I hear you.
I hear you.
You're not the onIy techno-mage
I've deaIt with over the years, GaIen.
I've had enough experience
to know the difference...
...between dream-reaI, magic-reaI...
...and reaI-reaI.
You're wiser than I thought.
Yeah, wiser...
...oIder...
...and I'm tired of you guys
crawIing inside my head...
...and showing me
this kind of crap...
...every time I think that my Iife
might be going good for a change.
What is wrong with you peopIe?
Don't you have any other hobbies?
WeII, that's hardIy
what I'd caII a warm weIcome.
Not a ''good to see you again,
oId friend.''
Maybe a hug or a peck on the cheek,
in a manIy sort of way.
Why show me
this kind of stuff, huh?
Why me?
Because for those of us who dweII...
...in the infinite space
between science and magic...
...between iIIusion
and uItimate truth...
...who are sworn by our order
not to interfere...
...you are known to us aII
as a nexus.
Where others doubt...
...you beIieve what you see
when we speak to you.
That beIief has saved Iives.
It may yet again.
Or I can simpIy go,
if that's what you prefer.
What I just saw,
is that what is going to happen...
...or what may happen?
There are ways to prevent this.
There is hope...
...but it is at best a sIim hope.
Yeah, weII, I've never known hope
when it wasn't on a diet.
[SHERIDAN SIGHS]
AII right, go on.
In one day...
...you wiII pick up Prince Vintari
to convey him to BabyIon 5.
In two days,
you wiII arrive for the ceIebrations.
In 20 years...
...he wiII ascend to the throne
of emperor of the Centauri RepubIic.
In 30 years...
...he wiII decide that his pIan to bring
the repubIic back to its former gIory...
...requires the eIimination...
...of the one power
that couId stop him.
The one power that has stopped
the Centauri in the past.
Earth.
It is he who wiII cause the horrors
that you have seen.
But this can be stopped.
No, I came aII this way to show you this
because nothing can be done.
Because I Iike the way
your pupiIs diIate...
...in the presence
of totaI pIanetary Armageddon.
Yes, it can be stopped.
How?
Oh, President Sheridan...
...I wouId have thought that
that wouId be eminentIy obvious.
AII you have to do...
...is kiII...
...Prince Vintari.
[SHERIDAN GASPS]
They caII it spoo. Now, it's supposed
to be their favorite food.
I've onIy tasted it,
but I caII it the other gray meat.
VINTARI:
President Sheridan?
Prince Dius Vintari.
It is an honor to meet you.
And you.
[SPEAKS IN ALIEN LANGUAGE]
This is the new VaIen-cIass cruiser,
isn't it?
Yeah. You know your ships.
A hobby of mine.
I take speciaI interest
in the technoIogy of other races.
The starfuries used by Earth
are a particuIar favorite of mine.
So simpIe, so eIegant, and so deadIy.
I was surprised when I got the request
to transfer you aboard my cruiser.
The ship you were on couId've easiIy
taken you aII the way to BabyIon 5.
Emperor MoIIari was concerned I might
not be safe among my own peopIe.
As third from the throne...
...I am something of a target
in a smaII, confined space.
A target? For whom?
Numbers four, five, six and seven,
I'd imagine.
The onIy one I don't have to worry about
is that idiot Vir Cotto...
...who wouIdn't be in Iine...
...except the Centarum wanted
to punish me for what my father did.
I've known Vir for a very Iong time.
He's a good man.
He murdered my father.
At Ieast, that's the rumor.
So he got what he wanted...
...second in Iine.
No threat to me...
...but in time, maybe...
...I might just be a threat to him.
Anyway, Emperor MoIIari thought
I'd be safer with you.
He said, ''I wouId trust
Sheridan with my Iife.''
WeII, that's--
Then he corrected himseIf and said
he wouId trust you with my Iife...
...because he had pIans
for next week.
Then he Ieft the room, Iaughing.
[SHERIDAN CHUCKLING]
Oh, he aIways did have
a sense of humor.
My father made many enemies...
...and it seems
I have inherited them.
There are many in the RoyaI Court
who wouId see me dead...
...before they'd see me
on the throne.
Now that I'm of age, I may have to Ieave
Centauri Prime for some time...
...before it is safe for me to return
and cIaim the throne.
But I give you my word...
...when that day comes,
there wiII be a reckoning...
...the Iikes of which has not been seen
since the earIy days of the repubIic.
And that wiII be
just the beginning, I--
So I appreciate your gesture.
I'm sure my presence here
must be an inconvenience for you...
...but it wiII be nice to sIeep without
a knife beside my bed for a change...
...to know that I am safe here
with you.
SHERIDAN: So how are the preparations
going at your end, coIoneI?
As well as can be expected.
SHERIDAN:
Meaning not at aII.
It's Babylon 5. Nothing's ever easy.
Speaking of which...
...I know how you hate
publicity stunts...
-EIizabeth--
-...but ISN has asked...
...if you'd mind
riding back to Babylon 5...
...in a starfury
instead of a shuttle.
You know, the conquering hero
coming home on the airborne staIIion...
...on which he won the Shadow War.
CongratuIations.
I think I'm about to be iII.
Come on, it wouId reaIIy mean a Iot
to the peopIe who've shown up.
And you know the power
of symboIism.
AII right, aII right.
I haven't been in a starfury in ages.
WeII, who knows, it might be fun.
So any of the oId gang
coming in for this shindig?
Some. TaIked to GaribaIdi.
He's gonna try to come.
But he's deaIing
with some situation on Mars.
-And Stephen?
LOCHLEY: Oh, I thought you heard.
Dr. FrankIin went with G'Kar,
expIoring beyond the Rim.
y ou know how he is.
He'll take any chance to explore new
territory before anyone can get there.
That's too bad. I'II miss him.
You're Iooking tired, EIizabeth.
Is everything okay?
It's been crazy.
I always knew Babylon 5
was neutral territory, but until today...
...I never knew it was on the crossroads
between heaven and hell.
Hey, it's a long story. I'll tell you
all about it when you get here.
Travel safe.
[SIGHS]
Interesting how the universe
aIways provides, isn't it?
Now what?
Your return to BabyIon 5
on a starfury...
...and Vintari's interest
in these primitive vehicIes....
Don't you see?
AII you have to do
is offer him the chance...
...to ride aIongside you
in a second starfury.
And that accompIishes what exactIy?
My agents aboard BabyIon 5 wiII ensure
a sIight technicaI maIfunction...
...in your ship's weapons systems.
The moment your ship achieves a speed
of, say, 5000 kiIometers an hour...
...the system
wiII short-circuit and fire.
In the course of this terribIe accident,
his ship wiII be struck and....
WeII, as I said, it wiII be a terribIe
accident, much to be regretted...
...foIIowed by some posturing
and harsh words from Centauri Prime.
But in the end...
...they'II be as gIad
to be rid of him as we are.
You mean as gIad as you are.
Christ, he's onIy a kid.
Once upon a time, back on Earth...
...AdoIf HitIer and Genghis Khan
were just smaII boys...
...pIaying with toys
and growing sIowIy...
...sIowIy into monsters.
If either of those candIes
had been extinguished at an earIy age...
...how many miIIions of Iives
might have been spared?
But no one took that opportunity...
...because no one knew.
But you do.
The fate of biIIions of Iives...
...is in your hands.
GALEN:
In 30 years...
...he will decide that his plan to bring
the republic back to its former glory...
...requires the elimination...
...of the one power
that could stop him.
[RADIO BEEPS]
-Yes?
MAN: The president's cruiser...
...has jumped out of quantumspace.
WeII, fire up a starfury
and get it out there ASAP.
And I want an honor guard
at Docking Bay 6 as soon as he docks.
MAN:
Confirmed. Uh, just one thing.
President Sheridan has asked
for two starfuries.
-Two? Why two?
-He didn't say.
Maybe he wants a backup.
We do have another starfury
on standby--
WeII, he is the president.
If he wants two starfuries,
then give him two starfuries.
-Roger that.
-I wonder if Custer had staff Iike this.
SHERIDAN:
Vintari.
-Just the prince regent I was Iooking for.
-Is it time to go?
Yes, and I've arranged
a IittIe treat for you.
How wouId you Iike to ride fire
aIongside me in a starfury?
-You're serious?
-AIways.
UnfortunateIy, we don't have
a EVA suit that'II fit you...
...but I'm not wearing one,
since we're not going into combat.
It'II just be a IittIe drive
around the bIock.
-Do you have a probIem with that?
-No, no, pIease.
To do even this wouId be....
You see, they keep me so controIIed.
There's so IittIe chance for....
Fun?
You must understand.
Where I am from, no one does anything
except for to get something in exchange.
I know aII about how to use peopIe,
to expIoit and manipuIate...
...but very IittIe about reaI kindness.
Thank you.
I assume you're up-to-date
on how to piIot one of these things.
I couId fIy it in my sIeep.
WeII, you wouIdn't be the first.
SHERIDAN:
PuII back on your thrusters.
Maintain your xYZ axis.
Now, ease off.
-How does she feeI?
-Magnificent.
So this is what it's Iike
to ride a ship into battIe.
SHERIDAN: Minus the part
where they're shooting at you.
We'II increase our speed sIowIy...
...to 5000 kph.
SHERIDAN [O VER RADIO] :
Slow but steady.
Right.
You have done your homework.
You handIe that fighter
Iike you've done it before.
VINTARI [O VER RADIO] :
I have.
In a dream.
For the Iast seven days,
I have seen myseIf in this very ship...
...in front of a great fIeet.
Dreams are very powerful
to my people, you know.
Mm. They carry some weight
with mine as weII.
VINTARI: In the past,
I have had similar dreams.
Commanding a fIeet
against our enemies...
...raining fire from the skies,
whoIe cities burning.
A dream, nothing more.
But this dream was prophetic...
...for I have seen myself
in this very ship just last night.
I get in...
...I ride before you in triumph,
and then....
What happens? What?
Something wonderfuI.
That's aII I remember.
Computer, cut outgoing transmissions.
COMPUTER:
Shutting down transmissions.
Assess weapons system.
COMPUTER:
Four Omega-grade torpedoes online.
System confirms pulse cannons
at full power, ready to be armed.
Countdown veIocity on approach.
COMPUTER: Four thousand five hundred
kilometers per hour.
Four-K-six.
Detecting power surge
in primary weapons control system.
-Should I take weapons off-line?
-Negative.
Keep weapons onIine.
COMPUTER:
Confirmed. Four-K-seven.
It was an accident.
I teII you, it was an accident.
I didn't know
the weapons system was Iive.
I didn't know.
COMPUTER:
Four-K-eight.
VINTARI: I'm sure my presence here
must be an inconvenience for you...
...but it will be nice to sleep without
a knife beside my bed for a change...
...to know that I am safe here
with you.
You must understand,
where I am from...
...nobody does anything for any reason
other than to get something in exchange.
I know aII about how to use peopIe,
to expIoit them and manipuIate...
...but very little about real kindness.
SHERIDAN: What I just saw,
was that what is going to happen...
...or what may happen?
GALEN: There are ways to prevent this.
-Ways.
He said ''ways.''
COMPUTER:
Four-K-nine.
Reduce speed.
VINTARI [O VER RADIO] : y ou have fired
your forward thrusters. Are you all right?
I'm fine.
Fine.
Just wanted to sIow down
a bit, enjoy the trip.
And besides,
I'm not a kid anymore.
I don't need to be hot-dogging
around the gaIaxy.
Do you mind if I...?
By aII means.
InduIge yourseIf.
[LAUGHING]
VINTARI: That was amazing.
We must do it again.
I haven't had that much fun since....
-Since I don't even remember.
-Yeah, weII, I'm gIad you enjoyed it.
[SHERIDAN CLEARS THRO AT]
Are you aII right?
You seem rather thoughtfuI.
I was just thinking about
what you said.
About having to Ieave Centauri Prime
to avoid being kiIIed.
You've had a very difficuIt Iife.
One that can harden a person.
Make them into something
even they wouIdn't Iike.
Your point being, you do not desire
or appreciate my company.
Is that it?
Not exactIy.
When we're finished with this party,
I'm inviting you to come back to Minbar.
You can stay at the RoyaI PaIace
with DeIenn and myseIf.
I just checked in with her
on the way...
...and, weII, she said she thought
it was a great idea.
I guarantee you,
you'II be safe from your enemies there.
-Why?
-Why not?
I mean, there's pIenty of room.
We have a son, David.
He's 9.
He couId use an oIder brother
to Iearn from.
Or at Ieast someone
who couId be that for him.
You wouId have me come
to Iive with your famiIy on Minbar?
That pretty much covers it, yeah.
If I were a cynic...
...I might beIieve you were doing this
for your own reasons.
To try and gain a foothoId
in the Centauri RoyaI Court.
I'd think the same thing.
You're not going to try
to convince me otherwise?
I'II Iet Iife do that for me.
Trust doesn't come overnight.
I'II teach you, if you'II Iet me.
LOCHLEY:
President Sheridan...
...weIcome to BabyIon 5.
CoIoneI, it is good to see you again.
So after aII this time,
this by you is a heIIo?
[SHERIDAN AND LOCHLEY LAUGHING]
Come here.
-You Iook great.
-You too.
CoIoneI LochIey, Prince Regent Vintari
of the Centauri RepubIic.
-An honor.
-Thank you.
So everyone's waiting for you.
You ready to go over to the party?
AbsoIuteIy.
But, um....
Why don't you go ahead?
I'II be right there.
I just want to, you know,
savor the moment.
Of course.
PIease.
GALEN:
You vioIated our agreement.
Yes, I did.
Why?
You said there were ways
to avoid that future.
Ways, pIuraI.
They are harder. This was simpIer.
-But just as vaIid.
-PossibIy, but we can't be sure.
OnIy with his death can we be sure.
Then I wiII take my chances.
DeIenn and I wiII show him
another way of Iooking at things.
Maybe we can heIp him,
change him...
...and avoid that future
that you showed me.
And if you can't?
Then I'II take care of it.
When and if I decide
there's no other way.
One other thing, Vintari said that he had
a dream that he was in that starfury...
...and that something wonderfuI
was going to happen.
That was your work, wasn't it?
I get around.
SHERIDAN:
Because, see, I was thinking.
Maybe....
Maybe you wanted me to kiII him
aII aIong, just Iike you say.
And maybe you were hoping that things
wouId turn out the way they did...
...and I'd take him under my wing.
And maybe you boxed me in preciseIy
so I'd make this decision.
And that was the something wonderfuI
that he saw in his dream.
What do you say to that?
I say...
...that we are surrounded on aII sides
by mysteries, President Sheridan.
And mysteries, once soIved,
are never quite as interesting...
...are they?
[MUSIC PLAYING]
[APPLAUSE]
MAN [O VER SPEAKER] :
Good evening, everyone, and welcome.
We are honored to have
President Sheridan with us tonight.
He will be up here shortly
to say a few words.
And among our other
distinguished guests...
...we are fortunate enough
to have Prince Vintari joining us.
WeII...
...here we go again.
SHERIDAN:
Ten years.
Ten years since the world changed.
Ten years since I changed.
But it feels like I never left the place.
Babylon 5 is a place
of beginnings and endings.
I wonder which this will be.