We have confirmed movement
on the west side of the perimeter.
Roger that, Dwayne.
What's your position?
Airborne in position to the south
of the surveillance area.
We have movement from inside
the compound. Everyone stand by.
Code 1. Code 1. We have gunfire
on the ground from the east.
Repeat, east side.
Chopper 1 and Chopper 2,
we have authorization.
Take down all elements
within the compound.
Marshall, we have one escapee
heading your way on a motorcycle.
Roger that. I have a visual.
He has turned towards the north.
Air support required immediately.
I have the electronic lock.
Unloading the chain gun.
Suspect is still heading north.
Switching to rockets.
Gonna bring him down
for you to clean up, Marshall.
He's down, he's down.
On foot and still heading north.
- He's all yours.
- Roger that.
Retrieving the sequencer
was the right thing to do.
However, the Majestic drug research
program is none of your concern.
The consequences are the same,
no matter how you look at it.
We made the treaties,
they broke them.
Now you expect me
to clean up after them?
- That's not gonna happen, you hear?
- Marshall, I repeat, let it go.
We've received new orders, sir.
0800 hours to Paris.
A training mission.
Oh, well, let's go pack our gear.
Do we stand down, sir?
- That's right.
- Sir.
Well, anyway... I mean, I'm...
Your room keys, sir.
They come from
a really good SF team...
...and Admiral Morgan
recommended them as replacements.
They have two days' field training
before our next assignment.
They'll be all right.
Okay, children, let's go.
So Marshall Lawson.
What do you guys know about him?
I mean, the man walks
with an air of confidence...
...that's rarely seen
in this day and age.
What?
What? I'm serious. He does.
Yeah, him and his girlfriend,
Dwayne.
There's just two things you need
to know about Lawson.
One is he's a bad motherfucker...
...and two, he's a bad motherfucker.
- I hear that.
- That's the truth.
Here's to what might could be
a real good team.
- Cheers to that.
- Cheers.
- And if not, you can always kill us, sir.
I'm thinking about that already.
You're all about to cut your teeth now,
let me tell you something.
Grab a beer at the bar.
Just take it easy.
- Sir.
- Oh, take it easy?
Okay.
Those fucking guys have no idea
what we're up against.
Yeah, well, I've got a bad, bad feeling
they about to find out.
Requesting permission
to leave the premises.
- Can't get no love around here.
- We're thinking of going to a titty bar.
I ain't getting no love
and I'm too old for love.
And I'm too poor.
- Why don't you go on.
- We'll catch you later.
All right. Thank you, sir.
Just remember. Tomorrow, 0700.
Be here.
- Oh, yeah. On the dot.
- Right.
This place is cold. It could
freeze the balls off a penguin.
- Where the hell are we going now?
- All right.
Guys?
- Yeah.
- Oh, there, there.
Morning. Morning. Morning.
This is the best day of my life. Yeah!
Oh, man. All right, I love you.
- Oh, dude.
- Oh, my...
She's the one. She's the one.
She's the one.
- Hey.
- Hello.
Any chance? Party, later.
- We've got a party back at our hotel.
- At the hotel.
You want me to go,
you have to talk to him.
- What, talk to him?
- Yeah.
See you in a minute.
Can I talk to you for a minute, man?
What's your pleasure?
That girl.
Treat her right.
Okay.
And I'll send someone around
to collect.
Deal.
Okay. Thank you. Bye-bye.
- We got a deal.
- Thank you.
- Cheers.
- Carl. Let's go.
Thanks, man.
- There you go, man.
- Thanks, man.
Thank you very much.
You've been so very kind tonight.
Thank you. We've got love.
You be all right by yourself?
All right.
- What are you doing here?
- I'm following new orders.
Just like you.
Okay.
Come on, guys, open the door.
Jesus, guys. Come on.
Jerk off all over the wallpaper
all night.
I'm up. I'm up next.
Least I can get it up next.
At least I can get it up
in the first place.
Honey, you're with the wrong guy.
I might not know what I'm doing,
but I can do it all night.
Come on, guys, open the door. Phil.
- All right, I'll see you in the morning.
- See you later.
Hey.
Well, let's have a look.
- Check it out.
- What the fuck?
No. Don't bother.
They're all dead.
Come with me.
Oh, Jesus.
Detective Lambert, et vous?
Yeah, I'm Commander Lawson
and this is Chief Dixon.
And we're all active military.
These are my guys.
I'm gonna have to claim the bodies
and take them in for a special autopsy.
The bodies are mine.
They are under my jurisdiction.
Okay. Listen to me, young man.
I'm gonna have somebody in your
government call you immediately...
...and explain who has jurisdiction
over these guys.
Do you hear me?
Just keep an eye on your watch.
Within about 20 minutes, you're
gonna be told who gets the bodies.
Dwayne, find that titty bar.
Thanks.
- Hi.
- Yeah.
- What's your name?
- Reina.
Maybe you can help me
with something, Reina.
Some buddies of mine
were here tonight.
You see who they were
hanging with?
Can't have you upsetting the girls.
Just making small talk.
Why don't you make it
somewhere else?
Look, I was just asking her
a few questions.
I'm looking for some buddies
that were here tonight.
I'm sorry about your trouble,
but the police will take care of it.
Yeah, well, the police
ain't working fast enough.
I guess the police will handle it, then.
- What do you got?
- Just like you figured.
Massive physical trauma,
but also traces of a new drug, CTX.
Apparently, it's the new party drug.
We've had several
overdose victims recently.
What now?
I don't know, man.
I just needed some time to think.
You okay?
My team, they're well-trained.
Real well-trained.
Whoever did this,
or whatever did this, they're good.
It was brutal.
Yeah, well, that might be...
...but it was an assassination,
that's for sure.
Revenge for some past operation?
Could be. I thought of that.
It could be.
Revenge is a two-way street.
I had local police
arrest the club owner.
You wanna check him out?
No, I'm going
to Majestic headquarters.
Access denied.
ID, please. This is a restricted area.
I'm sorry, commander,
but this area is now closed...
...even to someone
with your classification.
That's very strange that they
would have pulled my clearance...
...and not told me about it.
Commander, I need you
to step aside.
I'm sorry, commander,
I need you to vacate the facility.
Yeah?
Did Robinson tell you
why they revoked your clearance?
No, not really.
Okay. When and where?
Café, east side of the building.
Twenty minutes.
I'll see you there.
Didn't I tell you
to stay out of sight, Aroon?
And didn't I pay you to stop people
from looking for me, Lambert?
I can't help it if the U.S. military...
...is taking an interest
in your activities.
How was I supposed to know
that Uncle Sam...
...would send in some of his finest?
Those boys were having fun.
Yeah?
You know, the irony is
that Marshall and his team...
...weren't even looking for you.
Those boys were looking
for some R and R.
And they found it.
Your girl Reina,
she had a little too much fun.
She might have got a little
out of control, I suppose.
Well, then, it's a little
out of my jurisdiction.
Can you get me out of here?
Lambert, this is still
a U.S. military investigation.
Just trying to help.
Get the fuck out of here before
I have your French ass kicked out.
I just heard about your team.
I'm so sorry, Marshall.
If there's anything I can do...
I really need to know who did this.
Very impressive record.
I like to think so.
Head of the biochemical research
program in Western Europe.
Top-secret research.
You're a top dog, Aroon.
Be all you can be.
Why not? Your partner didn't mind.
Yes, well, Tia's a very special girl.
Besides, they'll need her
for the cover-up.
Although, if she's not careful,
they'll probably make her the fall guy.
We've been monitoring this area
for more than six months...
...because a top-level
Majestic researcher went AWOL.
Let me ask you something.
What's the story with Majestic
and drug movement?
They control the
CTX research program...
...but Werner wants everybody
and everything to stand down...
...until we know what's going on.
Yeah?
Hello, Robinson.
Listen to me,
you arrogant little prick.
I don't understand any of this
fancy research you're fucking with.
But what I do understand is this:
Three of my boys got murdered
and I want to know why.
Wrong place, wrong time?
Your girl Reina was a little careless.
We found this...
...in the hotel room...
...and this in your club.
The autopsy confirmed significant
traces of this chemical...
...in the three dead bodies.
Your boys must have liked it, then.
Listen, asshole.
I want to know what's going on
in your club.
And what's happening
to the people around here.
Are you making me an offer?
Sure. Either you tell me...
...or I shoot you so full of this shit
that it'll make you talk...
...or it'll kill you.
I'll handle it. Yup.
I need access to an armory.
- I'll see what I can do.
- You know the weapons I like.
I gotta deal with Robinson first.
You've no idea
who you're dealing with.
So fucking enlighten me, because
right now you are dealing with me.
Dwayne, meet CTX.
CTX, meet Dwayne.
So how does it work, this CTX?
Could you give me five?
I have orders to shut you down.
All military drug-testing programs
have been canceled.
- lf I were to ask you why?
- You don't even need to ask.
Aroon's defection has caused
a serious breach in our CTX program.
So we're talking about
chemical warfare.
Chemically-induced warfare.
So who do you work for?
Someone who doesn't like
a lot of questions.
She does have access to seemingly
unlimited Russian financing, though.
And that's one of the reasons
I don't like asking a lot of questions.
Why here?
When you experiment,
you need to test.
When I was in the Army, I had access
to as many guinea pigs as I wanted.
Soldiers. For research.
You have no idea how many soldiers
gave up their lives for science.
It was funded by the military.
Once I went AWOL,
I still had to perfect the formula...
...and that meant testing it.
On who?
John Smith. Jane Doe.
Innocent people
as your guinea pigs?
It's amazing what types of corruption
you can buy these days.
We cannot get caught
in the spotlight.
But what we can do
is limit the damage.
And in a couple of months,
it'll all blow away.
Okay. No questions asked.
- Not by the wrong people.
- Like Marshall.
That's why you're gonna
work with him.
All you have to do is to make sure...
...he does not unnecessarily
compromise our agenda.
Now, you seriously think
I can help you in this?
If you work with me on this one,
I'll make it worth your while.
Look, I know that
you and Marshall are close.
But he can't give you
the career you want.
Not the opportunities a young, gifted,
vibrant biochemist really deserves.
- So this is what it's like, huh?
- What's that?
Making a deal
with the devil himself.
- Have you had contact with him?
- Aroon?
No. I worked with him.
I taught him everything he knows.
Except how to resist temptation.
I decided to introduce CTX
to the club scene.
New party drug.
Has an exquisite high.
Very pleasurable.
Instantly addictive, but very...
- Lucrative?
- Yes.
But when one doesn't have CTX
for a while...
...one becomes a bit
of a lethargic mess.
Traces of CTX lodge themselves
in your system and become dormant.
They gradually change your DNA.
And under the right circumstances,
they can be triggered.
Especially in situations involving
conflict or aggression.
And that's what I think
happened to your boys.
They probably got a bit
carried away with Reina.
She mistook their libido
for aggression and, well...
Spare me the psychology.
When your body is suddenly
flooded with adrenalin from the CTX...
...you become a bit like a wild animal,
fighting for survival.
You become a killing machine.
You have no morals.
You have no humanity.
And that's what the government was,
and is, interested in.
A drug that makes soldiers
mindless killers...
...right up until
the point that they die.
- And Tia knows this?
- Of course.
CTX was our baby.
We developed it together.
Robinson and Werner kept
the whole operation very hush-hush.
It was to be their big step up
through the ranks.
We want to talk to your boss.
I don't think she'll be interested
in that conversation.
We'll see about that.
Where is she hiding?
Where is she?
I'm doing you a favor.
If you were all to arrive there,
she'd kill you instantly.
You think the U.S. Army is just
gonna walk away from this?
Even if they did, I would
hunt you down and kill you myself.
Well, it's already too late.
A large quantity of CTX is going to be
released into the city's water supply.
Everyone within a 100-mile radius is
either going to be addicted or dead.
You got it all wrong, Aroon.
Oh, you're going to regret that,
soldier boy.
I don't think so, guinea pig.
Revenge is a two-way street.
Watch him.
I'm going to get a medic.
Need a light?
- We're being followed.
- Who are they?
I don't know. I'm about to find out.
I think they might be
Robinson's boys.
Can I help you?
- Why's that?
- Well, because you're following us.
I'm not following you.
You know what, man?
I bet you if I reach in your pocket...
- Yeah, yeah, yeah.
- What is this?
Well, see now, Naval Intelligence.
I'm disappointed. You lied to me.
Tell me something.
Should we be cooperating
with Robinson and Majestic?
None of that stuff works.
So you're telling me
Tia is our only option?
That's right, baby. That's right.
Tell me what you know.
It's Majestic.
They're putting together
another strike team.
We've got to try
and persuade Tia to join us.
Sir, this will turn ugly.
I think the ship already
sailed on that.
It's still containable.
We need to contact our people,
bring them in for their own protection.
Now, you know the liaison.
Now, you worked with her.
She wouldn't endanger the program,
right?
You trained them.
They've worked together before.
They're close.
I can't guarantee you anything.
Just a friendly visit.
- Your idea, or hers?
- Does it matter?
She might cut out your allowance.
Just like Robinson and Werner
cut out yours?
- Only for a little while.
- I'm sure.
First, they need you in the trenches,
with Marshall and his grunts.
I wouldn't be there
if it wasn't for you.
Oh, come on.
The right deal will come along
and you'll be a defector someday.
Not as a fugitive from the law.
Now, I may not have my own dentistry
or retirement plan, exactly...
...but I am doing what we love to do,
Tia.
Well, enjoy it.
Because it ain't gonna last.
Oh, yes. Of course.
I forgot. Marshall.
You remember the excitement when
we first sequenced the CTX formula?
You and I,
we complement each other, Tia.
Work for me.
Work with me.
So do I take it that's a no?
Yes.
Of course, you realize
there will be consequences.
- Were you followed?
- We were followed.
- But we took care of that.
- Good.
If words gets back to Werner
that I'm talking to you guys...
I don't think you'll have to
worry about Werner.
He might not be happy
about our personal thing...
...but he knows who sent me here
and he knows why I'm here...
...so he's not gonna say
nothing to me.
My entire fucking team's
wiped out...
...so you know what would be
really helpful right now?
If you stop feeding us this bullshit...
...and give us decent intel
that we can use.
What the fuck are you talking about?
Why do you think I'm here?
I'm very sorry about your team.
I'm sorry for your men.
But you know what I think
would be very nice?
If you'd realize that I'm on your side.
You know Aroon's escaped.
He knows you're onto him.
And I know he's gonna
follow through with his plans.
If that's the case, I'll brief your team
on what kind of weapons will work...
...and what won't.
- What will you do about Werner?
- Forget it.
I'll go to the admiral myself.
Believe me when I tell you, he will
give us carte blanche for this mission.
They're Lambert's cops.
Let's have some fun.
Hey, guys, they are onto us.
Let's call for backup.
It is unfortunate you could not have
persuaded Tia to join us.
She would have been a great asset.
Yes. I'm sorry to have failed
in that regard.
Don't be ridiculous.
Nothing can stop us
from reaching our goal.
Tia and Marshall will be
relentless now.
They'll do all that they can
to hunt us down.
First, they have to find us.
Be assured, Marshall will use
all of his resources to do that.
It will be too late. Right?
- You want me to go ahead with it?
- I'm surprised you haven't already.
It was your idea, after all.
- It's fairly radical.
- Brilliant.
We are forced to react now.
Consider it done.
CTX will enter the city's water supply
within an hour.
It'll spread very rapidly.
Most of the population will be addicted
come, say, dinnertime.
Where is the other body?
Detective Lambert, phone.
The undercover agents are dead.
- All three of them?
- Yes, sir.
You wanted to see me?
We've had traces of CTX show up
in the town's water supply.
Do we know where?
My intel is tracing the readings
back to the source of the CTX.
Good, that is worth knowing.
How much time we got?
Current measurements predict
15,000 people...
...will be fully addicted to CTX
in the next 12 hours.
I'm afraid Werner and Robinson
will let this happen...
...and make us the scapegoats.
Marshall's not gonna let that happen.
He's got a new team together.
Tell Marshall I'm having
his armory brought here.
Thanks for the decent intel.
You're welcome, soldier.
What are we doing here?
It's my place.
I have two agents here to brief us.
- Admiral, you wanted to see me?
- Yeah.
- Do I need to be worried?
- Not in the least.
- Everything's under control.
- Everything?
Are you keeping me
informed of everything?
Admiral, I can handle it.
Handle it?
At the end of the day, none of this
will ever have happened. Okay?
I never liked the CTX program,
or Werner and Robinson.
- Who handles the case locally?
- Detective Lambert, I believe.
I want to talk to him.
We're gonna have to start
kicking over some trash cans.
Our low-orbiting recon has determined
the parameters of their activities.
It includes the outskirts of the city,
as well as...
Marshall, don't shoot.
We need her alive.
Nice timing, Dwayne.
Dwayne, get me the injured
out of here, ASAP.
Get me a cleanup team in here,
ASAP.
Got the Wicked Witch of the North
here. Try to secure her.
Get her into the Majestic lab
and in interrogation, ASAP.
Dwayne, give me a hand,
would you?
So, what's the intel?
We have confirmed reports
of primary victims...
...those most vulnerable
to the infection.
Sadly, more of these will just pinpoint
Aroon's base and the CTX lab.
- How are we gonna deal with them?
- The way we always do.
Let's go to the armory.
Marshall, I have these just for you.
These Nanographite blades...
...were built for a man
with your kind of fighting skills.
They are of
the strongest substance known...
...and will extend to fight as fast as
the reflexes of the person using them.
Now, they're assimilated
to your body.
They should balance the reflexes
of someone addicted to CTX.
They'll come in handy.
I think this is a lot bigger than any
one of us could have ever imagined.
I still got a few tricks up my sleeve.
I'm glad somebody does.
I'm gonna check it out.
What the fuck were they thinking?
It's just really a shame
it turned out this way.
- What's the story with Tia?
- Tia's good.
That's my girl. I trained her.
She has a lot of special abilities.
She has a lot of special technique.
She'll work out good for us.
We're fucked, aren't we?
I don't think so.
You think we have a chance?
I do.
Are you losing control
of the situation?
They're in a secure area.
Nothing should endanger
the program.
We are all in danger
until they are dead.
Unless we can bring them to us,
on our terms.
You got a plan?
Well, see, we're kind of between
a rock and a hard place.
We had to come in here
to get stuff we needed...
...but as soon as we accessed
the building, Werner knew.
So we got trouble.
I'm starting to think
we should call for backup.
Unfortunately, it's not going to be
backup that comes.
It's going to be a strike team
to take us out.
Oh, shit.
Okay, guys.
Get your teams up and out.
I've got something to do here.
Let's go.
So, what have we got?
The old transit holding center
has gone online, sir.
Which means
they've occupied the building.
Send in a strike team. Soft entry.
- Morgan's onto us.
- But he's not the problem.
We're talking mass hysteria
if this gets out.
Let's make goddamned sure
it doesn't.
Well, Reina.
Here are your choices: talk or die.
I hope you do the right thing because
enough people have died already.
Where is Aroon's base?
Reina, do you hear me?
I'm running out of patience.
I will never tell you anything.
This time you really pissed me off.
You killed all of my best men.
That wasn't nice.
Now, you know
what this will do to you.
Now, I'm going to give you
about three seconds.
In three seconds,
if you don't tell me...
...I will kill you.
Just like you did to my men.
One.
Two.
Three.
Bastia!
Not so tough after all.
- She did the right thing.
- He's a very good listener.
Clear.
- Clear.
- Sir?
They're gone. Let's get out of here.
Damn it!
The lab has been
completely wiped, sir.
We have a shitload
of weapons missing...
...and technology unaccounted for.
Who code-accessed the building?
The liaison, Tia.
And Marshall Lawson.
- You know him, right?
- Oh, yeah.
He's a headcase. Does what he wants.
We had to transfer him out.
Where are they now?
We are using a tracking device
as we speak.
Wait right there, sir.
This area is restricted.
Can I help you?
Detective Lambert. Local police.
And?
These are undercover policemen.
My guys.
The autopsy showed up
a big amount of a substance...
...and the rumor is that
it was developed by the military.
And you have evidence
to support this?
Is three dead bodies not enough?
No. I don't think I can help you.
You're wasting my time.
This is not military business.
Take it up with my superiors.
You bet I will.
Are you sure this is secure?
Yeah, I'm pretty sure. I set it up.
- You don't think we should call it in?
- Let's get there first.
Well, we will call in
when the time is right.
So, what are we going to do?
We're going to send in
our best A-team.
I've gone to a lot of trouble
to teach my number one finest...
...who's infected with CTX...
...and who's not.
You know that.
Once they know we've made them...
...they will be killing us real quick.
It's either them or us.
First come, first served.
It's off the A88. Just east.
Can I talk to you?
Yeah. Talk away.
In private?
Sure.
Clean the slate.
Find the bitch and take her out.
Robinson, yeah. Go ahead.
We got them.
Safe house on the edge of town.
Make sure you get it right this time.
I pray we're making
the right decision.
Can I trust you?
I certainly hope so.
You know I care for you.
I know.
Me too.
Identification, please.
Hey. I'll cover the back on my own.
Your team, cover the front.
- Clear.
You sent in a team...
...without my authorization?
I had to make a split decision.
I think it was the right one.
You seriously underestimated
Marshall and his abilities.
We've got a secure call
coming in for you, admiral.
Who is it?
Won't say. But he's on
one of our secure walkies.
- Patch him into the speakerphone.
- Done.
You're on with him now.
- Admiral?
- What can I do for you, Marshall?
I'm flattered, really flattered,
you recognize my voice.
You're the only one
to pull a stunt like this.
I'm assuming the strike team
is dead.
Yeah, that's a good assumption.
Tell Werner he needs to get up
earlier than that.
Aroon's base has been located...
...in a small village somewhere
outside of Bordeaux called...
Bastia.
I can handle this.
Marshall...
...tell me when and where.
All right. I'll send you an encryption
with the gory details...
...but suffice it to say
that I'd like my favorite A-team...
...to shoot in here right quick.
And we're going to do this
the old-fashioned way.
It looks like we'll be
working together after all.
I'll provide the intel and the training,
you give me the men.
Order B-company to mobilize.
Let's move out.
If we maintain
the element of surprise...
...while the sections enter
and search the village...
...then I will lead the attack force...
...and push forward
towards Aroon's base.
Any specifics that the Army
should know about?
Watch for the rapid pulsation
in the eyes.
If you see that, you have no time.
Because of the CTX,
they are pumped full of adrenaline...
...giving them almost superhuman
strength and reflexes.
I say, again, they are animals
out to kill you and your men.
What about containment, Marshall?
We believe
that the perimeter's secure...
...and we will be able
to stop any breaches.
Oh, I'm pleased to hear that,
Marshall.
But if this fucks up,
if the world goes down...
...you're going to have to
go down with it.
Well, in that case,
maybe we could take Werner with us.
He can report back to you
everything we're doing. How's that?
Good idea.
Well, I'm...
I'm not dressed.
That's okay. We'll put camos on you
and give you a machine gun...
...and let you come with us.
Detective Lambert
for Admiral Morgan.
Sir, you've got a call for you.
You said to call you
with information.
I am here at the cathedral.
This is where
you need to send your troops.
You know it's out of my jurisdiction.
It's okay, we're on it.
Okay, salut.
Troops are on the outskirts
of Bastia, admiral.
Section one in position.
Section two in position.
Section three in position.
Marshall?
This is Marshall. Go ahead, admiral.
Our intel tracking tells us they have
gone to ground in an old church.
I have those coordinates, sir.
And, Marshall...
...my troops are still deployed
in the village.
I can't send you any backup.
From here, you and your guys
are on your own. Good luck.
Copy that, sir.
Let's check out the guardhouse.
Okay, don't move.
Just a few questions for you.
Leave us alone.
Who is at the cathedral?
I don't know.
Watch their eyes for CTX symptoms.
Quiet, don't move.
Check the eyes
for changes in dilation.
- Tell me or I'll kill you.
- Go fuck yourself.
They're on CTX. I can see it.
Don't move.
Let's head to the cathedral.
The eyes, check the eyes.
Check their eyes.
Clear.
Get up.
This one's okay.
Let's go, men.
He's okay. Let's go.
Let's go.
- What is it?
- Nothing.
Gotta be something
to make you hang back.
Right, let's just keep up
with Marshall.
He'll be fine.
We need to rely on our instincts
to get out of here alive.
- So, what is it, soldier?
- Aroon's lab.
Gotta be somewhere around here.
- Let's take a look.
- Okay.
- CTX?
- Yeah.
It's still unrefined.
It needs to dry out
to get its powder form.
How much is all this worth?
Enough to get scared.
Real scared.
Shit. He fucking did it.
It's the city's water supply system.
- And?
- He's contaminated it.
Effective enough
for a hundred-mile radius.
Bastard!
We're splitting into fours.
A-team goes left...
...B- team goes to the right, let's go.
I told you there'd be consequences.
Dwayne, lead the B-team.
Yes, sir. Let's go.
Nobu, let's move.
Sir?
Fuck.
Let's go.
I lost everybody, sir.
They're all dead.
So...
...now you've come
to kill me, Marshall.
But as you know,
revenge is a two-way street.
Maybe you'd consider
joining forces?
I see, of course not.
You're a military man,
a man of honor and integrity.
That's too bad.
In that case, you will all die.
I promise you.
Nobu and I will take this bitch.
Dwayne, watch the back door.