No.
l don't want to do this anymore.
Please!
Please just let me go.
Let me go.
No! No!
(PANTlNG)
Please. Just let me go.
(SPEAKlNG LATlN)
Please just let me go.
l won't tell anybody. Please!
The fire is life. The fire is strength.
The blood of The One
feeds the eternal flame.
No! No!
(SCREAMlNG)
She's not The One.
She has to be The One.
You said you could feel the power.
And the signs, the signs can't be wrong.
The signs weren't wrong.
Why are you doing this?
l thought we were sisters.
We are, but sometimes sisters
do horrible things to each other.
You can't leave me here!
No!
(GRUNTlNG)
(ROARlNG)
(GlRL SCREAMlNG)
TRlNA: Oh, l just can't wait
for you girls to see this place in the spring.
The azaleas are just glorious.
lt's so green. Look at the trees.
Oh, boy. This brings back memories
of when l went to Temple Hill.
Party girls.
Jocks.
Oh, he's cute.
Oh, brainiacs over here.
Dumb but rich.
Dumb but loose.
Dumb but rich and loose. Always popular.
Mom, you really shouldn't
stereotype people like that.
Oh, l'm not stereotyping, honey.
l'm just saying water seeks its own level,
and somehow fat girls
always swim up to Kappa Omega Delta.
God love 'em, but they're ugly.
Not really caring,
but don't you think
something might have changed
in the 70 years since
you went to school here?
lgnoring you.
Wow. Sometimes wishes
really do come true.
And l'm getting mine, aren't l?
LlNDSEY: Look at that one.
TRlNA: Oh, yes.
l thought l smelled something unpleasant.
''Pi Epsilon Delta.''
PED.
What kind of girls do they make in there?
Not the kind you'll ever need to meet.
Let's just say their time has,
thankfully, come and gone.
All the way down there again
Break everything you see,,,
(GASPS )
There it is! Look!
Alpha Nu Gamma.
lt's just like the pictures. lt's beautiful.
l hope we get in.
Do you really think we'll get in?
l think you could have six heads
and a tail and still get in.
Sounds exclusive.
Oh, must you, Sarah Jane?
Yes, actually, l must.
l have worked my ass off
to ensure a place
in this house for you girls.
Two congresswomen, three governors,
and at least 12 CEOs
of major Fortune 500 companies
have lived under that roof.
Believe me, you could do worse.
God knows you have.
Take a breath
so you can breathe,
Hey, helpless,,,
TRlNA: Oh, he's cute.
SARAH: Yeah, he's all right.
TRlNA: Well, well, Sarah,
maybe we'll find someone that
meets your specifications.
Yeah.
Take a breath
so you can breathe
Hey, helpless,
you are just like me
TRlNA: ...as a student, Sarah,
you'd be perfect.
Well, l'll tell you one thing,
absolutely nothing's changed
since l went to school here.
For the good.
And bad.
Now, you girls don't get too crazy here.
l mean, if all goes well,
and l'm sure that it will,
you'll be out of this dump
and living at Alpha Nu by Friday.
And if it doesn't go well?
Hey, you're paying your own tuition.
Now, l know you girls
are gonna have a wonderful time.
Those four years in the sorority
were the best four years of my life.
There's a ringing endorsement
of motherhood.
You know, it's hard to believe,
but l am actually gonna miss you.
Dead plant.
Oh.
Sarah, now, try to behave.
Now, if you want to get initiated,
these girls have to like you.
-Do we understand each other?
-Yeah. We understand each other.
(CHUCKLES )
Lindsey. Oh.
Oh, gosh, you're so beautiful.
l hate to leave you.
Now, you take care of your sister.
Ladies, you have a wonderful time.
Not too wonderful.
Toodles!
(SCREAMS )
-What's wrong?
-Nothing. Absolutely nothing.
Can you believe it?
We are finally, finally, finally here.
l've been waiting for this day
my entire life.
Nobody knows us here.
We can reinvent ourselves.
High school's over.
We can be happy. We can be popular.
We can have friends.
l have friends.
Friend. We're friends.
No. We're sisters. Totally different.
Please. Do you really want to spend
another four years
as the freaky Goodwin girls?
This is our chance. We can go on dates
and join a sorority, the best sorority.
We're gonna be popular.
Please don't screw this up for me.
Why do you think...
Okay. l won't screw it up for you.
l promise, no weirdness,
just a new beginning for both of us.
LlNDSEY: Thank you.
(SlNGlNG)
lt goes without saying
We've been this way
for a while
GlRL: lt's really cute.
(TOWEL SNAPS )
(GlRLS LAUGH)
You've got to be kidding me.
l know. Neat, huh?
We all get to be together.
Yeah. All we're missing is
Linda Blair and a broomstick.
My cousin said if you have even, like,
one little blemish,
or if your nail polish is chipped,
they'll blackball you before the first vote.
They're talking about rush.
l know. l'm actually fairly
fluent in stuck-up bitch.
Hi. l'm Vita.
Sarah.
Hey, what time
are you guys walking over?
Maybe we could all go together.
You're rushing?
l'm sorry if that came out a little harsh.
lt's just l'm pretty sure we're not rushing
any of the same sororities.
Yeah. You know the expression,
''One of these things is not like the other.''
Uh-huh.
l'm an Alpha Nu legacy,
and my mom is president
of the alumni committee.
No way.
Well, we're rushing there, too,
so if you guys want
to walk over together...
Apologize to my friend.
You're friends?
-Yeah. Via...
-Vita.
Whatever. Apologize.
Look, Vita, l hope that you...
l mean, we were just
totally kidding around, right?
l'm sorry.
-And give her your shampoo.
-What?
You heard me.
Thanks.
Apology accepted.
You're horrible.
Ridding the world of willowy blondes
is kind of my thing.
You're, like, officially
my new favorite superhero.
And even though Brad and l
were voted cutest couple,
and everybody thought we'd get married,
l had to break up with him
because, A, l wasn't really
in love, in love with him,
and, B, l knew the long distance
thing would never work out.
How's that sound?
Delusional.
You don't even know anyone named Brad.
But l could have if...
lf you didn't have me for a sister?
l didn't say that.
You know that isn't what l meant.
l just figure if l'm starting a new life,
l might as well do something
about the old one.
Well, it'll definitely play better
than expelled, beat up, and spit on.
So does he still want you back?
Totally. That's the best part
about imaginary boyfriends.
They're very loyal.
(CHUCKLES )
Uh, Linds,
you have gigantic breasts
growing out of your breasts.
Well, this dress doesn't look
good without a little padding.
-A little?
-l need to look good tonight.
Why? Are we rushing a lesbian house?
-You can't go out like that.
-Why not?
Because, A, l'll be forced
to mock you, and, B...
Those are my socks, aren't they?
(SCREAMS )
LlNDSEY: Sarah!
(SARAH LAUGHS )
Hi.
That's so weird.
l was just coming by
to borrow a pair of socks.
l hate you.
l'm... l'm Finn. Almost forgot there.
RA for all of the second floor,
elevator to snack machine
and all points in between.
Needless to say,
my parents are very proud.
l'm Sarah,
and this is my never-speaking-to-me-again
sister, Lindsey.
Twin sister, right?
Not that it matters or anything,
but when they told me
that twins were moving in...
So, do you wrestle a lot?
Did you want something?
No. Yes.
Yes, l was just coming by to welcome you,
tell you that my room
is just across the courtyard
if, you know, you need anything.
That...
That was so not meant to sound
inappropriate or sexual.
Keep working on it.
And give you these.
They got dropped off at my room,
which l think l mentioned
is just across the courtyard.
lt's an invitation.
To rush Pi Epsilon Delta?
That's that creepy house.
Oh, my God,
why would they send us these?
Tradition.
They're, like, one of the oldest
and most formal houses on campus.
lt's strictly invitation only.
See? Now that sounds exclusive.
LlNDSEY: Don't even think about it.
The only place we're going is Alpha Nu.
-So who gets these?
-l don't know.
l've actually never even met someone
that's gotten one before.
Must be something special about you.
Yeah, something like that.
See you around.
Temple Hill, where feminism
officially went to die.
Shut up!
Wait, we need some sort of signal
for when one of us is ready to go.
You know, something subtle like...
(RETCHlNG)
l swear, you're as bad as Mom.
Why do you judge people
before you even know them?
Uh, isn't that what
they're about to do to us?
Yes, but it's their job.
Hmm.
Do you have any idea
how stupid that sounded?
Again, yes, and again, shut up.
(PAPER DOLL PLAYlNG)
Lindsey and Sarah Goodwin.
GlRL: Hi, welcome to Alpha Nu!
Yes, right here, please.
Yeah, take one of these.
Just a little more
We can still see you
We can make you better
Wow, not a Skipper or Midge
in the whole bunch.
You know, l swear l will hold you down
and pluck out your eyebrows...
Relax! For the next two hours,
l will be totally sweet,
funny and charming.
l promise.
(GlRLS SQUEAL)
-Hi!
Welcome to Alpha Nu Gamma.
You two are adorable!
-Oh, my...
-Oh, my God, shut up.
They're sisters! Oh, my gosh!
-GlRL 2: That is so totally cute.
-GlRL 1 : So cute!
But we're just so excited that you're here,
and we understand
if you're, like, nervous, because, like...
BOTH: Totally, duh.
This is the most important night
of your entire lives.
So whatever you do,
just remember, don't screw up,
because we're, like, totally judging you
the whole entire time. Okay?
GlRL 1 : l can't do it.
She's kidding.
Take a breath. lt's okay.
(CHUCKLES )
See? Nobody laughs.
You really gotta stop doing that.
GlRL 2: No way. lt's foolproof.
lf anyone actually falls for it, they're out.
Cruel but effective.
-Anybody fall for it yet?
-Those two over there.
(LAUGHlNG)
Oh, my God. Look at Shelly's dress.
Heinous color.
Hi, l'm Esme.
Sarah and Lindsey.
ls Trina Goodwin your mom?
Yeah. Do you know her?
Totally. l love Trina. She's so cool.
So you don't know her.
Well, she paid for our new kitchen. So...
Actually, her fourth husband
paid for your kitchen, but...
Wow, your bracelets are really amazing.
Where did you...
SARAH: Thanks.
l've been collecting them
for a couple of years.
l just broke up with my boyfriend.
His name was Brad.
That's horrible.
lt's okay.
They weren't in love, in love.
Pace yourself.
Give the girls some punch.
Thanks.
Oh, my gosh, you guys, l'm so sorry.
lt's so hard to catch up
with the girls, you know?
Are you having fun? So, okay, wait,
did you just graduate from high school?
Where did you go?
GlRL 2: Oh, my God, your dress is
so cute. Where did you get it?
Don't you hate it when, like...
GlRL 1 : Oh, l know.
Just a paper doll,
l'll tell you what to do
To make it so your mother
doesn't recognize you
Just a paper doll
Our pills give you a rush
y ou'll lie down and you'll wake up,,,
(GHOSTL y WHlSPERlNG)
l am having the best time.
Me, too.
Can we go now?
-Sure.
-Really?
l love you.
You did so good tonight. Thank you.
l'll go grab your jacket
and meet you outside.
-Okay.
(GlRLS CHATTERlNG)
Sarah, wait. You can't go
until you meet Chorinne.
She's our chapter president.
So you're the one
that l've been hearing so much about.
l certainly hope our sisters
have been making you feel...
(GASPS )
Oh! What happened? Are you okay?
l'm so sorry.
No, don't... Don't be silly.
lt wasn't your fault.
LlNDSEY: What did you do?
Nothing. l need to go.
Wait, don't. You don't have to go.
Sorry about your, your dress.
lt was nice to meet you.
Wait, you don't have to...
LlNDSEY: Sarah, wait.
-You still have your doubts?
-A few.
What if she doesn't wanna pledge?
We're Alpha Nu.
When's the last time
anyone turned us down?
LlNDSEY: Sarah!
SARAH: Just leave me alone!
LlNDSEY: Sarah, wait!
Sarah!
Don't touch me.
What is your problem?
l don't know, Linds.
l don't know what my problem is,
which is kind of my problem.
Things were supposed
to be different this time.
This was my chance.
You promised.
You think l did that on purpose?
l didn't even wanna go.
Oh, so because l dragged you there,
you decide to humiliate me
in front of everybody?
Decided? l didn't decide anything.
lf l had decided anything,
l would decide to be normal.
Sarah.
(SOBBlNG)
So what do you want me to do?
Do you want me to
go back there and tell them
that just because l'm a freak
that they shouldn't
take it out on my sister?
'Cause l'll go. l'll go right now.
l hate it when you say stuff like that.
You know it isn't true.
lt's true. lt's always been true.
l'm sorry.
Sorry l'm a freak
or sorry for being a bitch?
Both.
That's fair. l'm sorry, too.
LlNDSEY: So what did you think,
you know, before the exploding glass
and the running out
the front door screaming?
Honestly? l kind of liked them.
ls that possible?
Well, in your defense, l think
they spiked the punch, but...
(SARAH LAUGHS )
l kinda liked 'em, too.
Sarah, l wanna join so bad...
(LlNDSEY SCREAMlNG)
-SARAH: Lindsey.
-Oh, something grabbed my ankle.
Nothing grabbed your ankle.
You were on that root.
Here. Come on.
No. l can't walk.
-l think it's broken.
-Broken?
(GROANlNG)
Let's see if we can use their phone.
Come on.
No, that's PED. l don't wanna go in there.
Well, they're already out here.
GlRL 1 : Are you hurt?
Can you guys help me? My sister tripped.
GlRL 2: Sure.
Thank you.
GlRL 3: Here, lean on me.
We'll just go inside
and use their phone really quick.
GlRL 4: We've got stuff inside.
GlRL 5: l think it might be broken.
Told you.
My great-grandmother.
People say there's a resemblance,
but l really don't see it.
Eugenia Hunter.
Sarah Goodwin.
Was your great-grandmother
in the first pledge class?
No, she was our founder.
PED is the second oldest house
on campus.
Who's the first?
Alpha Nu. lt's been a battle
since the very beginning.
We were afraid
you weren't going to make it.
Oh, right, the invitation. Thanks for that.
We would have stopped by
sooner, but we just...
We got in late,
and we kind of had to unpack.
Was that before or after
you went to Alpha Nu?
You're still wearing your nametag.
And l guess l should have
unpacked a better story.
lt's really none of my business,
but, like l said, we have something
of a long-standing rivalry.
No offense, but it kind of
looks like they're winning.
We're not so big on quotas.
Some years we pledge dozens.
Other years, none at all.
lt just depends
if we find the qualities we're looking for.
What are you looking for?
Let's see.
How's that ankle coming along?
Don't worry. l won't bite.
How is that possible?
Sometimes things aren't
nearly what they seem.
So are you sure you're okay
to walk back to the dorm?
LlNDSEY: l'm okay, really.
Good. Good night.
Thanks.
Why did you send us an invitation?
l wondered if you were gonna ask me that.
Your mother used to be a friend.
Good night.
Okay, creepy.
There's no way she and Mom were friends.
(SCREAMlNG)
They asked me back!
l got in.
(EXHALES )
l'm gonna be an Alpha Nu.
-See?
-Open yours.
Alpha Nu and PED.
You know what they call them?
Pigs, elephants and dogs.
-Who calls them that?
-l don't know. Everyone. Us now.
You know, Linds, l don't know
if l'm really cut out for this sorority thing.
LlNDSEY: What do you mean? Sarah...
lf you really wanna pledge,
then l think you should do it.
No, we talked about this. We agreed.
lf we're going to do this,
we're doing it together.
-lf l jumped off...
-Yes, l would jump off the bridge.
l jumped off the garage
because you told me to, didn't l?
Yeah, and you broke your leg
in three places.
You won't break anything.
Fine. We can pledge.
Oh!
(BOTH LAUGH)
-MAN: Here you go, man.
-Subtle.
MAN: Heads up.
Ladies.
Holy Abercrombie.
Guess we can take Greek god off
the endangered species list.
He's perfect. Can you imagine?
-No.
-l meant for me.
Again, no.
Why not?
Oh, Linds, you, your expectations.
Let's try and keep a little perspective.
MAN: Go long. Heads up, man, heads up.
Good catch, bro.
His name's Damien, Gamma Alpha Delta.
He's sweet. l'll put in a good word for you.
Really?
Sure, that's what sisters are for.
Congratulations, by the way.
We are all very excited.
(GlGGLES )
Oh, eyelash.
See ya.
She didn't let you make a wish.
lt's okay. They're all coming true.
(CHUCKLES )
SARAH: l swear, if you burst into song,
l'll be forced to beat you.
-See you tonight.
-LlNDSEY: See ya.
European Mysticism. l'm impressed.
No Psych 101 for our Miss Goodwin.
lt sounded interesting.
So how goes the quest
for social acceptance?
l got in. Alpha Nu.
lmpressive.
-You think so?
-Totally.
Really? l wouldn't have pegged you
as a big advocate of the Greek system.
Well, l'm not, really,
but l'm also not allowed to ask you out
if you're living in the dorm.
Are you asking me out?
Good morning, Sarah.
Good morning, class.
Welcome to European Mysticism.
l'm Dr. Hunter.
Please open your notebooks.
And depending how we interpret
the prehistoric cave paintings
at Guoncaux,
there is evidence that man
has been studying the occult
for over 30,000 years.
Can anyone tell me
what the word ''occult'' actually means?
Yeah, uh, witches, devils...
The dark side?
No, no, no, it actually means ''hidden,
''unknown, that which
we do not understand.''
But the world is full
of things we don't understand,
and when we don't understand something,
we tend to be afraid of it, or worse yet,
ashamed of it.
lsn't that true, Sarah?
(CLASS WHlSPERlNG)
Why don't you all take a moment
to copy this down?
DR. HUNTER: (ECHOlNG)
But you truly have nothing
to be ashamed of, Sarah.
So young, so powerful,
so many wonderful gifts.
Don't worry. This doesn't concern them.
You poor thing. You live in constant fear,
afraid you might hurt yourself
or someone you love.
That's not true.
l can show you how
to control it, how to use it,
how to claim your rightful place
in the world.
l don't know what you're talking about.
Then l suggest you start paying attention.
Your life depends on it.
CHORlNNE: Hey.
Wow.
You're a little tense
for a girl who's pledging
the best house on campus.
ls there anything that l can do to help?
Why is everybody
always offering to help me?
l don't want any help. l'm fine.
Look, if you're just doing this
because my mom gave you guys
a bunch of money...
CHORlNNE: Wow, l'm guessing
that you didn't have
a very big going away party back home.
Look, l'm just trying to be your friend here.
You don't even know me.
l'm beginning to wonder if l want to.
l'm sorry. l didn't... l don't know.
lt's just been a very strange day,
and l've had a lot going on.
No offense. Hanging out with...
A bunch of screaming, stuck-up fembots?
Your words.
My thoughts, but your words.
Hanging out is truly
the last thing l need right now.
Well, l think it's exactly
what you need right now.
lt's good to know
that people are on your side.
You know, that there's actually
a reason we call each other sisters.
Yeah. l already have a sister.
Hey, Goodwin, what happened to you?
One second you're there,
the next you're not.
What's the matter, am l too fast for you?
l'm sure hoping.
FlNN: Don't mean to chat and dash,
but l've got, like,
two seconds to get to this TA gig.
No rest for the indigent.
So, uh, why don't you come by
and you can look over my notes?
Not meant to sound
inappropriate or sexual.
(CHUCKLES )
And here l thought you were having
boy problems.
(CHUCKLES )
-FlNN: Sorry. Sorry.
-SARAH: l hardly even know him.
Well, you should definitely
do something about that.
He's cute in a
slightly overeager, pick me,
last-puppy-dog-in-the-window kind of way.
l guess l kinda like that.
Yeah? Well, l'd say you were
a little north of ''kinda.''
See?
A friendly shoulder and a lovesick hottie.
Life can't be that bad.
Look, initiation's Friday night,
and after the ceremony,
we throw this huge party.
You should totally invite him.
That is, of course,
you make it through hell week.
Hell week?
CHORlNNE: lt's not nearly
as bad as it sounds.
Well, for me, it isn't.
For you, it'll kinda suck,
but l wouldn't worry.
l can almost guarantee
that l'll be seeing you at initiation.
VlTA: l know Kappa Omega Delta
isn't really considered
the best house on the row,
but it was either there or PED.
You know what people
call them, don't you?
l didn't know you rushed PED.
Oh, yeah, l rushed everywhere.
But if l pledge PED
and you pledge Alpha Nu,
we won't be able to talk to each other.
lt's like a rule or something.
-LlNDSEY: Well, if you ask me...
-Nobody did.
-l thought PED was invitation only.
-Oh, it is, which is so cool.
-Dr. Hunter thinks l have a sixth sense.
-Freak.
Not you. Dr. Hunter. Do you?
What?
-Have a sixth sense.
-VlTA: l don't know.
l mean, l always kinda
know stuff about people
before l even meet them.
lt's kinda weird that she knew that.
Maybe she has it, too.
But you'd think l would have known that.
Hey, you guys wanna go down
to the dining hall?
l hear they leave desserts out.
No, thanks.
l've gotta go over to Finn's
to look at his notes.
-l thought you were dropping that class.
-l am.
(SO SMALL PLAYlNG)
Now she really
wants him back
Well, she should
He's walking down the street
with a fake grin on his face
Getting dirty looks from
the jerks who run this place
Waving to the locals
who don't know he's got it all
FlNN: Hmm.
(KNOCKlNG ON DOOR)
Just a sec.
Um...
The football players are
at the other end of the hall,
if that's who you're looking for.
Well, don't you remember me?
l saw you earlier with Sarah. l'm Chorinne.
Oh, yeah, no. l know who you are.
l mean, everybody knows who you are.
l was just...
l was just a little unclear
what you're doing in my doorway.
Make that very unclear.
Well, l might as well just be honest.
Back at the sorority house,
we were playing a little game
of truth or dare.
Naked?
Sorry. Just trying to be clear.
(CHUCKLES )
Continue.
l was dared to introduce myself
to the hottest guy l'd never met.
Hi.
Oh, me.
Really?
So...
ls that it?
Well, actually,
it was a double dare.
So, there might be just
one or two other things.
FlNN: Whoa !
SARAH: Finn, l'm here for my tutoring.
Okay. No, no, no.
Oh. Hi, Sarah.
FlNN: Sarah...
(DOOR SLAMS SHUT)
Sarah!
Wait!
(SlGHS )
God, l hope that doesn't cost me tenure.
Ladies...
Oh, that's right. lt's trash day.
l must remember to drag
those cans out to the curb.
Somebody needs to drop a house
on that old woman.
Oh, l wouldn't let it bother you too much.
After Friday, l doubt we're gonna
have to worry about her anymore.
Did you see she's wearing pearls now?
(SlNGlNG) That look that paralyzed
lt's too intense, those eyes
y ou steal my words, my thoughts, my life
y ou're robbing me
Look, she must be putting in
a good word for you.
You'll know for sure
if she takes her clothes off.
Don't do this. Please.
l'm sure there's a reason...
Lindsey, whose side are you on?
l'm on your side, but...
Maybe it was a joke,
or it's part of hell week, you know,
like a loyalty test.
Or maybe they know each other
and you were breaking them up.
Have you thought of that?
SARAH: l really don't care why she did it.
That's her idea
of what it means to be a sister?
(GRUNTS )
Sarah!
l'm sorry. l didn't...
Hmm.
(GROANS )
l think she turned us down.
(DOOR OPENS )
You said you could help me.
l want you to help me make it stop.
That's fine, but can it wait
until the end of class?
No. Do your blackboard thing.
Why don't you take a moment
to copy this all down?
(PENS SCRATCHlNG)
So what am l? What's the matter with me?
Why am l such a freak?
-Do you really need me to tell you?
-Yes, l need you to tell me.
l need you tell me
that there's some sort of rational...
Tea?
Well, l'm not what you think l am.
l'm not a...
-A what? A witch?
-l'm not.
Fine. You can call yourself
whatever you want.
l prefer ''magi.''
Of course, that just tells you how old l am.
But there's no denying
that you're one of the chosen.
-Your powers...
-Stop saying that.
l don't have any powers.
Listen, there's no time
to keep debating the obvious.
Trust me, Sarah. lt's a lot
easier to accept your gifts
than it is to fight against them.
Good. At least that's settled.
No, it's not settled. Nothing is settled.
So true. There's a battle going on, Sarah,
and l'm afraid you're going to
have to choose a side.
You mean that thing
between you and Alpha Nu?
That ''thing,'' as you call it,
has been going on
since the beginning of time
in one location or another.
-Wait. Alpha Nu...
-They call themselves ''vestals.''
As in ''virgins''?
l know. Everybody has the same reaction.
lt's an honorary title.
ln all of life, Sarah, there's good and evil.
There's light and dark.
There's balance and counterbalance.
Our power comes from the earth.
lt lives within us.
Theirs...
Theirs is acquired,
lt's manufactured
through spells and potions,
but it comes with a cost,
lt must be worshiped and fed,
manipulated and maintained.
Sugar?
But they haven't been properly
tending the flame,
the true source of their power.
They've gotten complacent and greedy.
They've been flaunting their power
when they should have been conserving it
and patiently waiting,
They've been so sure
that The One is going to walk
through their door at any minute,
that perhaps it's understandable.
The One?
EUGENlA: Occasionally,
someone is born with such strength,
such energy, such life force,
she can affect the whole balance of power.
She's called The One.
No. There's no way.
They cannot possibly think
that l'm this One.
l mean, l just tossed
Boobarella off a bridge.
That should tell them something.
Volumes, Sarah.
lf the flame goes out, so do they.
They're desperate.
Trust me, if you're a goat or a virgin,
l'd avoid that side of campus altogether.
They're not gonna give you up
without a fight.
You said l had a choice.
lf you pledge PED, you'll be safe.
Then we might finally be able
to wipe them off the face of the Earth.
And if l pledge Alpha Nu
and give them what they want?
You won't live past Friday.
The power is in your blood,
and the only way they can get it
is to drain it from you.
Sarah, they don't want you as a member.
They need you as a sacrifice.
(STUDENTS CHATTERlNG)
LlNDSEY: The first thing Mom did
when she drove us onto campus
was warn us about that house.
Don't you think she had a reason?
Like, l don't know, maybe they're insane?
Yes, l know. lt is insane.
But at the same time, it makes sense.
Who thinks it makes sense?
-l do.
-Oh, good.
'Cause, you know, that's what matters.
lt means that there's a reason for me,
for the way l am.
For why my entire life has sucked?
Lindsey.
This was supposed to be my chance.
All l wanted was a chance.
l just wanted to pledge a sorority.
Was that too much to ask?
Oh, my God.
Have you not even been listening to me?
l'm sorry, but this isn't about you.
'Cause it's never about me.
Eighteen years, it's never been about me,
but how could it be
when my sister's the lt?
-The One.
-Whatever.
l just...
l don't know. Are you jealous?
Are you threatened?
Are you afraid that l might finally get a life
and leave you?
Why is it that every time
you sense l might be happy,
you try to destroy it?
That's not true. That's never been true.
l would never do anything to hurt you.
But that's all you've ever done.
Since the moment we were born,
it's like l didn't exist.
Everything's always been about you,
managing you, helping you.
''Don't make Sarah mad.
Watch out for Sarah. Where's Sarah?
''Don't let Sarah wander off.
Don't leave Sarah alone.
''Don't let Sarah try to kill herself again.''
(GASPS )
You've ruined everything.
(DOOR SHUTS )
(PEOPLE CHATTERlNG)
You're looking tired.
Don't you ever knock?
l've disemboweled people for less.
They're fighting.
l told you.
We're running out of time.
lf she's not sacrificed on Friday,
we could lose everything.
Not looking forward
to the depths of hell, huh?
lt's funny, because it seems
like you'd feel right at home there.
-How can you be so calm?
-Yoga.
Oh, and not having a soul helps, too.
The knife of truth.
lt can only cut the flesh of The One.
ESME: But it won't do us any good...
Guess it still works.
She won't come willingly, Chorinne,
and her blood means nothing
if she hasn't been initiated.
All this time, we've waited for The One.
We can't wait any longer.
We need her power.
Thank you, Esme,
but this isn't my first trip
to the sacrificial altar.
She'll go through initiation.
Her sister will see to that.
And just how do you think
you're gonna get the sister to help?
CHORlNNE: Easy.
l'll make a wish.
(MUSlC PLAYlNG)
Hey.
Sorry. l didn't see you there.
You're all sweaty.
l like it.
Okey-doke. That should do it.
Hey, wait. Wait up.
What...
What was all that about?
Oh, nothing. lt's just a little something
that l'm brewing up.
-Want some?
-No, l'm good.
You sure?
Say, l don't know what you're doing later,
but if you leave your window unlocked...
Well, isn't that against the rules?
Yeah, well, you never seemed
to mind breaking the...
So, come by around 1 1 :00?
Yeah, sure. Whatever.
Good boy.
Hey!
You're not leaving, are you?
Yeah.
l...
l'm Damien.
Lindsey.
A little strong, don't you think?
Oh, it's the caffeine.
Always messes with the proportions.
-Do l have something on my shirt?
-No. Oh, eyes up. l'm sorry.
So you're an Alpha Nu pledge, right?
No, it didn't really work out.
No big deal. lt's just, you see,
l'm a Gamma Theta Delta,
and we usually only date Alpha Nus.
So, would you like
to go out with me sometime?
Please say yes.
Yeah, that would be...
-You're a jerk.
-What?
No, l'm sorry. l won't look down again!
l... Lindsey!
Five minutes ago,
l would've given anything to be one of you.
But that's what we want, too.
And if you think
getting your flying monkey
to pretend l'm hot is going to make...
How is this possible?
We attribute it to healthy living.
l mean, what's the point
of having inner beauty
if you can't see it?
Everything Sarah said was true.
No offense, but l doubt
anything Sarah said is true.
You have to consider the source.
l mean, people are jealous of girls like us.
They say such vicious things.
lt's really kind of pathetic.
l knew you were meant to be an Alpha Nu
the moment l met you.
-But Sarah...
-Has nothing to do with this.
lt's you we want.
Sarah means nothing to us.
And we'll be so hurt if you say no.
Please, just think about it.
You really do look good.
(DOOR SHUTS )
Do whatever you need to do.
Hey.
SARAH: Linds, l'm so sorry.
Are you going somewhere?
We both are. Linds, it's just... lt's wrong.
The sooner we get out of here...
They still want me.
Who wants you?
Alpha Nu. They want me to pledge.
And when they told you that,
you ran screaming in abject horror,
tossing crucifixes and garlic
in your wake, right?
Something like that.
SARAH: Just grab your stuff.
We've really gotta get out of here.
l already packed all of my...
(GHOSTLY WHlSPERS )
They're just using you to get to me.
This isn't about you, Sarah.
No one's out to get you. Honestly.
SARAH: We don't have time for this.
Just get your stuff. Let's go.
LlNDSEY: No!
You can't make me go with you!
-l'm trembling.
-l didn't do that.
lt's not me! l'm not doing it!
Open the door, Sarah!
Sarah! Sarah, what are you doing?
SARAH: Here, watch out!
Help! Somebody help us!
-SARAH: Calm down, please!
-LlNDSEY: Help!
SARAH: Calm down.
l'm trying to put it out!
Help! Somebody help us!
(FlRE ALARM BUZZlNG)
Sarah, please! Make it stop!
SARAH: l'm trying! l'm trying!
LlNDSEY: Sarah, do something!
Sarah, please, make it stop!
Sarah!
(LlNDSEY SCREAMlNG)
(POLlCE SlRENS WAlLlNG)
Lindsey, please, don't do this!
Goodbye, Sarah.
Lindsey.
l went by your room.
This is pretty much all l could find.
You know, before the mandatory
evacuation and our end of the floor
being declared uninhabitable
because of smoke damage.
Hey, good news!
Even though initiation isn't until Friday,
Dr. Hunter said l can move in right away,
which is nice, considering l don't have
a place to live, either.
The first part was the good news.
The second part was just
kind of stating the obvious.
No, it is good news.
l'm glad we're gonna be together.
Hey, do you think you can find me
something to wear?
l smell like a briquette.
A project. Excellent. l'll be right back.
You're more of a fall, right?
Never mind. l'll figure it out.
So, what do you think?
lt's like you were expecting me.
Just so you know,
l'm leaving as soon as l can get Lindsey.
l don't know if that'll be possible.
Leaving or getting Lindsey?
Why don't you get cleaned up?
We'll talk in the morning.
How do l know l can trust you?
Good night, Sarah.
Welcome to Pi Epsilon Delta.
And don't worry.
(GHOSTLY WHlSPER)
You'll be safe here.
(GROWLlNG)
(ROARlNG)
(PEOPLE CHATTERlNG)
Addicted to porn.
Cheated on his SATs.
Boxers instead of briefs.
Pretty good, huh?
l mean, l always kind of knew stuff.
lt was a little unfocused, but ever since
l started working with Dr. Hunter,
l've gotten a lot better at it.
''Boxers instead of briefs'' is focused?
lt depends on what you're focusing on.
That one.
Calls his mother every Sunday.
Terrified he has bad breath.
Okay, first, if you never
wanted to see me again,
which l totally understand,
but l think that you should hear my side
of the story before you rush to judgment,
you could just have told me
instead of burning the dorm down.
So uncool.
Second, are you okay?
l mean, l've been going crazy
trying to find you.
Obviously, l'm a little
conflicted emotionally.
l'm fine. Thank you for asking.
But, first of all,
l didn't burn the dorm down.
And you're kind of a jerk for thinking l did.
Second...
Former Boy Scout. Totally sincere.
Briefs.
Excuse me?
And second, l forgive you
for temporarily falling under the spell
of the princess of darkness.
Call me later. l'm at PED now.
Well, l'll just call you later at PED.
That went well.
Oddly, but well.
SARAH: What else?
-Really wanna know?
-Yes.
Wants to be a doctor. Likes cats. Virgin.
-You're making that up.
-Who knows? l might be.
Mind reading, not really an exact science.
So, what do you know about me?
Obviously, not a lot,
since you're still sitting there.
You like the color blue,
and you're not as scary
as you think you are.
Anything else?
l don't know why you did it.
l was kind of hoping you could tell me.
l knew that.
l don't really remember
the before, just the after.
The blood, the hospital, the ambulance.
Maybe it was about the attention.
l'm thinking about getting rid of them.
LlNDSEY: Well, it's about time.
You could use a makeover.
Lindsey? What happened to you?
You look pneumatic.
Do they make noise if you...
-Whoa !
-MAN 2: Oh, yeah!
Oh, my God.
Thanks for giving the guys
in the cheap seats a thrill.
MAN: Nice.
-What the hell's going on?
-l'm an Alpha Nu.
We have a certain image to maintain.
-But this isn't you.
-LlNDSEY: lt is now.
As Mom said, people find their own level.
l've found mine.
Looks like you've found yours.
Don't be jealous.
l'm sure we could
make room for one more.
Personification of evil,
and that isn't her real hair color.
SARAH: She doesn't scare me.
VlTA: Really?
She scares the crap out of me,
and l'm not even marked for death.
Come on.
You better be scared of me.
You've been a very bad little pledge.
You know the rules.
Alpha Nus don't speak to pigs,
elephants or dogs.
l'm sorry.
lt won't happen again. She's my sister.
Not anymore.
She made her choice, and you made yours.
You're not regretting it, are you?
-No.
-Good.
But, you know, you have been getting off
pretty easy, because it's hell week,
and your fellow pledges have been proving
their loyalty by scrubbing toilets
and waiting on the actives
hand and foot, while you...
Oh, it would just be so sad
if you didn't make it to initiation.
No, please. l have to be initiated.
Just tell me what you want me to do.
CHORlNNE: l'm so glad to hear that,
because some sacrifices
are gonna have to be made.
(SHELF CREAKlNG)
Concentrate on the books.
Focus your mind on moving them.
The power is inside of you.
l'm trying.
You're not, and more importantly,
l think you're failing to understand
the gravity of the situation.
l understand the situation.
My sister's tongue-kissing the devil,
while l'm learning how to
pull a rabbit out of a hat.
lf you could actually do that,
l don't think l'd be so worried.
We have to get her out of there.
Honey, she made her choice.
She didn't know what she was doing.
l can't leave without her.
There's no place on Earth you can go
where they won't find you.
Your only hope of protection
is going through initiation at PED.
Only then will you come
into your full power.
So initiate me.
What do you need?
Blood, eye of newt? What?
There's a time and place for everything.
These rituals were set long ago,
quite literally in stone.
The ceremony cannot take place
until the rising of a full moon.
Why can't you people just say ''Friday''?
When you're talking eternity,
''Friday'' is a relatively new concept.
But without my so-called powers,
then their pit of eternal badness
will just go out and they'll go away, right?
Hardly.
As vulnerable as the Alpha Nus are,
they're not gonna give up without a fight.
l wasn't kidding when l said they're gonna
be tossing every virgin they can find
into that pit in the hopes
of keeping it alive.
They wouldn't really.
They're Alpha Nus.
There's nothing they wouldn't really.
Fortunately, we're in
the middle of sorority row,
so good luck with that virgin thing.
Most likely what they'll just do
is try and kill you so we can't have you.
You said you knew my mother.
l met her when she came through rush.
This was clearly the girl
we'd all been waiting for.
l thought l had convinced her
to pledge PED,
but Alpha Nu has a way of
playing on insecurities, making promises.
She wasn't as strong as l had hoped.
Not as strong as you.
Right.
But they'd misread the signs.
We all had.
She wasn't The One.
She was pregnant,
just a few weeks, with twins.
With you.
With The One.
We would all just have to wait.
You mean my mother knew all about this?
She knew and she let me
come here, brought me here?
Your mother would never have
wished this upon you.
l don't understand.
Your mother was killed
right after you were born.
Trina Goodwin is not your real mother.
She is.
(GHOSTLY WHlSPERS )
TRlNA: What do you mean she isn't here?
l delivered her to your doorstep.
Well, it might have helped
if you'd delivered her
with a slightly cheerier disposition.
This is not my fault.
Well, we'll just see
what National has to say about that.
(GASPS )
Eighteen years ago, l was called in
to clean up one of your mistakes.
l killed that girl
with my bare hands for this house.
l have spent my life
raising her two disgusting little spawn
for this house.
So do you think l am going
to stand by for one second
and watch this house destroyed
by some gutless little uppity nothing
who can't get her act together?
(GASPlNG)
Let's see what National
has to say about that.
(PANTlNG)
How's your mom?
Good.
-We were roommates.
-l know. Your picture's on our fridge.
We have Lindsey.
Two thousand years ago,
she would've been left out on a rock.
She means nothing.
Except as bait.
-They're quite close, you know.
-l know.
lnitiation is tomorrow night.
The blood of The One
will be drained and fed
to the eternal flame.
Do we understand each other?
We understand each other.
Oh, goody.
Tell your mom l said hi.
Toodles!
CHORlNNE: We should've dragged
that hateful cow
down here by her black roots
and thrown her into the pit.
ESME: Well, by this time tomorrow,
you'll be able to do anything you want.
CHORlNNE: The fire's getting stronger.
lt knows The One is near.
Where is she?
PED.
Can we get to her?
Not a problem. She's worried
about her sister and about the boy.
Why the boy?
He's a virgin.
l guess we have
something of a reputation.
Well, l'd hate for all that purity
to go unappreciated.
(CHATTERlNG)
-We have to talk.
-No!
-Please.
-Just stay away from me.
l'm sorry.
Was that Lindsey? 'Cause, wow!
She really looked...
Are you okay?
-Do you wanna talk about it?
-No. l'm fine, really.
Will you just read your book, please?
You know what always
makes me feel better
when l've had a huge fight with my sister
because overnight she's turned
into some stuck-up uberbitch?
Just guessing.
Well?
l have no idea.
Kissing.
Not my sister.
But, no, seriously, l'm not making it up.
lt's actually, like,
a documented medical fact.
Lips, endorphins.
There's some connection there.
l mean, l don't really know
exactly how it works,
but it's true.
Yeah, l've heard that.
lf you don't love someone
The rules that hurt the most
Are the rules you cannot see
l thought for sure
what l'm gonna do
y ou'd be there with me
You're right. l do feel better.
Well, why don't l put this back,
and you can buy me a cup of coffee?
Will there be more kissing involved?
l've still got a lot of pain. l do.
Yes, there will be more kissing involved.
You know, l think there's supposed to be...
l think there's supposed to be
a band playing later.
Wait, don't you have initiation tonight?
Don't you have, like...
Don't all the sororities do their...
Whatever the sororities do.
You're not playing truth or dare, are you?
(GHOSTLY WHlSPERS )
FlNN: Sarah! Sarah, run! Get out of here!
SARAH: Finn! What's going on?
Finn!
Where are you?
Hi, Sarah. Oh, you've gotta be careful.
l've heard horrible stories about people
who get lost in here
and never find their way out.
(GRUNTlNG)
Your breath smells like virgin.
l'd have to say that
you're a corrupting influence.
Where's Finn? What did you do with him?
Let's just call him plan B, shall we?
You shouldn't have turned us down, Sarah.
We hate that.
l bet not as much
as l hate having my heart cut out.
l'd love to do it right now. lt'd be so easy.
And it would feel so good.
We could tell people it was an accident.
Or l could tell them because, well,
you'd be dead.
Please, Sarah,
you may be The One, but let's face it,
l'm a senior.
Your mother would be so disappointed.
(GROANS )
Hi.
CHORlNNE: lnitiation is in
a couple of hours.
How could you let her get away?
ESME: Well, she's more powerful
than she looks.
Well, you are obviously a lot stupider
than l ever imagined.
Where is she now?
How the hell am l supposed to know?
How's PED for a wild guess?
God, you're an idiot.
(FlNN GRUNTlNG)
Finn.
SARAH: Finn.
Sarah.
Lindsey, you scared me,
for so many reasons.
Oh, Sarah, you can't be here.
-They have Finn. You have to help me.
-l know. lt's a trap.
They're all waiting for you.
You have to... You have to go.
l can't. Not without Finn and you.
-No, they'll never let me go.
-Lindsey, please.
Sarah, l'm so sorry.
You were right about everything.
lt's all my fault.
lt's not your fault. lt's nobody's fault.
Listen, we'll go away, just us.
We'll go where no one knows us.
lt's gonna be okay, l promise.
They moved him to the basement.
l know the way.
Thank you.
Hey, that's what sisters are for, right?
Come on.
(FlNN GRUNTlNG)
Linds, what is this?
Finn!
Hold still. Lindsey, help me!
-LlNDSEY: l can't.
-SARAH: Why not?
Well, because, actually, this is the trap.
That's kind of what
l was trying to tell you.
Guess who just made president
of her pledge class?
Just so sorry
your mom couldn't be here to see it.
Look, l swear l have no idea
what is going on right now,
and l'm so desperately hoping to wake up.
But one thing l do know,
taunting the demonic priestess,
not a good idea.
Just stay behind me.
l'm gonna get us out of here.
All right, look, l don't want to hurt anyone,
but l have three sisters, so believe me,
l have no trouble hitting a girl.
lf l had something to hit them with.
So, what do you say, Sarah? No waiting.
You first.
l'll even help you with the shackles.
Sarah, fantasy and reality are
crashing together in a very strange way.
You really need to get
a handle on those hormones.
This is so much easier
if you offer yourself willingly.
lt's actually kind of an honor.
-Never gonna happen.
-We'll see.
Lindsey!
lf she were my sister,
l'd have slit her throat ages ago.
But still, l get the idea that
you would still trade your life for hers.
Don't even think about it.
(GRUNTlNG)
Okay, now l'm feeling really emasculated
by the whole chair thing.
-l'll do it!
-As if l'd care.
And ironically,
the only person that knife can cut is...
You.
l'm bleeding.
l thought you said
that thing wouldn't cut me.
FlNN: Sarah, come on.
Let's go.
-No! Lindsey...
-Sarah!
Not another step.
Please don't hurt her.
You promised you wouldn't hurt her.
Who am l to argue with The One?
What's happening?
Lindsey!
-Sarah!
-Lindsey!
LlNDSEY: Sarah!
-Come on. We gotta go.
-Lindsey!
Come on!
You called me ''The One.'' l'm not.
That isn't possible.
Oh, l wouldn't worry
your pretty little head about it.
Right now we've gotta get you ready
for initiation.
Sarah, you've got to tell me
what the hell is going on.
lf this is just a dream,
please wake me up or take your top off.
Finn, you need to go back to your dorm.
l have to do this alone.
My sister's life depends on it.
No, Lindsey cannot be The One.
That's impossible.
Oh, l'm afraid it's true.
lt's really quite brilliant
if you think about it,
hiding the real power in the twin
that's least able to defend herself.
Lindsey's truly the perfect vessel.
Nothing obvious, nothing overt.
No, but the signs.
The signs all pointed to Sarah.
Everyone thought so, not just me.
Though you were the one
in charge of watching
and interpreting.
Well, fortunately,
we figured it out before it was too late.
Unless, of course,
you've managed to lose her, too.
Nope. No, she's safely locked away.
One does have to appreciate
the irony of the situation.
lt's not like Lindsey has ever done
one thing in her pathetic little life
to make anyone think she had our fate
coursing through her veins.
Whereas Sarah's power
was always so obvious...
CHORlNNE: You know what
l think is ironic?
That you've spent the last 18 years
bleeding the wrong daughter.
l deserved every drop l took.
Poor Sarah, thinking she's been trying
to kill herself all these years.
lf l didn't hate her so much,
l'd almost feel sorry for her.
And l bet all those spells
that you needed her blood for
would've worked a lot better
if you'd actually used the right girl.
Well, no use crying over
spilt potions, as they say.
l've really gotta get going.
-You have an initiation to...
-CHORlNNE: Sit down.
l've spoken to National.
They'd like me to let you know
that your services are no longer required.
And they'd like back every drop of blood
that you've stolen from them.
TRlNA: This is ridiculous.
She wasn't even The One,
and it wasn't that much blood.
Lucky you.
You know, if you girls are gonna try
to intimidate me, pick better props.
That knife can't hurt me unless...
Unless it has the fresh blood
of The One still on it.
(GHOSTLY WHlSPERS )
Well, then, of course,
it could cut through anything.
You wouldn't dare!
(TRlNA SCREAMlNG)
At least the day wasn't a total loss.
You might be content to toss souls
back and forth across the millennium,
but l'm not.
This has to end. We need to stop them.
What do you mean,
there's nothing you can do?
l didn't say...
Vita, will you please
stay out of my thoughts?
Sorry, but now that l've turned it on,
l can't figure out how to turn it off.
They're going to kill her.
l know. l'm sorry.
She really is.
She doesn't believe you.
She's going after Lindsey
with or without your help.
-EUGENlA: Vita.
-Vita.
Sorry.
Sarah, there's less than an hour
before initiation.
l don't care about initiation.
All l care about...
You'd better care.
Once you're initiated,
your powers reach their full strength.
Only then will you be able to draw
on the combined strength
of the sisterhood.
lt's your only hope of saving Lindsey.
Then bring on the white dresses.
All right, girls, let's get moving.
We don't have any time to waste.
Cover for me. l have to see Finn.
Finn? What are you gonna say to him?
lt's the only way l know he'll be safe.
l think he'll be okay with that explanation.
Oh, my God, Sarah,
do you have any idea how...
No, you seriously have to explain...
-Shut up. l don't have much time.
-For what?
Don't wanna be myself
Because l'm nobody
Just be careful, okay?
Hey, yeah, yeah
Don't wanna be myself
Because l'm nobody
l accept the gifts
that Mother Earth has bestowed on me.
ln doing so, l promise
to protect and defend her
as she protects and defends me.
l pledge my life to the eternal flame
and bow down before its powers.
l shall now call her disciples ''sister,''
and pledge to never betray
their trust or their faith.
l am what l am because of it,
and l willingly accept
and welcome my responsibilities.
l pledge myself to Alpha Nu Gamma
and embrace my sisters and their mission.
l swear on my life allegiance
to Pi Epsilon Delta...
l am an Alpha Nu from
this moment forth...
SARAH: From this moment forth, forever...
BOTH: Forever throughout eternity.
Throughout eternity.
Welcome.
-Welcome.
No. l don't wanna do this anymore.
(ESME SHUSHlNG)
Somebody help me!
(SHUSHlNG)
l don't want to be The One. Please.
l don't wanna be The One.
Please.
lt's time.
(SPEAKlNG lN LATlN)
Sarah!
(SOBBlNG)
(SPEAKlNG lN LATlN)
(GHOSTLY WHlSPERS )
LlNDSEY: Sarah! Sarah!
(RUMBLlNG)
The fire is life. The fire is strength.
Go.
-But the eternal flame...
-Will go out if you don't stop them.
Come on.
Come on! Come on!
Upstairs, quickly! Oh, God! Quickly!
The blood must be drained from The One
and fed to the eternal flame.
(WOMEN CHANTlNG)
(GRUNTlNG)
(SHOUTlNG)
GlRL: Help me!
Nobody picks on my sister
and gets away with it.
LlNDSEY: Sarah!
SARAH: l know. lt's okay. lt's okay.
You clearly don't know
who you're dealing with.
The fire's dying, and so are you.
The only person dying here tonight is you.
(SHRlLL WHlSTLlNG)
(CHORlNNE GRUNTlNG)
(GASPlNG)
l'm afraid that knife
won't do you any good,
unless, of course,
you have your own blood dripping from it.
Your friend was right.
Don't taunt the demon.
(CHORlNNE SCREAMS )
(GASPlNG)
But how?
l took her suggestion.
SARAH: Lindsey.
Lindsey!
Lindsey.
l told her. Sacrifices had to be made.
Rot in hell!
(SHRlEKlNG)
(GHOSTLY SCREAMS )
(CHORlNNE SCREAMlNG)
Will she be all right?
She's stronger than she looks.
She is The One, after all.
Sarah.
l won't be long.
-Where are you going?
-To find the rest of them.
EUGENlA: Sarah, it's over.
No, it's just the beginning.
(BELL RlNGlNG)
y eah
Well, you can bump and grind
And it's good for your mind
Well, you can
twist and shout
Let it all hang out
But you won't fool
The children
of the revolution
No, you won't fool
The children
of the revolution
No, no, no
Well, you can tear a plane
ln the fallin'rain
But you won't fool
The children
of the revolution
No, you won't fool
The children
of the revolution
No, no, no
y eah
No way
ESME,. That's the trouble with fire,
y ou never know
when it's gonna flare up again,
Wow