Miserable country, miserable people.
And we're in the worst of it.
The Belzan.
Chechen folk tales don't concern me,
only Chechen bullets.
But so many stories,
and they all have the same ending.
Anyone who enters
the forest never leaves.
What?
Special Ops Patrol Charlie, ETA?
- Answer the radio.
- Yes, sir.
Alpha Base, this is Charlie.
About 15 minutes.
Ten-four, Charlie.
Why'd you stop?
At the last village
there was a child missing.
We make ourselves
a target out here.
Radio control,
this is Major Korkov.
Investigating a bicycle.
Radio control?
- What's wrong with the radio?
- I have no idea.
Radio control?
Haunted.
Outside.
Secure the area. Report anything.
Damn. I know this is a trap.
Follow me.
Move out, huh?
Delta One in position.
Copy, Delta One, we're a go.
Tunnel.
Russo, gun.
Remember, clean sweep.
Computers, maps and weapons.
Thank you.
Looks like we found some decent intel
on that laptop.
Dude got a Dell.
I want you to know
you did real good down there.
Thanks, sir.
In basic at Fort Bragg
I saw some great soldiers.
Moved up to the Delta, you are seeing the
finest warriors that history can produce.
Come to the 'Raq, and you are
seeing the best within the best.
And within that final elite group,
they all tied for second place
because you, my friend,
are a step ahead.
I want you to know
you did real good down there.
But from a command standpoint,
we cannot use you.
You take risk.
Going in without your gun drawn. Stupid.
There's no need for a lone wolf who
pulls his unit into a hot situation.
You need to trust the man next to you,
exist within...
Exist within the command structure.
Yeah, I hear it every time.
Then write it down, Russo.
Write it on your eyelids.
You think it's boring hearing this,
it is boring saying it.
You point, I fetch.
That's my job, but...
That's all you want, fine.
Chopper's here. Let's move out.
Hi, Jim.
Thanks for coming
on such short notice.
Yes, sir.
- Have a seat.
- Thank you, sir.
I hate rescue operations.
To rescue somebody means
the machine broke down,
and I don't like the other
team calling my plays.
And, thanks to you,
we have their playbook.
Because of that,
Allied Command sent me a rainmaker.
WMDs, nuclear, biological, chemical.
Target the source, stop distribution.
Your Iraqi raid exposed a network that is
hell bent on acquiring these weapons.
Key money men, factory locations,
most of which were in Europe,
but there is one in our neighbourhood.
Four hundred miles to the north,
the Belzan Forest in southern Russia,
specifically the Chechen Republic.
The Belzan Forest is impenetrable,
not even the Russians will touch it.
Locals believe it is a mythical beast,
easily woken.
This is Katya Zemanova.
Counter-terrorism, psyops, tactics.
Dr Benton Walsh. He was one of ours.
Employed by the Army for medical research,
but when the President cut
stem cell funding, the Army let him go.
Now he's a fugitive.
What? Wait a minute, she's on...
She's on our side?
She's Agency.
I've been tracking the doctor for a
year through former Soviet states.
His science is weapons grade,
but he needs a sponsor.
On the hard drive you recovered
were references to a WMD doctor.
Coordinates are inside
the Belzan Forest.
The Chechen rebels are begging
to fund anyone
who can give them an ultimate weapon.
Drop a daisy cutter on that number
and problem solved.
We can't bomb Russian territory.
A Russian Spetsnaz team
has been sent into the area,
we need to extract the doctor
before they do.
His research is too valuable
in anyone's hands but our own.
You're gonna need good men
in great numbers.
Quiet and small.
Keep the winning percentage high.
One team, your Deltas.
Ms Zemanova will accompany
as an advisor.
Permission to speak candidly, sir?
It's denied,
but you are the commander
of this operation.
Bring this one home, Jim.
Bearcat One, Bearcat One.
Who is it?
Didn't get a clear look.
Could be Keating. Not 100% on that.
Yeah, that's Keating.
- Total FUBAR.
- Ten-four, sir, are we go with Plan B?
It's a go.
What? Whoa!
We got to put you
on a liquid diet, man.
Can't have you dropping bombs like...
Russo. Man, I'm sorry. My bad.
Downey, hey, Russo, stand down.
Russo, stand down.
Downey, stand down.
Nice shot.
Russo, go have that
checked with the medic.
Yes, sir.
I have noticed between missions
that activity in this camp resembles
a Thai shore leave.
Shore leave are for sailors, soldiers.
Downey, you know
how I feel about sailors in my army.
Yes, sir.
I'm gonna give you a bit of advice,
Mr Popularity,
you will never be a leader
rebuilding latrines,
so why don't you just pick
three of these sailors to help you.
Yes, sir.
Ten-hut.
Be seated.
Where's Downey?
- Work duty, sir.
- Again?
Yes, sir.
Who's the civilian?
Katya Zemanova, direct from Langley.
She'll be non-combatant.
Russo, combatant.
Our medic, Lieutenant O'Neal,
and my RTO.
Name's Candell, ma'am.
You can call me Can Do.
- Right.
- And my right hand, my LTC.
Pleasure to meet you, ma'am.
All right, the Belzan Forest.
Heavy cloud coverage
makes satellite imaging impossible.
Thermals found a hot spot.
This'll be our target.
Expect unpredictable weather changes.
Tomorrow, 0830,
fast-rope insertion into the LZ,
two clicks by foot to the forest.
Expect RPGs and heavy resistance.
When you step inside the Belzan,
know that you are entering a completely
unknown, hostile environment.
Dense foliage, open pockets,
a river, the rest is rumour.
It's bigger than New York City,
and more dangerous.
Our target is the doctor.
Straightforward extraction, keep him alive.
All other hostiles eliminated.
Outline transit will
be a stolen Russian Mi-8.
Extraction point will be
the southern tip down here.
This is a town that survived
the first Chechen war.
It was abandoned
mysteriously one year ago.
The Russians used it as
a staging area, so will we.
Sir? Who are we shooting at?
Chances are Chechen rebels
have set up camp.
They'll do anything
to protect the doctor,
but we've also got a Russian Spetsnaz
team in the same theatre,
so rules of engagement apply.
This is not a fantasy league or video game.
We will not run what-if scenarios
with Russia's elite.
Yeah, I'm talking to you, Russo.
Sir, you gotta admit, Delta Versus Spetsnaz,
that's a pretty cool video game.
Can it.
Anything you want to add?
Rebels normally
run in 10 man cadres,
but expect more spread out force
in the forest.
Count on them to fight, and keep fighting,
even after they've stopped breathing.
Look for pulled pins
and trip wires on bodies.
Your death is their glory.
And on that, dismissed.
Colonel, so we're clear, not only
am I bringing a weapon on this mission,
I'm also trained to use it.
I can take the
safety off and everything.
Understood.
And for the record,
I've never been to Langley.
And I'm not from any farm.
I trained in the field.
With all due disrespect,
did we run out of Americans?
Because if we did, I'm sure there's
a few British chicks that can do the job.
I was born in Russia,
but I am also an American citizen.
I'm well versed in constitutional law.
And on the Fourth of July,
I like to blow things up.
Is that Yankee Doodle Dandy
enough for you, Colonel?
- You think they have gone?
- Why would they stay?
You get the ammo, I will protect you.
- I have position. You go.
- You cannot shoot.
- I shoot the same as you. You run faster.
- That's because you are fat.
- I am not fat!
- You are fat!
You ate all your food already.
I will shoot you right here.
Okay, I'll go.
Why would they stay, right?
But next time, no shortcuts.
Dmitri?
- Yeah.
- Did you get him?
Yes, sir, double tap.
All right, well, here's your radio,
cowboy, fully juiced.
Thank you, sir.
Sir? I just want to tell you,
I'm glad you're on this op with us.
What is it? My aftershave?
No, sir, it's just that you're the
only one that Russo listens to.
Maybe Captain Russo's
gonna surprise some of you guys this trip.
No, I hope not.
Surprise is the best form of attack, sir.
Downey, you lost, boy?
Colonel's orders. Something about
teaching you girls how to hunt.
- You good to go?
- Yeah. Ready.
CIA, Russian, woman. Triple threat.
- Sounds more like three strikes to me.
- Don't fall for foreign girls, Downey.
They're human shields.
The good news is about having two girls
on a mission...
- What's that?
- Closer drop. Save my feet.
- Are all Deltas such pansies?
- Not all.
- Hey, is that thing loaded?
- Yeah.
You know, in the Marines,
payback's called friendly fire.
- Then I'm damn proud to be Delta.
- Yes, sir.
- Come on.
- Let's go, let's go, full capacity.
You still mad at me?
Tell you what, when we get back,
I'll bake you a bundt cake.
We're getting one of our own guys?
Was one of ours.
Better get him before anyone else does.
- Okay, nap time's over.
- Two minutes. Two!
Gear up.
Let's go, move out.
- Radio check.
- Loud and clear.
Roger, roger.
Martinez, any movement up ahead?
Nothing, Colonel.
Eyes open, everybody.
We're about ten clicks out...
You hear that?
What, sir?
Nothing.
No birds, no animals.
Not even insects.
- What the...
- Dead deer?
Deers don't wear uniforms.
Easy.
Man, that looks like...
Whatever it is, it looks like
it's been chewed up and spit out.
What we got here?
It's hard to say, sir. Whoever this was
got completely blown apart.
Dead three or four days.
Where's the blast damage?
The grenade fragments?
Kalashnikovs on the ground,
brand new AKs.
Sir, these boys panicked.
They were shooting in every direction.
Well trained in any terrain.
The units rotated constantly, the elite.
Chechens didn't do this.
Then what, then?
Bears? Stalin's ghost?
Let's move,
still got some ground to cover.
Heads up, eyes open.
- You don't mind, do you?
- You take the bullet.
Clear.
Russo, gun.
What have we got here?
Besides the stench,
probably a weapons testing facility.
Some of the doc's early work.
Check out this gear.
- Daddy likes to watch.
- Yeah, I can see that.
- Candell, check the radio.
- Yes, sir.
- Russian Army, new issue.
- Probably stolen.
- What have you got?
- Nothing, nothing but static.
Looks like troop movements.
Yeah, maybe,
but this coordinate is right there.
Clear.
Don't let your guard down.
I got this.
- So your boy's a birdwatcher?
- No feathers, no birds.
- Bats.
- Bats did this?
And I'll bet that's what fed
on the bodies we found.
- He was strapped in.
- What have you got?
- Another body and bats.
- Bats?
Did she say bats?
Man, I'm telling you,
bats don't eat meat. They don't.
- Move out.
- Candell, back me up on this, man.
Bugs and fruit as far as I know.
Shoot, there was a colony up there
at the school I went to in Austin.
Me and my girlfriend used to sit up there on
the Congress Avenue Bridge, drink beers,
watch them fly around all night.
Hell, she thought they were cute.
- He's right, they are cute.
- Hold that thing up to the tree.
- Flying chameleon?
- Meat-eating flying chameleon.
- Check this out. Blends in with the tree.
- I'll bet that's what got the Spetsnaz.
You don't really believe
those tales, do you?
If you make a joke of it,
you'll be cursed.
Don't be silly. You don't believe setting foot
into the forest would actually get us killed.
If we don't get through the forest before
it gets dark, then we'll be in danger.
No. We must go around.
Wait a minute.
I'll prove it to you.
If what you were saying was true,
I would be dead by now.
Enough with the silly
superstitious, let's go.
It must be the birds.
Why were you running?
- Downey, get up there.
- Yes, sir.
What's a beautiful woman like you
leading Deltas in a place like this?
Colonel wants you to hang back,
Russo has point.
Which do you think means more to me?
The men or the mission?
- Definitely not men.
- Good, then we can agree on one thing.
You're a means to an end.
You got this cute little
anger thing going. I like it.
- You have a problem, too?
- With what?
- With Russian women.
- With Russian women?
God, no. I hate the Agency.
I once read that Spartans,
the greatest warriors on the planet,
used to sing as they
marched into battle,
top of their lungs
to freak out their enemies.
- What army did you sign up for?
- I'm a student of warfare, man.
Singing relaxed them.
- Most of the battle takes place in your mind.
- Yeah?
I'll tell your folks at your funeral.
Russo, hold your fire. Russo!
You were lucky, don't be stupid. O'Neal!
Now let the doc take a look at you.
- Twelve degrees north.
- How many out there?
- At least two!
- Lay down cover fire.
I can cross that
distance in seven seconds.
Russo, damn it. Why don't you just
take control of your man?
Colonel, Downey and I will flank
the second shooter.
- Roger that.
- But, sir...
Russo, cover your eyelids
and read the message.
Go!
All right, Russo, one shot.
When you have it, take it.
Clear.
- This one's been fed on as well.
- Jeez.
Same Spetsnaz team.
I want answers.
Full disclosure.
Will it make you run any faster,
shoot any better?
Listen, lady, we just gave cause
for World War III. Who's out there?
- I don't know.
- Another bat victim?
He wouldn't have
lived the hour, Colonel.
Looks like we just
averted World War III.
Move out.
- How do you feel?
- I feel good.
I should probably stop
trying to picture her naked.
No doubt.
Chick will take you to hell and back.
You often travel the Belzan pass?
No more than is needed.
Been witness to any strange events?
- Like two farmers forced onto a truck?
- Even stranger.
Have you seen anyone in the woods?
- You know of us?
- We know nothing.
- We see nothing.
- You've seen me.
Answer truthfully.
Two days ago patrol went missing
along the pass.
- Tell me who did it.
- We know nothing. Please believe us.
- Why do you protect the rebels?
- We do not.
Nobody goes into the Belzan.
What goes on in there?
Our sheep go missing, then villagers.
You get too close, you go missing, too.
Unlikely.
Sound the call. The whole battalion
prepped and ready in one hour.
Russo, you copy?
Affirmative.
Where the hell are you?
Staring at a power line
half a click from the first sniper.
- Coming to you.
- Copy that.
Martinez!
No. Colonel.
Delta Force, welcome to the party.
Russo, what happened?
Soldier.
Ounce of C4 under a pressure plate,
or a tripwire.
Trees are marked like minefields.
Either way, Martinez is gone.
There's that sound again.
- What did you see out there?
- Nothing.
This is rebel territory, it's a trap.
Yeah, well, trap or not
that's our destination.
Hot spot coordinates
are in those trees.
All right, single file.
I got point.
Wait for my...
This is it.
Colonel.
Get down!
- Colonel!
- Move, move, move.
Go, go, go, go, move!
Go, go.
Don't look, go, go!
Rebels, but no bats, go this way.
I got O'Neal.
Tell those men to stand down,
but keep the Americans in sight.
Okay.
Candell, Candell.
You all get out of here,
I got this.
Fire in the hole!
Candell!
- No.
- No!
- What happened? Where'd they go?
- I don't know.
Wait a minute, wait a minute. I'm getting
something, I'm getting something.
Echo Two-Five, come in.
Echo Two-Five, say again.
- We lost Candell.
- Candell didn't make it.
Yankee Three-Four,
this is Echo Two-Six, over.
Yankee Three-Four, this is Echo Two-Six,
emergency situation, over.
Here, drink some water.
- Can't reach base camp without the radio.
- Candell is gone, radio's gone.
- Downey.
- Yankee Three-Four,
this is Echo Two-Six, over.
Work within the system,
bunch of crap.
Watch your back.
O'Neal won't make the base camp,
her wounds are too deep.
Well, we need to call in a medevac,
get her evaced immediately.
There's no time for that.
She's slowing us down already.
- Just what do you suggest?
- Make a tough decision.
I don't know what
they teach you at Langley,
but O'Neal's as tough as they come.
She'll make it until we say otherwise.
O'Neal's in bad shape.
Extraction's an hour after sunset,
but she needs an evac now.
We're not going anywhere.
Right now we're the experiment.
- Hey, what about O'Neal?
- What about Martinez?
You think I'll leave here
without popping the doctor?
Look, we've seen bats, Chechens.
Count on a strong Russian response
from the team they lost.
Russians find us, we're dead.
There's no room for revenge, man.
It's the system.
We're Delta, act like it.
You giving orders now?
After Martinez and the Colonel,
I am ranking officer.
That and $20 will get you a happy ending.
We're still getting the doctor.
We can't find them, sir.
What do we do?
How was life in America?
Your early years, the formative ones?
- I've never been to America.
- That's right, that's me.
And you never went to medical school,
did you?
No.
You were born about 30 miles
from these woods.
Trained to hunt and shoot
before you ever saw a television.
You couldn't tell a polypeptide
from haemoglobin.
Yet you think I'm better suited
to advise on military matters,
on search and destroy,
on the very thing you're paid to do.
They've slipped off the map.
We'll find them, sir.
Good.
I'd hate to have to
breed your replacement.
No way of telling how many are inside.
Let's move.
Katya, O'Neal, hold position here
and lay down supporting fire.
Take the two to the east. I'll clear
an extraction path on the west side.
- Who gets the doctor?
- Stay here.
You cover us.
Doctor Benton Walsh, you are now
property of the United States of America.
Let's move.
Where are they?
Come on. Get the move on.
You ready to move?
Okay, I got you.
As much R&D as I could find.
These rebels are loaded.
Guns, grenades, C4.
They got a WMD hardware store back there,
but none of the pieces fit.
Rocket casings, triggers, fuel cells.
Whole bunch of almost, but not quite.
They bought anything
they could get their hands on.
Yeah? How much were you?
The bats are coming back,
we need to get inside.
Get ready to move out.
Save it.
- I'm not going anywhere.
- Yes, you are.
I can't feel my legs.
I can't stand up.
- What part of that sounds like I can walk?
- You'll lean on me like before.
Do I have to spell it out for you?
I'm dead.
The clock ran out on me an hour ago.
I'll cover you.
When you get back just tell them...
Listen, lady, I go back without you
and Downey rolls a grenade in my tent,
and I'm sure as hell not staying here.
Now get on your feet and move.
Move.
All right.
Echo One-Five, do you copy?
Echo One-Five, come in.
What's causing the interference?
- The sequence is still running.
- Shut it down.
If you shut down the computer,
you lose control of the experiment.
- You take off the leash.
- Don't care, as long as it saves my team.
Suit yourself.
You killed my only friend.
That means you're gonna die.
Without me you won't get within a mile
of your rendezvous.
Hey!
- We don't have time for this.
- Then make time!
I'll get you out.
I can direct you away from the bats.
- Why should we believe anything you say?
- Because you and I want to live.
We lost O'Neal, man.
It's time to saddle up.
Take the intel.
He's coming with us.
- Are you crazy?
- This man is my prisoner.
You keep him alive,
zero chance of making it.
You think if he got free,
he wouldn't gut you in a second?
- I need my hands.
- Negative.
What happens to me happens to you.
Whoa.
There's just a few,
you're probably safe.
- Downey, transport carrier.
- Let's take it, move.
Katya.
Keys.
Freaking bats.
Colonel Korkov!
- Colonel Korkov...
- Read it to me.
Radar station detected an abrupt
change in radio interference
- around the Belzan Forest.
- Changed how?
It's gone.
They triangulated the origin.
Good luck, sir.
- What is it?
- Good news.
They're gone.
- Are you all right?
- Yeah, yeah, fine.
- What do you see? You see anything?
- Only trees.
And no bats.
I read your dossier.
Born in America,
schooled in America,
employed by America.
Sounds like a pretty good deal to me.
America makes very good killers.
And not even a thank you.
Tell me, Doc, what did we do to you?
What did America do to me?
Lied.
We say every man
has basic human rights.
No. You have the right to nothing.
The world belongs to the strong.
That's how it works,
that's the natural order.
Downey, Downey,
coming up on a fence.
Fence?
Keep going.
- Keep going.
- Roger that.
- You might want to buckle up.
- This truck is Russian,
they don't have any seatbelts.
Don't you move.
What the heck?
Why'd we stop?
Yeah, we have some sort of visual
out in the front blocking the truck.
- Roger, let's check it out.
- Copy.
This shouldn't have happened.
- What the hell's this?
- Another great moment in science.
- These are ours, our food supply.
- Dead less than 24 hours.
You did this.
You interrupted the sequence.
Face it, Doc. Your control is
slipping, or you never had it.
Cover, cover!
Let the doctor go!
What, Russians?
- Chechens. Patrol by the river.
- You lead us into an ambush.
- I thought Deltas were the best.
- Shut up.
- They're moving, trying to flank us.
- All right, we pull back.
Pull back.
Russo, the mission has priority.
My priority is killing the enemy,
whoever they might be at the moment.
Can't go left, can't go right.
Can't go back.
- We're being herded.
- Let's move.
Russo, let's move out on my six.
Do you know who I am?
I'm the one who find your hiding place
in Kiev.
The bomb you left
killed a good man.
I hope you were close, 'cause you're
going to see him very soon.
Downey, stop!
What?
Marked for a reason.
We're Delta, act like it.
Thanks.
Don't let them get away!
Russo, take point.
- Damn it.
- Right back to the cage.
He turned us around.
- It's Candell.
- No, no, hey! He's dead. Let it go.
- Where are the bats?
- They're here.
Listen, I have an idea.
Bats got this one.
Find the rest.
- Careful. Careful!
- Move in slowly.
That worked.
Past the trees, half a mile.
I don't know.
I think it's past the trees, a half mile.
- Delta Base, this is...
- How well do you know this woman?
- Come in.
- Better than you.
Watch her. She never lets the
briefcase out of her sight.
- Planting the seeds of doubt, huh?
- Delta Base, come in.
There's not a government in the world that
wouldn't kill us for what's in that case.
You hear anything?
Low level chatter.
Sometimes it's used to
mask a big operation.
Sometimes it's just
low level chatter.
Well, good news,
hour after sunset,
this is all in the rearview mirror.
Let's move out.
Russo.
Russo?
Go, go, go, go, go.
Downey.
Clear.
Sit him down.
- All clear.
- Okay, we hold here.
- I'm gonna set the beacon.
- Roger that.
Rescue Three-Five,
we have a beacon signal.
Roger, base, beacon clear.
Moving toward extraction.
Do spies get bonuses?
It's classified.
Maybe I'm in the wrong service.
This teamwork stuff sucks.
You're more the lone wolf type.
Drop me in Afghanistan before 9/11,
the world would be a different place.
So you depend on time travel.
It helps.
I like working alone.
It took 14 months, two dozen agents
and a Delta team to bring in Walsh.
He's a tough man to catch,
and not for lack of good intel.
In the end we got lucky.
You never work alone.
- Where's Downey?
- Setting the beacon. Marking the LZ.
- Relax.
- I'll relax when we land at base camp.
He has a history of escape.
Look. Head down, shoulders slumped.
That's a man
who knows he's been captured.
That's when he's the most dangerous.
- Russo, do you copy?
- Copy, over.
Clear here, coming back to you.
It appears you have
me at a disadvantage.
We've never met,
but you know all about me.
Then you should know that
I'm not coming back to America,
that better men have tried.
You know that these men will
die unless you release me.
The man you killed was a damn
fine agent and my mentor.
And one day in May,
he would have been my husband.
Goodbye, Doctor.
- Next time, be on time.
- Yes, sir.
Helicopters on the way, sir.
Thank you for your escort.
I leave you to your reunion with
the motherland, Agent Katya Zemanova.
It will be a short one.
- Where's the other Delta?
- I thought he was with you.
They're headed right for us!
Bank left! Bank left!
Downey!
I got him. I got him. Go!
I got you.
Hand the case over.
I don't think so.
Born and bred to crave all blood,
except mine.
A little DNA for my own safety.
You can stay and die,
or you can run.
Run for your life.
Since we're gonna
destroy the intel anyway,
two for one.
This is for Martinez.
This is tower
confirming beacon status.
Roger, tower, beacon unchanged.
Moving in towards extraction.
I guess he's not coming back.
- How bad is he?
- It's not looking good.
He's in and out of consciousness.
He needs a medevac right away.
Extraction team's already en route.
- It's the best I can do.
- By air?
Did you see what happened
to the last helicopter?
- What else you got? We got any more mags?
- No.
What are you thinking?
I'm gonna go back to the lab,
turn on the computer
and call the bats back.
Blow the place to kingdom come.
You're not serious.
If I don't, nobody goes home.
The Russians are coming.
If you're lucky, you'll go to prison.
- Most likely you'll be shot as a spy on sight.
- I told you teamwork sucks.
Don't wait for me, I'll find my way out.
That's an order.
Wait, this is suicide.
What makes you think you'll make it?
Bats bounce off me.
- Air power will take hit.
- I want troops on the ground now.
We missed the battle.
I will not miss the war.
Boom.
- Is this it?
- There's one more out there.
We gotta go. Russians are inbound.
They're coming right at us.
We need to get back
to the lab to get Russo.
Name!
Why is Delta here?
I know the U.S. is
bringing back the rebels
working with the doctor.
Dirty pig.
I don't think your
country will miss you.
So smart?
Take him away.
Armed Forces Television
has intercepted the broadcast
of a debriefing of Russian forces who
lead a raid on a terrorist stronghold.
- Here's Paul James with a special report.
- Russian troops located and destroyed
- a biological weapons laboratory...
- What a load of crap.
Hey, welcome back, soldier.
That's the problem
with secret missions.
The better you do them,
the less the world knows about it.
Did we?
The mission.
We did it, right?
Doctor's dead.
You're not.
Mission
accomplished.
Subtitles by LeapinLar