In the city, you're nothing...
... unless you're part of something
better than yourself.
I joined a gang
when I was 10 years old.
I loved being a gangster.
I loved my barrio.
Maybe that's why I became a cop.
With that power
came responsibility.
With responsibility
came opportunity.
And with opportunity
came corruption.
It was like the plague.
Everybody got sick.
Hold up, Salim. Chill out.
There's somebody coming.
There's nothing to see out here, sir.
Go back inside.
Salim, kick back, homey.
You want a bullet in your head too?
Oh, you don't fucking hear me?
I'm gonna shoot you in your face.
- In the motherfucking head.
- Salim, damn it. Salim!
- Undercover.
- Undercover!
I didn't give a fuck
about killing two gangsters.
That was our mission.
They were our quota.
Those were our orders.
I believed in what I did.
I believed in protecting the people
from the dirt on the streets.
I believed there was a difference
between us and them.
But man or animal...
... there are some lines
we should not cross...
... and my partner killed
an innocent man.
Still...
... I never thought I'd be a rat.
I love my partner like a brother.
And I love my unit
like my own family.
But after that night, I had changed.
I didn't have a choice.
My conscience
was taking care of that.
I know. I know it's a cliché.
- But they taste so good. Want one?
- Why you rolling up on me at my crib?
I think it's best
we talk in person, so hop in.
We need something else.
We need your partner
to corroborate your testimony.
- No, he ain't gonna roll.
- We need you to talk to him.
Look, I'll take a poly,
do whatever it takes.
Won't fly in court. You know that.
One more finger-pointing rat will.
Some finger-pointing...
...a little name-calling.
Should do the trick.
Some reason you don't
want him coming in?
He knows what you're doing...
...maybe he'll change his mind.
Today's the day.
Guys like me
are what we always were:
Expendable.
Elijah, did you clean
your room this morning?
- No.
- Go clean it.
- Okay.
- All right. Thank you.
Gotta go.
My son. Motherfucking superhero.
Catch any bad guys lately?
- Early tomorrow morning...
- What's this?
... we will take the children to the
forest and leave them there to die.
Turn that shit off. Baby.
- Yeah?
- His mama's coming to pick him up.
- That bitch?
- Daddy, don't go.
Hope she gonna be
on time this time.
Don't forget your lunch.
Fucking asshole.
Can I suck your dick,
Officer Sancho?
Go put your uniform on.
Come on, dog.
Why you think we gotta
bitch up to them IA fucks?
Fifty to life a good enough reason?
Not to wear them fag suits.
You really want me to wear that?
I ain't getting in that ride with
you looking like that, man.
I ain't doing it.
I'd take a bullet for you,
cuz, but this shit?
Punk-ass motherfucker.
You owe me, cuz. You heard me?
Excuse me, sir?
Oh, fuck.
Seeing ghosts again, homey?
A lot of ghosts in this fucking town.
Better check yourself today.
They'll Section Eight your ass.
What time they wanna
see you today?
- Six p.m.
- Yeah, me too.
I hope it don't take too long.
Gotta make me some money today.
Get me some rims
and a motherfucking Rolex.
Adel, your nametag's
on upside down...
...and you got a fucking
diamond in your ear.
I look good, though. Hear me?
So, cuz, one of them street ho's...
...hands over 40 quarters
to her pimp.
Pimp says, "Quarters, girl?
Which one of them niggas
paid you in quarters?"
Ho says, "Well, all of them,
they all done paid in quarters.
One at a time."
Just wanna make it through this day.
That's all I wanna do.
I just wanna stick my dick
in something.
You'd fuck a donkey
if you had the chance.
That's not very nice.
What's up, ladies?
You ever have a black and blue?
- You're a pig.
- Get out of here.
Go on, don't be mad.
We can make it, baby.
She just ran that light.
Crazy-ass bitch.
I should have
gave that bitch a ticket.
Nasty-ass trick-ass bitch.
What do we got here?
Oh, these motherfuckers are lost.
I'm sorry, we're lost.
You shouldn't be down here.
You don't belong here.
- Roll your window up.
- Directions?
Don't even think of helping them,
hear me?
Okay. Remember what I said,
it's a mistake.
- Just tell them...
- How can I help you, ma'am?
- What?
- I'm sorry?
- How can I help you?
- I'm having trouble with his accent.
- I'm sorry... No, Salim, come on.
- Looking for a restaurant.
- The address...
- Oh, shit, nigga.
- Sir, please exit the vehicle.
- Son of a bitch.
- What?
- Sir, please exit the vehicle.
Oh, you can't understand
my nigger accent either?
Get your punk ass
out the car, bitch.
Put your hands on the hood.
Hurry up, motherfucker.
I'm not fucking with you.
Face down.
Don't be eyeing me and shit.
What is this? You don't need that shit.
Stay still, motherfucker.
What the fuck is this?
What you got in there?
You don't need that shit.
Don't move till I say move.
- Yes, sir.
- Don't "yes, sir" me. Just stay still.
Look at this.
All the bells and whistles.
Put your hands on the ceiling.
What is that, seat warmers?
You got them too in there?
Come on, let me see.
Bet you like to take it
to the grocery store, huh?
Spread your leg.
Oh, shit, I know what this is.
I love the vehicle. You like it?
Can l...?
Do you like the motherfucking
$65,000 vehicle?
- Yes. Yes, I like it.
- All right, then. Get in it and drive off.
Hurry up, sir.
Ain't got all day in this motherfucker.
Go straight under the bridge,
there will be an on-ramp.
- Go ahead and hop on the freeway...
- Zero to 60 in eight seconds. Let's see.
Go ahead, I'm gonna
close my eyes. I'm not looking.
Adiós, amigo.
I hate white people.
Can we go now?
Hey, he was disrespecting you, cuz.
Liberal prick.
- They were Charlie. You know it.
- And you my motherfucking homey.
Got to soldier up, cuz.
Hey, look at this. Look at this.
It says "lawyer."
Look at all them.
Fifty names in there.
You know he was
into some dirty shit.
Craig Humphrey.
What kind of name is that for a nigga?
Humphrey.
Looking good, ladies.
- Check out these bitches.
- Sanchito, all in blue today?
- You know how we do it.
- This is mucho macho, cabrones.
- Going to the prom?
- lf you're my bitch.
- Hey, watch it.
- Don't touch me, nigga.
- Oh, it's on now?
- Always on.
Come on, none of this.
All right, let's get going.
- Good luck today.
- Thanks, dog. I appreciate that.
- After you.
- Thank you, baby.
Before we get going...
...Officer Wallace
has something to share.
Tell your fellow officers
about your experience.
Yes, sir.
I was approaching
a somewhat hostile crowd...
... surrounding a drive-by
shooting victim.
I noticed that the victim, some
gangbanger known as Little Angel...
... had his brains falling out.
Where were you guys?
What do we pay you for?
And the mother was trying
to put the brains back in.
But the more she tried...
...the more they kept falling out.
It was like spaghetti or something.
Then she said,
"No wonder people kill cops."
Nobody in here feels worse for her
than Officer Wallace. Is that right?
Yes, sir.
- That isn't why people kill cops, is it?
- No, sir.
Why do people kill cops, Wallace?
Sir, because they
see us as the enemy.
- Because they distrust us.
- No.
It's because those people...
...are not people at all.
What's the difference between
us and them, Wallace?
- I don't know.
- Think about it.
- Officer Sancho?
- Sir.
- What do we do here?
- Sir, we fight fire with fire.
There's a war out there
on the streets.
And the blood
on that poor mother's hands...
...is blood on all of our hands.
Now, you go out there today
and knock heads with the enemy.
Make sure...
...the letters P-O-L-l-C-E is branded
on the head of every gangbanger...
...like a cowboy's branding iron.
Remember, you are the elite.
The chosen few.
One felon a day
is all you need to do.
Dismissed.
Fellas?
That's a sweet little story
you told there, rookie.
- Shut up, nigga.
- You know?
- You serious?
- Don't push my baton, nigga.
Who the fuck you pushing, bitch?
You're a rookie.
Don't forget that shit, motherfucker.
- Why you messing with him, anyway?
- Trying to heat the young kids up.
Know what I mean?
Bye, Salim.
Lieutenant, give us a minute,
will you?
- Sure.
- Thanks.
So...
...today is the day.
I can't tell you how much faith
I have in you two.
- Thank you, sir.
- You know how these things go.
Somebody on the outside
thinks they can do our job better.
They get upset
because we play ball.
But as long as crime
keeps going down...
...all we gotta do is ride it out.
And ride it out
is what we're gonna do.
- You can count on us, sir.
- Good.
You okay, Armando?
A little nervous, sir.
Look, I know only the best intentions
were behind what happened that day.
Mistakes happen in the fog of war.
You're a good man.
The world is a bad place.
You do the best you can
in a bad place.
- Remember that.
- Yes, sir.
Last week...
...more third-strikers
were put away by us...
...than any other division in the city.
Be proud.
Walk tall.
I'll take care of you.
Don't worry.
Yes, sir.
A man said:
"Someday a real rain's gonna come
and wash all the scum off the street."
Only, it don't rain in the desert...
...so we gotta do all
the scum-washing ourselves.
Nigga better get a life vest.
- Little hair of the dog?
- I'm a drunk. I'm always thirsty.
- See you in a second.
- Cool.
Right.
- Yo, captain.
- Yeah.
So how are the kids?
Bury them under
the fucking freeway.
- What about the coke?
- Don't worry, you'll get yours.
Yeah, man, pleasure
doing business with you.
- What's happening?
- You know the drill. Come on.
Are we supposed to be
wearing a wire?
Bet this reminds you
of Valentine's Day...
...when your father would
make love to you.
- Quit your bitching, pussy.
- Fuck you.
You got a problem with it?
Talk to the man.
Come on.
What time are you guys meeting IA?
- 1800.
- What did the captain tell you?
He said to stay away from
corrupt motherfuckers like you.
Got your stories straight?
We in the loop. Don't worry about us.
We know what's happening, you know?
So, what do you got planned
for the rest of the day?
Same old, same old.
Got a little time for
a little ring-a-ding, then?
For sure.
I don't think so.
Do you know
the definition of opportunity?
No?
Opportunity: A favorable
juncture of circumstances.
Or, let's see,
another one would be...
...if you like, a good chance
for advancement of progress.
You understand that?
Opportunity:
Advancement of fucking progress.
Lieutenant?
Excuse me.
Yeah.
All right, good.
- Perfect.
- "I don't think so," motherfucker?
Embarrass me in front
of the lieutenant like that?
Hey, don't think for us.
What the fuck we doing here?
What we doing?
All right. Okay.
Try me.
Well...
...what do you think?
- We're in.
All right.
That's what I like to see, kid.
- Well, to good living.
- That's what I'm talking about.
Cheers.
Now, here's the deal.
There's a guy named Brax
who's been reaching out to us.
I know Brax. That's Damian Baine's
right-hand man.
Nigga owns
every nightclub in town.
Well, he's got some scam
that he's in a real hurry to get done.
- You guys cool with that?
- Cool.
I can set up a meeting between you
and him at this Mexican joint, all right?
Now, there's 13 keys...
...of the most pure shit
you ever seen...
...sitting downtown in Evidence
with your names written all over it.
We get these 13 keys to Baine...
...who's responsible
for getting it back?
Who the fuck do you think?
I almost forgot, shit.
I got you guys...
...courtside seats
to the playoffs tonight.
- What?
- So make it quick at IA, understand?
- You guys are gonna have fun.
- That's what's up.
You know what I mean?
You guys enjoy the game.
Nigga, I've never been
courtside to the playoffs before.
What? I ain't never even
been to the playoffs before, shit.
Why would that cheap motherfucker
give us free tickets to the playoffs?
I don't know.
But it says something that he's coming
to us and not that wetback.
Know what I mean?
Man, it's just a fucking game,
that's all it is.
Hey, don't stick your dick
in the gift horse's mouth.
All right? It means something.
You heard me?
Sir. Today's the day, my nigga.
We on the come up.
We coming up.
I don't like it, Salim.
Take a leg up when you get it, shit.
Why in the hell would anybody
give us a leg up?
- To show trust in us.
- Trust in us.
Hey, man, we get in with Baine,
we get rich. Hear me?
Pretty quick to get on that
Baine program.
Don't hate the player,
hate the game, cuz.
You know the deal.
You're Officer Sancho?
Do I look Mexican? It's my partner.
- Your badge is upside down.
- It's been one of them mornings.
- Hey, beautiful.
- Officer Sancho?
Yeah.
- Something wrong, officer?
- Yo, cuz, we in a hurry.
Yeah, well, I'm not.
So give me a minute while I call
the requesting judge, okay?
Sir? Sir.
Listen, we're late,
our job's on the line.
We really need to get going.
You wouldn't want another
dealer on the street...
...if we're fucking late, would you?
Motherfucking candy store.
Toxicology was here earlier...
...ran a test sample,
so no funny stuff.
No funny stuff.
You. Sign that.
Had more than a few pieces
of evidence disappear...
...after being checked out
by your division.
Zip that up. This gets back by 5.
- I'll take that.
- Follow procedure, officers, 5:00.
What the fuck
was that shit about back there?
- What?
- My name on the slip, that's what.
- What name you want?
- How about your own?
- Why mine, bitch?
- Well, it's your fucking gig, ain't it?
Oh, no, fuck that. We partners, man.
We in this together.
As always.
You got something to say? Say it.
Fuck it. Say it, motherfucker.
Yeah, I thought so.
Watch my back, cuz,
while I check this nigga.
Hey, what's up, bro?
Same old, same old.
Salim Adel.
You in here sorting through
the little table full of niggas?
What you looking for? You ain't come
in here to do the black man harm?
- Friendlies in blue, that's all.
- Oh, yeah?
Salim Adel
in a fucking faggot suit.
And your mother, how is she?
Not very well, not very well.
I am sorry.
You ain't the only one
sucking dick, selling rock.
- Shut the fuck up, nigga.
- What?
Hey, there ain't gonna
be no disrespect.
No disrespecting.
I ain't disrespecting you, cuz. We
played football together, remember?
Used to run with the same set.
Don't talk to me about no fucking
football, nigga. I'm a fucking OG.
I'm a ghetto superstar
and an international pimp.
I got fans all over
the fucking world, nigga.
True as a bullet in a pig's head.
Look, you need a busboy...
...to clean up all this fucking trash
in front of this place.
No, brother, everybody's got to eat.
If you say so.
Man, go into the car, nigga.
You, go to the car.
Yeah, I wanna talk
to this nigga by myself.
Everybody, get the fuck
out of here, matter of fact.
- See this shit?
- What the fuck is this?
That's one of them new joints too.
A Mark Xll or some shit.
Got all the bells and whistles.
High connectivity and shit.
So you get what you told?
- Thirteen.
- Let me see it.
No, cuz, not here.
Keeping it safe
until we know what we're doing.
You're a smart motherfucker, huh?
Hey, man, I'm in a big motherfucking
hurry, and I heard that you was too.
- So, what's the dealio?
- Tell you what the deal is.
You gonna be a rich fucker if you
shut your smart motherfucking mouth.
If you don't shut your
smart motherfucking mouth...
...l'm gonna walk out
on your punk ass.
All right, man. When and where?
Come to the club.
In the back. And bring the shit.
Today is the day, nigga.
You ain't gonna believe
this shit, cuz.
What? We're supposed to
go to Baine's crib...
...with the bricks in our hand?
Don't start getting
all paranoid on me.
We ain't giving them shit.
Staying in the car.
They said to bring the shit in.
Why we ain't gonna bring the shit in?
Baine got his drugs...
...lieutenant got his hands clean
for the murders.
There's no way we could
turn him in to IA...
...if we're both fucking dead.
What the fuck did you just say?
What the fuck you thinking
about saying to IA?
about telling IA, man?
- Nothing.
- You damn right, nothing.
Better check yourself for that shit.
What the fuck you looking
at me like that for?
What, nigga?
Why the fuck you be
disrespecting my friends?
They ain't your friends, nigga.
Leave the shit in the car.
Hey, hey, hey. Listen...
You gotta stop believing the hype.
Thinking that there's some
gang war out here and shit.
Well, there ain't. It's done.
Everybody's so rich off the narco,
they ain't mad-dogging anymore.
We the only gang that's left.
So wise up, nigga. Wise up.
You know, he invited us to Vegas.
Hear me? But he said,
"Don't come wearing your blues.
Because you ain't gonna get
your nut sack sucked that way."
We go see Baine,
the shit's staying in the car.
Let's not get jumped in, man.
This is our time now.
No.
The shit's staying in the car.
We hook up with Baine,
we're on top of the pile, man.
I wanna go to Vegas.
I wanna get my nut sack sucked.
I know you wanna get
your nut sack sucked.
How many nuts you think
a bitch can keep in her mouth?
Come on, man. Ho's got to eat too.
Don't look at me like that.
Ever seen me go off?
I only got but two.
Shit, not counting the one
in your asshole, that's three.
That's tres. How do you say that?
"Motherfuckos." You shit pesos.
That's all I'm talking about.
Vegas. Vegas, nigga.
The shit stays in the car. I don't give
a fuck how many nuts you get sucked.
I don't know how
to make it work. Keep that.
That shit ain't for niggas.
What's up?
You all dressed up, huh?
Are those real blue contacts?
Please, that real gold paint
on that bullshit-ass chain?
Don't fuck with Jesus.
Yeah, right.
Yo.
This is Brax. I'm out here with them.
We waiting for my man.
He got what we need.
We're good to go.
Armando Sancho.
For a long time I've heard
about the myth...
...today I meet the legend.
Mal Creado gang, right?
Back in the day.
Yep.
Yeah, some men talk the talk...
...but you walk the walk.
Salim Adel.
What am I seeing on the West Coast?
My motherfucking homey.
Thirteen keys of righteous dope.
Hey, girl.
Dancing is done.
If I was selling your pussy,
I'd be rich already.
Bad men carry python snakes, see?
Careful, she bites.
I bite too.
Go on, get out of here.
Yo.
Salim Adel.
You talk that loud again,
I'll assume you're an informer.
And informers get killed.
I have an opportunity for you.
There are some Canadian
Hell's Angels down at the beach.
They are sitting on hundreds and
thousands of dollars. Maybe more.
They think they're big time.
But crime is easy...
... when you don't fit the profile.
They bring the chronic down
from Canada, flip the shit into coke.
Buy all the dope in town...
... sending the prices sky-high.
I have a huge problem with that.
They're idiots.
They will buy coke
from anyone half-connected...
... and stupid enough to walk up
to the door and say, "Nantucket."
Nantucket.
They think this a vacation...
... but you don't ruin my business
on a vacation.
And a nigga's never on vacation...
... trust me when I tell you, because
a nigga always fits the profile.
Yeah.
Do you know what a "jux" is?
- Police.
- Don't move.
- Put them up.
- Make me do it.
Yeah, that's right. Thirteen keys.
So we use the drugs to get the money
and keep both?
- Sounds pretty easy.
- lf it's so easy...
...why don't you just do it yourself?
I don't want any problems
with the Hell's Angels.
But if you make it look like a bust,
real pig action, cherry top popping...
...then we're all happy.
And the whole community is happy.
- Rodriguez and Sayed?
- No.
The lieutenant told me you guys
were the best for the job.
This has to happen right now.
These guys are leaving
for Vancouver tonight.
This has to happen right now.
Lieutenant made the call already.
They said they coming over
in about an hour.
What we getting paid?
We split the loot three ways.
Me, you...
...and me again.
Sound fair?
Hey, hey, hey. Relax, man, relax.
We got the fucking job, cuz.
We got the job.
What did I say?
- What did I fucking say?
- You said, "What did I say." Hey.
You said,
"Leave the shit in the car."
But you was wrong, man.
They didn't fucking jack us...
...they hired us.
We're gonna go back to the lieutenant
and tell him, "No fucking way."
We're gonna go to our IA meeting,
and then we're gonna go home.
And we're gonna survive.
You're scared.
I've never seen you scared before.
Yeah, maybe you should be too.
You don't think I know what's up?
All I know is they wanna get rich...
...I wanna get rich,
and I know you wanna get rich.
I'll tell you what you get.
You get got as soon as you
walk in that door.
If they wanted to kill us,
they'd have done it already.
They'd have done it
at the motherfucking taco stand.
Man, you gotta chill
with the mind-fuck, cuz.
Your punk ass can't handle
the motherfucking pressure.
Now, get this
motherfucking gun off me.
What the fuck is wrong with you?
I mean, listen to me, man.
I'm talking hundreds of thousands.
Maybe even more.
I know you can use
some real money...
...instead of dealing with all this
little fucking weaselly shit.
What, you think I'm a dumb nigga
just because I wanna buy shit?
Doesn't matter
what you spend it on.
We both want it.
Shit, we both need it.
Fuck it.
We ain't got nothing
better else to do.
What we got, huh?
Not a motherfucking thing.
Man, we do this one gig,
this one motherfucking hit...
...nigga, we set for life,
you heard me?
I ain't gonna shoot anybody.
We go in there clean...
...we take the money
and we walk the fuck out.
Hey, I ain't looking
for no battle neither.
So from here on out,
what I say goes.
- You got it?
- Yes, sir, master.
Shit.
You say that shit,
or I'll walk out this fucking door.
What you say go.
What you say go, motherfucker.
My nigga.
- Maybe today's the day after all.
- Good.
Let's go punk down
the motherfucker.
Thanks for coming, captain.
We appreciate your time.
Whatever I can do to help.
- Ready, gentlemen?
- Ready.
You testified that the two young men
killed by your officers...
...were both gang members?
- Yes.
The older man your officers shot
outside the bar...
...you said he was intoxicated
and confrontational?
He reached into his pocket
for what they thought was a gun.
The safety of my men is
my first priority.
I thought it was
to serve and protect.
- My men are soldiers.
- Soldiers kill people, captain.
Cops help people.
Until Officers Sancho and Adel
were hired by me...
...the only light they saw was
the flash from a gun.
If you politicize this event
and ruin their lives...
The only lives we're
concerned with...
...are the families of the men
who lost their lives that night.
That's why you'll never understand
what it means to be a cop.
They said Bay Street.
Why we at the beach?
Fucking dirty-ass hippies
freak me out, man.
Looking for somebody
stupid enough...
...to walk up to a door with a bag
and say, "Nantucket."
Thought that was gonna be me.
If this is a fucking set-up,
we're not getting shot in the head.
We're gonna go in
and make this jack move happen.
Who's a ruthless-ass motherfucker?
I like it.
Okay, you ready?
Okay.
Now, see? Yeah.
That could be good.
Good. Yeah, I'm good.
- You look good. Might take me out.
- See?
Dude, dude, what are you loo...?
Man, what are you looking at, dude?
Honest. Come on, man.
Look. Look, it's right here.
- See something you like, it's right here.
- Fuck you. You can't just pimp me out.
Well, get it cracking, man.
What? You don't like what you see
or something?
I won't kiss you
in front of your boyfriend.
- He's not my boyfriend, okay?
- Excuse me.
Shit, I can kiss
whoever the fuck I want.
And maybe I wanna kiss you.
Oh, is that right?
- Hey, police.
- Shit.
Shit.
Hey, don't run. Don't run.
Don't run, you motherfuckers.
I said, stop, you bitch.
- Come here. Come here.
- Don't make it hard on yourself.
Put me down.
What, you forgot the rules now?
You're not supposed
to fuck with the Man.
Shut it.
What happens when you run?
- What's the rule? You get a beatdown.
- That's right.
You trying to get a beatdown?
Why you running, anyway?
What, you got something to hide?
We run because you two
motherfuckers is too violent.
We run because you shoot me,
then put a gun in my hand.
Shut up. Did I ask you?
Hey, leave him the fuck alone, man.
I just caught something now.
What we got here, lovebirds?
- Nice friends you got there.
- Yeah, well...
...at least we ain't
a bunch of pigs, right?
Who the fuck you spitting at,
motherfucker?
Who the fuck you spitting at?
- Salim.
- Crazy little bitch.
Stay the fuck still.
Salim, let her go. Come on, let's go.
Fucking spit on me.
Hey,
I'm guessing white cotton panties.
I bet you I can get you wet
in front of your boyfriend.
I bet you she's a cue ball.
- Nice and tasty too.
- Come on, Salim, let's get out of here.
Nigga, hold up. Hold up.
I just wanna make sure she ain't
hiding nothing underneath here.
- Don't worry, Rita, he can't touch you.
- Rita?
Is that your name, huh?
Is that your name?
All right. Well, Rita, just think of this
as a visit to the gynecologist.
What did I say?
Score one for the niggas in blue, huh?
White cotton undies.
Yeah, man. Oh, wait, wait, wait.
Hold up. Wait a minute, wait a minute.
I forgot. Are you cue-balled or not?
- Let's see up here.
- No. No, please.
Yep. Her stinky's bare.
You done?
We done.
Go on, get your shit
and get the fuck out of here, girl.
Bye, baby.
Hey.
I'm going to kill you.
Because I am a cop killer.
English, motherfucker.
Let's cut to the chase, captain.
Do you know if any of your officers,
Sancho and Adel included...
...were involved in criminal activity?
No. Absolutely not.
Okay.
Violence is a language that
people understand.
And sometimes,
when it's necessary...
"When it's necessary."
Oh, it sounds beautiful.
These convictions you hold...
...are far more dangerous
to the truth than to lies.
You're knee-deep in a pile of shit.
We're all knee-deep in a pile of shit.
And it doesn't matter how high up
you think you are.
It doesn't matter
if you can smell it yet.
It's the same pile of shit
we're all sinking in.
Don't let morality make you stupid.
Splooge?
What kind of name is that
for a nigga?
That's the sound my dick makes
when it's slipping into your girlfriend.
You know, maybe you should
lay off the shit a little, officer.
Maybe you could get it up
and not have to threaten little girls.
- What did you just say to me?
- You heard me, coke dick.
You believe this guy?
Man, this is a violation
of informants' rights.
Plus, you guys didn't even pay me
last time.
This nigga rat on his own peeps
and he wants us to be fair.
My peeps?
Baby gangsters ain't got
no morals nowadays, cuz.
Oh, okay, so just because I'm black,
I'm a gangster?
You stupid,
ignorant, racist motherfucker.
I ain't no gangster. You a gangster.
Shut him up.
You feel better about yourself
with that badge on?
It's a fucking piece of plastic, yo.
- Little name-calling should do the trick.
- Man, shut him the fuck up.
A rat is what you are.
Lowest piece of shit
on the face of the earth.
Won't fly in court. You know that.
You heard me?
Why'd you get this motherfucker?
You couldn't have picked
another nigga?
You picked
this stupid motherfucker.
A parasite is what you are,
motherfucker.
Rat on your own fucking people.
This motherfucker ratted on
all you motherfuckers.
This little punk-ass nigga here.
Splooge.
I ain't calling you Splooge no more.
I'm gonna call you "dick juice."
Fucking pay me.
Hey, shut him the fuck up.
See, you done fucked up, right?
You know that, right?
Just to let you know,
Rita's gonna kill you.
Rita.
- Oh, yeah, Rita.
- Fuck you.
You don't know what
you're talking about.
Oh, shit, what the...?
Now what?
We watch, wait and look for anything
that doesn't look normal.
Hey, cuz, I think I see something.
Motherfucking duct tape
good for everything, yo.
Anybody here strapped?
I need a piece.
You're up, nigga.
Come on. Come on.
Fuck that lumpy-head-ass nigga.
Big egghead-looking, crackhead,
Michael Jackson-looking fucker.
- That's one ugly nigga right there.
- Oh, shit.
As soon as you inside,
you see the money...
...and they know
you won't jack them...
...that's when we come in like
Scud missiles, dropping them down.
And all you gotta do
is drop the drugs...
...jump down
and crawl your black ass outside.
And what do I get?
- They jacking that nigga up.
- They roughing that nigga.
You don't get beat no more.
That hurt? Sorry.
At least give me a gun.
I gotta pack some heat.
Give me that thing.
Give me a ray gun.
Keep it moving.
This is for police.
- Oh, shit.
- Deep-fry that nigga.
Yo, I wish we had a camera.
This when you need a camera.
You didn't hear him?
Gimpy, didn't you hear the man?
Keep on moving.
Look at the white boy pull up.
They not gonna fuck
with that white boy.
- I'll bet you $ 100.
- You out your mind.
- They about to beat his ass down.
- Put your money up.
Give me that.
You turn your back
and you think it's all right?
You guys real police?
Are we real police?
What's it say on the back
of his jacket?
"Are we real police?"
What's that supposed to mean?
Is this a real stun gun?
- I told you. I told you, nigga.
- Oh, shit.
They stunned that nigga.
Deep-fried that motherfucker's brain.
Told you. Give me
my motherfucking money.
There you go.
Grab your shit.
You look nice and dumb.
They'll give you whatever you need.
Go ahead, motherfucker.
Hurry up.
He looks like he's 12 years old.
Little bitch-ass nigga.
Look like he going to the crib too.
Yeah, he is going in the crib.
What the fuck you want?
Nantucket.
What, Daddy picked you up
from kindergarten?
He gave me some candy,
threw me in the back of a van...
...and told me to touch his wee-wee.
God, a young nigga can't be
an entrepreneur? Shit.
This shit is taking all fucking day,
man.
Doing what we need to be
doing, nigga. Don't sweat it.
So, now, what's in the bag?
Weigh this shit.
You weigh it.
Hey. Dickhead, you weigh it.
- You weigh it, eh.
- No, you weigh it, dickhead.
- No, you weigh it, eh.
- Shut up and weigh it.
You got crabs, eh.
I got runner-ups, okay?
Someone do the shit, I'm gonna play.
I got runner-up on your mom, eh.
Right there, eh.
- Oh, yeah? I got...
- Hey. Fucking shut the fuck up.
I said, weigh the shit.
I'm not fucking babysitting.
Sorry.
I didn't tell you to fucking
close the bag.
Open the fucking bag, all right?
I gotta test the mess.
- That okay with you, Mr. Entrepreneur?
- Whatever.
Freeze, motherfucker! Police!
Put them where I can see them.
Get on the motherfucking ground.
Drop it!
- Stay down, bitch.
- Turn the fuck around.
Don't fucking move.
Shut the fuck up.
Son of a bitch.
What are you doing here?
Armando, you look like shit, eh.
They fucked you good.
Sent you to kill your own family.
But you are family until you die.
Now you see.
Hey, man, English, motherfucker.
Hey, you ain't no real fucking cop.
- Fucking puto motherfucker.
- You know what?
I'm tired of fuckers
calling us fake cops.
- What's up, then, bitch?
- No, back the fuck up.
- I'll pop you in your face.
- Back the fuck up.
All right, then. All right.
I'm unarmed.
No gun. Nada, eh.
So let's make a deal, all right?
Oh, now this motherfucker
wanna make a deal.
- I don't mind paying a little tax to...
- Put your head down.
But you know you're crazy
if you take this money.
Well, you're going to have
to answer to Roland.
The state of California thanks y'all
for your patronage.
Come visit the Golden State anytime,
you heard me?
- Salim.
- Motherfuckers paid in this bitch.
Salim.
Where the fuck did Splooge go?
Oh, shit.
I'm shot.
What the fuck? Niggas is shooting
in there. We gotta go.
Get up. Get up. Come on.
You with me?
Get up, they're coming.
Come on.
Salim!
Keep your fucking head down.
Keep it down.
What's with the blood over here, man?
What's going on?
What you got to say for yourself?
Where's the shit at?
The black dude took the dope,
and the Mexican dude took the money.
Get the fuck up.
What the fuck you doing?
This ain't no fucking game. Get up.
The bullet went straight through,
man.
- That's good.
- I just gotta stop the bleeding.
Duct tape good for everything,
right?
Oh, man, what the fuck did
I do to you?
What the fuck did I do to you?
The fucking money's gone,
the fucking dope's gone.
I'm fucking shot, man.
Fucked up. I fucked it up big.
- It was all my fault.
- Don't worry about it, carnal.
You're home. I got your back, ése.
You know who the fuck that was
back there?
That was my family.
My first fucking family.
Finger-fuck those bitch, cuz.
We gotta get to a safe house.
I need a doctor. I'm in fucking pain.
- I need a fucking doctor here.
- Duct-tape that shit.
- I'll kick the back of your fucking head.
- Where is this piece of shit?
He ain't skateboarding down the
boardwalk with 13 kilos, motherfucker.
Motherfucker, you crazy?
What the fuck?
Where the fuck you going?
Oh, this is some fucked-up shit.
Salim!
Get out of here.
Now, motherfucker.
Stay right there. Stay right there.
Little nigga.
What the fuck you looking at?
You were supposed to feed them,
make them fat, and kill them.
Yeah, it wasn't my fault.
You're right.
It wasn't your fault.
Love for you still, my brother.
I want them all dead.
Go on!
- Stupid fucking niggas.
- All right.
Call your fucking boys
and make sure they clean it up.
I've sent troops over
to Salim's house.
I'm gonna make a personal visit
to Sancho's and see what I can do.
- All right?
- What did you say to Internal Affairs?
Did you honestly think
that I was gonna take the fall?
I'm just looking out
for number one, captain.
And you are on a short leash.
So you better keep me close.
They're always watching.
Oh, fuck.
Fuck.
You were right, man.
Baine set us up.
What are we supposed to do, man?
Oh, fuck.
What, you deaf and mute now, nigga?
Say something.
What the fuck we supposed to do,
cuz?
You don't know?
I just asked you what the fuck
we supposed to do.
You tell me, homey.
Oh, you crazy now?
What, am I talking to
my motherfucking self?
Why were you so anxious
to do this today?
Why were you so anxious?
Why's my name
on that goddamn slip?
Nigga, have you lost
your motherfucking mind?
Hell of a lot easier to come up
with me out of the way, isn't it?
You don't know
what I'm talking about.
You're my partner, man.
You're my best friend.
That's on everything.
That's for life.
You heard me?
You heard me, cuz?
That's for life.
Oh, fuck, fuck, fuck.
My nigga.
Oh, shit.
What else am I supposed to do,
you know what I mean? Shit.
I ain't got nowhere else
to motherfucking go.
My homey.
Fuck.
What's really going on, cuz?
I had to do something today.
What did you do?
That's the motherfucking doctor.
- You called it in?
- Yeah.
When you was chasing Splooge.
Shut the fuck up.
Don't say nothing.
Salim!
Easy, motherfucker.
Drop the piece, turn the fuck around.
Drop the fucking piece.
No, we're a long way
from fucking brothers.
Turn the fuck around
and drop your fucking piece.
- Drop it.
- We're on the same side, man.
What side is that?
- You looking for me, motherfucker?
- Fuck.
Now you drop your shit, bitch.
Take this motherfucker's gun, cuz.
That's right, bitch. You like that?
Get your ass in there, motherfucker.
You got that nigga, cuz.
Your partner's on the floor
bleeding like a stuck pig...
...and you think this is funny?
You better start talking, motherfucker.
Who sent y'all to fuck us up?
Man, they knew you were gonna rat.
What the fuck do you think?
They thought I was gonna rat?
Who the fuck is "they"?
Think this is a joke?
I ought to put this motherfucker
in your eye and blow your head off.
- Say something, motherfucker.
- We can still get out of this, man.
Who set us up, motherfucker?
Lieutenant, man,
who the fuck you think?
Lieutenant sent us here,
lieutenant sent you to Baine.
- Damn it.
- Well, what the fuck the drugs for?
Payment for your murder.
Only Baine fucked up.
He was supposed to take you out,
make it look like a gang hit.
- You lying, I'll put one through your...
- I'm not fucking lying.
- How'd he know we'd take the job?
- You heard him.
How'd he know
we were gonna take the job?
Because, you stupid fuck...
...everybody knows you're a wannabe
who can't stand on his own feet.
Word?
Yeah, word.
- You swear to God?
- I swear to God.
You raise your hand and swear?
Your other hand, motherfucker.
Yeah, bitch. I swear to...
- That's what's up.
- That's my fucking hand.
You fuck. God.
Let him live.
We can still do some good.
I will fucking kill you.
Don't run.
We done good here.
Hey, hey. Hey.
Fuck that shit, cuz.
And you know I'm driving.
Shit. It's on.
You got your watch,
you got your rims.
- How does it feel?
- It feels good, motherfucker.
What the fuck do you want me to say,
I'm sorry?
All right, maybe you're right.
Maybe we go to IA, come clean.
- Fuck it.
- Now you wanna come clean.
Who we gonna say killed
Rodriguez and Sayed, huh?
- Gangbangers.
- Gangbangers?
- Word up.
- They're gonna believe...
...a beaner and a nigger that just stole
13 keys and killed two cops?
All they care about is the lieutenant.
About the robberies, the dealings
and the drugs and shit.
We go together.
Tell them everything.
Let me ask you something, cuz.
How the fuck could they think
we'd rat?
As fucked up as I am, I could teach
you a thing or two about loyalty.
Fucking city.
I never could make sense of it.
I know what I gotta do.
I don't expect you to come with.
What you say go, remember?
It's been a long time, my brother.
I was loyal, carnal.
Loyal to who, is the question.
None of that pinche mierda
would have happened...
...if you'd told me you was
protecting H.A. now.
I'm a businessman.
And when it comes to green,
I'm fucking color-blind.
And I don't need your
fucking permission or approval...
...on how I conduct
my business, officer.
Sorry.
Where is my money?
I don't know.
I swear on my Evita's life,
I don't fucking know.
We'll see.
Your shoeshine boy,
he knows where the money is?
Have you ever seen what
someone looks like with no skin?
You see what a man is.
I mean, really is. Flesh and blood.
It's very interesting.
I enjoy it quite a lot.
And I never skinned a nigger before.
You have one choice.
You tell me where the money is,
or you have a bullet in your head.
One pull of the trigger for yourself...
...or, as I assume you will
choose to do...
...two pulls of the trigger
for your partner.
I am curious to know
where your true loyalty lies.
Cuz, tell this nigga what happened.
Tell him we got jacked and don't know
where the money is. Tell him, cuz.
Who wants to go first?
Fine, I choose.
It doesn't have to be this way.
Just tell me where the money is.
One to yourself, or two to him.
Shoot that bitch.
Shoot that white bitch.
- Shoot him.
- Pull the fucking trigger, ése.
Do it, ése.
Salim!
You want a bullet in your head too?
You don't hear me, motherfucker?
I'm gonna shoot you in your face.
Salim!
I'm just bullshitting.
- Oh, shit.
- Hey.
Oh, shit. Hey, hey, hey.
Redemption is remembrance.
I killed an innocent man.
That's some gangster shit right there,
homey.
It shows integrity, yeah. Bravery.
Pero redemption does not come
so easy.
Do it, pig.
Do it.
- Grab it, puto.
- Grab it.
Fuck. Fuck.
All right.
I know... I know where the money is.
I know where the money is.
Stashed it in a motherfucking alley.
That the kind of family
you were looking for?
who would die for you?
Hey, let us go, man, now.
I'll take you to the dough.
One pull of the trigger for yourself,
or two for him.
That's not the deal, cuz.
- You got one more shot, puto.
- Shut the fuck up. The game is over.
You kill me, you don't get the dough.
That's what's up.
Look at him.
Look at him!
Hey, motherfucker...
...I want you to look at him.
Look at him.
You take a good fucking look at him.
It's never over.
There's only one kind of wisdom...
... and that's hindsight.
Everything happens in bits...
... and you don't wake up
until afterwards.
Until it's too late.
What's it smell like?
Take him to get the money.
In that final moment...
... you wait for something,
anything, to take you away.
And what returns,
what finally comes home to you...
... is your own fucking self.
Nothing can save you from that.
Police officer. I need help.
Help.
I need help!
You can't change
the color of your skin.
the color of your heart.
You can change
the colors you wear...
... but deep down inside,
you'll always be...
... the same salvationless
motherfucker you always were.
No idea. No.
Hey, where the fuck you been?
Jesus.
Got the chem-lab report.
Fake shit. Cut with
some heavy-duty rat poison.
Fucking payback.
Bye, bitch.
It's never easy grieving
over the death of a partner.
Even if he went crazy
and tried to kill you.
The pressure of knowing he did wrong
that day must have gotten to him.
You had no choice,
it was self-defense.
After he killed Rodriguez and Sayed
single-handedly.
We're even more sorry
about your girlfriend.
I'm sorry he made it personal.
Our deepest sympathies.
But my son Elijah's okay, right?
So according to your report,
after roll call...
...you went on your rounds.
Sancho turned on you, went ballistic.
You went in pursuit.
You told Officer Sancho
that you were gonna come clean...
...and let IA know that he was
responsible for the shooting.
You understand that?
Good.
You showed yourself to be
a real hero today.
You should be proud.
Oh, I called Internal Affairs.
Let them know you'd be a little late.
I'm sorry it got so messy, Salim.
Listen, you're gonna be at IA
for a little while.
You still have
those courtside seats?
Nobody talks about the day
of their death like, "Today is the day."
But today was the day.
You see things a lot more clearly
when you're dead.