Scooby-Doo, where are you?
It's Mr. Beeman, the reaI estate agent.
Mr. Beeman?
Yeah, he was printing miIIions
of counterfeit doIIars in the basement...
...with his printing press.
What we originaIIy thought was moId
was reaIIy green ink.
See?
I wouId've gotten away with it, too...
...if it wasn't for that big dog
and you meddIing kids!
And that's how we soIved
''The Case of the Moat Monster''...
...one of our most frightening mysteries.
Stories Iike that aIways give me
the heebie-jeebies.
No wonder you became a reporter.
That Moat Monster aImost sIiced you up
Iike a pepperoni pizza.
And then we wouIdn't have
Coast to Coast with Daphne Blake...
...your very successfuI syndicated series
on Americana.
Going on its second season, I might add.
I never miss it.
Thanks, Chris. You know, the reaI reason
I changed jobs was because...
...the monsters and ghosts aIways
turned out to be bad guys in a mask.
Got a IittIe boring?
No kidding. In fact, that's why the gang
went their separate ways...
...except for Fred and me.
She means Fred Jones, who's now
the producer and one-man crew...
...of Daphne's show.
How about getting a shot of Freddy, guys?
Is he cute or what?
So what's coming up for the new season?
A new series of segments caIIed
Haunted America.
Sort of a
Ghost to Ghost with Daphne Blake?
Right, but this time I intend
to find some reaI haunted houses...
...for my viewers.
It's too bad the rest of the oId gang
won't be aIong for the ride.
Yeah, I reaIIy miss them.
Yeah, we reaIIy miss you, too, Daphne.
Yeah!
Don't go away,
we'll be right back with Daphne Blake.
Hey, you two! Get back to work!
We're right on it, Boss-man, sir!
Got something, Scoob?
No offense, oId buddy, but I think
your nose might be Iosing its touch.
Pretty sneaky,
but they can't fooI your nose.
That's right!
No one brings contraband food
into our country with us on the job!
Let's go check it in, Scoob!
Is this the jackpot of jobs or what?
Yes, we do carry the Hair Raisers series.
Number 23, The Vampire Village? Got it.
Number 24,
The Creepy Clown Town? Got it.
Number 25,
Menace At Mummy Manor? Got it.
Yes, I'II hoId them tiII Tuesday.
Two weeks from Tuesday?
Yeah, that's fine.
'Bye.
SoIving mysteries was a Iot more fun
than seIIing them.
Mystery Ink Bookshop.
Freddy?
Jinkies! Sounds great. Count me in.
Hi, Boss.
You ate aII the contraband!
Excuse me!
Untrue, Boss. We didn't eat it aII.
There's stiII a coupIe of GorgonzoIas Ieft!
HeIp yourseIf!
You're a coupIe of GorgonzoIas.
You're fired!
What a grouch!
Looks Iike we're unempIoyed again, oId paI.
Yeah! UnempIoyed!
Take it easy, buddy.
Something wiII turn up.
So what if this was the greatest gig ever!
So what if we starve.
Turn to skin and bones.
HeIIo. Freddy?
We just caught you on the tube!
Busy? Nah. Scoob and I were
just thinking of taking some time off!
Yeah! Yeah!
Sorry I'm Iate, Daph.
The traffic was murder.
Is this everything?
-Got the maps?
-Yeah.
Are you sure
you haven't forgotten anything!
Fred, what is with you?
Yes, I'm sure I'm sure.
WeII, then....
Surprise! Happy Birthday, Daphne!
Gosh, it's great to see you aII!
I've been working so hard...
...I guess I forgot my own birthday!
I hope you don't mind....
I asked the gang to come aIong.
This is the best birthday present ever.
It'II be just Iike oId times.
Yeah! OId times!
Easy, boy. It's great to see you, too.
Speaking of oId times,
Iook what I have for you, Scooby.
Scooby Snax!
Oh, boy!
Go Iong, guys!
I've been saving these Scooby Snax
for a Iong time.
Too Iong, VeIma! They're staIe.
Don't worry, guys. We're going
to New OrIeans for our first segment:
Haunts of Louisiana.
New OrIeans has
some of the best food in the worId.
And the best ghosts.
I hope. WeII, Iet's get going.
HoId it. There's just one more thing.
Groovy!
Perfect! Mystery Inc. is back in business.
Bad guys in masks, mechanicaI cIaws...
...magnets, hoIogram projectors.
Just Iike the good oId days.
Too much Iike the good oId days.
I've got a show to do.
I need a reaI Iive ghost.
That's an oxymoron.
Doesn't anybody want a beignet?
What I want is a house
that's reaIIy haunted.
I mean there must be one
somewhere in Louisiana.
There is. l work in it.
Sorry, I couIdn't heIp but overhear.
I work as a chef in a house
on Moonscar IsIand...
...a house that reaIIy is haunted.
Jinkies!
My name is Lena. Lena Dupree.
Fred Jones. This is VeIma DinkIey
and Daphne BIake.
Charmed.
Moonscar IsIand? Where is that?
It's in a bayou not far from here.
A pirate named Morgan Moonscar
died on the isIand.
And his spirit stiII haunts the pIace.
No offense, Lena, but it's probabIy
just some guy in an oId pirate suit...
...trying to scare off the IocaI kids.
The ghost is reaI.
Of course, if you're too scared to go--
Scared? Me? No, I don't think so.
If you want to check it out,
you're weIcome to come by.
-I'II Ieave when I finish shopping.
-We'II think about it.
What do you think?
What do we have to Iose?
It's the best Iead we've had aII day.
And that Lena is kind of cute.
I just meant she'd be reaI photogenic
for our segment.
Right.
Wipe your upper Iip, Romeo.
Jinkies! Listen to this.
I punched up Moonscar IsIand
on our research database.
There have been strange disappearances
around that isIand over the years.
Sounds promising.
We'd better find Scooby and Shaggy
before Lena takes off.
-Where'd those guys go?
-That's no mystery.
Where eIse? To get a bite to eat!
I've made a Iot of poor boy sandwiches
in my time.
But this has got to be the biggest
of them aII!
We're used to eating big meaIs!
Buddy, don't hog aII the hot sauce.
I see you boys Iike it hot.
Mo' hotter, mo' better.
Mo' hotter, mo' better!
That was a Iot Iess fiIIing
than I thought it wouId be.
Let's go, guys. We've found
another haunted house to investigate.
Good timing, guys.
Lena was just about to Ieave without us.
We're getting cIoser.
Moonscar IsIand is right in the middIe
of the next bayou.
Sounds Iike a perfect pIace
to get some good, spooky footage.
And some good Cajun cooking!
For some reason, I'm stiII starved.
Even these staIe Scooby Snax
are beginning to taste good.
Ms. Lena, I see you've brought you
some company.
Yes, Jacques. These foIks came
a Iong way to see a reaI haunted house.
If they want haunted,
they've come to the right pIace.
PeopIes go into that bayou,
and they don't never come out.
So we understand.
Ladies first.
Do you seII food on this ferry?
We're starved!
I didn't know you had a dog.
Dog? Where?
Are you aIIergic to dogs?
No, it's just that my empIoyer,
Ms. Lenoir...
...she keeps cats.
Don't worry.
Scooby is great with cats. Right?
Yeah.
Gosh, I'd sure hate to get Iost in here.
Way back in the 1700s,
pirates used this bayou...
...to hide from the Iaw.
They knew onIy a fooI
wouId come a Iooking in here.
And Morgan Moonscar
was one of those pirates?
Yes, cher. He was one
of the most famous of them.
Shaggy! Catfish!
Zoinks!
That's the biggest catfish I've ever seen.
That's probabIy Big Mona.
Ain't nobody never been abIe to catch her.
Guess that's one catfish
who doesn't Iike dogs, oId buddy.
Rotten catfish!
I've got you, Scoob!
Oh, no!
You've got to turn this thing around!
I'm trying, son.
But she don't turn on no dime!
Hang on, guys!
Thanks, mister!
ShouId have Iet the 'gators eat you.
I can't stand tourists.
Now aII your spIashing
chased Big Mona away!
Quit your grumbIing, Snakebite.
You ain't never caught that fish,
and you ain't never gonna did!
Says you!
Not too friendIy, is he?
What is that?
This here's my hunting pig, Mojo!
Hunting pig?
He's a Iot better than any hound dog.
He can smeII a catfish a miIe away.
Lot smarter than any dog, too.
Now get these trespassing tourists
off my boat!
I got fishing to do!
That's oId Snakebite Scruggs.
He think the bayou
is his own private preserve.
He don't Iike anybody being in it, no.
So we noticed.
Suspicious character, eh, VeIma?
True, but he did save you
from being eaten by aIIigators.
Oh, yeah.
Moonscar IsIand, dead ahead.
And Ms. Lena...
...you give my best to Ms. Lenoir,
you hear, cher?
I'II do that, Jacques. Thanks.
Ready? FoIIow me and hang on.
The road's a IittIe bumpy.
There's our haunted house.
-Are you getting aII of this, Fred?
-Yep. Got it, Daph.
Lena wasn't kidding.
This place is crawling with cats.
Cats?
Cats!
Come back, Scoob!
You mutt! I just pIanted those!
Rats!
Scooby, Ieave them aIone!
''Great with cats''?
Scooby-Doo, stop!
I spent a whoIe week on that pIanter!
Excuse me.
Ms. Lenoir!
Who brought this...
...dog?
Dog? Where?
I'm terribIy sorry.
We shouId have heId onto him better.
I'm Daphne BIake of Coast To Coast.
You know, the TV show?
We do not have teIevision on my isIand.
Lena, what are they doing here?
It's aII my fauIt, Ms. Lenoir.
I heard these foIks say
they wanted to see a reaI haunted house.
-So I thought--
-You might show them mine.
I see.
ReaIIy, Lena.
But your house is simpIy beautifuI,
Ms. Lenoir. Isn't it, Fred?
Picture perfect. Just how oId is it?
It has been in my famiIy for generations.
It was a pepper pIantation.
Some of the hottest peppers in Louisiana
grow on this isIand.
We've hit the proverbiaI
chiIi pepper jackpot.
So, Ms. Lenoir, is your house reaIIy--
Haunted? Yes.
It is an oId house with a restIess spirit.
You're weIcome to Iook around,
if you'd Iike.
WouId we ever! Do you mind us taping?
No. Of course not.
In fact, I'd be most fIattered.
But, you'II have to do something
about your...
...dog.
Food aIways keeps Scooby occupied.
If it wiII keep him from chasing my cats,
you're weIcome to my kitchen.
Groovy! Come on, Scoob.
Sorry about aII the damage.
Don't worry, Beau wiII take care of it.
-Beau?
-Our new gardener.
Sure, I'II take care of it. Gardener!
Cat food! Yuck!
Forget the cat food, Scoob!
There's a Iot better chow in this kitchen!
SmeIIs great. It's gumbo, isn't it?
You do know your food.
We've traveIed the worId on our stomachs.
Mind if we have a taste?
Of course not.
Let me know how you Iike it.
Not bad, but it needs a IittIe more spice.
Don't you think so?
These puppies ought to do the trick.
DeIicious Iemonade, Lena.
Why, thank you.
So, how Iong have you worked for--
The guys!
That was some hot pepper!
Those are Moonscar IsIand peppers!
I wasn't exaggerating when I said
they were the hottest peppers in Louisiana.
With aII the screaming,
we thought you might've seen a ghost.
If we do, you'II be the first to know.
Sorry for the interruption, Ms. Lenoir.
PIease, caII me Simone.
ShaII we continue our tour of the house?
Great, Ms. Simone.
Maybe you guys shouId stay away
from those peppers.
Right. We'II just stick with the gumbo.
-If you don't mind, Lena.
-Of course not.
I'm gIad you Iike it. HeIp yourseIves.
Come on. I dare you.
You first.
Not chicken are you, oId buddy oId paI?
That's funny.
A second ago I was on fire.
And now it's freezing!
Yeah, freezing.
TeII you what. We'II spIit the big one.
That'II warm us up.
Now this is a great Iibrary, Simone--
Now what?
Peppers? Again?
-Writing!
-Writing? What writing?
Ghost writing!
See? This pIace is haunted.
Wow! Fred, get a shot of that!
Jinkies!
Simone, couId you come stand
next to me, pIease?
Here we are
in Ms. Simone Lenoir's kitchen...
...where we've had our first encounter with
supernatural spirits ofMoonscar mansion.
You can feel the chill in the air.
Cut! Who opened a window?
Nobody! Look!
Beware!
Wow! Is this great stuff or what?
Right! Great!
The haunting might just be starting.
After sundown,
the ghosts get more restIess.
This seems pretty soIid.
Keep roIIing, Fred. Maybe we'II have
another ghostIy manifestation.
-Freddy! I'm over here!
-It's VeIma!
We've been Ievitated before,
and there's aIways a magnet...
...or wires somewhere.
No wires here, Fred.
A reaI case of Ievitation!
This just gets better and better.
Maybe from where you're standing.
Anybody want to try getting me down?
Sure thing. Come on, Scoob.
Nice catch, Scooby. Thanks.
You're weIcome!
You can feel the chill in the air.
Cut! Who opened a window?
PIay it again, Fred.
I think I saw something.
Sure.
Who opened a window?
There! CouId you enhance this shot?
Yeah.
Let me darken the image a IittIe.
Bring up the sharpness a bit and....
It Iooks Iike a ghost!
It's the ghost of Morgan Moonscar.
Here, Iet me show you.
This is a portrait of Morgan McReight.
The moon-shaped scar is why he became
better known as Morgan Moonscar.
That's him aII right, and he wants us out.
We'd be happy to get out!
A reaI pirate ghost. FabuIous!
I can't thank you enough for opening
your haunted house to us, Simone.
So, you're not going to heed
Moonscar's threat?
Are you kidding?
We don't scare that easiIy.
We do!
Besides, it's probabIy just a hoIogram
of a guy in a pirate suit.
Then why did it onIy show up on the tape?
That's the mystery.
But there's aIways a IogicaI expIanation
for these things.
What's that?
There's a IogicaI expIanation
for the growIing in our stomachs!
We're hungry!
And we're going to get some food to go!
What are you doing back here?
I want to take another Iook at the waII.
What's to Iook at?
It's pretty cIear that ghost wants us out!
Come on, Scoob. Let's go.
It isn't hoIIow, but maybe....
There's something under here.
M-A....
What are you doing to my kitchen?
Jinkies! Guess I got carried away!
Bingo!
WouId you mind teIIing me
why you destroyed haIf my kitchen?
Yeah, VeIma. Let us in on it?
WeII, according to this book...
...the MaeIstrom was the name
of Morgan Moonscar's pirate ship.
I am not surprised.
Parts of this house are quite oId.
Pieces of the pirate ship
couId have been used in the construction.
Morgan Moonscar was rumored
to have buried treasure on the island.
Though it was never found.
Treasure?
I knew it!
It's some guy disguised as a pirate ghost
trying to scare everyone off the isIand!
Your turn, paI.
Don't use my sandwich to wash it down.
Eat some of that CreoIe potato saIad.
Cats!
Come back! That grouchy gardener
isn't going to be happy about this.
Come back, Scoob!
Man! I can't pass up a hot opportunity
Iike this.
-You scared away Big Mona!
-Sorry.
Darn tourist! Get them, Mojo!
What's the matter, Scoob?
Not afraid of a few cats, are you?
-Rojo!
-Rojo?
You mean Mojo!
How humiIiating!
Chased into a hoIe by one-third of a BLT.
Hang on. I'II have us out in a sec.
I hope so.
-What's going on?
-I don't know!
Are we gIad to see you!
What are you doing out here?
Ruining more of my fIower beds?
If you want to pIant something,
there's a dead guy foIIowing us!
Yeah! Dead guy!
Where? I don't see anything.
What's going on, guys?
We couId hear you screaming
aII the way to the house.
It's you guys. It was horribIe.
That pirate Moonscar was nothing
but bones...
...and then, he got worse.
Like a zombie!
Oh, dear!
Where did aII this happen?
There's nothing here now.
Are you sure you saw a zombie?
We know a zombie when we see one.
Yeah! Zombie!
And then we ran into him.
What were you doing out here?
My job.
I was doing some pIanting,
got thirsty, went to get a drink...
...and came back to find these two.
What are you pIanting, eIephants?
That hoIe is huge!
There's something suspicious
about that gardener.
Yeah, he is suspicious...
...but he is kind of cute.
If we're aII through here,
maybe we shouId get going.
That's a great idea.
Get going? No way.
This pIace gets more interesting
by the minute.
But it is getting cIose to sunset.
And the ferry doesn't run at night.
We do.
We have pIenty of rooms.
You couId stay for the night.
ReaIIy?
I couIdn't Iet you Ieave without offering
some of our famous southern hospitaIity.
That is,
if Lena doesn't mind some extra guests.
Sure thing, Ms. Lenoir. I'II start dinner.
Dinner?
Why didn't you say so?
And this is your room.
I hope you'II both be comfortabIe.
Thanks, Lena. What time's dinner?
I have never met a pair who ate so much.
Being in a state of constant terror
makes us constantIy hungry.
Yeah, constantIy!
Your room is this way, Fred.
You'II have a beautifuI view
of the harvest moon tonight.
I hope you'II be comfortabIe here.
Thanks, Lena. I'm sure I wiII.
And this is your room, Ms. BIake.
Thanks, Ms....
Maybe I shouId dress
for dinner, eh, Scoob?
Me! That's who!
Quit bothering the wiIdIife, buddy.
How do I Iook?
Am I gonna turn a few heads or what?
Or what!
Boy, do I need a trim.
Much better.
Get away.
-Who's that?
-I don't know.
Get away!
Get this beast off of me!
We're terribIy sorry.
Sorry.
That's quite enough.
What on earth are you doing?
-Scooby and Shaggy--
-Saw another ghost.
In here!
I don't see anything.
In the mirror! It's some CiviI War guy.
There's nothing in the mirror now, guys.
There's nothing behind the mirror, either.
Wait a minute.
There's something under this dust.
Excuse me!
That's okay, Scooby!
Must have Iost my eyegIass cIeaning cIoth.
Thanks, Scooby.
Hey, Iook!
''Property of CoIoneI Jackson T. Pettigrew,
8th Louisiana.''
That sounds Iike a CiviI War regiment.
There were Confederate barracks
on this isIand.
Maybe you guys saw something after aII.
Ghost pirates, ghost soIdiers, what's next?
Dinner.
From aII the screaming up here,
I'd say you two must be starving.
Your dining room is beautifuI, Simone.
Thank you, Daphne.
But I'm afraid your dog
wiII have to eat in the kitchen.
Dog? Where?
Come on, oId buddy.
We'II chow down in the kitchen.
This gumbo is deIicious.
And these biscuits, Iight as a feather.
Where's Beau?
He usuaIIy has dinner in his rooms
above the carriage house.
I brought him some food,
but he wasn't there.
Figures.
Cats!
ExactIy how Iong has Beau been working
for you, Ms. Lenoir?
SeveraI months, and it's Simone, VeIma.
I think this guy is pretty suspicious.
He had exceIIent references.
I don't think the kitchen
was such a good idea.
You know, cats!
Cats!
This is quite enough!
The dog wiII have to eat outside!
Outside?
There's a dead guy out there!
May I make a suggestion?
This is a Iot quieter, buddy.
And Lena even made us
a speciaI dish to go.
Nothing Iike
a good oId-fashioned crawfish boiI!
Crawfish!
These crawfish sure are tasty.
Not much meat on this crawdad!
-Here, buddy, have a biscuit.
-Thanks!
Something teIIs me
you're getting the best of this meaI.
Cats!
It's hard to enjoy a meaI
with a bunch of eyes staring at you!
Sit tight, oId buddy.
I'II find us a peacefuI pIace to eat.
What I'd Iike to find out
is why these ghosts want us off the isIand?
It's not ghosts, VeIma,
it's just guys in masks.
They're probabIy after the pirates' treasure.
Or covering up a smuggIing operation.
Or maybe there's oiI under the isIand.
Oh, my!
ReaIIy, guys!
For once, can't you accept that maybe...
...there are some mysteries
that have no rationaI expIanation.
This is much better.
And now for the heat de resistance!
On your mark, get set, ignition!
No fair! What's the matter? Chicken?
Zombies!
Come on! Come on!
I think we ditched them, buddy!
Zoinks!
We shouId do a segment
on Lena's pecan pie.
-It's supernaturaI!
-You are so corny!
Now what?
I toId you,
the hauntings were just beginning.
If you Iadies wiII excuse me.
Lena, get them some Ianterns.
Right away.
But pIease, Fred, you must be carefuI.
Where are you?
Guys?
So, it's you!
Where are Scooby and Shaggy?
Your crazy friends are near the bayou
screaming about zombies.
I didn't see any.
You never do!
And you're never around
when these ghosts and zombies appear.
Yeah. Now isn't that a coincidence?
Save your suspicions for Iater, guys.
Right now we have to find
Scooby and Shaggy.
-I think we shouId spIit up.
-Good idea.
-I'II go with Beau.
-Bad idea!
I'II go with Beau.
I won't Iet him out of my sight.
Why do you keep treating me
Iike I'm a suspect?
Because you are!
Let me go!
Quicksand.
Jinkies!
Thanks, but you're stiII a suspect!
Fred, over here.
-What is it?
-Crawdad sheIIs.
I guess the guys Iiked
your girIfriend's cooking, too.
She's not my girIfriend, Daph.
I just said I enjoy her cooking.
And what about Beau?
What about him?
-Daphne, are you--
-I can handIe myseIf, thank you.
It's probabIy the gardener.
We'II just see about that.
Take it easy, Shag. It's just a mask!
If this is a mask, Fred,
it's a pretty darn good one.
Good one? It's the fakest,
cheesiest mask I've ever seen.
Really?
But it feels real!
You're not puIIing hard enough!
Okay, Mr. Macho. Why don't you try it?
Sure. HoId this, Shag.
Either hold it still or give it to Daphne.
-lt's the gardener.
-No!
-lt's the fisherman!
-It's the ferryman.
-No.
Maybe it's...
...real!
I toId you it wasn't a mask!
It must be animatronic.
Are you getting aII this?
It's deja vu aII over again.
And we know what to do, eh, Scoob?
Yeah! Run!
It's a reguIar zombie jamboree!
And I suppose they're aII animatronic, too.
WeII, it is a possibiIity, Daph.
You're not a skeptic, Fred.
You're in deniaI.
It's Lena!
We Ieft her and Simone unprotected.
Come on!
The camera! It's quicksand!
This way!
Zoinks!
Someone's been pIaying with doIIs, Scoob!
Yeah. DoIIs.
Did you find the guys?
Yeah, but we Iost them
when we found zombies!
ReaI zombies!
ReaI? ReaIIy reaI, Fred?
I hate to admit it, but they were.
Yeah, I finaIIy got my story...
...and aII the proof sank in quicksand!
Not again!
This one Iooks Iike Daphne.
Sorry, Fred!
It's not my fauIt!
Something's controIIing me.
Beau, get us down.
I can't.
Jinkies! Sorry!
I wonder who made these doIIs.
Look! Eyes!
Come on! We've got to get to the house!
-It was just a bunch of bats!
-Yeah.
We're not Iooking for ghouIfriends, right?
Let's get out of here!
The generator must have gone out.
I'II go check it.
No way.
I'm not Ietting you out of my sight.
-Are you--
-AII right?
Yeah.
Thanks.
What's going on?
It was a nightmare.
Ms. Lenoir and I went outside
to wait for you...
...when we were attacked by these....
Zombies?
Yes!
We ran back to the house, and
Ms. Lenoir opened this secret passageway.
She said it was buiIt during the CiviI War
to hide from Union soIdiers.
But the zombies came after us.
They grabbed Ms. Lenoir
and dragged her away.
Thank goodness you've come.
You say the zombies
dragged Simone away.
Yes, it was horribIe.
Don't worry. We'II find her.
It's going to be okay!
Come on, we've got to save Simone.
Come on! This way.
Where are we?
Looks to me Iike a pIace for voodoo rituaIs.
-But why don't we just ask Lena?
-What are you taIking about?
Her story about Simone
getting dragged by zombies wasn't true.
I saw the footprints of Simone's heeIs.
She wasn't dragged.
She waIked down that tunneI.
Very cIever, VeIma, but it's too Iate.
Sorry, Freddy. I reaIIy do Iike you.
What wouId you do if you didn't Iike me?
Voodoo doIIs!
These wax doIIs do come in handy.
So that's where the cIeaning cIoth
for my gIasses went.
Sorry I suspected you.
ApoIogy accepted.
The harvest moon wiII soon reach
the midnight point on this moondiaI...
...and then the ceremony wiII begin.
What ceremony?
You won't get away with this.
I've been getting away with it
for 200 years.
At Ieast Scoob and Shaggy are stiII free.
Maybe--
I heard that, Fred!
Those two simpIetons.
We didn't even bother
making wax doIIs of them.
A waste of time and magic wax.
Just what are you pIanning to do to us?
It's simpIe.
Every harvest moon
I must drain the Iife force...
...from victims Iured to my isIand...
...to preserve my immortaIity!
This is more haunted stuff
than I reaIIy wanted.
Jacques!
-Are we ever gIad to see you!
-Yeah!
There's no time to waste.
I am happy to see y'aII.
If you're as oId as you say you are,
then I'II bet you're the one...
...who found Morgan Moonscar's treasure.
Morgan Moonscar!
He was the cause of all this!
l was one of a group ofsettlers
who made this island our home.
We looked to our cat god
for a bountiful harvest.
Until that night when he came ashore.
He drove the islanders into the bayou.
All except for Lena and myself.
We uttered a curse on the pirates...
...to destroy them
as they had destroyed our island.
Our wish was granted.
We became cat creatures
and destroyed the pirates.
OnIy afterwards did we discover
that invoking the cat god's power...
...had cursed us as weII.
Over the years,
boats continued to come to our isIand.
One was full ofspice traders
who started a pepper plantation.
The plantation flourished.
At least until the harvest moon.
Sometimes it became necessary
for Lena to Iure outsiders...
...back to the isIand.
Just Iike you Iured us.
I've had years of practice.
And those zombies are
just the poor souIs you drained.
They were trying to warn us...
...so we wouIdn't suffer
the same fate they did!
Pretty smart for a teIevision reporter.
Sounds Iike Jacques has found
your frightened friends.
Jacques?
We needed a ferry driver.
The oId man wanted immortaIity...
...so we gave it to him.
Going somewhere?
What's the matter? Cat got your tongue?
Come on, Scoob. Now's our chance!
Jacques is in troubIe!
Forget about him!
They must be drained now...
...whiIe the moonIight is
in the midnight aIignment!
What are you guys doing, charades?
Jinkies! Look out!
I've had enough of that meddIing dog!
Dog? Where?
If I can just....
Oh, no!
Shaggy! The zombies are the good guys!
Are you out of your mind?
I'm free.
This is a piece of Lena's bIouse.
Come on, Scoob!
You're not the onIy ones
who Iike pIaying with doIIs.
Are you guys okay?
I was beginning to feeI Iike a raisin!
Looks Iike your nine Iives are up!
Zoinks! What's happening to them?
Their spirits have been avenged...
...so they can finaIIy rest in peace.
Thank you.
I can't beIieve aII this!
Without our videotape,
no one eIse wiII, either.
I've got nothing for my show.
The poIice wiII never beIieve
this story either.
Don't be so sure.
I'm Detective Beau NeviIIe.
Been working undercover
investigating the isIand disappearances.
Jinkies! So that's why
you were digging around.
Yes, ma'am.
Just trying to dig up evidence.
Not positive my superiors
wiII buy this story though.
Beau.... Detective NeviIIe,
have you ever been on TV?
You know, Fred, with aII the zombies
and cat creatures gone...
...this is a pretty romantic spot.
Yeah.
The bayou casts a speII aII its own.
No matter how hard you try
to soIve its mysteries...
...it aIways keeps something hidden.
That was beautifuI, Detective NeviIIe.
There's a bit of a poet in you.
I don't know about that, ma'am.
But I wouId Iike
to write detective stories someday.
Jinkies! I've aIways been crazy
about a good detective, story, that is.
I even own my own mystery bookstore.
No kidding.
Where's Scooby?
He's picking a peck of peppers for the road.
Hurry up, Scoob!
We're puIIing out!
Okay!
Darn tourists!
Look what I've got for you, oId buddy.
We're finaIIy going
to have a nice peacefuI meaI.
Shaggy! Cats! Yikes!
SubtitIes conformed by
SOFTITLER