This is your final boarding call
for flight number 732 to Hong Kong.
Excuse me.
All passengers must proceed
to Gate 31A at this time.
Wait!
Sorry, sorry, sorry.
Cutting it close, sir.
Have a good flight.
We made our expectations very clear.
We thought you'd be happy.
You see, our production is two months
ahead of schedule.
Chen, we've been over this and over this.
HouseMart operates on the basis
of just-in-time delivery.
Hell, just about every company
in America does the same.
We get the product in,
we put it on the shelves,
we move it out the door.
No warehousing, no excess costs.
But with more merchandise,
you have more to sell, happy customers.
Let me make this really clear.
If any more shipments arrive early,
we will refuse them.
You want to produce all this surplus,
you pay the warehousing costs.
Tell your bosses everything will be
just as they want it.
-They'll be glad to hear that.
-lt was a mistake is all.
Okay.
What kind of shifts
do you got these guys pulling, Chen?
We are very strict, very fair.
Never more than 12 hours.
This way please.
Yeah, I got a three-hour layover in LA
before the Washington flight.
No, you better tell Toby
I'm gonna miss the game.
I'm gonna try like hell to make it though.
I hate for him to be disappointed.
Everything went great here. Crazy though.
Eleven meetings in three countries
in six days. Never again.
Towel, sir?
Excuse me. Ma'am?
Bless you.
Excuse me.
Your towel, please.
I thought doctors were supposed
to know better.
I quit seven years ago.
Promise not to tell?
As long as you promise
to meet me in Washington next month.
I wish I could, but God knows where I'll be.
That's it?
I enjoy my vices but only in moderation.
So much control.
It's second nature.
Why don't you stay a few days?
I'm better in small doses.
Oh, says who?
Everyone who's ever tried
to make it more permanent.
I'm impressed.
Almost six hours without a page.
I gotta go.
Thank you.
Hey. How are you?
How many confirmed?
Only one dead.
Infected?
Eight as of last night.
So there's still a chance of containment.
We need to monitor all news services
in Asia for any potential cases.
You have everything you need?
Yeah, like a Boy Scout. Always prepared.
Hey, anybody here?
Do I count?
-More than anyone.
-Hi.
Six days ago the Chinese government
informed the WHO
that a strain of the H5N1 virus
had been discovered in a marketplace
in the Guangdong province.
Now over 1.2 million birds were slaughtered
in an attempt to eradicate the strain.
But not only does it appear that they failed,
but some of their equipment
may not have been properly sanitized
which may have inadvertently lead
to spreading the disease.
At least six of the victims
work at a manufacturing facility
where a lot of the villagers are employed.
And there is a very real possibility
that we may be looking
at the first human-to-human transmission
of the avian flu virus.
The village has been contained
though, right?
Well, as soon as the government
was alerted.
So we might be able to stop it?
Only if less than 20 people are infected.
But there are only eight so far.
Look, the reality of containment
will be difficult if not impossible.
But in this case
the global surveillance system
seems to have worked
and we caught it early.
So let's think positive thoughts, okay?
The respiratory distress is quite severe.
Continues to worsen.
There's a lot more than eight patients.
Twenty-five in the last 1 2 hours.
Which means we've lost any chance
of containment.
I do not believe
we ever had any such chance.
You seem surprised.
Aren't you the one who always said
it's not a matter of "if" but "when"?
How bad do you think it'll be?
Maybe we'll get lucky.
The pandemic could be mild like 1957 or '68.
Those weren't mild symptoms.
No.
I think at this moment,
Iuck is not on our side.
Great hit! Run, Toby! Run! Run!
-Run, Toby!
-Go, Toby!
Good job, son!
-Hey, Ed, how's it going?
-Hey, good, good.
Hey, Dan told me you got that promotion.
Yeah, yeah,
I took your advice and went for it.
That's great. They're lucky to have you.
So what did you say to him?
I told him he was being a jerk
and to grow up.
Good.
You know, maybe you shouldn't
hang around him so much.
I can handle myself, Mom.
I'm not saying you can't,
I'm just suggesting...
Are you okay?
Here, Dad.
You're coming down with something.
No way.
Connellys don't get sick, right?
I think I'll turn the straw around just in case.
"O ye of little faith."
Okay, Toby, it's two outs!
Run on anything! That's it!
Go, Toby!
-That's it! Run! Slide!
-Run! Run!
It's really unprecedented.
Forty-three governors from around the
country flew in for this emergency session.
I'm glad they're taking it seriously.
Very seriously.
They've been meeting with the secretary
and director of FEMA for an hour already.
We'd encourage each of you
to update your emergency
response protocols immediately.
Make sure your comprehensive pandemic
flu planning effort integrates...
Secretary Reed, she's here.
Dr. Varnack, Secretary Reed.
Dr. Varnack, I saw your speech
at WHO last year.
It's nice to finally meet you in person.
You, too, Secretary Reed.
Call me Collin, please.
I have a feeling
we're going to be seeing a lot of each other.
Yeah.
They're a little worked up.
Director McGarrett,
when will we have an answer?
Some time over the next two weeks.
All right,
in order to answer some of your questions,
we've invited Dr. Iris Varnack
from the Epidemic lntelligence Service
to brief us.
She just returned from China. Dr. Varnack...
Thank you.
We have been tracking the H5N1 flu virus
since 1996.
Now, over that time,
less than 100 people have died
and most of them
handled poultry on a daily basis.
Two weeks ago, everything changed.
The H5 virus mutated
and is now transmissible
from human to human.
So you're saying
this is the start of a pandemic?
Come on, we can't start
throwing around the word "pandemic."
-The public will panic.
-Well, that's what it is, isn't it?
-Like the Spanish flu.
-The Spanish flu killed 50 million people.
-That's not what you're suggesting, right?
-No.
Actually we believe
that it could be much worse.
The H5 virus has a much higher fatality rate
than the 1918 Spanish flu virus.
We expect two to three waves
in the next year or so.
I mean, we believe
that the ultimate global loss of lives
could reach as high as 150 or 350 million.
And what if we close our borders?
Now. Today.
Shut down all the airports,
seal ourselves off.
I'm afraid it's too late for that.
Well, since 9/11 and hurricane Katrina
we've upgraded
our emergency response plans.
This is much worse than Katrina.
This is like a hurricane Katrina
hitting every city in every state
at the same time.
It is going to be a long and brutal ordeal
that will rip apart the fabric of society.
The public is gonna be demanding
a vaccine and we don't have one
and we may not have one
for four or five months.
Well, why don't we have one
if we've known about it since 1996?
Because every single strain
of influenza is unique
and so you can't develop a vaccine
until that particular strain
comes into existence.
Rest assured though,
every pharmaceutical company in the world
is working around the clock
to develop a vaccine.
It's just a very slow process.
Well, you know what, Collin?
That's not gonna be exactly comforting
to the people sitting at home
scared out of their minds.
They're going to be looking to us
for answers.
Governor Newsome,
what I can tell you is that time is our friend.
The longer the flu virus is around,
the less lethal it becomes.
So the more time we can buy,
the more lives we can save.
And how long before it hits here?
We're sure that we have at least
a few weeks before it hits America.
That's if we're lucky.
Sixteen hundred rolls so they get $50 a roll.
If we put them, I think it was this aisle
right here, we got them stacked down there.
Really, all in all,
after adding the six extra aisles,
probably 16 months,
18 months to recoup all the costs on it.
It's basically gonna be good.
The other stores around the country
are finding the same.
Seems like switching the placement
of the toy aisles with the hardware
has actually worked really well.
It's a great suggestion, Ed.
The new signage also seems
to be having a positive effect.
Ed?
You feeling all right?
Ed? You all right?
Could you get her to stop?
Make her stop.
It's all right. I think they're buying the bat.
No, it's...
Oh, jeez man, your nose.
Here...
Maybe you should call a doctor.
Get the hell away from me!
Somebody call 911!
Hello!
Dr. Daily, please report to ER seven.
Hello?
I want to see my husband!
What's going on, Mom?
Why won't they let us out?
Oh, it must be some kind of mistake.
Mrs. Connelly, I'm sorry to have kept you.
What the hell is going on?
If you could just
come back this way with me please.
I'm sorry. Alone.
An associate of mine is gonna come
and take a few samples from you.
What kind of samples?
Just precautionary.
I want to see my dad.
It'll be okay, guys.
I'm just going to go see him
and then I'll come back and tell you.
It'll be all right.
He's dead, isn't he?
In New York, representatives
to the United Nations met today
in a rare closed door session
as fears continue to mount
over the recent outbreak
of avian flu in China.
Speculation that the virus
has now become transmissible
from human to human has reached
a fevered pitch around the globe.
Kelly Firland is live from Hong Kong.
He was fine.
He just had a little cough, that's all.
What's wrong with him?
I'm not currently at liberty to discuss this...
He's my husband.
I need to be with him.
Of course.
She'll take you.
I need to speak with Secretary Reed.
It's lris Varnack.
Well, could you please find him?
Yes. It's an emergency.
Secretary Reed?
It's lris Varnack. I'm sorry to call so late.
Yes, we've confirmed that it's the H5N1.
The patient lives in Richmond
but he's Just returned
from the Guangdong province.
There's no telling how many people
he's been in contact with.
Well, whether or not Ed Connelly
is our patient zero here in America, I mean,
you can Just bet that he's one of many
we'll see in the next few days.
The President wants to meet the press
and address the nation.
He needs to do it quickly.
The avian flu is in America.
He's coding. Let's start compression.
Push some epi here.
All I can tell you
is what the President said last night.
The avian flu is here.
We're doing everything possible to ensure...
First we're educating medical personnel
around the country about the flu
to ensure the highest level...
Hospitals have detailed plans
about the isolation of infected patients...
Developing a vaccine is our highest priority.
-What kind of precautions?
-Will you be closing schools?
What about churches and malls and
all the other places where people gather?
Look, this administration
believes that those decisions
are best left to the respective states.
There is still a lot of debate
about whether or not masks
are an effective means
of keeping the virus from spreading.
Washing your hands thoroughly,
those are the kinds
of common-sense precautions
everybody should be taking.
I want to reiterate
there is absolutely no need for panic.
The pneumonia on the lungs causes the
acute respiratory distress syndrome.
Not all patients with H5 get ARDS,
but those that do,
at least 40 to 60% of them will die.
An hour prior to his death
he complained of body aches so intense,
he thought his bones were breaking.
Coughed so violently
that he tore apart his abdominal muscles
and his rib cartilage.
Basically, he drowned in his own blood.
Does anyone here actually have symptoms?
This is worse than last week.
We got more Tamiflu but only 300 doses.
What, they're all gonna be screaming
at us again?
There isn't any us, hon.
I'm off in 15 minutes.
You can't just stay a little longer?
I can't. They closed my kids' pre-school.
I gotta pick them up before my
neighbor leaves for her night shift.
What am I gonna tell all these people here?
You'll figure something out
or they'll eat you alive.
Hi, Judy.
Why are so many people dying
while others seem fine?
That's an important question, Richard.
Not everyone who is exposed
to the virus will get sick.
Now, we think that factors like age
and genetics and your immune system
do play a part...
-Hey, Sandra.
-Are you at the Connelly neighborhood?
Yeah, I just got here.
Is it as bad as we heard?
It's even worse.
I'm on my way to see
Governor Newsome now,
provided they let me
into the fortress of solitude.
I'll call you back.
Thanks.
Dr. Varnack, sorry to keep you waiting.
What can I do for you?
Flip that switch.
There you go.
Governor Newsome,
it's quite a setup you've created
for you and your staff here.
As bio-secure as we can make it.
We even have a re-circulating
air filtration system.
From here I have contact
with every governmental department
in Virginia and DC.
My job is to protect the people of this state,
and the best way I know how to do that
is to ensure continuity of leadership.
Now is there something you needed?
Yes. The director of the CDC
asked me to come see you.
You've instituted quarantines
in several neighborhoods around the state.
That's right.
A couple of housing projects,
a military base, and the neighborhood
where that first victim lived.
Well, at this point, quarantines won't stop
the spread of the virus.
It's already here.
And it sends a terrible message
to the rest of the country.
I think it lets the public know
we're doing something pro-active.
It makes them feel safe.
These are gonna be extremely trying times
and people are gonna resort
to desperate measures.
Now, all the quarantine does is
make them feel like caged animals.
The residents in all those areas, they're
getting food, water, medical supplies...
You're cutting them off from their humanity
which is the one thing that is gonna
get us through this pandemic!
Doctor,
maybe you've spent too much
time in Africa or Bangladesh
or wherever.
Maybe you're used to people
sitting back and accepting their fate.
But that's not what we do in this country.
What we do is fight
with every weapon in our arsenal.
Now, if that means we have to make
some tough choices, then so be it.
I was elected to make those tough choices.
We have to take care of each other.
I couldn't agree with you more.
That's exactly what I'm doing!
I assume you can see yourself out.
There you go.
Thank you.
Steve Stuart.
Three days.
Address?
602 Oleander.
There you go.
These'll last you for three days.
When are they gonna let us out of here?
I don't have that information.
My mom wanted me to get
some more gloves and masks.
That's impossible.
They're all made in China
and there's nothing coming
from over there right now.
Lauren?
Hi, Mrs. Koppel.
How are you all doing?
As well as we can, I guess.
We were all cleared of the virus.
Thank the Lord.
I've been saying prayers for you.
We all have.
Tensions escalated as the
New York City Mayor's proposed
electricity rationing met with
stiff resistance from the city council.
And on Wall Street today
transportation stocks
continue their tumble
for the 18th straight day.
Congressional debate over closure of the
financial market...
Your husband is doing well, I hope?
I wish I knew. He's still in lraq.
He hasn't answered his e-mail
in a couple of days.
My husband Albert, he was a soldier, too.
Many months would go by
and I would hear not a word.
I don't know how you stood it.
No one gave me the choice.
$19? For coffee?
Nobody has fresh coffee anywhere else
around here. You can't get it.
For you, $17.
I've called the police. The baby's in there.
Devon? What's going on? Where's Tracy?
They're all sick. I was afraid to go in.
I couldn't...
Scott what are you doing?
Come on, don't do this...
I couldn't save her.
Nobody could.
Okay, well, we'll get you some help, okay?
We're all gonna die.
Oh, God!
Jesus.
It's been three weeks now
since the first victim of avian flu died.
But citizens here in Moscow
are less concerned with health risks
than with Russian president Alexandrov's
recent ban on all public gatherings.
Crowds poured into Red Square today
in protest
and were met with resistance
from the state police.
So tell me what's happening.
It's like the Wild West out here.
Criminal gangs hitting delivery
trucks, warehouses.
There's a huge black market opening up.
Are you guys having any problems
with local law enforcement
walking off the job?
Yeah, we've lost 25% of our force.
How many inmates is he talking about
putting on the streets?
As many as possible.
Evidently, it's really bad inside the prison.
They've got no way
to treat or isolate all the sick.
Well, we can't just release
convicted felons into the population.
-You want to do this another time?
-Yeah.
We have to demand that they send back
our National Guard units immediately.
Now, when I make this call,
can I count on you two to support me?
-Absolutely.
-Yes, of course.
Okay, thanks.
I'll call you later.
-Mike.
-Yeah?
We just got word from the White House.
They're not releasing any of the strategic
national stockpile of Tamiflu to us.
Why the hell not?
New York and California
are declaring priority
because of the number of infected.
Plus the Pentagon's saying
it needs more for the military.
That's part of our emergency protocol.
I don't know how much it matters.
Everything I'm hearing is that
the anti-virals aren't working anyway.
That is not the point.
We were told we could count on it!
What's the use of having a plan
if nobody wants to follow it?
Finally. Two faces I actually want to see.
Your father called.
He and your mom are up at the cabin
like you suggested.
-Good. Did they take lots of food?
-Yeah.
You really think it's gonna get that bad?
Might as well be prepared for the worst.
Bored out of your mind yet?
I never thought I'd say it,
but I'm sick of my PlayStation.
How long are we going to be here, anyway?
We're going to be out of here
before you know it.
Every vaccine manufacturer in the world
is working on
developing something to stop this.
I just never thought the flu
would be such a big deal.
How long do you think it'll be?
Soon.
We're going to be out of here real soon.
This is ridiculous.
All we have left is rice and flour.
All right.
No, it's not all right.
You have to go down
to those idiots at the barricades
and tell them we need real food.
Okay, honey.
Mom...
Mom!
What is it?
Toby. He's sick!
No. No, he can't be.
He can't be.
We were fine. We were all fine.
Oh, my God. Oh, sweetie.
Oh, my God.
I can't have my baby here!
I shouldn't even be in here!
Do you know how dangerous this is for me?
For my baby?
Excuse me.
We gotta get some help over here.
Somebody will be right with you, sir.
Just, my mama needs something.
You gotta give her something for the pain.
If you just sit with her,
we'll get you some help.
We've been waiting a real long time, okay?
She's hurting bad.
Okay, just... I'm going to find you
something, okay? Just sit tight.
They just closed the 8th and 9th floors.
They're full?
The whole damn hospital's full.
The hallways, the cafeteria. Everywhere.
What is that?
I'm not staying here.
Tell me, what is that?
Are you taking the supplies?
My mom and my little boy are sick at home
and it was probably me
that got them that way.
I'm not doing this anymore, and don't
you dare make me feel guilty about it!
Alma?
-Alma!
-Curtis?
-Curtis? Curtis!
-Alma.
Curtis!
Curtis, you're home!
They brought us back.
The whole damn National Guard,
they brought us back.
Look at you. You're so thin.
I was sick a couple of weeks.
I didn't want to worry you.
With the flu?
I'm okay, look at me. I'm better now.
You were sick and you didn't tell me?
Sweetie, you have enough to worry about.
I know, but you should've told me.
Everything's gonna be fine.
It's okay, everything's gonna be fine.
Dr. Varnack,
I hope your efforts there
are proving more successful than our own.
These are dark times indeed.
The reason for my writing is to let you know
that our common foe has mutated yet again.
The H5 has become resistant to anti-virals
which means we have no more
weapons left with which to fight.
The government is keeping it quiet,
but we are in terrible trouble.
What you have witnessed so far
has been bad, I know.
But America and the rest of the world
must prepare for worse.
Much, much worse.
I missed you.
I can't believe you were sick
and I didn't know.
I know, it just...
It hit me and I literally started having
these hallucinations and...
I was out. I just
dropped down right there.
A couple guys actually
thought I'd been shot.
I'm better now. Mostly better anyway.
It takes some people months,
even years for their body to fully recover.
No, not me, baby. I'm invincible.
Girl, I'm like superman.
You've only got resistance
to this particular strain.
If it mutates, you're...
Just let me enjoy my little power
for a while, okay?
Okay.
So what exactly are you and the Guard
gonna be doing?
Just keeping order.
Just helping out.
Whatever the police or fire department need.
Whoever needs us.
Well, I need you more than any of them.
And I need you.
I need you.
I need you but I'm gonna be late.
I have to go. I'm late!
-Don't go!
-Are you kidding me?
My overtime's gonna get us
a bigger apartment.
We're all facing dire shortages of
everything from food to aspirin to soap
as warehouses around the globe
continue to empty out.
Though the worldwide death toll
has now passed 350, 000,
experts warn that we will see these numbers
double or even triple very quickly.
Now it's time to go to...
There weren't any more coffee beans
anywhere but there's instant if you want...
Six of the largest national
insurance companies
all filed for bankruptcy protection
in federal courts today.
Attorneys contend that it would take
several billion dollars to pay off
Iife insurance policies for those already...
Did you hear me?
-Alma, don't go.
-What?
Don't go. Just call them and quit.
Something.
Just don't go back.
I can't do that.
We don't have enough people as it is.
Every day you work there is like...
Like you're going down a street
full of land mines.
I'm careful, Curtis.
Can't get away from this, you know?
Can't get away for two minutes.
What's the point of running
when there's nowhere to run?
Tensions are at a breaking point
with both the NAACP and the ACLU
sharply condemning
Governor Mike Newsome's
continued quarantine
of several housing proJects
around the state.
Family and friends
of those under quarantine
have been converging on the Governor's
emergency headquarters
in growing numbers.
Calling the quarantined neighborhoods
death traps,
they are demanding the release
of their loved ones immediately.
The scene is much the same
across the nation
with critics insisting that current strategies
are clearly not working.
Like the protestors gathered here,
these critics believe
that political leaders and emergency...
Mike?