And no wonder, for Satan himself
masquerades as an angel of light.
Get the first-aid kit!
David!
Coming, Mom!
Whisper
- Hey, Sid!
- Welcome back to the real world.
Come on, check this out.
Oh... hey, you know what? Hey, Max,
look... I've got to be honest with you...
You wanna buy this place?
- I wouldn't even rob this place.
- Yeah, it's gonna be all mine.
- Ours!
- Ours, ours!
Look just because you worked on the kitchen inside,
doesn't mean that's the only option out here, OK?
No, Sidney, Max is a business man, we've been working on menus...
You know what? I've got a business plan, and it ain't got nothing to do with paper hats and napkins and menus...
I'm done with all this shit, Sid.
Hey, look... I've got this sweet gig, this
December with this guy named Jones.
We grab this little rich kid,
big pay day, everybody wins.
Don't listen to him. OK?
You know what? It's a nice idea.
But think about it, Max. You've got no money.
No collateral, no banks gonna touch you.
I'm gonna do this, Sid.
Well, I'm sure you will.
I'll call you in a couple of weeks, OK?
I mean it.
Get out of here.
It says here you've worked
food service before.
I've short ordered in Quincy,
Walton. A few places in Newport
And with a 50,000 dollars loan, you think you
can resurrect the old Hazel Street Diner, huh?
It's a corner shop, two busy streets,
lots of foot and auto traffic.
Yes, Mr. Truemont, I've reviewed that.
It's not nothing, not really something either.
How'd it go?
Did you get it?
I hope, Sid calls.
I'm gonna take that job, Rox.
I have no place else to go.
OK, sweetheart. I've got to set up
for your party.
So, Chloe will take over from here.
But I like it better when you do it.
Sandborn's party?
Chazzan!
- Wasn't that great, guys?
- Yeah...
It's beautiful, isn't it?
Now, hey! Don't you guys try this at home
with your pets now... Are you ready?
Let see if you can make them disappear.
One...
- Santa!
- Hey... Santa!
Ho! Ho! Ho!
One for everybody!
- One for everybody!
- Ok... Ok.
Ok... be careful! Alright?
- Over here.
- Alright.
No fighting! Ok... Ok, just a minute.
Abrakazzam!
What you want for Christmas, David?
What do you want, Santa?
- Ok, birthday cake time.
- Yeah...
Chloe, do you know where David is?
No, I'm not sure.
David!
Oh God!
Kidnapped your son
Don't call the police or we kill him.
I missed you, Sidney.
I don't mind your new hair cut.
Are you still glad you came along?
- What're you doing here anyway? Yoko... Uno?
- I'm good with kids, Vince.
- I've got two, what'd you want?
- Huh... two.
Hey! What the hell is that?
- I must’ a missed one.
- No shit.
- Don't matter, here's our boy.
- Alright.
I hope he took the right one.
- Sidney!
- Take it easy.
He's stoppin'.
- Is everything OK, guys?
- Yeah... just ran out of gas.
It's OK... it's OK, we've got 'em covered.
Bobby, where the hell are you?
We've got two flats on 128...
Bobby! For Christ's sake, I'm talking
to you, lazy ass...
Help me, get over there right away...
- What'd he see?
- Probably nothing.
Not here... Max, get the van, let's go.
- Fine.
- Come on.
But.. but, he wouldn've seen anything.
Do you want me to wake up?
You'll never wake up.
- Mrs. Sandborn! I'm Detective Whitley.
- You think you'll find him?
Ma'am, as I said on the phone,
we're pursuing all leads.
The fact of the matter is, the kidnappers
will probably call, they usually do.
Mrs. Sanborne! Detective Miles.
Look, I know this is a very difficult time,
but I need a list of all your employees...
Miles, can I talk to you for a minute?
Excuse me.
I've got this covered, alright? So you just watch, take some notes and see how we do things up here. OK, kiddo?
¶ Love is a burning thing ¶
¶ And it makes a fiery ring ¶
¶ Bound by wild desire ¶
¶ I fell in to a ring of fire ¶
¶ I fell in to a burning ring of fire ¶
¶ I went down, down, down,
and the flames went higher ¶
¶ And it burns, burns, burns,
the ring of fire, the ring of fire ¶
Ughh... I thought this was a summer camp.
And how'd you get your hands on this place?
Huh... he already gave me a couple’ a bucks
to watch it once.
Watch it, what? Collapse?
We all had our better days.
Come on, let's get him inside...
It's not getting any warmer out here.
It's frickin' freezing.
Alright... I just gonna put this on you...
and get you inside where it's warm. OK, buddy?
Alright. It's nothing... it's just the wind, buddy.
Get outta here!
- What?
- It's just a dog.
God blessed the 5th amendments.
There's nothing to be scared of,
it'll be OK. I promise, okay?
- I have to go to the bathroom.
- You got your very own bathroom just inside.
Inside where? Where am I?
Don't worry about that, David.
Just work with us... cooperate.
- Hell, I don't know... think of it as a game.
- Is he trying to hurt me?
No... just relax, buddy.
I'll get you some ice-cream later.
Would you like that?
Alright.
OK... in you go.
You can take off your blindfold now, David.
Oh, you are a regular den-mother!
Vince.
Sidney, if you'd let me know, I could
have brought my things and then, shit...
we'd have more channels then
you know what to do with.
Look, huh... I know I don't have to warn you,
but don't go, gettin' too attached to the kid, OK?
I got this.
- I'll put us next up.
- OK, thanks.
- Oh, wi wi poo poo, what is this foreign shit?
- We are near the border, Vince.
Border of what? África?
Hey, there we go.
Hah, yeah, all we need now is a pizza, and
we've got ourselves one hell of the evening.
Hey! Den-mother!
You seen his phone book?
Put it down... it's a sure fire way,
we'd leave a paper trail.
Oh, hi mom, yeah, I'm in camp,
I'm gonna have a fun few days.
It's gonna be fine... I won't let anything
happen to him, you know that?
Baby, I wish this was over.
It will be soon.
Bed time.
I found you this. I thought you
might get cold.
- Why are you wearing that?
- Well... it's so you won't see who I am.
- Oh...
- You try to get some sleep, OK?
It looks uncomfortable.
I won't peek if you wanna take it off.
OK, but it has to be our secret.
OK... I promise.
¶ Late night at the oasis
send my camel to bed ¶
Do you love me, Max?
Maybe.
When we have the money, you can
remove that if you hate it so much.
I can't remove it,
'cause the scar just comes back.
Baby, you think we're bad people?
There's no commandment in kids kidnapping.
It's stealing though.
It's not stealing... borrowing.
The kid's mother pays Jones,
David's back home tomorrow night.
Who is this Jones anyway?
Doesn't matter, Sidney also don't know Jones.
We get our cut for snatching the kid from home.
They'll do the exchange then we get paid.
Yeah, everybody wins.
Everybody wins.
Max!
What is it, baby?
Nothing. I'm sorry
I had a bad dream.
It's OK.
I'm hearing voices.
Would you check on David?
- Yeah.
- Thanks
I don't like it here.
Shit.
I thought you're in bed, I was trying not to scare ya.
Why was my window open, Max?
Don't let the others hear you calling
me that, you understand?
Sorry, sometimes you hear things you don't want to.
Come on, it's alright... go to bed.
Ohh! Goddammit!
This little bastard busted my insulin.
- Hey, hey... calm down.
- He was in the trunk, he must've kicked it or something.
- He didn't do it on purpose.
- Just relax, man, how long if you need more?
Every morning, man, right now!
Alright, give me the keys
There must be a pharmacy around here somewhere.
There's one down the road but they're
gonna know you, no way, we can't have that.
Well, I'll go to Portsmouth! Give me the keys!
No, no, that'll cut it too close, I got to be
in Wesley by 5 o'clock to talk to Jones.
- I told you that one car thing was a bad idea.
- The only bad idea is, bringing you along.
Hey!... You take it easy.
Max, take him to Portsmouth.
Alright, go... get him the hell otta here.
Oh, God!
- Come here, you little bastard!
- Just leave him alone!
- Knock it off!
- How you like this?
- Sidney... he's seen our faces.
- Let me just think a minute, alright?
Max, did you lock the door after
you looked in on him last night?
What did she just say?... What did you do?
What did ya... tucked him in or something?
- I swear I locked it.
- Ahhh...
You're better than that, Max, you know
what this means, don't you?
He probably knows our names too.
That freaky kid screwed us again.
He's seen our faces.
- I don't know if we can let him go now.
- What?
- Just stop doing anything till I get back.
- Alright, Max.
- Fine
- Hello! Diabetic!
Just a little bit more, right there,
that's good, stay right there.
Alright... you hungry?
We gotta get back.
Hey, Sidney never believe we got to
Portsmouth and back that quick. Come on.
Let's kill a few hours, man, just to cover us.
Alright.
You have sown the wind and
shall reap a whirlwind
Yes?
- You're not helping yourself in here, kid.
- Am I in trouble?
I don't know... that all depends on you.
You think you can huh... forget about what
we look like? Our faces, voices, names? Hmm?
Why?
Alright, huh...
How about if I give you a little bedtime story?
A couple years back, me and partner
did a job on this registry.
Everything was going real smooth like,
until the teller set off the alarm.
We warned her, don't touch it, don't
go near it, but she did anyway.
Now, my partner, well, he was
forced to blow her brains out.
Put a bullet right through her head.
Bang... well, there you have it.
Nobody likes a squealer.
Nice... what is it?
The teller's beaded necklace, it broke
and the beads spilled all over the floor.
How'd you know that?
I know lots of things.
And I know it wasn't your partner
that killed the teller.
That's not what you told the police.
You told that story so many times,
until you actually believe it.
And I know something else.
What's that? What do you know?
I know that you're about to have
a heart attack.
Trying to scare me?
Too bad the car's not here.
Stop.
That was your plan, right?
One car means fewer complications.
I'm afraid you're gonna die here, Sidney., in this lonely old cabin, and shit about the in the room,.
Sidney!
911. What's your emergency?
I'm sorry... wrong number.
I'm sorry, Sidney, Max will be here soon.
No... we can't let them know we're here.
Hang on, OK? Max will be here soon.
We'll be OK, then.
Max, baby, it's Sidney, his heart...
I... I'm so sorry, Max.
David was keeping me company,
I was afraid to be alone, Max.
Sorry about Mr. Braverman.
Really, really sorry.
Wow... there's a lot of spiders.
I thought they hibernated in the winter.
- I wonder where the hive is?
- The ground's too frozen to bury him in.
We leave him here a couple’ a days.
Take him with us when we go.
Bigger share now.
Who gives a damn, the kid
just brings us bad luck.
So, what're we gonna do?
We've got two choices, we would drop the
kid by a highway and call it a bust...
Wait, no, no, this is for nothing and we
go back to being broke? No, Goddamn way!
Or... I go to that ring... try to find Jones.
I'm sure if it's still on, we'll get paid.
Yes, and it's a bigger share now.
Vince, I swear to God, you or anyone else...
Sidney's share goes to his niece.
Alright, look, whatever,
So, you're gonna go speak to Jones?
Wait... I thought we were voting.
I vote we let David go.
I've got a bad feeling about this whole thing.
Max?
Take this. For protection.
From what? Elves?
Little boy abducted
Scion of Beacon Hill family
grabbed from own 8th birthday
Where is Sidney?
He died, he's... dead.
He had heart attack.
That's unfortunate, is the child still alive?
Of course...
We took a picture, in case his mother
wants prove.
What the?... Well, I have to take another one.
Don't bother! You prepared to call
the mother, right?
Yeah, tonight.
You have what you need?
Yeah... untraceable phone scrambler.
Expert took it all up.
The guy's a pro.
Then, meet me at the Boston Park Ave.
at 10 tomorrow.
You'll get the details for the drop, where
your money is at, and watch your back.
- So, these are all the images, Marla?
- Uh huh.
- Excuse me.
- Oh, Detective... how nice of you to join us.
The kid must still be on Mississippi time.
So, did we narrow down the car Marla?
- Not really, but still looking for a big American car.
- Mh'hm
What about the van?
Wiped clean before they torched it, but I can
be more thorough, when we tow it in.
So, we got nothing.
Not necessarily, look, at least two
of these things have a print.
Including a clean thumb print and a fore finger.
Chances are somebody has a record.
Ahh, that's good, it's real good.
- Let's take a little ride, OK?
- Where're we going?
Just got a few more things to do,
before we can get you home.
But, I'm having fun here.
Not sure, I wanna go home just yet.
What'd you mean, buddy? Of course, you do.
Come on, let's go.
Baby, we should turn back.
Too late for that.
Just keep him down.
Sorry, sweetie.
You can look now, David.
Alright... Scrambler, ready.
Decoder, we're on.
They might not be able to trace us.
- I'm calling your mom, David.
- Oh, good.
We're on, don't forget to do the wire.
OK.
Yes?
Ms. Sandborn?
Speaking.
We have your boy.
I want prove he's alive.
Yeah, alright.
OK.
David?
David, is that you?
Come on, buddy. You're almost there.
Get him to say something.
Say something.
Just say hello.
Come on, David, don't be scared.
Yes, be scared... you should be very scared,
of who I am and what I'm gonna do to you...
It's OK... you just say hello, honey.
- Go ahead.
- Goddammit, say something.
- Alright!
- Vince, don't hurt him!
Hey, what're you doing?!
Back off!
Vince, stop it!
David, it's OK. It's OK.
She did.. she just said my name!
- Oh, boy... damn you...
- What's happening?
- Damn you! She just told them my name!
- Back off!
- What'd you do that for?
- Leave the kid!
- Hang on a minute... hang on.
- Take it off, Max!
What the hell, are you doing?!
We lost them.
OK, next time they call, let's double up.
- Did you get a match?
- No.
- Any signal trace data?
- No
- Ms. Sandborn, sorry you had to hear that...
- Is David alive?
- We didn't get a voice match, didn't know the location.
- Is he dead?
- Did they kill him?
- Catherine, we don't know, we have no idea.
So, what you guys wanna do now?
I could really go for that ice-cream.
- Alright, that's it!
- Vince!
Don't you hurt him!
It's OK. It's OK. Everything's fine.
It's not OK!
What're you doing, Max?
What I should have done a long time ago!
Stop using my damn name. It's a good
way for a kid to wind up dead.
Will I be your first?
Max, look out!
What the hell was that?
Did you see that?
Max?
Can't sleep, huh?
Nightmares.
You want some company?
No thanks, Vince, I just wanna be alone.
Please forgive me.
Vince?
Vince, is that you down there?
Your move.
- Hey, who let you out?
- Nobody.
- Where's Max?
- He went to go talk with someone called Jones.
Hmm, I'm glad someone is up on these things.
Where's Roxanne?
Why?
Hey, listen. After that stunt you pull last night,
you should be laying down in the cell next to Sid.
You couldn't kill me, you don't have it in you.
Well...
Wanna play?
- Aahh...
- Good morning!
How come she's not your girlfriend? The way
she acts around you, seems like she likes you.
What the hell would you know?
Last night... I could hear her through the walls.
She was praying.
She was asking for God's forgiveness.
For a secret, a secret she's
been keeping, even from Max.
What secret?
"A gruesome discovery was made today
outside the tunnel near Welsham, Main".
"The body of 17 years old girl was found
in an abandoned car near the local rock core".
"The authorities are holding
a young man for questioning".
Oh my God!
Vince, don't sneak up on me, OK?
Did you hear that?
No.
Oh... it was nothing.
What's the matter, princess?
- It's about Sidney, I could have saved him.
- What?
Wait... that wasn't your fault.
It's not your fault, baby.
Thank you, Vince.
Have you ever missed me?
No, can I go?
Sometimes, I miss you.
You asshole, you swear, you weren't
gonna say anything.
A deal is a deal. OK?
- But you have been keeping secrets.
- What secrets?
I know about our baby, and what you did.
- How? I never told anybody.
- Then, why you shouldn't tell me?
Vince, it was a mistake.
It's OK... I just want you one more time.
Rox, if Max knew what you did...
you think he would still see you as a fit mother?
Our secret.
Your call was a disaster.
I know, it was a mess.
The damn kid is a handful...
- I didn't ask you for a report card.
- Yeah.
Obviously we're not arranging a drop today.
Your reason I had to drive 5 hours to hear that?
Well, Max, If you were able to provide proof
of life, we wouldn't have this problem.
See what's in front of you?
Alones box.
You know what inspired him?... Death!
What's this got to do with it?
It doesn't have anything to do with it.
You only got one choice now. Kill the kid!
You hired me to grab the kid, not kill him.
We made one bad call, we'll call again.
The mother will pay, any parent would pay.
We're not done until we get our money.
You got me?
No, you don't get me, Max!
You will do what I tell you.
Be prepared to dispose of the body.
You got to be aware of all the possibilities.
I'm not killing anyone, and sure as
hell not an 8 year old.
Huh! If only you knew who you're dealing with.
Listen, Jones! I don't give a damn
who you are, I ain't doing it.
The last thing I would do, is cut
off his ear and send it to his mom..
Less effective than one might think.
Return the phone, we'll meet tomorrow morning
for the last time, at your restaurant.
- What's the deal, Jones?
- What?
Jones? I'm not Jones, I don't know
what you're talking about, I swear!
What the hell is this? Huh?
I'm not Jones, man, I don't know any Jones.
Then who the hell is calling me?
Somebody said he'll pay me, OK? To put the phone back and pick it up once he was done with it
The guy that paid you, what's he look like?
- What did you do?
- Waugh...
It stays you remember?
- Hey, kid.
- Abrakazzam!
That's very cute, give it here.
- I give to Max when I tell him.
- Tell him what?
About you and Roxanne.
Oh... Check.
You like games, huh?... I know a game.
Come on... down there.
David?
So, where're we going?
To play my game, OK?
I'm gonna show you something.
Alright... stop right there... Ok.
You see that? Through the trees?
Just keep looking.
- I don't like this game.
- Are you gonna cry?
- Huh?
- Oh... I thought you might need that.
No!... Ohhh...
Got some more to say? Huh?!
Please... don't kill me.
I told you... you don't have it in you.
David! Come back here!
David?
David!
Hey!
Your move, Vince.
Very clever.
I'm just gonna wait here.
Well, you see, the longer you make me wait...
You're done running?
That's good, very good.
Because, I am gonna break your legs.
David!
You wanna yell out for Max?
Maybe he could help you.
But who's gonna help you?
Are you threatening me?
Jesús!
No... not Jesús.
Checkmate!
David!
He fell!
I got you.
Yeah?
It's Marla.
FDA licensing database got a hit on a Vincent Delayo.
Looks like he filled an order for insulin two days ago.
I thought that just might work.
Where?
Reggie’s Pharmacy, 227 Maine Street,
Welsham, Maine. I'll call Whitney now.
Don't.
I'll tell him for you.
See you soon, kiddo.
- Your eyelids look heavy.
- Dreams... bad dreams, David.
No more Vince though.
- That's the most horrible thing.
- Don't it make you just a little bit happy?
Happy?... You think what happened
to Vince made me happy?
I can see it in your eyes.
I heard that the eyes are the windows to the soul.
David!
- Could you leave us a few minutes?
- No problem, Max.
Sorry I was away.
- Then don't go see Jones tomorrow.
- I have to get our money.
No... baby every time you leave, something awful
happens, look, just let him go tonight, can we please...
Rox, we need the money.
That's what happens when everybody wins, your
friends are dead, I've no idea why we're trapped here...
And these things I hear in the middle of night, I wake up and I feel like somebody's putting ideas in my head.
Hey. Hey, easy baby, easy, look at me...
We're almost there.
Where's your ring?
I'm cleaning it.
There's something wrong with this place.
We leave tomorrow, I promise.
- Oh my God, where is it?
- Looking for this?
You lost your ring in Vince's bed, Rox.
No, Max, you don't understand, I can explain.
- Vince, he made me...
- ... You do what?
Max, you were away for 3 years, and I had no one...
And I made a mistake, and Vince
was gonna tell you but... I had...
Max!
Can I come, Max?
Max! Please let me explain...
where're you going, baby?
- To the meet.
- At 7 at night?
- I'll be there early.
- You can't leave me alone!
Does Roxanne know, you're gonna kill me?
Stay right there, ma'am!
How many of you?
I asked you a question!
I'm alone.
Easy, ma'am.
You found me, Mr. Policeman, it's about
time, I didn't think that you would.
- Everything is gonna be alright, David.
- Our life's are like stories, you know?
There is a beginning, a middle and an end.
That's Max's story, your story is
over here too, Mr. Policeman.
Don't you want to know how it ends?
Police suspects child is dead
Why haven't you told him about
the bodies in the basement?
Don't make things up.
There's nothing down there.
You believe me or her?
Not another step, lady!
Hey! Wait!... Open the door!
You're going away for a long time.
Open this door, lady!
You better do something, Roxanne...
can't have babies in prison.
This is your last chance. Open this door.
Last chance!
Go away, I killed that man.
- Roxanne, you had no choice.
- I didn't want him die.
Of course you didn't.
It's gone.
My whole life I had it.
What are you, David?
I'm an Angel.
The voices in your dreams, what did they tell you?
They said to kill Max... but I would never...
His soul, Roxanne, is going to hell.
No, baby, hell is not real, it's...
It's something parents frightened
their children with, there is no...
- such a place.
- Are you certain?
I've seen it, Roxanne.
The wicked, in eternal damnation.
- God will punish Max for his wickedness.
- Max isn't like that.
Not yet, but he wants to kill me.
- The death of an Angel...
- No, he would never.
Eternal damnation, Roxanne.
Please, David, I'll do anything.
Would you kill him?
To save his soul?
Would you kill him... for him?
While you decide, can you help me with
the fire? I'm too young to play with matches.
Sam! Go away from there.
Our business is nearly concluded.
I know you're watching me.
I'm not playing this game anymore.
Good, this is a business deal... you will hold up
your end, with a bullet in the back of his head.
That's not the deal I made.
How dare you hang up on me?
You had a bad 4 days with David, Max?
Try 8 years?
You're Jones?
There's enough here for more than just
a down payment, don't you think?
- I'm not gonna murder a little boy.
- That is the last thing he is.
Do you really think he is human?
We have something in common you and I... we both
let a wolf in our home and locked the door behind it.
When I adopted him, I thought
I'd have the life I always wanted.
But I had no idea, what he is capable of.
Or all the ways he can get to you.
I'll give up all I have to get rid of him.
He just gets inside your head and
he whispers these horrible thoughts...
and paints these visions you can't escape.
He is getting stronger, Max.
And I have no idea what he could be capable
of in a year or a week or even now...
and he's not gonna stop, until all of us are dead.
Who's watching him over right now?
He killed his own father. He killed his last nanny.
Do you not think he's going to kill her?
Listen to me, I'm begging you...
please, kill him.
You hired the wrong guy.
No, please.
I'm sorry.
Come on, come on... come on.
I'm sorry, you have reached a number...
Shhh... Do you hear that, Roxanne?
Hear what, baby?
Bad man coming.
Rox?
Rox!
What're you gonna do to, David?
Nothing.
Max, say you forgive me.
Of course I forgive you.
Hide, David!
Get the gun, Max.
Take the cop's gun.
Run.
Put the gun down, Rox.
We can get otta here and leave all of this behind us.
You.
David!
No!
Max!
For your soul, Max!
- David, come to me!
- Get otta here, Rox!
Over here.
Come and get me.
Look
Hey, Max.
Behind you.
Can't you see me?
Over here.
Nice shot, Max.
Good God, Rox!
You can't leave me.
Don't...
Rox... I'm sorry.
Rox!
Oh, no!
Ohh...
Oh... no, no, no.
I'm just getting started here.
Poor Roxanne... she thought I was an Angel.
You can't kill an Angel.
- A demon, maybe.
- Oh... what's a demon? One of the angel to fall.
Like you're gonna fall, Max...
Don't look so sad, killer.
You're on a winning team now.
No commandments. No guilt.
I was sent for those who're desperate.
I come to them when they're weak...
When their life’s are hopeless.
When those they love reject them.
I come to them, whisper into their ear,
and I can be very convincing.
Why, David?
- Why all this?
- Casting for souls, Max.
That's what I do.
And me?... What do I do?
You're as weak as the rest of them, so,
be a good boy and put the gun to your head.
Do it... or hear my voice every moment of your life.
It was a good game, Max.
Good game, Max... but it's not over.
Yeah, David... It is.
- Rox?
- You can't kill an angel, Max.
They will always be with you, Max.
Always.
Ho! Ho! Ho!
Merry Christmas! Ho! Ho!
Bless you... Merry Christmas.
Ho! Ho! Ho! Merry Christmas!