Our God is marching on
Glory, glory, hallelujah
His truth is marching on
In the beauty of the lilies
Christ was born across the sea
With a glory in His bosom
that transfigures you and me
As He died to make men holy,
let us die to make men free
While God is marching on
Glory, glory, hallelujah
His truth is marching on
Please be seated.
Chuck always said to me,
"Wilbur...
you talk too much".
So he'd be pleased
that his beloved daughter, Marie,
is going to say a few words.
I know that daddy
would be very pleased to see
so many veterans here today.
Especially members of
the 401st Bomber Group.
I guess he would want to talk
I guess he would want me
to talk about his life...
...and about the most
important thing in his life,
his love for my mother.
He was a brave man
in wartime in his lifetime,
and in the long illness
that led to his death.
But his was an unspoken bravery.
His heroism was as quiet
and as constant as he was.
Many loved him.
You don't smoke.
I thought I'd take it up again.
You should be in there, you know.
I know what she's gonna say.
I just can't sit there and
listen to all of that.
I understand.
Only you would understand.
I'm really sorry.
No need to.
It was his time to go.
No, I mean about being late.
I mean I'm sorry about that too,
I mean, about him...
It's all gassed up, dad.
It's ready to go.
Good.
Sure you want this?
He would.
You won't remember daddy
for what he said.
As you know, he didn't say much.
He never spoke to me
about the past,
about the war and
about his medals.
Not even once.
He felt that a man should be
judged for his work...
...and for the way
that he led his life.
Marie will be upset that you
missed her eulogy.
I don't think Marie cares
either way if I'm there.
Your husband was a fine man.
Yeah.
You'll miss him very much.
No.
Well, I know you loved him, so
He never believed that, Peter.
All the years I wore this ring
we never talked much about love.
Would you like me to
take you back inside?
No.
They'll roll him out
when they're through.
At least he has a grave.
Hello.
Bloody hell!
What the devil do you mean,
creeping up on me like that?
What you digging for?
Who the hell are you?
I'm Jimmy.
Eleanor Reilly's wee lad?
I know you.
She's my granny.
My mum went away
she is back any time now.
Does your granny know
you're up here?
Don't know.
Well, you go home
Tell her Mr Quinlan said you're
not to come up here again.
This is a dangerous place,
do you not know that?
The Army is here all the time.
If it's not them,
it's the Republicans,
the bloody IRA.
So what are you doing here then?
None of your bloody business!
You're digging something.
I dig here sometimes
for my granny.
I can keep a secret, you know.
You tell me one secret
you've ever kept.
My granny keeps photographs.
In her dressing-table.
You what?
From the war Americans.
And that's your secret, is it?
Yes.
Well, it's not any more,
you halfwit!
You just told me.
But you asked.
Do you want to spend your whole
life being a complete eejit?
No wonder your mammy buggered off.
Oh, shit!
Jimmy.
Come on, back up here.
Give me a hand
Come on
And listen don't you
tell your granny.
Promise... Cross my heart.
Yes.
What is it?
Treasure.
The past, boy.
The past.
That's a Harvard.
Here he comes.
That's Jack.
Is that your crazy father?
It's a tradition, Marie.
God, you're as stupid as he is.
Flies beautiful, doesn't it?
He could have killed us.
He's not allowed to fly that low.
Don't make a fuss, Marie.
It's exactly what your daddy
would have wanted.
Oh, really?
Is he doing it for daddy,
or is he doing it to impress you?
You don't know
what you're talking about.
Is he coming around again?
Oh, I certainly hope so.
You should take this.
There's a family trapped.
That's it.
One down, on the right.
Michael Quinlan,
where in God's name have you been?!
Get in that shelter right away!
Everybody outside, come on. Run!
Run!
No messing about, come on!
Eleanor.
Didn't expect to find you here.
Well, where did you
expect to find me?
Not usually with us.
In the Georgian Hotel with one of
your gentleman friends.
I do more for the war effort
than you, Mrs Doyle.
Making your woolly underwear
for the troops.
And you taking it off fast
as they can put it on.
Michael,
we missed you at evening Mass.
You'd have got here
in time for a seat.
Michael.
You're a big lad now.
Will you be joining the Army,
fighting for King and country?
No, I'm gonna
be a fireman like my Da.
You can sit here, Michael.
Can I sit there?
No.
We can't possibly mix
both congregations, Michael.
I'm forced to agree
with him there, Michael.
Cathal?
Sweet Jesus, is that you?
You're taking a chance,
aren't you?
Cathal, you'll
get yourself caught.
They've put
a reward out for you.
I don't care.
Here.
These are for you.
Look, I had to see you.
Eggs!
Dear God in heaven!
He has connections
over the border.
I thought you were away fighting
for the other side, Cathal Thomas.
He's right.
It's a dangerous place for you.
Is he fighting for the Germans?
IRA.
You should join us.
Don't you dare.
Thousands of good Catholic Irishmen
serving in the British Army,
fighting against Fascism
My son's one of them.
And you... you're a damned traitor.
Cathal.
I say, hello,
are you all right in there?
Hello?
You all right in there?
Cathal, no.
Don't!
We'll not say anything.
If he's a policeman,
I'll kill him!
He's a Brit.
He's Army, not police, Cathal.
He won't know you.
Hold the door.
Come on, Mr Cobb!
Hurry up!
Come on!
Hello?
The door is stuck.
Don't.
Don't say a word.
Evening.
Good evening, Officer.
Everyone all right?
Fine.
We're fine.
Do you think they've gone for
the night, sir?
I think so, but there may be
some unexploded stuff.
So best stay down here
till the all-clear
Could you pass the word.
We need an ambulance
in Market Street.
Four casualties.
I like your helmet.
What on earth is this?
Where did you get it?
Bloody thing is loaded!
Who gave this to you?
You little idiot, Quinlan.
What are you doing with that?
Belonged to his old Da.
From the last war.
Souvenir.
He'll scalp your arse, so he will.
I've got to confiscate this.
No need to tell the police,
though.
Sure, he's only a wee lad.
No.
No need.
Are the police up there now?
The local boys?
Afraid not.
Just my chaps from the barracks.
I'll come up and give you a hand.
Thanks.
Oh, Jesus.
Get the hell out of here, Cathal.
We should have given you up.
You could have, but you didn't.
None of you did.
Is this what we're looking for,
Mr Quinlan?
Just a piece of iron?
Aluminium.
From the fuselage.
Or the wings, maybe.
Biggest piece I ever found - B-17.
You know what that is?
Sure.
It's a rock group.
A band.
It's not a bloody band.
It's an airplane, you eejit.
Oh, right.
Crashed here.
50 years ago.
Ten people killed.
Blown to bits.
They've all forgotten,
but I remember.
You remember it crashing?
I heard it.
I lived down the bottom,
Murray Street.
Still do.
What do you do this for,
Mr Quinlan?
What are you looking for?
Why should I be
looking for anything?
Why do you dig all this up then?
Just shut up and
give me a hand here.
See if we can lift it.
Hey, Ethel Ann, come on.
But... okay.
Wilbur?
Oh, no.
Okay, chocks in and checked.
Come on out, sirs.
That was the most incredible
thing I've ever done!
Hello, fellas!
That was fantastic.
Jack, those B-17s are
just the greatest!
It's a piece of cake to fly, too.
Pilot showed us how.
Oh, sure.
You wanna take us up now then,
Chuck?
You know.
I feel like I could though,
you know.
You look swell, Ethel Ann.
Yeah, okay, come on.
Who wants a soda?
Let's go to Joe's.
But I thought you all had classes?
So, we skip one.
You'll get in trouble.
We're all gonna get in trouble,
there's a war coming!
Yes, trouble!
Big trouble!
So, it's supposed to be
the final approach...
...and we're thinking
something's wrong...
We're flying at the runway at,
God, 200 knots!
And the instructor says,
"Well, buddy... " well
...how about putting down
the flaps?".
And the pilot goes,
"Oh, shoot!".
And wham!
Puts down the flaps,
but he pulls back the stick
at the same time.
That airplane must have been
standing straight on its tail.
No, wait,
I saw you guys coming in.
You were like that was me.
Anybody want another soda?
No, thank you.
No, thanks, Jack.
I wish I'd been up there with
you I really wanna fly.
I don't think the Air Force
would like that.
You got any cash?
There's plenty of girl pilots.
Amelia Earhart.
Yeah.
But not in a B-17.
Not with a bunch of hairy
apes like us.
So what about pilot school?
Still going?
I don't know.
The other guys are okay,
but I got problems with math.
They won't stop me
from going up there.
Bombardier, gunner.
I don't care.
Nor do I,
so long as you're happy.
I'm happy.
I've never been so happy.
Seems the whole town is
in love with that girl.
Never thought she'd choose
the country boy.
Country boy?
I trust him with my life.
Don't worry, my lips are sealed.
Young love, huh?
Come on.
One hamburger and three fries.
Chuck
Come on, lover boy.
Come on, guys.
Marie.
Marie?
I guess you upset her.
Not hard to do.
Stupid tune.
Oh, come on,
they were great tunes.
I need a drink.
Steady, you've had a few already.
Why not?
I can have anything I want now.
Yeah.
What do you want, Ethel?
Go inside.
Well, at least let me
get the door for you.
I can get the door, thank you.
I've lived here long enough.
Well, just as you please.
This house.
Yeah.
Does seem kind of strange,
doesn't it?
Coming back to the house that he
built without him in it.
Yes.
Sure.
Jack, thank you for
the air raid and all.
My pleasure, girl.
Scared me half to death.
You ought to lose your licence.
Yeah, that's what the Sheriff said.
But I told him it was
an old tradition.
Class of June '42.
Go home, Jack.
What do you mean, now?
Yes, now.
Come on, dad.
Okay.
You won't forget
to do something for me,
will you, Ethel?
What's that?
Grieve.
Your father's picture
at the Air Academy.
Put it back, please.
Sorry.
You never talk about those times.
Neither did dad.
No.
Did you know a lot of these boys?
Yes, they were
a great bunch of guys.
We had some good times.
Could you tell me about it?
Could you tell me about them?
What you want to know
is whether I did it
with one of them and which one.
No.
Well, why not?
It's notjust a picture,
they were flesh and blood.
Okay, just forget it.
Have you been with Pete yet?
What?
Jack's boy, Pete.
Have you been with him yet?
Mom, what has gotten into you?
How much have you been drinking?
Time you got something
for yourself, Marie.
Life is passing you by.
Peter is a nice guy.
I'm just not ready.
But you must never,
ever let a man build you a house.
No.
As long as you stay there,
he'll stay with you.
You may try to hide him
but he'll be there, inside it.
Why don't you try it with Peter?
Would you stop talking about sex?
You shouldn't be thinking about
that right now.
Really?
Well, what the hell else
should I be thinking about?
Daddy! We just buried him!
Yes.
Right.
I guess this means I won't be
getting any any more, huh?
I'm sorry, sweetheart.
Me, too.
Your father was a fine man.
I guess I should be
grateful to him.
Grateful?
The boys at the Academy I didn't.
I mean, it wasn't like that.
I was faithful.
I was always always,
always, always faithful.
So, how do you say three
I's in Spanish?
I, ya, ya.
It's so big.
He had his cousins
helping him over the winter.
But they're back at the farm now,
so we're helping him finish it.
That's it.
Good morning.
Morning.
Teddy around?
Back at the house.
Thank you.
It's beautiful.
He's sure been working hard.
Hey!
I wasn't expecting you so soon.
I fell asleep upstairs.
You've framed out
the upstairs already?
Sure have, I there's
so much more to do though.
Could you guys help me
bring up the latest delivery?
That pile up by the road?
Yeah.
Sure
Yeah, we can do that for you.
Come on, Chuck.
Jack, these are my best clothes.
Come on.
How come you've told me
so little about this place?
It's no secret.
Where did you
get the money for it?
My dad left
me this piece of land.
A little cash.
I worked in a sawmill last summer,
and they they paid me in lumber.
I wanna look upstairs.
I thought you told me you were
away getting an education?
That was it, I guess.
I read books, too.
Place is solid.
Building up to a standard,
not down to a price,
is what the lumber guy said.
Oh, I'll bet he did.
Hey, buzzard.
He's around here all the time
Keeps me company.
You've almost moved in.
Yeah.
I may be running out of time.
What do you mean?
The war I guess.
So it's gonna come, then?
That's why we all
joined the Air Academy.
Why are you doing all this?
Your folks wouldn't
like me one bit.
But when I do ask them,
I've gotta have something I can show.
Something I can give you.
You're building this house for me?
If I get into the Air Force
become a Sergeant maybe, then
that'd be something.
And then I could ask your folks.
I'd be some kind of gentleman.
You are a gentleman, Teddy.
I sure don't smell like one just now.
Let me try.
Excuse me?
Let me smell you.
Are you kidding?
No.
I wanna remember you.
Just as you are now.
Don't move.
I wanna remember
this moment all my life.
Teddy, Ethel Ann?
No.
Teddy?
Come on, Chuck... Let's go.
You're so beautiful.
Sometimes I can still smell it.
What?
Aviation fuel.
That was 50 years ago.
And you said it burnt.
Some soaked into the ground,
maybe.
I can't smell it,
but, look, I found this.
What is it?
Granny says
I shouldn't mix with you.
You promised me
you wouldn't tell her.
She says you're worse
than a Protestant.
What's worse than a Protestant?
An atheist.
Mr Quinlan, what we're doing,
is it illegal?
Probably.
Only there's a man over there.
Do we stop digging?
Turn away, don't look at him.
He'll not bother us.
You took your time, Cathal.
Mr Thomas to you
There was no need
for you to be here.
Just an observer.
Do they think I can't
run my own operation?
Why did they change the target?
Wouldn't want to
lose support community.
And we have interests in that area.
You mean you're
selling drugs there.
Beautiful view
Who is the old man?
He's digging up an airplane.
It crashed here.
And you let him do it?
I know him.
Digging on Black Mountain
is a bad idea.
Never know what you'll find.
What I gave you, what is it?
It's very good.
A switch... Radio, maybe.
Intercom.
I'll get it home,
do some research.
I found that, you know
By rights it's mine.
Shankhill Road.
Yes.
You're an atheist then?
You don't believe in God and
the Blessed Virgin Mary
and all that stuff?
No.
Why not?
30 years of being
a fireman in Belfast.
Clearing up after that lot.
Will there be a second one?
There's always a second one.
That's the one does the damage.
They wait until the Army get there,
or the police.
Or the bloody firemen.
There.
It's ready.
Last time a man used this switch
was 50 years ago.
And that man was killed.
Right here, in this very spot.
Here, you found it, you do it.
No, thanks.
Why not?
Don't want to.
All right
I will.
Jesus.
What the hell was that?!
It's too bloody soon!
It was supposed to be
set for 20 minutes.
Maybe just as well.
High Command thinks that bombs
may be a little old-fashioned.
"Counter-productive at this stage
of the struggle. "
Counter-bollocks!
It's a war we're fighting here
Yes that we are.
And maybe you're
losing it for us, Cathal.
Have you thought of that?
We have suffered a serious
setback in Hawaii.
Many American soldiers and sailors
have been killed by enemy action.
American ships have been sunk,
American airplanes
have been destroyed.
The lives of our soldiers and
sailors depend upon the manner
in which each and every one of us
fulfills his obligation to
our country.
Gunnery School?
Yeah.
Well, when do you go?
Next week.
Chuck is training as a pilot.
Jack is gonna be a navigator,
and they need gunners, so that's me.
I have to go.
So it's over, then?
All this.
Oh, no.
I'm gonna send postcards home
every day.
My folks think I'm walking out
with Chuck.
Good old reliable Chuck.
If they only knew it was you.
Well, I'm not gonna send them
to your folks' house, Ethel Ann.
I'm gonna send them here I mean,
when any of us guys get leave
we're gonna come back here,
we're gonna finish the house.
I can put a telephone in.
What are those places in college,
where everybody stays
like brothers?
Fraternity.
Okay, well, this will be
our fraternity house.
Chuck can get away
from his parents
and Jack can get away from
all of his girlfriends
and we can be together.
I mean, this is your home.
It can't be my home without you.
When I'm through Gunnery School,
they'll give me some leave.
You could marry me.
We could do it secret,
but when I'm back for good,
we'll do it proper,
we'll invite everybody.
Is that all right?
Ethel Ann, say it's all right.
It's gold.
I love you.
I guess I'm just not used to
feeling so much.
I will always love you, Teddy.
I'll be yours till the day I die,
I swear it.
There won't be room for anyone
else in my heart but you.
No-one else, not ever.
Till I'm laid in my grave.
I love you.
Mom, are you all right?
What are you doing in my room?
This is not your room.
What do you mean?
I'm moving back into this room.
But you and daddy were always
in the other room, you
Okay, if you want my room,
that's fine.
I understand.
Mom, why don't you come to
the grave with me today?
It's a beautiful grave.
We can just be there together
with him.
Who?
Dad, of course.
Your father, he was a fine man.
He saved my life, actually.
You know, picked me up
put me back together.
Always treated me right.
He was a fine man,
he was a good husband.
Is that what you want?
No, what I want is for you to
start grieving like everyone else.
Grieving I was 21 years old.
My life was over.
You don't know what grieving is.
21?
What do you mean?
It's none of your business.
That was before you married daddy.
Before I was born.
What happened?
I am going to
move in here tonight.
This is my house,
and if you don't like it,
you can leave.
So leave.
Hi.
Have a seat.
Can I get you something?
No, thanks.
Peter, would you mind
giving us a minute?
Sure.
Thanks.
Sorry.
When I was a kid,
this was the Soda Fountain.
Your Ma used to come here
all the time.
She loved those disgusting
root beer floats.
Her life was over at 21
That's what she said.
I'm trying to understand, Jack.
What happened to her?
The war happened,
for Christ's sake.
And the kids she knew,
some of them didn't make it back.
Yeah, but you did, and dad did.
Yeah, that's right.
He was shot up in a B-17,
she nursed him back to health
she put him back together.
No, she said that he
put her back together.
Well, they helped each other.
All right,
so they helped each other.
But what happened?
She said her life was over, Jack.
Hi, Jack.
Oh, hi.
Look let me give you
a piece of advice.
If I were you,
I wouldn'tjust come in here
and start digging around.
The past has gone.
Digging around?
What am I supposed to do?
Pretend that nothing is wrong?
You don't understand what
it's like at home without dad.
I knew Chuck for 50 years.
For 40 of them, he sat right
there where you are now.
Don't tell me I don't understand.
And if your
Ma doesn't want to talk to you
that's none of my business, is it?
So get the hell out of here.
And that's just
what she told me to do.
Hey, you okay?
I'm sorry.
What did you say to her?
Too much.
Not enough.
Hi, granny.
You know, I made you your tea.
And it's gone stone-cold,
and I had to give it to the cat.
No, not more of
that filthy stuff!
Please, don't do that.
Oh, no, Jimmy.
At least use your own blade.
Don't be using my good knife.
In fact, I wish you wouldn't
go up that mountain at all,
do you know that?
Because things go on there
that you shouldn't be
poking your wee nose into.
What things?
Just things, son.
And I wish you wouldn't mess
around with that Quinlan fella.
He said he knew you
when you were young.
Never, never, never!
He's a born liar, that fellow.
Always was.
So you did know him, then?
If you spent more time
looking for ajob...
Don't be stupid, granny.
Don't you call me stupid!
I've worked all my life.
There are no jobs.
Then go to London,
find your mother.
And that pimp she ran away with.
And clean that up after you,
will you?
And don't use the sink again.
This is not a hotel.
This is me who has to keep
this place clean, young man.
I'm not spending my life
cleaning after you
Ethel.
Ethel and Teddy.
Teddy?
Looking sharp.
You ready?
I'm ready.
Want a beer?
We got it all worked out.
Great.
Jack stole the key.
I borrowed it.
This place looks great.
Nice job setting it up.
Yeah, I thought I'd bring
her straight back here, you know?
Carry her across the threshold.
Sure.
Be out of your way.
Oh, no.
Me and Ethel Ann,
we don't want that.
I mean this is the last time
we're gonna have to spend together
before we leave.
And you're both officers, right?
So I'm not gonna be able to
talk to you after this.
Yeah, you will.
We got plans.
We're gonna fly together
in the same plane.
There's no there's no
chance of that.
Yes, there is.
I've been dating this girl down
in Personnel Administrations.
I can pull some strings.
Yep, we can fly together.
No?
What do you mean, no?
I've been working on
this girl for weeks.
Well, I mean,
what if we didn't come back?
All three of us in one B-17.
Jesus Christ, Teddy.
No.
Okay?
We are not all flying
in one plane.
If I don't make it through this
I gotta know
that there's somebody
to look after Ethel Ann.
To take my place.
There's no-one could do that,
Teddy.
Oh, really?
So I'm the only person
in this room
that's in love with Ethel Ann?
What are you talking about?
No, I mean,
I think she's a great girl.
She's wonderful.
But, no!
You're not in love with her?
No, I'm not!
All right.
But Chuck is.
God, Teddy, I...
It's okay, buddy.
It's okay.
She's yours, Teddy.
I never I would never,
ever, I swear.
She doesn't know, she never will.
Chuck... shut up.
It's just practical.
I need to know that there'll be
someone to look after her.
What about Jack?
Jack?
Whoa, no.
Guys, I'm not that kind of guy.
He's already got girls
in every state.
I drink, I smoke, I belch.
And he can't dance.
I can't dance.
You're the dancer.
You're the guy.
This isn't even gonna happen.
You're gonna come back,
you're gonna have seventeen kids.
You're gonna gonna
find a nice girl from Idaho.
She'll be a potato.
In a sack.
So it's all right then
if I can fix it
for you and I to fly together?
Jack, that would be great.
Teddy, I never
I know.
I know that, Chuck.
But if something happens to me,
you gotta care for Ethel Ann.
Promise me.
I promise.
Jack, you promise to help?
Sure I promise.
You guys believe in God?
Yes.
I don't know.
No, me neither.
Let's say a prayer.
Dear God...
tomorrow we're leaving for combat.
And today I'm getting married.
Both of which are pretty dangerous.
Oh, hi.
Jack.
Maybe you were expecting Pete.
No.
I guess you haven't seen
each other for a while, huh?
Jeez, that music is loud!
Yeah, it is.
She's not going out any more,
not even to dad's grave.
She's drinking,
she's cutting everyone off.
Well, you are, too.
Pete misses you, you know.
For God's sakes, Jack,
I like Peter,
but now is not the time.
Okay... Sure.
Front bedroom.
She won't sleep in her
and daddy's room any more.
She's moved into mine.
The front room?
She's moved back in there?
What do you mean, back?
That was always my room.
They were always in the other one.
Jack?
Look
Answer the phone, Marie,
and give her these, please.
I'll come back some other time.
Jack?
Jack
Hello?
Is that America?
Is this ajoke?
No, wait.
It's all right, I got through.
So maybe you'll finish
before midnight!
Could I speak to Mrs Gordon,
please?
You've got the wrong number.
No, I mean, sorry, I mean
Mrs Roberts.
Mrs Ethel Roberts.
That was my mother's name
before she was married.
Who is this?
My name is Jimmy.
Could I speak to her?
About what?
I'm calling from Belfast and
I don't have a lot of money.
All right, just a minute.
Pennsylvania 6-5000
Mom?
Yes.
There's a phone call for you.
Will you pick up the phone?
No, thanks, sweetheart.
Mom?
No, thank you.
It's a man, says he's from Belfast.
Mom?
Pennsylvania 6-5000
She doesn't wanna answer,
you'll have to leave a message.
Hello?
Can you hear me?
Now, just a minute, please.
Mom?
Hello?
Did you pick up?
Who is this, please?
My name is Jimmy Reilly.
I'm calling from Belfast.
Could I speak to Ethel.
I'm sorry, I'm not sure
what her name is now.
Marie?
Marie, you can hang up now,
please.
Okay.
They told me she
wouldn't have the same address,
not after 50 years
but I thought I'd try anyway.
Are you there?
What do you want?
I have something
belonging to you.
Well, I think it belongs to you.
It's a ring.
A gold ring.
It's got names on the inside.
A ring?
Yeah
It says 'Ethel and Teddy'.
Hello?
Can you hear me?
Oh, bugger!
Wait a minute
wait wait there.
Please, do you have any money?
I do, and I've a mind to use it
if you would get
the frig out of there!
Oh God.
Look, listen to me,
I'll call you back.
Okay?
Hello?
I'll call you back.
Bugger.
Sorry, America.
Long distance.
You could have walked there
in that time!
I wish he would.
Mr Quinlan?
It's me.
Bloody hell!
It's 6.30 in the morning!
Please, I need a phone.
It's really urgent.
I found something.
Well, it wasn't your brains,
was it?
Go to hell!
I found a ring!
On the mountain.
A gold ring.
It belonged to one of the crew.
It's got names on it.
I went to the library
and they told me
to call
the Veterans Administration
only I had to keep calling,
and it cost a packet.
And when my granny found out,
she went apeshit.
So, I had to use the phone box
and call America,
but I ran out of money,
and that was last night,
and I have to call her back!
Who?
Ethel.
The name on the ring
You wanna see it?
No, I don't.
I don't want it.
Get out.
Get out!
Mr Quinlan.
Are you all right?
So, you found it.
You stupid bugger!
Doesn't mean a damn thing to you,
but you found it!
And then what do you do?
After 50 years, you just call her
up out of the blue!
"Oh, guess what I've got!"
Well, I thought she'd be pleased.
Only, I was halfway through,
and I ran out of money.
What do you want me
to do about that?
Well, I just wanted to
use your phone.
Get inside
Come on.
I don't believe it!
This is incredible.
All this stuff.
Don't touch it.
This is fantastic!
Phone is there.
Go on.
And be quick.
Three six nine two?
Yes, who is it?
Gander?
Do you know anyone in Gander?
Yeah, it's an airbase.
Teddy!
Yes, I'll pay!
Teddy?
See you Jack.
Ethel Ann?
No, it's not Teddy, it's Jack.
Sorry.
Jack, hi!
How are you?
Oh, it's so good to
hear from you.
Where the heck is Gander?
Newfoundland.
Well, what's it like up there?
Raining.
Are you on your own?
No, Chuck got back a week ago.
He hurt himself,
but he's okay now.
Hey, you should see me
in my nurse's uniform.
I'm training to be a nurse.
Chuck says I look great.
I bet you do.
It's so good to hear from you.
Have you spoken to Teddy?
Is he okay?
The last I saw him, he was good,
but I broke my ankle.
Yeah.
I was dancing.
So, I'm coming home on leave.
Jack, you're crazy!
He broke his ankle in a dance.
Hey, can I talk to Chuck?
Yeah.
He wants to talk to you.
But then I wanna talk to
you again, okay?
Here.
Thanks.