Ron clark.
Ready for
your first day?
Yes, ma'am.
I'll be with you
in a minute.
And i'll introduce
you to your class.
[Sighs]
Hi.
What happened
to you?
Teacher says
i can't learn,
so i should go out
with the trash.
Woman: Ok, settle down.
Let's get out
our silent reading.
I'm mr. Clark.
What's your name?
Hadley craig.
Nice to meet you.
Uh, you know,
i'm so sorry.
I'm so forgetful.
What's
my name again?
It's mr. Clark.
Oh. See? You just
learned something.
Let's get you
out of there.
Mr. Clark?
Yeah.
Is you gonna be
our new teacher?
Woman: Alan,
no whispering.
Get the chairs!
My hair!
Get the jell-o mold!
Bill,
grab the other table.
[Indistinct shouting]
We'll arrive
at swan quarter by 5:00,
like we always do.
Woman:
Mr. Clark, hi!
Pick up the shrimp bait
at the general store
like we always do,
and hop the ferry
over to ocracoke island
for some fine
flounder fishing.
Like we always do.
[Tapping]
Woman: Well, folks,
it's not quite
the end of the year
summer celebration
we expected,
but let's take a moment
to thank our own mr. Clark,
whose fifth grade class
tested number one
in beaufort county
for the fourth year
in a row!
[Cheering]
We have a surprise
that we have put
together for you.
Unfortunately,
it's outside.
Oh, man!
[Indistinct chatter]
Oh!
[Laughing]
Y'all know
mr. Clark began here
as a temporary teacher.
Well, we've all chipped
in on something
to help him feel
more permanent.
Aww.
[Cheering]
[Thunder]
I love it here,
but i've got
to move on, mom,
before they use
that parking space
for my grave.
New york public schools
are desperate
for good teachers.
The newspaper says
they're beggin'
for them.
Dad, every year,
i tell my students
to go for what
they want in life.
Dream big. Take risks.
It's time
i started living up
to my own words.
Mrs. Clark: Ohh.
I'm gonna miss you guys,
but i gotta go.
We understand,
sweetie.
Good-bye.
People get killed
in new york.
Announcer, on radio:
This is radio roanoke,
where the sun
is shining
and the temperature
is 78 degrees.
* and the night sounds
start to whisper *
announcer, on radio:
News and sports in 5, baltimore,
but now let's get ready
to rock 'n' roll
with the smokin'...
announcer, on radio:
That was the mellow midnight
voice of johnny hartman.
This is wnyc,
in new york city.
Next up, something cool
on a hot night.
[Mellow jazz playing]
[Car horn honking]
Come on, pal!
Get outta the way!
Ron: Ok. Sir...
come on! I'm tryin'
to park here!
Rent's due at 10:00.
Cash only.
Checkout's at 11:30.
Ok. This is great.
And, uh,
what's your name?
Yolanda.
Thank you, yolanda.
Hi!
[Neighbors arguing]
[Grunts]
[Sighs]
New york.
[Sirens wailing]
Good morning.
Goorning.
Yolanda, good morning.
Do you have a list
of the public schools
in harlem?
Sure i do, baby.
Ok. Thank you.
Why you want school
listings for?
I'm a teacher.
And you wanna teach?
Up in harlem?
Yes.
Well, then, honey,
you gonna need
something else.
Personal injury
lawyers.
'Cause once
your white behind
goes on up in there,
they'll be carrying
you back out
the same way
you went in.
What kind
of foolishness is this?
Goin' on up there
to harlem, tryin'
to teach. You know...
ok. Thank you.
Taxi!
Right here!
It's this way, son.
Thank you so much
for coming in.
Y-you're welcome.
If you could just look
at my resum?
I apologize.
We just don't have
a position available.
Yeah, but all my kids
ed above grade level.
I'm sure they did.
And good luck to you.
[Laugh track]
Ma'am, you forgot
your purse.
Thank you.
Dinner was great.
You're welcome.
Thanks.
[British accent]
So, my merry men
and ladies,
let us steal
from the rich
and help a poor, brave
waiter go henceforth
into the kitchen
and command
your dinners.
Nice hat. It distracts
the customers
from that accent.
Hey, watch out.
I got a bow and arrow.
What show are you in?
Everybody works here
is an actor.
I'm a teacher.
You are
gonna change before
your first class, right?
Very funny.
How about you?
Me? Oh, i'm taking
a break from acting.
The cleopatra gig
is very challenging.
Hey, who's that?
That's
the queen of egypt.
In love
with mark antony.
No, i...
i mean, uh,
who is that?
Marissa.
And she's
even more beautiful
out of costume.
I'm jason.
Otherwise known as...
mark antony.
Sorry.
It happens
all the time, bro.
Don't sweat it.
Table 5
sent it back!
[Siren]
Oh, man!
Get back
in that classroom!
Hey! Hey!
Come on, you little...
hey, come on, man!
Hey! Hey!
Enough!
Tayshawn mitchell,
my office. Now!
I'm not playin'
with ya, son.
I ain't no son.
Mr. Solis,
what the hell was that?
That boy is your student.
Not anymore.
Hey, you walk away,
you stay away.
You can have
the little bastards.
I could start
right now.
Heh.
You're lucky
you got detention
and not
an assault charge.
Hello. I'm ron clark.
I wanted to let you know
i taught sixth grade
for 4 years
in north carolina.
You need a teacher.
I need a job,
so let's help
each other out.
Mr. Clark, i'm sure
you're very sincere,
but i'm afraid
you might be
a little too...
too what?
Too white? Too tall?
Too ugly?
Nice.
I specialize in raising
standardized test scores.
Principal: This is
the honors class.
These students scored in
the top 10 percentile on
the state exams every year.
We divide each grade
into 4 classes
according to their
achievement scores.
What about this class?
This class tested
at the bottom
of the entire new york city
school district.
They do seem
a little bit
squirrelly.
Oh, they're a bit more
than squirrelly.
These students
have problems
with learning,
discipline,
social skills.
Like tayshawn mitchell.
2 strikes, going on 3,
toward the juvenile
detention center.
I'm your man.
I have an opening
in grade 3.
If your credentials
check out...
hey, you have
an opening right here.
No.
Last year, this class
went through
6 different teachers
before christmas.
Yes. Nobody wants them,
and i do,
so what's the problem?
Test scores are
very important to me.
It's how i keep my job.
I can start right now.
You can start on monday.
State exams are in may.
Woman: You are
out of control!
Boy: Yo, man!
[Folk music playing]
Let's come back here
tomorrow.
I think
she liked me.
High-five, bro.
On a break.
Oh! Grr!
Aah!
200 bucks!
And nothing!
Jeez! You should have
heard them in there!
Oh, cleo, we got
your snake right here.
And then
they just stiff me!
Want half?
Yeah, sure.
You're
a teacher, clark.
What is it?
I mean, why don't guys
grow up?
Ooh, i'm afraid
my level of expertise
expires
at the sixth grade.
You got a job?
Inner harlem elementary.
I'm gonna start meeting
my kids tomorrow.
Uh, you might want
to hold on to this.
It may be
your last meal.
Nah. They're
gonna love me.
[Tango playing]
I like to meet
all the parents,
ms. Vazquez,
before i start teaching.
Julio?
To get them involved.
Uh...
julio!
Damn it.
Where is he?
He a clown, mr. Clark,
but he's a good boy.
I had him
when i was only 14.
That's ok.
Like...
like i was saying...
what?
[Loud]
I was just saying...
[lowers volume]
[Normal]
You can help out
by working with
julio every night
on his homework.
Sure. Ok.
Together, we can
get him excited
about learning.
American history...
[laughs softly]
Solar system,
pre-algebra.
I just want julio
to achieve
his full potential.
So, mr. Clark...
are you married?
No.
It's very nice to meet
you all today.
You know, i've never had
a student from india before.
How do you
pronounce your name?
Bad-rl-yah.
I like to read,
especially...
quiet, larki.
Men are talking, ok?
[Hip-hop music playing]
* what's that? *
* they don't need no... *
[baby crying,
dog barking]
Shameika wallace?
I'm mr. Clark,
your new teacher.
I called earlier.
It's saturday, fool.
Woman: Shameika,
who is it?
Nobody.
[Children yelling]
Oh, are those
your brothers?
No. They're my kids.
I'm 12 years old,
and i got 3 kids.
Woman: Who are you
talkin' to?
I'm mr. Clark,
shameika's
new teacher.
What the hell happened
to mr. Solis?
Fool quit.
He's wet.
I swear to god,
you teachers come in
and out of the school.
Yeah, i know that.
That... that's
why i'm here.
I was hoping you
would work with me.
I already got
a job, mister.
I got 2 jobs
and 4 kids
and a brother on parole.
I'm late for work.
* test it, gonna make
a man out of you *
* yeah, i get you to scream and
demandin' respect with a left *
* how can i respect you? *
* get another hand on my rhymes,
makin' you drop *
* this other dawg, here's
another shot to the soul *
* tell me what can i do
at 13 years old? *
* gonna lay your hand
on my child *
* go on, come and get me *
* but by then,
i come crunk wild style *
* and then i try
to hold the kids back *
* 'cause they gave me
satisfaction *
* to hear me askin'
and bangin' *
* please, drop down
on your knees *
* and you knowin' that it's
gonna be a while
with the demon... *
[jeering
and teasing]
* but you can never get,
so can bet *
* that i'm comin'
to make a man out of you yet *
* shadowboxer *
* just a shadowboxer *
boy: Punk ass!
[bell ringing]
Woman: Hey, that's enough.
Morning.
Get moving.
Nice to see you,
tayshawn.
Morning,
principal turner.
Ok. Good morning.
Oh! Hello.
I'm ron clark.
I guess i'll be...
teaching...
[bell]
Yo, man, you know
you owe me $5.00.
Anyway, so like...
no! I know!
She said all that stuff!
Oh, she is...
yeah, dream big
about what?
Big butts?
Oh, ho ho!
Dream about yo mama.
All: Whoa!
Take your seats.
Girl:
Yo, teacher.
Shameika's feeling
sick today.
Yeah, sick
of damn teachers.
Tell him, chica!
Ok, because this is
our first day,
i have a surprise
for all of you.
What?
I'll tell you, julio,
if you turn around.
Today, there will be
no schoolwork.
[Bang]
Shameika, don't do that.
Shameika, don't.
Or what?
What are you gonna
do? Suspend me?
Go ahead.
Suspend me.
I wanna leave!
Student: We all
wanna leave.
Me, too.
Hey, look. The fool's
leavin' already.
[Laughing]
[Slam]
[Loudly]
Sit down.
You see this?
This means
that this year
is going to be
different.
This year is going to be
about more than school.
This year, we are going
to be a family.
But you don't look
nothin' like me.
[All laughing]
I'm going to be
your family,
and you are going
to be my family,
and that means
that i am not leaving,
and you are not leaving.
[Bang]
You have
any lip gloss?
Yeah.
Ha ha ha.
Bathroom.
[Sweeping]
[Car alarms blaring]
Boy: No, shoot it!
[Bell rings]
What the hell?
Come on.
What?
Ohh!
Whoa.
Nasty.
Yo...
well, what do
you think?
We think
it looks stupid.
Who vandalized
this room?
I did, sir.
Mr. Clark...
this sort of stunt
may have gone over big
in aurora,
but it doesn't work
for me.
My school.
My rules.
My way.
Students: Ooh.
[Bell]
Lunch!
All right.
I need... ohh!
Put your gum
in here.
Gum in here.
Hurry up!
All the gum
in this jar,
the gum jar.
Come on.
I'm starving.
Right in here.
Hey! No,
i see you. Come on.
Right in there.
Thank you. Thank you.
Thank you.
Ok. To you
left. More left.
[Bump]
They're
just testing you.
They want to see
if you really care.
See if i care?
They weren't even
looking at me.
Well, one of them was,
but i think
he was picturing me
in a dark alley.
We have to turn this...
ow!
[Grunts]
Do these legs come off?
All right.
I think it looks
good right there.
You know, school's
supposed to be exciting.
Ok.
Now you sound like one
of those dumb-ass
commercials
that used to come on
at the cartoons
on saturday morning.
So, what? You didn't
like school?
School sucked.
I hated it.
Yeah, well,
if i was your teacher,
you would have
loved it.
[Grunts]
Marissa: Ron,
just relax.
Step away
from the table.
Yeah, that's what
s doing.
[Chuckles]
So, now that you
helped me move,
i guess i have to be
your drive-you-
to-the-airport,
feed-your-fish,
never-forget-
your-birthday
kind of friend.
Uh, not to mention
my cover-my-weekend-shift-
because-i'm-going-
to-l.a. -with-jason friend.
He's going to meet
some producers.
You know, he's trying
to get on a daytime
heartthrob thing.
So, how long
you two been
going out?
Almost 2 years.
Oh.
I mean, we're not
living together
or anything.
He's busy. I'm busy.
But it's good.
Yeah,
it sounds good.
All right.
Well, we got 3 hours
before our shift.
Who's hungry?
Oh, so, you're
a union mover.
This is gonna cost
me a pizza, huh?
Can i have
your attention, please?
Before we start today,
i would like to go over
3 rules for this class.
If you follow them,
we will all have
a lot of fun.
All right!
If you do not follow them,
there will be consequences.
All: Ooh!
You all remember
rule number one...
we are a family.
Give me
a damn break, man.
We're not in kindergarten!
That means we help
each other out,
we stand up for each other,
we defend each other.
Girl: Sure!
Rule number 2...
we respect each other.
[All talking at once]
Hey, you will
call me sir.
Not man, not dawg,
not fool.
If you are asked
a question,
you will say, "yes, sir,"
or, "no, sir,"
not, "yep," "nope,"
"uh-uh," "nuh-uh."
Uh, nuh-uh, fool.
Respect, julio vazquez.
You will not talk
unless i call on you.
If i am talking,
you are listening with
your eyes right here.
Rule number 3...
we will form a line
to enter and exit class
and go to lunch.
Come on!
Are you kidding me?
Shameika.
What?
"What, sir?"
Oh, shameika,
thank you.
For what?
Reminding me about
rule number 4...
no smacking of lips
and rolling of the eyes.
If you break one
of these rules,
your name will
go up on the board.
So stupid!
If you break
another rule,
you will get a check.
[Class groaning]
Come on.
If you break
a third rule...
all: Ohhh!
Hey.
Hi.
What you reading?
Nothing.
Oh, i didn't read
that book till high school.
Julio: You figure that,
by seventh, man,
the odds are 10 to 1.
That's big bucks, man.
That's big bucks!
What's julio doing?
Say, man, i don't know why
you're going for the 24th.
Taking bets...
on you.
On me?
When you're
gonna quit.
My sister say he's gonna
be gone by friday.
Gambling is
illegal, especially
when you're 12.
And by the way,
i'm not leaving.
Yo, come on, dawg!
How am i supposed
to make some paper
around here?
Boy, something smells
really good in here.
Could i ask a favor
of you ladies?
Sure.
I just wanted to,
uh, know if...
dr. King talked
about justice
rollin' down
like waters...
here, pass these
around, guys...
and righteousness
like a mighty stream.
It's like on a hot day
when you go outside,
and "whoosh!" somebody
opens up a fire hydrant,
and there's water
streaming all over
the place!
And everybody's runnin'
around and going crazy.
That's what dr. King
wanted justice and
freedom to feel like.
So, tonight, after
we've gone over
dr. King's speech,
i want you all
to start a journal
about your dreams
and aspirations.
[Bell rings]
Hey, man,
it's locked!
What's up?
Rule number 3... we all lin up
to go to the lunch room.
[Class groaning]
You know what?
Here's my rule...
i ain't standin'
in no line.
Oh, ok, shameika.
But because we are
all a family,
if one of us
doesn't get in line
for the lunch room,
then none of us
gets lunch.
[All shouting at once]
I'm starving!
Mr. Clark!
We're starving!
Shameika,
just do it.
I'm hungry.
Yeah.
[Sighs]
Very quietly,
2 lines, right up
against the wall.
That's good.
Nice and quiet.
Oh, looks like
somebody's not hungry.
Stop fighting. Let's go.
No talking.
And stop.
Shameika, did you
cut in line?
No, sir. I did not.
You do know that
i have eyes
in the back
of my head, right?
I was here! Ask her.
Stupid...
all right, we're all
gonna stand here
until shameika decides
to tell the truth.
Come on, mr. Clark!
What?
I didn't cut
in no line!
Hey, you're in mr. Clark's
class. No food.
Huh?
Yo, come on, mr. Clark,
i'm starving, man!
I'm about to faint,
i'm fallin' down...
julio, get to the back
of the line.
And take that hat off.
It's up to you
whether we eat or not.
Shameika,
this is a family,
and families treat
each other with respect.
They never, ever,
lie to one another.
Did you cut in line?
Come on, meka!
Come on. Let's go!
We are all
just waiting...
on you.
Yeah.
Thank you.
Now, what is
rule number 5?
All: No cutting
in line.
That's right.
Now go eat.
About time!
I'm proud of you.
Thanks a lot,
shameika.
Uh-huh. Yes, mom,
i miss you, too.
Yeah, i know there's
a job for me back home,
but, uh, things are
going very well here.
Well, it took the kids
a little while
to warm up to me. Yeah.
Honestly, we're
getting along great.
I want you all to take
a good look around
at your new, clean room.
Whatever.
I'm not going to ask
who wrecked it.
Eyes right here.
I was hoping we could
have fun this year,
and i think
that we still can,
but only after you learn
to follow all of my rules.
[Smacks gum]
And you will follow
all of my rules.
[All smacking gum]
First of all,
he a freak.
"Take your seats,
call me sir."
Too many damn rules,
man.
Telling us how to do
this and do that,
making us walk around
in a damn line.
He ain't my daddy.
He could be your daddy.
You don't know.
You should talk, girl.
Excuse me.
Shut up.
All i'm saying is,
this is our school,
all right?
We do what we wanna.
Yeah, 'cause he's just
gonna leave anyways.
That's what you said
last week, girl.
He's still here.
You wait. He going.
Badriyah: I hope not.
What?
I like mr. Clark.
That's 'cause you
from a foreign country,
and you don't know
how we do here.
How... do we do?
Do like us, baby.
You want to be like us,
you gotta do like we do.
Come on.
* yo, yo, let's go,
let's go *
all: * yo, yo,
let's go, let's go *
* hey, hey,
ron clark, let's go *
* go, go, yo,
yo, yo, yo *
* yo, yo, yo,
* strawberry shortcake *
* cream on top *
* tell me the name
of your sweetheart *
* is it a? *
* b-c-d-e... *
that's really good.
Shameika, you're
really good at this!
[All shouting]
Hey! Hey!
Come on!
Go to your seat!
Come here.
What?
Yeah, go to
your room, julio!
Hey, who's talking to you?
Was i talking to you?
You gonna hit me?
No.
But you did break
rule number 2.
"You gonna hit me, sir?"
[All laughing]
Hey, get off me, dawg!
You think that's funny?
Shameika, you're in charge.
All: What?
Tayshawn!
Look, don't do this! Hey!
Look, i know
you have 2 strikes.
You walk out now,
they'll expel you
for sure.
Just get back in there.
Why?
Because i would
miss your glowing
personality.
Mr. Turner
doesn't have to know
anything about this.
Just...
give yourself
another chance.
[Exhales]
Hey. You still cool
with helping me
move to my new address
on saturday?
Yes, definitely.
I mean, jason
would help,
but you've
got the fly
blue car, so...
this is supposed
to be well done.
It is well done.
What are you talking
about? It's rare.
Fine, i'll burn it.
Just take out the rest
of the order.
I know how to do my job.
Congratulations.
On what?
Officially becoming
a new yorker.
Jason: You ready?
Oh, yeah, babe,
i'll be right there.
Well, you better go.
Hey!
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
Don't forget
the parsley.
Thank you.
Raquel arenas.
Raquel, do you have
your journal?
Mm-mmm.
Alita sanchez?
Shameika wallace?
Shameika, did you bring
your dr. King journal?
Nope.
Got no dreams to keep.
Badriyah?
Julio vazquez?
Sorry, i couldn't
get to it, boss.
Why are you all
doing this?
Got better
things to do, yo.
Oops, my bad.
Forgot to say,
"yo, sir."
Guess i get a check.
You want to get
a detention?
Yo, i really, really
like your nail polish.
Thank you.
My mama bought it.
Look at me when
i talk to you.
My double bad.
Another check.
[Shouting] look at me
when i talk to you!
[Shrieks]
Go to hell!
You win.
You did it, girl!
Bounce!
All: Bounce, bounce,
bounce, bounce,
bounce, bounce.
All: Whoo!
[Horn honks]
Hey! What happened?
Why aren't you
in school, kid?
I don't want
to talk about it.
Just... show me new york.
I've been here for 3 months.
I haven't seen a damn thing.
Today?
All right,
let's go see
some damn things.
You know,
when i was a kid,
i used to call it the
entire state building.
[Laughs]
That's cute.
Ok, you know what?
We walked the entire
island in a monsoon.
I bought you 3 pretzels
and 2 hot dogs.
Now you're gonna
do something for me.
Anything.
Tell me
what happened.
I shook a desk with
a 12-year-old kid in it.
I wanted to throw it...
and her... right out
the window.
Well, they've seen that
kind of anger before.
Well, not from me.
L... i totally lost it.
What, you felt helpless?
They feel
that way every day.
These kids can do
anything i'm asking
them to do, more.
They just... won't.
So...
today i gave up.
Don't give up, ron.
Oh, yeah?
How long has it been
since you've auditioned?
I don't know.
2 years and
7 months.
What? Broadway's
not gonna miss me
if i'm gone.
Those kids,
they'll miss you.
Maybe you can be
that one guy
that turns it
around for them.
[Bell rings]
Mr. Clark was crazy man
on friday, you know?
I think he's gone for good.
I say we should just
all go home.
Think so?
Yeah.
Well, thanks for
your advice, son,
but if mr. Clark
isn't in his class,
i'm sure we can
find someone to
cover for him.
Why we gotta do that?
Good morning, julio.
Mr. Turner.
Fool came back.
Fool did, indeed.
What's he doing?
He's crazy!
Everybody take
a look around.
Within these 4 walls,
you can be strangers,
or you can be
a family.
Within these 4 walls
can be the end
of your story,
or you can make it
a beginning.
A beginning that is better
than anything you ever
imagined possible.
Since i got here,
you have not listened
to me once.
Yeah.
So, here's the deal...
today we are going
to learn grammar.
[All groaning]
If you are quiet
and you listen,
every 15 seconds, i will
drink a chocolate milk.
If you can do it,
you may get
to see me puke.
So, do we have a deal?
All: Yeah!
Ok, good.
Julio?
Yes?
This is not
for you to eat.
I want you to watch
the clock,
and every 15 seconds,
bang the jar
with the ruler,
like that.
All right.
When i hear the gong,
i will slam down
one of these.
The time starts...
now.
Every sentence
has a subject
and a verb.
What the hell's
a boomerang?
Shut up, alita!
I guess you guys
don't want to see me
drink all
the chocolate milk!
All: Shh!
The verb
expresses action
in the sentence.
[Giggling]
Shh!
[Bang bang bang]
[Laughing]
In this sentence...
[bang]
[Bang bang bang]
Chug, chug, chug,
chug, chug, chug,
chug, chug, chug...
uh-oh!
Aw, come on!
Come on, come on!
Oh-ho-ho!
Chug, chug, chug,
chug, chug, chug!
Yeah!
Whoo!
Now, can anybody
tell me
the verb in
this sentence?
Ohh.
Ahem.
Feels?
Yes, yes!
You gonna puke now,
mr. Clark?
Yes!
[All laughing]
Whoa!
Ohhh!
Ew!
Oh!
Blech!
Yeah, come on.
Keep going.
Hey, can you guys
teach me how to do that?
[All laughing]
Oh, you don't
think i can learn
how to do that?
No!
Ok, all right,
i'll make you a deal.
If i learn how
to double dutch,
then you guys gotta learn
something from me.
What?
Everything
you need to know
for the seventh grade.
Is he for real?
All right.
So, you gonna jump?
Yeah.
Ok, ok, ok, can you just
go a little slower?
Nuh-uh.
You gotta do
like we do.
Ok.
* nah, nah, nah,
nah, nah, nah *
all right,
all right.
Ready, set...
go.
[Singing in spanish]
[Laughing]
Come on, man.
You're ain't dancin'.
You're jumpin'.
Aw, come on, now.
Almost had it that time.
[Cheering]
Whoo!
Hey.
Hey, mr. Turner,
this is fun!
You really think it
appropriate
to do this
with the students?
Well, i'm certainly not
gonna double-dutch with you.
[All laughing]
These kids are
at the bottom of the barrel.
Don't talk about
them like that.
Now all i'm asking
is for your students
to pass.
Oh, every one of my
students will pass.
What?
I'm not
going to pass...
good.
They've become somebody
else's problem.
The problem
isn't the kids.
It's not even what
they can achieve.
The problem is
what you expect
them to achieve.
[Sighs]
You are setting
the bar here.
Why? Set
it up here.
They can make it.
This community
judges us by scores.
Government funding
People who give me scores,
they get my respect.
Ok, good, in may,
they'll all test
at grade level.
[Sighs]
I don't see
how that's possible.
Oh, i'm sorry,
did i say grade level?
I meant above
grade level.
Every single one
of those kids
in that class
just wants
your respect.
Hell, i want
You want my respect?
Stop acting like
a 12-year-old.
I always wanted
to go rock climbing.
But there i was,
on the edge
of this cliff,
ropes on me,
and my friends
are yelling,
"jump, jump, jump!"
And i looked down...
and it is
a long way down.
So, i'm on the cliff
and i'm yelling,
"i can't, i can't, i can't."
And my friends
are yelling,
"yes, you can.
You can do it!
Jump! Jump! Jump!"
And i did.
I thought i was
going to die,
but when i jumped out,
it felt like
i was flying.
I did something
that i never thought
i could do.
And it was
pretty cool.
Now you guys
may not know this,
but in this classroom
we're rock climbing
every day.
We are climbing
up and up and up.
And we are there,
and now it's
time to jump.
I know you're scared.
But i want you
to do it.
I want you to jump.
I want you guys
to feel what it's like...
to fly.
So, i want each of you
to come up here,
and light one
of these candles.
Ok, come on up, guys.
And when you
light a candle...
it symbolizes
that we are
joined together.
And if you trust me...
you can learn more
than you ever dreamed of,
and that's a promise.
[Feet shuffling]
[Buzzer]
The revolutionary war...
industrialism.
The civil war.
The civil rights
movement.
I want you all
to get the great
big picture
of american history.
That's why, this year,
we're going to learn
all 42 presidents
of the united states,
in order.
Class: Aww...
no, once you know
the presidents,
it'll be easy
to remember what and when.
[Rap music coming
from outside]
Come on.
[Muffled rap music
continues]
Mr. Clark: None of you
passed the test...
and there's going
to be punishment.
Class: Ohh.
I want you to pass
these all around.
[Class groans]
[Rap music playing]
* now let's get down to some
presidential learnin' *
* start with george washington
straight from mount vernon *
*the first president
and commander-in-chief *
* fought the revolutionary war
so we could be free *
* john adams was second,
thomas jefferson third *
* when we fought
for independence *
* their voices
were heard *
* when in the course
of human events *
* we took a stand and
we've been doin' it since *
*it's a tribute
to the leaders of the u.s.a. *
* it's a presidents rap,
all right, all right *
* ok, ok *
[cheering]
* it's a tribute
to the leaders
of the u.s.a. *
* it's a presidents rap *
girls: * it's
the presidents rap,
all right, all right *
* ok, ok *
* it's a tribute *
* to the leaders
of the u.s.a. *
* it's the presidents
rap, all right,
all right, ok, ok *
all right,
back to your seats.
Back, back, back...
* to the leaders
of the u.s.a. *
* it's the presidents rap *
* all right, all right,
ok, ok *
"r" to the "o"
to the izzle.
"R" to the "o"
to the nizzle.
"R" to rizzle...
"r" to the "o" to the...
ra-kizzle.
Thank you, mr. Clark.
Here you go.
Girl:
This is my first "a."
Hey, good job!
Shameik-izzle.
Thank you, mr. Clark.
Boy:
Yo, man, i told you...
second boy:
You got an "a", too!
Now, give it up
for your sizzle selves.
It's ok to be proud
of yourself for doing
well on a test.
[Bell rings]
Girl: Come on,
let's go.
Oh, my god...
[low chatter]
[Overlapping chatter]
Can you hold up
for a minute?
I wanted to ask
a favor of you.
Me?
Could you
empty your pockets,
please?
I believe
this constitutes an
illegal search, sir.
Right on the desk.
That morning at your house,
your mother's purse...
nah, see, you
got it all wrong.
Me and her have
this deal, you know,
i take care of her,
and she takes care
of me.
You see?
No, i don't.
Bet you about
to tell me that
crime doesn't pay.
Sometimes it costs.
And in this case...
3 one-hour study sessions.
With me.
[Sighs]
I mean, for real,
you should be workin'
for us, little brother.
See, make yourself
some easy money, right?
I already got
enough trouble.
The man don't care
about no kids.
He's too busy
to take you down there,
i'm tellin' you.
Tayshawn!
He a 5-0 or somethin'?
What's up?
Nah, nah, man,
he ain't no police.
He just, uh, some fool,
man. I'll handle him.
Don't worry, y'all.
Be back.
[Muttering]
You ok?
Yeah, i'm cool.
I wanted to bring
you this.
Here.
You could bring up
your math and english
with some extra help.
Tomorrow's saturday.
I could meet you
at the coffee shop
by the school.
I'll buy you lunch.
Ll be there at noon.
Noon.
Can i take that now?
Yeah, thank you.
Too bad he didn't
show up.
Here i am,
not even 2:00.
I'm early, sir.
Down for study session
numero tres.
, 3 up
fp.
Then we get another
2 cards up.
Ok, so that's
5 cards up.
Yeah.
Can you add
those up for me?
You know,
we gotta bet first.
I bet 5
fake dollars.
Lli'alanth 3
that's good.
Now what's the
square root of that?
Uh... oh, square root.
Ok, i think the square
root is... [snores]
What number, multiplied
by itself, gives you 36?
Uh... 6?
That's good.
Heh heh.
So, what you got?
Pair of 7's.
Well, i guess i get
all the chips.
Because i got three 10's.
Oh, pay up, dog!
Wanna go again?
Shameika wallace?
Didn't we have
an appointment
after school today?
Musta slipped my mind.
We have to talk about you
turning in your homework.
I told you...
the fire alarm
keeps going off
in my building.
3 times this week?
I get busy, forget.
Last night i just
didn't do a good
enough job.
Would you like
to show me your homework?
I'm sure i can
help you with it.
This is really... close.
We can fix this.
Yeah?
For reals?
Sure, we can work
on it right now.
There's a few
spelling mistakes,
[knocking]
And just
arrange some of the
paragraphs different...
yeah.
[Yelling]
There you go.
He's been cranky
and fussy all day.
I think maybe
he's got a fever.
Ok. Thank you,
mrs. Benton.
Mr. Clark, i can't work
on my paper right now.
I goa go make dinner.
I'll do it.
You'll do what?
I'll make dinner,
and you work
on your paper.
All right?
Ok.
Start with that
third paragraph.
Hi.
Ok, where's the food?
Ron: Dinner's served.
I'm tryin' to concentrate.
Concentrate later.
Dinner's served.
I tried like you said.
I moved the third paragraph,
and it sounds really good.
Good.
Ok. Now, that's for you.
And who gets
the baby food?
He does.
Ok, you're gonna
like this.
This looks really good.
* ooh oooh *
[door slams]
What's he doing here?
He made us dinner.
You don't think i can
take care of my family,
mr. Clark?
No. Yes.
Please, leave my house.
[Door closes]
I come home to find him
in my kitchen cooking
for my family.
This girl has a job to do.
Ms. Wallace,
can we please not
talk about shameika
like she's not
in the room?
I'll talk any way i want.
Now, i send my daughter
to school to be educated.
I don't expect a teacher to
bring school up in my house.
It's called homework.
Excuse me?
She has too much of it
to be babysitting
all the time.
Mr. Clark.
Shameika
has more potential
than any kid
in my class.
Why can't you see that?
How dare you!
How you going to tell me
what i should
and should not see
in my daughter?
I am merely suggesting
that you give her
a chance.
I'm taking
my child home now.
The white tornado here
better not be teaching
at this school
when i bring her
back tomorrow.
Ms. Wallace, i can
assure you i will deal
with the situation.
Come on, shameika.
Please don't fire,
mr. Clark!
He was just trying
to help me, mama.
He's just
trying to help.
That's... that's ok.
Please don't leave
because of me, mr. Clark.
Ms. Wallace,
wait.
I'll meet you outside.
Why are you doing this?
You gave her
these grand ideas,
and this world is just
going to crush her down.
I don't believe that.
So, you're just going
to drop into her life,
and now you you know
all about it, right?
I just know
she's a great student,
a born leader...
creative, intelligent.
Shameika?
My shameika?
Yes.
If she tests
well enough in may,
i think we might
be able to get her
into manhattan west
for middle school.
That's for gifted kids.
Maybe mrs. Benton
can keep the boys
a little longer every day.
Ok.
Good morning, mr. Clark.
Good morning.
Morning, mr. Clark.
Julio, did you do this?
You like it, mr. Clark?
It's really good.
You got quite
a talent for this.
Well, it's one
of my manys, dawg...
sir.
Thanks.
Good morning.
Yo, what up, tay?
[Taunting]
Do you like me,
mr. Clark?
Hey, don't hate on me
'cause i got skills.
Skills?! You mean being
a straight up punk?
You real good at that!
Yo, come on, tay,
just chill out.
You telling me
to chill, homey?!
to chill?!
Come on, man, i mean,
mr. Clark likes
that art crap, ok?
So, he thought i did it,
and i just went with it.
I'm sorry, man!
Aah!
Superintendent stevens
has joined us
to determine if tayshawn
mitchell should be expelled
from inner harlem
elementary.
I vote yes.
Send him to juvi.
This isn't
a democracy,
mr. Brampton.
Howard, would you let
mr. Turner finish
what he was saying?
You're his
foster parent.
You got the say here.
We don't need
his lazy ass around
the house all day.
What did you
just say?
Mr. Turner:
Ahem.
Look,
if we expel him,
he's only going to
fall further behind.
Mr. Clark, our students
can't simply
do what they want
with no consequences.
What about
the consequences
for tayshawn?
We are supposed
to be keeping these kids
in school.
Mr. Turner: Let's all
just take a step back.
Remember that i have eyes
in the back of my head,
so, stop fighting.
This is not a test.
This is my phone number.
I want you guys to call me
if you have any questions
about homework,
need any advice, or you are
in trouble.
That's 24/7.
Pick up your math workbooks
at the front of the class.
And we have a book report
due tomorrow.
[Bell rings]
Remember, there are
2 variables in this equation.
Ok? So "x" equals...
"x" equals...
come on, tayshawn,
you can do this.
Yo, not with you
all up on me, man!
Yeah.
"X" equals 3/8!
Yes! Ah, that's great.
Just keep doing it
like that.
This doesn't sound good.
How long you been this way?
A week. Maybe more.
Well, you have pneumonia.
I can send you home,
but you'd be confined
to bed rest for 2 weeks...
minimal.
Yeah, i can't do that.
Or i can admit you
to the hospital right now,
mr. Clark.
[Beeping]
[School bell rings]
[Voice strained]
Ok, everybody,
take your seats.
Mr. Clark, you look
really white.
Yeah, even more than usual.
We have 4...
4 weeks.
Now, i know that doesn't
seem like a lot of time,
but if we work
really hard,
i know we're going to do
great on these exams.
So, let's go over
our science topics
from last week.
Who knows those?
Magnetism, chemical reactions,
and gravity.
Ok, good. Gravity.
Gravity...
is important because...
ok, we get it, mr. Clark.
Gravity makes you
fall down.
Girl:
Is he kidding?
Always joking.
He not kidding!
Mr. Clark?
[Commotion]
I hope he's all right.
For you.
Hey, mariss...
thank you.
Wait. Come over here.
Can't have our mr. Clark
looking all sloppy now,
can we?
You know, a guy
could get used to this.
Come on,
teach already.
Ok, now just because
i'm on this video tape,
doesn't mean
that i can't see see you.
Alita, is that gum?
All right,
is everybody ready?
All: Yes, sir.
Gravity...
the force of attraction
between 2 objects.
That is gravity.
Now, according to the
definition of gravity,
why did the egg fall?
Because...
and no, julio,
it's not because the egg
and the floor are hot
for each other.
[Laughter]
Turn around and face me.
The egg fell because
the force of the mass
and the distance between
the egg and the floor
caused a reaction.
And, now, get out your
workbooks, because i have
to clean my floor.
Morning, mr. Clark!
Good morning, tisha.
Got my kids' homework?
Good to have you back.
That's not true.
Yes, it is.
I want my cd back
and my money, bitch.
Stupid, i gave
that cd back!
No, you didn't!
Yes, i did!
You always...
it's mr. Clark!
Yo, what up, mr. C?
You tell me.
You guys have one week
till the state exams.
One week
to show mr. Turner...
and your parents...
and yourselves
what you can do.
And you guys don't
have anything you
want to tell me?
There's no way we're
gonna pass those tests.
We always mess up.
Don't jump on us,
man... sir.
I mean, it's
nothing personal.
Everything we do
in this room
is personal,
how we talk
to each other,
how we work together,
and how we've
prepared for these tests.
But we're
way behind now.
We're not behind.
You're ahead!
Everyone thinks
we're losers,
mr. Clark.
No.
You are not losers.
These rules?
They represent
everything you've
accomplished this year.
Discovering new things,
believing in each other,
believing in yourselves.
And i'm proud of you.
Compared to all that,
this test? Pfh.
It's nothing.
Mr. Clark,
we have to get
certain grades
to graduate, right?
So what if we,
you know, choke?
But you're not
going to choke.
You guys didn't work
hard all this year
just to get ready
for some tests.
Every day,
in this room...
we are learning things
far more valuable
than you can get
in some book.
I teach you...
and you teach me...
and, together, we
learn to love to learn.
[Exhales]
So...
next week...
you're gonna
take that test,
you're gonna do
the best that you can do,
and you are going
walk out of that room
and know that you can
do anything you want
for the rest of your lives.
All right,
tomorrow is the big day,
but don't worry.
You know the material
backwards and forwards.
So, just get
a good night's sleep
and, you know, good luck.
Badriyah, can i talk
to you for one minute?
And, tayshawn,
can you wait for me
at the door, please?
I know that it's
been hard for you
to fit in.
But, you can be smart
and still be cool.
In fact, you're
so smart and cool,
you can do anything
you want to do.
I want to be
a doctor.
Ok, good.
You better kick
some butt on that test,
then, doctor.
Thank you, mr. Clark.
Good luck!
Tayshawn!
Yo, kid, get it done.
Know what i'm sayin'?
Do this.
Hey, what up, t?
Yeah, little brother,
where you been, man?
We been looking for you.
You forgot
what's up?
Hey, check it,
we got some goods
we gotta move now.
Come on.
It's raining, dude,
come on.
Hey!
Look, you can't
be in and not roll.
A'ight, you can't
be like that, son.
I was thinking maybe
we could walk
to school together.
We can do
a last-minute review
of the test on the way.
Yo, you want it this way
or that way, payaso?
Which way? Come on!
That way.
Pff. Punk.
Ok, so,
when you get
to the math section...
go get 'em.
Good morning.
Do not open
your test booklets
until i tell
you to begin.
Keep your eyes
on your own paper.
When you've chosen your answer,
fill in the corresponding
answer bubble completely
with a number 2 pencil.
If you require
an additional pencil,
please raise your hand
and one will be provided.
Do your best...
and no talking.
You may begin.
Think they're
as nervous as we are?
I'm not nervous.
Antacid?
Thanks.
[Bell rings]
It was 36.
No, it was
32 apples, right?
That test was
hard, mr. Clark.
Double mocha latte,
no foam?
Hi! Come on in.
How were the tests?
Oh, uh, good,
i think.
I think the kids
did pretty well.
Yeah, ok, whatever.
I'm freaking out.
I got an audition.
Oh, my god,
that's great!
No!
No, that's not so good.
Jason got a job
and he asked me
to go to l.a. With him.
L... l... i don't
know what to do.
Tell me what to do.
I tell sixth graders
what to do,
and last time i looked
you weren't
in the sixth grade.
So, thank you very much...
for stopping by.
L...
well...
what's going on?
What time is it?
Does it look like
any of us got a watch?
Shut up, julio.
[Bell rings]
"Whatever you do,
do not open the closet."
All: Julio, no!
Don't! Don't go!
Will y'all calm down?
[All scream]
Hello, kids!
Julio, i knew you were
gonna open the closet!
[Laughter]
You guys have
been working so hard
for the last
3 months on this test,
and whatever
the scores are,
i want you to know
i'm proud to be
your teacher.
I'm so proud that
i asked your parents
to let me take you
somewhere special,
and they said yes.
So, go get
your envelopes
and open them.
Shameika?
Raquel?
Right here,
right here!
Elise.
Oh, my god!
Phantom of the opera!
Guys, we're going
to broadway!
We are going tonight,
so come get your playbills.
Thank you, mr. Clark!
Thank you,
mr. Clark!
[Excited chatter]
Oh, thanks, mr. Clark.
Thank you, mr. Clark.
Thank you!
[Tv playing
in background]
And this phantom guy,
he's like so in love
with this girl
that he's got
to grab her up,
you know?
And then he takes her
to this secret crib,
and then... and then
he keeps her there,
and then
they find him.
Then what happens?
Well, i'm not
going to tell you.
You'll find out.
[Door opens]
What the hell?
You ruined my wall!
I told you to paint
that crap in the street!
Not in my house!
No!
Get off of me, man!
Get off of me!
You think you can
do whatever you want?
You piece of garbage!
[Gasps]
[Groans]
Ah! Oh!
Ok, guys, go in.
The play's gonna start.
Let's go in.
Come on, get in there.
Let's go.
I can't find tayshawn.
Go look for him,
mr. Clark.
There's plenty
of parents here.
We'll look
after the kids.
Tayshawn.
[Soft groan]
[Sobbing]
Tayshawn?
[Moaning] ohh...
i'm here.
Get away, get away!
I ain't worth it.
No, no, no.
I know you are.
I saw your work.
And it's beautiful.
It's ok.
Oh, it's ok. It's ok.
Where am i gonna
go now, mr. Clark?
I'm gonna help you.
I'm not going anywhere.
Ok?
Here we go.
Tayshawn.
You'll be staying
here for a while.
Thanks, mr. Turner.
You're welcome.
Hey.
You're gonna
be safe here.
It may take
a while, ron,
but, uh, we'll
find him a place.
I give you my word.
So, which room
was yours?
I'll see you
first thing in the morning.
Yes, sir.
For highest
achievement
in science,
badriyah santhanam.
Thank you, mr. Clark.
You are welcome, doctor.
For most outstanding
achievement
in mathematics,
julio vasquez.
Thank you, mr. Clark.
For exceptional
artistic achievement...
tayshawn mitchell.
And last,
but not least...
shamel...
[door opens]
I'm sorry
to interrupt
your end of the year
party, mr. Clark,
but i just
received a fax
from the board
of education,
informing me
of the results
of the state exam.
I felt
it was important
to give you
the scores myself.
These are probably
not the scores
you expected.
This class,
this
sixth grade class,
tested higher than
any other class.
You even
tested higher
than
the honors class.
Congratulations.
Congratulations,
mr. Clark.
Thank you.
Very impressive.
[Parents laugh]
[Sighs]
Shameika, your award
wasgoing to be
for highest achievement
in english,
but i'm afraid i'm going
to have to change that,
because looking
at your exam scores,
i now see that you
achieved something
that no other student
in the entire district
achieved.
Shameika wallace,
ahem, you earned
perfect scores
in english and math.
Oh, my god!
Mr. Clark, mr. Clark!
[Chuckles]
Thank you!
Yeah!
You did it!
Mr. Clark...
for always being there,