Understand, Chapel.
This is a very sensitive operation.
[African women singing]
That island is a CIA asset.
I want those independent contractors...
believing they're liberating those people.
Did you think
that I was going to tell them...
that they're risking their lives
so we can get rich off diamonds and oil?
I need the best on this one
and I need plausible deniability.
I shall give you the best.
[Exhaling] Kruger and Dekerk.
CHAPEL: Munitions experts,
South Africans.
More specifically, Afrikaners.
There is not a gun or a bullet
they cannot find or use.
Five hundred kills to their credit.
Lovely.
This is Mr. Samuel Kay.
MIS and Al specialist.
Fluent in nine computer languages.
Can, or more precisely, has hacked
his way into every system in the world...
including your own.
Especially when you consider
with whom they shall be working.
Maxine Barnol.
Where hardware hacking
and bribery won't work...
you need a muse.
Extraordinary.
9-3-60. This is Blind Eagle,
do you copy, over?
Mr. Radio Jones,
communications specialist.
And the only person capable
of talking Mr. John Seeger...
into joining our little party.
[Gun firing]
DRESHAM: John Seeger.
The most decorated soldier
in the First Gulf War.
[Gunshot]
He's a wild card, Chapel.
Yes. The best at doing what he does.
Will he know we're behind this?
Only if you want him to.
Just make sure you keep it
under control, Chapel.
We don't need a war.
Peace.
[Men shouting]
Though you cannot see it...
over that hill a fierce battle has erupted,
sending civilians fleeing for their lives.
[Guns firing]
KRUGER: It's perfect.
Johnny, hotwire this piece of shit
and lay a charge.
You, rookie, it's time to show us
what you're made of.
Jack a car in town,
and we move in on the target.
Once she's clear, we go in with the truck.
Do you think she's up to it?
BRIGID: Hmm.
Well, if she doesn't call us
after five minutes...
we'll do it the old-fashioned way.
[Pinging]
[Engine revving]
[Birds chirping]
BUTLER: The children will be down
in a minute.
Please get their breakfast ready
on the table.
I'm taking the Ambassador his coffee now.
I have an urgent message
for the Ambassador.
[Grunting]
[Guard yelling in French]
[Guard grunts]
Guys, we're all clear.
[Gun cocking]
[Engine revving]
- May I pour your coffee for you?
- Yes, please.
You two! Come with me.
Come with me now.
It's okay.
[Guard grunts]
[Muffled screaming]
[Boy grunting]
KRUGER: Bonjour.
What are you doing here?
You know what the fuck I'm doing here.
Your foreign policy sucks,
and we need you as insurance...
to get out of this mess.
- I'm the French Ambassador!
- I know who the fuck you are.
I'm running a bit of a tight schedule,
so let's move!
[Muffled screaming continues]
Get up on the truck.
Move!
Get! Go on!
All right, get on the truck.
It's not a fucking holiday!
Move!
All right, let's move out!
We don't want to keep our friends waiting.
[Engine revving]
[Whimpering]
Three days ago,
heavily armed mercenaries launched...
a lightning raid
overthrowing Sibi Al Fukar...
and his corrupt cadre of army officers...
who have held this tiny island nation
in their iron grip for over three years.
With the surprise arrival
of a brigade of French commandos...
these mercenaries have been dislodged
from their positions around the city...
and put on the defensive,
forced into a shrinking perimeter.
As the French mass for a final assault...
these besieged soldiers of fortune
now face a stark choice.
The inside of a French jail cell or death.
[Men shouting]
[Gunfire]
FEMALE REPORTER: Colonel. Colonel.
Colonel, will you risk an attack
even though these mercenaries...
have taken civilian hostages?
[Shell exploding]
Colonel Roland, when do you strike?
They have nowhere to go.
We will overtake them
but we'll have hostages to consider.
With your permission, I'd like to cross
the line and talk to the mercenaries.
And yes, I understand what that means.
Let her through.
- Who the hell are you with?
- Looks like I'm with the mercenaries.
[Man screaming]
[Gunfire]
[Groaning]
[Gun firing]
[Man screaming]
Chief, I don't know where these numbers
are coming from!
We're outnumbered. We're in trouble.
Where are all these Frenchies
coming from?
Get head office on the secure line.
- Where's Kruger and his men?
- Last call we heard...
Kruger took the French Ambassador
and his family for extra insurance.
Why did you agree to work
with a slap-dick like that anyway?
It wasn't my call.
[Men shouting]
[Shell exploding]
MAN: You two, move!
Camera crew coming in!
SEEGER: Maxine, what are you doing here?
Man, you're supposed to stay out
of the danger zone to gather intel only.
You hear that?
Oh, okay, well how's this for intel?
The French have landed.
Somebody fucked us! Who?
[Guns firing]
[Men groaning]
Radio, give me that com unit.
Damn it!
Hello, Bravo! Bravo 1-2-3.
Do you copy?
Got our employers on the line here.
Maybe it's time to swallow our pride
and call for a little help.
This is another CIA "fuck you," isn't it?
Oh, right, I forgot, the creed,
"Care for no one, fight for everyone."
It's a good motto, isn't it?
Sigma, this is Alpha 9. I repeat, Alpha 9.
Do you read me?
SEEGER: [Over radio] Sigma,
this is Alpha 9. Say again, Alpha 9.
Chapel, you guaranteed me
this French fiasco would not happen.
SEEGER: Sigma, this is Alpha 9.
I repeat, Alpha 9.
You know,
I think we're in a refund situation.
Shall I make the check out
to the CIA or to you?
- It's your call on this one, Dresham.
- Fuck you, Chapel.
It's a bit more for my mercs to handle.
Shall we call in the troops?
Those mercs, did they figure out
who they're working for?
And what difference does that make?
Because right now we need deniability...
more than we need them back
in one piece.
You understand me?
We're still working the plan, Sigma.
SEEGER: Didn't you say there would be
no counter-support?
Can we expect any help from your end
with our extraction?
You really want them back, Chapel?
No help at all.
Chapel, you and Dresham fuck us on this...
I'm gonna stick my.45 up your ass
and break every bone in your body.
- Chapel, this is getting out of control.
- You know something?
The next time that you and the Agency
want to plan a little business trip...
dial someone else.
Fucking Yank. Excuse my language.
All right, Jones, call in the chopper.
Samuel, load up all the wounded.
Send in a goddamn chopper now!
You'll never learn, will you?
- Who do you think we're working for?
- Heads up!
I'd settle for
just getting the fuck out of here.
I shouldn't have dragged you
into this, John.
They used me to get ahold of you, man!
[Screaming]
You hang on, son.
I'm gonna get you on that chopper.
Take care of Eddie.
Hang on, Jones, you hear me?
Shondra.
Hang on, man.
Promise me.
[Paul grunting]
Paul! Paul!
SAMUEL: Go! Code blue!
There's our pickup. Let's go!
Stand back! Don't move!
I'm press! I'm press!
You just killed an innocent man, asshole!
[Sobbing]
[Men yelling]
KRUGER: Colonel, this is Kruger. Come in.
Mr. Kruger.
There is nowhere for you to run.
Now listen up...
I got the French Ambassador
and his lovely family here...
and the truck is rigged to blow,
so stand the fuck down.
Tell them to hold their fire.
[Groans]
[Man groaning]
Repeat. Everyone, stand down.
Pull forward!
[Speaking French]
- Colonel, what the fuck are you doing?
- Repeat, everyone, stand down.
On my mark,
get the fuck out of that truck!
[Brigid grunts]
Now! Get out!
Go! Move!
[Women screaming]
Keep moving!
Come on, men! Move!
Left bank, 20 degrees!
Come on! Come on!
[Jeep horn honking]
KRUGER: Hey, hey.
No worries, Johnny boy.
We made it, didn't we?
[Kruger grunts]
I ought to fucking kill you right now, boy.
- I don't think so.
- Yeah, maybe not right now.
[Grunting]
I hear the blacks in the States
fly really well.
So why don't you and your buddy...
hop in the tail and fly the fuck out of here!
I'll fly on the tail, Kruger,
if you don't mind me...
throwing this grenade up in this helicopter
with all you motherfucking white folks!
Forget about it.
Yo, Seeger, come on, we're full!
Leave him, we're full, man!
Come on. Let's get the fuck out of here!
Come on!
Come on! Let's go! Let's go! Let's go!
[Radio chattering]
Maxine?
She'll play it through. She always does.
EDDIE: The car's going too slow.
Come on. Go.
Oh, yeah. We're catching up.
Whoa!
REPORTER: [On TV] Today, Galmoral
was turned over to the UN by the French...
ending a conflict
which began as a small coup...
by antigovernment mercenaries...
now celebrated as heroes here.
This small island nation has its first taste
of freedom in over 100 years...
and democratic elections...
You were correct.
One week, and he shows.
Guess you know him well.
Take him.
- And meet me back at base.
- Take him?
You make this shit sound easy.
The lady says it's a go.
Mom, it's the door.
Put your video game down
and answer it for me.
Do I have to?
Hey, Eddie.
I don't know if you remember me.
You used to live on the Army base
with me and your daddy.
But Mom said he's not coming home.
Well, there's nothing he wanted more
than to be with you.
Eddie. Go to your room, honey.
Why are you here, John?
State Department already notified us.
Why him?
Why my baby?
It was that coup in Africa, wasn't it?
The one on the news?
He always believed
he could make a difference.
Casualties of war.
You went along because of him, John.
So tell me what I lost him to.
Some stupid cause?
And now they're gonna fly him back...
and leave me with a folded flag
and a bunch of medals.
It's not that simple. It was a covert op.
- They're not bringing him back?
- Well, I'm bringing him back.
And I'm telling you,
he's gonna get full military honors...
and a proper burial.
Listen...
What is this?
I'm gonna look after you
and the baby now.
What the hell is taking so long?
Don't worry.
He's gotta come out eventually.
[Grunts]
[Cell phone ringing]
Tell me you've got him.
Unfortunately I'm alive, and they're dead.
John. John, it's good to hear from you.
Look, I'm sorry about Jones.
You know we had to maintain
plausible deniability.
You know what? You fucked us,
and I'm not getting over that.
But we can talk about that, John.
- So why don't you just come back in?
- Oh, I'm coming in.
Believe me, I'm coming in.
I'm coming in to get you.
- You wanted a one-on-one.
- John, listen...
Surveillance at the United Nations
in New York...
turned up one of the people
you red-flagged.
He had a suitcase filled with money.
Thank you, Kelly.
So, you're back in business, Chapel.
[Tires squealing]
Now, there's two ways
we can do this, John.
We can all end up
looking like Swiss cheese...
or we can go have a nice cup of coffee.
What's it gonna be?
Let's go have a cup of coffee.
Get this truck out of here.
- Thank you.
- Kelly?
Just in from the FBI, sir.
There's been a shootout in Miami.
One of the dead has been identified
as a South African national.
He's a mercenary.
We used him in Galmoral with Seeger.
Great.
Also, our two men staking the Jones'
house, they've been found dead.
Goddamn this. Where is Seeger?
A witness said someone
matching his description...
was taken away at the scene.
Maybe his friends.
Seeger doesn't have friends.
Besides, a commando-style
rescue mission in Miami...
is gonna cost somebody
a great deal of money to organize.
Get the jet ready. We're going to Miami.
Dresham here, I need authorization.
- Well, here's to you. Cheers.
- Yes.
I heard the French had you.
Like the CIA had you?
I didn't know I was gonna be
twisting in the wind like this.
I'd have never let them do that to me
and I'd have never let them do that to us.
The only reason I took this job
was so I could look you in the eye...
and tell you
I've killed for money, I've lied...
but my heart never got sold out
with the contract.
Until now.
MAXINE: He's waiting for you.
You deserve each other.
And I thought ladies liked the bad boys.
I think she's mad at me.
How are you, John?
I understand your anger.
I don't think that anyone really
appreciates all that you do for them...
especially your country.
Yeah, three people died today.
I was kind of wondering why.
Either for nothing or for something.
It's your choice. You make the decision.
CHAPEL: This is our assignment
for Mr. Ahmet Dasan...
a billionaire extraordinaire.
Mr. Chapel has arrived, sir.
- Ahmet Dasan.
- Pleasure.
Please, walk with me.
- You are aware of my problem?
- Yes, sir, I've looked into your request.
But I must say,
it's beyond my capabilities.
Quite simply put, it cannot be done.
I am sorry.
In four days from now,
the United States Justice Department...
will be transferring my son
from South Africa...
to a lockdown facility
in Leavenworth, Kansas.
A lovely facility, I'm told.
Guarded by the largest infantry division
of the US Army.
A well-known fact.
But until then...
the South Africans are detaining Kamal at
the Randveld Prison outside of Cape Town.
I'm told it's a lovely facility, too.
To snatch your son from Randveld...
the most heavily fortified prison
in the southern hemisphere.
- Yet, it is not quite Leavenworth.
- Almost. Trust me, it can't be done.
I have controlled the arms pipeline
through the Middle East for 20 years.
Money? I am a billionaire
many times over.
And I would spend every bit of it
to free my first-born child.
But in order for an operation of this type
to be completely successful...
I should anticipate a certain risk
and a certain expense.
That is just your payment, Mr. Chapel.
A quarter down, the rest
when my son is standing before me.
Now, tell me again
how some things just can't be done?
I do stand corrected, sir.
You will find $20 million
in an account in the Cayman Islands.
When that amount has been depleted,
it will be automatically refilled.
And how many times may I deplete it, sir?
You will know when you've reached
the limits of my indulgence.
How?
There will be a bullet
in your head, Mr. Chapel.
Everything you need to know
about Randveld is in these files.
You decide.
Here you go.
I'm not interested.
My employer's money has no idea
of what that concept means, John.
[People chattering]
[Shondra's voice playing in reverse]
John, they said they'd kill us
if you didn't help them.
Please, John, don't let them hurt my baby.
We need your help.
They say they're going to take us to Africa.
John, I am going to need your help.
You know what?
I'm kind of fascinated that you just
don't have any means of persuasion.
Are you referring to a gun?
SEEGER: Mmm.
I don't touch a gun.
And guns don't touch me.
That's why I'm still alive.
I think it'd be good if you let them go.
I think it would be nice if you understood
that I'm a pushover, but I am not an idiot.
And you promised Radio Jones
that you would take care of little Eddie.
And little Eddie is being taken care of,
as you can see, quite well.
You kind of got me over a barrel.
How much time do I have?
You have all the time in the world
as long as you do it within four days.
- Four days is just not enough time.
- But we have money.
And money has a way
of making time irrelevant.
There might even be
something in it for you, John.
What do you say
we get this show on the road?
Tell the pilot we're ready to go.
DRESHAM: Okay, great.
Look, I want a search
of all the high-end hotels in Miami.
The penthouses.
Chapel's going to be in one of them.
[Woman chattering over PA system]
Never mind.
What a pleasant surprise.
Thank you.
Someone's got some explaining to do.
Computer support,
I'm gonna need somebody...
who can get a hands-up on that
right away.
- Do you have any word on Samuel?
- Loyalty in a mercenary.
John, that's a character flaw.
- It is, isn't it?
- Actually, he's on board.
CHAPEL: Couldn't resist being here
after that disaster in Africa.
Excellent. I suppose I'll get
to see him soon.
Samuel?
Would you like to inform John
as to why you came so willingly?
- I'm here for you, John.
- Fellow mercs reunited.
Oh, the hate and mistrust.
Warms my heart.
John, you never asked about Maxine.
- I thought you and she were...
- You're right. I didn't ask.
Chapel must have deep pockets
if he was able to buy you.
I suppose so. Sorry, have we met before?
Oh, we partied on the same island once.
Now, tell me about Chapel
and your boyfriend.
As far as I know, they've already taken off.
- Kelly, get on it.
- Yes, sir.
- You can keep the money.
- Honey...
you work for me now.
What do you have?
Private jet manifest
shows 15 unidentified passengers.
- Going where?
- Flight plan says South Africa...
but it could be anywhere
south of the pyramids.
- Maxine?
- Chapel has plenty of muscle and money.
Where he chooses to flex them
is none of my business.
Oh, really? Oh, but
seeing Seeger one last time was, right?
You're really afraid of him, aren't you?
Why? Does he have something on you?
- So John does have a weakness.
- Meaning what?
CHAPEL: Meaning he'll come for you.
So, we're going to Africa, huh?
How about a safari?
[Door closing]
Look, I don't like the way shit went down,
you know that.
And those men you let in?
One thing for sure,
when you're a mercenary...
you're always gonna have casualties.
[Speaking Afrikaans]
- Guaranteed?
- Guaranteed.
[Exclaims in disgust]
- Where's the goddamn car, Kelly?
- Over there, sir.
Then what the fuck happened?
Where are they?
- They passed through the VIP line, sir.
- How did they do that?
- They had diplomatic passports.
- Great. Of course, they did.
CHAPEL: This is Kamal Dasan,
son of Ahmet Dasan...
Greek billionaire arms dealer.
Our job is to break him out of prison.
Our intel says that Dasan, Jr...
is being kept at the most secure facility
at Randveld.
So, there's guard stations at every point
and marshals backing them up.
But I don't think we'll have
a problem with that.
How the fuck you figure that?
At 10:00 there's gonna be a shift change.
Because of the large number of guards
that are entering and exiting...
they're disabling their alarm system
for about six minutes.
That's when we'll make our move.
So, this is what's gonna happen.
The perimeter sensors are still left on.
Samuel's going to disable the system
in the northeast sector...
which is gonna indicate
a break-in in that area.
Obviously, when that happens
all the exits will be automatically locked...
except for the guard entrances,
for obvious reasons.
From this entrance, they're gonna
have direct access to the core...
which is where our boy is.
We may have to take
a couple of guards out...
and then we may have to deal
with the marshals with CXL.
What do you think, Kruger?
You think you can handle that?
Fuck, yeah, but why don't we use
nerve gas on these pussies?
Well, with nerve gas, we're quite afraid...
that we may kill everybody,
especially our boy...
similar to the girls
that you are used to killing.
You wanna dance, motherfucker?
Get up. Get up!
So I think it's much better
if we act like professional soldiers.
- Don't you?
- That's not in your job description.
- Let's get back to work.
- Yes, sir. That would be nice.
We have a hole for you in Angola...
with your name on it, Kruger.
Everybody feeling up for this?
All right.
[Ship horn blowing]
John asked me to give you this.
MAN: Mr. Dresham
would like to speak to you.
[Car door closes]
What did he want?
He wants me to gather intelligence for
an operation he's running in Cape Town.
Did he tell you what the target was?
Is it the Agency that wants John so badly
or is it just you?
Does it matter?
[Tires screeching]
- Have the Americans arrived yet?
- They're right behind you.
Mr. Dresham, Spano Malik,
Chief of Police, Cape Town.
Mr. Malik, we have reason to believe
there's going to be an attempt...
to break into the black vault.
This is an official request from the CIA.
Your Foreign Affairs Division
have asked you to help us on this one.
This is absurd. Totally absurd.
- Humor me.
- It's not possible. Can't be done.
The bank's security systems...
were designed
by Cape Town's top security specialists.
Well, what are we talking about here,
some sort of private army or something?
Mr. Malik, you should assume these men
are as well-trained as they are financed.
Considering they've overthrown
the governments...
of some of your largest depositors,
maybe you should pay attention.
So, what's the CIA's interest?
There's an American national involved,
but we'll take care of him.
But even if your information is correct,
it's still impossible.
Impossible?
Maybe.
- Well, let's sign you in.
- Let's.
All control points are guarded,
blast doors that seal on the first alarm.
Video surveillance, naturally.
The doors are titanium-vanadium alloy...
with six different blast buffers.
Yeah, you could blow them in, but with
the amount of explosives you'd need...
you'd probably bring
the whole building down on top of you.
MALIK: This is the storage database
for the 12 largest banks in southern Africa.
You see, Mr. Dresham,
money is no longer a dollar bill.
It's a string of computer numbers
with a name attached...
and our many depositors from all over
the world require three things of us...
safety, security and anonymity.
Well, of course they do.
MALIK: There are no hard copies
to these blueprints.
- Absolutely no one has access.
- Good.
The software is all hardwired
so they come up only on this unit.
Try to copy, delete, print,
or transfer any of them...
they auto encrypt on a 256-bit key.
The vault itself is opened...
only with two magnetic strip keys...
and a corresponding
offsite security code...
- which changes every six minutes.
- Impressive.
Clearly, your client's money is
in very, very good hands, Mr. Malik.
Indeed. I mean, these guys would be crazy
to even try...
They won't. They don't have a chance.
We intend to put a stop to this little party
long before it gets that far.
Good.
Well, our department expects
to be kept fully informed. Understood?
Well, actually, I don't even do that
for my own government...
but I'm here for you.
Mr. Malik.
Shall we?
Seeger's gotta be crazy
to try and break into that place.
Why?
You heard the man,
nobody has access to those files.
I want you to find out where Seeger
and Chapel are operating from.
- I don't think he trusts me that much.
- Really?
Well, you don't get paid to think, Maxine,
so fuck him and find out.
Pimp.
Can anyone tell me why we've put
the control station so far from the prison?
Because they invented
wireless transmission.
I mean, you did buy us that cellular
relay tower on the mountain, right?
Indeed.
So, we control half the cellular phone
transmission in the city, why?
Because when the prison goes down...
the locals might triangulate
our communication traffic.
- Now, where would that lead them?
- Hello, old boy.
I understand that you want
to use Maxine as a distraction.
She's been in bed with Dresham all along.
Oh, wrong choice of words.
But we do need to do something
about her.
Who's going to do it?
- I'll do it.
- Well done.
- Seeger, you don't have to do this.
- Well, this time it's different.
His name is Eddie,
and I made him a promise.
MAN: That was a wonderful night, honey.
WOMAN: It really was, thank you so much.
[Bike engine roaring]
Where the hell is he?
He said to meet him here
and wear my best.
Remember, use the beacon
if I lose you in traffic. We want Seeger.
I get it. You don't talk because, like,
maybe if you had to kill somebody...
afterwards it would be hard.
You know, you got that statuesque
kind of, you know, stoic look on your face.
See, with me, it's never hard.
[Jazz instrumental music playing]
- Where are we going?
- It's a surprise.
Why did you have me dress up like this?
Well, I promised you
after this last fiasco was over...
I'd take you out, do something nice,
so here we are.
- Are we being followed?
- No.
Bulldog, take that side road.
Side road?
Strange road, two men like you.
That could mean one of two things, right?
Either this will end up being really bad
or really good.
Max, how well do you know me?
- Really good.
- There you go.
[Violins playing]
Right this way, sir.
Lobster's good here.
I'm gonna order you some.
Thank you, sir.
[Cell phone ringing]
[Playing lively tune]
Chapel here.
SEEGER: Listen, Chapel, my friend.
We played your game long enough.
Now we're gonna do things my way.
And what made you think
that you have any leverage, old chum?
One call and there's a bullet
in the boy's brain.
A terrible thing to waste,
wouldn't you say?
I'm talking about the bullet.
Periodically I'm gonna call you
and ask for proof of life.
You're gonna give it to me right away...
and if you don't, the game's over,
you hear me? Now, put the boy on.
All right.
Very well.
SHONDRA: The little boy packed
his school bag and got ready for school.
[Cell phone ringing]
Chapel here. Put the boy on.
Are you there, John? Listen.
Eddie?
SEEGER: Eddie?
Yeah.
- Is that you, son?
- Yes.
Listen. How're you doing?
- You and your mom all right?
- Yeah.
- All right. You hang in there, you hear me?
- That's quite enough.
John, you've had your proof.
Now get back to work.
I'll play you something sexy
to put you in the mood...
for you and the lady of your choice.
[Playing lively tune]
It's a dangerous game
you're playing, John.
Yeah, it is. One second.
[Door latch clicking]
- You looking for me?
- Yeah. That's it for you, poepol.
[Grunting]
[Groaning]
[Toilet flushing]
[Screaming]
[Sighing]
[Water gushing]
[Clattering]
Damn, that's a lot of work.
You know, Bulldog,
you never did say where you're from.
But let me guess, don't tell me. Detroit.
Detroit, Michigan. How'd you guess?
You know what? I'm from Detroit.
Highland Park.
Two Motor City boys, just like that.
Let's get out of here and go have a drink,
what do you say?
- You buying?
- All right.
We're gonna have to leave a big tip.
[Violins playing]
What happened in there?
Care to dance?
We located them
on a satellite track this morning.
- Where are they?
- At a deserted church in Woodstock.
They were using it as a staging area.
- Good. So you got them, right?
- No.
When we got there, they must've just left.
The place was deserted.
- Motherfucker's hitting the bank.
- The bank?
Seeger, he's hitting the bank right now.
Listen, I want every cop in this
godforsaken place at that bank right now!
- You understand me?
- Right, right.
MALIK: I want all cars down to
the Credit Natal immediately. Right now!
[Tires screeching]
[Sirens blaring]
It's a go to you, John.
Well, well, well.
You've made it abundantly apparent
that I don't work for you anymore.
But I'm just curious.
Why do you keep sending your boys
to mess up my dinner dates?
John?
You know, I can make
all the bad things go away.
Everything but this.
Tiger, this is Mouse,
what's happening at the Beehive?
All set to go.
You got any activities at target?
[Gates creaking]
[Keys clacking]
Change of the guard coming up
in three, two, one.
Alarms are down.
Go ahead and move in.
- Copy that, alarms are down. Go in now.
- Right, we're going in.
[Prisoners chattering]
Get me out of here, man!
[Alarm buzzing]
We're almost there.
Is our support in position?
Hey, you copy?
What the fuck, are you asleep?
Okay, we're running out of time.
Let's move!
Back off!
[Groaning]
Get the fuck out of my way!
What the fuck?
SAMUEL: Yo, Kruger.
Remember you said you'd rather die
than integrate?
Yeah, well, now's your chance.
Fuck!
It's a setup. Let's get the fuck out of here!
KRUGER: Keep your eyes open.
What the fuck?
[Men shouting]
Damn! TV in this country is quite violent.
[Chuckling]
[Alarm buzzing]
You got an open vehicle on your left.
[Groaning]
Let's go, go, go, go! Get us out of here!
Hold fast.
Come on, you wanna play chicken,
motherfucker?
Go!
Take the wheel!
[Tires screeching]
We are home and dry, my brother!
Come on! Let's go!
[Laughing]
You son of a bitch, John.
Oh, that's not nice. Come on, now.
- Is this your first time in the field?
- Fuck you.
SEEGER: You got any last words?
You're a patriot, John.
I mean, we both know
that's what you are, right?
I mean, those hostages,
I think about them everyday, you know.
Somehow I just kind of feel
like that's not quite the truth.
Oh, looky here. It must be your lucky day.
Po-po's just came up in here.
DRESHAM: What are you waiting for?
Back door!
COP: It's empty.
The man's a fucking ghost.
Fuck this.
DRESHAM: It's unbelievable.
All right, be at target in four minutes.
[Cell phone ringing]
Dresham.
We gotta talk fast.
This better be worth real money
because after this, I'm done.
You said you had to talk fast.
I got John to loosen up
a little bit last night.
He told me that Credit Natal
is just a diversion for the real target.
Randveld.
You gotta be fucking kidding me.
It's a diversion.
They're hitting Randveld Prison.
Clean this fucking mess up.
We got a 409 in progress
at Randveld Prison.
I want all units
to Randveld Prison immediately.
Yeah, go!
[Sirens blaring]
SEEGER: Samuel.
SAMUEL: All clear.
- May I help you?
- Detective Eric Morris, Cape Town Police.
We have a situation we'd like to discuss
with your security.
Sure.
Yeah?
Sir, we have a Lieutenant Eric Morris from
Cape Town Police Department to see you.
Okay, escort him down.
So, what's this about, Lieutenant?
As you know we've received
some credible intel that there's...
a bomb threat here,
particularly in the black vault.
I haven't heard a thing.
Well, check with your supervisor.
I'm sure you will.
Reach out and rob someone.
We're having a communications problem.
I can't confirm what you're saying.
All right. Listen, son, what's your name?
- Stanley Morgan.
- Okay, Stanley.
We can do this the easy way
or the hard way.
Easy way is you're gonna tell me
what I need to know and I'll be out.
Hard way is I'm gonna be scraping you
off the ground from outside.
SEEGER: This is a time-critical situation.
Look, even if I wanted to
I couldn't help you.
All right.
You do have the magnetic keys, don't you?
Yeah, but we don't have
the security access codes.
You know what?
That's where this will come in.
No problem.
SEEGER: We got about six minutes,
and the clock is ticking.
But I really should contact someone.
Let's pull a code from cyberspace.
You guys better step back,
'cause it could get a little exciting in here.
[Panel beeping]
[Vault door opening]
[Whispering] This is gonna be fun.
[Machine whirring]
Showtime.
Okay...
Samuel. You're on.
Oh, I'm always on, baby.
Damn, I'm good.
Nice work, Samuel.
SEEGER: Okay, access the account firm
in Greece.
We're looking for big depositors,
preferably high up in the government.
- Will the Army Chief of Staff do?
- Yes, ma'am.
- General.
- Yes?
A call from South Africa,
they say it's of a personal nature.
Yes? Who is this?
The secret number to the account
with my hand on the plug.
At least you'll have known
that at one point, you were very wealthy.
- Lf not a little corrupt.
- My deposit safe?
- Or should I just let the world know now?
- What do you want of me?
Listen carefully. Act quickly.
Today's extradition of Kamal Dasan...
son of Greek billionaire arms dealer,
Ahmet Dasan...
from Randveld Prison
to Leavenworth, Kansas...
has been complicated by an invasion
of the high-security facility...
by a group
officials are labeling mercenaries.
No word as to whether Dasan...
So, where the fuck is my son?
My guess is, boarding a heavily guarded
military flight...
to Kansas and questioning your love.
- Are you saying your man betrayed us?
- Yes, it does seem that way.
I'll tell you what, I'll just keep what's left
of my advance and call it even.
Cheers.
NEWSREADER: If convicted,
Dasan faced life without parole...
for allegedly assisting his father...
- Son of a bitch.
...in the transfer of bombs to Al-Qaeda.
An unspecified number of inmates
have been killed.
[Cell phone ringing]
Yes, we shall see
if they have outlived their usefulness.
- Yeah.
- Hello, John.
You've truly fucked me on this one,
haven't you?
You've gone straight to the bank.
You've cost me a lot of money on this one.
Yeah, well, you win some
and you lose some, Chapel.
Yes, I know that.
But you may have offed little Eddie
in the process.
I'm looking at him right now.
Oh, he's terrified.
You know I can find you wherever you are.
Go for it.
I know that, old boy,
which is precisely why...
I have a proposition
that will cost you nothing...
and save little Eddie in the process.
While you are in the black vault
playing with other people's money...
do you think that you could find it
in your heart to wire me some?
In exchange for those two, of course.
- How do I know you won't kill them?
- Oh, you don't.
But as you said,
you can find me anywhere.
- All right, first, proof of life.
- Yes, of course.
Master Eddie,
say hello to your Uncle John.
- Hello.
- All right, Eddie. I'll be there.
Don't you worry, son.
I will.
Now, John, I'm not a greedy man.
But I should think that $100 million
U.S. Dollars would be an appropriate sum.
I'll get it done.
Good. Then I should expect it
within the hour.
[Cell phone beeps]
And now...
it is time to say your final goodbyes.
You lied.
It's a fib, really. Right, Eddie?
I prefer apples.
Mommy?
- Are we gonna be all right?
- Yes, we are.
I want a contract out on Chapel so rich...
even the FBI
will try to collect on it.
$500 million. Dead.
Sir, these men are here.
What? Didn't your checks clear?
Come with me, you are under arrest.
What is this about?
Get me the Army Chief of Staff.
- Yes, sir.
- Bullshit!
Samuel. We don't have much time.
We've got company coming in.
You're gonna have to hurry up.
SAMUEL: Okay, shutting down.
All right, John, the rest is up to you.
- Are you done?
- Almost.
There's just one last person
that deserves to be rich.
You're kidding me.
John.
[Police sirens wailing]
John, John. We got company coming in.
There was a compromised access code.
I'm not sure, it could be terrorists.
I received a page
that an access code was issued.
- What's going on?
- That's the Americans, sir.
- They're checking the vault for a bomb.
- A bomb? What are you talking about?
Asshole alert.
You opened the vault?
You fucking idiot.
Arrest them now. Go!
[Alarm ringing]
You're kidding me.
You're not.
Wait here.
- Come with me, sir.
- Yeah.
MAN: Don't shoot!
[Sirens blaring]
MAN: Move! Move! Move!
- The vault below.
- Right! Got it.
Stop them! Stop them!
[Groans]
Take them out now!
[Groaning]
Now, you wanted a one-on-one?
Now, in prison...
even if you got a lot of money,
you can't spend it.
Somebody's got some explaining to do.
I'm afraid you're gonna have
to come with me, sir.
Ladies first.
POLICE DISPATCHER: Victim at 329.
WOMAN: What are they doing?
Transport by private ambulance.
- They need you inside.
- All right, sir.
[Grunting]
[Unlocking handcuffs]
There you go.
All right, you know what?
Don't un-cuff her.
You sure?
You guys.
Us guys, we're bad.
[Tires screeching]
What took you so long?
[Groaning]
Oh, Jesus.
That's on me.
MALIK: $52 million
deposited into your account.
Now I see why you wanted him so badly.
You, Mr. Dresham, are under arrest.
Shall we?
[Maxine laughing]
You hear that shit, man?
This route will take us directly
to the Botswana border.
Wait a minute, now,
we got unfinished business.
They're at the safe house.
There should be absolutely no mercy.
I want Seeger and all of them dead.
Now, you're to fetch young Eddie
and Mummy.
- I never touch a gun.
- Sorry.
That's your job.
Idiot.
Come! Let's go!
Come on. Get in the car.
- Stay ready.
- Yes, sir.
[Car engine starting]
Secure the perimeter.
I don't want anything coming through.
Keep your hands off my son!
Straight ahead. Got it?
Come on, come on, kid.
Stop looking around.
Stay.
[Whispering] Keep an eye out.
[Seagulls cawing]
I'm going inside the house.
Take the wheel.
I'll meet you on the other side.
We've got company.
Kill them all!
[Groaning]
Bulldog!
- Where's the boy?
- In the safe house. Southaven.
Gun!
[Screaming]
- Bummer. Damn.
- Bad parking.
[Tires skidding]
Sam, you go in around the back.
Bulldog, you stay here.
Come with me.
[Man grunting]
MAN: East perimeter, all clear.
[Screaming]
MAN 1: Did you hear something?
MAN 2: I'm not sure. Check it out.
[Gun fires]
Hello!
Get back!
Leave him alone, he's just a little boy!
He's scared!
Let him go,
or I'll kill him right here, right now.
Stay.
- I really need the bathroom.
- No, you don't.
You need to stay down there.
- Are you guys okay?
- Thank God you're here.
You all right?
- Watch them for me, will you?
- Okay.
All right, just hold on a second.
All right, we'll get you out of here.
Are you okay?
Yeah. Thanks.
Hello. Is anyone out there, please?
Come on.
Maxine.
- Bulldog. Take care of Eddie and Shondra.
- This way.
This is Merc 9. I've got a read on Seeger
in the west garden.
This just ain't your motherfucking day.
Chapel here. Do you have a read
on Seeger?
CHAPEL: Hello, is anyone out there, please?
Hello. Anyone, please.
Where are the hostages?
A read on Seeger, please.
Read, please. Anyone there?
Damn it!
You have a gun.
You gotta break your own rules, I guess.
Go ahead. Come on, shoot me down.
I didn't think so. You know why?
Yeah, because I'm the only son of a bitch...
who could do the things
that you always want getting done.
And quite right you are, sir.
I'll see you on the next gig.
[Car engine starting]
[Piano music playing on radio]
Have you seen Chapel?
You mean to tell me
you let that milquetoast pussy get away?
Milquetoast?
Man, I always thought he had
an explosive personality.
Oh!
Isn't that terrible?
Notice I said "had"
an explosive personality.
Let's go.
[Guns firing in unison]
SEEGER: I promised
I would bring him back...
with full military honors.