Good morning, America.
It's now twelve noon
in Salamanca, Spain.
In a short time, world leaders from over a
150 countries will meet here at Plaza Major,
to sign up to President Ashton's
bold new counter-terrorist strategy.
Since 9/11 more than 4500 people have
been killed in a rising tide of global terror.
Those lives will not soon be forgotten.
Today, world comes together to
take a stand against this violence.
We may be on a brink of historic agreement
between Western and Arab leaders.
Security services are on
high alert here in Salamanca,
and we now go live to our
news team on the ground,
and our reporter Angie Jones.
-5, 4, 3, 2...
I am standing inside Plaza Major
in Salamanca, Spain,
where crowds are lined up for a kick-off
of what is, without a question,
a landmark summit.
For months now, President Ashton has been
working with leaders from five continents,
to forge a new ground-breaking alliance
in the ongoing war on terror.
And now here, today,
Western and Arab leaders
will meet for the first time
to formalize this new coalition,
designed to, once and for all, put a
stranglehold on international terror.
Bring him up.
Tell us, Angie, what's the mood there?
-For the most part, hopeful.
Certainly, everyone here
is very sympathetic
to those who lost loved ones
in a recent bombing.
I did, however, speak to delegates...
-What is she doing?
...took a hard line, suggesting
that the US Foreign Policy...
Kevin, shut her down.
That's great.
Thanks, Angie.
Angie, what the hell was that?
Not everyone loves this, Rex.
Why don't you leave the punditry to
someone who's paid to have an opinion.
Hey, I'm cool with censorship.
I know the American people love that.
Come on Angie, lighten up.
Got it!
-For you.
-Yes. I told her. You wanna tell her too?
Fine.
Who is the clown on two?
Camera two are you gonna move or what?
We're here for the summit,
not the sideshow.
Man, it's like training a freakin' dog!
OK everybody, the President
is about to arrive.
When he does, we're on him.
Let's have our ducks in a row.
Three wider, four stay where you are.
C'mon, Kevin, get it moving,
I'm dying here.
Camera five, give me the motorcade.
Camera seven, concentrate,
I wanna go close on the President.
That's good, tighten up, five... good.
-Isn't that?...
-Thomas Barnes.
Why didn't we know he was here?
Shit. Grace, we should've had this.
-I know....
Kevin, call the archives.
OK, the President is approaching the Plaza.
All cameras ready.
Angie, we're back in
twenty, and remember...
we're here for the
summit, not the sideshow.
-There are other stories here, Rex.
-Which I don't give a shit about.
Unless the protesters set themselves
on fire, they're not our story.
Kevin, you got it?
-Yeah.
This was only last year.
I can't believe he's back already.
-You know, if we're the
only ones who have this...
-No, he won't talk.
I mean a year ago we had Hill,
we had that guy who saved Reagan...
-McCarthy.
All of them. It was a total hero piece,
Barnes wanted nothing to do with it.
-Well, that was then.
-Look, it's a shame...
it would've made a great side story,
but we've no time to work it in.
That was then, this is now.
OK, guys? We've got our story.
Okay.
Camera five, give me a single.
Three, four, get ready at the podium.
three go wide, four you're in close,
I wanna start with leaders
and end with the Mayor.
Thank you so much for being here.
Now three go back.
Camera six get ready,
we're coming to you.
Today, we make history.
That's good. Two, give me crowd.
Camera five, give me something
else to work with. That's good.
Angie, when this is over I want a fifteen
second fill, something to wrap it up.
Keep it simple.
-Want me to dumb it down?
-Get off it, Angie, come on.
Therefore, I offer you my city,
my country...
Ready with the graphics?
This summit can very well
be the defining moment...
-Pull out four, three...
Oh My God!
The President appears
to have been shot.
I heard two shots,
and the President fell.
What is he doing?
OK, five, stay with that guy.
Everyone else, give me Ashton.
Three, stick with the President.
Just stay with him.
That's good, just stay with him,
stay with him. Hold it there.
This is insane.
Yeah, yeah, coming in.
Number three, you gotta do better.
-They're not letting me through.
Don't give me this bullshit,
figure it out!
What the hell was that?
-It appears to be an explosion...
Camera four, turn around,
find out what that was.
Kevin, get the cameras going, we're gonna
have to uplink everything we've got.
Computer, uplink...
OK, Angie, you're on, lets go.
We are live, Angie, this is it. Go.
-I'm in the picture, right?
-Shit. Get Mark to stretch.
I know this is tough, OK? I know that.
We need you to tell us what's going on.
Focus, okay?
-Angie, please tell us what you're seeing.
-Deep breath, go.
The President of the
United States has been shot.
There have been several gunshots.
It appears there's also bomb
that went off inside the Plaza.
The people running scared...
Mark?
Mark, you gotta fill.
It seems that a huge bomb...
-Oh my God! Angie!
Angie!
Angie! Come on, kid, get up.
Kevin, pull the feed.
Turn it off.
Good morning, America.
It's now twelve, noon,
in Salamanca, Spain.
It's time.
All teams to the control...
It was before he lost it.
-C'mon...
Six months ago.
He's not that guy anymore.
Give him a break.
What are the chances he
freaks out on me when we walk?
I'd put it at 50-50.
We doing this?
Mr. President.
All teams, this is control.
Eagle is on the move.
Tell us, Angie, what's the mood there?
-For the most part, hopeful.
Certainly, everyone here
is very sympathetic
to those who lost loved ones
in a recent bombing.
Thanks.
For what?
For getting me back out here.
Don't thank me yet.
Mr. President, here we go.
What a beautiful baby.
Thank you so much.
A wonderful day.
Hey! Drop it.
All clear, number five.
Thank you so much for being here.
This is a wondrous day.
Today, we make history.
Señor Presidente,
fellow members of the European Union,
our friends from Africa,
President Ashton,
and citizens of the world.
This is a great day that
I invite you all to our town...
And it is the sad part
that we must...
Back annex building should've been cleared.
-Copy, it'll be cleared.
I've got a flutter on a second floor,
seventh window from the left.
Copy. We'll check again.
It's just a fan someone left on.
We got it.
Therefore, I offer you my city,
my heart, and my hope.
Barnes!
-Please.
-Get him out of here,
get him out of here!
Move, move, lets go!
One, two, three!
-You got him?
Find that shooter.
Control, I want you to clear a half a block out.
Clear all the buildings along the back annex.
No one goes out or in without our go.
OK, you got him?
Control. Come in, control.
We need a 20 on POTUS.
Damn it!
Listen to me!
We have to get out of here!
There's a bomb!
-Barnes!
Why did you run to the President?
Barnes!
I have to protect the Mayor. It's my job.
-You got up there pretty fast.
-Barnes, he's a cop.
-I don't care, he knows something!
Get him out of here!
Don't release him!
-It's a set up!
Control! Control, come in.
There's no response from control.
-I just spoke with them.
-We need to find that shooter.
-This never should've happened.
Except that it did.
And it happened on our watch.
I can't live with that.
We'd better find him.
Sir, we need your camera.
-Sure.
Where's the zoom?
-Right here.
Right there, that's where the flutter was.
The shot was up, to the left.
You saw the shooter?
-No.
But I saw something
like flash of light.
A saw a man in that window, sir.
-I'll check it out.
I'm coming with you.
-No, no!
If you're wrong,
let me take the heat.
Sir, did you film this entire thing?
-Yes.
-Show me.
I think I have a shooter on tape.
Go forward.
Oh my God!
There's a bomb in the podium!
-This never should've happened.
-Find that shooter.
A flash of light.
Find that shooter.
Jesus, Barnes!
Medic! We need a medic here!
Take it easy now, buddy.
Barnes...
Hey, hey, stop him!
Stop him! Stop! Stop!
Hey, freeze!
Secret Service.
I need to see your tapes.
-Yes, Kevin...
I need to see any footage you have
of the back part of the Plaza.
OK. Give me footage of the
back part of Plaza on two.
-Got it!
Give me everything.
Please play it back. Yeah.
Barnes, you were right.
-About what?
-About the shooter.
I'm in pursuit lead at the
back annex, heading west.
Repeat, heading west.
-Did you call it in?
No, no, I need you to.
-I got it. Go!
Control. Come in, control.
Control, come in!
This is Agent Barnes.
Control is down.
My partner is in pursuit of a suspect.
We need immediate assistance.
Just outside the back annex.
Headed west on a surface street.
Do you copy?
Back up is on it's...
What? Barnes, what is it?
Rewind that.
Stop.
Oh My God!
What? What did he see?
I'll be at the underpass.
And now, President of the
United States.
Thank you so much for being here.
This is a wondrous day.
Today we make history.
I'll be at the underpass.
...my heart and my hope.
Get him out of here!
Let me go! I work for the Mayor!
Let me go!
Hey, who are you?
Veronica!
We have to go!
We are all in danger!
She threw something!
Please, please, listen to me.
He's telling the truth.
I am police! My badge is here.
Listen to me. We have to go!
Calm down. Are you armed?
-Yes. I work for the Mayor.
Listen to me. We're in danger.
We have to get out of here.
Barnes!
-Why did you run towards the President?
I go to protect the Mayor.
It's my job.
You got up there pretty fast.
-Barnes, he's a cop!
I don't care, he knows something.
Get him out of here!
I've been set up!
You've got the wrong person!
Medic! We need a medic here!
Hey, stop him! Stop!
Hey, stop him!
Hey, freeze!
Get out the way!
Freeze!
Stop him! Someone stop him!
I'll be at the underpass.
Get down! Get down!
Call the police!
Move!
Out the way!
Shit.
Surprised to see me alive?
It's amazing!
What are you seeing?
-Oh, you speak English.
-That's right.
I was just watching...
people over there.
Hi, my name is Sam, nice to meet you.
-Howard Lewis, nice to meet you too.
American?
-Yeah.
Wow! What brings you here?
Just... looking for little excitement.
First time, eh?
-In Europe? Yeah.
I just felt like it was a right time.
What about you?
I go where the moment takes me.
That must be nice.
No family, right?
No, none that I know of.
You're saying you have
kids running around.
-Are your's with you?
-No, they're with their mother.
We got in a sort of a
bad patch right now.
I decided to get away for a while...
-I'm sorry.
-It's fine, it's fine.
I think it's my cue.
-Yeah, it was nice to meet you.
-Nice to meet you too. Best of luck.
Yeah, you too.
-Tell me your name.
-Anna.
-That's a pretty name.
You look about the same
age as my son Nathan.
Can I buy her another cone?
-Oh, no, it's okay. Thank you.
-No, really, it's no problema.
No, thank you very much.
Anna, I'm sorry.
Forgive me.
...President Ashton.
Welcome.
Thank you so much for being here.
This is a wondrous day.
Today we make history.
It is with great pleasure that I
invite you all to our humble city.
The hopes of the world are with us.
We must act together.
What is happening?
What's he doing?
Get him out of here!
-Let me go!
-What the hell were you doing up there?
-Answer my god damn question!
-Veronica!
Veronica!
We have to go!
Please, listen to me!
-Calm down.
-We have to go!
-Wait...
-Step away, sir.
-She threw something!
-A gun. It's loaded.
-Hey, back up!
-Listen to me, he's telling the truth!
Veronica! Veronica!
Hi, leave a message.
-Bev, it's me.
You're gonna see on the news
when you wake up in the morning,
that the President has been shot.
He was here, in Spain.
And I think I just saw
the guy who did it.
Look, I'm all right, I just
want you to let the kids know
that I'm fine, and that I love
them very much and...
and I think I got it all on tape.
I don't know what to do...
Sir, we need your camera.
-Sure.
-Where's the zoom?
-Press this button right here.
That's... that's where the flutter was.
The shot was up, to the left.
-You saw the shooter?
-I saw something, like a flash of light.
It was... right there, there was
something in that window right there!
-I saw a man in that window, sir.
-I'll go check it out.
I'm coming with you.
-No, no!
If you're wrong,
let me take the heat.
Sir, did you film this entire thing?
-Yes.
-Show me.
I think I have a shooter on tape.
Go forward.
Oh my God!
There's a bomb in the podium!
Medic!
We need a medic here!
Anna!
Where is your mother?
Where is she?
I gotta get you somewhere safe,
then we'll find your mother.
I need your help. I need you
to watch her, okay? All right?
Her mother is gone,
I don't know where she is.
-She'll be safe with me, don't worry.
-I'll be right back, all right?
I'll be right back. Wait for me.
-Take me with you!
I got to help the police.
Just stay with this lady
and I'll be back when I find your mom.
I'll be right back, okay? I swear.
I'll be right back.
Get out the way!
Mom?
Police!
Get out the way!
Move!
Police!
He's a cop.
Freeze!
They shot him.
Mom!
Anna!
When exactly do you think
the changes will be ready?
It's not like I have to
make the speech now.
I suppose I can just wing it, how much
trouble can I really get myself into?
Thing is, we both
know my limitations.
-Are we stopping?
-Yes sir.
Luke, I'll call you back.
NSA has just confirmed the threat.
Control handover complete.
-Roger that.
Where's Phil?
-At the hotel.
He's now at the Joint Chiefs.
You're sending a double.
-Yeah.
Delivering POTUS to the hotel.
Control, reversing the car,
POTUS is returning.
We're going to issue a statement
to the press that we'll be deferring...
Deferring, that's great.
Today of all days...
Christ.
Sir, we've used doubles since Reagan.
I'm not sure photo ops is appreciating this a bit.
Control, we have POTUS and
we're moving to the castle.
Eagle has arrived at the Plaza.
Control, we have POTUS and
are entering the castle.
Sir?
-Talk to me, Phil.
NSA called about five
minutes ago, it's real.
And the summit?
-We're not thinking of pulling out entirely.
Why would we?
Do we know who's behind this?
-It looks like a local group
with some sort of a vague connection
to the Mujahideen Brigade.
-Why issue the threat now?
-Couple of weeks ago,
US Special Forces uncovered a plot to
smuggle a dirty bomb out of Morocco.
We took their bomb, and their men,
and this may be their retaliation.
They try to kill me
as a retaliation?
POTUS is moving.
Safe for Eagle to exit vehicle.
-Copy that.
This is them?
-That's Suarez.
As far as we can tell,
he leads the group.
What do we know about him?
He's from Morocco,
educated in Paris.
He went off the map for a while,
but he surfaced in Beirut.
Couple of days ago, we intercepted an
e-mail between members of his group.
Embedded in it were links to maps,
blueprints of the area.
It wasn't until this morning
that we received the threat.
You talked to Joint Chiefs,
what do they recommend?
That we go after their leadership.
-Here in Spain?
Morocco.
We have a satellite locked
on one of their camps there.
You want me to call in a strike
on a friendly Arab nation?
They're harboring terrorists.
Is this intel certain?
-Absolutely.
Control, we're clear on seven.
Why aren't we focusing on the ones who
are here and are actually doing this?
-We are.
-This summit is too important.
-I know that sir,
but we're looking for five people
out of six million.
We are trying.
-Try harder.
Welcome.
This is a wondrous day.
Today we make history.
He doesn't even look like me.
Señor Presidente, fellow members
of the European Union,
President Ashton,
and citizens of the world,
it is with great pleasure that I
invite you all to our humble city.
Is that Thomas?
-Yes, sir.
I thought he was still inactive.
-He was.
Well if he's back,
why isn't he with me?
We're checking if he's ready.
-You sent him out there.
-We need someone to sell the double.
Sell?
He took a bullet for me, Phil.
And look at him.
He doesn't stop
punishing himself since.
Look, I liked him every bit as much
as you did, but we needed to know
we can count on him again,
before we put him on your detail.
So you threw him out there
to see if he's good?
Is that what you do
to your friends now?
Therefore, I offer you my city,
my heart and my hope.
This summit can very well be the
defining moment for this Presidency.
Jesus.
The President appears to have been shot.
-My God!
I heard two shots,
and the President fell.
Get the Joint Chiefs
on the line, now.
Mr. President.
-Sir.
Mr. President, the Chiefs have
a satellite lock on their village.
They are ready and waiting.
Ted?
-Well, there is an issue of when we can go.
We go now.
You can't give the order.
You've been shot.
If we go now, we risk telling the world
that you weren't really there.
But I wasn't there.
We get the Vice-President to do it.
No, we're not going there
on the 25th amendment.
Tell Rick to work up a story
that I was shot, but I'm OK.
That's not gonna fly.
-If we have to go to some
hospital and put on a show,
that's what we're gonna do.
We're not sitting this one out.
-Sir, we have to talk about this...
-I'm done talking!
Christ!
Sir, we gotta go now!
We have to attack. Sir?
Find out what the hell
is going on down there.
Mr. President...
Tell them to stand down.
-Sir, we have to respond.
Bombing a camp in Morocco would
blow this summit out of the water
and that is exactly what the
bombers want us to do.
-Mr. President, we have to act strong.
-No, we have to be strong.
They sent us a warning because
they want us to react.
They know our playbook, they are
banking on us doing what we always do.
We will hit back. We have the world's
sympathy right now, that's...
Honor that. Let's finish
what we came here to do.
OK, copy that. Sir, everything is being
prepared to transport the President.
Alright, that's it, we need to get the
President to Air Force One, right now.
I'm done hiding, Phil.
This is the President, is my wife there?
We have to be better than this.
-Sir.
-Yeah, get Air Force One ready,
and send a chopper...
-Hey, it's me.
No, we're fine, we're safe.
Good morning, America.
It's now twelve noon,
in Salamanca, Spain.
I am standing inside Plaza Major
This is for good luck.
I want to know if he's okay.
This was taken fifteen minutes ago,
I think you'll find that we're
taking good care of your brother.
What have you done to him?
He's still in one piece,
you should be happy about that.
If you do what you're supposed to do
your brother will be fine, but if you fail,
then this will be the last thing
you'll have to remember him by.
You look after yourself.
I'll be at the underpass.
Louis. Stick with the protesters.
They never see this side of the story.
To the last detail.
The beauty of American arrogance
is that they cannot imagine a world
where they're not a step ahead.
Reception.
Control, we have POTUS and
are entering the castle.
Copy that.
Eagle has arrived at the Plaza.
Javier.
-Yeah.
-Are you in the position?
-I'm on my way.
-Good.
For the moment Americans think
they've dodged the bullet,
do not be late.
-Don't worry about me.
I won't. Your brother spoke very highly
of your Special Forces training.
Do not disappoint him.
You just make sure my brother
will be at the underpass.
How's our boy doing?
Are we go?
There he is.
What are you seeing?
I think it's my cue.
-Yeah, it was nice to meet you.
-Best of luck.
Let's make ourselves a shooter.
That should keep him occupied.
Javier, are you ready?
Eagle is down!
Let's go, move it!
-Control room clear.
-Do you have the frequency?
4-1-9-1-0.
Control. Come in, control.
We need a 20 on POTUS.
Control!
Take care of him.
Lets go.
This is control, there are agents down.
I repeat, agents down.
We have a situation at the front
requiring immediate backup.
Heading to the lobby to assist.
Move, move, move!
Things clear on seven.
Get Air Force One ready and send a
chopper so we can get outta here.
No, we're fine, we're safe.
Get up! Get up!
Multiple casualties, I repeat,
multiple casualties.
Hey!
We need your help... now.
C'mon.
He's got no pulse.
Secret Service. I need to see your tapes.
-Yeah...
I need to see any footage you have
of the back part of the Plaza.
OK. Give me footage of the
back part of Plaza on two.
Again...
two... again!
Washington, this is Agent Barnes.
-Go ahead.
Control is down, my partner
is in pursuit of a suspect.
We need immediate assistance.
Just outside the back annex.
Copy that. Give me a heading.
Headed west on a surface street.
Do you copy?
Heading west, copy that.
Back up is on it's...
What? Barnes, what is it?
Barnes?
Oh My God!
No. If you're wrong,
let me take the heat.
Barnes, you were right.
-About what?
-About the shooter.
I'm in pursuit lead at the
back annex, heading west.
Barnes, what is it?
Barnes!
Secret Service, get out of the car!
Washington.
-This is Barnes.
-Go ahead.
Look, I know how this is gonna sound,
but Agent Taylor has gone rogue.
-What?
You gotta call in other agents back.
I know I made the call, but there's
something else going on here.
Control is compromised.
Listen to me, damn it!
God damn it!
Let him go.
What are you talking about?
-My brother.
I've done my part,
now you let him go.
-Put the gun down.
-Make the call,
or I pull the trigger
and your plan is finished.
Again.
Go ahead. Do it.
Do it and your brother is dead.
Can you live with that?
Knowing that your brother
died because of you.
Javier, listen to me.
He is going to be delivered
at the underpass.
Don't mess it up now.
You'll get your brother back.
Nothing...
nothing...
had better happen to him.
Nothing will.
Shit.
This is Agent Barnes again.
I've lost Agent Taylor, I need
a GPS location on his cellular.
-Copy that.
We did it.
Not yet.
Mommy!
Yeah!
-Barnes, POTUS has been abducted.
Present location unknown.
No signal for Taylor's phone.
It's imperative we locate
and apprehend Taylor.
Son of a bitch.
-He fell down.
-Leave him.
It's me.
-They bought it.
-What about Barnes?
He took the bait.
He's pissing in the wind.
He has created a manhunt for
a shooter that doesn't exist.
Have you got Javier?
We may need him later.
I'm on my way.
I thought he was
supposed to be dead.
We need to tie up
all of the loose ends.
Who's the loose end?
You are.
Lets go, lets go!
This is Agent Barnes,
I've located Taylor.
He's driving Salamanca police
vehicle, registration S-073654.
Headed south, repeat, south.
Just get me to my brother.
Christ, it's Barnes.
We got company.
It's Barnes.
-Can you lose him?
-I'm working on it.
C'mon, c'mon!
Shit!
-Have you lost him?
-I'm still working on it.
Well, until you do, stay clear
of the rendezvous. All right?
-No, we go to the underpass.
-You heard what he said.
I'm picking up my brother.
Are you out of your mind?
I worked too hard for this.
Either you're coming with me,
or I'll drive myself. You choose.
Shit.
Oh, shit!
Shit! Get him off my ass.
Happy?
Just drive.
-Where's my brother?
-Surprised to see me alive?
-Where is Veronica?
-Veronica said that...
I don't care what she said!
You both tried to kill me.
Where's my brother?
Looks like we've both been set up.
Mom!
Come on, lets go!
Where is he?
Back off.
Lets go, lets go, c'mon!
I will ask you again.
Where's my brother?
Go to hell.
Freeze!
Give me my brother!
He's dead.
God damn you! You used me!
I trusted you,
you son of a bitch!
Who's got POTUS?
You're too late, Tom.
Why the fuck did you do this?
You can't stop us.
No one can stop it.
This war will never end.
What have you done?
Who's got the President? Kent!
Stop him!
Get him under control!
Mom?
Anna!
Mom!
No! Don't kill him!
Look out!
Mom!
Jesus Christ.
Anna!
Mr. President?
Barnes, is that you?
Mr. President.
I've got you.
Can you sit up?
Are you injured?
-Yeah.
But it's not important.
This is Agent Thomas Barnes.
POTUS is in hand.
I repeat, POTUS is in hand.
We need a pick-up seven
blocks east of the Plaza.
Hello?
-Oh, thank God.
Howard, are you okay? Are you hurt?
-No, I'm...
-Are you sure? Are you okay?
I'm fine.
-We got your message.
Are you sure you're alright?
Yeah! No, I'm... I'm fine.
-I'm fine.
-Kids were really concerned about you...
Thank you, Thomas.
You're welcome, sir.
Reports out of Salamanca now suggest
that the President is out of intensive care.
His condition is listed as stable.
President Ashton has made a point of
reassuring Americans that he's alright,
and that summit will
continue in days to come.
Meanwhile, word from Spanish
and the United States authorities
is that they shot and killed
the lone assassin
responsible for today's attack.
On that our John McKendrick has more.
Transcript AP
Edited by Leapinlar