Mortal Kombat
is not about death...
but, rather,
the preservation of life.
Liu Kang
and few chosen fighters from the Earth Realm...
defeated Outworld sorcerer Shang Tsung.
According to the rules of Mortal Kombat...
their victory preserved the safety of the Earth...
for one more generation.
Our chosen ones
were returned to Liu Kang's home on Earth...
only to enjoy
a brief period of peace.
For someone from Outworld
has a different point of view.
Shao-Kahn,
emperor of Outworld.
The earth
was created in six days...
so too shall it be destroyed.
And on the seventh day,
mankind will rest...
in peace!
This is not good.
Somehow he's opened gateways
to your world.
I thought our victory in Mortal Kombat
closed those portals.
- What closes can also open again.
- What is that suppose to mean?
Mother.
You're alive.
Too bad you... will die.
As long as I have the power Khan,
you will never rule this world.
As long as the portal remains open,...
your world becomes my world!
You will never win.
Master.
This ends now!
You hide behind a human?
Why not, Lord Rayden?
You hid behind them
your entire pathetic life.
No! Johnnnny!
Surrender, Rayden, or this one dies.
Then I will take your generals.
Because Earth does not bend
to the will of tyrants.
You would never let
one of your precious humans die.
Trade me for Johnny Cage.
Come bow at my feet.
YOU FOOL!
In six days,
you will all bow to me!
It has begun!
We can't let Kahn get away with this.
This is not a fight we can win here.
Annihilate 'em!
We must go.
Move back!
Kahn has opened the portal.
Your planet and Outworld
have begun to merge into one realm.
Think of it as hell on Earth.
My mother... resurrected.
How is that possible?
If I'm correct, your mother Sindel
is the key to all of this.
This can't be!
We won the tournament!
The rules say the Earth is safe
for another generation.
Obviously Kahn has cheated and broken the rules.
I believe he has resurrected your mother to keep
these portals open indefinitely.
By reuniting you with her,...
Kahn's spell will be broken...
your mother's soul
will be at peace...
and his portals closed.
- How could the Elder Gods allow this?
- I do not know.
But Kahn must be stopped,
or your world will perish.
We have six days until annihilation.
I beat Shang Tsung.
I can beat Kahn.
Yes... You beat a great sorcerer...
and you win the tournament,
but you're no match for Kahn.
If anyone's going to kill Kahn,
it's going to be me.
Enough!
You are far from ready.
When those portals open
Kahn's extermination squads
will be everywhere, hunting.
I am telling you this
for your own good.
Kahn knows I have no powers
in Outworld.
As the two realms merge,
I will lose my powers here on Earth.
Each of you must grow stronger,
together.
We are the only hope.
Together...
We couldn't even save Johnny.
What do these do?
Once inside the velosphere, you can
travel to anywhere on Earth in hours.
The inner winds propel you.
You'll be moving so fast, it'll be
as though you're not moving at all.
Whoa...
We need your help, Sonya.
I will take you
to find your partner Jax.
Forget it.
- If I die, that's fine,
but I'm not losing anybody else.
- Alone, you are vulnerable...
but if you work together as a team,
you can do much.
- What about us?
- The two of you will travel to the Hopi mesa.
You did great last time Liu,
but this time you will need help
in what you are about to face.
Go deep into the night.
Seek the counsel of one called Nightwolf.
You will not find him.
He will find you.
I will speak with the Elder Gods
and I will demand answers to what Shao-Kahn
has done.
-Ready?
-Ready.
Here we go.
They are faster than I remember.
I can't wait.
This is amazing.
It's a hot air rising
from the Earth's core.
We've harness its energy.
What's going on?
Where are we?
The interchange.
Roll to your right. Hard!
Hold on to me.
Father, the merger has begun.
Earth is under attack.
And it is glorious!
Tell me... did you make Rayden beg for his life
before destroying him?
Rayden... is of no concern to us.
YOU LET HIM LIVE?!
He could not be stopped.
I have no use for excuses.
I have broken the sacred rules
to keep the portals open.
If the Elder Gods learn of our plot...
we shall both suffer the consequences.
I do not understand.
How can you fear the Elder Gods?
With control of the Earth,
our power will be absolute.
Until the sixth day has passed...
we can take no chances
with Rayden and his mortals.
Do not underestimate
the power of the human spirit.
Liu, if anything happens to me, I want you to...
Kitana!
I have lost everything.
I am not going to lose you, too.
Liu, the missile!
You must go.
There will be others.
I killed you in the tournament.
You killed my older brother.
So, why did you help us?
I helped her.
Because legend has it the princess
is the key to stopping Kahn plot.
You've been following us.
Why?
Two days ago, Kahn reprogrammed Smoke
to come after you instead of me...
in order to keep you apart
from Queen Sindel.
Alright.
So how do we get to Nightwolf now?
We have a common enemy,
Sub-Zero.
You must help us with your powers
if you want to stop Kahn.
Let's hope you succeed.
Get over here!
Take it!
SUCKERRRRS!
KITANA!
I've got to find Kitana.
Kahn wants you to go after her.
Don't.
Without Kitana, it's over.
We've lost.
What happened here, she proved you alone are not ready
for what's ahead.
You'll take the same track back
and turn where I showed you.
Don't worry about me.
Is it like this everywhere?
With each hour, the merger
of the realms grows closer.
More of the Earth will be destroyed.
I will meet you at the temple of the Elder Gods.
Jax!
Thought I was supposed
to be rescuing you.
Yeah, well I couldn't wait.
What the hell have you done
to yourself this time?
Cybernetic strength-enhancers.
It takes what you've got,
and quadruples your muscle capacity.
You've got a real confidence problem,
you know that?
These locks must be
on some kind of a remote-access mechanism.
What's going on? What you doing here?
Everybody split.
The whole facility is going to be trashed
by an extermination squad.
- EXTRMINATION SQUAD?!
What you mean, extermination squad?
- Look!
All you need to know is they're trying to kill me,
and probably you, too.
ME?! I don't even know these dudes!
Where you been anyway?
Damn it!
I can't get you free Jax.
Alright now, stand back, stand back.
Let's see what I'm made of.
Yeah... Now that's what I'm talking about.
Wish I had these babies back in high school.
- You're gonna wish
you were back in high school.
- Is that right?
C'mon Jax, Hurry!
What the hell is that?
Death is the only way out.
Major Briggs, Sonya Blade...
Shao-Kahn will be pleased.
Shao what?
I'll take homeboy.
Yo, I take it this ain't something
we can talk about.
I guess not.
Sonya, heads up!
Catch this!
Let's do this.
No.
Yeah, now what?
Cybernetic strength-enhancers!
Nice look...
But I'd lose the wall.
I was just getting
a feel for it, too.
Watch out, honey.
Watch out!
Damn!
You barbecued his ass.
Look at this.
- Does this mean what I think it does?
- Too bad I didn't get myself new legs.
My squads have already claimed thousands
of innocent souls on Earth.
And I will claim millions.
By now, you'd be behind bars on display
in a ZOO.
If those bars could keep me away
from you, Sheeva...
I would welcome them!
Silence!
What is your report?
Two of Earth's best warriors
have been taken...
Kabaal and Stryker.
Tell me, did you make them beg for
their lives before you destroyed them?
But Master... I thought if I let them live...
I have no use for excuses!
Rain...
this will never happen again.
It will never happen again.
It is true,
this will never happen again.
It is also true I need a new general.
You can die in duty or by my hand.
The choice is yours.
Centaurs are known
for their hunting prowess.
As your general, I will personally
hunt down every human soul...
And spare no one!
Motaro can't be trusted.
Long ago, I proved myself
as the personal protector of Queen Sindel.
Your orders are mine to follow.
The energies they waste
with their sniveling...
I will use to capture souls...
For you.
No.
You are all far too impetuous
for such an important work.
You... are my new general,
Queen Sindel...
unless anyone else
has a different point of view.
Pretty cool, huh?
It's my animality.
Who are you?
Wouldn't you like to know?
So you're Rayden's prodigy.
I've seen better.
Don't sweat it.
I've seen worse, too.
If you are Nightwolf,
you know I won Mortal Kombat.
Don't get cocky.
The tournament had rules.
This time, anything goes.
It was a mistake even coming here.
You think you're ready Liu Kang...
but if you were,
would Kitana have been captured?
Can you help me get her back?
Maybe...
Kitana is important.
But to beat Shao-Kahn,
you've got to pass three tests.
First one's courage.
- I don't have time for these stupid games!
- To test your courage and find your animality...
you've got to put yourself in a dream state.
And just how am I supposed to do that?
Well, there's a slow way
and there’s a fast way.
I don't have time for the slow way.
That's what I thought you'd say.
Sweet dreams, Liu Kang!
I had faith in you Liu Kang,...
but you have failed me.
You are not the warrior
I thought you were.
What if I fail?
What if I fail everyone?
Your brother's soul is mine!
Fight from the inside, Liu.
It's the fire inside of you,...
your everlasting faith in yourself...
that can never be defeated.
Liu Kang, the fire that burns inside you...
is guilt.
You lost Kitana.
You are not a leader.
Find that power inside you.
Feel your animality.
You...
will...
FAIL!
I am Jade.
I have searched the mesa for you Liu Kang.
Of all the horrors darkness holds...
to die alone...
that is my worst fear.
With you Liu Kang, I'm not afraid.
This is almost too good to be true.
The same could be said about you.
No!
My heart...
belongs to another.
I can't.
There's not much time left.
Is this just another dream?
How can you beat Shao-Kahn
when alone I'm too much for you?
First you betray me,
now you laugh?
You are more pure and faithful
than I heard.
You have passed the test Liu Kang.
A test?
This was just another one
of Nightwolf's crazy tests?
We could have killed each other!
But we live.
I will lead you to the temple
of the Elder Gods.
I can't.
If this was just a test,
it was only his second.
I'm not ready yet.
Not ready to save Kitana?
Because she's the key to all of this.
And I can take you to where she's kept.
She's alive?
For now, yes.
For how long, I cannot say.
We must go.
All your past betrayals
I can forgive.
Kitana, please accept this offering...
for I do not want your death.
You sorely test my patience.
You destroyed my family.
You drove my mother
to kill herself.
I am your enemy forever.
So kill me now... if you dare.
Foolish child.
A struggling worm and a hook...
lands a bigger catch
than a dead one.
No trees, no animals.
Damn.
What's going on here?
Nature's dying.
The merger of the realms
is almost done.
You know Sonya, you keep talking
about mergers and realms and all that...
but it don't mean squat to me, alright?.
I can't explain it.
The merger is close,
we've only got a few days left.
Use your imagination.
Use my imagination?
You keep talking to me like that Sonya,
and I'mma split, alright.
Look...
you dragged me out the base
with some lunatic killers after us...
put me in a spinnin' ball, take me
halfway around the world.
If I'm gonna die today,
at least tell me why.
Nobody told me
why Johnny had to die.
What is it with you?
And who the hell is Johnny?
O.K. Sonya, I'm your partner.
If you can't trust me,
who can you trust?
Well obviously, nobody but me.
Nobody but you?
Every time you ever needed me,
I was there.
I'm stuck in the middle of nowhere
because of you!
I don't even know where I am!
I need to use the rest room.
I ain't got no toilet tissue.
I got metal things on my hands!
Sonya wait!
Kitana?
You wish.
I told you these arms were good
at something.
Thanks Jax.
I owe you one.
I don't know how much longer
I can take this.
But you do look good in mud.
Jax.
Well you do.
I gotta go find a river.
We better roll.
Let's do it.
They don't use parachutes.
I have come
to the Eternal Palace...
because your sacred rules
have been broken.
Shao-Kahn has invaded the Earth.
As always Lord Rayden,
you are granted three questions.
The first must be:
Why was this treachery allowed?
We do not control destiny of men.
Everyone possesses the ability to change their fate.
So you will stand by and watch
the ruination of Earth?
You are correct...
in believing Kitana is the key
to closing Kahn's portals.
But if I reunite her with Sindel...
how can I be sure Kahn's portals
will stay closed until the next tournament?
Only when Shao-Kahn is destroyed
will the future be safe.
After living along with humans,
do you truly believe they’re worth saving?
More than anything I know.
Do you love them enough
to sacrifice your immortality?
I don't see no street signs,
no mailboxes.
Which tomb is the Elder Gods'?
Just keep moving Jax.
Sonya!
You know this dude?
Yeah.
Is that Jax?
Who is she?
Jade, this is Sonya Blade.
Major Jackson Briggs.
You've got an incredible set of legs...
for kicking I mean.
Where's Kitana?
She was kidnapped by Scorpion.
You lost Kitana
and you picked up her?
She helped me get here.
Now thanks to you,
we got Kahn's extermination squads on us butts.
Can I make a suggestion here?
Let's put this petty stuff aside and start worrying
about bigger things, like staying alive.
He's not here, either.
We're just gonna sit here
wait for this dude to show?
Without Rayden, it's hopeless.
Never give up hope.
At least not so early in a fight.
Rayden?
It's a new look.
Who's the girl? Can she fight
as good as she looks?
Better.
Good, because I was expecting
a team of fighters.
Instead, I hear fighters
war with each other.
Oh, give us a break Rayden.
We've been through hell.
Compared to what lies ahead,
you've been through nothing.
Where's Kitana?
Kahn took her.
It's all my fault.
This is not about blame.
We're together in this.
Each of us must help and support
the others, like a family.
What's the deal with your arms?
I've known you one minute,
and you're dissin' me already?
I mean no disrespect.
You have real skills.
Those arms are not your strength.
They're your weakness.
Oh, well thanks for the tip.
But these things right here,
state of the art.
Faith in yourself
is all you need.
And I say that to all of you.
I will try to open a portal to Outworld
while I still can.
Follow me!
My powers are leaving me.
Who does this dude think he is,
Moses parting the Red Sea?
Destroy... everything!
Whenever you're ready Rayden.
Come on.
That was fun.
They have taken the bait
and fallen right into our trap.
Proceed as planned.
I will await your arrival
in Outworld.
My skin is burnin' up,
but I'm freezin' inside.
Feels like I got microwaved or somethin'.
You never do get used to that.
My God is that what I think it is?
The realms are merging.
This will continue to happen unless
Kahn's portals are closed.
Time is against us.
- All those people in their cars...
- Torn between realms.
It's like a nightmare or somethin' man.
We have to stop this.
To do that,
we must rescue Kitana.
I know Kahn took Kitana
back to his fortress.
Hold up, hold up. Kahn?
You mean Mr. Bad Attitude back there?
You want us to check out his crib?
No way.
I ain't going
on no suicide mission.
Rayden!
Jax is right.
That's probably
what Kahn wants us to do.
No!
There is a secret passageway.
It was the one I used to escape.
How could you believe
the ruination of the Elders' temple...
would not put our plan in jeopardy?
It was necessary
to convince the mortals...
that their only hope lie in Outworld.
You seem confident that Sindel
will capture Rayden and his mortals in your trap.
I promise you father, on my soul.
All the millenniums of planning
will be rewarded.
You will be proud.
Know this...
I will take your soul myself
if you fail me now.
I will rally
the extermination squads...
and prepare for victory.
The merger
will soon be complete.
All your friends will be dead.
This must have been Edenia.
The royal family's temple.
Kitana told me I would find it here.
Look like this babe is havin'
a bad hair day.
They must have followed us.
Perhaps, but it may be
a blessing in disguise.
We need Sindel
to close Kahn's portals forever.
- I'll take care of her.
- I'll rescue Kitana.
Something finally went right for a change.
We won.
Who finished off Sindel?
After she blasted you,
I surprised her from behind.
Maybe she came in handy
after all huh.
You are witness to the dawning
of mankind's final day!
The two realms will be one!
Rayden and his mortals
have fallen for my trick...
and failed to stop us.
Bring Rayden and his mortals
to bow at my feet.
So then with their dying breaths,
they can witness the birth...
of the greatest army
in existence!
It's a trap Liu. Leave!
Up there!
The date's over.
Only your love...
can reunite her body and soul.
Kitana...
your love...
can break the hold
Kahn has over your mother...
and close his portals to Earth.
I have prayed for the day...
when our love...
will bring us together again.
Love.. I have never loved you.
With such a pathetic child as you,
what reason was there to love?
I knew it could not be true.
It cannot be.
But it can... and it is.
And you are powerless...
Thunder God.
It's over.
You fools.
You've been tricked.
The legend was a lie.
Kahn's portals stay open.
Now the merger
is nearly complete.
How could you do this to us?
It was so easy.
You will die for this, Jade.
That's it.
We trusted you, man.
And what happens?
You take us
on a wild goose chase.
I don't understand.
You were advised
by the Elder Gods.
The Gods must've lied to me.
Yo, forget your gods...
and immortals...
and all that junk!
I say the only ones we can trust
from here on out are humans.
Nobody else, not even Rayden.
Don't you understand?
By leading us here,
he is mortal now, just like you.
All his powers
have been sacrificed.
That's even worse.
How do we stop Kahn now?
There's more to this than Kahn.
If Sindel is not the key
to closing Kahn's portals,
then Kahn
has a higher allegiance.
Wait a second.
That tattoo.
I've seen it before.
On a robot and a woman.
They both tried to kill me.
And both of them
worked for Kahn.
This tattoo is a family crest...
bestowed only to my bloodline.
It is a permanent mark...
that allows safe passage
through the portals...
for the bearer
and his passengers.
The tattoos you saw, did they
flee the fighter upon death?
Took off like a bat out of hell.
Temporary passes.
The did not share my bloodline.
But if it's your family crest...
how can Kahn's side
have it, too?
My father is an Elder God.
And only they can bestow
such a marking.
Your dad's an Elder God?
Funny how you failed
to mention that before.
If your father's an Elder God...
what does that make Kahn?
Shao-Kahn is my brother.
It was not my fault.
I did everything you ordered.
It was your job
to lure them to an ambush.
If they escaped,
then you failed me!
We could never
have stopped them alone.
Listen to her.
She speaks the truth.
We would've died trying.
You.
You are already dead!
And you...
will be soon.
You will mount a defense
around my newest temple.
Prepare for Rayden to make
one last attack.
You said Rayden
was no longer to be feared.
I am to be feared!
For if you fail me now...
I will feed
your rotting corpse...
to the worms!
Your hallowed position
atop the worm pile appears...
to be most tenuous.
Now your failure
will be my opportunity.
Man, you got
one dysfunctional family you know that.
Years ago,
my father decreed...
that his heir to the family throne
must be strong enough...
to kill his own brother
in battle if necessary.
I beat my brother...
but I could not kill him.
Only one thing is certain.
Kahn must die.
This time you're going to kill him.
I could not then.
I cannot now.
So what do we do?
You will do your best.
It is all that can be expected.
I will pray for you all.
Listen to me.
Liu is our only hope.
I want to fight Kahn...
but I don't know if I'm ready.
You must believe in yourself Liu.
We believe in you.
My home.
The Temple
of the Order of Light.
Your family.
There's so no time left.
Whatever time we have...
we must use well.
Are we really ready to die here?
If we die...
we will die in battle.
Together.
Prepare for final battle!
Khan!
So good of you to join us, son.
In less than one hour, the merger
of realms will be complete.
Father, you alone
have the power to end this.
Stop!
I do not want to remember you
this weak!
It is not weak to value life!
I offer you one final chance
to return to my side, Rayden.
To rule all realms
with your family.
They are my family.
Then you shall die with the rest
of your pathetic human race!
FINISH HIM!
You should've killed me...
when you had the chance...
brother.
My brother died a long time ago.
His heart, anyway.
I win...
brother.
You cannot die.
I am proud to die...
a mortal.
Like you.
This is the beginning
of the end!
Show them the way...
to oblivion!
Mr. Ed is mine.
I'll take my mother.
Leftovers are fine with me.
Yeah I'll make you eat that thing.
I can't take
too much more of this.
Is that all you got?
Is that any way
to treat your mother?
My mother's dead.
As soon will be her daughter.
That just leaves
you and me, Kahn.
Pathetic and weak.
Clearly Rayden has molded you
in his image.
Without your weapons...
you are no match for Motaro.
Jax, help!
I got everything I need
right here!
Help!
Get off her.
Get down, Sonya.
- You OK?
- I'm fine.
So you finally got
your confidence back, huh?
Finally asked for help, huh?
Whatever you are...
you will live
to see the end of Kahn...
to give my mother's soul peace.
Face it, Liu Kang.
You...
will fail!
I can feel... it!
Now I done seen everything.
Impressive.
You've come prepared.
But not good enough.
Your blood flows, Kahn.
Just like the blood from a mortal.
Father...
How can this be?
I warned you
there would be consequences...
for breaking the sacred rules.
But I did not expect this.
Must I do everything for you?
The fate of the universe...
will be decided as it should be.
In Mortal Kombat.
Nothing can alter your destiny,
nor mine!
I can, and I will!
That was the longest week
of my life.
Oh, come on, Jax.
Could've been worse.
Could've been the last week
of our lives.
Yeah I guess that's right.
What's up with that?
Was I dead?
It is only right
that Shinnok's son...
be allowed to take his place
in the Eternal Palace.
You've become one of us.
I will never forget
this moment, Liu.
You've all made me very proud.
I will be watching you...
so stay out of trouble.
And remember...
be there for one another.
You're a family now.
Credit to: pawelwrc1@o2.pl
>> Napisy pobrane z http:/napisy.org <<
Modify by
-nttalex-