Chuck, see what it is.
( growling )
Hey, Miller,
we got something.
- Well, what is it?
- Will you just come here?
Well, I'll be.
They were right.
Yeah, I thought it
was a bunch of bull.
Who was right?
What are you guys
talking about?
Where've you been
for the last month, kid?
Why do think the Indians
have been picketing since
we started this job?
Yeah, man, they're claiming
we're disturbing some
ancient burial ground.
But the Katona tribe is
more than 20 miles away.
Yeah, I know,
But they think anytime
someone finds a freakin'
arrowhead around here,
The land is theirs
and they want it back.
Man...
This thing looks
over 100 years old.
Yeah, and it's gonna
look good in my den under
that moose head too.
- Hey, man, wait wait wait!
- ( growling )
What was that?
Nothing. Come on, guys,
we got to clear out this junk
So we can finish the job.
Now hit it with that pickax
and try to break it up.
Break it up?
Shouldn't we try to save it?
It might be worth something.
Whatever you say, son.
Give me that pick.
( growling )
What the hell was that?
You think those picketers
are out there beyond
the lights?
Yeah, and they're probably
getting a good laugh at
our expense too.
Jeez, that guy
is a hothead.
Well, let's just see 'em
come any closer.
Miller, you're taking
this way too far.
Give me that.
Come on, guys,
let's get out of here.
Not until we finish.
Riley, help me.
( rumbling )
What the hell was that?
An earthquake?
I don't know.
I think Hanson's right.
I say we call it a night,
fellas.
Riley,
I've changed my mind.
That sounds like
a good idea.
( growling )
( roars )
( screams )
Come get it.
( shrieks )
( screams )
Hey.
- Hi, honey.
- Hi, Dad.
Look at you.
You have grown up.
That's what happens.
Yeah yeah, I guess so.
Guess it's just more dramatic
'cause you're not here
all the time.
Well, here, let me take this
and let's get moving, huh?
Did your mother have
any instructions for me?
Instructions?
Yeah, like the last time
you came out
She told me how
to wash your clothes.
Even told me how
to make your toast.
That was two years ago.
I can make my own toast now.
Wow, you have grown up.
You said that already.
Look, your mother's in Europe
for the summer,
So like it or not,
We are stuck
with each other.
We can make it go
a whole lot quicker
If we're at least civil
with each other, huh?
I don't suppose
she gave you any instructions
on how to do that.
No.
I guess we're on our own.
( laughs )
What's all that?
Oh, a developer is building
a swanky resort.
Katonas are all
up in arms about it.
A swanky resort?
Here?
I know.
Come on, I'll get
your bag.
It's okay.
I got it.
Just like your mother.
Dex, I told you before,
don't call me here.
I'll see you tonight.
Morning, Sheriff.
Lolli, what's new
besides you having a date
with Dex tonight?
Did the picketers
give you any trouble?
No, I just walked by.
- Where's Kelly?
- She's coming in.
Even when you're together,
you're not together.
Lolli, is anything
happening?
Well, Sadie Riley called,
Said Paul didn't
make it home last night.
Maybe he's just pulled
another all-nighter
out at the site.
- I mean, they're
working 'em like hell.
- Yeah, Dex told me that.
I don't think so, Sheriff.
That was Lisa Miller.
Neil was supposed to
take their kid
to school this morning,
never came home.
He was working out
at the Krantz site
too, wasn't he?
I think so.
Mark, take the second car.
Go out along 81.
I'll check the 395.
Maybe they got in a wreck.
- On my way.
- And I'll meet you
out at the site.
Copy that.
Big Jim,
what are you doing here?
In case you haven't noticed,
the sun is up.
Well, truth be told,
today I got
babysitting duties.
What are you talking about?
The field trip,
the university kids,
the archeology class.
Remember that?
Oh, right right.
When is that?
I'm on my way over there
right now.
Well, keep an eye out
for Miller's truck while
you're out there, okay?
- Yeah, sure. See you later.
- Yeah.
- Kel!
- Hey!
- My Kelly Belly.
- ( giggles )
Oh, girl.
Look at you.
Hollywood is working
for you.
You look just one of
those Hollywood Hotties.
I don't even
live in L.A., Loll.
I live in upland.
Well, it's still
1,000 miles closer
than I'll ever get.
Well, don't go too far.
I need you to hold the fort.
Listen, Kel,
I gotta make a run.
I'll be back in an hour
or so, then we'll get you
situated, okay?
I got it covered.
All right.
Pomeroy, it's 8:20.
Where are the cement trucks?
Why aren't we pouring?
The foundations
aren't ready yet, sir.
I thought you had
that handled.
- Well, I did, sir, but--
- But what?
You told me you had
your best men on this
all night.
I did.
Well, where are they?
Why isn't the job done?
That's just the thing,
Mr. Krantz.
When Dex and I showed up
this morning, they were gone.
- They quit?
- Jimmy!
I don't think so.
Their cars are still here and--
And what?
Dad! Dad!
- Not now, Dex.
- We found more, lots more.
What are you talking about?
You found what?
I think you should see
this for yourself, Mr. Krantz.
This way, please.
Jimmy, wait here.
This is all I need.
This could be
an incredible find,
Mr. Krantz.
Right.
Cover it up.
What?
- Not now, Dex.
- You heard me.
Pomeroy, I told you
I want it buried.
But, Mr. Krantz,
Dex has a point. This is--
No "buts," Pomeroy.
The Native American Council
finds about this,
they could shut me down
for weeks, possibly years.
I've got too much invested
in this
to see shoot it down
the tubes right now.
Understood.
Dex, you know what to do.
Get the survey team started
on the second quadrant.
And you tell 'em
if they find any more
of these relics,
I want 'em bagged
and sent straight back to me.
Son, you heard the man,
get going.
Whatever you say, Dad.
( exhales )
All right.
How many men beside you
and your boy know about this?
Just the morning crew
of 10, sir.
Tell them I'm gonna
double their salary,
and I want them on the Hawaiian
project as of tomorrow.
Jimmy'll make all
the arrangements.
What about Miller
and the other two
that split last night?
If they come back again,
tell them I want to see
them first.
Now let's get this show
on the road.
I'll get the tractor
warmed up.
Yeah, you do that.
Look at him, will you?
He ain't had a hammer
in his hand in his whole life.
So what's up with
the big cheese anyway?
I didn't think
I'd see him out here
until the ribbon ceremony.
You know Mr. Krantz.
He loves to micromanage.
He wants you all to be
on the lookout
for any Indian relics
you might find in
the next parcel.
Maybe he should
come out with us and survey
and scout around a bit.
That's not gonna happen.
He's not gonna get his ass
out of the trailer.
It's gonna be
110 in the shade.
Meaning the faster
we get this done, the faster
we get out of here,
so let's head out.
Don't forget
to check in later.
Jim on radio:
hello, Steve.
Evans, go ahead.
It's Jim here.
I got the students
all situated pretty well
out at the Krantz site
and I'm headed back.
Any sign of Riley's truck?
That's a negative.
All right, well,
keep looking, will you?
Right, I'll keep my eyes open.
See you later.
Look at him, will you?
I thought we were out here
to study archeology,
not astronomy.
Give him a break, Josh.
I want to see the eclipse
too when it happens.
It's not gonna happen
for two more days, Rach.
Right.
Hey, Professor!
You find something,
Mr. McMurphy?
Not yet.
I was just wondering
how the stars
were looking this morning.
Your comedic talents
overwhelm me, Mr. McMurphy.
I'd think you'd want to drop
all your other courses
and concentrate solely
on standup.
Sorry, Professor.
Just kidding.
I know, but if
I've taught you anything
over the last semester,
it's that a good scientist
knows when to look down
and up.
Hell, a major celestial event
like this won't take place again
until 2078.
I can wait.
Is it true this is
the best place to
see it, Professor?
According to the observatory,
the optimum place
for viewing
the eclipse is right here
in the Alabama Hills.
I guess that's why
all the motels in town
were full up.
It's history.
Just like what you're digging
for here in the earth.
When you three realize
all the sciences are mutually
bound together,
you'll finally have learned
something meaningful.
Now keep working.
Hey, Professor,
wait a minute,
check this out.
What now, Mr. Cook?
Hopefully not more of
your would-be arrowheads.
No no,
this is something else.
Man, that's weird.
What is it?
- It's bones.
I can tell you that.
- Keep brushing.
Yes, by all means, Mr. Cook,
keep brushing.
That's no dinosaur bone.
Rachel:
it looks like a mammal.
I think it's a femur.
- ( rumbling )
- ( groaning )
Jeez, what was that?
A tremor.
I didn't know that
we were on a fault line.
We're not.
- ( rumbling )
- ( groaning )
Is everyone okay?
- Yeah.
Yeah.
Okay.
Let's get back to work.
( Chuckles )
( growling )
Oh my god!
( roars )
Run!
Get to the jeep!
Now!
Let's get out of here.
Oh my god.
( screams )
( Rachel screams )
Oh my god!
Oh, god!
Oh oh, please!
Please!
( sobbing )
Please, please don't!
Don't!
No no!
( screams )
Just in the nick of time.
Excuse me, sir.
There's a call on the car
phone for you, sir.
Right, take care of it.
Skipper, I'll give
the place the once-over.
Yeah.
That's Pomeroy over there.
Maybe he knows something.
Look, just make sure
that second quadrant
is clear, okay?
Sheriff, glad you're here.
I was just about to call you.
About two missing men,
right?
Actually three.
Well, there's Miller,
Riley and who else?
A new kid-- Chuck Hanson.
Just came on the past week.
Any idea what happened
to them?
Not a clue.
Pomeroy.
What's the Sheriff
got to say?
Sheriff,
this is Richard Krantz.
Mr. Krantz, it's a pleasure
to meet the man behind
the curtain.
You got quite
an operation here.
It's just the beginning,
Sheriff.
This desert is gonna
be an oasis within
two years. You wait.
I'm sure you're right,
Provided your workers
don't keep disappearing.
So they didn't make it home
either, I take it.
No.
You're working them
pretty hard, aren't you?
I pay them well, Sheriff.
This may be a little sensitive,
but why don't you question
the picketers
that are in front
of your office?
They're doing
everything they can
to hold up this project.
So you think the Katonas
are behind this?
No secrets
about the threats.
- Not to mention phone calls--
- Jimmy!
Yes, sir.
All I'm suggesting
is that the Katonas
have a definite motive,
and you should at least
question them.
Mr. Krantz,
until I find some evidence
of foul play,
I don't think
I'm gonna do that.
Sheriff.
I found this out
beyond the construction
perimeter in the brush.
That's Miller's rifle.
Along with this.
Well, that should be
enough evidence
for you to start
an investigation, Sheriff.
Mr. Krantz,
if it's all the same to you,
you do your job
and let me do mine.
Let's go.
All right, Pomeroy,
you're still pouring
today, right?
Yes, sir.
All right, let's get
the lead out.
We got some
foundation to lay.
Mark, I want you
to bag that stuff up,
drive it over to forensics
at County seat.
- Tell Coogan
to put a priority on it.
- Sure thing, boss.
And call Sachetti
at the impound.
Tell him to tow
those vehicles in
for a going-over.
What do you
think's going on?
I don't know.
I'm not quite sure,
But I don't trust that guy.
I think he knows
a hell of a lot more
than he's telling.
Where you headed?
Take a drive over
to the reservation,
talk to Storm Cloud.
Maybe he knows something.
Maybe he does,Chief.
Okay.
Yeah, no, that's fine.
It just means I'm gonna have
to make three separate trips.
Best get started
then, Mikey.
The Sheriff wants
those vehicles towed
in immediately.
All right.
I'll get on it
right away, Mark.
Right away.
Almost.
Well well.
- When did you
get back in town?
- This morning.
This morning?
I see.
What took so long?
Things.
I see.
And so now you're back
for the whole summer?
Apparently.
Do you have anything
you want to say to me?
Yeah.
Yeah, actually,
as a matter of fact I do.
I hayesed you.
Me too.
( squeals )
Man:
you make no sense at all.
Advancing our cause
doesn't mean you have
to be belligerent
with everyone
who disagrees with you.
I only want what's right
for our people and us, Kaya.
That's just it, Black Hawk,
there is no "us."
- There never was.
- What do you mean?
I don't wish to be a part
of your militant stance
with the townspeople.
Now you talk
like your grandfather--
Weak, tired,
unwilling to stand up
for our rights.
If the white man has
taught us anything,
it's that we must fight
for what we want.
Yes, fight,
but I do not like
how you do battle.
Well, hello, Sheriff.
- Kaya.
- You come to arrest
us all today?
No, nothing like that.
Just need some questions
answered is all.
- Is your grandfather home?
- He's just starting
sweat lodge.
Okay, I can come back later.
No, please,
I'm sure he'll see you.
Come.
Yeah?
All right.
So how's your teaching
been this semester?
It's okay, I guess.
It's been a bit tough.
With the cuts
in federal funding we've had
to combine a lot of classes.
But the students
have adapted well.
Maybe you folks
should think about opening
a casino around here.
Grandfather doesn't
believe in them.
Says they weaken the spirit.
Maybe so,
but it sure would bring
in some much-needed revenue.
And it would also bring
drunkenness,
prostitution and crime.
Steve:
oh, good morning to you,
Storm Cloud.
Sheriff Evans is here
to ask you some questions,
grandfather.
I didn't think you'd mind.
Running Wolf,
it is always good
to see a brother.
Haven't heard that name
in awhile.
Maybe you should use it
more often.
I might, if I could
only convince people
to get beyond the color
of my hair and eyes.
One just needs to look
at your beautiful daughter
to know that your bloodline
runs strong.
- So how is Kelly?
- She's fine.
Just got back in town today.
She has the spirit
of the Katona.
And her mother's attitude.
She's young.
Come.
Well, if you'll excuse me,
I must be going, Sheriff.
My next class is at 11:00.
Thank you, Kaya.
( hissing )
You have come about
the incident at the worksite,
have you not?
Yes, that's right.
How did you know?
I heard about it earlier.
- From who?
- Chinkana.
Chinkana.
Don't know him.
It's Indian for grapevine.
Yes, three men
have gone missing.
And you think that someone
here may be responsible?
Maybe, maybe not.
There have been threats made
by some of the picketers.
Angry words don't always
lead to violence.
Three men are missing,
but I didn't say anything
about violence.
If you know something,
Storm Cloud--
I know that
that's why you're here--
to accuse one of us.
This is just a follow-up.
None of our people set foot
on that ground last night.
And neither
should anyone else.
What happened to the men
was a sign.
The construction must stop.
With all due respect,
Storm Cloud,
That land is not
on the Katona reservation.
Still, it is on unholy land.
Listen to me.
I was out there just
this morning.
There is nothing there
to indicate
that your ancestors
were ever there.
Our ancestors,
Running Wolf.
Our ancestors!
Have you forgotten that
your grandfather,
A great chief, is buried
on this reservation?
No, I haven't.
You must never forget.
The blood of the chiefs
also flows inside of you,
Running Wolf.
It's what gives you
the strength over evil.
I understand that,
Storm Cloud.
But being Sheriff allows me
to extend that power
for the good of all.
Then know that whatever lies
out beyond our borders
should be left undisturbed
for the sake of all.
Well, half-breed,
who do you
serve today, hmm?
Indian or White Man?
Both equally.
If only it were the truth.
Dude, I say
we call it a day.
We got about another hour
of daylight left.
Let's just go ahead
and knock it off, though.
Then we don't have to
come back tomorrow, okay?
Whatever.
Hey, Lou, go ahead
and move to your left
about a foot, would you?
All right,
but let's make this quick.
I'm toast already on one side.
- ( rumbling )
- Whoa! Hey hey, hey!
What was that?
What the hell are you guys
doing down there?
- You didn't feel
that up there?
- Feel what?
We had a serious earthquake
just hit us down here.
You didn't feel it?
Come on,
quit fooling around, you guys.
Let's just get this thing done.
I didn't feel anything.
Okay.
Hey, Lou, do me a favor
and move forward
about three feet.
That's more like it.
( growling )
No!
What the--
Dave, Dave!
What the hell is that?
Let's get out of here, man.
Come on!
( groans )
Holy--
( screams )
( chanting )
Step forward, warrior.
You have seen
the Bone Eater.
It has risen,
And the sacred moon
will soon obscure the sun.
Time is short.
I must know its secret
before it's too late.
There is no secret,
only death.
They brought this demon
onto themselves.
But we can use it
to our own advantage.
No.
The Bone Eater is an enemy
of all life,
not just the white man.
Once all six renegades
have been resurrected,
The creature
will be unstoppable.
You must find the bone axe.
The creature must be destroyed
before the six become one.
If you're too afraid
to wield that power,
then tell me
of this sacred weapon.
I will find it myself.
Now who is being foolish?
Once the eclipse
has completed,
It will take the will
of the gods to destroy it.
I don't believe you.
With the creature
as our ally,
we could drive the white man
from all of our land,
Restore our people
to prominence!
Anger clouds you,
Black Hawk.
You cannot befriend evil
to do your bidding.
There must be a way.
And I will soon discover it,
With or without your help.
( continues chanting )
( loud rock music playing )
Hey, Kelly,
turn the music down, will you?
I'm on the phone.
All right!
I'm sorry, Sal.
If you don't mind,
could you repeat that?
Yeah, no problem.
I said I found traces
of crystallized blood
and bone samples
- embedded
in the cloth you sent me.
- What does that mean?
Well, for that to happen,
the victim would have had
to have fallen
straight into a blast furnace.
There's nothing like that
out there.
And here's something
for sherlock Holmes:
The shirt itself
shows absolutely no signs
of being burned.
Could the blood samples
have been introduced
into the cloth
sometime later?
Not a chance.
You sure about that?
I'd stake my pension on it.
Well, thanks, Sal.
As usual,
you've ruined my day.
Sorry, Steve.
I'll send you
some free aspirin,
on the county.
Yeah,
I'll be looking for it.
( wolf-whistles )
Come on, Dad,
nobody does that anymore.
Well, I guess
I'm getting old, Kel.
Where you going
all made up like that?
I'm going up to big pine
to see a movie.
Tonight?
We haven't spent
two minutes together.
We have all summer, right?
Yeah.
I don't want you going up
to big pine tonight.
What's the big deal?
It's just a date.
With who?
It's not that Sachetti kid,
is it?
- What if it is?
- He's too old for you.
Dad, he's just 21.
Well, four years at your age
is a lot of difference.
Mom is four years younger
than you.
It's not the same thing.
It is to me.
I can handle myself!
Yeah, well,
that's just what I'm afraid of.
Look...
Can't you just humor
your old man once
and stick around?
No, I'll be back later.
No, you'll be back
at 11:00.
Dad, I'm 17.
My house, my rules.
- 11:00.
- Whatever.
Great.
Let me
get this straight.
You just compromised your
integrity for money?
What he's doing is wrong,
Dad, and you know it.
Look, don't lecture me
on what's right and wrong,
all right?
That money is putting your ass
through engineering school.
You don't want it?
You wanna spend the rest of
your life digging ditches?
- That's fine with me.
- Money isn't everything, pop.
And I'd rather you not sell
your soul to Krantz
just to put me
through college.
Look, son,
it's easy to have high morals
when you're 22.
But at my age,
how am I gonna start over?
A man like Krantz
has the power
to ruin me
for the rest of my life.
Only 'cause you gave it
to him, Dad.
( doorbell rings )
Kaya,
is everything okay?
I hope it's not too late.
No, not at all.
Please, come in.
Anything I can get you?
No, thank you.
I'm fine.
So what brings you over?
Look, Steve,
I know why you were
at the reservation earlier.
It's those missing men.
Storm cloud sent you,
didn't he?
I felt that he was
holding something back.
No no,
I came on my own.
Look, Kaya,
All evidence points to the fact
that these men are dead.
Now if you know something,
you need to tell me.
Well, it's not something
you're gonna want to hear.
It's Black Hawk,
isn't it?
No.
Have you ever heard
the legend of the Bone Eater?
Yeah, the curse of Torak.
Yeah, my older brother
used to spook me
by telling me scary stories
about it.
Well, according to Storm Cloud,
the legend is true.
- Come on.
- Two centuries ago,
The Katona tribe
and white settlers alike
were menaced by a band
of six renegades
led by a young shaman
named Torak.
Yeah, he was bypassed
as rightful chief,
So he broke
from the tribe, right?
They harmed so many
in their quest for power,
engaging in ritualistic murder,
even cannibalism.
It took several
medicine men
and many warriors
to finally surround the six
and destroy them.
They were buried
unceremoniously
in the same area
where 30 years ago
A group of miners uncovered
the sacred bone axe.
Tragically, the creature
awoke from its slumber.
The men were pierced
with shards of sharp bone,
disintegrating them.
( growling )
( screaming )
Kaya:
Before the miners realized what
they had done, it was too late.
One of them was able
to pierce the creature
with the sacred bone axe,
sending it back
into the earth.
But unfortunately,
none of them survived.
By building on that land,
Krantz has desecrated
the sacred ground
And once again
awakened the Bone Eater.
That is why Storm Cloud
wanted the ground left alone.
Kaya, this is
the 21st century.
I can't act on legend.
These are evil spirits
that were sealed
in the earth eternally
with a sacred war axe.
Yeah yeah,
and before he died
Torak cursed his killers,
Saying that his bones
and the bones of his brothers
would rise up
like a demon
and take revenge.
Right after the ghost
of Christmas past.
I should not have come.
Kaya, I'm sorry,
listen.
Please please,
forgive me.
It's just that I've got
three men missing,
presumed dead, and I can't go
to these people's families
With legends
of bone creatures.
Steve, this demon lives.
We are in great danger.
Kaya.
For what it's worth,
Thank you for coming over here
and telling me this.
It is only worth something
if you listen.
Now just for a few minutes,
okay?
Relax, Lol,
nothing's gonna happen.
Well, maybe something.
Yeah, if you're lucky.
I got something for you.
Yeah, I got a good idea
what it is too.
( laughs )
No, really.
Here.
Oh my god, Dex.
You're so sweet.
- What is it?
- Go ahead and open it.
I can't believe it.
It's so beautiful.
- Where did you get this?
- At the site.
You're kidding me.
No no, there's tons
of great stuff out there.
But when I saw that,
I knew it was meant for you.
I took it to the town jeweler,
had him shine it up like new.
You're the best.
Here, wait.
Let's see what it looks like.
So what do you think?
It's beautiful,
just like you.
( growling )
What was that?
I don't know.
( screams )
Run, Lolli, run!
( phone ringing )
Hello.
- ( beeping )
- ( whimpers )
Hello, Kelly?
( horn honking )
( screams )
- He's gonna kill me.
- No, he won't.
- You have a legitimate excuse.
- Yeah, well...
What's wrong with you?
I don't know.
You just get in here today,
and I'm already thinking
about you going back.
Don't.
Why don't you just stay?
And live where?
With my father?
We'll be lucky
if we make it through
the summer in one piece.
So come live with me.
Do you want to be the one
to tell him that?
No, thanks.
Jeez, it's so late.
I gotta go in.
Do you want me
to come in with you,
try to explain?
No no no, I think it's better
if I do it myself.
- Where is my purse?
- I think you left it
in the back seat.
What is that?
That? I don't know.
It's some old tomahawk.
I found it lying
around the lot this afternoon.
Now...
Why don't you slide
over here a minute?
Oh, jeez!
Okay, you have to go.
Okay okay.
Hey, call me tomorrow.
Okay, just drive.
Do you know what time
it is, young lady?
Late, I know.
It's 3:15 A.M.
That is beyond late!
Kelly, I thought I told you
to get back home
before 11:00.
I would have been, Dad,
but there was a huge accident
on the other side
of the county line.
Come on, that kind of B.S.
Doesn't cut it with me anymore.
I'm not lying.
If you don't start telling
the truth, you can forget about
ever seeing that
Sachetti kid again.
You can't tell me
who I can date.
When you're in my house,
I sure as hell can!
Look, Dad,
There really was
an accident, okay?
Traffic was backed up
for miles.  I'm surprised
they didn't call you.
Yeah, me too.
( phone ringing )
Yeah, Evans here.
Hey, boss, sorry to wake you.
It's Roberts.
That's okay, buddy.
I was up.
Just got a call from Burns
down at the station.
He got a dispatch
from highway patrol
about a truck accident
a couple hours ago
up near Big Pine.
Yeah, Kelly was just
telling me about it.
Sheriff,
there's something else.
A vehicle was found
smashed to pieces
up on Krantz's property
near the site.
How's it affect us?
They found a purse
on the side of the road.
Sheriff, it's Lolli's.
Are you sure about that?
Yeah, they found her county I.D.
Inside the wallet.
- They called us right away.
- Right.
I'll go check it out.
Sheriff, if it's okay,
I'd like to go.
Yeah, I'll see you
out there.
What was that about?
Nothing, it's just routine.
Now who's B.S.ing?
I'm sorry, honey.
I really am.
I shouldn't have doubted you.
So what's really the matter?
Lolli may have been hurt.
I'll call you
when I know more, okay?
Hank, you got any
of this figured out yet?
Not yet, Steve,
But it's the damnedest
thing I've ever seen.
The skid marks are here,
yet the truck's over
100 feet away.
Looks like somebody moved it
after the accident.
That would take
half a dozen tow trucks.
Yeah, and why the hell would
anybody want to do that?
And the driver?
Not here.
I figure he must
have been thrown clear
and wandered off in a daze,
unless somebody
carted him off.
Where'd you find this?
Right over there
by the shoulder.
Show me exactly.
Heads up.
Here comes trouble.
Yeah, you got that right.
Sheriff, this is getting
way out of hand.
You haul that chief in
for questioning
and I guarantee you
he's gonna crack.
Mr. Krantz, there's still
no proof that the Katonas
are responsible for this.
When are you gonna to wake up
and smell the war paint?
First, three men are missing.
This driver's the fourth,
to say nothing
about my property.
Now it's obvious
to me that they are responsible
and I want to know
when you're going to
make an arrest.
Let me ask you a question
for a change.
What?
Have you uncovered
anything unusual recently
out at your site?
What's that got to do
with the price of eggs?
Well, have you?
No, I have not.
Well, you realize
of course that failing
to notify the authorities
of a historical find
on state-granted land
would constitute fraud.
Could even subject the owner
to severe civil
and criminal penalties.
You know, Sheriff,
I've been in business
a long time.
I've gone head to head
with the top men in
almost every field.
And I don't intend
to be intimidated
by some bumpkin lawman
who has a soft spot
for his people.
Now I suggest that
you find out what's going on,
and I mean fast,
because the next phone call
I make
is to your boss
in the county office.
Fine.
Here.
Number's on the card.
Excuse me, Mr. Krantz.
Mr. Pomeroy's on
the car phone.
- he says it's urgent.
- what does he want?
- He wouldn't say, sir.
- I'm leaving here anyway.
Come on.
- Yes, sir.
- Let's go.
You complain about having
to get me coffee.
Never again, Sheriff.
What a pair.
All right, where was
that purse exactly?
Right over here.
Found it
sitting right here.
Thanks a lot, Hank.
She came from the woods.
She was running.
Hard.
You can tell all that
just by looking at the grass?
My grandfather taught me
when I was a kid.
Yeah, but how can you tell?
A good Indian tracker
can read a trail across
solid rock.
Come on.
Got something, Sheriff?
Yeah.
Yeah, look here.
This branch was broken
fairly recently
and it came from at least
15 or 20 feet up
in these trees.
So whatever was chasing her
was at least that tall.
A bear?
A 15-foot bear?
Not likely.
Well, what then?
What's this?
Look at these relics.
This could be an old
Indian's grave.
I thought the ancient tribes
never buried their own
in the ground.
No, they burned the bodies
as offerings to their gods.
Monroe to Sheriff Evans,
come in.
This is Evans, go ahead.
Hey, Steve, those helicopters
haven't found any sign
of that missing driver yet,
but we did spot an abandoned
vehicle
Along the road to the lake.
All right, we're close.
We'll check it out.
You got it.
A couple patrol cars are coming
down the service road as well.
We'll meet 'em.
Out.
Let's go.
Look, Miss hayes,
I'm dumping $110 million
into one
of your communities.
The least I can get
is a little damn cooperation.
I have to let him run
his investigation.
Investigation?
Is that what you call it?
Because I'm up to my ears
in O.T. Pay.
I've got delays upon delays
because my men won't come
to work.
Now I don't care who's running
this investigation.
I just don't want them running
my corporation into the ground
- while they do it.
- I understand.
And I am more than sympathetic
to your position.
However, I can't,
and I will not railroad
any officers
under my jurisdiction
to bend the law
to suit your financial needs.
Miss Hayes,
if I'm not mistaken,
Your term is up
in three months
and you're seeking
re-election.
I know this because a number
of people in your party
have contacted me regarding
substantial contributions.
Maybe they think
what I'm doing in your town
Is worth a little more
consideration
than I'm currently
being given.
Is that a threat,
Mr. Krantz?
Politics and favors
make wonderful bedfellows.
Do you understand
what I am talking about?
I understand this.
I will talk to Sheriff Evans
myself.
You just better pray
that everything going on
at that worksite
is on the up and up.
Do you understand
what I am talking about?
Good day, Mr. Krantz.
Mr. Krantz,
we're here, sir.
- Where is it?
- This way, sir.
- Jimmy, you wait here.
- Yes, sir.
Anybody else see this?
No, I just uncovered
it myself.
I called you
as soon as I did.
I sent the other guys
to the main site as soon
as I saw it.
How long do you estimate
it's been here?
A hundred years,
maybe two.
Well, I don't care
how you do it,
but I want it gone,
you understand?
Mr. Krantz, this is more
than just plowing under
some artifacts.
Pomeroy, do you
like your job?
Sir?
You do as I tell you
and there's a nice bonus
in your next pay envelope,
okay?
- Mr. Krantz--
- No buts.
You bag up the bones
and get 'em off my property.
You got it?
Got it, Mr. Krantz.
Good.
Jimmy.
- We're out of here.
- Yes, sir.
Copy. They're running
the plates right now, Sheriff,
But this is Pomeroy's truck
all right.
Yeah, I tried
to call his father
but the cell service
is dead out here.
Yeah, a 9mm
missing the clip.
- Looks like
more of the same, huh?
- Sure does.
What now, boss?
I say we hitch a ride
back to our cars.
I'll check in at the office.
You stop by the Pomeroy place.
- It's on the way.
- Roger.
( fire crackling )
( knocking )
- Where's Storm Cloud?
- He is not to be disturbed.
- I will see him now.
- No!
He is on vision quest
seeking a way to undo the evil.
He can't do that!
That fool!
How dare you transgress
the prayers of a chief?
Have you forgotten
your place?
I have no place
with cowards.
( siren wails )
Damn!
( exhales )
Hey, Mark, what's up?
I wasn't speeding,
not down that hill.
No, Seth. No tickets today.
The Sheriff wanted me
to talk to you.
Why, what's wrong?
I'm wondering if you know
where Dex is right now.
No, what happened?
I found his truck
down by Pine Lake
This morning, abandoned,
no sign of him.
So what are we talking about,
another kidnapping?
No, I can't be sure
of that.
I'm going right down there.
Where exactly is it?
I'd appreciate it
if you talked to
the Sheriff first.
Mark, come on, please,
take me to where the truck is.
- ( rattling )
- What was that?
Nothing.
I didn't hear anything.
There it is again.
What you got in the bag,
Seth?
I, um...
Seth, what's in the bag?
( growling )
Get in the truck!
What the hell
is that thing?
I don't know,
but it looks like
it's gonna take more than
bullets to kill it.
( gun clicks )
( screaming )
Oh my god, no!
- Hey, Steve.
- Jim.
Any word on Lolli yet?
No, nothing yet.
I checked with her mother
and some of her friends
and nobody's seen her
since yesterday.
How about Roberts?
He checked in yet?
No, not a peep.
I'll try to raise him.
Yeah, he's probably sleeping.
I could use some myself.
Oh, Commissioner Hayes
called.
She said she wants
to talk to you right away.
Oh, brother.
How'd she sound?
Same as usual-- pissed.
Yeah, get her on the line
for me, will you?
Yeah, sure.
This is Evans.
Steve, Hayes. What the hell
is going on down there?
What do you mean?
I've got Richard Krantz making
a lot of noises up here
About some Indian uprising
against his new development
project.
That's not even close
to the truth.
He says the evidence
is overwhelming
and you've refused
to make any arrests.
Hell, I could go down there
right now and arrest
the whole damn tribe,
but that's not gonna stop
what's going on.
Well, it better stop soon.
There's a bank full of money
at stake here,
not to mention
the political fallout
if this project isn't completed
on schedule.
And if you can't handle it,
the governor is gonna have
to send in the militia
to keep the peace
and protect those workers.
Got it?
Yeah.
Yeah, I got it.
Good, keep me posted.
Hey, Steve.
I tried Roberts twice
on his car radio,
still no answer.
Well, try his apartment.
If you get him,
you let me know.
Yeah, will do.
( panting )
Grandfather,
where are you going?
It is time.
I've seen the end.
We must find the bone axe.
But it took many warriors
to destroy Torak.
Kaya, please.
There is no other way.
- The beast must be stopped.
- No, not the Bone Eater.
There are too few
of you to defeat it.
I cannot undo
what has been done,
but I can
put a stop to it.
Now please, Kaya.
Stay with the tribe.
You'll be safe here.
Dad!
Dad, did you
find out anything?
No, nothing yet, Kel.
Who would do such a thing?
I don't know, honey.
We can't assume
the worst yet.
She is still
just a missing person.
They've had choppers
and search parties scouring
that area all day.
If she's out there,
believe me, honey,
they'll find her.
Are you sure?
I promise.
I'm doing everything possible.
Burns to Evans.
Burns to Evans, come in.
What's up, Big Jim?
I just got a call
from the emergency room
over at the trauma center.
They found Mark
lying on the side
of the road up near
Whitney Portal.
They're bringing him in
right now.
What's his condition?
Well, according to
the paramedics on the scene,
he's in pretty bad shape.
They want you
over there pronto.
I'm on my way.
I'm coming with you.
All right, all right,
jump in.
Burns to Evans.
Burns to Evans,
Come in.
This is Evans,
go ahead.
Steve, there's a woman here
from the reservation.
She says that
it's imperative that she speak
with you immediately.
- What's her name?
- Kaya.
Big Jim, tell her to meet me
at the hospital.
Steve:
Any idea what happened?
Based on his condition,
I'd say something outside
of the norm.
How so?
Follow me.
Look, honey,
why don't you go out
and wait in the hall
While I talk
to the doc, okay?
- Okay.
- All right.
This one's got me stumped.
The bones in his right arm
and his right hand
are completely gone,
resulting in this
fleshy mass.
What could have done
something like this?
I'm just a country doctor.
I'm not a specialist.
Can he talk?
Well, understandably,
he's in shock.
I wouldn't bring him out.
Well, did he say anything
when they picked him up?
Yeah, the paramedics said
that he was rambling on
about being attacked
by some giant
skeleton-like creature.
Obviously a delusion
from the pain.
Yeah yeah, right.
You take good care
of him, doc.
What are you gonna do?
I'm gonna try
to find that delusion.
I want six others to patrol
that south perimeter.
You hear so much
as an owl fart,
you shoot first
and ask questions later.
Mr. Krantz, we have
a problem at the main gate.
- What?
- The Katonas.
Son of a bitch!
We request peaceful access
to your property.
Krantz:
you're too late, chief.
You Katonas have
taken this situation
way out of hand.
It is you, Mr. Krantz,
that has broken this ground.
And it is you
that have uncovered these unholy
relics of our ancestors.
I don't know
what you're talking about.
The bone axe.
It was here somewhere,
and we must find it.
You take one step
through that fence,
the only thing you're
gonna find is hot lead.
You understand me?
- ( shrieking )
- What the hell is that?
Get out.
Come on, get out of here!
Come on, go!
Go now!
Go! Go!
( screaming )
Can't get it open.
( both scream )
Jimmy, come on!
Oh, god!
No!
( both scream )
Dad, who would
do that to Mark?
Well, if you believe
Storm Cloud, there's some
sort of weird creature
running around the Indians
call the Bone Eater.
You don't really
believe that.
Well, something's going on,
and right now nothing
is making any sense.
- Steve!
- What are you doing here?
It's Storm Cloud.
What is it?
He took some of
the tribe and he went
down to the worksite.
Why?
He's looking for
the sacred war axe.
Yeah, well,
all he's gonna find is trouble.
- You have to stop him.
- Burns to Evans,
Burns to Evans,
Come in, please.
This is Evans.
Go ahead, Jim.
Steve, I just got a call
from the Krantz site.
They say they're surrounded
by Storm Cloud and his people.
All right, I'm on it.
Kaya, take Kelly home
for me, will you?
I just hope I can get there
before it escalates.
( siren wailing )
What's the war axe
look like?
It's an ancient Indian
weapon made with sections
of buffalo jaw,
much like a tomahawk.
I just saw
a tomahawk last night
in the back of
my boyfriend's truck.
- It was really old.
- Are you sure?
I'm positive.
He said he just found it
lying around the impound lot.
We gotta call him
right away.
Storm Cloud?
( chanting )
Storm Cloud.
Go, Running Wolf.
Go now!
I can't hold it
for very long.
Hold what?
Sheriff, get in!
Get in!
Go! Go!
( roars )
Sheriff, what the hell
was that thing?
Something I've got
to stop before tomorrow.
That I can tell you.
You mind telling me
how you plan to do that?
You just let me
figure it out.
I appreciate the lift,
though.
Yeah, no problem.
What the hell were you
doing out here anyway?
Kelly called me
on my cell phone.
She wanted me
to give you this.
I found it yesterday
in the impound yard.
She said for you
to take Storm Cloud
to the reservation,
Said that he would know
what to do with it.
Yeah, well...
Storm cloud
didn't make it.
Sheriff, no offense,
but I really think
that you need to call
the Army or the FBI.
They won't believe it.
By the time they
decide this thing is real,
it'll already be too late.
All right.
What are you gonna
do about it?
I want you to drop me off
at the reservation.
Then I want you
to head back to town.
You get Kelly
and her friend Kaya.
You wake 'em up
if you have to,
but I want the three of you
as far from Sweetwater
as possible by sunrise.
All right.
- What about you?
- Don't worry about me.
Mike, you gotta be
miles away from here
before that eclipse tomorrow.
You got it?
Yes, sir.
So what's the deal
with this weapon?
It's the key to stopping
all the evil.
- How?
- ( horn honking )
Come, we must go.
I'll tell you on the way.
Mike, what is going on?
Where's my father?
Your father's all right.
He went up to the reservation
to get something.
He went with
Storm Cloud?
The Sheriff said
Storm Cloud didn't make it.
Oh my god,
Kaya, I'm so sorry.
Ladies, listen,
the sun's gonna be up soon.
We gotta be out of here
before the eclipse, okay?
I'm not leaving
without my father.
Kelly, the last thing
that your father said to me
was "get my daughter
and get her out of town
and don't let her
talk you out of it."
- No, but--
- No, there's gonna
be no talking.
Get in the truck right now.
Both of you, come on.
I see you're finding
your Katona roots.
Put the knife down.
Put the axe down first.
I can't do that.
I said,
Put the knife down now.
Whatever you say,
Sheriff.
What's the matter?
You get soft doing
the white man's bidding, huh?
( yells )
( grunts )
May your soul find peace.
Hyaa!
( horse whinnies )
It's getting darker.
Yeah.
It's starting.
( growls )
( whinnies )
( roars )
Whoa!
Hold on, hold on!
Oh my god!
Dad!
Baby.
- Are you all right?
- Yeah.
- All right?
Welcome back to the tribe,
Running Wolf.
I never left.
( instrumental music playing )
Subtitles by LeapinLar