In the land of "SPARTA"
Are babies born,
Checked for errors
By the ancient prophets.
Ah! Are you my mother?
Because I am ready,
To your nipples used to suck!
And if there is a mistake in Saturday ...
Then the babies were launched.
If it is a Vietnamese baby,
Then Angelina is the first option.
Lovely, huh?
And then you Leonidas ...
AWOE!
The perfect Spartaan.
GOOD KVALIFICIRAN BY PROFEET # 12
At a young age,
Leerde Leonidas all to fight.
Come on, you little opdonder.
Come on!
You can not win me!
You will never be a good Spartaan, never!
Here Grandma ... Suit?
He was tortured ...
But torture is not very!
Tell me again, Mr.. Bond,
What is your account number?
Who's really weather, Mr.Bond?
I am Leonidas.
You are my patience to the test
Double "00"
I am not double ooooh ...
Let the sun shine even more for me.
That looks good from huh?
But it is this time
Not in your mouth.
Ah, there you are!
Mr.Bond ... This is best mothers.
Leonidas was put in the middle of the wilderness,
To learn survival.
He remained calm sitting,
And went into famine ...
No Mayo?
This is worthless!
The beast, looked Leonidas ...
With red eyes that burn
If the fire in hell.
Man, you have Feets Happy!
I am on the point of my Happy Feet
Under your ass to kick, idiot!
Brave penguin!
Where are you going, mietje?
I take you my sletje, Leonidas.
This can get you from me.
-- Oh, I absolutely stink!
That's because your mouth was open.
You are dead Leonidas.
Let us say ...
Like Anna Nicole!
Damn, I stuck!
We have a Penguin in distress!
Help! Help!
"In the event of an attack penguin glass onto"
My rear!
My achterwerk hurts ...!
Why do you kill me thus?
Come on, man!
I will be good!
We have come together.
I made a joke!
And the boy who once was in the wilderness ...
Keerde back as a king!
Wow!
Boops!
You want to write something here?
They are still really too!
Yes!
Trouw you with me?
What's that?
-- The combination of my kuisheidsgordel.
Leonidas was immediately sold ...
65p [
He married Margo and they
Gave him a good son ...
Life in the land of Sparta,
Was good.
Yes! Yes! Well done!
Thank you Papa!
Give me your hand.
Remember my son ...
A warrior must learn
To his head instead.
Fight with your head,
Think with your heart.
Let him the piledriver agree,
Treasure!
The piledriver?
That's my boy.
My Queen!
-- Captain!
So, therefore Leonidas teaches the future
King of Sparta how to be a man.
I know that even if I
Was beaten by my father
Lijk you on him?
No, my father was an alcoholic.
Xerxes messenger wait, my king.
Leonidas Greetings!
-- Greetings messenger!
Why the devil was that?
What?
-- You have given me just a tongzoen!
Thus Spartan men greet each other here.
High five for the women,
Tongzoenen and open for the men.
I get the picture!
-- What snap you?
You live in a free society.
Yes!
We are free!
-- There is nothing wrong with that yet ...
I do so with great black men.
Yes!
Come messenger, let's develop
Eindje go.
The great king Xerxes, the whole world
With his Persian army already has taken.
He is not satisfied with his
Last victory ...
Sparta!
Let us continue to talk to the
Death put large.
Okay!
Xerxes is a kind of God king,
He has a friendly offer instead of a war.
"PUT DES DEATH"
There will be no blood flow ...
Until that the Spartan men
Piramides start building,
You women are seksslavinnen!
And your children ... Working in the sweat.
Because they make Nikie.
That sounds reasonable.
I believe that you also
Sun thinks about, Treathero.
Say against Xerxes,
That his proposal,
And his work ...
What the devil?
What?
He took me!
That I did not.
But ... Your wife is a whore!
This means war!
It has been good ...
We have been in San Francisco ...
The West Hollywood!
We have no need Sparta.
I am simply against Xerxes
It is not continuing.
Trap him under his ass!
This is ridiculous.
Belachelijk?
This ... ... Sparta!
Why did you believe it?
He had already entered.
My king, he will say against Xerxes
Sparta That is not at issue.
So, whatever you do,
Trap him in the pit of death.
Hou benefit to people in the
Death to put spades, really!
I wonder why people always
To my head zeuren.
I am an adult child,
Look now, I give my baby breastfeeding!
Sometimes I give him kunstmelk, you know those balls,
That is similar to breast milk but from balls.
That stop you in your mouth!
He thinks it is good, he baby?
I could very well buy
This entire set I bought in an alley
Of a Mexican woman.
Why do you think all
I always verziek on?
Am I crazy one, right now?
Oh, verdorie that is my responsibility!
You can not hold him, hear!
I am not gay!
Leonidas!
-- Bryan Seaquest?
Let us listen to what the jury
This matches.
Really ... Leo man, I could not follow you
When you gave trap, man!
That did you do good, man.
Paula?
-- You ... Let me move.
Simon?
I found that really terrible trap.
-- Ah, Simon?
I have even seen better stairways,
1 with a donkey bone!
And I am not talking about you, Paula!
-- Oh, go yourself anyway #!:$!
Seaquest has been dropped!
Excellent, my king.
It's time for your appointment with the prophets.
Umazanije AFZUIGING
The prophets had a way
Conversation with the King.
For everything smoothly ...
Did the King with a bag full of products.
Oxytan ... Nutrogina ...
It has a high spf.
It provides all protection.
Look here for,
Hydroxide for extra dry skin,
This is good for you,
Rub it over your ugly face.
What do you need, King Leonidas?
Ancient prophets ...
I need your advice.
I have an army of 300 men needed
For a war with Perzien.
I will deal with them first, before.
And then I shoot achterlangs,
And then I pack them again.
What?
Why are you so to laugh!
Nothing special ... It's nothing ...
What's so damn funny?
Look, here is everything,
So you can see ...
This is an attack from behind.
Attacks from behind, which is good.
Like a rear attack by Elton John.
Hold on! This is not funny,
It is a serious matter.
None Spartaan leaves for a war
Without first listening to the Oracle.
The Prophets choose only the
Most beautiful girls of Sparta ...
For their Oracle to be.
Konden you find nothing better than Betty?
-- It has a good appearance.
Oeh!
I see are like Jabba the Hut,
For me that is very sexy.
Ooh.
Well, she likes ... I think ...
A shaved head,
One that saves the world.
Hebbes Leon!
I am not a hero.
Klootzak says what?
-- What?
Borstwaxer says what?
You are great!
What, what do you say all against me?
I can not.
If you are at war with Persia,
Then you will surely die.
You go out, man!
What?
He looks like a Ken doll.
It is cold.
Here was Leonidas
Like ...
Tommy Lee?
Kobe
Shaggie!
Dr.Phill
Lara Reed
Borat?
And the Oakland Raiders
Why is my prince so restless?
I can not sleep.
That whole back.
Are you still considering what the young
Oracle said?
There is only one woman who is worth
To listen to.
Oprah?
-- Your wife?
Of course, of course!
How will I be in the room,
With the critical eyes of the public?
Well, Harry says
THAT IS NOT GOOD NEWS
This film but a cheap
Version of "300".
Even if you do not support that article ...
I do so very much, and Sparta.
This may be our last night together.
Do you doing?
As we have never previously done together?
97 ... 98 ...
99 ... 100!
I have my record broken.
Captain!
-- My King!
Got my army prepared
To fight to the death ...
For the freedom of Sparta?
Yes, my King!
I wanted to be 300.
This looks like ... Less.
These are all men
With the best performance.
Hotny Mitterant with a 10 ...
Beautiful buttocks, and.
Yes?
-- Not married.
We are ready to fight for you,
My King!
We never, we never give us over!
On eternity!
He has a good heart, my king.
Beautiful male breasts.
That is true.
These men are good.
You are a good master, Captain.
Such a good friend ...
Do you nowhere.
-- Thank you!
Thank you.
Zo!
S got a great package.
My father!
Hello, my son.
Proposals?
Leonidas, this is my son, Soniel.
My king.
Why not fight it?
He is not a fighter.
And he's my only son who
My name will remain on it.
What do you think?
Jammie!
Say, sister.
I think he Venus.
And if you do not like ...
Then kiss my fat ass!
Oeh.
Congratulations, Soniel.
You are on the verge of a
Spartan warrior should be.
Spartaan?
My child!
I will never forget you,
You are still so small ...
One day you will see big and strong,
Like your father.
That's your son.
Imbeciel!
Make good for your mother.
Keep it right, my son.
Come back with your shield,
Or without.
When I would come back without ...
Then I want you go.
I can never.
If you are dead,
Then I go pay the rent.
Quite frankly ...
I have always been a
Like chicken fat.
The men are ready for it, my King.
Well, as it should be to be
For an army that will tackle Persia.
Where will you go?
The Oracle says, if we go into war
That we should go.
The Oracle says,
Or I would sign or not ...
It is as bogus long-term prospects.
But I sign now different.
Enter the character captain.
Spartans, in-formation!
The Spartans come to the south.
Forward!
Oh no, not me.
I will survive.
Oh, as long as I know how I
Someone must take.
I certainly know that I will survive.
I have my whole life to live,
I did all my love to give.
And I will survive.
I will survive.
Hey, hey!
Hmm, hmm.
-- Oehoe!
The Spartans reached onvreesbare
"Hot Gates"
The danger in every corner loerden.
Stop ... Kangoeroes!
Uitgedroogd tired of the journey,
Waiting patiently the Spartans
On their energy drink.
Gay drink!
Are you also true?
What's on your mind, my king?
Well, here somewhere a secret passage
Hot run by Gates.
As we see the Persians by inward,
Well their numbers say nothing
Captain, your men
No other effect found,
They can use the Persians
For us to attack?
No, Sire!
I know such a way, my king.
Reverse you, ugly monster.
There is a secret passage,
Just before "Hot Gates"
If the Persians behind you arrive,
They may not find you there.
Wait just like captain?
Ask yourself even before, sample.
Paris Hilton?
-- Hello boys!
What's happened with you?
Oh, you mean that bump?
Yes, that bump!
It started with, you go to prison,
You are allowed out of prison,
You go back to jail,
And again, over and over again ...
I was totally in the war
Even Tinkerbell has been under must suffer.
They no longer moves since Saturday
They still poept which I find strange.
And I then?
They have changed me in this ... This,
Terribly ugly monster.
And I do not even know ...
Oh!
Yes, wait a moment.
Hello? Hi Nicole!
Nothing just a few men with their swords.
No, I mean real swords, viezerik.
Yes, I am hungry, have you eaten anything?
Oh, you have an almond eaten?
Oh yes, then you are ready for today.
Day, sexy ...
Listen, it is my desire to
A Spartaan be.
What can you do?
Have you seen my video?
Oh yes!
He is pretty good.
I am sorry, but we can not use.
No, this is not fair!
Mama!
I am not as dumb as I look see.
Help!
Look, Persians!
I am a follower,
God of the great king Xerxes,
I came to accept,
You can surrender.
Oh, we have not come to us to give.
Xexes will enjoy that you
His slaves.
Spartans!
Let us fight!
Oh, we go hard stamp.
We are Spartans,
We can stamp hard ...
For us ...
Because we stamp out loose!
Oeh, oeh!
Spartans! Yes!
Persians!
Let them try to see why we have
3 years internationally run!
You guys are Cocks.
Oh, come on!
We love the Persian cuisine
We eat baklava ...
We love kipburgers
And colored tartare.
Oeh, ah ... Oeh, ah, Per ... oeh see!
You need to shake with that ass!
Let's get started!
Oh, please say!
Oooh.
Oee!
Oeeee!
Come on in my kitchen
With that weak case!
You need to shake with that ass!
Your turn is over!
Dancing with the Spartans.
Would you say that we have lost?
-- Dans you but otherwise at the bottom of the cliff.
Come on man! Can we not talk about?
I know these idiots just pas!
We then called the battle ...
But they win the war.
Bud Meister presents:
True genius men!
Today we drink on you,
Mr. war makes ringed homosexueel.
Does nothing more than a learning onderbroek and keep.
You beat the enemy with all your oil hairless wonder.
Of course there is danger, brullende lions,
Tamping elephants,
And a very nice little man named tok load-bearing, Cher!
You have only had a date
But they will remember you forever.
Konings Your instinct says that you must wash,
Cut and cut with every man you see.
But enough now about your career
Kapster as ...
Let's talk about the war.
So this Bud's for you
King Leonidas!
Because when it is difficult,
The stronger antiques.
"Mr. war ringed homosexueel beard."
Queen Margo,
We need to talk together.
Quieres, what do you want?
Beautiful tomatoes!
Your man you need.
You must persuade the Chancellor to more men
To send your husband to support.
My husband is dead,
He said that I had to go further.
Anyway, I already have interest in J.B.
A little to the right ...
There it is!
If Leonidas loses,
And Xerxes are talking about,
You are deprived of your crown.
Stay am not Queen?
Auw, that was too hard.
You will get anything.
The palace ...
You Nintendo Wii ...
-- No, no, no! Ha!
Your 20 "rims of your escalade ...
And your gardener.
Antonio?
My husband asked me need ...
I will do everything for,
Whatever it takes.
I will make an appointment with the Kanseliers.
But in order to win their votes,
You have the support of Treathero needed.
He has a great influence on ...
The Kanseliers.
King Leonidas,
Xerxes is aantocht!
Xerxes! He seems as much at that
Fat guy from the movie of Borat.
I am the great God King Xerxes. Oeh!
-- Oeeehhh!
Auw, ue, ue!
This I can not now.
Auwww!
-- Ah!
Damn!
I am sorry, Xerxes.
-- It was Cool, it is good Cool, I have nothing ...
That was my intention.
Oh, damn!
I tell you, boy.
You say balls!
I come with a very large army,
To kebab of you to do.
Before this battle is over,
People will know that even
A God King could fall.
Listen Leon, I come to talk with you.
Listen first agree to my proposal.
Ladies!
Xerxes Hello!
That will be for me.
Hello! ... Really? Okay!
That was the bank.
They want to buy back your suitcase ...
For one weekend,
For two persons,
In Las Vegas Nevada,
In the Palm Hotel and Casino.
I have always taken a look at want!
Everything that you need to do is ...
For me bow
And Sparta to me.
Deal or no deal?
Accept the deal!
-- No!
Accept it now!
And Sparta then?
Press that button!
-- Yes, grab it, grab it!
Press that button now!
Pak!
No deal.
-- Ooh, damn!
By the time
With you that I am ready ...
Will Sparta disappeared.
It will just seem,
As if you never have existed.
I will make sure that you,
From the history books.
Well, I think this is all fine, Xerxes ...
Because I can not read.
Xerxes was nothing more to say.
But ...
From every corner of his empire,
Riep it is the most visual fighters on
Order for him to fight.
Your mother is so vast, if they
Breast-feeding comes from oil.
Your mother is so dumb,
They thought 2Pac's rest home ...
A Jewish holiday.
Your mother is so thick,
Its size is ... Uhm, uhm ... witch!
First, once waste!
Your mother is a witch, even
Rosie O'Donnel wants no appointment with her.
Oh, you did it!
No, you did not!
Well, your mother tits,
His smaller than yours.
These are my bitches.
Your mother is so thick,
That thousands of men say that they are not
Some fat ass. And then they lie.
Auw, oh, my eyes!
If you do that better, huh?
Your mother is so thick, as it should poepen,
Would Gore El her for the rioolprijs.
Yes, that may be so but,
Your mother is so hairy ...
The only language they can ...
Wokkie!
Brrrr! Brrrr!
Xerxes watched how his army
Was defeated.
It seemed as if every muscle
In his body froze.
Or maybe it came by Dentyne lce
Kristalen with cool menthol.
Lyness said that you wanted to see me.
That is my urine tester.
Yes, I do testing.
Leonidas has more troops.
Without their support will lose Sparta and ...
Bla, bla, bla, bla.
I will do everything ... For my husband,
Everything?
It's crazy!
I am now really even buttocks!
Goodbye virginity.
I promise you,
That you will not enjoy.
For 8 years I dream about certain ideas.
That's okay!
I have already krabbetjes.
Treason, dear Spartans,
And I give you everything that you go to calls.
That looks hot!
Bend down to me!
Bend down for the great God King,
Xerxes.
I am handicapped, I do not bend.
-- Ai!
But, I want to look forward!
-- Yes!
Good!
-- There is a secret passage,
In Hot Gates,
You can completely encircle Leonidas.
And how long you before?
I want my plate is sponsored ...
Oh, and I want these new Channel bag ...
Thank you ...
I wanted ... Something that was fun.
If you have something to say,
Say it now,
I have to do more.
What was it again ...
Oh God, Jesus, yes!
I want this puist disappears.
Aaaaahh.
While Xerxes the secret passage
Do not find in Hot Gates,
Will their numbers are not queer.
My King!
Come first breath ...
Give him a mix!
What's boy?
Xerxes, the secret passage
Found in Hot Gates.
Oh, shit!
I vervloek Paris Hilton.
I hate her.
Certainly a few thousand Persian soldiers.
Can any time here.
Idilio ...
How great is it?
Oh, it's ...
It is but a scratch, my King.
You have no eyes.
The gods have blessed me and
There as a reserve.
No, they have not,
You had only two.
Jeremy has an eye as a reserve.
But I can still fight.
Ho, Idilio ... Idilio ...
Idilio!
Idilio ... Idilio!
-- What? Walk with me.
No, no, no, that direction.
Your life is very important ...
You must go back to Sparta,
And tell our story.
Yes, my King,
Another message for the Queen?
More you do not have to say.
Now, Idilio. Let them know how
13 Spartans,
Fighting for their honour ...
For recognition ...
And for freedom.
Good luck, Idilio.
Spartans!
This is your last chance.
I bend down,
Or you will die.
I bend not for a man!
Ga nou on your knees!
-- No!
Go!
-- Enough!
Well, you lacing is loose.
Oh, thank you.
You see, it was really so difficult?
No, wait a minute!
Attatatata! No, no.
-- I have not voted for you suffer, I have not voted for you suffer!
I was just on my laces!
-- No, no! Stop!
You have recognized me as your God King.
Five Hi!
What?
What, what, what the devil is so funny?
You!
-- Me?
You look like a woman.
You idiots wear panties bananas,
And you laugh me out?
Now you make me really angry.
I call on everyone.
Hello, where are you?
I know where I am.
Bring me my best army.
You, 13 small butts
Are nothing compared with my
Best Persian army,
That runs in the millions.
This is just a blue screen.
Sounds crazy, that gives the visual effect,
It is obvious you soon.
The army is very impressive.
As you can see.
Gentlemen, I present to you,
Queen Margo.
Shake it, baby!
Okay boys,
Let it rain!
Well, Kanseliers ...
I ask u. ..
Your king ... My beloved husband,
, You need help.
Sparta will be lost if you
Not the rest of the army transmitted.
Gentlemen, our only hope for survival,
We submit to Xerxes,
For him bend down and begging
That he can forgive us.
Do not be seduced by the words
Te ...
Icy slut!
Oeh, have you not say.
-- Yes, yes, that I have said.
Queen Margo brought a fantasy upwards.
This seems obvious from Tobey Maguire Spiderman 3
I am so bad!
It was only sand! Oeh!
Oh, no!
Oh, baby.
Roosje yet!
What is happening?
Oh, oh, God, what filthy.
How nice to find me now, zandman?
Oh, no!
You vacuum bitch, no!
Neeeee.
Kietel my nipples agree with a feather,
Xerxes is Treathero's top 5.
Treathero was a traitor?
Daaag ...
Anyone for sending
More troops is ...
Say then: Hi!
-- Hi, Hi, Hi, Hi.
Spartans!
Huh!
We have you surrounded,
Lay down your weapons!
Come get them.
-- In-formation!
Uhm!
-- The Spartan boys protect others' backs.
Is that just your sword boy ...
In my back pricked?
No, I did not hang my sword!
Then go on.
My son?
Today you are a real Spartaan.
Thank you father.
Attacks!
Stay, Spartans.
Remember this day boys ...
Because today is the day
You will die.
What?
I, I mean that they will die.
Today is the day that they die.
That was what I meant to say.
Go for it!
Oh, what a bunch of idiots!
God, what are they smart say!
Hercules comes in me up,
And I address you now.
Ghost Rider!
You go to hell.
Sterfffff.
I stop your war!
JO!
"ROCKY"
No!
-- Jo, Sonio?
I nok your head off!
-- Oh, shit!
Sonio!
You will here for a penalty, Balboa.
Go for it!
Luiers for adults?
"BOTOX"
Botox, for adults!
Yes!
Ha, ha!
Xerxes!
It is ... ... Beautiful day.
He is not attractive SUN.
Come on Barbie,
Let's go celebrate.
Oeh!
Hmm.
"SanAndreas"
Shit!
It's enough with that
Dumb violent video games.
Ah, the transformeer cube.
Okay baby,
Let's go transform.
I am Xerxessterk, which is due
Alien invention of this technique.
Let Buddy alone!
He is a God King ...
-- Please!
Leave him alone!
Oh, Die inventors technique.
Leonidas words were actually ...
A God King has been dropped,
But alas!
Well on top of them.
I, I must ...
Oooh ...
Oeh ...
Pfff!
Queen Margo?
-- Yes!
Leonidas and the Spartans,
Deaths for their honour,
For recognition.
They are ...
A beautiful death died.
"1 year later"
Today, we stand in front of 30 thousand perzi?s
But we have now,
100 thousand soldiers!
Ahuh, huh, huh ...
On the victory.
Ah!
Follow me boys!
And that led, the blindness of Idilio
100 thousand Spartans away from the Perzi?s ...
To Mallibu ...
Just at that moment was Lindsay Lowhand
The rehabilitation center. Again!
At first I was scared,
I was paralysed.
Did that I would not be able to live
Without you at my side
But when I sit nights thinking
I do not how many times you had to sit.
And I was stronger.
And I learned how I could go
And now you are back,
From space.
Subtitles?
Sync by deswert