Fuck you
Hey,
I'll see you in hell, baby.
Excuse me.
-Hi, honey, you were great.
-You think so? What about the clients?
They loved it. You were fantastic.
Look, I gotta go. I'll see you at the party.
Love you.
Hey, how you doing?
-Hey.
-I'll just...
-Great.
-Hi, hon.
-Hey.
-What do you want me to do with that?
-Take a sip.
Ladies and gentlemen, boys and girls,
if I could just have your attention
for a moment, please.
I am sorry to interrupt this great party and...
It is a great party, isn't it?
Yes, yes.
And I know you would like to show
your appreciation
for the man who has made this all possible,
created this wonderful company,
this wonderful organisation,
this great building.
Ladies and gentlemen,
our friend and our boss,
Matthew McKay.
Hey, everybody,
a small hand for Trevor Jones.
-No, no. A small hand.
-Small. Small.
It's nice to know that the lure of free booze
still gets the employees
to do that hard overtime.
Yeah.
Hey, I even got a full day's work
out of brother Bobby.
Put a few more hours in the day,
we could've fixed
the Sistine Chapel too, big brother.
Screw that guy. He didn't have a deadline.
-But you guys met yours.
-Yes, yes.
You guys are great!
Let's see. Who else have I gotta thank?
Oh! Oh, the beautiful,
talented, partner of mine,
the president of Client Coordination.
Julia, you're so sexy.
Julia!
You and l.
You know, Julia and I started this ad agency
with a few pesetas in our pockets
and a prayer in our hearts
and look at us now.
Wow.
Clients, they keep asking me, "Hey, Matt,
"how come your shit
always looks so great?"
The answer's always the same.
It's you guys.
Now, with the new JetAir ad,
we got the potential Sony campaign,
and what is the... The Hugo Boss.
All with big, fat-ass budgets, I might add.
We are becoming the hottest agency
in this town!
-Yeah!
-Yes!
All right, enough! Get drunk!
Yeah.
Well said. Well said.
-Hey, Trevor!
-Hi.
-You doing okay?
-Yeah.
-Hey.
What are you doing up here?
Down there's where you're gonna get laid.
No, thank you very much.
All they want is shorter hours, higher wages
and a chance to move up in the agency.
Not worth the trouble.
Right.
Yeah.
Hey, dude. Thanks.
Great job, man. Great job.
Sure.
-Trevor, what?
-What about my agreement?
Jesus Christ,
everybody wants a piece of me.
I need a clone, Trevor.
Clones are illegal and expensive.
Besides, that would just give me
two children to mind.
Sign my agreement.
-You won't be so overworked.
-Oh, yeah? You're sure about that?
My personal pledge.
You know, the agreement's
been ready for weeks.
Julia's signed it.
Now it's just up to you.
-Maybe I should move on.
-Oh. Maybe.
-What does the contract say again?
-You know what it says.
-The fine print.
-There is no fine print, Matthew.
It's simple. A single page.
I get 25% of the agency.
Okay.
I'll take a look at it tomorrow.
Yeah. Yeah, that's a promise.
-Hi.
-Hey.
-You made it.
-Yeah.
I made it back in one piece.
Trevor.
You rang?
I'm so hungover.
It's this annual accounting.
Are these credit card statements right?
Well, these are Julia's.
You'll have to ask her.
I know the cost of wine and dine,
but 130,000,
that's more than a few good meals.
Has Accounting seen that? Just say no.
Not yet.
Listen, we can...
We can deduct a slice of this,
but not the whole damn pie.
Okay, bury them for a few days, will you?
Trevor?
What is she spending it on?
How about entertaining clients?
You're getting more aggressive every day.
Yeah, well, stress is a great motivator.
That stupid expense report again?
I know. I wanted it to come
after the anniversary.
It's like, I put so much time and money
into this, you know?
I just don't want the surprise to be ruined.
-How many years now?
-Seven.
-Wow, lucky year!
-I know.
-Hi!
-Oh!
-How are you?
-Fine.
-You look good.
-Thanks.
-How's our sexy man doing today?
Oh, your sexy man is just great.
What's he doing here?
I don't know.
Hi, hon.
Who's your boyfriend?
He's a local tennis pro here.
-Tennis pro? What's his name?
-Juan.
-Don Juan? Mr Don Juan.
-Hi.
That's all right. Why don't you go practise
your forehand in the goddamn can,
Don Juan?
Excuse me, ladies.
Excuse me, lady.
-Hey, Eva, how you doing?
-Hi.
Listen, I'm glad you're here,
I've got a couple questions.
One hundred and thirty thousand
in cash withdrawals.
What the fuck is that, Julia?
You know what, Eva?
Why don't you go back to the office
-and pick us up some lunch?
-Yeah, sure.
Yeah, lunch.
You can answer me some questions
about thousands and thousands.
-You are completely drunk.
-I just had a couple drinks, okay?
Just answer me this question.
Look at this.
Thousands in lunches in the Pyrenees.
What's in the Pyrenees?
It's a client perk programme
that I'm working on.
-I actually think you'd be proud of it.
-Answer my fucking question, will you?
I'll see you at home.
What's in the Pyrenees?
Julia?
-How are you?
-I'm good, how are you?
-You're looking great, Julia.
-Thank you.
-So you got a beer for me?
-Of course.
We're almost done right now.
What have we here?
Could send a man over the edge.
What do you think, Alvaro?
-lt does tell a story.
-lt certainly tells the first chapter.
I have the distinct feeling
things are going to change around here.
They say the higher you climb,
the more people see your arse.
That's never bothered me.
I always figured the pleasure was theirs.
Where were you?
I was in a meeting. I left you a message.
That was three hours ago.
The meeting was long
and there was a lot of traffic.
Yeah.
-Matt, what's wrong with you?
-What?
-I don't know. What's wrong with me?
-It's like you're acting crazy.
Baby, I'm your wife. Talk to me.
Can we talk?
-Please. Yes.
-Yeah? Okay.
Well, I'm talking about the Don Juan,
the tennis pro.
I'm talking about lunches in the Pyrenees.
I'm talking about 130-fucking-thousand.
I thought we went through this already.
-Shut up.
-Shut up?
Yeah.
So why'd you take my money? Huh?
Did I take it? No.
Did I use it?
-Yes.
-Oh, you used it.
Okay.
-Come here.
-Stop. No. Stop, you're scaring me.
Matt, stop it.
Stop it!
Just do one thing. Just tell me the truth.
Can you do that? Can you?
-Can you... Can you do that?
-Yes.
Go away, go away.
You fucking...
Matt, you just hit her, man.
Yeah.
It's not like Xavi here
did a job on her, right?
I'm in a bad spot, bro.
Where does it end?
It'll settle itself, man.
That's how it always ends.
Bad spot.
Just lay off her face, bro.
She's a good-looking gal
and we don't need the bruises.
Matt, come on. Let's go to the bathroom.
Yeah.
Come on.
Maybe you should call.
Tell him he has to apologise
before you'll come back.
I can't trust him.
It's like he's become obsessed.
Trust and obsession
don't make a good mix, do they?
No, they don't.
Men bullshit like that all the time.
They think that acting jealous will make us
believe they're not cheating themselves.
Maybe he's having the affair,
and to cover himself, he's accusing you.
-Men are such idiots.
-Matt would never do something like that.
And he'd never hit you, either?
-Hey, Miguel.
-Hi.
Sorry I'm late.
You sounded upset on the phone.
Is everything okay?
No.
It's not okay.
Let's just finish this.
I don't know what to do.
He's changed.
He's gone crazy. It's like a side of him
I've never even seen before.
I don't even know who he is.
Matthew.
As you ordered.
Your wife, entertaining clients.
And,
partnership agreement.
To be signed.
Did I or did I not give you my word?
Matthew?
Matthew!
Fuck you!
Yeah!
Yeah! What...
What the fuck are you waiting for? Come on!
Who is he?
Are you following me?
-Who is he?
-Where'd you get those?
Those pictures aren't what you think.
-Wind down the window.
-No.
-Come on, open the door.
-No, you're acting crazy, Matt.
-Open the door.
-No.
Okay.
-What the fuck are you doing, Matt?
-Huh?
Stop!
-Stop! Don't you trust me, Matt?
-Trust?
-Why are you acting like this?
I'll show you trust, baby!
Those pictures are not what they look like!
He's an architect! He's gay!
He's gay!
I hired him to build a cottage for us.
It was gonna be a surprise for you.
I don't believe you.
-We're gonna die!
-Stop! Fucking stop, Matt!
It was gonna be for us.
-Why are you doing this?
-I don't believe you!
Watch out!
Please! Please!
Please stop!
Just pull over
and let me out of the fucking car!
Get out of the way!
Watch out!
-Baby, please! I'm begging you!
-Maybe you should drive.
No, please, I'm begging you! Please!
-Yeah! Let me see what you can do!
-Baby, stop!
-Help!
-That's it!
Let me out of the car, Matt! Pull over!
Watch out!
-Let me out of the fucking car!
-Till death do us part!
Watch out!
Hi.
Advice, honey.
Two words.
Restraining order.
Where the hell have you been?
You have no idea
what we had to go through
to get you out of here.
This is serious, Matthew.
You're both lucky to be alive.
Yeah, I heard she's in a hospital. Where?
And she's filed a restraining order.
Now with both of you gone,
I am running the agency,
so you either sign this, or I am gone and...
Which hospital?
-She's filed a restraining order.
-I haven't seen one.
Have you?
Where?
Hospital de Barcelona.
-Let's go.
-What? Me?
Oh, no. No, no, no. You're on your own.
Back off.
Security, we have a
visitor out of control.
Third floor, east wing.
Good... there, down the hall.
Sir, come with us
please.
Hi, this is Julia. Leave a message
and I'll call you back. Thanks.
Hey, baby.
It's me.
Pick up the phone. Pick it up!
Okay.
I'm sorry.
I really am.
You were right. I was wrong.
I need you, baby.
I need you.
I'm going to join AA, I'm gonna go clean.
I mean, this is ruining my life, you know.
It's ruining our life.
I need you, baby.
You're my addiction.
Call me.
I'm going to join AA, I'm gonna go clean.
I mean, this is ruining my life, you know.
It's ruining our life.
I need you, baby.
You're my addiction.
Call me.
I can just see it sliding here, bro.
Did you know MC Systems
wants to reconsider their offer, Matt?
When was the last time
that you screwed up a presentation, bro?
Oh, you don't remember?
The last time Julia left.
Man, I can see the walls
are just coming down around us, Matt.
And you and I are the only ones
picking up the pieces, bro.
Yeah. You see a lot
of fucking things, Bobby.
Yeah. I'm just seeing what's out there, Matt.
Nothing you haven't seen before, right?
Right.
Man, she should just fucking vanish. Poof!
Thin air. Bye-bye. Yeah.
It's your decision, bro. It's your call.
Yeah.
-The pizza guy.
-Yeah.
Xavi would do it.
Xavi would definitely do it.
It's your call, Matt.
Okay.
Just do it.
-Matt.
-What?
You're making the right decision, bro.
Alvaro, it's Trevor.
Do you know a guy called Xavi?
No, he... He feeds Bobby McKay.
Description? No, sorry, I don't have one.
But I know where he hangs out.
And he calls himself Pizza Man.
Oh. Okay.
I'll call you from the car.
I know this Xavi.
He's an old raider.
A real bad one.
You walk the streets,
I walk the hallways, life meets.
This was my gift to Matt McKay
three years ago
when we landed a large account.
He pushed a round in, fired a shot in the air.
The chandelier came crashing down,
smashed into a thousand pieces.
He likes to start a campaign with a bang.
Matt wants to kill his old lady.
Why?
She sleeps with her poodle.
You don't need personal stuff.
All you need to know is that Xavi
will see that it happens.
Do you know what this gun is for?
If she goes down with rounds from this gun,
and this gun is found in Matt's possession...
You follow?
Ballistics would nail him.
So I get to her,
and you get to him.
Simple.
You squeeze off the shots,
give me back the gun, I return my gift...
-Life goes on.
-Life takes a turn.
And Xavi?
Well, you have to make sure
you get to her before he does.
We don't want fucking Xavi
screwing up the world now, do we?
-What if McKay looks for his gun?
-Well, there's another one there just like it.
Don't you hate to buy a gift for someone
and not get one for yourself?
-lt comes in handy sometimes.
-You are one son of a bitch, Trevor.
I like to think we're sons
of the same bitch, Alvaro.
Hello!
Oh, let me see the ring.
Oh, my God!
Come on, guys.
Keep moving. Keep moving.
Do you have a shovel, Mrs McKay?
So you took those photos of me,
and then you discovered
my husband wanted to kill me?
I didn't see a reason for you to die.
But you must leave here.
Others will come.
I believe you're a practical woman,
Mrs McKay,
and perhaps we can arrive at some
financial arrangement.
-I can protect you.
-Protect me? How?
Mrs McKay, you were on your knees.
-Either he kills you or...
-I can't.
-I can't kill.
-You will die then, no doubt.
But if you wish to think it over...
Who are you really?
Just a man who appreciates
the gifts of others.
My brother's the curator
for a museum in Madrid.
My sister's an artist,
and her paintings hang
in the galleries of Barcelona.
It is unfortunate
when art
is abused.
And a tragedy
when such beauty is destroyed.
If I decide to do this,
is it possible
that you tell my husband that I was killed
and then I could surprise him
a couple days later?
Is that possible?
Of course.
What's a life worth, Mrs McKay?
-Any problems?
-No. No problems.
How was it?
Two shots. In the woods.
Put out a missing report.
I doubt we'll find her.
It's clean.
Let's go back to my place.
Yeah.
Matt, I just got word from Xavi.
Xavi? What'd he do now?
I don't know, Matt. He didn't go into details.
Yeah, details...
Look... Wait... Wait, wait, wait.
No...
No, l... I didn't want her to suffer.
I told you, Xavi's a pro.
He didn't go after her to make a meal of this.
She went quick, Matt.
Did she say anything
before she went, Bobby?
I'm in a fucking bar, okay?
And I told you I just got the word,
but I don't have any of the details.
But that's it. She's gone.
Listen, Matt. You gotta stay cool.
You don't want to know anything here, bro.
Okay? You gotta stay calm.
You're going to be questioned
about this, Matt, and so will I.
The last thing we need is the details
running around in our minds
when the fucking cops are in our face.
The less we know, the better we look.
You're going to feel a lot better about this
in the morning. All right?
Wait.
No. What? Yeah.
Hi, this is Julia. Leave a message
and I'll call you back. Thanks.
Hey, Julia, pick up the phone.
Pick it up. It's me.
Fucking Bobby's gone insane.
He's saying that you fucking...
I don't know, you went somewhere.
Anyway, it's important. Call me. I love you.
Hello?
Hey, Trevor.
Matthew, what's happening?
I... I did something...
And now, I'm going to do something else.
What are you talking about?
Julia. She went somewhere.
Where? Where did she go?
She went somewhere.
Matthew, will you please tell me
what's going on?
I got my gun in my hand.
And I'm gonna blow my fucking brains out.
Matthew, listen to me.
Put the gun down. Do you hear me?
I'm coming right over.
Just... Just put the gun away, okay?
I'm on the way.
Yeah? Huh?
Yeah?
Yeah, I'll call her. I'll fucking call her.
Hi, this is Julia. Leave a message
and I'll call you back. Thanks.
Julia, hey. Why don't you pick up
the fucking phone, you bitch?
Huh?
I'm just kidding.
It's really important
because I've got my gun in my hand.
I never fired a gun before, you know.
I love you.
He seemed fine when I spoke to him
on the telephone last night.
But, well, he had been separated
from his wife recently.
That's Julia.
It's so complicated.
They...
Recently, there seemed to be tension.
-Hi, I'm Julia McKay.
-Detective Jimenez.
Where's my husband?
Someone called
and they said that there was an accident.
-Oh, my God. Oh, my God! No!
-Please! Please!
-What happened? What's going on?
-Wait!
-Bitch! You knew this would happen!
-Hey! Wait a minute! Wait! Stop it!
What's going on?
-Oh, my God...
-You have to speak to her.
I know these are difficult times, senora,
but we will need your statement.
When you are ready.
I can't.
-Trevor, please tell me what's going on.
-Julia, I'm sorry, so sorry.
Maria. Xavi.
I don't know.
-Xavi?
-No!
Fuck!
What?
You gave me the gun.
You told me the job was done.
Xavi never showed.
I questioned your information on that point.
Why did you lie to me?
Xavi never showed?
Well, Xavi always shows!
He's a show-up fucking kind of guy!
Did you kill him
and take a higher price from her?
I have a question for you
of a more serious nature.
McKay shot himself with his own gun,
they believe.
Did you have time to replace his gun?
Or did he use yours?
Where were you between midnight
and 1:00 a.m. that morning?
I'm sure ballistics will tell in the end.
Wherever you were, don't worry.
Your secret is safe with me.
I gave you a down payment!
I'll return it.
But if you use it to touch
one hair on her head,
it will be the last living thing you do.
Here's your money.
You bastard!
"Matthew McKay, owner and CEO
of American-owned Advantage Advertising,
"one of the largest advertising agencies
in Barcelona..."
McKay. M-C-K-A-Y.
"McKay, the recipient
of several prominent awards,
"considered one of the stars
of the advertising industry..."
"Police were led to his residence
after his cleaning lady discovered the body.
"The death appears to be a suicide."
Suicide.
"But an investigation
is now underway by Barcelona police."
What's his key man policy worth?
Not good.
Five million.
Yep. Let's pray it's a suicide.
Julia, do you have a moment?
Yeah, please.
Listen, I know this is probably
not a great time,
and there is no delicate way to put this,
but we are in the middle of campaigns,
shoots, product planning, development.
The clients are calling.
They want to know what's going on.
If we don't find a replacement
for Matt right away,
we could lose them all.
Well, perhaps this can wait. I'm sorry.
No, no, no.
Can you give me a list
of the possible candidates?
Of course.
I hear Frankie Barrera
is unhappy at Baseline.
You're right.
The crying is over and I'll get through it.
We'll get through this together, Julia.
All right, come on.
Let's go tell the troops
that everything's going to be okay.
Inspector Jimenez, the man had
a life insurance policy worth five million.
My company just wants to know
if this is being ruled a suicide.
-Not yet.
-Not yet?
With all due respect, the man shot himself.
When you shoot yourself, you die alone.
And he died alone.
What could possibly be the deal here?
The deal is you keep your foot off my floor
and wait until I complete my investigation.
Okay?
Mrs McKay, your husband's death
appears to be a suicide.
But we are obligated to investigate further
when a shooting is involved.
I understand.
We retrieved a video message from the
memory card of your husband's PDA phone.
It's for you.
Julia,
a lying,
cheating,
bitch.
I love you.
You're a whore. You...
Fuck you.
Hey,
I'll see you in hell, baby.
Oh, my God.
It goes on after that, then just ends.
It cuts out before he shot himself.
I don't know who he is. He's being crazy.
He's not the man I married.
Did you have contact
with your husband yesterday?
No. He left me a message on my cell phone.
And he threatened me.
I hung up before it finished.
What time was that?
It was around 1:00 a.m.
You have seen this before?
Yes.
Your husband believed you were involved
with this man.
These pictures aren't what they seem.
He's an architect. His name is Miguel.
I hired him to help me restore the cabin
I was going to surprise
my husband with as a gift.
And you told him this?
Yeah. He didn't believe me.
He got violent with me, so I left.
Am I a suspect, Detective?
My point is, your actions
may have led to your husband's death.
And the man in this picture?
His partner is my tennis instructor.
A male instructor.
I'm sure if you stop by the house they share,
they'll give you any information you want.
Would you like the address?
No, that won't be necessary.
As I said, we are looking at a suicide.
I will call you if I see it differently.
Thank you, Mrs McKay.
Good girl.
You're walking away.
It's best we not be seen by my colleagues.
What do you think happened?
You like to surprise your husband
in unusual ways.
Evidently, he didn't like what he heard.
He wanted to die.
I imagine he had some problems.
You're a dirty cop who preys on his victims.
You are fortunate
to be walking beside me today.
There's a Detective Jimenez.
He just showed me a video,
my husband's PDA.
It was his last living moment
before he killed himself.
He addressed it to me,
but I need to see it again.
Can you please help me?
That would be in Homicide.
You don't strike me as a man
having trouble getting around.
-Mrs McKay, you shouldn't...
-Julia.
Please, call me Julia.
You should let the investigation
take its course, Julia.
If it helps you through this difficult time,
I'll see about the video.
-Thank you, Alvaro.
-Okay.
I'll see you in hell, baby.
You got time to take
a look at something... Sorry.
It's a mess, but the bulk will soon be gone.
Look.
I was about to pack this.
Julia, I've been to the movies.
A microphone.
Listen, put this back where it was.
All I need you to get
is the photos and the press clippings.
Leave everything else as is. This is serious.
-You did good.
-Thank you.
All right, I have to go.
I have to see the man about insurance.
Okay.
-Hi.
-Mrs McKay.
My sympathies.
Please. Late breakfast? Early lunch?
No, thanks. I'm short for time.
Well, as you know,
I'm the keeper of your key man policy,
and I'm here to monitor the results
of the investigation...
-Yes.
-...to ensure that should events take a turn
-for the better...
-The better?
Should your husband's death
not be ruled a suicide,
my company will pay the benefit,
which is five million euros.
I'm aware of the policy,
but the benefits aren't of my concern.
It's how I'm going to sleep at night.
My interest in the investigation
is solely to please my client, Mrs McKay.
Now your performance in the
interrogation room was quite convincing.
Do you have any other thoughts to offer?
I'm sure it'd please you and your company
if my husband's death was ruled a suicide,
therefore you wouldn't have to
pay off the policy.
Mrs McKay, please...
Chuck, right?
Do you mind if I call you Chuck?
I know it must be difficult for you
to deal with my tragedy.
But I am determined to find
out if this was a murder or a suicide,
and to tell you the truth, Chuck,
I hope it is a murder.
Mrs McKay, you're gonna give me
indigestion here.
To all of you, my sympathies.
I am Natalia Mylar
and I am presiding over the probate period.
It is not my intention or position to question
the lack of propriety in this matter,
but from a formal standpoint,
there's little to review,
as Matthew McKay left behind
no formal will.
I hereby declare that the assets, the estate,
and all its contents
be left to his legal spouse, Julia McKay.
Thank you for attending.
I know how Matt took care of you
all of these years, and I fully approved of it.
Nothing will change, Rose.
Thank you.
Eva, can I speak with you, please?
It's been such a crazy day.
Everything's so up in the air, you know?
-You did a great job in here.
-Thank you.
I'm really looking forward
to moving to this office.
The boss with the big cojones
gets the corner.
But you seem a bit distracted.
-Can I tell you something in confidence?
-Sure.
They found a video
on the table at the condo.
It was on Matt's PDA.
It was left running.
It was his last living moments.
-And they also saw something else on it.
-On the video?
The video kept running for, like,
five more minutes
after he left me the message.
There was someone else
in the condo that night.
No.
I have a copy of it in the editing room.
I don't know who it was,
but the police have a copy, too.
So someone else was in the room
when he shot himself?
Yeah, but he must've shot himself
after the PDA ran out
because there was no gunshot on it.
My God, Julia.
Look, I don't mean to put this on you,
it's just that I have no one else to tell
and you're my only friend.
I'll let you get back to work.
I know you're busy.
No, it's okay. I'm just opening
a lot of those sympathy cards.
I'm gonna stay in the office late tonight.
I have a lot of catching up to do.
But if it's okay with you,
I'd like to stay at your house
because I don't want
to go back to the condo.
Yeah. I better catch up myself.
Thanks, Eva.
-How's homicide?
-Homicide's homicide.
One day, if you're lucky,
you'll work with the dead.
Better than working with
the scum that should be dead.
You don't want to be
among corpses too soon.
No.
The bitch drained our family, man.
Bobby, will you calm down?
What are you talking about?
-Matt didn't have a will, Trevor.
-Well, did you expect him to?
-She took the fucking cars, too, man.
-Bobby, that was just Matt's way.
-He expected to live forever.
-She needs to chill, Trevor.
Yes, perhaps she does,
but, Bobby, so do you.
Let's go talk about this in my office.
Hello, Julia.
Hi. I really need to see you.
I'm leaving the office now
and I was hoping that we could meet up.
It's about Trevor.
Yep. Julia?
Hello?
Shit!
Requesting back-up,
723 Diagonal Avenue.
Advantage Ad Agency,
requesting back-up, thank you.
What's the matter, Julia?
You looking for a way down?
I know of one.
Over the top.
I've got her. Get the car, I'll be right down.
Hey, did you hear?
I hear Julia had this terrible accident.
Or was it suicide?
Maybe something just drove her to it, huh?
Come here, you stupid bitch!
Are you scared?
No! Help me! Someone!
Help! No, please don't.
Please don't do it.
-No, please.
-This little piggy went to the market...
And this little piggy fell off the roof.
No, please.
Excuse me.
There's a body in the alley,
two others left in a car.
Anyone else?
Don't think so.
So now you're in the
advertising business?
Guy in back is Bobby McKay,
on my radar for trafficking.
He works here.
She was the target.
I'll hear your statement later.
Thank you.
I called you because I saw the video.
There was someone else in the room.
I found a microphone in Matt's office.
Trevor was monitoring his calls
right before he died.
You think Trevor was in the condo?
I left the videotape out and he took it.
Now he knows that I know
someone else was in the house.
You think he wants to kill you?
If he knows that I know
someone else was in the house
and I think it was him,
yes.
-Can you describe Trevor's car?
-An Audi sedan. Why?
There's an Audi sedan parked
300 metres behind you.
I can't see who's inside,
but we can walk that way
and see if it moves.
Do you believe me now?
We have to stop him before he stops you.
Should we work on this together?
Jimenez wants to make peace.
I guess he figures
you'll get this anyway,
ballistics and gun registration.
Matt McKay was
killed with his own gun.
Thank you, Anna.
Julia, it's time to proceed.
Look, I know I've been a bitch lately
and I haven't been listening to you,
and I want to.
I'd like it if we could sit back down
and go over the clients
and review company policy.
Well, yeah. That would be great, yes.
I'd like to very much.
Well, I think that this weekend
I'm gonna go away to the cottage
and just relax, you know?
Yes. Yes, I think you should.
I'd like if you joined me.
I know I could really use the company.
We could make dinner,
drink some wine, relax.
You know, go over the new plan
and then come Monday morning,
-we'll start anew, you know?
-Well, yeah.
That sounds great. Yes, I'd love to.
-Good.
-I haven't seen the cottage yet, you know.
Okay, well, hasta manana.
Running short on suspects, Anna.
Know what I think?
She provoked him.
She didn't expect
things to go that far,
but she wanted grounds for divorce,
and a big settlement, of course.
But she didn't break any laws,
and his prints are on the gun.
It's a suicide.
I couldn't do what you're doing, Julia.
You already are.
You know what I mean.
I wasn't born with that.
Yeah, well, look where it got me.
I have a man trying to kill me.
But please, Julia. Don't do anything...
Don't worry.
It's gonna be fine.
Now I need you to go set up
and show me how brave you are.
Okay.
Yes, o.k. o.k. o.k.
Alvaro needs back-up
in the Pyrenees.
When?
4 p.m., details will come later.
There goes our weekend...
It had to be him.
He's crossing all the lines.
Exactly.
Hello? Anybody home?
Yeah, come on in. I'll be right out.
-Hi. You got here early.
-No traffic.
-Want to go for a walk?
-Oh, I'd love to, yes. Sure.
See your domain, huh?
Okay, let me go get my jacket.
Easy to appreciate.
Yeah, the only thing that changes
is the time of year you look at it.
Matt used to love it up here.
Especially the sunsets.
I'm sure.
What do you think of Matt's last words?
-Last words?
-On the video.
-Jimenez didn't show it to you?
-No. No, Jimenez didn't.
It doesn't matter.
So what did you see on the video?
I told you, I didn't see the video.
Where the fuck are you going
with this, Julia?
Let's just go back to the cottage.
No.
I would rather stay here with the view.
So what did you see on the video?
I saw a man that looked exactly like you.
You know, Matt had that gun.
Why is that gun being pointed
at me, Trevor?
You know.
-I know what?
-You know enough to put me away.
And who said I'm gonna tell?
Start walking.
It was you.
Yes, I went to the condo.
I saw your stupid, fucked-up husband.
He didn't even have the guts to kill himself.
It wasn't difficult to give him his gun back.
Say bye-bye and take two steps backwards.
Trevor!
It's over! Drop the weapon.
Do you see this?
This is what you used
on my fucked-up husband.
Drop the weapon now!
I'm recording everything.
Now! Drop it!
I'd be careful where I go with this, Alvaro.
Remember our little meeting on the bluffs,
where you took the money
and agreed to kill Xavi
and take out Julia?
You're trying to place me
where I wasn't, Trevor.
No, no. I'm just telling you I have
a collection of very interesting recordings.
-Can you prove it?
-Of course.
Isn't it just like Trevor Jones
to cover his hairy ass?
Now, who should we
be killing here, Alvaro, huh?
You arrest me, and we'll be taking showers
together in the morning,
passing the fucking soap.
Don't believe him, Alvaro.
It's obvious she has to go.
I'm sorry, Julia.
But now it's about my life.
Don't.
I'm not going to push you.
You know that I bury my bodies.
No!
-Fuck! Where the fuck is she?
-I don't know.
Let's go.
Where'd she go? Well, where is she?
On your fucking knees.
On your fucking knees!
One chance, or you will die.
Where is the recording?
Walk about 10 metres.
I'll be starting to fire,
Iike I caught you chasing Julia.
I'll get them. I'll burn them!
Just don't shoot, okay?
Where?
-Where are they?
-ln my fucking office in the fucking safe.
What else do you fucking want?
Julia...
You wouldn't.
What happened?
Mrs McKay?
Are you okay, Julia?
Where is Alvaro?
It's okay.
Stay with her,
you come with me.
Julia. Julia.
-You're a brave girl.
-Thank you. See you in a minute, okay?
"Julia, Congratulations!
Don't spend it all in one restaurant! Chuck"