[Male Voice]
Have you had enough yet?
[EXhales]
[Groans]
Are you ready now?
[Birds Chirping]
[Audience Applauding]
Thank you.
And every single
free choice you make...
arises from either a thought of love
or a thought of fear.
- There is no other choice.
- [Shutter Clicks]
And if I had one thing to say
about what we're trying...
to understand here tonight,
it would be– it would be this:
That feeling inside of you...
that love inside of you-
that's God...
eXpressing through you as you.
Yes?
- [Microphone Feedback]
- My name is Daisy...
- and I just wanted to say I loved your book.
- Thank you, Daisy.
And I'm-I'm feeling like I finally understand
what it means to be awake in my own life.
- Feels good, doesn't it?
- It's totally amazing!
- Mm-hmm.
- I walk around feeling like I've been given a secret.
Well...
- the secret is out!
- [Laughing]
- [Applause]
- The problem I've been having...
is that some of my friends,
even my family–
If I say anything remotely spiritual,
they get this glazed look on their face.
- [Man] Ah.
- And I know that look...
because it's the same look I've had,
or used to have, every day of my life.
I know eXactly what that feels like.
And the good news is,
you're not crazy.
- Good. [Laughs]
- 'Cause we're both crazy.
- [Laughing]
- And if that's the case...
- we're in very good company.
- [Laughing, Applauding]
Instead of worrying about
what people think about you...
concentrate on
what you think about you.
- [Applause]
- That's important.
Any regrets?
- Many.
- Care to name a few?
- You're not a lawyer, are you?
- [Audience Laughing]
I wish that I could have come to
this point in my life without hurting-
wish I'd come to this point
in my life without...
hurting so many people–
especially the people I've loved.
But without them...
I might not have come
to this point in my life.
See, it's important
for all of us to remember...
that the universe
is conspiring in our favor-
always, and in all ways...
despite circumstances
and appearances...
or most importantly,
our perception of them.
- You've got a lot of nerve!
- I'm sorry?
- You're a hypocrite.
- It's all right. It's all right. It's all right.
Standing up there preaching
about God and love.
You've been married
and divorced a lot.
If you talk to God, how come you can't
keep a commitment with a woman?
[Man] I can't tell you how many times
I've asked myself that same question.
The women in my life...
are all wonderful.
They treated me a whole lot
better than I treated them.
I betrayed them.
I let them down.
I let my kids down too.
I admit that.
More than that I cannot say
without invading their privacy...
and that I am not gonna do.
What I can do is love
as much as I can from where I am.
To make every gesture and action
sponsored by love.
- Sounds to me like you've written a book of lies.
- [Audience Murmuring]
If what you're asking me is, did I make
all of this stuff up, the answer is no.
I've wondered what you're wondering.
??will anyone believe me,
believe what I'm saying...
believe where this came from?"
And I guess that
that's up to you–
to each of you.
I only hope that you don't
disqualify or marginalize the message...
because it's coming through
such a fallible messenger.
My name is Kay,
and I just wanted to thank you...
for admitting your mistakes.
[Man] Well, thank you, Kay-
um, and all of you.
But the truth of it is, I'm still making
those mistakes to this day.
That's why these conversations with God
are such a miracle for me.
They-They came out of a need–
a desperate personal need–
for me to change my life.
And, um, you know, uh...
if I've been successful
at it in the way I'd like–
I don't know,
but-but it's the way it happened...
and it's the way it's–
it's still happening.
[Kay]
My question is...
if God has one message–
his most important
message to all of us–
and you could put it in one paragraph,
what would it be?
[Man] Well, I could fit it
into five words.
??You've got me all wrong."
- [Cheering]
- Thank you.
Thank you.
Good night.
[Crowd Chanting]
Neale! Neale! Neale!
[Rain Falling]
[Woman]
Here's your plane ticket. You're on the 10:00.
Thanks for everything,
and I'll see you in New York.
[Thunder Rumbling]
[Vehicle Approaching]
[Tires Screeching]
[Siren wailing]
- Still nothing, huh?
- I'm trying, honey.
You could have fooled me. Look,
I don't get this. I've got eXperience–
Your eXperience has nothing to do with anything.
And we've been over this, Neale.
- [Groans]
- As long as that bow tie's around your neck...
nobody's going to take
a chance on hiring you.
Really?
So, what is it eXactly...
that you people do around here?
Mostly we hand out checks to people
who blame us for their problems.
Sorry.
What did the hospital say?
Well, they said I should start
feeling better in a few days...
but, uh, it's been
almost a month now.
Wow. They seem
to have missed something.
- What?
- Neale...
you have a broken neck.
[Lighter Flicks]
- [Knocking]
- [Man] Mr. Walsch, it's Michael.
[Knocking]
Come on, Mr. Walsch.
I know you're in there.
[Neale]
No, I'm not.
- You're three months behind on your rent.
- [Door Closes]
I told you. I lost my–
- Your job.
- Job, yeah.
Yes, I know. And I'm sorry
about your accident, Neale.
But I'm not gonna lose my job
because you lost yours.
Come on. I'm out there.
Every day, I am.
I'm trying.
Isn't there someone you can call?
No. Those calls were made
a long time ago.
I mean, I got–
I got nowhere to go.
5:00, Neale.
[No Audible Dialogue]
- [Thunder Rumbling]
- [Blows]
[Inhales, Groans]
[Children Chattering,
Laughing]
[Child Babbling]
[Woman]
Okay, who's ready for bed?
I'm coming in there.
I hope you got your R.J. 's on.
[Chattering,
Laughing Continue]
[Woman]
Brush your teeth?
[Child Babbling]
[Woman] Yes? How about you?
Did you brush your teeth?
Oh, looks to me like
somebody had an extra cookie.
- [Children Laughing]
- Am I gonna have to tickle you to get you to go upstairs?
[Children Chattering,
Laughing]
[Dogs Barking In Distance]
[Woman]
I'm gonna get youl
[Children Chattering,
Laughing]
[Thunder Rumbling]
- [Woman] Hurry up.
- [Child Laughing]
[Thunder Rumbling]
[Panting]
- Come on.
- You're doing it wrong!
It's the way I did it
on the other side!
Nope.
That don't go there.
You're doing it wrong.
Let me show you how to do it.
- That's not what the instructions say.
- Nope. That don't go there.
Let me show you how to do it.
Tie the line to the tree.
Make it high enough...
so you don't kill yourself
in the middle of the night.
I kind of wish I had
one of those old canvas jobs...
that you pitch from the inside!
I take it this isn't
your first time pitching a...
tent.
[Groaning, Panting]
[Wind Whistling]
[Thunder Rumbling]
[Sighs]
Please, God...
don't let me die here.
[Audience Applauding]
[Neale] To God,
there is no separation...
between financial abundance
and spirituality.
In fact, they go hand in hand.
Don't you find it odd
that we live...
in a society that devalues
our most important jobs?
- What do you mean by that?
- [Neale] I mean, we have no problem...
giving a football coach
five million a season...
or-or an actor
10 million per movie...
but somehow we've got it wired...
where people involved
with spirituality...
should be penniless,
celibate and-and abstinent.
[Applause]
- And preferably all three, you know?
- [Audience Laughing]
- [Woman] Yeah. Right.
- I mean, I don't know about you...
but l-I don't– I don't remember
voting for any of that.
- [Audience] No.
- So imagine a world...
where money was given
to people who give us the biggest gifts.
- Teachers.
- [Woman] Oh, yes.
- Artists.
- [Audience] Yes.
- Nurses.
- Yes.
Uh, firemen.
You know, policemen.
- Writers.
- [Laughing]
- And mothers!
- [Audience Affirming]
[Woman]
Mothers. That's right.
Yes.
People who connect us,
not disconnect...
or-or-or distract us, you know.
Imagine that world.
And we can have it,
because, people...
we're the ones.
We've always been the ones
that we've been waiting for.
We are. We are.
- [Applause Continues]
- [Woman] Yeahl
[Applause Fades]
[Wind Whistling]
[Birds Chirping]
[Male Voice]
You awake in there?
I said, are you awake in there?
Just a minute.
[Groans]
- Morning.
- Uh, good morning.
Name is Oscar. How about you
step out of that tent for a minute?
Uh, what for?
I know you got in late,
but I run things around here...
- and you should be aware of the rules.
- Uh, rules?
Yeah.
I'll walk you through them.
How about you come a little bit
closer so I don't have to yell?
- Okay.
Rent is $25 per week.
Over there
you've got your bathrooms.
Now, our maid quit
about a month ago...
so we'd appreciate it
if you would clean up after yourself.
- Okay.
- Those cabins back there–
- freight on them: 75 per week.
- Right.
Now, down by the water
you've got another picnic area.
Those are reserved for real campers
and real campers only.
Uh, real campers?
They usually arrive by automobile.
- They tend to stick around
a couple of days, then move on. - [Groans]
Guy like yourself–
comes up in the rain...
with a tent and a bedroll–
we call them professional campers
around here.
- Yeah?
- You professionals have a way of lingering on–
kind of like those guys over there.
[Chuckles] I should be back
on my feet in a few days...
as soon as I, uh, find a job.
Because you got in late,
last night's on the house.
But collection for the week
starts on Friday at 3:00 p.m.
If you're here, I eXpect payment on time.
There's no eXceptions.
Okay.
If not, you're out.
We understand each other?
Uh, yes. Yes, we do.
Well, good morning to you then.
And by the way?
- Yeah?
- If I were you, I would put that cover...
- on top of your tent.
- What's it for?
It's for the rain.
- [Vehicle Door Closes]
- [Engine Starts]
- [Vehicle Rulls Away]
- [Man] I see you have lots of experience.
Radio.
That says a lot.
Uh, why don't you have a résumé?
Doesn't matter.
How about you tell me...
why Osborne and Associates
should hire someone like you?
We have over 20 applicants.
Why you?
Well, uh, despite
outward appearances...
I've held supervising positions
for three companies.
Which makes me wonder
about your work ethic.
Or maybe you're on some type
of desultory path.
- It means ??lack of purpose."
- Uh-huh.
Yeah, well, the truth of it
is I was laid off...
when the stations were
bought out and consolidated.
I mean,
everything's corporate now...
and I'm nearing 50
and so overqualified...
that you're probably
not going to hire me, are you?
Well, the thing of it is, most applicants
carry a master's degree. You don't.
No, I don't, but I still think I can do
a good job for Osborne and Associates.
Well, around here, we demand excellence,
Mr. Walsch, not good.
I'm sorry.
Okay, listen. L-l-l–
I really need this job.
You're... overqualified.
[Oscar]
Next.
NeXt.
Chef, let's go.
- Hey, don't let them get to you.
- [Men Chattering]
Outsiders make them
a little bit jumpy. That's all.
So I'm guessing you're gonna be
sticking around for the week?
- There we go.
- Thanks, Daddy.
- I'm sorry?
- It's harder than you thought, isn't it?
- [Objects Smashing]
- [Man Grunts]
[Oscar] Look, there's
a convenience store on the corner.
They've got a recycling center.
That's how these guys pay their rent.
You get yourself a bag of aluminum cans,
you're halfway to making the week.
Bag a day, you get your food,
you get your drink.
No, l-I don't drink.
Thanks.
Yeah? Stick around here
long enough, you will.
[No Audible Dialogue]
[Siren Wailing In Distance]
[Dishes Clacking In Distance]
- [Siren Wailing]
- [Vehicle Approaches]
[Vehicle Rasses]
[Siren Fades]
[Sighs]
- God. You scared me.
- What the hell do you think you're doing?
- Well–
- These are mine.
This is my area.
[Groans]
I'm sorry. I didn't know.
Well, now you do.
Okay.
[Man]
I see you met Oakley.
- I didn't know there were territories.
- Well, we call them areas.
Yeah, well, he could've
just told me.
I'd have– thanks–
given him the damned cans.
Yeah, when a man relies on threats to
communicate, it usually indicates a weak cause.
- Hey, don't let it bother you.
- Okay.
- [Man] Sure is pretty, isn't she?
- [Neale] Who is she?
- That's Sunny.
- [Chef] Yeah, I wouldn't mind...
changing her tire,
if you know what I mean.
How long you been saying that?
Dreams don't have deadlines.
I got a better chance
than you do, you old fart.
- I beg to differ.
- Then you keep on begging.
- Hey, thanks.
- You okay?
Well, compared to what?
[Chuckles] That's a–
That's a hell of a point.
Here.
What happened to your neck?
Oh, that's a... bull-riding accident.
Wasn't pretty.
Well, then I'd say
today's a better day.
It ain't Irish, but it's effective.
[Sighs]
No, thanks. I don't drink.
Something wrong with you?
- I just never got around to it, really.
- Huh. Hell of a thing.
Yeah.
Here you go.
No, you, uh–you keep 'em.
I'll help you get going.
All right, what's the catch? Yesterday
you looked at me like I ran over your dog.
I don't have a dog.
Something you'll soon
figure out–
People on the street?
Hardest friends to make.
Even tougher ones to lose.
- Does that mean we're friends?
- [Laughs]
Not yet.
[Man Shouting] Give me those pallets
right nowl Come onl Let's gol
[Shouting Continues,
Indistinct]
Catching up on your reading?
Oh, it's, uh, padding
for under my sleeping bag.
Neale, come on in here.
Come on. I'm not gonna bite you.
Come on in here.
- All right.
- You boys hungry?
- Neale?
- You sure you have enough?
Son, the right Dumpster
always has enough.
A man's just gotta know
where to look. That's what it is.
- Any guacamole?
- Sometimes I wonder.
I'm not in the mood, Chef.
I'm really not.
- [Chef] Monday-now that's
gonna be your slow day. - Here we go.
Tuesday and wednesday things are
gonna pick up, but only just a little.
Now, your fast food,
you're gonna see that on Thursday...
mostly 'cause folks
racing around like a bunch...
of crazy rats trying to make it
through the work week.
Why?
Because Friday's payday.
Now, you take Saturday night,
your date night-
that's when folks
pay the most for their food...
which is why you'll see
the guacamole on Saturday.
Why, you ask?
It's because of the–
Help me out here, Fitch.
- Discretionary.
- Income. EXactly.
This is almost done.
And Sunday's gonna be your slow day
because most folk eat at home.
Okay, boys, get your plates.
- Neale?
- Come and get it.
Uh, no.
Uh, but thanks.
- [Chef] Boy's still wet behind his ears.
- Ah, let him go.
You'll be back.
- [Horns Honking]
- [Vehicles Rassing]
Yo. Do you need something, buddy?
- Yeah, the bathroom.
- Yeah, we-we got two bathrooms.
- Thank you.
- Where you think you're going?
- Uh, to the bathroom.
- Oh, you need to use the head?
- Mm-hmm.
- Right. Tell you what. You see across the alley?
- That tree over there? You see it?
- Yes.
Good. Then go lift your leg up
on that with the rest of the dogs.
You people make me sick.
Why can't you get a job like everybody else?
- What's the problem?
- He thinks he's coming inside to use the bathroom.
- In and out, okay?
- Thank you.
[Insects Buzzing]
[Groans]
[Vehicle Door Opens]
- [Moans]
- [Door Closes]
[Engine Starts]
[Truck Rulls Away]
[Neale]
Excuse me?
Hi.
Oh. [Chuckles]
Hello.
Uh–
I'm Neale, and, uh,
I think I'm a little–
Harry. Yeah. I'm the, uh–
Uh, I'm the janitor.
- Hi, Harry.
- Hi.
Um– Harry, how do–
how did you like the book?
Oh, oh. It's-It's– It's wonderful.
I've been waiting
for this day ever since...
your name came
on the schedule months ago.
Oh, well, here. Um, let me, uh–
let me show you to the– to the greenroom.
Yeah. Um–
Listen, Harry, um–
Uh–what did you like
about the book?
Oh, l-I don't want to bother you.
Oh, not bothering me at all.
I'm, uh– I'm interested.
I spent a lifetime in anger–
toward my father.
I'm not gonna stand here
and drop sugar all over this...
'cause my old man
was a mean old cuss.
I hated him.
Strong words, I know, but true.
And this book–
your book–
helped me finally, after 20 years
of that anger, that-that hatred, to–
well, to forgive my father.
What I was feeling about my father was
really what I was feeling about myself.
And I had to forgive myself
for the feelings I had– the anger I had–
toward my father.
That's the first time
I think I've ever said that out loud.
Well, here, here.
Page three.
I know your book.
- Sure do.
- [Chuckles]
??My most common
form of communication...
??is through feeling.
??Feeling is
the language of the soul.
??lf you want to know what's true
for you about something...
Iook to how you're feeling
about it."
[Sighs]
[Groaning]
- Fitch?
- [Groaning Continues]
Fitch. Fitch?
- Can you hear me, Fitch?
- Jesus. I'm drunk, not deaf.
- [Coughs]
- Why are you doing this?
I'm not doing anything.
[Coughs]
That damn pancreas has got
a mind of its own.
I'm just playing the hand I'm dealt.
Don't start with me.
- You're killing yourself. You know that?
- Don't ask me to stop drinking.
I can't do that.
You're gonna be a real
pain in the ass, aren't you?
All right.
[Coughing]
- [Scanner Beeps]
- [Woman On R.A.] Cleanup in aisle three.
Cleanup in aisle three, please.
[Bag Rustling]
[Coins Rattling]
Um–
Thank you.
[Groans]
[EXhales]
Good morning.
[No Audible Dialogue]
[Laughing]
[Crowd Chattering, Laughing]
- [Crowd Applauding]
- [Camera Shutter Clicks]
[No Audible Dialogue]
- [Cheering]
- Ho, ho, ho! Merry–
[Child]
Hi, Santal
[Cheering]
[Camera Shutters Clicking]
I'm not gonna die in that park.
[Wind Whistling]
[Dog Barking In Distance]
[Dial Tone]
[Beeping]
- dd [Rock]
- [Woman] Good morning. Rrogramming.
- [Neale] Yes. I'm calling about the ad.
- Come again?
[Clears Throat]
EXcuse me.
Um, could I speak with
the program director, please?
He's on air at the moment.
What can I help you with?
Well, I'm calling about the ad, uh,
for the weekend radio deejay.
Hello?
That ad wasn't supposed
to run until neXt week.
Well, I'm holding the paper
in my hand.
Which paper?
The Ashland Daily Tidings.
I'm sorry.
What is the date today?
Today?
November 7.
[Woman]
Hello?
No– Uh, no.
I'm-I'm still here.
Sorry. Um–
Is there a position available?
Yeah. It's been a revolving door
around here for the last siX months.
Tell you what. How 'bout I take
your name and number...
and I'll make sure Roy
gives you a call.
Is there any chance I could
converse with Roy today?
[Imitating Neale] He's eXtremely
preoccupied at the moment...
but I'll see what I can facilitate.
At what number can he reach you?
Uh, yes, y-yes.
He-He can reach me at, um–
He can reach me at 555-7507.
And my name is Neale.
[Imitating Neale]
Hello, Neale. I'm Leora.
Nice chatting with you.
Yes, well, it's been nice chatting
with you too, Leora. Thank you. And bye-bye.
- And look forward to the call.
- [Laughs]
[Groaning]
[Jackhammer Rattling]
Hey–
[Jackhammer Continues]
[Neale]
Excuse mel
EXcuse me!
Uh– Do you know how long
this is going to be?
I'm-I'm, uh–
I'm eXpecting a phone call.
- It's– It's sort of important.
- What the hell now?
- [Ringing]
- I don't know. It just died.
Figure it out. We got two more stops
before quitting time. You, come here.
- [Neale] Hello?
- Neale?
- [Man] Scrap that there.
- Uh, h-hello.
Hi. It's Leora.
- Hi, Leora.
- Did I catch you at a bad time?
- [Shouting]
- No, no, no, no. It's perfect. Perfect. I'm good.
- How are you?
- Good. Listen.
I told Roy about you.
He'd like to have you come in...
- tomorrow, say around 9:00?
- [Man] What's happening there, Dennis?
Uh, tomorrow would be great.
Yeah, sure.
- Just bleed the line!
- That would be good.
- [Shouting Continues]
- Okay. Uh, you know where we are?
- K.Y.O.L.
- I'm sure I can find you, Leora.
- Okay. Then we'll see you tomorrow.
- Right. Okay.
- Bye-bye.
- [Hammering Resumes]
Thank you!
So let me get this straight.
What you're saying...
is that we're all having
a conversation with God all of the time.
- Of course.
- Can you give me an eXample of what you mean by that?
Sure. Um, do you ever pick up the phone
to call someone, and they're already on the line?
Or, uh, do you ever drive down
the road feeling as though...
nothing makes sense of your life...
and the next song on the radio
speaks directly to you?
It's as if the lyrics
were written specifically for you...
and suddenly everything
falls into perspective.
Or, um– Or what about
when someone enters your life...
seemingly from nowhere,
and you wonder why they are there...
and then one day
it all makes sense...
and you wonder how you ever
got along without them?
Of course.
We've all had those moments.
[Neale]
That is God.
[Woman]
Well, it happened to him. It can happen to you.
- Is happening to you– and you.
- I stand corrected.
We'll be right back
with Neale Donald walsch...
and his book Conversations With God.
[Birds Calling]
[Rooster Crows]
I knew I had something
back there that would work.
Great.
And, uh, thanks for– thanks for
cleaning up– the shirt as well.
I'm gonna look employable.
It's only fear.
That's easy for you to say.
You're not the one going back out there.
What if it doesn't work?
What if it does?
Neale, you're afraid...
to give up the very thing in yourself
that brought you here in the first place.
Give up?
I'm running on empty.
And that's why you're here.
Uh, well, no. I'm here because–
because I lost my job.
You're here
because you lost yourself.
Well, right now I just want
to get this job.
You will.
You're ready for that now.
This is your opportunity
to eXperience real love.
What did you have in mind?
For you to be a man.
A real man, Neale.
Not a predator.
How many women is it going to take?
How far do you need to fall
before you realize that your behavior...
is an attempt to destroy yourself?
Heal that...
and you'll be free.
[Sighs]
[Chef] Come here, Neale.
Let's have a look at you.
[Fitch]
Come here.
Didn't I tell you
she was some miracle worker?
- [Rooster Crows]
- [Fitch] So how'd it go?
I don't know.
Son, we've been trying to get a look
inside her trailer for years.
How is it?
- It's good.
- She make your head spin?
She made his head spin.
- How we doing on time? Fitch, you with us?
- Yeah. Yeah.
Neale.
We know, uh,
what a big deal this is for you.
Help you with the bus fare.
And you got enough time
to get a hot breakfast too.
Maybe some bacon, eggs,
pancakes with syrup.
And toast. Don't forget the toast.
And some jelly.
Grape if they have it. And some biscuits.
Maybe some biscuits with–
- You eating this breakfast, or is he?
- [Laughs]
- Guys? Thanks.
- [Fitch] Go on now.
Yeah, go on, Neale.
- My man is stepping up.
- Yeah.
Funny, huh?
What's the big deal if someone wants
to look at your watch, right?
Hey, have we met before?
Uh, uh– No, I don't think so.
- I'm Carly.
- Hi.
Uh, ??You come here often?"
- [Clears Throat] Name's Neale.
- Neale.
I'm kidding, of course, because if you had,
I would have seen you, right?
I'm like a fiXture on this bus.
Whew. That's me.
You'd think one of these days
I would buy a car.
Nope.
I love people too much.
I'm a receptionist. I work for
a construction company up in Medford.
We are getting
crazy busy lately. Yeah.
No. 'Cause the thought of sitting in a car
by myself all day long? Not for me.
I love people.
- Wait. I said that already, didn't I?
- Yeah.
[Laughs] Yeah, well, it's true.
Call me crazy.
- [Laughs]
- It's nice meeting you.
- Oh, are you getting off?
- Uh, you know, l-I think so.
- [Bell Dings]
- Shoot. God, isn't that just how life is?
I mean, people just moving in
and moving out, and you never know why...
or if you're ever even
gonna see them again.
- I never thought about it that way.
- Makes you think, doesn't it?
- Well, good-bye.
- Oh, no, no, no, no.
You don't get to say ??good-bye."
??See you later."??Till we meet again."
Anything but ??good-bye."
I mean, ??good-bye"
is something that you say...
when you walk out on a bad job
or you leave a bad lover.
- Yeah. Yeah.
- Yeah.
Well, um, see you later.
[Chuckles]
- Later.
- [Carly Laughs]
Hey. Now that's
what I'm talking about.
[Man] We're talking to
dead people, folks. Spooky stuff.
You've been listening to
Fat Friday Morning Freak-out Show.
Bob and Jane will be here
with me on Monday.
They got a new book called
Breaking Up with Mommy–
or Daddy or Your Cousin
or whatever the damn name is.
And they're gonna be
doing a book signing...
at Medford Regasus Bookstore
starting at 7... 00 p.m.
On Monday, I will be talking
to an angry deli worker.
He's mad at you idiots who go
and order sliced turkey breast...
and then at the last minute
change it over to sliced ham.
And then for coming in
at 8... 00 at night-
- [Neale] Good morning.
- You must be Neale.
- Yes.
- Leora.
- We spoke on the phone.
- I'm Rockin' Roy, the Morning Boy–
- Of course. Thanks for getting me in.
- You're not in yet.
- [Roy] Stay young. Stay cool.
- You still have to meet Roy.
- dd [Rock]
- He's a handful.
You tellJainey I wanna talk to her.
I don't remember approving this, uh,
drunk Russian guy for tomorrow's show.
Nobody cares about this. I mean,
so what if he drank too much vodka...