" DAYS OF DARKNESS "
SUBS BY: * JPetway *
RiPPED - EDiT BY: * N3krA *
When what was amused!
What place is this?
This zone was of the soldiers.
The best place in order that
camps what I already saw.
It is brilliant.
What is that?
The ladies like of champagne.
You know that the champagne gives me sob.
It is trying to seduce me, Mr. Turner?
Only I want to celebrate this moment.
Definitely you á the woman for me.
Respect sweats decision.
I can wait.
You cost that.
Are you well?
Yes, only I have some câibras.
For what-?
It comes here.
Listen.
Do we return for house
and a doctor examines him, yes?
What thinks that it happened?
I do not know, wanted.
Oh, let me see.
I will be going to help it.
I do not like this, Steve.
I will stay well.
Be careful.
What happened?
- Steve, comes, let's go!
- What?
One hurry Steve! Let's go!
God, I lost the keys!
Diabos, darling, let's go!
Hurry up!
Diabos!
Help me, Steve!
Cursed-
God, Steve! Please!
Let's go, it enters. Enter!
One gives the keys.
Quick! close the window, Steve!
Lift it!
Stop looking at the map!
Let's go away from here!
I am trying!
No!
Follow me.
What place is this?
Listen.
You if ofereu like volunteer, Simon!
Ear, do I know him?
It can be. Who is you?
Steve. Steve Turner.
Yes, well, I do not know him.
However it seems to me known.
Well, I did some actings.
Jake! When it took care!
Quilting stitch to ignore it.
Hello, I am Lin.
Hello, I am Steve.
She is my girlfriend Midami.
Mimi. My parents were hippies.
What diabos is happening?
Survival.
They are Slasher and D.J.
Yes.
And Trent.
You are a very strange man.
Come.
We go.
We go, cursed wretch.
Place us there.
She needs to lean.
Ok, calm.
Slasher, D.J., take it for inside.
I will finish here. They go.
I have it.
What is happening there?
In a minute we will be selling cars,
perhaps celebrating in the night club.
You are married.
And soon the place colapsa.
And the rest of the city?
It is a disaster, old man.
The persons were shouting,
there was fire. God.
And suddenly,
everyone
he began to eat between you.
Simon also saved us.
Yes, Simon. Yes.
He is D.J. I am Slasher.
Slasher?
Yes, raise one's hands an offer is wanted.
A good agreement is wanted,
lower the prices.
And lower them and lower them.
We sell cars.
Slasher sells for the whole country.
What place is this?
I think that it is a station
of microwave outdated NORAD.
However perhaps I am mistaken.
I am going to fly his head.
For on my corpse.
What is happening with you, cursed bitch?
It has no idea.
This is the brother of Trent.
This is a thing.
You were giving one almost it kills me
30 seconds ago.
There is no place for them here.
What is it doing?
Sometime did it have a son?
Or a brother?
He loves them incondicionalmente.
Listen, I did already
more than 2000 movies.
I seized more than 8000 types-
to 2013 for the tail-
- mummy!
- I feel, wanted.
Listen, my world,
you are not good for Jane.
I did not even think that
it might have children.
I was pregnant soon.
Well, I caught 70 types this week.
However did I miscarry?
Did I give it in adoption? No.
Because to master.
She is of my blood itself.
Therefore I cannot leave
what does Herbert kill.
Listen!
They attacked my daughter in my front.
He was 3 years old.
They were my neighbors.
He sat down in my patio
and it bit the arm
since a chest of chicken is dug.
I killed it first.
Is it threatening me, Simon?
Let's love the ghosts.
We cannot kill Herbert.
We have not been eating and have
more two persons to feed.
Are they all crazy?
I think which debit to sit.
I am going to shit.
I caught animals lovelier than you.
~Você did not hear that, fondness.
I am not a child, mummy.
You are a girl. She is my girl.
These are my towels.
Do not touch them, yes?
Cannot we get on well all?
When what fancied.
Very funny.
Trent, we finish of saving him
the life and that of his brother.
But the day of the Sir will come
like thief in the night,
in which the skies will pass
with great crash
and the elements burning
they will be undone
and the land and the works that in her are,
they will be burned.
2 Peter, chapter 3, verse 10.
It is which God has.
What thing?
I do not like his attitude.
Trent, his attitude is crap.
Imbecile.
D.J., place it on the table.
Please.
With care.
They are Jane, Kylie
and I believe that you know Simon.
With care.
I need a cursed mouthful.
I need a cursed cigaret.
I need to go away from here.
It is making me nervous.
Be going to watch the enclosure.
Yes, lady.
Thank you.
Do you come?
Since something had been better to do.
Military training. Sometimes it is useful.
How is she?
Well. Only precise to rest.
Do you have water?
Yes, clear.
What happened with his arm?
One of these things bit me.
What?
I am well.
Let me see.
Wait here. I return next.
Listen.
Obliged because of helping us.
How did it find this place?
It was coming here from boy.
With my oldest brother.
Vínhamnos to camp
and we were playing of war
of killing and deluding the enemy.
And here we are.
It is made graceful as everything ended.
Does it think that that is made graceful?
20 years of service.
Soon in my last horse,
I decided what was sufficient.
What happens if he sees me doing this?
She is still pure.
I have been watching it.
Only it is waiting
is not the certain man, wanted?
It was going to make the commercial part.
To produce, this type of things.
It was in my party itself of farewell.
He was going to buy a boat.
And now we are here.
That is made graceful.
Call, Steve,
with you, did funny anything happen?
Only we were camping.
Let's do in way as if a plan had been
inside this head.
Is that completely what you have?
Listen, this is our food.
No, this would be my breakfast.
What is it doing?
It swims.
One of these things bit him.
Listen, I - Oh, diabos!
We need it!
It is infected.
How does he know of that?
I am not going to risk my life.
It can go.
We are going to maintain it here.
We will tie it and will observe it.
How does one call?
For the devil with that.
Right. He does not know anything about him.
It even might help.
He might be a scientist!
Listen, we are going
to leave it here this night.
I will undertake to him.
It is better than he is a scientist.
It will keep below Thing.
Herbert.
It is a thing.
- One calls Herbert.
- Thing!
I will not leave Mimi.
God!
17 bullets remain for us
and did it shoot for the ceiling?
Done well, Rambo.
I have no problem in using this,
specially when we were infected.
Listen, I feel well.
Go for the loft.
Please.
Do not make throwing in you, disgraced.
She will be well.
Go.
I present to him the thing,
his companion of room.
He is going to want to eat me.
Yes, well, perhaps you the coma.
That it rests!
Because it does not take away the necklace?
It does not understand me.
He has been eating there.
See.
What diabos-?
It cannot be.
Give birth!
Does he want to know?
It was going to give
this to him for the breakfast.
Let me go out from here!
Listen, I have medical training.
My girlfriend is sick
and it needs my help.
Hear, I must keep her.
It needs treatment.
Up there, it is his responsibility.
He wants to be responsible for the death
of an innocent girl?
Please. Let me go out.
I have no problem in using the weapon.
To purpose,
Lin said that his girlfriend is pregnant.
Walk.
Is it pregnant?
I do not know. Feel.
I felt it.
Feel now.
It is already kicking.
Am not I pregnant, yes? It cannot be.
I did not do anything. I swear him.
I do not understand.
I yes. You do not want to do this now.
He wants to wait
for when will we be compromised
and soon go and it catches other.
You would never do that comk.
I love it the rest.
Cursed liar.
We had no sex!
I am still pure!
Read the signs, people.
The comet?
Lift the eyes for the skies
and look at the land below;
because the skies
they will be undone like smoke
and the land will be aged
like clothes of putting on.
And in the same way
his residents will perish.
Isaías, chapter 51, verse 6.
They, them from the outside,
ressucitarão the dead men
and these souls will join his bodies.
The pregnancy of a virgin
in front of you.
The Antichrist is between us!
What stupidity.
This is not the pregnancy of a virgin.
It has at least three months.
I was in the Texas three months ago.
No!
Be removed of me.
I already do not even know him.
I have it. Go.
Calm, dear.
We need you there, welded.
Well, of acoerdo. But he must eat.
Ok, that is completely.
It is what there is
up to the tomorrow breakfast.
He eats.
Are you a doctor?
In fact I am not a doctor.
I come from a doctors' long line,
but it was in the end of this line.
I know the basic thing.
What is happening, Dr. Steve?
I am not a doctor.
Ok, nurse Steve,
it did not bring him
here in top to the party.
I think what we if discover
since they survive these ghosts,
we will be able averigüar
since in releasing of them.
Do not say to me!
Did you already discover?
Listen, I think what we if will speak
on what it happened this night,
we might find traces, connections.
Because we do not begin with you, Chad?
Die!
This might benefit him.
Sometime did he think about that?
Well, I live in a group
to 300 Km. to north from here
and it was in the city...
I have been in the world
of the Adult Entertainment for... 20 years.
If anybody does not know.
I was at alone home.
On my typical Friday of night.
Fish and a bottle of wine...
Well, he liked the idea and-
he wanted to be going to have dinner,
still that that was-
we had to retreat some hours.
I was and soon...
after the fourth Martini...
Something happened.
I like calling O Penis that broke through
the back of the porn star.
It had listened to the news on the peace
and I heard that the President was saying
that we were not worrying.
I fainted. We knew what it links-
that the comet was there
four days ago.
Great thing.
He was telling us not to worry.
Soon the sound was made stronger.
Bum!
And there was one face.
It was running in the street.
It was running in the
street and was shouting
and these things-
these things attacked it in my front
and they ate it.
And soon I - began to drive
and there was a truck
blockading the way
and these things were in my turn.
And soon I saw this place.
Trent?
I have not anything to say.
It is so which debit to be.
We cannot do anything to save us
it does not even stop to save the humanity.
Please. To help might in.
I work for my father in his church.
Recruitment,
I direct the local meetings of AA,
this type of things.
Are you afraid?
No.
If so God arranges it,
because it came here?
Because it brought his brother?
Listen, if we know it
what is happening with these people,
perhaps let's be able
to save them, save Herbert.
So it is how it arranges God!
Is that completely?
It did not bring him here to top
why does he say the same stupidity
that we are saying all
these last days.
I want to show something them.
What disgust!
I already know what it is this.
This went out of inside
of Herbert's pants.
It is his.
What, does the fez link even?
I do not believe.
I think that this is
part of the transformation
what do these things cross.
Ok, already I listened sufficiently
of these medical idiotices.
We should have eaten.
So that unless they plan
to gather oysters of ghosts,
this is the plan.
My group is
to a few hours to north from here.
I have great food and great grills.
What, to maintain someone on the outside?
No, in fact,
to maintain something in the side of inside.
You will see, I-
I kept a lion
of one of my movies.
It died, but I keep
on having the high grills.
I have vegetables, tomatoes,
all that we need.
I need of you two and of you.
What?
Because it would be
going to want to do that?
Well, to you for the reproduction
and to you for defense, work,
masculine company.
Does he want that he is his slave?
No.
My helper in the group.
And we would be his whores.
Well, something so,
but it would give them food.
Take this.
I do not need
that none of you delays me.
I go away from here.
I think that we should examine Herbert.
Who comes?
They will not touch my brother.
D.J., now.
I lament, shepherd.
We go.
What do they think what they are doing?
We are going to examine Herbert.
No, they will not do it.
If I must spend one night more here,
you and his enormous lamentation
they will spend the night down with Thing.
He is completed.
Be silent, bitch!
I think that he is right.
I am right, now move!
Move!
No.
Quilting stitch!
You will go also,
because the life complicates us?
Move and let us do ours!
You also, pastorzinho!
Of agreement.
I will spend the night there.
I will go away in the morning.
If be linked, they bring near Thing of me,
I will blow up his heads. Understood?
Expert.
No, you use this. I will tie it.
Thank you.
Already! Let's go!
Tie it!
Set it free!
Down! To the ground!
- Hold it.
- We go.
Ok, takes away his pants.
Steve!
- Lower them boy!
- Oh!
- That must hurt.
What is that?
It takes. Try with this.
Hold it.
Oh, it is a sort of bag or nodule.
Move!
Oh, for God!
If you are one of these things,
do his testicles fall?
Yes, and the penis.
When it identifies human cloth,
it is not a virus nor a bacterium
since it is not transmitted by the saliva.
How can he be sure?
My uncle - is alcoholic.
It drank so much
what him fell a finger of the foot.
Bad circulation.
Perhaps if the body is cancelled,
the genital ones are
the first ones what they if fall
when these things
they rot up to dying.
Perhaps.
Perhaps his penis has fallen
because they did not give to him
the possibility to defend his cause.
Hold it.
I love you.
Please, listen to me.
Only I have his word.
I can see and feel the proofs
for myself.
I do not know what there is...
but it grieves me very much.
Please.
Do not speak with me.
I was trusting you...
with mine all heart.
Steve, please. I specify what helps me.
I cannot help him.
It can kill it,
so a favor does us to all.
It is him who has the weapon.
You estrá good, fondness?
Is this you-?
David is my pair.
We were married eight years.
Tare is our 3-year-old girl.
It is divine.
Then you and a queer.
We do not like queer here.
This falls better in me
of which in you, imbecile.
You are the same as me.
The sodomitas are bad and sinners
against Jehovah in the majority.
Genesis, chapter 13, verse 13.
I have not to apologize.
It is completely written in the book.
The queers if they will proliferate
up to the end of the world,
and they will bring
final justice to the humanity.
Lucas, chapter 17, verses 28-30.
Does that seem to him known?
I have just lost my daughter and my couple.
Oh, they are paying for his sins.
I have no problems with that.
What does his blood whitewash on us...
and on our children.
It is well.
I would have done the same thing.
Yes, it was continuing insulting me.
I would have cut the arm
one had been gay.
What it is not.
Well, I have a son.
Listen, old man,
I have a place in Florida
for you and my family, yes?
In serious.
Listen, I will go away tomorrow.
I will return.
I will take a risk.
I know that they are alive.
Thank you.
That means very much for me.
Burn for burn,
injured by wound,
blow for blow.
Exodus!
TEstá with coldness, fondness?
Yes.
Oh, God!
Slasher, might close the door,
please?
Yes, clear.
I, personally, like the breeze.
It makes me feel living creature.
However if the girl goes-
Diabos.
Shoot in him!
Do something!
I cannot!
D.J., do something!
Close the door!
Who diabos-?
Be well, I make friends!
D.J., hurry up!
Move!
Hear, hear. Calm.
It is already. He breathes.
Oh, God!
- Ok.
- Calm.
Oh, wanted.
I undertake.
What diabos exists there with you?
What? Is it going to shoot in me?
He does not know that it is a thing of mentally
handicapped person to point to a weapon for a woman?
And now what?
- We will close the gate.
- I will not go outside.
The hero now is afraid!
Be dark!
You are a viado.
The weapon happens.
Do not be rude.
I do not believe that it has the courage.
Do you have it?
Simon, is enough!
Diabos!
It is already sufficient!
Chad, we need the weapon.
No, Steve, we should
have guarded the bullets.
Why? For an emergence?
No, use the carving knife.
We will let them pass from one to one
and we will use that.
To let the enemy in here?
This is the thing more rude
than I already heard in my life.
We should have left and secure the perimeter
or we will die here inside!
Listen, give us the weapon.
Simon will guide us even outside
and we will follow it.
Give me the weapon!
Of agreement. I will do it.
However not in the night, ok?
I do not see well in the night.
There will be much more in the morning!
Chad is right.
It will be better to try in the morning.
Right.
That is what he was trying to say to them.
Someone has
a clean T-shirt to lend me?
I.
Did I lose anything?
Hello.
It grieves me.
Show off.
Here below.
And here.
And in the neck.
There are only the pains of the pregnancy.
Like a ninja, eh?
I cannot-
Move! Then move!
We are ready, let's go!
Steve, covers the sides and the bottom.
Open the door.
Do it!
Move.
Hammer.
Let's do this.
Oh, diabos!
Recarregue - to!
Very well. I am ready.
Brave.
They delayed the inevitable
thing for one more day.
Listen.
It is not worthwhile.
Slash! Slash!
Guard a seat for me in the club, friend.
Soon I will be with you.
What-?
We forget one.
- Promptly?
- Yes.
Go.
Wait - ok.
Diabos.
Oh, for God!
What?
See that.
When it took care with the corners.
Yes.
Not so far and down.
Nurse Steve?
I do not know-
What, it finds that I yes?
Oh, God's mother!
Cut it. Let's see what it has inside.
What disgust.
What is?
It seems human.
It has three arms.
Cut an arm to see if it feels pain.
That is revolting.
What, it is playing?
It will help us to know
if we can kill this thing.
The arm continues moving.
The body
it does not seem to have reacted very much.
Let's see.
Gee, it is cured alone.
A new body is going out.
I already see the form
of the fetus developing.
I think what it must do
a complete autopsy in this body.
We have to see it
what more do we can averigüar.
No?
Yes.
Care.
What is this long vein?
It is tied
to all the principal organs.
It rises up to the neck.
We are going to turn it.
Hear, it rises up to the head.
Open the head.
Shake it.
Where is the rest?
Look under the table. Thereabouts.
It is not here.
Not here.
I adjust what we need.
Perhaps be in the loft.
The door is opened.
Some volunteer?
I will go.
I also.
To the loft?
Yes.
It gives him silver coin.
Always.
Diabos!
God!
Please, help me!
Diabos!
This thing attacked Simon!
It attacked it!
It is big now.
It attacked it and I could not do anything.
I could not-
Help us, he calls himself
what is the will of God,
I will kill him right now!
- I will go.
- No.
I will go.
It is our end of the same way.
Be quiet.
It was waiting that everything was happening
since God arranged it.
I will leave these creatures they pass.
The queers are worthy of the death
for his sexual antinatural practices,
revolting and depraved.
Levítico, chapter 20, verse 13!
The creature killed Simon.
For God, it arrived late.
Diabos.
We have not any more water not even eaten.
My girlfriend is pregnant.
The son belongs of another man.
Only three bullets remain for us
and a world full of human dead men,
controlled by creatures in his head,
what, in any way is made a list
with the fall of a comet.
Might it be worse?
You also might be castrated.
Well, this is what we have.
It looks that these creatures
there are a sort of parasite,
what does he survive of his hóspedeiro
and it finishes killing it.
Soon it castrates the man
and it substitutes his reproductive organs
for his embryo itself.
It seems amusing.
However for what?
They are adapted.
They are...
treating of fundirr his DNA with ours
to create a hybrid creature
what can survive
in the atmosphere of the land.
It can reproducir-se assexualmente.
Then each man-ghost
probably it is to days of incubating.
The men cannot go out.
They will take control of the world.
And we?
Men.
A minute.
Mimi, comes here out.
Go up to the grill.
Why?
Only do this.
Walk thereabouts.
How does one feel?
Worse.
Come here.
Is she one of them, no?
Chad.
Diabos!
One stands up.
She is one of them. It must die.
He does not know what it is doing.
Chad, lowers the weapon!
Shoot in her! Shoot in the cursed one!
Get up!
It can go. We do not need you here.
It is committing a great mistake,
I make friends.
Yes? We will help it. D.J.
You did the correct thing.
I return next.
Is he you?
Yes.
Listen.
I feel very much.
It never had to doubt of you.
Where am I?
In the loft.
In the refuge?
Yes.
I think that I fainted
when it pointed to me with the weapon.
I am starving.
Really I have
one of these things inside me?
I am a mother.
Cursed ghosts.
Listen, Trent.
Let's make love. Now.
Perhaps this is his last opportunity...
in the life.
Come here.
So.
Please, Deus, please.
Cursed bitch.
What did it do with me?
Oh, God!.
No! My baby!
For what? For what?
My baby! No!
No!
I have it. Are you ready?
I return next.
What?
I think that I already
know what it happened.
Everything began with the comet.
These creatures, parasites, were
frozen in the ice of the comet.
Possibly unicellular organisms
waiting to fall in a planet,
somewhere of the universe
to continue his cycle of life.
To the being released by the impact, it if was distributed
for everyone with the radioactive rain.
Any living organism breathed
this replete powder of parasites.
It is like a lonely ringworm.
These parasites do what better they know:
They survive and develop
in a bigger scale.
What waste.
These things are going to incubate soon.
We should have gone for a safe place!
For a fort.
An impenetrable refuge
naked peak of a mountain, perhaps?
Perhaps, but we need to eat.
If to be here, we should
have idealized a system to survive.
The autosufficient group of Chad
it can be a good option.
We need provisions right now.
I will go. However I cannot make that alone.
I go with you, girl.
I also.
Dispose of me.
No. You stay here
and take care of his girlfriend.
And we need someone in the entry.
Kylie, can I tell him a thing?
Clear, my love.
I respect you very much.
Thank you.
- Let's do then.
- Yes.
We go.
We go. Move!
- Diabos.
- Follow in front!
- The gate!
- Let's go!
Oh, God!
Mimi, bring the weapon!
No! Wait, Kylie!
Go out from here! Go!
What is that?
It seems a shot.
She is Lin.
Be here.
Oh, God!.
What does he want?
A second opportunity.
What did he say?
Listen, Steve,
there is nothing any more
outside of what you buzz.
You saved me the life. I must respect that.
And like or not, we are joined in this.
Because I do not trust you?
Very well.
From now on, all we will have arms.
Let me pass.
Open the jacket and go round.
One does not make repenting of this.
Oh, chocolate.
I have great-
I have great canned food.
Tengo seeds, music, creators,
cool fruit drinks, books, plays, liqueur.
I have even... this.
We go, Steve, it is my group.
I...
I need of companhía.
I need help. It is a very big place.
Only Mimi and I remain here.
Diabos.
Ok, do you want to begin a community?
Or it is ready to catch a dwarf,
or it is ready to do to him his friend.
This is one of my lines of-
Quadruple risk.
Perhaps know some of his works.
Do not call.
How is she?
Lin wants to operate
it if it manages to return.
I wait that yes.
And not to return?
It might have brought the good.
I went to all the shops of the city,
the city is completely flooded.
It was that or the illicit local liqueur.
In the end, the majority is so.
Besides more, of everything necessary
to prepare ours.
Yes!
- Yes.
Illicit liqueur!
Listen, Steve.
I even have a bag of calçinhas.
What look to him?
No?
No! No!
Do something!
Please!
Steve, I have soporiferous drugs.
No, not - Am I Chad, yes?
I am Chad.
Now see!
Wait, hear, hear.
Take away this thing of inside me.
When Mimi was wanted,
I know that what I am to do
probably cost to me the life,
but I do not mind.
To see you suffering
is worse than the death itself.
I love you and want that he keeps on living-
not only for me,
but for the good of the humanity.
You amaré forever.
Steve.
I love you.
It is the alcohol.
They do not like the alcohol.
They do not like the alcohol, wanted.
All drunks were when it fell.
I had taken champagne
in the night that the comet fell.
They do not like the alcohol in the blood.
I am going to take him from here.
Take this.
Antibiotics.
A minute.
We should have gone to a group of Chad,
to secure it, to sow corn,
trees of apple,
what does he want
that it has in the camionete.
And we should have
put a ring in his finger...
it as early as possible.
What does it mean?
Would you get married with me?
Yes, clear.
For the happy couple.
Take, drink this.
It is well.
Yes, I know. It is awful.
Ok, there has one. Shoot in this.
Wait. Take.
Diabos.
Come, we go.
Listen, we go.
SUBS BY: * JPetway *
RiPPED - EDiT BY: * N3krA *