[ Screaming ]
[ Car Alarms Wailing ]
[ Dogs Barking ]
[ Panting ]
I HATE THOSE THINGS.
OH.
???? [ "Reality Used To Be
A Friend of Mine" ]
?? OOO-OOO
OOO-OOO ??
?? REALITY USED TO BE
A FRIEND OF MINE ??
?? MAY BE WHY THE QUESTION
THAT'S ON YOUR MIND ??
?? BUT REALITY USED TO BE
A FRIEND OF MINE ??
?? REALITY USED TO BE
?? PLEASE DON'T ASK ME
'CAUSE I DON'T KNOW WHY ??
?? BUT REALITY USED TO BE
A FRIEND OF MINE ??
?? I USED TO BE FRIENDS
WITH REALITY ??
?? SHE USED TO BE A PAL
REAL CLOSE TO ME ??
?? BUT SHE TRIED TO HIDE FROM ME
WHAT WAS IN STORE ??
[ Howling ]
[ Woman ]
STANLEY, IS THAT --
UMMM.
PUT THAT BACK !
HEY, I JUST WASHED
ALL THIS STUFF.
IT'S MY GEAR.
SORRY, MAN.
IT'S OKAY.
WHAT'S MY MOM
SHE'S BUMMED 'CAUSE I
SNAKED YOUR LAST BAGEL.
GRAB A SHOVEL,
MAN.
YOU DON'T WANNA HELP,
THAT'S JUST FINE.
[ Stoney ]
UH-HUH.
DAVE, BE MORE OF A GEEK.
THERE'S NO WAY
[ Girl ]
YOU'RE A DISEASE.
AND NO ONE WILL EVER SWIM
IN THIS STUPID POOL.
LATER.
LOOK, DAVID,
PLEASE DO ME A FAVOR
HIGH SCHOOL
IS OVER, BUDDY.
GET INTO IT.
WE'RE LOSERS.
I'VE DECIDED SOMETHING, STONEY.
I WANNA LOOK BACK ON
AND THINK THAT I STARTED
SLOWLY BUT I FINISHED
HIGH SCHOOL'S ALMOST OVER
AND I DON'T HAVE
I KNOW, ME NEITHER.
YOU SHOULD BE STOKED
'CAUSE YOU GOT THROUGH
THE LAST FOUR YEARS WITHOUT
IT'S NOT ENOUGH.
I MEAN, I WANT MY OWN
JUMP OFF THE GYM,
SPLATTER ON THE STREET
IT'S NOT FUNNY.
I'M NOT GOIN' DOWN AS
WHEN I FINISH THIS POOL,
I'M GONNA HAVE THE
I'M GONNA BE THE PROM KING !
AND I'M GONNA GRADUATE A LEGEND.
[ Stoney ]
WELL, WHAT ABOUT ME ?
OH, WELL YOU'LL
BE THERE TOO.
THANKS, BUT ROBYN SWEENEY,
SHE'S NOT GOIN' TO
-I WISH SHE WOULD BUT SHE'S NOT.
-WHAT ARE YOU TALKIN' ABOUT ?
ROBYN SWEENEY
IS MINE.
SHE'S BECOME A MAJOR BABE
AND SHE LOVES ME.
SHE FINDS YOU CRUSTY,
DAVE.
SHE'LL SEE
THE TRUTH.
LIFE'S ABOUT GREASIN'
THE DO-BACK, BUDDY
HIGH SCHOOL WAS
INTERESTING, RIGHT,
BUT IT WAS KIND OF
LIKE A HARSH RIDE.
WE'RE GOIN' ON TO BIGGER
AND BETTER THINGS, BUDDY.
STONEY, I AM ON TO
BIGGER AND BETTER THINGS.
COUNT ON IT !
[ Stoney Yelling ]
[ Stoney ]
OH, WOW !
?? I'M A STONEY CRUSTY DUDE
?? DID YOU KNOW THAT ?
[ Stoney ]
?? I GOT A MOP
EXCUSE ME.  COULD YOU MOVE.
ME AND MY FRIEND, DAVID
HEY, THERE'S ROBYN.
HEY, ROBYN.
FOUR-WHEELIN'
OVER THE FERNS.
LOOK, DAVE, YOU'RE GONNA
HAVE TO MELLOW OUT, BRO,
SHE ALWAYS SHINES YA.
YOU DON'T UNDERSTAND.
YOU HAD PRE-FRESHMAN
HISTORY.  YOU COULD'VE
SHE HADN'T HIT
"BABEHOOD" YET.
MILK DOES A BODY GOOD.
CHECK HER.
[ Stoney ]
SHE'S CLEAN, BUDDY,
AND HE'S GOT HER.
[ Chuckles ]
MATT WILSON ?
WHAT A JERK.
WHAT DOES SHE
SEE IN HIM ANYWAY ?
[ Stoney ]
HE'S GOT THE BUFF SPIKES
DUDE, HE'S CHECKIN'
HER CHEEKS.  OOH !
HE'S GOT THE SERIOUS BEAK,
HIS OWN PERSONAL... OH !
FULL OF FUNDAGE, BRO,
THAT HE WEASES
OFF OF MA--
[ Stoney ]
EIGHTEEN INCH BI'S.
MINE ARE ONLY FOUR.
BESIDES THAT.
HE WALKS LIKE THIS,
RIGHT ?
JUST LIKE THIS,
THE NUGS FULLY LOOSE.
[ Indistinct Chatter ]
HI, MATT.
ALL RIGHT, EVERYBODY.
QUIET, PLEASE.
SETTLE DOWN, QUIET.
WE'RE GONNA START
SAME PLACE WE ENDED
LAST WEEK'S CLASS.
THAT'S TALKING ABOUT
PREHISTORIC MAN
IN THE -- ?
ICE AGE.
YES, ICE AGE.
WHY DO WE CALL IT THE ICE AGE ?
'CAUSE THERE WAS A LOT OF ICE.
WHAT DO WE CALL
THESE BIG CHUNKS OF ICE,
WE CALLED WHAT ?
WHAT DO WE CALL THEM ?
RIGHT.  YOU ARE PAYING
ATTENTION.  THAT'S GOOD.
THESE GLACIERS, AS THEY
MOVED DOWN OUR WAY,
THEY'RE SO HEAVY, COLD
AND THICK THAT THEY
AND THEY FORM
UNDERGROUND -- ?
RIGHT.  BELIEVE IT OR NOT,
SOME SCIENTISTS BELIEVE
UNDERGROUND GLACIAL MOVEMENTS
STILL IN THIS PART OF THE WORLD.
YOU KNOW WHAT I THINK
THAT IS, CLASS ?
[ Class ]
LAME !
LISTEN,
PLEASE REMEMBER...
THAT MOST OF THIS HEMISPHERE,
INCLUDING THE GROUND
ALL OF THIS WAS UNDER ICE
AT SOME POINT, SO I GUESS...
FINDING SOMETHING FROZEN,
DUG UP HERE OR THERE,
WOULDN'T BE THAT UNCOMMON
WHEN YOU THINK ABOUT IT.
SO MOVING RIGHT ALONG
ON YOUR JOURNEY OF KNOWLEDGE,
LET ME SHOW YOU
CRO-MAGNON MAN.
HE'S DOPE.
I'D GO OUT WITH HIM.
[ Class Laughing ]
NO, NO.
I DON'T THINK SO, ELLA.
CRO-MAGNON MAN, EVEN THOUGH
HE'S STANDIN' UPRIGHT AND ALL,
HE WAS EXTREMELY BRUTAL.
HE JUST TOOK
WHATEVER HE WANTED...
AND THAT INCLUDED
HIS WOMEN.
THAT'S BARBARIC !
INDEED.
???? [ Radio ]
STONE !
STONEY !
???? [ Radio ]
HEY !  COME ON,
CHECK THIS OUT.
FEEL THE GROUND,
MAN.
WHOA, BUDDY,
IT'S CHILLIN'.
IT'S NOT LIKE
CHILLIN', CHILLIN'.
BRO, IT IS CHILLIN' !
I KNOW.
IT'S SO, UH --
HELP ME.
CHECK IT, BUDDY.
OH, BUDDY !
DUDE, I KNOW
WHAT THIS IS, BRO.
IT'S A
MOUSTERIAN BOWL.
HEY, COME ON, DAVID.
BE CAREFUL WITH THAT.
WHAT'S A MOUSTERIAN BOWL ?
A MOUSTERIAN BOWL
FROM THE MOUSTERIAN ERA.
"PREHISTORIC ARTIFACTS
FOR FIVE HUNDRED, ALEX."
DON'T YOU EVER
WATCH "JEOPARDY" ?
BUDDY, THIS IS KIND OF LIKE
PREHISTORIC TUPPERWARE, BRO.
IT'S STILL PRESERVED...
LIKE SMUCKERS !
OOOOW !
[ Barking ]
EARTHQUAKE !
[ Rumbling ]
AHHHH !
OH !
OH GOD !
NICE SAVE, DAVAGE.
STONE ?
YEAH.
THERE'S A GUY
BURIED IN MY POOL.
[ Screaming ]
HELLO, FRED.
I'M GLAD I CAUGHT YOU.
ARE YOU AVAILABLE
FOR A MEETING
MS. MORGAN,
OPEN THE DOOR !
MOM, THERE'S A GUY
BURIED IN OUR POOL !
MOM !  MOM !
OPEN THE DOOR !
[ Indistinct Yelling ]
I'M WORKING !
CALL 9-1-1 !
[ Scratching ]
[ Stoney ]
THEY NEVER FOUND
YEAH, OR JIMMY HOFFA.
OR JIMMY MAHONEY.
HE WAS A KID I KNEW
IN CUB SCOUTS.
COME ON,
LET'S GO.
THEY NEVER
FOUND HIM.
DAVID, I KNOW
WHAT THIS IS.
IT'S A CAVEMAN.
WOULD YOU PLEASE !
NO, I'M SERIOUS.
NO WAY !
WHOA.
A CAVEMAN !
THIS IS UNBELIEVABLE !
DO YOU KNOW WHAT
THIS COULD MEAN --
THIS COULD MEAN FAME
OR POPULARITY !
FAR TOO MUCH
RESPONSIBILITY FOR ME.
ANYWAYS,
I'M ALREADY POPULAR.
YEAH, YOU TRAVEL
IN LARGE GROUPS
BESIDES, THIS IS
MY ONE CHANCE TO MAKE
YOU GOTTA HELP ME DIG
HIM OUT.  YOU WERE HERE.
I DON'T WANNA BE PART
OF ANYTHING, DAVE.
IT COULD MEAN MONEY.
YOU TELLIN' ME YOU
COULDN'T USE A,
SOME NEW BELL-BOTTOMS ?
A LITTLE FUN-DAGE ?
WEASE SOME OLDER NUGS
WITH A MANSION AND A POOL ?
SOAKIN' UP THE RAYS,
WATCHIN' ALL THE
"JEOP-ARDY" YOU CAN HANDLE ?
THAT WAS THE CLINCHER.
EVERYBODY'S GOT A PRICE.
[ Lawn Mower Motor ]
STEADY IT !
GIVE IT MORE GAS,
PERFECT !  HOLD !
THIS THING
WEIGHS A TON.
AHH !
HEY, THERE'S HIS PITS,
BRO.
[ David ]
THAT'S HIS HEAD.
THAT'S HIS SKULL.
[ Snoring ]
GET OFF ME !
WHAT ARE YOU
DOIN' ?
OW !  COME ON,
LET'S GET UP.
HE'S STILL IN HERE.
NO KIDDING, DAVE.
HE'S AN ICE CUBE.
WE GOTTA
THAW HIM OUT.
THIS HAS GOTTA BE
OUR SECRET, OKAY ?
YOU CAN'T TELL ANYBODY...
NOBODY !
CAN I TELL
STEVE KOOSER ?
ALL RIGHT ?  NOBODY !
YOU UNDERSTAND ?
THANK YOU.
DEE-DO-DAH.
???? [ Rock ]
????
THIS IS
KIND OF NICE.
HI, ROBYN.
HI, DAVE.
GUESS WHAT
I FOUND ?
NO.  COME HERE.
GUESS WHAT I FOUND ?
I DON'T KNOW.
I HAVE NO IDEA.
[ Whispering ]
I FOUND A CAVEMAN.
SHH.  YEAH.
OH DAVE,
IT'S COOL, RIGHT ?
I FOUND A CAVEMAN.
ALL BY MYSELF.
I DUG HIM OUT
YOU WANNA COME CHECK HIM OUT
AFTER SCHOOL ?
I'M ONLY INVITIN'
A FEW PEOPLE.
TEN MINUTES...
PLEASE ?
DAVE, I JUST DON'T THINK
I'M READY TO HANDLE A --
A CAVEMAN.
YOU'RE NOT ?
ALL RIGHT.
I UNDERSTAND.
BYE, DAVID.
[ Sighs ]
I LOVE IT WHEN
HELLO, DAVID.
AGH.
GOIN' SOMEWHERE ?
YEAH, I GOT A DATE
WITH YOUR MOM.
IT'S A JOKE.
I'M SORRY, JUST KIDDING.
[ Grunting ]
YOU'VE BEEN A HEADACHE
EVER SINCE THE THIRD GRADE.
I KNOW ABOUT YOUR STUPID
PROM-KING BULLSHIT.
ROBYN WOULDN'T PISS
ON YOUR GUMS IF YOUR
- YES, SHE WOULD.
- [ Chuckling ]
SHUSH !  HUSH, PLEASE !
SHOWIN' YOUR IGNORANCE
AGAIN, MORGAN.
SOME OF US PUMP
AND SOME OF US SLUMP.
YOU SHOULD
TRY SOME PUMP, MORGAN.
YOU'RE SO --
AM I ?
N-NO, STOP.
STOP IT !
WHY DO YOU
MAKE ME DO THIS ?
[ Dave ]
WHAT ARE YOU WRITING ?
MATT, NOT THE
FIRE ALARM !
MATT !  MATT !
GOD, HELP !
OH GOD !
HEY, COME HERE.
OH, TA-HA-HA.
[ Laughing, Jeering ]
[ Screaming ]
[ Sniffing ]
[ Grunting ]
[ Barking ]
[ Helicopter Whirring ]
[ Screams ]
[ Glass Smashing ]
HMM.
[ Truck Engine ]
[ Coughing ]
[ Engine Revving ]
[ Yelling ]
I'LL BE BACK.
?? THIS IS OUR PHILOSOPHY
ALL THESE THINGS
???? [ Continues Indistinct ]
?? NOW IN THIS LAND
OF DEMOCRACY WHY NO ONE
?? LADY LIBERTY ROCKS AWAY
NO TRUTH, NO JUSTICE ??
?? THE AMERICAN WAY ????
[ Groans ]
?? CLAP YOUR HANDS
AND DANCE ??
????
?? TREATY, OO-OH
TREATY, YEAH ??
?? TREATY, OO-OH ??
????
[ Gasping ]
HE MELTED.
DAVE, IT JUST WASN'T
MEANT TO HAPPEN.
COME ON, I'LL GO
BUY YOU SOME HO-HOS.
COME ON.
IT'S ALL RIGHT.
HE MELTED.
BORIS !
[ Alarm Sounding ]
[ Screaming ]
WHAT THE --
[ Sizzling ]
I CAN'T BELIEVE IT.
HE'S ALIVE !
HE WAS PRACTICALLY
AN ICE CUBE...
I SAY
WE JUST WALK.
OH, PLEASE.
HE IS OURS.
WHAT ?
BE HOSPITABLE ?
[ Sniffing ]
- OOH !
- AHH !  AHH !
HOW YA DOIN' ?
HI, MY NAME IS DAVE.
COME HERE, COME HERE.
INTRODUCE YOURSELF.
THIS IS STONEY.
STONEY, HE'S MY FRIEND.
UH, THIS IS MY ROOM.
IT'S OKAY.
UH, WE'RE
FROM ENCINO.
IT'S A PLEASURE
TO MAKE YOUR ACQUAINTANCE.
AND WE HOPE YOU DON'T
GNAW ON OUR BEAKS.
I KNOW WHAT
I'M DOING, STONE.
WE GO TO HIGH SCHOOL.
HIGH SCHOOL ?
HE DOESN'T KNOW
WHAT HIGH SCHOOL IS.
WHAT ANYTHING IS.
JUST BE
CALM AND EASY.
CALM...
AND EASY.
- [ Ringing ]
- [ Screaming ]
- GET THE PHONE.
- OKAY.  OKAY.
[ Caveman Laughing ]
IT'S OKAY.
SEE, I THINK
HE'S CALMING DOWN.
CALMING... DOWN.
[ Phone Beeping ]
[ Screaming ]
UGH ?
FIRE.
FLAMEAGE.
BUDDY'S INTO IT.
THAT WAS KILL,
LOOK AT HIS EYES.
HE LIKES THE BLUE PART.
HE'S GLOSSY-EYED.
LOOK, FREAK
OW !  OOH !
- UGH !
- OKAY.  AH, AH !
GIVE IT TO HIM.
NO !
UGH.  UGH.
- HERE, HERE.  LOOK, HERE.
-YOU GOTTA TEACH HIM.
WHOA !  OH.
HEY !
NO.
WHAT ?
DID YOU JUST --
- I THINK HE JUST SAID "NO."
- NO !
- NO ?
- NO !  NO !
NO.  NO.
COOL, BUDDY.
HE IS SO GREASY !
GREASY ?  HE'S A
PREHISTORIC PYROMANIAC.
WE GOTTA
TEACH HIM STUFF.
NO.  NO.
NO !
NO !  NO !
OH GOD.
WE GOTTA TEACH HIM
NO, UH-UH.
WE'RE GOIN' PSYCHO
THAT'S BORING, DUDE,
NORMAL !
STONEY, COME ON, MAN.
HANG WITH ME.
WE GOTTA PLAY
THIS THING OUT.
IF WE TELL ANYONE,
IF ANYONE SEES HIM, THEY'LL
THEY'LL CUT HIM UP
INTO LITTLE PIECES.
THEY'LL TAKE ALL THE CREDIT,
AND WE'LL STILL BE GEEKS.
I'M NOT A GEEK.
I'M A UNIQUE WEASEL, DAVID.
I'M JUST UNDERRATED 'CAUSE
I LIVE HERE IN ENCINO.
BUD ?
BUDDY ?
O-O-O-OW !
OKAY ?
HE NEEDS A BATH...
BIG TIME.
?? I'M TOO SEXY
FOR MY LOVE ??
?? TOO SEXY FOR MY LOVE
LOVE'S GOING TO LEAVE ME ??
????
?? I'M TOO SEXY
FOR MY SHIRT ??
?? TOO SEXY FOR MY SHIRT
SO SEXY IT HURTS ??
?? AND I'M
TOO SEXY FOR MILAN ??
?? TOO SEXY FOR MILAN
NEW YORK AND JAPAN ??
[ Growling ]
?? I'M TOO SEXY
FOR YOUR PARTY ??
?? TOO SEXY FOR YOUR PARTY
NO WAY I'M DISCO DANCING ??
????
?? I'M TOO SEXY
FOR MY LOVE ??
?? TOO SEXY FOR MY LOVE
LOVE'S GOING TO LEAVE ME ??
?? I'M TOO SEXY
FOR THIS SONG ????
STANDING O.
OUTSTANDING.
IF I HAD A BIC, BRO,
RIGHT HERE.
LET'S SHOW HIM
HIMSELF.
YOU WANNA SEE
YOUR MUG, BUD ?
UGH !
WHAT, DUDE ?
YOU SHOULD BE WITH
YOU LOOK BUFF.
RIGHT ?
HEY, CAN YOU
SAY "BA...UFF" ?
BA...UFF ?
[ Laughing ]
I LIKE THAT.
YOU KNOW,
WE GOTTA GIVE HIM
A COOL NAME.
AXL.
YEAH, BUDDY.
NOT AXL.
THIS IS SERIOUS.
WE'VE GOT THE MISSING LINK
STANDING IN MY BEDROOM.
LINK !  LINK !
WE'LL CALL HIM LINK !
OKAY, COOL.
MAYBE WE COULD CALL HIM
BECAUSE HE'S GOT
MY SAME 'DO...
AND HE'S FROM
THE STONE AGE.
I LIKE LINK BETTER.
OKAY, WE'LL
BUT CAN I
CALL HIM LINKAGE ?
COOL !
LET'S SEE HOW
NO, NO.
COME HERE.
OKAY.  OKAY.
YOU OKAY ?
UH, UH, LOOK.
SEE ?
UGH.
WHOA !
AHH !
AHH, OOW, OOO.
OOOW !
[ Chuckling ]
OKAY, OKAY.
UM, LINK.
LINK.
NO !
YOU'RE LINK.
I'M DAVE.  DAVE !
DAVE.  DAVE.
NO, DAVE, DAVE.
DAVE, DAVE, DAVE.
DAVE.
YES !
OKAY,
AND THAT'S --
THAT'S STONEY.
MM-HMM.
STO...NEY.
NO, NO.
STONEY.
YES !
AHH !
OKAY, OKAY.
AND NOW YOU ARE ?
DAVE !
AHH !
NO, NO, I'M DAVE.
YOU ARE ?
BUFF.
[ Sighs ]
NO.
IT'S ALL RIGHT.
YOU'VE HAD A HARD DAY.
- YOUR PARENTS !
- MY PARENTS !
OKAY, UH, UH,
TAKE HIM OUT BACK AND RING
BUT, DAVE --
NO "BUTS,"
FOLLOW THE WEASEL,
LINKAGE, COME ON.
[ Banging, Crashing ]
MY KITCHEN !
BUSTED !
WHAT ARE YOU DOING ?
I'M COOKING DINNER.
YOU'RE WHAT ?
BUSTED !
I'M COOKING DINNER.
I THOUGHT IT MIGHT BE
THEY'RE SURPRISED,
ALL RIGHT.
[ Ringing ]
WHAT IS
GOING ON HERE ?
WHERE'S THE FLOUR ?
I CAN'T FIND THE FLOUR.
HELLO, STANLEY.
WHO IS THIS STRANGE BOY AND
IT GOT STUCK, SIR.
COME IN.
[ Father ]
WHOSE FAMILY ?
BORIS, GET DOWN !
BORIS !
- BORIS, GET OUT !
-[ Dave ] GET DOWN !
-[ Link Screaming ]
- GET OUT, GET OUT !
HEY, DAD.
DAVID,
WHO IS THAT ?
THAT ?
WHO'S THAT ?
- THAT WAS LINKAVITCH CHOMOFSKY.
- WHAT ?
LINK... LINKAV--
DOESN'T ANYBODY IN THIS HOUSE
WHAT IS HE
TALKING ABOUT ?
DAD, LINKAVITCH
CHOMOFSKY.
OUR EXCHANGE STUDENT ?
HE'S HERE.
HE'S GONNA HELP US
DIG THE POOL.
- YEAH !
- [ Sighs ]
WHY DOES NONE OF THIS
SOUND FAMILIAR TO ME ?
I TOLD YOU ABOUT THIS
MONTHS AGO, REMEMBER ?
ABOUT SCHOOL GIVING US
EXTRA CREDIT FOR COLLEGE
AND LEARNING ABOUT
THEIR CULTURE AND
NOW YOU'RE GONNA
TAKE IT BACK ?
NO, NO, NO, I'M NOT
GONNA TAKE IT BACK.
THIS IS IMPORTANT TO ME.
THIS IS MY LIFE.
IT'S EMBARRASSING.
HE TRAVELLED HERE
- I DON'T KNOW, ESTONIA ?
- YEAH, ESTONIA !
MOM, COME ON.
YOU'RE NOT BUYING THIS ?
WELL, I --
DAD ?
ACTUALLY, I, I,
I THINK NOW...
THAT I, I, I DO
RECALL SOMETHING.
- SEE ?
- SEE, IT'S ABOUT FOCUSING.
YOU'RE BOGUS.
LARRY, HOW COULD I FORGET
HE'S AN EXCHANGE STUDENT.
HE'S GOING TO BE STAYING
YOU FORGOT ME
IN THE THIRD GRADE.
I SPENT THE ENTIRE NIGHT AFTER
THE PLAY IN THE PARKING LOT.
OKAY, WHERE'S
HE GONNA STAY ?
AND WHY IS HE
ATTACKING THE DOG ?
HE'S GONNA STAY IN MY ROOM.
HE'S NOT ATTACKING THE DOG.
- AS IF !
- SHUT UP !
- YOU SHUT UP.
- NO, EVERYBODY SHUT UP.
LARRY, IT'S OKAY.
I'M TIRED.
IT'S TIME WE DECIDE
WHAT WE'RE GONNA MAKE
I ASSUME YOU'LL
BE JOINING US ?
WE PRACTICALLY FEED THE
ENTIRE NEIGHBORHOOD.  WHY NOT
I ALWAYS EAT HERE
AND I LIKE YOUR FOOD.
GREAT.
[ Ringing ]
STOP IT !  NO.
NO, NO, NO.
[ Rings ]
[ Dave ]
I CAN'T BELIEVE YOU TOLD
[ Stoney ]
COW PAJAMAS ?
OOH !
SOME BETTY, HUH ?
BETTY.
GONZANGAS.
GONZANGAS ?
BUDDY, CONES.
I KNOW YOU'VE HAD
A BIG DAY, PAL.
I'M GONNA TAKE YOU
SOMEPLACE REALLY SPECIAL.
TACO BELL.
BETTER.
CONGRATULATIONS, LINK.
YOU'RE GONNA BE A SENIOR.
SMILE.
?? WILD THING ??
?? YOU MAKE
MY HEART SING ??
EVERYTHING GROOVY ??
?? WILD THING ??
OH GOD,
HE DOESN'T LIKE THAT.
THAT'S GLASS.
THAT HURTS YOUR BEAK.
STAND UP STRAIGHT.
[ Stoney ]
POOR STONE-AGER.
HE SPENT A MILLION YEARS
CHILLIN' IN A BLOCK OF ICE,
NOW HE'S GOTTA GO
TO HIGH SCHOOL !  AGH !
WHO'S THAT GUY WITH
THE DORK SQUAD ?
OH MY GOD,
HE IS TOTALLY RUDE.
WE HAVE GOT A
MAJOR FIND HERE.
THIS GUY'S OUR TICKET
TO FAME AND POPULARITY.
ALL WE GOTTA DO IS GET HIM
ENROLLED IN SCHOOL AND HE'LL
THAT'S HARSH.
WE'LL MAKE HIM FAMOUS.
WE'LL TEACH HIM SOME
STUPID PET TRICKS AND
YOU'RE WEASIN' OFF
HIS GIG.
OH PLEASE !
HE'S A CAVEMAN,
LOOK AT HIM.
HE'S PRACTICALLY
WE FOUND HIM.
WE CAN DO WHATEVER
WE, WE, WE ?
NO, NO, NO.
I JUST WANNA BE
HIS FRIEND.
FINE.
HELLO, MRS. MACKEY.
AND WHAT DO WE
HAVE HERE ?
NOW I'M COVERED
UP TO FOURTH PERIOD.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT TO DO
WITH HIM AFTER THAT.
WILL YOU BE CAREFUL ?
I'LL BE COOL, MAN.
OKAY.
WHAT'S HE DOIN' ?
[ Dave ]
I DON'T KNOW.
LINK, BE CAREFUL !
UH, HEY, HEY --
HEY, LINK,
HOW'S YOUR MELON, BUD ?
[ Sniffing ]
WHOA !
EXCUSE ME.
HEY, HEY, HEY !
[ Grunting ]
WHOA.
LINK ?
IS THIS DUDE
TOTALLY FUNDAMENTAL
DID YOU MISS ME ?
ALWAYS.
WHO IS THIS ?
THIS IS
LINK.
HE'S STAYING WITH US.
YOU'RE KIDDING ?
THIS GUY IS STAYING WITH YOU ?
UH-HUH.
HE'S THINKIN' OF
BECOMING A HAIRDRESSER.
DESIGNING CRUSTY MOPS
FOR THE RICH AND FAMOUS.
OH.
UGH.  GONZANGAS.
NO !
BYE, ROBYN.
I THINK HE WAS SAYING
HE LIKES YOUR CONES.
I'M THRILLED.
GET OUT OF MY FACE !
ROBYN,
THAT IMPORT IS MINE.
THIS IS JUST
IN TIME FOR PROM.
IS HE FINE
OR WHAT ?
HE'S A LOOKER !
LINK.  LINK !
LINK, PLEASE,
COME SIT DOWN.
WHO IS THIS DIPSHIT,
ANYWAY ?
HIS NAME'S LINK.
HE'S FROM ESTONIA AND
I THINK HE'S JIVE.
JIVE, YEAH.
YOU DO ?
HELL YEAH,
AND I'M NOT THE ONLY ONE.
HEY, LINK !
[ Coughing ]
[ Bell Ringing ]
I'LL SEE YOU
WATCH HIM.
ALL RIGHT, DAVID.
WE GOT SPANISH NOW.
SPANISH IS LIKE GUACAMOLE,
La d?a es mi
en hermanos.
THE DAY IS BEAUTIFUL.
???? [ Rap ]
THE SUN ISN'T SHINING
ALL THROUGH THE NIGHT.
????
LINK, COME ON.
SORRY, YOU GUYS.
WHOA !
Vale, repitan en Espanol.
THE CHEESE IS
OLD AND MOLDY.
[ Class ]
El queso est?
[ Teacher ]
WHERE IS THE BATHROOM ?
¿¿ D?nde est?
el sanitario ?
[ Teacher ]
GOOD, ONCE AGAIN.
YOU'RE CUTE.
MEET ME
AT BLADES TONIGHT.
BLADES TONIGHT.
YES, WHAT ?
YOU CAN DROP HIM OFF IN FRONT
CAN DAVID AND I
GO TOO, PLEASE ?
YOU SMELL.
HEY, seniorita.
THAT HURT MY LOBES.
I DIDN'T DO IT.  THEY
STARTED THE WHOLE THING.
KASHMIR ?
RAJNEESH, IS IT ?
HOW MANY MINUTES
FOR THE BURRITO ?
[ Rajneesh ]
ONE MINUTE.
AH, MAKE UP
YOUR MELONS !
IS IT ONE OR TWO ?
[ Rajneesh ]
OKAY.
OKAY, MY FRIEND.
TRY AND EXPERIENCE...
WHAT I'M ABOUT TO CHIRP
IN YOUR LOBES, COOL ?
WE'RE GOING
TO DISCUSS GRINDAGE;
HOW TO FILL THE FURNACE,
PACK THE CHEEKS AND
YOU'RE USED TO
EATING TWIGS, RIGHT ?
BUT HERE IN THE U.S. OF A-AGE
WE GOT SOMETHING CALLED...
THE FOUR BASIC FOOD GROUPS,
AND THIS IS NOT ONE OF 'EM.
OH.
LOOK AT WHAT
WE HAVE HERE.
DAIRY GROUP.
MILK DUDS.  HIDE THESE
UNDER YOUR PILLOW SO
IF SHE DOES,
YOU'RE TWEAKED, BUDDY.
KEEP ON CRUISIN'.
FRUIT GROUP.
SWEET TARTS.
THESE ARE KILLER.
SO CITRUSY, DUDE,
KEEP ON CRUISIN'.
UH-HUH.
RIGHT, THIS IS
THE VEGETABLE GROUP.
CORN NUTS !  PUT 'EM
ON A PEDESTAL, BRO.
LOOK AT THAT !
THOSE ARE KILL, HUH ?
MEAT GROUP !
COME ON, THE MEAT GROUP.
THESE ARE MY FAVORITE !
HEY, YOU GOTTA BE EQUAL,
EQUAL, FIFTY/FIFTY.
HERE.  MMM.
MMM.
OOH !  FIGURES.
HOT ON THE OUTSIDE,
ICICLE IN THE MIDDLE.
YOU LIKE THAT, RIGHT,
'CAUSE YOU'RE A CAVEMAN.
COOL, BUDDY.
THE BEVERAGE !
ICEE, BRO.
THIS IS WHAT PUT
THIS PLACE ON THE MAP.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING,
MR. STONEY ?  NO, NO !
- YOU CAN'T DO THIS HERE.
- YOU MUST LEAVE NOW, PLEASE.
-LOOK, KASHMIR, RAJNEESH, CHILL.
-NO BUDS CHILL !
LINK AND I ARE
CRUISIN' THE MOUNTAIN AND
- NO WEASIN' THE JU-UICE.
- WEASE THE JUICE !
NO !  NO WEASIN'
THE JUICE.
NO WEASIN' THE JUICE.
HEY, JUST CHILL,
BUDS.
IT'S OKAY.
JUST CHILL.
I'LL BE BACK.
NO BUDS CHILL !
[ Screaming ]
OH GOD, NO !
WAIT !  STOP !
HERE WE GO !
[ Screaming ]
COMIN' HOME !
WAS THAT THE HOTTEST
OR WHAT, BRO ?
[ Stoney ]
?? JOY TO THE FISHES
?? JOY TO YOU AND ME ??
[ Dave ]
WHERE DID YOU GO ?
YOU JUST TOOK OFF.
DO YOU KNOW
HOW WORRIED I'VE BEEN ?
YOU SOUND LIKE
MY MOM.
WHAT'S ON HIS NOSE ?
JUST CHILL, DAVE,
'CAUSE YOU KNOW WHY ?
LINK AND I HAD A
STONEY TIME AT THE MOUNTAIN.
YOU TOOK HIM TO
MEGA MOUNTAIN ?
YEAH, 'CAUSE THEY'RE
RIDING THE VAPOR IN REVERSE.
THEY ARE ?
OH, COOL.
CHECK OUT THE FRESH NUGS.
WEASIN' THE JUICE.
O-O-O-OW.
BUDDY.
[ Link ]
CHECK OUT MY CAP.
OH MY GOD !
YOU GOT HIM
O-O-O-OW.
GEE, LINK, THAT
IS SO BEAUTIFUL.
YOU KNOW, MR. M.,
THE WAY I LOOK AT IT,
YOUR DAUGHTER AND I
COULD BE MARRIED...
AND WE COULD
BE RELATED.
SO, STANLEY,
HOW'S YOUR MOTHER ?
SHE'S REALLY BUMMED.
CAN YOU PASS THE PEAS ?
SURE.
THANKS.
MR. MORGAN, IF YOU'RE EDGED
'CAUSE I'M WEASIN' ON YOUR
'CAUSE IF I HAD
THE WHOLE BRADY-BUNCH
I'D GO GRIND OVER THERE.
SO DON'T TAX MY GIG SO
HARD CORE, CRUSTER.
- STANLEY, SPEAK ENGLISH.
- DAD !
LINK, HOW WAS YOUR DAY ?
HOW ARE YOU ADJUSTING ?
HE'S DOIN' JUST GREAT.
WE GOT HIM ENROLLED
DIDN'T WE, PAL ?
YEAH.
A SUCCESS.
[ Fly Buzzing ]
WHAT'S UP ?
HOW WAS YOUR DAY, MOM ?
WHERE YOU GOIN' ?
- WHAT'S HE DOIN' ?
- I THINK HE'S TRACKING A FLY.
?? SHOO, FLY
DON'T BOTHER ME ??
?? 'CAUSE YOU BELONG
TO MY FRIEND, LINK ??
GOOD CATCH.
MEAT GROUP !
[ Sniffing ]
HE'S INTO MUNCHIN' TOO,
YOU KNOW.
BLADES... FINALLY
PART OF THE ELITE.
HOW COOL ARE WE ?
WE'RE COOL.
DAVID, I EVEN SHOWERED.
CHECK OUT MY --
I GOT SOME RADICAL
DEODORANT ON, BUDDY.
?? OH NO
YOU'RE INVITED BUT
LINK, HEY !
I AM SO GLAD
TO SEE YOU.
OH, HON, LOSE THE GEEK SQUAD.
THEY'RE BAD FOR YOUR DEAL.
BLADES !
HUMMER PATROL,
BARNEYS INCOMING.
ROBYN.
GET HIM.
GOT HIM.
HEY, ROB--
ROBYN !
GOOD.
THAT WAS NOT COOL
AT ALL, YOU GUYS.
YOU COULD HURT HIS
PANCREAS OR SOMETHING.
I LIKE THE KETCHUP
AND MUSTARD.
WHOA !
IS THAT ME ?
BETTY.
BETTY ?
BETTY, BETTY NUGS.
BETTY NUGS.
ROBYN, DON'T FORGET,
WE'VE BEEN
NAKED TOGETHER.
NICE BODY.
REMEMBER WHEN
DID YOU SHOW THIS
TO ANYONE ?
THAT'S YOUR COPY.
SHOW ANYONE YOU WANT.
OH, I GET IT.
THIS IS LIKE YOUR
DO YOU MISS HER ?
UGH.
BECAUSE I CAN TELL YOU
FROM EXPERIENCE,
LONG-DISTANCE RELATIONSHIPS
NEVER WORK OUT.
ESTONIA'S A
LONG WAYS AWAY, LINK.
AND I'M RIGHT HERE...
SO LET'S WORK ON CHANGING
YOUR MIND.
RAD MOBILE
RAD MOBILE.
WHOA !
OR NOT.
YOU JUST THINK I'M
BAD FOR YOUR ACT,
RIGHT, AND YOU THINK
I'M GOOD FOR YOURS.
WHAT ?
MATT !
WHAT ARE YOU DOIN' ?
YOU'RE NOT ALLOWED IN HERE.
WHOA-OA-OA !
WOO !
WOO-WOO-WOO-WOO !
ARE YOU DEAF, DORK ?
DIDN'T I FORBID YOU
TO SPEAK TO HER ?
THAT'S ALL, LINK.
IT'S OVER.
END OF STORY.
[ Yelling ]
[ Indistinct Arguing ]
I'M SORRY.
[ Link ]
WEASE SOME JUICE !
HEY, YOU WANT
A PIECE OF ME ?
OH GOD !
I DON'T KNOW YOU.
I DON'T LIKE YOU.
AS OF NOW,
I'M ALL OVER YOU.
DID YOU SEE THAT ?
THE NEW KID,
WHOA !
DON'T JUST STAND THERE.
DO SOMETHING.
HIT HIM BACK !
LINK, HIT HIM BACK !
WHERE YOU GOIN' ?
WHAT DO YOU THINK OF YOUR
BULGARIAN DORK BUD, NOW ?
HMM ?
THAT WAS HARSH,
MATT.
LET'S GET
OUT OF HERE.
THE STENCH OF LOSERS IS
DOING DAMAGE TO MY SINUSES.
JUST STOP IT, MATT.
DON'T EVEN COME NEAR ME.
HEY, WATCH IT.
WHY DON'T YOU TAKE THIS,
'CAUSE I DON'T THINK
HEY !
I CAN'T BELIEVE
HE GOT NAILED.
A PACIFIST CAVEMAN !
YOU'RE MENTAL.
CAVEMENS AREN'T LIKE US,
DAVE.
THEY FOUGHT FOR FOOD AND
SURVIVAL.  THEY DID NOT
WHAT WOULD HE BE
FIGHTING FOR, HUH ?
FOR US !
TO BE COOL !
HE DOES NOT KNOW
WHAT COOL IS.
HE DOESN'T KNOW WHERE HE IS.
HE KNOWS NOTHIN'.
HE'S GOTTA LEARN
HOW TO DEFEND HIMSELF.
AGAINST WHAT ?
AGAINST BUTT HOLES
COME ON.
?? I'M GONNA KNOCK YOU OUT
MAMA SAID KNOCK YOU OUT ??
[ TV Announcer ]
OUR AIRPLANE'S BEEN
[ Dave ]
STOP !
HEY, STOP !
?? KNOCK YOU OUT ??
[ Grunting ]
?? I'M GONNA KNOCK YOU OUT
MAMA SAID KNOCK YOU OUT ??
MAMA SAID KNOCK YOU OUT ????
[ Bell Ringing ]
HEY, LOOK !
HEY, DUDE.
YOU TOOK IT FROM WILSON.
NO ONE'S EVER DONE THAT
BEFORE AND SURVIVED.
LINK,
COME BACK HERE.
OH GOD.
HE IS SO COOL.
?? MATTY TOLD HATTY ??
?? 'BOUT A THING SHE SAW ??
?? IT HAD TWO BIG HORNS
AND A WOOLY JAW ??
?? WOOLY BULLY ??
?? WOOLY BULLY
WOOLY BULLY ??
?? WOOLY BULLY ??
HEY.
HOMESLICE.
SEE YOU IN
MR. ALBERT'S CLASS.
SLICEY.
HELLO, LITTLE ONE.
WE TOOK A VOTE AND
THE COMPUTER CLUB
WILL BE A VALUABLE ASSET
TO OUR ORGANIZATION.
COMPUTER CLUB.
HOMEBOY.
WHY DOESN'T THAT HAPPEN
WHEN MATT HITS ME ?
GIVE YOURSELF A
FEW MILLION YEARS, DAVID.
[ Indistinct Chatter ]
LINK.  LINK.
LINK, GET DOWN.
ALL RIGHT,
COME ON.
NO, NO.
I WAS JUST PLAYIN'.
[ Teacher ]
ALL RIGHT,
WHAT YOU'RE LOOKING AT HERE
IS A REPRESENTATION...
OF WHAT CRO-MAGNON MAN'S
EVERYDAY LIFE
IF HE WAS HERE TODAY, YOU COULD
SIT NEXT TO HIM, YOU WOULD
STONEY, LET'S MOVE ON.
WE'RE GONNA LOOK AT
[ Growling ]
CLASS, THIS IS
SABER-TOOTHED CAT.
EVEN THOUGH HE'S
BEEN EXTINCT FOR
WHILE HE WAS ALIVE
YOU CAN IMAGINE THAT
WAS A TASTY MEAL
TO ONE OF THESE.
[ Link Screaming ]
THERE'S ONE NOW.
UH-OH.
LET'S LOOK AT
THE MAMMOTH DISPLAY,
LOOK OUT !
WHOA.
LINK !  LINK,
GET OUT FROM THERE !
LOOK AT HIM.
HE'S FLIPPING OUT.
HE KNOWS, DAVE.
WHAT ?
HE KNOWS.
HE KNOWS WHAT
HAPPENED TO HIM.
WE HAVE
TO HELP HIM.
LINK.
LINK.  LINK.
OW !
LINK.
HEY.  HEY,
COME ON, MAN.
LOOK, I UNDERSTAND.
FAMILY.
YOU OKAY ?
IT'S OKAY.
WE'RE YOUR NEW FAMILY.
WE'RE YOUR
NEW FAMILY.
IT'S OKAY.
IT'S ALL RIGHT.
[ Stoney ]
HE'S BURNT
SEEING AS WE STARTED
THE SCHOOL YEAR
AND NOW EVERYONE
KNOWS WHO WE ARE,
I DON'T THINK ONE MISTAKE
IS SUCH A BIG DEAL.
BUT YOU'RE DOGGIN' HIM.
JUST PROMISE ME,
JUST A LITTLE MORE MELLOW,
NOT SO MUCH ?
STONEY !
DAVE !
ALL RIGHT.
IF IT'LL MAKE YOU
FEEL BETTER, I'LL BE
ROBYN SWEENEY ?
HERE.
AGAIN ?
I'M SORRY.  I CAN'T GET
WHOA.  PARALLEL PARKING
IS NOT A THING, UNDERSTAND ?
IT'S NOT A FEELING,
NOT A STATE OF MIND,
YEAH.
GET IN THE CAR AND
OKAY, MR. BEADY.
- LINKAVITCH CHOMOFSKY ?
- UGH, UGH.
WHAT ARE YOU
LOOKIN' AT ?
UGH.
GET INSIDE THE CAR...
AND SHOOT
YOUR BARBER.
CONTRAST THIS
WITH HEMINGWAY'S
WHERE THE BLOOD SPORT
OF BULLFIGHTING...
IS USED AND
PERHAPS WHAT --
OH GOD.
RAD MOBILE !
BOYS, WILL YOU SIT DOWN ?
CLASS ?
YOU PROMISED ME MELLOW.
THIS ISN'T MELLOW.
LINK !  LINK !
DAVE.
[ Dave ]
WATCH THE PEOPLE !
OKAY !
[ Dave ]  STONE,
TELL HIM TO STOP !
[ Stoney ]
DIDN'T PHASE HIM, BRO.
ALL RIGHT, LINK.
JOKE'S OVER.  STOP !
- HE-E-E-EY !
- STOP THAT CAR, YOUNG MAN !
I'M YOUR TEACHER.
BOTH HANDS ON THE WHEEL !
[ Applause, Cheering ]
WHO WAS THAT ?
CROSSWALK !
CLOSE CALL, BUDDY.
[ Stoney ]
HEY, BUDDY !
HI, ROBYN.
HI, DAVE.
RED LIGHT !
[ Screeching, Honking ]
BOOM !
UP ON TWO WHEELS !
I'VE NEVER SEEN
ANYTHING LIKE THIS.
I GOT THE LICENSE PLATE.
IT'S E684-257.
YOU DON'T HAVE TO WRITE
THAT I LEFT THE KEYS
OW-O-O-O-O !
[ Dave ]
I THINK HE'S GOT
THAT CONCLUDES OUR
PARALLEL PARKING FOR TODAY.
[ Robyn ]
LINK, I THINK YOU
[ Stoney ]
HEY, LINK,
[ Dave ]
WHERE ARE WE ?
GREAT !
?? MOVE YOUR BODY ??
?? MOVE YOUR BODY
TO THE RHYTHM OF LOVE ??
?? MOVE YOUR BODY ??
?? MOVE YOUR BODY
TO THE RHYTHM OF LOVE ??
Hola, mi amigos.
IS IT OKAY IF I JUST
CHILL UPON HERE ?
YOU WANNA BE A MAN,
ese ?
EVENTUALLY, YEAH.
BUT I'M ALMOST THERE.
LOOK AT MY PATCH, BRO.
OHH !
Mucho macho.
OOH.
OH, THIS IS TEQUILA ?
WAIT,
WHERE'S THE WORM ?
THE WORM'S RIGHT THERE,
ese.
UT-UH.
I'M A WEASEL.
A WEASEL, EH ?
YOU WANNA BE
- YOU WANNA BE A MAN ?
- THEN DRINK LIKE AN hombre.
NO, I CAN'T.
YOU'RE SHOWING US
AH, YOU GUYS --
THAT'S DISRESPECTFUL,
WEASEL.
BE A MAN, ese.
DRINK IT UP.
DRINK LIKE A MAN.
YOU CAN DO IT,
WEASEL.
YOU CAN DO IT.
Andale.
[ Howling ]
WAIT.
i Otra, otra !
Otra vez, otra vez,
otra vez.
OKAY, OKAY,
STOP !
FIVE MORE, MAN.
[ Chanting ]
WEASEL, WEASEL.
[ Howling ]
[ Chanting ]
WEASEL, WEASEL.
WAIT, STOP.
DUDE, DO I HAVE
????
HEY, STONE.
HEY.
WHERE'S LINK ?
DANCIN'.
????
COOL,
LET'S GO DANCE.
I'M NOT GOOD.
LET'S NOT DANCE.
I, I JUST DON'T
LIKE TO DANCE.
HEY, WEASEL.
WHAT'S HAPPENING ?
DAVE, ENRIQUE.
HEY, MAN,
YOU SEE THAT
muchacha OVER THERE ?
OH MAN, YEAH.
YOU SEE HER ?
DON'T BE LOOKIN'
AT HER, MAN !
YOU SEE HER ?
NO.
IF I SEE ANY MAN
LOOKING AT MY muchacha,
BE RECOGNIZABLE
AS A MAN.
I WANT YOU vatos
TO HAVE A GOOD TIME.
SEE YOU LATER,
WEASELS.
?? FEEL THE RHYTHM
FEEL THE RHYTHM EVERYWHERE ??
FEEL THE, FEEL THE
?? MOVE YOUR BODY ??
?? MOVE YOUR BODY
TO THE RHYTHM OF LOVE ??
CHOMOFSKY.
GOT IT.
RABIES, DISTEMPER,
FLEA DIP.
WHAT IS THIS ?
IT'S A DOG LICENSE,
MAN.
ANIMAL SHELTER.
WHAT ARE THE
TWO BIGGEST LOSERS
A DOG ?
IT'S NOT
MM-HMM.
LET'S GET
OUT OF HERE.
?? DANCE ??
?? YOU KNOW
YOU REALLY TURN ME ON ??
?? COME ON NOW,
HONEY ??
?? YOU KNOW
YOU REALLY TURN ME ON ??
?? GET FILLED
GET FILLED ??
?? AND WHEN
WHEN, OH WHEN YOU DO IT ??
?? UH-UH-UH-OH
THAT'S THE SONG ??
????
[ Screams ]
WOW !  WOW !
?? UH-UH-UH-OH
THAT'S MY SONG ??
?? LET'S DO IT
LET'S DO IT
?? COME ON AND
JUST STICK IT TO ME ??
?? YOU TURN ME ON
COME ON NOW, SUGAR ??
YOU'RE RIGHT, ese.
SHE'S NOT WORTH IT.
- THE vato's GOT THE POINT.
- SHE AIN'T WORTH IT, HOMES !
COME HERE, vato.
POLICE.
Immigraci?n.
[ Dave ]
LET'S GET
OH SHIT !
STONE, TAKE ROBYN.
[ Burp ]
ROBYN, TAKE STONE.
GET HIM OUT OF HERE.
I'LL MEET UP
WITH YOU GUYS LATER.
[ Robyn ]
COME ON, I'LL DRIVE.
[ Making Monkey Sounds ]
LINK !
THE COPS ARE HERE.
GET DOWN.
COME ON.
WE'RE GONNA GET BUSTED !
YOU ARE BUSTED.
GET DOWN, MAN.
[ All Together ]
STONEY IS THE CRUSTIEST vato...
I'VE EVER WITNESSED.
SO DON'T HUSH HIS GIG,
BUDDY.
OW-O-O-O !
[ Indistinct Chatter ]
[ Stoney ]
EH, BUDDY !
BYE, GUYS.
DRIVE SAFELY.
NICE ELEMENT
YOU'RE HANGING OUT WITH.
WHO ARE YOUR FRIENDS
IN THE LOW-RIDER ?
GO HOME.
HUH.
WHAT TIME DO YOU WANT ME
TO PICK YOU UP TOMORROW NIGHT ?
IT'S THE PROM,
REMEMBER ?
YOU ARE JUST LIKE
EVERYONE ELSE.
ALL YOU CARE ABOUT
IS WHAT PEOPLE THINK.
IT'S REALLY PATHETIC.
HEY, WATCH IT.
MATT, I'M NOT GOING
TO THE PROM WITH YOU.
I WANNA GO WITH SOMEBODY
WHO'S REALLY COOL,
WHO'S NOT AFRAID OF
BEING HIMSELF OR HAVING FUN.
GOOD NIGHT.
WHO'S COOLER THAN ME ?
YOUR PHONE CALL.
YOU GOT ONE.
THANKS.
[ Phone Ringing ]
MATTHEW WILSON !
HELLO.
ROBYN ?
ROBYN.
DAVE, DID YOU GUYS
GET AWAY OKAY ?
WE'RE IN PRISON.
LOOK, THIS IS
MY ONE PHONE CALL.
I'M USING IT TO ASK YOU
TO GO TO THE PROM WITH ME.
JUST SAY YES,
OKAY ?
[ Sighs ]
NO.
WHY NOT ?
I WANNA GO
WHAT ?
WILL YOU ASK LINK
YOU WANT ME TO WHAT ?
LOOK, I'M SORRY.
I'LL TELL YOU WHAT.
WE'LL ALL GO.
WE'LL HAVE A GREAT TIME.
HOW ABOUT THAT ?
DAVE ?
[ Stoney Yelling ]
HEY !
¿¿ C?mo est? usted ?
Muy bonita...
es la d?a.
HEY, WAIT.
HOW WAS JAIL ?
DID YOU MEET ANYONE ?
HEY, WAIT !
WAIT UP.
THINGS JUST DIDN'T
TURN OUT RIGHT.
I MEAN, I DON'T
WANT 'EM CUTTIN' YOU UP
THIS IS JUST WHAT'S
BEST FOR YOU.
IT'S BEST FOR ME TOO,
ALL RIGHT ?
HERE.
FOR RAD MOBILE.
YEAH.
PUT 'EM
IN YOUR POCKET.
DON'T LOOK AT ME
LIKE THAT.
THIS IS JUST THE WAY
IT'S GOTTA BE.
GO ON,
GET OUT OF HERE.
GO ON.
GO ON, LEAVE.
GO.
I'M SORRY.
[ Stoney ]
HEY, HEY, HEY !
TALK TO ME, DAVID.
LET ME KNOW WHAT'S
WHAT ARE YOU DOIN' ?
I'M LETTING HIM GO.
WHAT ?
I CAN'T HANDLE HIM
HE'LL BE BETTER OFF
WITH SOMEBODY ELSE.
LISTEN TO ME.
CALL HIM BACK.
I CAN'T TAKE IT ANYMORE.
I'M NOT KIDDIN'.
IT'S TIME.
I'M SERIOUS.
CALL HIM BACK.
THAT'S HARSH.
HE'S NOT
MY RESPONSIBILITY.
YOU'RE THE ONE WHO WEASED
OFF HIS GIG THE WHOLE TIME...
'CAUSE YOU THOUGHT MAYBE
HE'D GET YOU SOMEWHERE.
NOW THE GUY GETS A LITTLE CRUSTY
AND YOU'RE GONNA BAG HIM.
IT'S NOT HAPPENIN', DAVE.
THAT'S NOT HOW IT WORKS
YOU DON'T BAG YOUR FRIENDS
'CAUSE THEY GET IN THE WAY,
LIKE YOU CARE ?  THE ONLY THING
YOU'VE CARED ABOUT IS NUGS,
I HAPPEN TO CARE
RIGHT NOW.
YOU CAME ALONG FOR
THE RIDE AND LET ME
'CAUSE YOU THOUGHT IT MIGHT
WORK TO YOUR ADVANTAGE.
THOSE ARE DESPERATE WORDS
OF A LOSER.
MAYBE MATT WILSON WAS RIGHT
ABOUT YOU ALL ALONG.
NO, YOU TAKE IT BACK.
TAKE IT BACK !
YOU'RE A LOSER.
- [ Link ]  FAMILY !
- ALL RIGHT.
I'M SORRY.
FAMILY.
YOU CAN LET GO,
LINK.
I'M SORRY, MAN.
IT'S OKAY.
I DON'T KNOW
WHAT GOT INTO ME.
I'M SORRY.
I DIDN'T MEAN IT,
STONEY.
I'M SORRY, BUD.
OW !
YOU LOOK GREAT.
HAVE A GOOD TIME.
YOU DESERVE IT.
[ Doorbell ]
[ Sniffing ]
IF YOU TOUCH HER ?
UGH.
YOU THINK
THEY'RE READY ?
DAVE ?
DAVE, HEY.
HEY.
YOU'RE NOT READY.
I, I CAN'T GO.
OF COURSE YOU CAN.
JUST GO UPSTAIRS,
NO, REALLY, I CAN'T.
I'M ON PROBATION.
I'M GROUNDED.
HI, LINK.
YOU LOOK GREAT.
YOU GUYS GO.
HAVE A GOOD TIME.
NO, NO, NO.
COME ON.
GO.
ARE YOU SURE ?
GO, HAVE A GOOD TIME.
GO, LINK.
GET OUTTA HERE.
HAVE A GOOD TIME.
DRIVE SAFELY.
GOD, SHE SMELLS GOOD.
[ Dave ]
TO LINK.
MAY HE HAVE A COOL TIME
AT THE PROM.
TOTALLY, BRO,
TO LINKAGE.
[ Sighs ]
THERE'S ALWAYS COLLEGE.
JUNIOR COLLEGE.
[ Matt ]
LINK, GET DOWN HERE.
GIVE ME A BOOST.
[ Grunting ]
WHOA.
[ Laughing ]
GOTCHA.
[ Crashing Sounds ]
[ Sister ]
DAVE !
HEY, WHAT ARE
YOU DOING ?
GIVE ME BACK
THOSE PICTURES.
NO !
HEY, GET BACK HERE !
THEY TOOK THE POLAROIDS.
COME ON.
THOSE ARE
[ Rumbling ]
[ Dog Barking ]
[ Applause, Cheering ]
IT'S UNANIMOUS.
THE VOTE FOR PROM KING...
GOES TO...
WAIT !
WHAT'S GOING ON ?
UGH.
WHAT ARE YOU
TRYING TO DO ?
THIS IS OUR SCHOOL,
RIGHT ?
YEAH.
WE HAVE A RIGHT TO KNOW IF
SOMETHIN' BOGUS IS GOIN' DOWN...
IN OUR SCHOOL,
RIGHT ?
YEAH.
RIGHT.
THIS HOMEY RIGHT HERE
HAS TAKEN YOU FOR A RIDE.
HIS NAME ISN'T
LINKAVITCH CHOMOFSKY,
MATT, WILL YOU JUST
STOP THIS ALREADY ?
SHUSH !
TRUST ME.
THEY'VE ALL
BEEN LYING TO US.
BUT I FOUND OUT.
I KNOW THE TRUTH.
DO YOU WANNA KNOW
THE TRUTH ?
DO YOU WANT TO KNOW
WHAT HE REALLY IS ?
YEAH.
[ Girl ]
TELL US THE SECRET !
HE'S A CAVEMAN.
[ Cheering ]
NO.  NO !
LOOK, HE'S A FREAK !
[ Applause, Cheering ]
- I GOT PICTURES !
- NO !
SEE ?
LET ME SEE
GIVE ME BACK THOSE PICTURES.
GIVE ME THOSE !
- [ Matt ] NO !
- [ Robyn ] DAVE !
HMMMM.
WHAT ARE YOU DOIN',
FAG ?
[ Cheering ]
[ Stoney ]
GO, GO, GO !
WATCH, WATCH, WATCH.
[ Link Yelling ]
UH-HUH.
SHUSH !
???? [ "Feed The Monkey"
by Michael Muir ]
????
?? OW ??
?? SHE LIKES TO FEED THE MONKEY
SHE LIKES TO FEED THE MONKEY ??
SHE LIKES TO FUNKY ??
?? SO GATHER 'ROUND AND
LET ME TELL YA ALL A STORY ??
?? ABOUT A BOY
AND HIS MONKEY ??
?? HE'S GOT THAT KIND OF MONKEY
THAT THE GIRLS WANNA KNOW ??
?? HE LIKES TO TAKE HIS MONKEY
EVERY PLACE THAT HE GOES ??
????
OW-O-O-O !
?? HEY, HO
JUST SAY THE MONKEY ??
WATCH THIS.
OKAY.
?? I DIDN'T REALLY KNOW
HOW YOU GET SO HUNGRY ??
?? I'D LIKE TO KNOW
WOULD YOU BE MY MONKEY ??
?? MONKEY LIKES TO DO
THE WILD THING ??
?? MY MONKEY DON'T SCRATCH
MY MONKEY DON'T BITE ??
?? MY MONKEY
DON'T SWING IN NO TREE ??
?? MY MONKEY DON'T TRICK
MY MONKEY DON'T FOOL ??
?? MY MONKEY
BE SWINGIN' WITH ME ??
?? MY MONKEY DON'T FREAK
MY MONKEY DON'T HIT ??
?? MY MONKEY DON'T
WEAR NO CAPE ??
?? YOU CAN TELL WHEN MY MONKEY
WANTS TO EAT ??
?? 'CAUSE HE TURNS INTO
A BIG OL' APE ??
????
[ Making Monkey Sounds ]
[ Horns Honking ]
????
WHAT YOU DID
WAS PRETTY COOL.
WHO CARES ABOUT COOL
ANYWAY, RIGHT ?
THERE'S ONE REALLY COOL
THING I WANTED TO SHOW YOU.
WHAT ?
THIS.
[ Cheering, Laughing ]
OH, DAVE !
HEY, BUDDY.
[ Alarm Ringing ]
[ Yelling ]
[ Stoney ]
IT'S YOUR CAVE NUG.
UGH.
[ Screaming ]
- AH-HA-HA-HA-HA !
- OW-O-O-O-O !
[ Link, Stoney ]
YEAH !
OH YEAH !
YEAH, BUDDY.
SHE IS SO GREASY !
DUH-H-H-Y !
AH !  HEY.
BUDDY,
OW-O-O-O !
YEAH !
I'LL BE BA-ACK !
?? WOW ??
????
?? OH YEAH, STONERS ??
?? WHAT'S UP, BRO
OW-O-O-O ??
?? BUDDY, FIESTA ??
????
?? DO YOU NEED A WOMAN
GOT THE LOOK IN HER EYES ??
?? WANNA CUT ME DOWN TO SIZE
SHOW ME WHAT YOU'RE GONNA DO ?
?? IT'S TRUE ??
?? WHO'S THAT GORILLA
STANDING BY YOUR SIDE ??
?? OH NO
THAT MUST BE YOUR BRIDE ??
?? YOU WOULDN'T BE
WITH SUCH A FOOL ??
?? OR YOUR MAMA TOO ??
?? THERE'S SOMETHIN' OVER HERE
I WANT YOU TO SEE ??
?? THERE'S A PARTY
BUT IT ISN'T FOR THREE ??
?? GET ALL THIS STRAIGHT
BETWEEN YOU AND ME BECAUSE ??
?? OH NO
YOU'RE INVITED BUT
?? WHOA NO NO
COME ON, BABY
?? WOW ??
????
?? HEARTBREAKER, YEAH
YOU CAME FOR THE SHOW ??
?? BUT LITTLE DID YOU KNOW
YOU'D END UP IN THE SPOTLIGHT ?
?? WELL ALL RIGHT ??
?? COME ON, BABE, WON'T YOU
SHOW ME WHAT YOU GOT ??
?? READY OR NOT
I WANT TO ??
?? HERE WE GO ??
?? OH NO ??
?? I'M MAKIN' PLANS
FOR THE REST OF THE NIGHT ??
?? SO TELL YOUR FATHER
THAT HE BETTER NOT BITE ??
?? MY JAWS ARE BIGGER
AND I'M READY TO FIGHT ??
?? SO COME ON, COME ON, COME ON
GIVE IT UP TONIGHT ??
?? WHOA NO
YOU'RE INVITED BUT
?? WHOA, NO NO
COME ON, BABY
?? WHOA NO
YOU'RE INVITED BUT
?? WHOA, NO NO
COME ON, BABY
?? WE'RE GONNA HAVE SOME FUN ??
?? WOW, HAVE SOME FUN, BABY ??
?? OH BUT YOU CAN'T COME ??
HA-HA-HA-HA.
?? WOW ????