The Battlestar Galactica,
veteran of the first Cylon war
fought almost a half century ago.
She was nearing the end
of her career in the colonial fleet
with no enemy to fight
and her useful days long since past.
She was scheduled to be decommissioned
and turned into a museum ship.
No one had seen or
heard from the Cylons in 40 years
and Galactica seemed
like a relic from an other era.
On behalf to Galactica,
I'd like to welcome you onboard, Apollo.
It's an honour to have you with us.
Morning, sir.
We must not forget the reasons why...
Commander Adama, if I may...
Captain...
I just wanted to say what a pleasure it's
been serving with you in your command, sir.
Captain Kelly, this is my honour.
As the secretary of education,
I was invited aboard for the ceremony.
It seemed like a routine
even a boring asignment at first
but it was
the most faithful day of my life.
Here we go.
- If you gonna play with the big dogs...
- No fear.
- I'm in.
- That's you, XO.
- Right.
30 to me.
and it looks like I'm gonna bring
this lovely little game to a close cause...
Full colours !
You have finally gone too far
and now you're done
Lieutenant, report to the brig !
Are you really gonna
press charges against Kara ?
- I couldn't talk you out of it, OK ?
- Not a chance.
She's insubordinate, undisciplined.
Probably one of the finest
fighter pilots I've ever seen in my life.
Better than I am, twice as good as you.
Like hell...
It seems familiar.
Captain Adama, sir.
Sorry I wasn't there to greet you
with the rest of the squadron.
Did they kiss you ass to your satisfaction ?
- So, how long has it been ?
- 2 years.
We must be getting old. Seems like
the funeral was just a couple months ago.
Your old man is doing fine.
We don't talk about it much,
maybe 2 or 3 times a year.
- He still struggles with it, though.
- I haven't seen him.
- Kara, don't even start.
- How long are you gonna do this ?
- I'm not doing anything.
- He lost his son, Lee.
- Zack was my brother.
- What was he to me, nothing ?
Today, we're talking
with Doctor Gaius Baltar.
He is currently working as a top consultant
for the ministry of defense
on computer issues.
but he's perhaps
best known for his controversial views
on advancing computer technology.
- Dr. Baltar, welcome.
- Thank you, Kella.
My position is very simple.
The ban on the search and
development into artificial intelligence is,
as we all know,
a old habit from the cylon wars.
Quite frankly, I find this
to be an outmoded concept.
- Do you love me, Gaius ?
- What ?
Do you love me ?
Are you serious ?
You had me worried there.
And now it is my great pleasure to introduce
the last commander
of the Battlestar Galactica.
Commander Adama.
Thank you very much.
You can not play God and
wash your hands of the things you created.
Sooner or later,
day comes when you can't hide
from the things that you've done anymore.
Who were the Cylons ?
They were machines
created by men
to make life easier on the 12 Colonies.
But there came a day
when they rose up against us
and the bloody conflict known
as the Cylon war was the result.
At his conlusion a truce was signed and
the Cylons left for a world of their own.
A remote space station was built
where Humen and Cylons
could meet and maintain diplomatic relation.
Every year for 40 years
we sent an officer to the station.
The Cylons sent no one.
Until one day
a Cylon representative appeared.
But not the robotic centurions
we were familiar with.
The Cylons had evolved.
It has begun.
So now you're telling me you're a machine.
I've said it three times now.
Forgive me, I'm having
a little bit of trouble believing that
because the last time anybody saw the cylons
they looked more like walking chrome toasters
Those models are still around.
They have their uses.
You were chosen for my mission.
Your mission ?
You knew I wanted
access to the defense mainframe.
Wait a minute...
The defense mainframe ?
- What exactly are you saying ?
- Come on, Gaius.
The communications frequencies,
deployment schedules,
unlimited access to every database.
Oh, my God.
In a few hours, no one will be left.
Humanity's children are returning home.
Today.
Wait, there has to be
another way out of here. I mean,
- you must have an escape plan.
- Gaius...
I can't die.
When this body is destroyed, my memory,
my consciousness,
will be transmitted to a new one.
I'll just wake up somewhere else
in an identical body.
You mean there's more out there like you ?
There are 12 models, I'm number 6.
- I don't want to die.
- Get down !
Moments ago, this ship received word
of a cylon attack
against our home worlds is underway.
You're trained for this,
you're ready for this.
As of this moment,
we are at war.
- =( Team Lords of Kobol )=-
Synchro
NikoMagnus
The Cylon attack caught us by surprise.
All 12 colonies were annihilated.
The human race was nealy wiped out.
Only a few thousands survivors managed to escape.
Enemy suppression fire,
all batteries execute.
And still the cylons
were endlessly pursuing us.
Starbuck, clear for launch.
Oh, frack me !
- Hold it together, guys.
- Come on...
Apollo, do you read me ?
Come on, bitch !
Looks like you broke your ship, Apollo !
I'm loosing power !
- I'm not gonna make it, Starbuck !
- Shut up and hold still !
Oh, no...
You are beyond insane !
They're coming in !
Battlestar Atlantia has been destroyed,
so is the Triton,
Soleria,
Columbia,
- and the list goes on.
- Who's the senior officer ?
Who's in command ?
Send a message
to all the colonial military units.
Use priority channel 1.
Message begins.
I'm taking command of fleet.
This is an official colonial broadcast.
All ministers and official
should now go to case orange.
It's an automatic message.
It's designed to be
sent out in case the President,
the Vice President and most of
the cabinet are dead or incapacitated.
As Secretary of Education,
I was 43rd in line to the presidency.
I had never thought the office
and suddenly it was thrusted upon me.
I, Laura Roslin
do now avow and affirm
that I take the office of
the President of the 12 Colonies of Kobol.
that I accept the office of the President
of the 12 Colonies of Kobol.
On Caprica, a group of people
had survived the nuclear holocaust.
but they would soon
succomb to radiation poisoning.
One Raptor from Galactica
had enough space to rescue a lucky few.
Aren't you Gaius Baltar ?
What are you doing ?
Giving up my seat.
Like hell.
A civilian should take my place.
Whatever future is left
is gonna to depend on whoever survives.
Give me one reason why I'm a better choice
than one of the greatest minds of our time.
- Helo...
- You can do this without me.
I know you can, you've proven it.
Get on board.
Stay back ! It's over !
I've got something for you.
It belonged to your grandfather.
He's a better father than I was.
Dad used to carry that
into court cases, he claimed he never lost
unless he lef it behind.
So you're worried too.
Sometimes you feel like the whole ship
thinks Starbuck would do better.
I don't.
How can you be so sure ?
Cause you're my son.
I see they've put you to work.
Ignoring me won't help.
No, I've decided you're
an expression of my subconscious mind
playing itself out during my waking states.
So I'm only in your head ?
Exactly.
We had something, Gaius.
Something...
... special.
- This is insane.
- And what I want most of all
is for you to love me.
Don't you understand ? God is love.
No !
Galactica and a small fleet
of civilian ships had escaped the Cylons
but our losses
were heavy and our future uncertain.
Are they the lucky ones ?
That's what you're thinking, isn't it ?
Maybe it would have been
better for us to have died quickly,
back on the colonies with our families
instead of dying out here
slowly in the emptiness of dark space.
We have a refuge to go to !
A refuge that the Cylons know nothing about !
On the memory of
those lying here before you,
we shall find it.
And Earth
will becomme our new home.
- So say we all !
- So say we all.
There is no Earth.
You made it all up.
You're right.
There is no Earth.
It's all a legend.
Then why ?
Because it's not enough to just live.
You have to have something to live for.
Let it be Earth.
We're gonna take the civilians with us.
We're gonna leave this solar system.
We're not gonna come back.
- We're running.
- This war is over.
We lost.
My father's right,
it's time for us to get out of here.
The human race was
reduced to less than 50 000 people
cramed into a ragtag fleet of ships and
protected only by the Battlestar Galactica.
We began the search for Earth
hoping to make it our new home.
We can't let them go.
Unfortunately, I agree.
If we do, they'll
return one day and take revenge.
- It's in their nature.
- We have no choice.
It may take
several decades to track them down.
Don't worry, we'll find them.
We jumped deep into uncharted space,
hoping to put some distance
between ourselves and the Cylons
but they followed us at every turn.
Eventually, we made the chocking discovery
that our enemies were not only chasing us,
they were also living among us.
Good afternoon and thank you for coming.
I feel it is time to reveal certain
information that hasn't until now.
We made it tightly garded secret.
The cylons have the hability to
mimic human form, they look like us, now.
This man has been
identified as a Cylon agent.
This man has also
been identified as a Cylon
and we now know that there
are duplicates of each cylon model.
anyone seeing either of this two men
at any time, anywhere, in the fleet
should immediatly contact the Battlestar
Galactica and the office of the President.
We haven't addressed
the real problem, of course.
Yes, there may be
cylon agents living among us
waiting to strike at any moment.
Some may not even know they're Cylons at all.
They could be sleeper agents programmed
to perfectly impersonate
human beings until activation.
If there's Cylons
aboard this ship, we'll find them.
We ?
You're not on their side, Gaius.
I am not on anybody's side.
One of our pilots, Helo, have been
trapped on Caprica and left for dead.
He was captured by Cylons Centurions.
Became rescued by a woman he thought
was his copilot and friend, Sharon Valerii.
- Sharon ?
- But this was not the woman he knew.
- In fact, she wasn't even human.
- Can you walk ?
Yeah, I think so.
She was a Cylon.
- What are you doing here, I thought...
- Let's move, mister.
A duplicate copy of Sharon, one of many.
And she was actually
on an important mission.
Fear swept through the fleet as we began
to search for sleeper agents in our beds.
And I began to experience
strange and disturbing visions.
So, what have you seen ?
There were snakes crawling all over
my podium during the press conference.
- How many ?
- About a dozen.
Pythie wrote about the exile
and the rebirth of the Human race.
And the Lords anointed a leader
to guide the caravan
of the Heavens to their new homeland.
And onto the leader, they gave a vision
of serpents numbering 2 and 10
as a sign of things to come.
So, according to the Scriptures,
if we have the arrow of Apollo
We could take it down
to Kobol and we could use it
to open the tomb of Athena
and find a way to Earth.
There is no Earth, you understand that.
It would seem that we were wrong.
- This is crazy.
- It is crazy.
Perhaps.
But that doesn't mean it isn't true.
If you go back
to Caprica and bring me the arrow,
I will show us the way.
- You sleep, I watch.
- No, you're the one who needs to sleep.
I couldn't sleep if I had
to listen Tyrol read the flight manual.
OK.
Truth is...
if something happened to you,
I wouldn't know how to deal with it.
The Cylons though indistiguishable
from the humans had one flaw.
They could not have children.
They believed that
perhaps love was the missing element
so they used
Helo as pawn for an experiment,
hoping to use his love
for Sharon to create a hybrid child.
- We had sex.
- Congratulations.
- Does he love you ?
- I think so.
Stay in your current location.
It shouldn't be too hard to convince
him to stay and start a life together.
If not, kill him.
Can you handle that ?
But their plan worked too well.
The Cylon Sharon fell in love with Helo and
she found herself unable to let go of him.
And even after Helo
discovered the truth about Sharon,
He couldn't let go of her either.
I just want you to know that
I genuinely feel something for you.
Helo, there's something else you should know.
I am pregnant.
The Sharon on Galactica was tortured by
the idea that she might be a sleeper agent.
Others began to suspect her as well.
This is not true.
No, it's not.
If you're working on a Cylon detector,
do you think I could be in the first batch ?
You know, to be tested.
You just put this
in the slot and wait for the results.
Green, you're normal human being.
Red, you're an evil Cylon.
It should take a couple of minutes.
Congratulations, Doctor,
you just uncovered your very first Cylon.
She probably doesn't know.
It should be interesting how
she responds when you tell her the truth.
I'm guessing her Cylon side
will take over and break your neck
before you can give away her secret.
Congratulations, it's green !
- You're not a Cylon !
- Really ?
A 100% human and very bright green, as well.
At my request, Starbuck
returned to the ruined city on Caprica
to retrieve the Arrow of Apollo.
Pretty, isn't it ?
Hello, Lieutenant.
Something I can help you with ?
Starbuck ?
I missed you.
You can't, she's pregnant.
The Sharon on Galactica was
a respected and beloved member of the crew.
Congratulations to both of you.
- Thank you.
- Thank you, sir.
Thank you, sir.
Until her cylon programing
was finally activated.
- Make a hole !
- Where are the medics and Doc Cottle ?
Off the ship, now, stand clear !
What's going on ?
What happened ?
Sergent of the guard,
secure that thing in the brig.
Let's go, let's go !
Let's get him down to sickbay RFN.
Her consciousness is being
downloaded into an other body right now
and when she wakes up,
she'll tell them exactly where we are.
She's right, we can't stay here.
Sharon the Cylon is right.
- She helped me get this far.
- OK, I get it !
I remember how you felt about her
but that is not the real Sharon.
That is some cheap knock off copy.
I'm not a copy, I'm Sharon.
I remember
the first day I met you, Starbuck,
you were pucking your guts
out in the head because...
Don't do that !
Carl do not think that I will not shoot...
I'm gonna let you kill her, OK ?
She's carrying my child.
They're not human, Helo. They're machines.
You can't have a baby with a machine.
I don't know what to tell you, OK ?
But I believe her.
She is not like the others.
She is not !
With Commander Adama clinging to life,
his crew on Galactica
lashed out on the traitor Cylon.
For Sharon, the process
of downloading and rebirth began instantly.
... right through it.
You're going to be OK, trust me.
We're proud of you, Sharon.
But this Sharon
still thought of herself as human
and when she walked to face her true nature...
And we love you.
... it felt more like a nightmare.
The Number 6 that died in the initial attack
on Caprica was also downloaded and reborn.
I still try to getting used to this body.
I mean I know it's identical but...
Even after all this time,
I still feel awkward.
I was a klutz too. I say knock things over.
This is a great chance to cleanse.
You got a new body, a new life.
And anything that you've built up
like anxieties or remorse or guilt,
- just let it wash away.
- I can't tell you how thankful I am.
- You've been a really big help to me.
- No, it's me who's thankful.
We all are. You are a war hero.
We could not have won without you.
All right, let's get
these weapons unload, let's go !
While on Caprica, Starbuck encountered
a group of resistance led by Samuel Anders.
Their time together was brief
but it touched each of them deeply.
I'm not gonna leave you here.
I'm coming back.
I said it.
I meant it.
Adama ! Adama ! Adama !
After a long rehabilitation,
Commander Adama regained his strength
and returned to his crew in the CIC.
Very good to see you, sir !
There are things
we don't say often enough.
Things like what we mean to one an other.
All of you mean a lot to me.
I just want you to know that.
Starbuck returned
to Galactica with the Arrow of Apollo,
Helo and the Cylon Sharon from Caprica.
Good to see you too, Captain.
- Lee, wait !
- Don't you fracking move !
Drop your weapon, sir !
Drop your weapon.
Helo !
Now put that thing out of the airlock.
- What ?
- We don't keep Cylons around here, Lt.
- You said you wouldn't hurt her !
- No !
Helo, listen to me !
One of those things
put 2 rounds into my father's chest.
- It wasn't me !
- For the love of Gods, Sharon !
This Sharon saved
our lives back on Caprica, tell them !
I know how to find
the tomb of Athena, do you ?
Kobol's a big planet ! You don't
find the tomb, you don't find Earth !
Madame President.
- Tell them to wait a minute.
- Yes, sir.
Must have been hard,
being back on Caprica, being home.
Probably saw some tough things back there.
Anyway, tomorrow this whole thing
is gonna end, one way or another.
We find the tomb or we don't.
We find a way to Earth or we don't.
I just want you to know, Kara,
that I'm your friend. I love you.
If there's anything you wanna talk about,
anything you wanna get off your chest, then
I'm here for you.
Did you say you love me ?
- Well...
- Lee Adama loves me.
- No, all I meant was...
- No, seriously, very sweet.
You love me.
No, you love me. You can't
take it back, there's no take backs.
- You're dreaming it, Kara...
- You love me.
- Dreamer.
With the Arrow of Apollo in
our possession, the prophecy came to pass.
Led by the Cylon Sharon, we found our way
to Kobol and the ancient tomb of Athena.
These patterns were
on the original flags of the 12 Colonies
back in the days when the Colonies
were called by their ancient names.
Aries.
Taurus.
The jewels match the constellations.
This is the map...
This is the map to Earth.
After months of captivity
in a cell aboard Galactica,
the Cylon Sharon gave birth to the baby.
A girl...
We made her.
It almost makes you
want to believe in the cylon God.
Almost.
This child will not be raised by the cylon
and I can not risk
cylon agents getting their hands on it.
I divised a plan to switch
the Cylon child with a stillborn human baby.
She finally went into respiratory distress,
we couldn't get her intubated in time and...
we lost her, I'm sorry.
- You murdered her !
- Sharon...
Die !
You killed my baby !
She's so beautiful.
You understand, Maya, that
this adoption requires absolute secrecy.
The mother is a Pegasus officer
and must remain anonymous
- for political and religious reasons.
- You have my word.
Maya, you won't mind
if I drop in occasionally.
Of course not.
Good.
With the Cylon child safely
hidden within the fleet, live moved on.
Adama awarded his son
Commander of the Battlestar Pegasus,
sister ship to Galactica.
Congratulations, Commander.
Congratulations.
Really...
You deserve it.
My term as president was drawing
to a close and a new election was coming up.
Doctor Baltar emerged as my chief opponent
and I was determined
not to turn the human race over
to a man I had never completely trusted.
I'm going to wipe
the floor with you, Gaius.
You must be losing your mind again.
If that's the best you can come up with,
you're in a lot of trouble, good luck.
I am picking up a large planetary body.
But the election took an
unexpected turn when a routine Raptor mission
discovered what would
become the central issue of the campaign.
Atmosphere is nitrogen/oxygen.
Organic molecular spectra.
Fresh water.
We may have just found a world
that can support human life.
Less than 20% of that place
actually supports human life so...
You're not seeing the big picture.
This is your new home.
The place where you will lead
a new life. This is the future, Gaius.
Now there's a depressing thought.
can you imagine if we actually
had to live on that thing.
You...
... are a genius.
And ?
Pay attention.
You're about to win the election.
We needed an issue, something
to set us apart from Roslin, this is it.
Permanent settlement on this planet.
After 9 months of running from the Cylons,
I couldn't blame people for wanting
to feel solid beneath them once again.
Combined with the fact that the planet
was in a nebula and hidden from the Cylons,
it proved to be
a powerful temptation for a reary people.
I knew in my heart it was
the wrong decision but Baltar pressed on.
You see, I have long been a proponent
in the search for Earth.
The promise of perhaps finding
not only a new home,
but also the prospect
of discovering our long lost
brothers and sisters
of the 13th Colony is a powerful one.
But the trouble is,
the Cylons continue to follow us
since the destruction of the Colonies.
And if we have
a chance to stop this deadly chase,
shouldn't we take it ?
My answer is yes.
I feared Baltar's motives and I long
suspected him to be a Cylon collaborator.
If you'll raise
your right hand and repeat after me.
But his plans to settle on the new planet
drew overwhelming support from the voters
and he was elected President.
And now,
because it was the first will of the people,
I'm going to sign
my first executive order
requiring
to immediatly establish settlements
on the planet we have come to know
as New Caprica.
The Battlestar Galactica and the rest of the
fleet jumped together towards New Caprica.
Send word to the Pegasus to launch
their initial ground team onto the surface.
Let's get a good look at our new home.
Gods help us all.
As I'd feared,
the bitter conditions on New Caprica
made life difficult for all of us.
Supplies were scares, the climat was harsh.
But for one year,
we were safe from the Cylons
and even I began to think
that this world was our new home.
Baltar's reign was an unhappy one.
Out of step with the needs of his people,
he became more dictator than president.
Our people began to organize
resistance against him and his move.
When you realize
that the engine you've built
is being used
for something so foul, so perverted,
that it makes you sick in your heart
and it's then that
you must throw your body on the gears
and make it stop.
As for me, I returned to teaching.
Bye honey, thanks, good job.
You know what ?
Why don't you take the baby and go on.
Okay ? I'll finish up here.
- You sure ?
- Yes. Go ahead.
I also continued to keep
a close watch on the Cylon child
whose existence was known
only to myself and a few others.
- Have you seen Sam ?
- He's over there playing pyramid.
Thanks.
Starbuck rescued Anders as she promised
Sam, you idiot !
The two of them left Galactica,
moved down to the planet and were married.
You're sick, you're supposed to be in bed.
I can't believe
I married a moron, are you okay ?
I'm all right, I'm fine.
The Battlestars Galactica and Pegasus
let a small patrol fleet
in orbit around New Caprica
just in case the Cylons returned.
- Commander ?
- Yeah, lieutenant. What is it ?
I'm not sure,
I'm picking up something on Dradis.
Dradis ? How can you
see anything in that soup ? I mean...
Oh my Gods, the Cylon fleet.
They found us.
We have to get out of here, sir.
We can't just leave all those people behind.
There's nothing we can do.
It's taken us forever
just to get to action stations over here.
We're in no shape for a fight, sir.
They'll be wiped out.
We don't have a choice.
We need to get out of here right now !
Begin jump prep. We're leaving.
But we'll be back.
Judgement day.
As long as you offer no resistance,
you won't be harmed.
- How do I know that ?
- You don't.
You also don't have any choice.
Very well...
On behalf of the people of the 12 Colonies,
I surrender.
As I watched an army of Cylon Centurions
march through our city I knew
our most difficult struggles lay ahead.
Now we face
an unknown future under Cylon occupation
with no word from Adama or the Galactica.
I pray to the Gods we still
have the strength to fight and to survive.
What do you want to do now Captain ?
The same thing we always do,
fight them until we can't.
- =( Team Lords of Kobol )=-
Thanks to watch Battlestar Galactica
with our subtitles.
---
www.seriestele.net
www.forom.com