There it is.
Pretty much how I remember it.
I was younger than you
last time I was here, Simon.
Well, it's big.
Yeah, so I can get bigger pets here,
right, Mom?
Sure! Get a cow. Get a whole flock.
Herd.
That, too. What do you think, Jared?
Jared?
Okay. Here we go.
It's okay, Mr. Tibbs. It's okay.
It has that old people smell.
It's just an observation, not a judgment.
You're angry about the move. I get that.
Just what are you expecting
your silent protest will get you?
At least acknowledge this isn't
the way to deal with your anger
the way you said you were gonna do.
Say yes with your head.
Two blinks.
Nothing.
Mal, you and Simon take your stuff.
Wait in the foyer while I go look
for the main circuit breaker.
Okay, Mom.
-Get out of the car right now.
-You're not my mother, Mallory.
No, I'm worse,
because Mom doesn't believe in hitting.
-Come here, you little...
-And he's out of the car! Thank you!
Stop it! I'm not gonna let you
keep acting like a jerk!
-I'll do whatever I want.
-No, you won't!
Mom needs this to work, so cut it out!
-Simon, get her!
-I'm a pacifist.
You're so annoying.
You think you know everything!
-Well, I know stuff you don't.
-Like what?
Nothing.
-Thanks for having my back, bro.
-I don't do conflict.
-What are you doing?
-Unpacking.
Why? I told you it was only temporary.
Dad's coming tomorrow,
and he's gonna take us back with him.
-I know. But what about Mom?
-She can have Mallory.
Come on, Simon, we can't stay here.
Look at this place.
It's the house that time forgot.
-And it's got that...
-Old people smell, I know.
And what's this?
Salt. There's salt on the window.
I know. It's on all the windows.
Yeah, and that's not weird.
I'm guessing she put it there.
-ls that the nut bag and her husband?
-No.
That's Arthur Spiderwick,
you know, our great-great-uncle.
The little girl's the nut bag.
I mean, Aunt Lucinda, his daughter.
She's the one who lived here
before they took her away to the...
To the...
To the nut house.
Right.
And why'd she get taken there?
Because she said
her father was abducted.
By?
By faeries.
Exactly.
Our crazy aunt stayed here
her whole life and never left, ever!
That's not gonna happen to me, or you.
End of discussion.
Has anybody seen my keys?
I know I left them right here.
Nope.
I guess Aunt Lucinda
liked honey with her oatmeal, huh?
And tomato sauce.
Wow.
Where is my fencing medal, Jared?
-Hanging on your bed?
-It's not there anymore.
Well, find the bed
and you'll find your medal.
I'm not talking about the bed...
You know what?
I'm not acknowledging your existence
until you bring my medal back.
Promise?
Well, actually, you'd have to
acknowledge his existence
in order to receive the medal from him.
Thanks, Spock.
You're the pride of the Federation.
Jared, give it back.
I didn't take the stupid medal!
-You're such a liar!
-Conflict.
-Shut up, Simon!
Hey!
We're not gonna do this.
New town. New house. New job.
This is our new life.
Let's not fall into old ruts, okay?
I know this house isn't perfect,
but we can make it work,
if we want to make it work.
-All right?
-All right, Mom.
Shut up!
Hi.
-Dad.
Yeah, we made it.
What's that noise in the background?
You know, scratch that.
I don't want to know.
-Just because I don't.
-I'm gonna go look for my medal.
I'll help you.
What?
It's your dad.
-Hi, Dad.
-Hey, buddy.
How's the Addams Family mansion?
Oh, the house? Yeah, it's great,
if you like big creepy houses
in the middle of nowhere.
-Now, come on.
-Seriously. There's nothing here.
-You'll see.
-Yeah, well, listen...
-You're still coming tomorrow, right?
-Yeah, maybe. I'm gonna try.
-Why maybe?
-Look, don't worry. I'm coming.
There's something
we need to talk about.
But tomorrow might not work out, okay?
-Y eah, I understand.
-Okay, good.
-You'll try though, right?
-Absolutely.
But I'll see you soon, though. Defiinitely.
Okay.
-See you, Son.
-Bye, Dad.
What did you say to him?
Can't you at least pretend
you want him to come and see us?
Jared Grace, put that broom down!
-There's something in the wall!
-Now!
You said you were gonna stop
hitting things when you got angry!
I know I said I was gonna stop yelling.
Please, please, don't do this.
We'll clean it up, Mom.
You go to bed. You need to sleep.
-Nice move, pinhead.
-Shut up.
Something's in there, moving.
Probably a red squirrel.
Very common in this region.
Or it could just be a rat.
We don't need any more holes
in the wall!
Great. I'll get blamed for that.
Check it out.
This is one of those things
they use to send food upstairs.
-What are they called?
-Dumbwaiter.
Hey, those are Mom's keys.
And my medal!
What? You still think I took it.
Yeah, Mal, you busted me.
I took your medal,
hid it here and re-plastered the wall.
I don't know how you did it.
I just know you did it,
because you always do it.
-And now you're gonna clean it up.
-You told Mom we were gonna clean it.
We means you.
Simon, don't you want to know
where this thing goes?
Not really.
Simon!
Simon, wake up!
I went up. It's a room,
a secret room, upstairs.
There's a desk and a chest,
and I found this book!
-Something was in there!
-A red squirrel?
No, not a squirrel.
Unless squirrels can spell.
It wrote in the dust on the desk,
"Jared Grace, leave this place."
Wow.
That's really...impossible.
It's late.
Just go to sleep.
"Do not dare to read this book,
"for if you take one fateful look,
"you barter at your life's expense
and face a deadly consequence."
What the...
How did you guys get out?
Dear reader,
what you now hold in your hands
is the culmination ofi a lifie's work.
And you will soon see, as I have,
that there are fiantastical creatures
living among us,
hidden through mimicry and magic.
This book will give you
the tools and techniques
needed to lifit the veil
and see the unseen.
The secrets you are about to learn
have been kept hidden fior ages,
secrets that many ofi this realm
would prefier to stay hidden.
The creatures you will meet
are truly a sight to behold,
and most ofi them do not
like being observed.
But, over time,
I have garnered their trust.
Some, I am quite happy to report,
I now call firiend.
But a rare fiew are, quite firankly,
to be fieared.
The darker fiorces ofi this realm
all live in service ofi one creature,
the ogre, Mulgarath.
The secrets herein are powerful,
more powerful than even I was aware.
Never befiore has knowledge
ofi the fiantastical realm
been assembled in one tome.
And so I implore you, dear reader,
to use this infiormation wisely,
fior the ogre, Mulgarath,
seeks this knowledge
with relentless persistence.
Ifi he were to obtain the infiormation
in these pages,
I can assure you his intentions
would be ofi the vilest sort.
He assumes many fiorms,
and so you must constantly
be on guard.
I deeply fiear that the more I learn,
the more I place everyone around me
in grave danger.
So, reader, beware.
I beseech you, beware.
Mom!
-What's going on?
-Mom! Mom, please, help!
What happened to you?
-Hold still.
-Please, Mom, just cut it! Cut it!
-Okay, calm down.
-Mom, please!
Just cut me out! Cut it out!
Please, just get a scissors! I don't care!
-What happened?
-He ruined my hair! Get him out!
Jared, you've gone way too far this time.
-Mom, please! Please!
-What? I didn't do this!
I've been sitting in a footlocker
for the last two hours, reading!
Yeah, right!
Ask Simon.
Well, he was in a footlocker.
-Just cut me out!
-Field guide.
Mom, just cut it!
I'm not enjoying this.
I told you, I'll help you catch
a woodchuck or something.
I need the practice. Now, come on.
Simon!
That's not fair. He distracted me.
-What does "appease" mean?
-"Appease."
You know, placate, pacify, assuage.
-ln English.
-To make nice.
Is that what you came out here to do?
Well, apology not accepted.
I'm not apologizing 'cause I didn't do it!
This did.
A brownie is living in the house
and wants us to leave.
Wow. That's incredible.
You can read!
I'm telling you,
something is in that house with us,
and Arthur Spiderwick knew about it,
and that's why he wrote this guide!
I'm a little lost.
Who needs to be appeased?
-The brownie?
-No, a boggart.
So there's a brownie and a boggart?
A brownie turns into a boggart
when it's angry,
and it got angry
when Mallory destroyed his nest.
It likes honey.
-That's why all the honey's there.
-Really?
Don't listen to him, Simon.
Come on, let's go eat.
Hello!
Hello?
Sorry I wrecked your home,
but I made you a new one.
And I got you some honey.
I read you liked it.
Hope you do.
Hope it, you know, appeases you.
I'll be over here.
I'm really hoping you actually exist.
Hello?
Oh! My, my, my.
That is just tasty, tasty, delicious honey.
So good! So yummy, yummy, yummy!
Wait! No! I won't hurt you!
Here, here, have some more honey!
I shouldn't, I shouldn't, I really shouldn't.
I mean, if you insist.
Oh, my, my, my! That is good!
Where are you? Why can't I see you?
You don't see us, but now you do.
But only if we want you to.
We? You mean
all the magical creatures
Arthur Spiderwick wrote about.
The book! Oh, my gosh!
I'm sorry, master, I've failed!
Failed, failed, failed!
Your instructions were simple,
"Protect the book."
And I did it, I hid it,
I bound it and I wound it.
I did my best, locked it in the chest!
But you looked and looked
and found the book!
And from the chest,
the thing was stolen!
You foolish boy!
Idiot! Are you blind?
I put a note right on the cover!
Can't you read?
Why do I write notes
when no one's gonna read the notes?
I'm sorry. Here! More honey!
No! I'm not falling for that!
Oh, that is so good.
And they say I've got anger issues.
"Protect the book. Don't let it get took!"
Right, you had to protect the book.
Who told you to protect it?
-Wait! What did I say?
-Protect the book, protect the book.
It wasn't complicated.
I just had to protect the book. That's all.
Arthur Spiderwick.
So he wrote it
and asked you to protect it.
I said, "Master, we must destroy it!"
He said, "We must protect the book.
"Keep it in the circle,
safe from the ogre."
Ogre? Do you mean Mulgarath?
All the years protecting it
now ruined by a little twit!
Circle, circle, little jerkle.
Little jerkle broke the circle!
Whoa! Stop! What circle?
Okay.
Look. Here, here.
So it protects the house
to protect the book.
-Safe from who?
-Them!
What? Who's them?
I don't see anything.
Tibbsy, come here, boy!
Breakfast time! Mr. Tibbs?
All right, what did you do
with Simon's cat?
They're not here for the cat.
They want the book!
What is that? What's out there?
It's goblins! Goblins are here.
And all because
you took the book out there
and practically waved it in their faces,
you little twerp!
Simon!
Go ahead!
Now look at the mess you made!
Simon! They're taking him away.
What's happening?
The Stone! The Stone!
Look through the Stone!
What the hell?
No! No!
-The book stays or we all die!
-I need it! Let go!
It must stay in the circle! In the circle!
Mom!
-Mom! Where's Mom?
-She went to work, okay? I'm in charge.
Hey, where are you going?
Psycho.
Help me!
What are you doing? Help!
Help!
Give me, give me.
Give me a leg! Hey, give me!
Give me a leg! A leg!
That's not a leg!
This is a leg! Imbeciles.
Oh, my God.
Simon.
Don't move.
Slowly lift your foot.
Then we must shake on our alliance.
What? It's good.
-Who are you?
-I am Hogsqueal.
And I am here on a mission
to destroy the ogre, Mulgarath,
who killed my family!
Can you help me save my brother?
Please?
Yeah! Sure!
I was gonna suggest that
right after you let me out of this cage.
-So, come on! Free me!
-Okay, okay.
Get it open. Yeah, yeah, yeah. Good.
Now get behind me
and keep your mouth shut.
Okay, here's our plan.
I will find a safe position over there
and create a distraction with my stick.
Then you leap out with your knife
and finish the beast yourself.
I like that plan.
That's a good plan. I'm smart.
What beast?
The ogre, of course! Mulgarath!
-I just want to save my brother.
-Again with the brother?
Okay, fine. If we kill them,
saving him will be much easier.
Trust me. Now drop that stone.
You'll need both hands
to choke a goblin.
But how do I see without...
Nailed him!
I have given you the Sight,
a gift only a hobgoblin can bestow.
Oh, gross!
You're welcome. Now, let's go.
-Simon!
-Jared.
Oh, my God! Oh, my God!
Jared, what's happening?
Get me out of here.
Just hang on.
I'm gonna cut you out.
-Jared!
-Get back.
Hide.
Jared!
Mulgarath!
-What are they doing?
-Summoning Mulgarath. Get ready.
Mulgarath! Mulgarath! Mulgarath!
That's Mulgarath?
That's the ogre
you're all freaked out about?
That old man?
Don't be fooled
by what you think you see.
That's just what he wants.
I beg your forgiveness.
I asked my friends here
to invite you to a nice little meeting.
Then they got a bit overzealous.
That's a goblin for you.
My apologies.
What do you want with me?
It's not what I want with you.
It's what I want from you.
Arthur Spiderwick's field guide.
I know you found it.
That's right, you can simply
walk back the way you came.
Just give me the book.
I don't have it.
I don't. Look.
Search him!
What? If Mulgarath learns the secrets
in that book,
he could kill us all!
He's weak in his human form.
It's now or never.
Come! Death to the ogre!
Bird!
Delicious! Come back here!
I'll be back! Kill him if you get a chance!
Remember the plan!
Move!
Pockets. Search the pockets.
The pockets! No, these!
These are pockets, idiot!
Master, this is all we found.
Do they have the book?
No.
But I know where it is.
I'll go get it and give it to you. I swear.
I'm placing my trust in you.
If you give me the book,
your life will go on
as if nothing ever happened.
However, if you fail,
I'm afraid I'll have to find somebody else
to get my book for me.
Go. Go on.
Run along.
Go.
Mulgarath! Mulgarath! Mulgarath!
You failed me, Redcap!
There are two human boys
with the same faces.
The Jared and the not Jared.
We took the wrong one.
Then find the Jared,
get the book and kill them!
Kill them all!
Move out!
Stupid!
Those things were gonna kill me
over your stupid, stupid book!
-They're right over there.
-I can't take this.
Let's just get to the house
and give it to them.
Hey, it's not at the house.
It's right here in my backpack.
-What? Then let's just give it to them.
-No, they'll just kill us anyway!
Well, let's just...
-Give it!
-Stop!
Give it!
Book!
-Get them! Go! Go! Go!
-Come on!
After them!
Get them! Get them! Rip them apart!
But not the book! Don't hurt the book!
Jared! Jared! Over here!
Help me! Help me!
Come on!
-Calm down!
-Keep them away! Keep them away!
It's okay. There's a protective circle
around the house.
-We're safe inside it.
-There you are.
You know, Mom left me in charge,
so you can't just run off
without telling me.
-Get her.
-Mallory, this way, now!
Now! Now!
-What? Don't yell at me.
-Mal, come on! Come on!
Run to the front door, fast!
I'm not running anywhere,
and stop throwing rocks at me!
Listen to him!
You're surrounded by goblins!
Get inside the protective circle!
Oh, God, Simon,
he's got you in on this now?
For the last time,
there's no such thing as...
What's happening?
No, Mallory, they're short.
Aim below your knees. 10 o'clock.
10 o'clock!
Mallory! Mallory! 12 o'clock!
Behind you! Behind you! 6 o'clock!
3 o'clock! 3 o'clock!
Come back! You're safe. You're safe.
You're safe.
Now do you believe me?
Mom!
It's gonna be bad! It's bad!
-Oh, God.
-No, that's bad.
-Mom!
-Jared!
-What were those things?
-I told you, goblins.
It's okay, Simon. It's okay.
No, it's not okay! It's not! It's not!
He's right. What am I saying?
Of course it isn't!
How many of those things
are out there?
I don't know! I don't know! Okay?
Sit tight! I'll be right back!
Jared! God, he's gonna get us all killed!
I'll be right back. Keep pressure on that.
Pressure? What?
Jared?
Why are they doing this?
What do they want from us?
The book.
Oh, God!
They're coming from everywhere!
I know, I can see.
This can't be happening.
Where did you get that book?
So, the book was in here
with a big warning that said,
"Do not read," and you read it?
It's a book. I didn't think reading it
would unleash goblin fury, okay?
But that's the thing,
you never think of anything!
-You're always doing this!
-Yeah, right.
You don't think, you just do!
Maybe I could think if you'd stop talking.
You do stuff and we pay for it.
Hey, if you're so smart,
what do you think we should do with it?
If freaky goblins want this book,
I say we give it to them!
No!
Back off! The book stays here!
-Right here! Here, here, here!
-No! Mallory, no! No!
What is that hideous thing?
Haven't I made myself that clear?
Touch it and you'll pay!
-Stop it! Chill! Chill!
-Touch it and I'll bite your fingers off!
Get me some honey from the kitchen.
-What?
-Just do it!
Come on, try it! Try it!
I invite you to try it!
-Go!
-You'll be fingerless, you...
You, get away!
-You ruined everything!
-Okay, protect the book.
Okay, I promise.
-Mallory!
-I'm coming!
-Okay, honey's coming, honey's coming.
-ldiots!
-I don't need your stinking honey!
-Here, drink, drink.
-It's okay. It's okay.
-It's okay?
There is so much about this
that's not okay.
I don't even know where to start.
Why can I see him
without that stone thing?
Because he's letting you see.
Thimbletack, what happens
if goblins get the book?
You die, I die, we all die. Bye-bye.
-What does he mean, we all die?
-I think he means we all die.
He can't know the secrets. He can't!
The ogre is not to be trusted.
He's right. We can't give it to Mulgarath.
He'll just kill us anyway.
I heard him say so.
Then let's just burn it.
No!
Give it! Give the book!
Give it!
Sorry, master! Forgive us!
Give the book!
Okay, okay, okay, wait!
You win. You are strong,
smart human boy.
So don't be foolish. Give us the book.
We'll leave you alone.
I don't believe you!
No!
Now you've done it! Now you will pay!
Book!
Book, book, book.
Book, book, book, book, book.
-It's cold.
-You can't stay in the circle forever.
And when you leave, here we will be.
Let me guess,
the book's got a charm on it.
Lest there fall any more harm on it.
Great.
-They're not leaving.
-I know.
-They're never leaving!
-I heard you.
-Why does he want that book so bad?
-I don't know.
Well, figure it out!
All I know is Mulgarath
can't break the circle without this book,
so we're safe as long as
we stay in the house.
Until when?
We stay here long enough,
we're gonna end up like her!
Wait a minute.
-She can help us.
-Aunt Lucinda? Are you kidding?
We don't even know her
or where she is!
I think I do.
She's at the Woodhaven Sanatorium.
But how do you get to her?
-There, all safe.
-Good. Now go. Make haste.
Okay, I think I have this figured out.
Some sort of secret tunnel system,
goes all the way to town.
About a mile, that way.
The first ladder you find, go up,
and the sanatorium's here.
Thanks.
You ready?
Oh, yeah. Now I'm ready.
-All right. Let's go.
-Mallory?
I already told you, Simon, you can't go.
Not with that leg, you'll slow us down.
I know, but I found this.
It'll make it easier for you to see.
Okay, Simon?
Go!
-Hey, are you there?
-Show yourselves!
Yeah, right here, on the porch!
Come to me on the porch!
Yeah, yeah, good.
Right here, over here.
Yeah, are you hungry?
-Right here on the porch.
-Come on. Hurry up. Get in.
Go! Go! Go!
They're coming! Open the door!
Jared, hurry!
-Come on!
-Get in, get in!
Let's go! Go, go, go!
Wait, wait, wait.
This way, this way, this way.
Hurry, hurry, hurry.
Dig! Dig!
Go!
"Goblin defenses.
"Tomato sauce burns the skin like acid.
"Vinegar fumes asphyxiates.
"Salt, blinding effect."
Are there more?
What does the book say?
-Step away from the book!
-Okay, okay, you open it.
Where is it?
Where did he put it? Where?
Oh, there.
Oh, no. Jared.
-What did you do with it? Liars! Liars!
-No, it wasn't me.
All of you, liars! Where's the book?
-You brought the book?
-We need to show it to Lucinda.
-Which way goes into town?
-Right.
Get the troll.
Now left. Go left!
-It's a mole troll.
-What?
Run!
This way!
Go, go, go!
Jared!
Jared, come on!
Are you okay?
Oh, man, did I hit somebody?
Yes. Thank you!
Then you hit F1, tab, tab.
Then shift-return to get the total.
I know, it's a lot to remember,
but let's just go through it again.
Here you go.
So tomato sauce really kills goblins?
Jared, come on.
-You're really in a hurry.
-We're just really excited to see her.
-Those are nice flowers and sword.
-I take fencing.
Lucinda? You have visitors.
More salt.
There, there, there, now.
It's okay. It's okay.
Aunt Lucinda?
I'm Mallory Grace,
and this is my brother, Jared.
Our mom's Helen.
We have some questions.
-See, we moved into your house.
-What?
Oh, no, no, no.
No, it isn't safe.
Why have you done this?
Mom said you gave it to her
since she's the only living heir.
-No, you have to get out of there.
-We can't.
We don't have anywhere else to go.
-lt isn't safe. You don't understand.
-Yes, we do.
We know everything. We've seen.
It's okay. They've seen.
Mallory, look.
No, no, not for you.
She's right.
Eat that and you'll never crave
human food again.
-How do you know that?
-I found this.
Your father's field guide.
Inside, quickly, quickly!
Quickly!
Do you know what you've done
by bringing it outside the circle?
Don't you know what could happen
if it falls into the wrong hands?
No, we don't.
That's why I brought it to you.
Then you haven't read it.
He did.
Then you know more than you should.
And your lives are in danger.
Didn't you read the note?
Please. We don't know what to do.
Can't you tell us something
that'll help us?
This book has brought nothing
but heartache and misery to my family.
I would say it was his life's work,
but, in truth, it was his life.
The last day I saw him
he was so agitated,
almost delirious.
I remember him
running through the house,
a crazed look in his eyes.
That was the day he created the circle.
A book Mulgarath would use
to destroy all the other fiaeries.
And then nothing could stop him,
even humans,
from becoming the most powerful
creature the world had ever known.
My fiather immediately did everything
he could to protect us.
Everything except...
Master must destroy the book!
No! We need to protect it!
Keep it inside the circle,
safe from the ogre!
I just need more time, Thimbletack.
I need more time.
But I didn't know
about the circle, you see.
London Bridge is fialling down
Falling down
Oh, no!
London Bridge is fialling down
Lucy!
Come away from the toadstools!
-What?
-Stay inside the circle!
-I can't hear you!
-Lucy! No!
London Bridge is fialling down
Daddy! Please, help me!
Somebody's dragging me, Daddy!
-Leave her alone!
-Daddy!
Lucy, come! Come! Stay there!
-Stay inside the circle!
-Daddy! Daddy, what's going on?
-What's happening?
-Don't go over the mushrooms! No!
What are those?
Daddy, what are those things?
Tell me!
Daddy! Daddy?
Daddy?
The sylph protect
the entire fiaerie realm,
and the secrets my fiather discovered
put them in danger.
So they rescued him firom the goblins,
but took him away firom me.
-Daddy!
-Lucy! I'll be back!
Each day,
I would stare down that drive,
and dream of him
walking up those steps
and holding me in his arms once again.
But he never did.
One night, I dreamt that I saw him
in the woods.
So I went out to look for him,
but something wouldn't let me.
When they say suicide
and you say goblins,
here is where they put you.
They thought I'd read the book, you see.
Mulgarath will stop at nothing
to get these secrets,
which is why you and your family
are in grave danger.
And there is only one person
who can help you.
-Who?
-My father.
Your father? But your father's dead.
No! No, no, he's not dead.
The sprites have told me he's alive,
held captive by the sylph
for all that he knows.
You must find him,
bring him his book
and have him destroy it.
It is your only hope.
-No!
-Give me that!
Where did he come from?
-No!
-Horrible, horrible!
Mom?
Useless!
-Worthless! No.
-Wait. Wait.
Wait a minute, wait a minute.
What's this? What's this? No?
You had the book in your possession,
and all you bring me is pages
of nixies and phooka habitats!
Don't hurt me.
It hurts!
"Charm for protective circle."
Forgive me, master.
When the moon rises,
the book will be mine.
Redcap, we have a potion to make.
Oh, no. This is not good.
Must find human boy. Must warn him.
Or maybe I'll just hide. I like that plan.
So, you say you found this book,
and it tells you how to see faeries
and goblins and magic sprites,
and that's what this is all about.
I told you you wouldn't believe me.
-What do you think about all this, Mal?
-It's true, Mom.
No, it's not!
Do you really think I am so stupid
that I don't see what this is about?
You hate the house
and you want to go back to New York
and to our old life!
Well, let me just be really clear
when I say
that isn't gonna happen.
Because we can't afford New York,
because...
This is why Dad left, you know.
Excuse me?
When someone's trying to tell you
something you don't wanna hear,
this is what you do.
You just stop listening and start yelling.
You did it to Dad all the time.
-Stop it.
-I saw you.
Yeah, you saw what you wanted to see.
You wouldn't listen,
and that's why he left!
Get out.
-What?
-I said get out.
Gladly.
I hate you,
and I don't want to live with you!
Don't you think you should just tell him?
Go inside, Mal.
We'll deal with this when I get home.
Oh, my! We're so organized.
Organized, organized, organized.
Look at that. That's very good.
More bombs for you.
The book! What happened to the book?
What did you do to the book?
-It's okay, it's okay. I'll talk to him.
-Stained!
You said you wouldn't take the book,
and you lied!
-You tricked him!
-I know. I'm sorry.
Jared, I think you should come
and see this.
See? No goblins.
-Do you think they've given up?
-Wrong!
Goblins don't give up.
They're too stupid to know how.
They're relentless,
and they're out there right now, plotting,
which is why I came back for you.
Now is the perfect time to...
Bird! Bird!
Come here, come here, come here.
Don't go up there! No, come here!
-What is that?
-It's Hogsqueal.
Wait a minute.
-Do birds live in these little houses?
-Yeah.
Oh, my gosh. That's genius.
Who thought of that?
You can stick your tongue right in.
Hogsqueal! Hogsqueal!
You said the goblins are plotting.
To do what?
They have pages of the book.
That stupid book!
You don't understand.
I talked to Spiderwick.
I shared hobgoblin secrets.
But Mulgarath stole just that one page,
then used it to kill my entire family!
If he gets ahold of the whole book,
he will do the same to everyone,
including you!
And now he's coming.
"When the moon rises," he said.
But we'll be waiting. We'll set a trap.
You with your knife and me hiding safely
near these bird homes.
-Who is that? Who's up there?
-More humungous humans!
Recruits for the alliance!
Huh? Huh? Join us on our quest!
Vengeance or death!
Hopefully vengeance.
Okay, here's the plan.
No, no. Wait, wait, wait!
We must unite! We must stay focused!
Dad, I've left like four messages.
Why haven't you called back?
Where are you?
You've got to come here right now.
There's all this crazy...
All this weird stuff's been happening.
Bad stuff, real bad.
And you, you said
you were gonna come get me.
So where are you?
He's not coming, is he?
He's with someone else.
He's moved in with her.
He's not getting back with Mom.
He's not.
Mom wanted him to tell you himself.
She's been waiting for him to do that.
It's okay, Tibbsy. It's okay.
Oh, God, they're coming.
Jared, what do we do now?
Lucinda said our only chance
is to take the book to Arthur Spiderwick
and have him destroy it.
What?
We don't even know if he's alive,
let alone how to find him.
-What? What are you looking for?
-He had a pet.
A pet?
And Fluffy the dog is gonna save us?
It wasn't a dog. It was this, a griffin.
"When I call upon him
in the native tongue of the tree elf
"with whom he dwells,
he comes to my assistance."
See? His pet can find him.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Summon a griffin in native tree elf
to find a 1 25-year-old man
who may or may not be alive?
That's our plan?
And you know how to summon
a griffin in native tree elf?
Of course.
Is that it?
Did it work?
I guess not.
Whoa! That sounds like a big one.
Whoa. Whoa. Whoa, whoa, whoa.
-Jared! Jared!
-Simon, be careful!
Yes, yes, yes! Find Arthur Spiderwick.
Bring him the book.
There's your ride. Off you go.
Go, go, go!
What? You want us to ride that beast?
He's not a beast. He's a bird.
He's a big-boned bird!
There's no way we can possibly...
It's okay. Calm down. It's okay.
Cool pet.
Hurry up! What are you waiting for?
Get on him!
My God, it's him.
Arthur Spiderwick.
He's alive.
Whoa.
-How are we gonna get home?
-Arthur Spiderwick?
Thank God we found you.
You don't even know
what we've been through.
-I'm sorry. Do I know you?
-Not really.
Lucinda, your daughter,
our great-aunt, she sent us.
Lucy? She's only 6-and-a-half years old.
No. No, she's 86-and-a-half.
Well, that's nonsense.
I was with her only this morning.
Or was that yesterday?
No, that was 80 years ago!
Listen, you gotta believe me.
You're my great-great-uncle.
Help me out, guys.
Guys?
What's happening?
What's the matter with them?
The sylphs.
Their songs must have altered
my perception of time.
That is what they do.
Lucy's an old woman now, you say?
That must mean that my wife is...
Oh, my God, what have I done?
Look, I'm sorry about all that, really.
But you gotta help us. I found your book.
The field guide? No!
No, not here. Not now.
Don't listen to them.
Follow me.
Here! Under here!
Quickly, while they're distracted.
The book, give me the book.
Oh, the field guide.
The field guide.
You should never have read this.
You should not have brought this
outside the circle.
I know. I know, but I brought it to you
so you could destroy it.
Destroy it?
No. Are you mad?
I have uncovered all of their secrets.
And this book is my validation.
This book is my life.
You're 1 25 years old! Your life is over!
And your daughter
spent her life without a father,
all because of that book.
I never imagined
that the things I'd learned
could possibly have led to this.
Look, I know stuff I wish I didn't, too,
but there's nothing I can do about that.
One thing I know for sure
is that you gotta destroy that book.
-What's this?
-What?
-What's wrong?
-Where's my book?
-What is this?
-Thimbletack, he switched the pages.
But the real book
is still inside the circle. It's safe.
-No, Mulgarath got pages.
-What?
-He'll break the circle as soon as...
-As soon as the moon rises, I know.
That's when Mom will be getting home.
I gotta get back.
No! They won't let you leave.
They'll keep you here for
the same reason they're keeping me.
We know too much.
Then what are we gonna do?
Please, you've gotta help us!
If I'm as old as you say I am,
I'm useless outside this glade.
The last thing I said to my mom was,
"l hate you."
Listen, son.
The boy who had the tenacity
to find me,
doesn't need my help.
Now, Mulgarath wants the power
that comes with knowledge.
You have that knowledge.
You are the book now.
And you have to get out of here. Now.
Yes!
I think I can distract them.
On my signal,
run to your brother and sister.
You'll only have a few moments
to escape.
-But...
-Await my signal.
But...
Here! Here! I have the field guide!
Do you want it? Yes, here!
Come take it!
You can keep it safe right here!
Now!
Yes, Byron! Yes!
Get them home safely!
Come on, snap out of it! Come on!
Oh, shoot!
They started spreading the potion.
Oh, no. There's Mom.
-Mom! No! Turn around!
-Go away, Mom!
Stop the car!
What?
-Mom, move over!
-What are you doing?
Mallory, you drive!
Get the car inside the circle!
-Go, go!
-You're not driving this car!
Stop it! Mal, stop!
Thank God.
Will someone please tell me
what's going on?
-Jared, what do we do now?
-Protect the house.
-Simon, the sage in the planter boxes.
-I know, I know.
-Hang them in the windows!
-I'm on it.
Mal, go upstairs
and get all of Lucinda's salt.
-All of it?
-All of it!
-Okay. Okay.
-Thimbletack!
-Jared!
The circle's about to be broken!
Please come out!
Jared! Jared! What is going on?
-Mom, you've got to believe me. Okay?
-No! No!
One more word about faeries
and goblins and I swear...
Goblins, I know. But I hid the book.
They'll never find it.
Well, I hope they don't. Unless...
Why is she screaming?
I'm the one who should be screaming.
The circle's about to be broken!
Mom, no! He's not the problem.
They are.
Get in there! Get in there!
We have to protect the house.
Understand?
Hurry, hurry! Yeah, get every opening!
Okay, the living room's done!
-Simon, do the music room!
-Okay, okay, I got it!
Steel, it cuts and burns.
Good thing we're New Yorkers.
Wait, wait, here it comes.
Here it comes.
The circle is broken.
The circle is broken! Attack!
The windows and doors are protected.
Get down there. Go low! Go low!
Break it! Break on through! Come on!
The rest of you, up! Up, up, up!
Go, you toads! Go! Find the book!
Where did they go?
Did it work?
Come on, Jared! Come on!
Let's go! Let's go!
Get back, Jared! Get back!
Go, go, go! Run!
Give it to me! Give it to me!
-Simon, get the back door!
-I'm on it!
Mal, help me!
It won't hold for long.
Give me a hand.
Go on! Get in there! Where did they go?
Where are they? Where are they?
Come on, let's find them.
You, over there, to the left.
You, to the right.
Spread out, spread out.
Oh...
Are you okay?
-lt worked.
-Yeah.
Book safe?
Yes. Good job, Thimbletack.
Thank God.
What is it?
Come on.
Dad?
What happened?
Richard?
-What are you doing here?
-What's going on?
Where do we start?
With this, I guess.
What's that? Let me see.
No!
Not until you tell me
what you need to tell me.
What?
The last time we were on the phone,
you said the next time we met,
you had something
you needed to say to me.
So what is it?
Look me in the eyes and tell me.
I just want to hear you say it.
I...
I just wanted to tell you that I love you.
Let me see.
Jared.
Wrong answer.
-Jared!
-Get back! Get back!
What did you do?
-It's not Dad!
-What?
Oh, my God!
Now give me the book!
Run, Jared!
Give me the book. Give me the book.
Back off!
Thimbletack!
Give me the book!
Jared!
Oh, yeah.
Give me the book now!
-You want the book?
-Yeah.
Go get it!
Jared! Jared!
-Jared, are you okay?
-Jared, you did it.
Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
Jared, are you okay?
Yes! Death to the ogre!
We did it! You sent him right to me,
and I ate him! That's teamwork!
The taste of vengeance is sweet!
I can still taste a little! Oh, it's good!
I did it! I knew I could do it!
They said I couldn't, but I did it!
-It's the field guide.
-Here, we'll help you.
Jared.
I'm sorry I didn't believe you. I mean...
No, I'm sorry.
-No, listen, l...
-For what I said, I didn't mean...
Jared, it's not your fault.
It's mine.
I was trying to protect you,
but I guess I should have
just told you the truth.
Your dad does love you,
and if you want to stay with him, that's...
I don't want to live with Dad.
Is it okay if I stay here with you?
Is it okay?
Who else is gonna protect us?
I'll go put this in your old room.
My old friend Thimbletack.
Book safe, Lucy. Book safe.
And if my father were here,
he'd say, "Job well done."
Aunt Lucinda?
I think you should come see this.
Am I dreaming?
No, my child. You're not.
Child?
Do you know how old I am?
Yes, I do.
I'm so sorry.
I was so captivated by all
the magical creatures I found
that I lost sight of the one I already had.
But I see now,
and I may never be able
to forgive myself.
You came back as you promised,
so I forgive you.
My dear, because the book was saved,
the sylph allowed me to come see you,
but I cannot stay.
Because if I do,
all my years will come back to me,
all at once, and I will turn to dust.
Then this time, take me with you.
Daddy.
Oh, Lucy.
-Come with me.
-Okay.
Hey, come on.
Fly while you can, griffin.
I swallowed an ogre whole.
You could be next.