In the V.S. A group works citizens,
That voorde government ...
Mysteries and crimes research.
This is the Veritas-project.
Veritas is 'reality' in the Latin.
Ten years later.
Well gone, Jimmy.
Remain concentrated.
Well played, boys. We go
This two-four-two play on ...
On two.
- Completely stuff. On two. Clear?
Does it go well?
On the strike.
Red forty.
Again a nice action of Jimmy Boltz.
Take them to graze, Boltz.
Great action.
Remain concentrated, Jimmy.
What is well, Jimmy?
- I know nothing.
Take you him but.
You have heard 'm.
This play over Lenny. Clear?
Play. Red twenty.
Blue two forty.
Fluffy, Tote.
Two hours.
Jimmy man, what do you well?
Jimmy, stuff went you well there?
Abel Frye ...
- Par don can, I past it?
What is with Jimmy?
- Stand up once.
Get the trainer.
You have enough seen, Mrs. Wyrthen?
This is my third player all.
Abel Frye.
According to me Abel has to get him.
- Abel?
Is not he a juut?
- Does he look there so?
Convince me with your money.
- Here. But jou I do not depend on.
And that is appropriate.
Hundred grammes fresh metamfetamine.
- Give but.
I go now.
- Excellent, fellow.
Take the back-doors the alley.
Fifty grammes, so?
If this thing waged, I happen
A week to buy astern to more.
Look once, these two rats
Be outside on poking around.
One of them this carried.
On the ground, you.
With your hands on the back.
Are you also a cop?
- No, I it swore.
There he is to dumb for.
All you know but never. Convince me.
You have still three seconden.
Jacky Morelli my dealer is.
- That I cannot.
Your last second goes in.
Ed buys via Gomez, he intends drain me.
- Why buy you then in us?
Gomez holds all the money itself.
I can nowhere else forth.
Police.
Everybody on the ground.
On the ground with your hands
On your back. Now.
Did she handcuffs to.
What is this? Removed she here.
Appear, pus.
Not too happen that your me
This thing have allowed to carry.
We hunt all months on Gomez.
- Now everything on tape stands.
And the appointment?
- We care about a pleeggezin ...
Till we have his family.
- And for Gomez' other zwervertjes.
There our handsome daughter is.
- She is always crackled, he?
I said still so: Not as much gel.
- We will it must shave.
Yes, shave.
- As soon as we home be.
Go to Roger Highschool
Occult business, three victims
I am that Abel Frye-gedoe
Completely sat.
Kramer is breathed upon still, Anderson
Is still in life danger and now Jim.
We know does who it.
- Yes, but that nobody happen.
Must see you that.
I am not scared for a spirit.
I do not go there heus
Less doorspijbelen.
Say Abel that he there on goes
And you also.
What have done I?
- You are weird, that cost extra.
You treat me today to lunch.
I hou the draft money well.
Wait.
Towards splendor, expect well even.
No, I can there no more against.
- Look well once to you forth.
Abel is our back coverage. We indicate
Only the victims on.
We put the thing on his head.
That is just real force.
It comes welweer good.
Jim Boltz still is sick?
Hopefully he is quickly better.
The Springfields are privately-speurders,
Self recommends the police them.
I cannot them. Everything has been verified all,
Maargoed, that you decide.
You want here
Really undercover works?
Be your brother and sister?
- We wait the D.N.A.-Test still off.
We occupy with
The reality are, what that also moge.
The reality is that I this granny
Without new partner can.
They have experience with infiltration,
Rebuilding and uitlokking.
I want to see that fellow well once.
- This is Max, your new mate.
He holds of quickies.
Elijah, you do five sections
On the highest level.
According to your file
Are you very intelligent.
Have I nothing on that level?
- You can be now 's cathedral.
I your guide well
To your grade.
Can I see your time-tables once more?
Higher mathematics is on the end of
The passage and biology is the kick on.
Norman, you comes as called.
You themselves guided way into their grade?
This is Norman Bloom, our science-star.
Further he is education assistant.
Nice your to learn to know.
Wauw, two of their kind.
No, you can not pray at school,
Because then your me impose your norms.
That me do not sit nice.
You press me now nevertheless your norms on
By to say that nothing can?
Well and fault individual is on it.
No nevertheless, titmouse?
- O, yeah.
And I call Mr. Carlson.
- Am I now naughty?
I have to you learn that tolerance
An ethical standpoint is.
If a freedom warrior or terrorist
Mean kills, he sat then fault?
Allicht.
Then is well and fault
Nevertheless not on it individual?
There we had nothing ov ...
Great, like you with Carlson
In dispute went.
That I get well once with pleasure.
He Elisha, bowl once.
Carlson is the homework forgetting.
Thanks.
In the lunch sets we your
On everybody for.
That seems me nice.
O crisis, Norman.
Still thanks for ...
What is that a nice necklace.
Are you a religion fanatic, or so?
- Yes, or so.
Do you happen in the sky?
Reckon but.
Nice so, then know you go without food
How celestial you be.
And then know you go without food
That you that sky never will reach.
V is X-kwadraat?
Thanks, hear.
O you, ego-alarm.
- I go up this side.
Stuff thought you to pass away?
The new study sphere.
- The fault of my parents.
What is so funny?
I can lie see Jamaica
With this thing.
Towards, I cannot without.
I cannot without.
Towards, return.
Have you still dead presidents?
- Lenny, him return his pair of spectacles but.
I do not have enough money
To they pay stay.
Lan Snyder has a plan.
Does he want to talk well with us?
- What have we to lose?
Logical that they got 'm.
Your all may nowhere
Other over have?
Do not work hard you from, maid. Close but
At the back in the file for Blake.
Do do not want to hear you the remainder then?
- No, I that story am so sat.
But this is not just a story.
- Tell further.
Abel Frye a pus was.
He got what with the girl
Of the part of the school.
That boy pestered Abel always.
- That had to miscarry.
She gave him the ticket stuff everyone
In was. He wept as a kid.
And in the forbidden wing ...
- Keelde he her.
He slaughtered hair.
The forbidden wing?
- If there deaths fall, is the forbidden.
Look, after he her
Had stabbed to death, he hung up.
His spirit roams now by the school
And he gets everybody that 'm calls up.
Like Ian Snyder
And his club with madmen?
How come you to this?
- Crystal Sparks' work hangs everywhere.
Abel has foreseen it now
On the spetters from it football-team.
Jimmy Boltz was the third all.
What smell you, jochie?
What there occurs, jochie?
Is that it?
What smell you well, Max?
There something sits
On this ticket of 50 dollars.
Do your him know occasional?
Listen Lenny,
She nothing deserved.
Know you that I your so
Apart can break?
Par don hear, ...
- Now you must pay attention.
We be even busy.
Do be sometimes problems?
We be busy, I said.
Twister is nice, he?
- Get 'm, Blake.
Against that study spheres?
There I fail on along.
Stuff has Abel his neck opgerekt?
- In the forbidden wing.
That we evade.
- Why?
That you see still.
- We do not go there in, heard.
The old wing has been renewed,
Just like the whole school ...
Maartoen runs out the money.
He, he is open.
In the dictionary is mentioned bans
A picture of dead bystander.
Do you do not go along or yet?
He hangs there no more, heard.
The spirit escaped
In it lop in the walls.
Then he must be in the master builders
And not in us.
Stuff is them along busy?
- She is crazy.
Does everything be fine still, maid?
- Yes, other allows I call well know.
You have a bump on your head, but
With what ice pulls off that well again.
Knocked down by a spirit?
What have been taken place, rate?
- Something has or someone struck me.
Really not ordinary cases?
What is it last what you have seen?
- Stars.
She is again the old man.
And before?
- When I have seen someone.
From this world,
Or from the next?
Why did not close you the school?
The half of the parents intends that also,
The remainder wants that their offspring succeeds.
The school management intends probably be that
That footballers the case not bottles.
Abel Frye has been the only exiled.
- De Jongs that hung up.
I accept that everybody at school
This picture has seen well once.
Abel Frye is rather
A school legend be.
... There is something wrong goes without food.
- Completely not.
You have such tin of on-school-sits
A-boy-that-I-find-nice.
Nonsense. We be now undercover,
So I must stay well in my role.
Everybody has fallen
For my role as popular maid.
I not. I am older then you.
- 2 minutes.
But this is something otherwise.
I know jou.
Can you keep a secret?
- Yes, that I vow.
It is something between jou and me
And everybody that I call later tell.
Goh what funny, Elijah.
If I would find someone there nice
And I do not say that that so is ...
Maarstel, what can go wrong there then?
We move frequenter then gypsies.
I am pleased quite with this life ...
But sometimes I wonder well once
How mean other life.
With boys exit,
Madman do and house arrest get.