We were supposed to recon the area
two hours ago.
The meet's set
For tonight.
- Couldn't be helped.
- Delay at customs.
That's a lot Of euros.
That's what alexander
The great said.
I'm the one who had to
Sign for the 32 million,
So don't let me catch you wearing prada
On the way home.
Middle man takes two
For his cut.
Petrov doesn't show
His face
Until the local guy
Checks you out.
let's make up
For lost time.
I think i got your sizes right.
It will help you Fit in better.
Fit in where?
The middle man, dragan,
The operates a club.
- We'll take it From here.
- It's not a gay club.
To hop the rope, you'll need arm candy.
That would be me.
Corner of the bar, maroon shirt,
gold chain.
- Dragan?
- Yes. Is right.
It's pleasure
To meet you.
You, too.
Let's do some business.
How long are you
Staying in kosovo?
Just long enough for us to conduct
Our business.
You know the price.
I am prepared
To pay.
It's a lot of cash
For a little african country.
It's not a lot Of cash to me.
Do you want to Count my money
Or do business?
I can have Petrov tomorrow
Here with your package.
So where is the money?
When i get The plutonium,
and i need To test it.
It has already Been tested.
It's pu-239.
Yes. Very
Reassuring.
Nonetheless.
You worry too much.
No. You see
The money
When i see petrov.
He doesn't like
To be fooled with.
Neither do i.
Tomorrow?
Tomorrow.
But tonight, you will stay
as my guest.
Are you hungry
Or thirsty?
No. I'm fine,
Thank you.
i would like to show you some
hospitality.
You're my new friend,
Right?
Follow me.
And this is?
A gesture
Of good faith.
Just like that?
Anything you want.
She does it all.
Backwards, forwards,
Upside down.
Whatever he likes.
More than ok.
First, tell me
Your name.
How long have you
Worked here, Dava?
Two months.
Wait.
But dragan said--
I know what dragan said,
But my religion
Prevents me,
As it also prevents me from refusing
a gift from my host,
So please
just
Just sit down.
you seem like
Nice man.
But others are not so.
I would never hurt you.
But will you
Help me?
If i were able to.
My friend
Nadia and i,
We come to kosovo
To be models,
But when we
Get here,
He take our passport,
He beat us.
He keep us hid.
There are others?
Some he sell, some he make
work here.
My friend nadia,
She's very sick.
If we don't get
Out of here soon,
She will die
In this hell.
Will you help us?
Trouble.
Who are they?
They're here
For the plutonium, too.
Terrorist arms brokers.
Looks like our sale
Just turned into an auction.
* The Unit Team  *
* www.seriessub.com *
* Presents*
* Season 4 Episode 3 *
Doctor, you feeling
Anbetter?
When do i move
To a real hospital?
About that.
- You've got my results.
- It's as you thought.
Radiation specialist
Is on his way now.
I can save him
The trip.
Filgrastim for
The white blood cell count,
Potassium iodide
For the thyroid,
And promethazine hydrochloride
For the nausea
Unless you can find me
Something herbal.
They don't dispense that medication
On base.
My question is this?
Were you poisoned by the plutonium,
Or did you just get
Sloppy in the lab?
It's an occupational
Hazard.
If your occupation
Is terrorism.
I was paid to test
Their isotopes.
I'd like to
Believe you,
And we still think
That you're
A valuable asset.
sure you do,
But i don't wish
To spend my last weeks
or days
locked up In here.
Client didn't tell you how he planned
To use the plutonium?
but i gather
From what you've told me
He'll sell it to someone who plans
to make quite a large bomb.
You gather that,
Do you?
When will i be moved
To a regular hospital?
You'll have your chance to see
your mr. Petrov again.
you have broken our agreement.
You are insulting Our country.
What can i tell you,
My friend?
It happens.
When did this
Other buyer appear?
There are always
Buyers
For a product
Like this.
He is willing
To pay more.
How much more?
5 million more.
No, no. I will not
Be your stalking horse.
The free market,
My friend.
I need more time.
I'm on your side,
But petrov, he doesn't
Like to wait.
I can beat
Their offer.
I need time.
How did you like
The girl?
She served
Her purpose.
Too old?
I have a 14-year-old
If you want.
That is very
Thoughtful of you,
But i must decline.
We got no time to dummy up
A wire transfer.
What about
The agency?
We're barred from contact
With the station.
We'd do better going
from my cut-out account.
for 5 million euros?
What do we use for collateral,
my old desoto?
If the black market's
Laying out 38 mill for nukes
They already got
Their buyers standing by,
Either narco-terrorists
Or al-qaeda.
- So where do we find these new players?
- We know they're In town.
and that they're well-guarded,
sitting on all That cash?
So how did our winning ways
compete with all that cash?
Can't outspend them,
Must outthink them.
Outspend them
Or outshoot them.
Does that
Include Dragan?
Starting with dragan.
The man's scum.
Yeah, but he's
Our scum.
Besides plutonium,
He traffics in girls,
Most of them younger
Than my daughter.
If we stay with dragan,
He may lead us
To the other buyers.
Eventually perhaps.
Hold on. We don't have
To do the recon ourselves.
There are others who might want
To help us.
Others?
Those who might
Want a favor in return.
I came back for you.
I need your help.
How can i help you?
There's a man
At the bar with dragan.
I need to know something
About him and his friends,
An address.
you want me to...
I don't care how.
- But if i do this...
- Then i will Help you.
Your friend nadia,
Is she the one
Stuck to dragan's side?
Then i will get you
Both out.
One for you,
Mrs. Bechet.
Another for you,
Mrs. Dahl.
it's like
Christmas come early.
is there any
Cash in here?
asking the wrong guy.
I'm just the pony express.
Looking.
My own california
Teaching certificate.
I'm back
In the classroom.
Oh, my god.
I start this morning.
At least you won't
Have to fake it.
Vice president of marketing,
Aerodyne alliance.
I'm still waiting
To find out
What this alliance
Actually makes.
maker
what we say we make?
Aircraft engines,
Custom appliances.
our new base of operations.
Your new clubhouse.
Don't expect me
To sweep up.
Why do i feel like the girl
with the glasses
At the homecoming dance?
- i'm sure it's not deliberate.
- Everything here Is deliberate.
Taking my kids away
From me was deliberate.
there's no good
In complaining.
It's unfair.
It's unfortunate,
It's regrettable,
It's tragic,
But it's not unfair.
The army's trying
To keep us safe.
Maybe they're still
Working out your cover.
And maybe i'm better off
without one.
We're all going to
Make it through this.
- Wait up.
- I heard you, mom.
you didn't
Let me finish.
I get it.
You didn't ask for this job.
Can we talk
About this later?
look At it this way.
We're both new here.
At least now we can
Look out for each other.
I don't need
Looking after.
Just to keep our
Stories straight.
I'm not gonna blow
our cover like you almost did.
come on. Let's try and
be Nice to each other?
Look. I'll see you
After school.
Man, i am so sorry.
Really. Are you ok?
Yeah. I'm all right.
Just get to class!
This is jessica
At the agency
Confirming your
Interview this afternoon.
I'm sorry. You have
The wrong number.
Kim cahill?
It is. Yes, but--
I have your employment card
right here.
Your interview's
At 1:00.
The interview.
A wonderful couple with a teenage son
and an infant daughter.
And what exactly are
They looking for?
They need someone who can start
right away full-time.
I see, but...
They just lost their nanny,
And they're really in a bind.
A nanny.
Our old nanny quit
Out of nowhere,
Just disappeared
Without an explanation.
So above all, we really need
someone we feel we can trust.
Of course. Some people just
aren't cut out
For children.
Well, your references
Are excellent.
Looks like most of them
Are from kansas
That's right.
What brings you
To california?
My husband's company transferred
him out here.
What does he do
For work?
He's in the private aircraft business,
sales.
Unfortunately,
He travels a lot,
So that leaves me with plenty
of free time.
My wife's always
On the road for work, too.
- It's not easy with a newborn.
- No. Not easy for you.
Looks like you've had some experience
with infants.
i come from a big family
Nieces, nephews,
And a lot
Fo dirty diapers.
We also have
A 15-year-old, lucas.
- He's a real jock.
- Can't wait To meet him.
How about
This afternoon?
Excuse me?
Can you start today?
Did you get it?
Told him he was
So good
I wanted
To see him for free.
Where is he staying?
First, you help.
I need doctor.
After the doctor,
If you should run--
I cannot run.
As long as dragan
has nadia, i cannot run.
Let's go.
It works for my little
Emily, too.
Are you all right?
I'm sorry.
It's just that
My husband and i
Have been trying so hard
To have one of our own,
And she's beautiful.
I understand.
You do?
Marion and i did
Fertility treatments
For 6 years.
It's rough.
Harder than i thought.
Are you
On a protocol?
Fertility
Treatments.
I had to give marion
Shots twice a day.
We're trying everything.
- How many ccs Are you on?
- Gosh
There's so many,
I get them all confused.
It's the one
In the oil solution.
I became
A real expert.
To tell you the truth, i let
my husband be the expert.
He says, "bottoms up,"
And i don't even look.
It will work out.
You're very kind.
You know what they say.
Your children
Will find you.
I hope so.
Need any help?
No, thanks.
I'm just waiting
For my daughter.
Almost everyone's
gone home already.
- Yeah. Looks That way.
- Want me to go look for her?
No. It's ok.
No. I'd be glad to.
It's not necessary,
Josh. I didn't
Hurt you, i hope.
A little whiplash
Is all.
Oh, my god.
I'm sorry.
I'm kidding.
I had that kind of injury
last season right here.
I said it's not
Necessary.
Make you feel better.
I beg your pardon?
You never know.
I think you'll be better off
focusing Your attention
On girls
Your own age.
the girls here
are immature.
I prefer women.
Nothing like
Ambition.
For example, you.
I'm a teacher,
And you're a minor.
I'm 18.
You're not hearing Me, josh.
It's against school policy,
And it's against the law,
and it's against my wishes,
Which i have made plain,
So move on.
You don't have to be
A bitch about it.
Good-bye, josh.
you know, 10 years from now
when that face is all cracked,
You're gonna be thinking about what you
could have had.
Get out of my sight.
Someone was very rough
On that girl.
She says you're
Her boyfriend.
Just tell me
You can help her.
I can,
But it's involved.
I see. So let us
Make it simple.
I'll do what's possible.
I'm sure you will.
- Let go of her.
- She's a thief! Look!
Show him!
I will pay. I will.
- Morphine.
- Drug addict.
It's not for me,
I swear.
It's for nadia.
She has aids.
She always has pain.
Let us go.
- Who's there?
- Dragan sent me.
For his
Best clients.
Dragan saved
The best for last.
Maybe you had to
Prove yourselves.
How do you prove
Yourself?
Me?
I'm a specialist.
Good. Because i got something special
For you.
First, get me
A drink, will you?
You have
A lovely view.
We're out of ice.
Good.
I like it warm.
Where's your
Accent from?
You want small talk,
Get a girlfriend.
I don't have time
For it.
Feel good?
it's my turn.
Sure is.
Clear.
By the couch.
I got it.
Here.
They make money
The old-fashioned way.
They steal it.
I guess the bidding's
Closed.
Lucky for you
Maybe they found
Another deal elsewhere.
They didn't drop out
From the bidding.
They dropped dead.
these things
Happen, my friend,
- In a free market economy.
- But i don't think That petrov
Is gon sell you this plutonium
On the cheap.
But where i come from,
32 million is not cheap.
37 million.
That was the price.
When you had two bidders.
Now you have only the one.
One who will pay
37 million,
And they want
Your assurance
That no one else in this transaction
Drops out.
I believe
We have a deal.
I'm still not Getting the uplink.
Will you check
Your lnb connection?
Try doubling back the wire
before you hit The solder.
I got it.
Up and ready
For business here.
Great. And while you're at it,
Then we'll really get noticed.
you can put the chrome rims on.
Redcap, don't teach your grandmother
how to suck eggs.
Now we're just another
Wandering band of gypsies.
Smile, bridge,
For your home page.
Slavic lethargy.
What do you think?
How about something
A little more viral?
What do you want
Me to do, blow them a kiss.
They'll love that
In the toc.
Colonel ryan's not much
of a romantic
What?
Let's throw
This thing together.
We got half an hour
To get in place.
I just got a call
From the office.
- I have to go in today.
- You want me to stay with ella?
If you don't mind.
I'm sorry.
I thought i was gonna be able to work
From home today.
I can stay
As long as you want.
I'll watch her as if
She were my own.
Let me give you
My cell number
Just in case
You need anything.
I can't tell you
How grateful i am.
Don't worry.
Need to get used to the developmental
approach out here.
You know, if you
Ever have a problem
With the curriculum,
Feel free to stop
By my office.
would you Excuse me?
I see a student of mine
I need to speak with him.
- What are you doing?
- Going to class.
I thought you said the girls out here
Were too immature for you,
She's 16, and she is
not for you.
She's too young
For me, you're too old for me.
Let's try this.
You date who you want,
Lissy dates
Who she wants.
You're a predator,
and you're looking for a victim.
I understand.
I am not a victim.
You think i'm an easy mark,
I will correct you.
Stay away
From my daughter and me.
if you weren't making it so hard,
I wouldn't have to go that way.
Let's get this Straight.
If i find you anywhere near Lissy again,
I will make you
Regret it.
I could report you
To the principal
For using
Threatening language.
I mean, it is against school policy
and against the law.
Do you want me to take this
To the office?
What are you gonna say,
that i hit on you yesterday
And you didn't Report it immediately
As required?
And then i'd tell
The principal
That the reason you kept your
mouth shut
Was because you
Hit on me,
Threatened me
If i told anyone.
And now i have
An eyewitness.
maybe i should
Just go tell her myself,
Or
we could
work something out.
Dirt diver,
We're in place.
we're in position.
No one moves on petrov until we've got
A positive i.d.
Snake doc's
Got company.
Please.
I hope you don't mind
That i took the liberty
Of ordering
Some espresso.
Thank you.
I have 37 million
Reasons
Why we should conclude
Our business today.
I will have to see those 37 million
Reasons.
Cool breeze,
This is dog patch 0-6.
We got
A clear transmission,
But we can't get
A positive i.d.
Coming your way
Most rikki-tik.
Red cap, we're rolling.
I need
A look my way, please.
There is a location,
And we need
A little bit
Of time.
How much time?
Nyet, nyet.
Got it. Great!
Run it, print it!
Dirt diver, stand by.
We're gonna get
Your confirmation.
That him?
No. I don't
Recognize him.
That's not petrov?
I've never seen
This man before.
Dirt diver, we got
A situation.
That man with snake doctor
Is not petrov.
I repeat.
That is not our target.
We have deal?
You want, you want.
We have come
To the terms.
Let's get the package.
Hold.
How do i know that he
Is who he says?
Who do you think
I am?
I was told to deal
Only with petrov.
He's got
What you need.
That's who he is.
You lied to me!
Who is this man?
How do you know that
This is not petrov?
Because you have asked
The question.
He is not
Actually petrov.
I work for petrov.
You said petrov himself.
Where's petrov?
he is...it's just better.
He doesn't like
you know, to expose himself.
For 37 million, he can dance naked
in the square.
Until then,
No deal.
If he's delivering
A kilo of plutonium,
He''ll have it
Divided up
Into 15 to 20
Individual pigs.
Your man has
90 seconds exposure
Before
he risks radiation poisoning.
But he has to test it.
More than one pig.
Sometimes, they'll
Offer up one good sample
From a lot of
30 losers.
What's the threshold?
95% purity.
But it's good enough
To make a bomb?
Perhaps.
Perhaps?
If that kid files a complaint
with the principal
- A bogus complaint.
- Any complaint
The school is required
To open an investigation.
They'll dig Into my background,
And they'll Crack my cover,
And that opens the door
on all of us.
You need to slam
That door.
Has the boy gone
To the principal?
No, but he's got
Me in a corner,
And he knows it.
Tiffy, the first
thing you learn in combat
Is to assess the enemy's
strength.
What's ge got?
I mean, the threat.
An accusation.
The weight
Of his words.
In martial arts, we use the enemy's
own weight against him,
Make him extend himself
Until he's off balance.
So you want me
To what, throw him?
Use what he's using
Against himself.
The accusations?
And anything else you
Can bring to bear,
Anything you can
To raise him out.
To get down
On his level.
Break his will To fight.
I wasn't even doing
Anything wrong.
I don't care, Lissy.
Stay away from him.
Why?
Because
He's trouble.
Because why,
He's 18?
It's more than that.
He was the only one
who even talked to me
At school today, mom.
Remember
On the bus ride here
we were talking
about shared sacrifice,
About making compromises
For the greater good?
This is one
of those sacrifices
I'm asking you
To make,
And i wouldn't ask
If it wasn't important.
It's important.
There they are now.
Good.
I know.
petrov sent us.
And where is he?
He said he was coming.
My brother.
I'm here
As requested.
Let's make this quick.
Nato uniforms.
Smart.
It makes the border crossing
Less stressful.
Go ahead.
As promised.
Now it is your turn.
37 million
Is the price.
That was the price
Before you fixed
The bidding.
Violence draws
Too much attention.
Authorities
Must be pad off.
So
it is going
To cost you.
Me? I brought you
This money.
You also brought
This danger.
Take it from his cut.
No. He has
No more cut.
He owes me,
Or no deal for anyone.
- What do you want?
- Whatever is his.
Drugs, girls.
I am just
A small businessman.
but you of course
Have something
That you've saved
For a rainy day.
No? Fine.
You want us To find out
For ourselves?
Petrov, you don't
Want to do this.
What is this?
The cost of doing
Business.
Cool breeze, something's going down.
They got guns on snake doc.
What's with the soldiers
In the club?
I don't know.
What now?
We just
We hang back.
We want
That plutonium.
You were holding out
On us, dragan.
I will take all of the girls
as payment.
that's too far.
These girls are mine.
If you want to drop out
This deal over them, do it!
- That's enough!
- really?
Because you say so?
Let us conclude
Our business here.
Forget This business.
Forget your money.
I can find
Other buyers.
37 million, and you still
need the girls?
Well, it's
My commission.
You can't have my girls
Without paying.
I want to close
This deal.
And i'd like
To go home!
If he won't give them,
shoot them.
Wait!
- Sell me the girls.
- What?
Done. Now they're mine.
And now yours
Give me the keys.
We swap.
Fine transaction.
I hope your country
Appreciates
Your patriotism.
I hope so, too.
Tell dirt diver
Pick off the saab.
I want petrov.
I don't care how.
What about the money?
We go after the truck?
No. We can't.
We got to secure
The plutonium first.
Then we get the truck back
Push it.
- They could have crossed over by now.
- Come on. Push it!
The border's only
6 klicks out.
We can make it.
Tell snake doc
It's over.
Didn't leave me
A choice.
What about the truck?
What about the girl?
Negative. No girls
Here, doc.
We got petrov.
Good.
Did he say anything?
About you?
What do you want,
Colonel?
I want to know
Who hired you and why.
Petrov sells nuclear materials
to the highest bidder.
He doesn't care
Who wants them and why.
Nor does he hire
Academics like you.
To vet his isotopes when any
Out-of-work russian lab rat
Can do it
On the cheap.
He was paid to get you
bomb-grade plutonium,
And i'm asking you
One more time for whom.
Why don't you
Ask petrov?
Petrov's dead.
Well, so am i.
Not yet, you're not.
Save what's left
Of your life.
It's not my life
That matters now.
I made a mistake
Not coming to you first,
But being new here, I just didn't want
To be hard on the boy.
but you were clear with him
about the Sexual harassment?
In no uncertain terms.
That's why he Came after me
And threatened me
With physical violence
When i said no,
And frankly, i'm still
A little scared.
These days, You have to take
Every potential Threat seriously.
- Absolutely.
- Excuse me, mrs. Green. You're needed
Right away At the east entrance.
There's A serious situation.
Excuse me.
What happened?
- Mrs green It's not mine.
- What?
The metal detector Went off.
We found a handgun On him.
It's not mine, I swear.
I don't know how it got in there.
In the office.
Get the police Down here. Now.
Thank you.
For the greater good.
Who else got
These brochures?
They're only
For the show room.
We received a hundred
For display.
Then why does my new employer
have one?
One of those?
Are you sure?
Saw it right
On his desk.
The number
Was circled.
A voice on the phone
Tells me to interview with him,
And he's got
This in his house.
- Who is he?
- His name's Isaac reed.
He's in The import/export
Business.
Why would he have
A brochure from us
When we don't
Technically exist yet?
You know anything
More about him?
Just that his wife's
In the same company.
She travels a lot.
You haven't met The wife?
Do you think you can get
Back into his office?
I don't see why not.
He's already left
Me alone once In the house.
He trusts you.
More than that. For a man
Whose wife's Out of town,
He's a little Too friendly,
If you know What i mean.
- I think she should Call the colonel.
- Don't
It's probably
Just another test.
Maybe i wasn't
Supposed to notice The brochure,
But the better Guess
Our landing In this town
With these jobs
Is no accident.
- I don't understand.
- Neither do i,
But i'm going to.
No one.
Gone.
Over here.
Tire treads.
They switched
Vehicles.
Maybe a van.
Put the girls in there,
Drove off.
They could be
Anywhere by now.
You made the only choice
You could.
Is that right?
You had to get
The plutonium.
Think of the lives
You saved.
You had to buy the girls,
Hand them over, or else--
You know what?
Why don't you stop talking?
It doesn't help.
www.seriessub.com
The Unit Team