And her tits are, like, firm
as fuck, dude, like, firm as fuck.
Nice.
Yeah, they're totally nice.
And like...
and it's just getting hot,
I got my dick out,
it's like hard as fuck,
and, like, she's, like,
we're both, like, hot,
and, like, I' m ready for her,
she's fucking wet
and ready for me, right,
and then I got her shirt off,
I got my shirt off and shit,
and then she goes to take
her panties off, man.
She goes to take
her panties off,
and I looked down at that shit,
and I went, "Oh, shit."
I was, like, cover that shit back up.
This shit is so fuckin' nasty, man,
like she's got, like,
some nasty white shit
like drippin' out of her cunt, man.
That's fuckin' sick, man.
I know. I made her cover that shit up,
and she's like sitting there, like,
what the fuck is the problem?
Like she didn't even know
there's like this nasty yogurt shit
drippin' from her cunt.
I'm like, I' m like... the fucked up
part is, like, she's 14,
so I' m, like, thinking
where the fuck
has this girl' s snatch been
at 14, man?
Like, she's so fuckin'...
you know what I mean?
Wait a minute, wait a minute.
She's 14?
Yeah, man, 14.
Fuckin' 14?
Yeah.
Fuck that.
That's fuckin' bullshit.
Dude, she's 14.
Dude, I believe some shit
out of you... some shit.
OK? I' II buy some of your shit.
Like that story about the girl
with a fuckin' bag over her head
sucking your dick
'cause she was ugly?
I'll buy that shit, man,
but this sounds like bullshit.
It's not bullshit, man.
OK, what was her name?
It's Kate.
Kate, the fuckin' young, smelly bitch.
I don't buy it, man.
Dude, her name's fuckin' Kate.
So what are you doing
tomorrow night, dude?
I don't know.
Didn't really make any plans.
You goin' to that party
at Brian's house?
I don't know, man.
His last party was weak as shit.
Yeah, but first of all...
Waste of time.
There's gonna be free beer.
And second, it's
the Fourth of July, man.
Hey, do you think Christie's
gonna be there?
I... why?
I don't know, man.
Just asking.
You want to fuck her.
No fuckin' reason.
No, man, I was just asking.
She's not my girlfriend anymore.
If you want to fuck her,
go ahead, fuck her.
If she wants to, I mean.
Really?
Yeah, I don't care.
What are you looking at?
Huh?
Nothing.
I think they were lesbians.
Who?
Those two girls.
I don't think so.
Yeah.
No.
Sure.
How come no guys
ever check us out?
They do sometimes.
No, no one's asked me
for a phone number or anything
in such a long time.
They're just scared is all.
You think?
Gus was nice to me.
Yeah.
Because he wanted to sleep
with me, he was nice to me.
Like he'd say nice stuff
and then he'd make a move.
You know, he'd say
nice shit to me
and then I' d let him
touch me a little bit.
He'd say more nice shit,
and he'd try to work up
to a lot more than that,
and then I stopped him.
And he's all, like,
"I know you want it."
Right? I mean,
who even says that?
And he keeps trying to touch me
and I keep pushing him away and...
and then he gets mad.
He's not a nice guy.
Yeah...
but I wanted him to touch me,
I wanted to sleep with him,
I was just, like, you know,
building up to it,
like back and forth, you know?
So he gets mad for a second,
but then he's not mad anymore,
and then, uh, he's just, like,
silent for a whole minute,
and I' m sitting there thinking,
like, what the fuck is happening?
And then he turns to me
and he says, "I' m sorry."
And I still don't say anything.
So you see any fireworks
tonight, man?
Nope. Did you?
No.
Well, like, just that shit
that people were setting off.
It's fuckin' stupid, like,
all the shit that's cool
it's all illegal.
You know, all the shit
that goes up in the sky,
it's all illegal.
Anything that's cool is illegal.
Yeah, yeah.
I'd say.
Hey, do you have your eye
on any girls here tonight?
I don't know.
Did you see that Asian chick?
Yeah. Yeah, I saw her.
She's hot.
I fuckin' saw the Asian chick, dude.
Do you think Christie's
gonna be here tonight?
I don't know, man.
Lhope so.
You got a lighter or...
No, I think I fuckin' lost it.
Great.
I'll just go ask somebody.
Hey, um, do you have a lighter?
Uh, yeah.
Here you go.
Thanks.
You want a cigarette?
Sure.
So you know Brian?
Um, my friend knows him,
and she was telling me that he
has these, like, wild parties
and all this crazy shit
always goes down, but, uh...
yeah, so far...
What? What do you mean?
I don't know, it just seems
pretty lame to me.
Yeah, yeah.
I mean, I don't know, it's OK.
Yeah.
Well, um...
shit, maybe I could do something
to help you out.
Oh, yeah?
Yeah, like, uh...
I think I met you before.
You're Gus' friend, right?
Yeah, I' m Gus' friend.
I'm Gus' friend.
But did you ever hear about me?
Like, Bill?
You know, did you ever hear
about me from somebody?
Like did ever somebody say
you know this kid Bill?
Yeah, Gus has talked about you.
Gus?
Mm-hmm.
Hey.
Hey, what's up?
Aren't you burning yourself?
Naw, I' m fine.
This is a safe zone right here.
Whoa.
Check it out.
Are you sure that you're
supposed to do those inside?
Not technically, but, uh...
me and you.
Do you live here?
No, this is actually...
Brian was in there a second ago.
This is Brian's house.
Um, we go, like...
He was in my band,
um, high school.
You know what I think
about you...
What about your tattoo?
My tattoo?
Well, I got to tell you,
I was in military school
for three months
when I was in seventh grade.
Uh, it was cool you know.
Besides all the bad shit that
happened, it was all right.
And I got this tattoo
when I was out of that
military school for six years,
and it was last week,
and I fuckin' got this tattoo.
You having a good time?
It's OK.
It's OK? You should be
having a good time.
I just don't know
that many people...
That's why you
got to keep drinking.
Makes the time a lot better.
Do you dye your hair
or is it naturally blond?
No, I' m blond.
Really?
Yeah.
Come on, be honest.
I am being honest.
You OK?
It's fine.
You seem like you're really,
like, like, weird.
I don't know, you're looking
down at your beer and...
I'm not sure what you're doing.
I'm staying in...
staying in my parents' game room,
and, like, me, I could
sleep anywhere, you know,
and if it's on the floor
or on the pool table,
if it's what happens,
that's cool you know?
What?
Nothing.
It seems like you're laughing.
No, I' m not.
Well, I was thinking about
going on a cigarette run,
because I' m all out,
and I was thinking...
I was thinking, uh...
if you want to come.
Lhave some good CDs...
we could listen to.
I should stay here, actually,
'cause of Christie.
I don't want to just leave her.
It's like if I...
I know, but I' m her ride home.
Well, um, they have
really cheap cigarettes...
I think I' m gonna stay
'cause I' m her ride home.
I just... I just don't
want to leave her.
All right, well, I found...
I found this, like, weird
fuckin' awesome pot
in my brother's room.
It was, uh...
It was in his drawer, and, uh...
just a little sort of synopsis,
it's awesome,
and it'll make this party go
from boring
to fuckin' not boring
in, like, ten.
So...
I'm OK, but thank you.
You don't smoke?
I mean, I do sometimes,
but I' m Christie's ride home.
That's very responsible of you.
I respect that.
What's up, man?
What's up?
You're the kind of friend
that I wish I had.
Because my friends always
leave me places, and it sucks.
What was your name?
My name is Jessica.
All right, Jessica.
I don't want you to think
that I' m, like, hitting on you
or anything...
Are you...
Are you Missy Sanders'
older brother?
Am I
Yeah.
Um... no... well, yeah.
Um...
'Cause I was friends with her
in the fourth grade.
All right.
It's... I should really go find
my friend Christie,
'cause I haven't...
I mean, I didn't spend a lot
of the party with her, so...
What does that mean?
It means that I should go
find my friend Christie.
Hey.
Hey, Gus.
Have you guys seen Bill around?
No.
Well...
What?
I think he's with Christie.
I broke up with her...
and she broke up with me.
Hey!
How's it goin'?
Hey, what's up?
What's up? What's up?
You're back, huh?
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah.
I didn't expect to see you here.
Well, you know, I' m here.
There's a party goin' on.
Where you been?
Um... I...
I been all over, you know...
I was drivin' all over the place.
Cool.
You ever been to Nebraska?
No, no.
Well, you know how, like,
if you think of Nebraska
you can't really think
of anything that's there?
- Yeah.
- Yeah?
Yeah.
Well, there's actually
a lot of stuff there.
That's pretty cool.
So what are you doing here?
I don't know, I just...
I guess...
I really didn't know what
I was doing, and, uh...
I ran out of money, and...
I'm back, you know.
I'm just...
I uh...
lhad this job in Texas, but...
fuck.
I didn't want to stay there.
In Nebraska, all right,
in Nebraska,
there's this...
there's this road...
and it's, like, this
really long road, and it's...
after a while it turns into gravel
and I was driving
down this road, right?
This was... March.
And I' m driving
down this road, and...
and when the road ends,
it's like this state park, this...
It's like this big park,
and it seems like it's open
to the public, right?
But, like, I went into it, and it's...
There was...
Empty. It was empty,
as far as I could tell.
And...
I was walking around this park,
and I got up to, like,
the top of this hill, you know,
and it was like this one spot,
in this one direction,
I was looking out,
and for as...
like as far as I could see,
as far as I could see,
there was, like, nothing.
It was like I could see
some trees and...
I guess it was around sunset.
It was just... it was...
fuckin'...
I don't know.
There was like, I really felt like...
I really felt like...
I knew what it must have
been like to be...
really lost.
It was like...
I don't know.
It was...
- Hey.
How's it goin'?
It's OK.
Hey, you're Christie's friend,
right? Jessica?
Yeah.
I'm Gus.
We've actually met before.
Yeah.
I mean, not like officially,
just...
I've been places with Christie,
you know, where you've been.
Do you want to sit down?
I've heard a lot about you.
Really?
Yeah, Christie told me some things.
Oh...
Yeah.
She... she told me some things.
So what are you doing out here?
I was just watching fireworks.
Some people were
setting them off.
It's nice out here.
Yeah.
You remember the Fourth of July
as a kid?
I guess so.
I always thought it sucked.
Really?
Yeah.
I kind of like it now, though.
Ilike it.
You all right?
What do you mean?
I mean, you look...
like. Not so good or...
Really?
Well, I mean...
I mean...
I'm... I' m OK.
Well, you just kind of look
upset, that's all.
I'm all right.
You know.
Things are fine.
So what are you doing out here
all by yourself?
You're here.
Well, before, though.
I was watching the fireworks.
Why are you being
so nice to me?
What... what do you mean?
You're being nice to me.
I'm just being regular.
I'm not gonna sleep with you.
I wasn't thinking...
Well, if you were
or you weren't,
I'm just not, OK?
OK.
I know what people say about me.
I know what Christie said about me.
Really?
Yeah.
I start that shit, you know,
the shit about things I do.
I tell people...
I tell people a girl sucked my dick
through a hole in a paper bag.
Lhadn't heard that one.
Yeah.
No, I hadn't heard that.
Well, I guess you get a bigger
reputation than is really true.
I mean, some of it's true.
All right.
I mean, I do like...
I...
I really don't give a fuck
about your reputation.
Right.
I just think you're an asshole.
OK.
But...
Tell you what, let me start,
let me start over,
like, from scratch, OK?
All right.
Yeah, pretend like you
haven't been talking to me
for the last couple
of minutes, OK?
I want to set some stuff
straight, OK?
Hey...
Do...
Do you want to know what
Christie told me about you?
Yeah, sure.
Well, she said that, like,
at first you were, you know,
doing anything you could to, like,
try and get your dick in her,
but then, like...
Listen...
No, just wait,
just let me finish.
So that was just like at first.
But then after she stopped you,
you, like, said that, you know,
you wouldn't even touch her
if she didn't want you to
and you asked her if she
would be like your girlfriend,
like your real girlfriend,
and she just kind of
got up and left.
So did you mean it?
What?
Like not touching her?
I mean, did you mean it,
or were you just saying it?
I mean, yeah,
I guess I meant it.
Can I tell you something?
Sure.
Before I tell you, though,
you got to promise you're
never gonna tell anyone.
OK.
I mean, it's a serious promise, though.
It's something really bad.
Like I' ve never told anyone
before, like...
and I don't really know you, so...
but if you make a serious promise,
then I' II believe you.
I seriously promise.
OK.
OK, so...
I was at this party last year,
like right before school
started back again, right,
and there's this girl there,
like 14, right?
And every guy there
was looking at her,
like, every guy wanted
to get with her.
I wanted to get with her.
So, like, I see her drinking
more and more and more.
But then she, like,
she's gone for a while,
and I like, forget about her,
because there was, like, a bunch
of other hot girls there.
But the whole night it just
wasn't happening,
so, like, finally
I get really, really drunk,
like shitty drunk,
and I like, take these Vicodins,
and so I' m like totally fucked,
and I decide I' m gonna go
and head up to my buddy's room
to, like, jerk off, you know.
But I go into his bedroom,
and on the floor is this
14-year-old girl passed out,
and there's this guy in there
and he's about to get on her.
And, like, he's got her clothes off,
and he got his clothes off,
and he's... he's like
about to do it, you know,
so I like, I walk in
and I know what's goin' on
in, like, half a second.
And I' m, like, man, what the fuck
are you doing, you know?
And...
and he, like, gets up
and he, like, looks at me
and, like, buckles his shit
back up or whatever,
and then I' m like, man,
get the fuck out of here.
And so he leaves, and then, like,
so there I am standing there
with this girl passed out
on the floor,
so I like, go over to her
and I get her clothes
and, like, I put 'em back on her
and, I like, put her shoes on her,
and, like, I tie 'em back up,
and I just start to get this, like,
feeling, you know, like...
So I go over to the door
and I lock it.
And then I shake her
a little bit
to make sure she's not
gonna wake up or anything,
and then I take
like half a second, and then...
I don't know, I just, like...
took her clothes off
and I just got on her,
and I just, like, started,
you know.
And...
and I was, like, on her
for a minute, and then...
and then I stopped,
like all of the sudden
I just stopped, and...
I realize what the fuck I' m doing,
and so I go to get off of her,
and I opened my eyes,
and I look down
and I realize she's awake
and she's, like, staring
right back at me.
And...
I like, freak out,
like I back myself up
against the wall
and I' m, like, staring at her,
and she's, like, just...
she's just, like, lifeless,
like lying on the floor,
like not even moving at all,
and, like, I buckled
my shit back up
and I' m about to walk out,
and she goes,
and she goes, "Hey," and then
she's, like, sitting up now,
and she's completely still
out of it and everything,
but she's, like, sitting up
and, like, looking,
staring right at me.
And I just stare back at her,
and she says, "Hey, what
did you do to me?"
And she, like, started crying.
She just, like, started
crying and crying.
And I like, put
my arm around her and...
And then she started to...
she started to say, "I' m sorry,"
like over and over
and over again, like...
Like she wasn't really...
I don't know what...
She wasn't saying it to me,
like, she was just...
saying "I' m sorry," like she was
ashamed or something, you know.
And...
and I just blurted out,
"You can trust me.
Tell me to do anything,
I can do it," you know.
And she...
and she said,
"I don't want anything."
And so I just sat there with her
for a couple minutes,
and finally she just says,
"My name is Kate."
And then she just fell asleep.
And so I just sat there
for a couple minutes,
and then I walked out,
and that was it.
And after that I was, like...
I was, like, I was sure
I was gonna change.
I didn't want to...
like, just get laid
all the time, and, like...
fuck with people 's shit,
you know, like...
Gus...
I can do...
I can do good, like,
I can do bad...
I do bad things a lot of times,
but I' m not a bad person.
Gus...
You know how like shit happens
and, like, time goes by
and, like, you just...
like, school started up again
and that...
and it was like I just forgot
about it, like, like...
it didn't seem so close to me,
like, it's like I didn't even
do it or something, like...
Like I was telling
my buddy Bill the story,
like, the same story,
but, like, completely different
from what I told you,
like, I made up this whole story
about how this girl Kate,
she wanted to, like...
like she wanted to fuck me, and, like...
like she had this...
I made up this whole story
of, like, a completely
different situation,
but I met her, like,
I was talking about her,
I was thinking about her.
But I know what I did, like...
You know?
Do you want to go somewhere?
Sure.
Are you cold?
No.
Are you?
We've got a right!
You going down there with him?
Yes or no.
This is your last chance.
No beatin'around the bush.
Listen, I got a kid down there.
She can't possibly...
I couldn't bring her up here.
She can't possibly take
all the racket
of those things smashing
through the windows.
Well, you're her father.
If you're stupid enough
to go die in that trap,
that's your business.
I am not stupid enough
to follow you.
It is tough for the kid
that her old man is so stupid.
Now get the hell down
in the cellar.
You can be the boss down there.
I'm boss up here.
You bastards!
You know I won't open
this door again.
I mean it.
Mr. Cooper, with your help,
we could...
With my help.
Let him go, man.
His mind is made up.
Just let him go.
Wait a minute!
Judy, come on up here, honey.
Hey.
Wake up.
What?
It's almost 10.
Oh.
Get up.
Hey, Bill.
Nothin' much.
Yeah.
Aw, fine.
Ah, we didn't do it.
Yeah, yeah.
Hey...
Yeah.
Hey, man, I need
a phone number from you.
I need a phone number.
Can I get the number?
Right.
Yeah, what?
Yeah. Yeah. Cool.
Well, hey, how about
I get that number?
Wally Briggs.
You know that guy?
Hey, Wally, man, it's Gus.
Hey, man, you know that girl Kate?
Uh, yeah, Kate.
She's like 14 or 15,
she's got brown hair.
You know her last name?
You're not sure?
Uh, I was wantin' to...
I was wantin' to call her up,
see her or something, you know?
Hey, Dad.
Yeah.
I'm all right.
What are you doing right now?
Have you had breakfast yet?
Oh.
Well, what about lunch?
Hey.
Hi.
Uh... I guess you don't know me.
Um...
Have we met before?
Kind of.
I mean, uh...
we met at a party.
Oh.
Like a year ago, so...
Oh, OK.
What's up?
Uh, nothing, I was just, um...
I was in the area,
so I thought I' d stop by
and see if you were home.
All right.
Well...
OK.
Do you want to come in
or something and watch TV?
Sure, yeah.
Are you thirsty?
Uh...
For...
Do you want something to drink,
like a Coke?
No, no, thanks.
I'm gonna have one.
I could get you one, too.
OK, sure, if you're
gonna have one.
Thanks.
So what's been up?
Um...
not much, I guess.
Just hangin' out?
Pretty much.
Cool.
What do you like to do?
I don't know, just hang out
with my friends.
Nothing, really.
Ilike your ring.
Thanks.
Ilike yours, too.
Is it plastic?
Yes.
So...
did you ever have
a boyfriend, like, before?
Yeah.
How long, uh...
how long was that?
- A long time.
- A long time?
Yeah.
Like... over a year or...
Yep.
What happened with that?
We don't really have to talk
about that.
Unless you really, really
want to know.
Yeah. Something, I guess.
So has anything, like, really bad
ever happened to you?
Like what?
I don't know. Like anything.
Anything bad happen to you?
No.
I was just curious.
OK.
No?
Uh... no.
That's good.
Yeah.
Hey, Bill, what's up?
Man, I saw some
fucked-up shit today.
Yeah?
Yep. On the train.
This old lady bleeding
out of her nose,
like bleeding everywhere.
Shit.
All over the place.
No, seriously,
all over the place.
Fuckin' everywhere,
and everyone was looking.
That's fucked up.
Yeah.
What did you do today?
Nothing. I just messed around,
you know, whatever.
Yeah.
I'm sorry about the phone, man.
The phone?
Yeah, you know, I was kind of
being a dick, I guess.
Aw, man, it's cool.
No sweat.
Cool.
No sweat at all.
You seeing Christie tonight?
Yeah, I' m gonna see her
in a little bit.
She coming here?
No, we're going to meet up
at Stevens Amusement Park.
Really. Cool.
Hey, do you want to go?
Sure.
Cool man. You gonna see, uh...
Jessica soon?
I don't know.
Yeah, she's kind of a bitch anyways.
Yeah.
Yep.
Why do you say that?
Aw, I don't know, man,
you know, like...
she just seems like a total bitch.
Like what about her, though,
I mean...
Aw, man, I don't know.
Nothing in particular. Whatever.
Do you ever think maybe, uh...
What?
Nah...
Never mind.
What?
I'm pretty drunk, man, like...
You know what?
One time I got so drunk
and I was so fuckin' hungry...
And I' m not talking
about normally
when you get drunk
and you get hungry,
like, you know,
normally food sounds,
like the sickest shit in the world.
But I was so hungry...
I'm kind of hungry
right now, dude.
Yeah, me, too.
You know what shit fucks me up?
What?
The clit.
The clit?
You know, like, these girls
are always like,
"Touch my clit," you know,
"rub my clit,
I want you to rub my clit,"
you know, like,
I'm like, "Suck my dick."
I just want you to suck my dick.
You know?
Totally, man.
That's bullshit.
What the fuck.
Ilike saying "slut," though.
Yeah. Yeah, I guess.
You know, the word "slut."
Yeah.
Slut.
Bitch.
Slit, clit, fuck, bitch.
Cunt, cunt, cum, fuck...
Gus, Gus.
I don't know, it's kind of...
I don't know.
I get so fucked up, man, like...
You know, you ever get totally,
like, like, like fucked?
Right now.
No, not drunk.
Not drunk, though.
Oh.
I mean, like...
you know, like, fuckin' fucked
about shit that goes on,
like, uh...
Yeah, I guess.
Like you ever think about going
into photography, man?
No!
Like painting or, like, fuckin'...
studying insects or something,
you know?
I mean, I know it's
like fag shit or whatever,
but, like, you know...
That's all I' m trying to say.
But I mean what the fuck,
why not, right?
I don't know, man.
I guess.
What... no.
I don't know.
You don't know?
No. Whatever.
It's OK, though.
I mean...
Ilike Jessica, man.
Tits.
No, not her tits, man,
like not her ass or tits
or fuckin' hair or whatever.
Not her tits?
I mean, they're fine, man,
but, like...
Ilike... I like her, you know.
I really like her.
Cool man.
No, I mean I really like her,
you know?
Yeah, whatever.
It's cool.
But I don't want to fuck
with her shit.
Yeah.
You know, like shit we do,
you know,
like, it fucks with shit,
you know?
Yeah, I guess so, man.
I see where you're going,
I see what you're saying.
You know, like, I feel
really bad, feel like...
Dude...
If there's one thing I' ve learned,
it's not to feel bad...
about anything.
Don't do it to yourself, man.
Thanks.
You want to give me a hug, man?
What?
Ahug.
Fuck you, man.
I'm just saying, man,
what are you talking about?
Ahug?
Just give me a fuckin' hug.
No. I' m not giving you a hug.
No.
Just a fuckin'...
Fuck you, bitch.
Gimme a hug.
Get over here.
Thanks.
You're a good friend, man.
Yeah, I know.
You know what I think about
sometimes, man?
What?
Like, OK, like,
before something happens,
there's a chance for anything,
you know?
Like... um...
Like what?
Like, OK, for instance, before
we go to this park here,
you could go on any
of the rides, right?
Yeah. But I' m gonna go on
the Mummy's Revenge, dude.
Right. OK, right.
But I mean, like...
There's a chance for anything,
like anything could happen.
Yeah, anything could happen,
but I' m going on the Mummy's Revenge.
Right. I know you're going
on the Mummy's Revenge.
OK.
But, like, you know,
what if you didn't go
on the Mummy's Revenge?
What if something happened, like...
The point is, like, anything
could happen, like...
it's not... it's not set in stone
until you, like, actually do it.
You know... because it hasn't
happened, you know?
I guess. Yeah, man.
I don't know.
What are you doing
on your birthday?
'Cause I have
a really good idea.
I don't know.
I was thinking we should go
to all the stuff you'll be able to do
'cause you're 18 and all,
you know?
Buy scratch -offs and shit?
Yeah, like buy scratch -offs,
go to the porn store,
buy cigarettes legally.
Yeah.
So where you meeting
Christie at?
One of those corn dog stands
over there.
Oh. You think she's here yet?
I don't know.
Maybe not.
Yeah.
You like Christie, man?
Well, I guess I' m gonna leave
you guys alone for a while.
I'm gonna walk around by myself,
I think, just a little bit.
You sure, man?
Yeah, yeah.
You OK?
Yeah, I' m fine.
It's all good.
All right, man.
Come find us later.
All right, I' II find you later.
- Hey.
- Hey!
What's up?
Nothing. What are you doing?
I'm here with Bill.
He's meeting up with Christie.
Yeah, I know.
You're here with Christie?
Yeah.
Can I tell you something?
What?
It's kind of stupid.
That's OK.
I'm a little drunk right now.
That's fine.
Just to let you know.
It's OK.
I know it's kind of early and all,
but, you know...
Wow.
Do you want to take
some pictures?
Uh, like together?
Yeah, together.
Oh, yeah.
Sure, yeah.
Do you have three dollars?
I think I got, like...
I got, like, two.
I think I' ve got one.
You got one?
You want to split it with me?
Goddamn machine.
Come on...
I don't think it works like that.
Oh, maybe it does. Wow.
All right... all right.
Are you ready?
Ready?
Yeah.
Three, two, one...
Smile!
OK, OK...
Picture two.
Ready?
Three, two, one...
Smile!
Picture three.
Ready?
Three, two, one...
Smile!
We got one more?
Ready?
Three, two, one...
Smile!
Here we go.