Last week on Wild Palms:
I want you to set up an exchange.
The chip for Deirdre.
He killed Grace.
He's got my daughter.
You've got to tell the senator
about the Go-chip.
One day, I'll put out the sun...
...and make bare
every womb there ever was.
You wanna be a samurai, Harry?
Now's your chance.
I want you to put this on live feed.
Turn it off!
This is for Grace Wyckoff!
Come on! Move it!
Our fearful trip is done
The ship has weather'd every rack
The prize we sought is won
I'd like to acknowledge the efforts
of one among us.
Harry Wyckoff.
How does it feel
to be a leader, Harry?
Viva Zapata.
You wanna know how I really feel?
Sick.
Violated.
Like I killed Grace a second time
on television.
It got results.
Eli, they should have moved you right
from the Perceptory to Channel 3.
You would've made a hell
of a programmer, you know that?
It was a terrible thing, Harry,
but it opened people's eyes.
Grace would have demanded that.
Don't tell me what Grace
would've demanded.
You don't know anything about her.
- What do you want from me?
- Deirdre.
Kreutzer said he would give her back
if we gave him the Go-chip.
- I can't do that, Harry.
- Why?
Because with the chip,
he'll be immortal.
A holographic vampire,
unstoppable from some unspeakable...
...unreachable place.
He'll organize the death of the world.
You're as crazy as he is!
- Oh, listen to me Harry.
- No, listen to me!
I'm gonna have my family back...
...one way or the other.
Do you understand that, Eli?
And those are my politics!
And you can go to hell.
And then, now I'd like
to say a few words.
Hello
I must be going
I cannot stay
I came to say, I must be going
I'm glad I came, but just the same
I must be going
What is it, doc?
A heart attack or indigestion?
Stress of the last few days.
You're acutely hypertensive.
- I'd like to put you in Cedars.
- No.
- No hospitals.
- I can't force you.
I'm gonna medicate you.
I want you to stay in bed.
No alcohol or Mimezine.
You're no fun. Grindrod.
What about the Go-chip?
If I can get your pressure under control
you've got maybe a week or so.
After that, I can't say
what your body will tolerate.
A week, huh?
Grindrod!
Why haven't you bailed Josie?
We're trying.
My sister? In jail?
What's the matter with you?
Get her out if you have
to break her out!
We'll never contain this, Papa.
It's a fiasco.
Where's the murder tape?
Being treated at the lab.
Even the die-hard New Realists
think Josie's guilty.
They're running scared.
Then straighten them out.
You knew Harry was going to bust
into Channel 3, didn't you?
No.
You knew he was going
to use that tape.
Why, Paige?
Am I a handsome man?
Am I a virile man?
- Answer me.
- Tony, please.
Am I...
...a decrepit cuckold?
Stop it.
You were supposed to come back
with the Go-chip.
Instead you brought
a plague to my house.
You're hurting me.
Hello
I must be going
I cannot stay
I came to say I must be going
I'll go back.
I'll get Harry to hand it over.
I assure you...
...I did not come all this way
to die like a trapped wolf!
Like a circus dog!
I am a soldier!
I am mustering my troops...
...and we are storming heaven!
- Why'd you kill her, Josie?
- How'd you make bail?
- I didn't kill anyone.
- There was a doctored tape.
A fabrication.
In a few days we'll prove it.
Is your brother gonna choose
a new running mate?
- Will he drop out of the campaign?
- Absolutely not. Why should he?
- What's your defense?
- Not guilty.
But the whole country saw
you murdered you daughter.
Seeing is believing.
You must be kidding.
- One more question, Josie.
- Will there be a statement from you?
When will the tape be ready?
- Tonight.
- And the Go-chip?
I'm assuming Harry Wyckoff has it
in his possession.
Get word out in the Wilderzone.
If he doesn't turn it over
within 48 hours...
...we'll kill the little girl.
Honey? I'm home!
Coty's room.
I always wanted to see
what his room looked like.
It would have been mine.
Help me out, Peter.
Why did the Fathers take you
from Grace and me?
- What do you know?
- They steal children...
...dreams, memories.
A regular fire sale.
When they say, "Everything must go,"
they aren't kidding.
Why me?
Why my family?
You really don't know, do you?
Let's talk to the source.
Wild Palms?
Should we take the car or the pool?
Schenkl. How could I have been
so stupid?
How did they get Josie out?
When are we releasing the tape?
Tomorrow morning.
CNN, all the networks.
Channel 3 will run it
round the clock.
Do you think I should do
a feature during hiatus?
- Deirdre.
- No, wait. Wait.
Hi, sweetie.
Hey, Dad, can we see the tape?
Tabba, take Deirdre to the house.
Come on, little darling.
Tabba is gonna read you a story.
My God.
Please don't hit me, Harry!
You're just like your mother.
Don't look.
Get up!
What are you gonna do with me?
The Fathers must be stopped.
- And you're one of them.
- No!
I'm just a woman.
But the Fathers are good, Harry.
They want to bring freedom
of images to the people.
As leader of the Friends,
I must set an example.
- You must die.
- No, please, Harry. Don't hurt me.
Long live the Friends.
Death to New Realism.
Long live the revolution.
- The images are no-good.
- Get out of here.
The images don't hold.
You're diluting the images.
- Help you out today?
- No, thanks.
Got some kung fu,
some Johnny Carson.
Some bloopers
from Church Windows.
How about some holotropics?
Fugu just flown in.
- I got some Mimezine, Imagithol-
- Not today.
Say, you're the painter, right?
Sorry to hear about your friend.
Awful what happened.
We're seeing more
and more of that these days.
They call it image sickness.
I don't approve of drug dealers.
I don't even like the way you smell.
- Save your condolences.
- You know, I've been looking for you.
- Get the hell out of my face.
- You've got friends in high places.
They heard about your loss.
They made something for you.
To get you through the night.
It's your friend Tommy.
Come inside. I'll play it for you.
Come on, Twenty-Twenty,
you're gonna like what you see.
Continuing violence
in the wake of today's...
...allegations of doctored holotapes
and conspiracy.
A Channel 3 engineer has been
arrested in the bizarre case...
...and Harry Wyckoff, the disgruntled
head of business affairs...
...turned revolutionary, is now being
sought in the murder of his wife.
Only one week ago,
the nation was shocked...
...when Church Windows
was interrupted by a-
- Get up!
- Please don't hit me, Harry.
You're just like your mother.
I'm worried about my brother.
- Emotionally?
- Physically.
I talked to the doctors.
What if his body
rejects the Go-chip, Tobias?
What if it kills him?
It's all been
the emperor's new mind?
Never gonna happen.
You know your brother, Josie.
He hasn't come this far
just to let a little thing...
...like the body get in his way.
What will the senator be like
after the transference?
Ghostly.
He'll look like himself?
Like a hologram.
He'll be able to reach
into our dreams.
By then, half the world
will be on Mimezine.
He'll be like Christ.
This better be good.
It's Mr. Wyckoff on the holophone.
Well, well.
If it isn't America's most wanted.
Well, I hope I didn't catch you
at a bad time.
I wanted to tell you...
...you did a hell of a job
on that tape of Grace and me.
I knew you'd appreciate it.
The television programmer in me
was screaming:
"This could be a hit!"
Kill a mystery guest off every week.
Start historically.
One week, kill Caesar.
The next, Hoffa.
"Death to New Realism.
Long live the revolution. "
Who wrote that dialogue? Did you
think someone would believe it?
Does it matter?
We're already climbing again
in the polls.
Don't you get it?
No one gives a damn.
I want my daughter back, Josie.
Does the senator still
wanna make a deal?
- You have it?
- The Go-chip?
- Tell me where to bring it.
- Japantown.
Sunday, 4:00.
The Festival of the Ghosts.
Schenkl, you sick animal.
Don't project on me, Harry.
All those years...
You used everything I told you.
How many died?
If I ever get my hands on you,
Schenkl...
...I'm gonna just rip your neck out!
Oh, please, Harry,
stop the adolescent posturing.
Four o'clock, Sunday. Ciao.
What's this?
The Go-chip.
When they took it from your hand,
we embedded it in the coating.
The wedding band
that Josie gave me.
- I like the irony.
- Why now, Eli?
The word on the street is...
...that someone's gonna hit
the senator. Soon.
Tell them I don't want anything
to happen to him until I get Deirdre.
- I can't control that.
- Well, you've got to try.
What's the matter?
- What?
- It's the Mimezine.
Schenkl must have overdosed you
at the Perceptory.
Choko! Now, come on,
I still have some of the antigen.
Who is that sitting on my bed?
It feels like you.
Smells like you.
Is it a horror?
To be gotten through the night
by something made at Mimecom?
Is it a horror?
Hey, Tully, come on.
Stop painting, will you?
We're gonna be late.
It's the Fourth of July. They're making
bonfires on the beach.
If there is a God, forgive me.
For I am lonely, and I am blind.
Hold me.
Tommy?
Tully, come on.
Stop painting, will you?
- We're gonna be late.
- Tommy, don't leave me.
They're making bonfires
on the beach.
Tommy.
I need more tapes.
Hey, Twenty-Twenty, back so soon?
You gonna start paying
for these, Twenty-Twenty?
I'm strapped today, maybe next time.
I'm out of Tommy tapes.
Don't cut me off!
- You'll get your money today.
- I said, I'm out.
Look, a friend of yours
came by today.
I think she might be able
to help you.
Who?
A lady, said she'd be over
at the Mimoplex.
I think she got some tapes.
She'll fix you up, Twenty-Twenty.
Fix you up real good.
Sarah, it's Rauch.
You need help.
You can't hide
in the Wilderzone forever.
Leave me alone!
Let me in, Sarah.
They're looking for you.
- They' re gonna kill you.
- Liar.
- I don't believe you.
- Hello, Tully.
- Don't panic, I'm not going to hurt you.
- You...
You really see with those things.
Yes.
- And with the Mimezine.
- Phenomenal.
I'm so glad.
I brought some
Tommy tapes for you.
Very high quality.
I thought it would be better
I gave them to you myself.
That disgusting girl in the Wilderzone
keeps diluting the images.
That's why you can only
watch them once.
Why are you doing this?
I'm making amends.
There is something
you could do for me.
I've been looking for Eli Levitt.
No.
I understand he's preparing
to assassinate my brother.
Don't make me.
I love my brother very much.
As much as you love Tommy.
He's in the Wilderzone.
That's where you'll find Eli Levitt.
I'm giving you one more chance.
I'm gonna give you
all the tapes that you need.
Don't do it, Harry.
Give me a reason, Tobias.
There are still things you need
to know. Don't do it.
Everything I need to know
is in my right hand.
If you kill me,
you'll never see Deirdre again.
It's not safe for you
to be out and about.
Nothing's gonna happen to me
as long as I have the Go-chip.
Why don't you lay down
on the couch, Harry.
- Just like old times.
- Shut up.
Tell me what you know
about the Go-chip.
What will happen
when I give it to the senator?
- He will become immortal.
- Impossible.
Do you know what paradise is,
Harry?
No longer encumbered by the body.
Whatever you imagine
is made real before you.
That's the Go-chip.
What your father, Dex,
only dreamed about.
You're insane. All of you!
Too many of us now, Harry.
Synthiotics is worldwide.
When the election is over...
...we will enslave
those who aren't with us.
In a thousand Manzanars.
What's the matter, Harry?
Cat got your mind?
Are you okay?
What happened?
They found you in the 'Vette
on the street.
What happened to you?
Oh, just a heavy session
with my shrink.
- Choko's been working on you.
- That's comforting.
She says you have the sickness,
but you're not gonna die.
Terrific.
Does the senator know you're here?
I couldn't stay with him anymore.
You know, I can go for a major martini
right about now.
Do you have any green olives?
No alcohol.
Okay. Okay.
Yes.
Oh, she's a scary thing, isn't she?
It's good to see you.
Why the double ring?
It's a long story.
Let's get out of here.
Where?
Need to see some blue sky.
I open my eyes in the morning...
...and I think,
"Is what I'm seeing real?"
That's my first thought of the day.
What's real, Paige?
Can you tell me?
Deirdre's real.
Peter's real.
We are.
- Do you feel like traveling?
- Yes.
You know, we could fly away
somewhere.
Or live in a big old house
up in the mountains.
That's what Grace
always wanted to do.
I wanna find a Norman Rockwell-type
town, you know.
With maple trees and park benches
and shiny red fire engines.
A decent place.
Where people respect reality.
Ask her if this can also be used
for image sickness.
Get in there!
Come on! Move it!
I've been searching for you.
Shotgun wedding, Josie?
More a baptism.
Know who told me
where to find you?
Your old artist-in-arms,
Tully Woiwode.
- I don't believe that.
- Scout's honor.
Called me up, all by himself.
Even told me about the Go-chip.
Hidden in the wedding ring
I gave you.
Is nothing sacred, Eli?
- You won't win, Josie.
- Hungry, Eli?
You'll love the food here.
Soup's a little watery.
You're sick.
You didn't think I'd let you
kill my brother, did you?
Show Mr. Levitt to his table.
Get up.
I'll see you in hell, Josie.
I was going to suggest some wine,
but I don't think it's a good idea.
One should never drink and drown.
And you are
the designated drowner.
Goodbye, Eli.
It could have been so good with us.
So good.
They went up overnight.
Thousands of them.
Start the revolution without me.
- What time is the rendezvous?
- Four o'clock.
Harry, I wanna come.
- No.
- I'm still the senator's wife.
They'll be less likely
to pull anything if I'm there.
Schenkl.
Where's my daughter?
Let's go!
Let's go! Let's go!
- Do we leave the girl?
- No! Change of plans.
Move! Move!
Deirdre!
Are you okay?
- Yeah.
- You're bleeding.
- The ring.
- What?
Eli's ring. And the Go-chip.
They got the Go-chip.
Damn it!
The whole world is watching!
The whole world is dreaming!
The whole world...
Harry, Eli's dead.
They've called a war meeting
at MacArthur Park.
They're going to attack Channel 3
and the lab at Mimecom.
Where's the senator?
There's a surgical suite at Wild Palms.
That's where they did the procedure.
I'm going to get Deirdre.
I'll come back for you and Peter.
I've come all this way for you.
I'm not gonna be left behind.
Not now.
- Where's Tully?
- No one knows.
We're afraid he's been picked up.
- Come on.
- Come on!
Hello, Tully. Been a long time.
Probably not feeling too good
about yourself.
After what they did to Eli.
I am asking you to kill me.
I saved your father's life once...
...now you can cash me out.
This isn't Vegas, Tully.
Eli Levitt was my friend.
I am lower
than the lowest of animals.
You want redemption
for what you did, don't you?
There is a way...
...to pay back the woman
who did this to you.
You'd like that, wouldn't you, Tully?
You know what to do.
Now get me to the chopper
and take me to Wild Palms.
My sister's waiting for me.
- signs the campaign of
Senator Kreutzer is crumbling...
...as support grows for the fugitive
Harry Wyckoff.
Wyckoff released copies of his late
wife's diary to the media earlier today.
Diaries which support growing
allegations of murder, torture...
...and New Realist mind control
in the corridors of Mimecom.
- Sporadic violence continues-
- Yes, we'll come. Right away.
What is it?
Your brother underwent
the procedure.
He was supposed to wait for me.
- I wanted to be there.
- Something went wrong.
It seems Harry got the chip
to the boy, Peter.
He tampered with it.
Chickie taught him some tricks.
I have to go to him.
You blind fool.
What do you think you're doing?
Tully, please.
What a strange world.
So dramatic.
So predatory.
Don't kill me.
Not now.
Just when everything
was going so well.
Tully...
...we're like two old generals.
Yin and yang.
Jewel and the lotus.
I respect you.
Please, Tully.
Tell me what you want.
Once, I was a painter.
Mixing colors together was an ecstasy.
I lived for light.
Then one day...
...a woman tore the eyes
from my skull.
I can give you things.
With new technology,
things you can't imagine.
Beyond seeing.
Once, I was a painter.
Then one day,
my beloved Maisie was dead.
Isn't it strange?
Everything you could dream of...
...right in your grasp.
- It's over.
- No.
Who would have thought?
Do it.
I don't like this, Harry.
It's too quiet. I don't trust him.
It's all right.
Kreutzer has gotta be weak.
That's if he's alive at all.
Harry?
Is that you?
Yes, senator, it's me.
I knew you were coming.
That's why I sent them all away.
This is Mount Olympus now.
Mortals will not be tolerated.
- I've made an exception for you.
- There's something wrong with him.
Some hours ago...
...I received the Go-chip implant.
- How do you feel?
- They said it couldn't be done.
"Do not pass go," they said.
"Do not collect $200."
I wanna talk to you.
We never talked enough.
That was my fault.
Now we have all the time
in the world.
How well did you know my mother?
We enjoyed each other's company.
Bernice and I.
Dex wasn't too thrilled.
We had a child together,
did you know?
Dex thought it was his.
Named the boy "Harry. "
He found out. Dex did.
He tried to kill me.
I had to defend myself.
Why didn't you tell me
instead of this insane charade? Why?
The garden is filled with lies, Harry.
Little lies.
Thousands over a lifetime,
like lilies of the field.
My lies are Mimecom's.
State-of-the-art, for the masses.
You took Peter...
...my son, away from me.
You took everything from me
that I loved.
Tell me why.
Do you know what the unicorn does
when it's surrounded by hunters?
Tell me why,
you psychotic son of a bitch.
It somersaults into the nearest abyss,
breaking the fall with its horn.
You destroyed Coty.
Your brother, Coty.
It's rather like an Arabian tale,
isn't it, Harry?
You made a monster out of that boy!
What's happening?
Oh, my God.
We altered the chip.
Peter and I.
My son.
If there was time...
...I would tell you all
about your mother and me.
I would tell you things
only the wild palms know.
Can't feel my legs.
Ain't that the craziest thing?
Hello
I must be going
I cannot stay
I came to say, I must be going
Don't you leave. Not yet!
I'm glad I came, but just the same
- I must be going
- You ruined everything.
You ruined everything
that you touched.
What's the matter?
Wasn't this world enough for you?
I'll stay a week or two
You didn't have to run to paradise...
...Father!
Paradise is here!
Here, damn it! Here!
Paradise is right here!
I'll stay the summer through
But I am telling you
I must be going
Coward.
I could have loved you.
This is the way the world ends.
Not with a bang...
...but a whimper.
Harry, look!
Did you speak to Father?
- In the living room.
- Living room?
Funny, his body's
in the guesthouse.
You know,
I talked to him a while too.
Then he floated over the roof
like a Chagall.
It's over now.
Easy for you to say.
- Hello, Mother.
- Coty, let us go.
You're very James Bond today,
Mother.
She was always
in awe of Pussy Galore.
Hey, stay away!
All this time...
- ... I find out we're brothers.
- Harry Wyckoff, this is your life.
Look, our father is dead.
I'm taking Deirdre.
Why don't you come with us
and leave all this behind.
That's what Daddy wanted.
To leave everything behind.
And look what happened.
- It's Little Boy Blue.
- Peter, stay back!
I wanted to be here
with you and Deirdre.
That's where I belong.
How poignant.
What are you gonna do, Coty?
Kill us all?
Deirdre's watching.
What do you think she sees?
You think she wants to
stay with you?
Hey, she loves me.
The great child guru of Synthiotics,
a monster.
How can she love a monster?
Hey, don't you talk to me that way.
Deirdre, come to Daddy.
Leave her alone.
If you love Deirdre so much...
...let her make up her own mind.
She wants to stay with me!
She loves me. I know she does.
- Dierdre, come to me.
- I'll shoot.
In front of your baby sister? You're
gonna make a hell of a role model.
I'm sorry, baby.
For letting them destroy you,
I'm so sorry.
I'll kill you dead, Mama.
You wouldn't hurt me.
Give me the gun.
Mother...
- ... who am I?
- Give me.
Watch it!
Daddy!
Come here, baby.
Come here.
- Oh, are you all right?
- Yeah.
It's over.
Let's go.
Poor men have grown to be rich men
And rich men grown to be poor again
For I am running to Paradise
The wind is old and still at play
While I must hurry upon my way
And I am running to Paradise
My Captain!
Our fearful trip is done
The ship has weather'd every rack
The prize we sought is won
O Captain! My Captain!
Our fearful trip is done
The ship has weather'd every rack
The prize we sought is won
O Captain! My Captain!
Our fearful...
Where will we go?
I'm gonna take you to the tunnels
at the beach, where Chickie lived.
You'll be safe there.
I want you to be with the children.
What will you do?
I'll have to go back.
They need me.
Remember when you told me, Paige,
about a thousand years ago...
...that you wanted
a world...
...where you can keep
your dreams open at night?
O Captain! My Captain!
Rise up and hear the bells
The Fathers have fallen!
She talked back there.
Did you hear her?
You're safe now.
Daddy?
Yeah, baby? What is it?
There's so much I want to tell you.
There'll be lots of time, honey.
Lots of time.