- You all right, sir?
- Yes.
So what are you doing here
at 4:00 in the morning?
I'm a cop.
- Got a badge?
- Was a cop, I'm leaving town.
I just thought I'd stand here
for a while till I went.
That your car?
-What division you work out of?
-Downtown, Homicide.
- Who runs it?
- Captain Cronjager.
I can smell booze on you.
I'm waiting to sober up.
Want me to drive you home in
your car?My partner can follow us.
I'll wait till I'm sober.
Okay.
Where you from?
Where you headed?
Massachusetts.
Massachusetts?
All the way to Massachusetts?
You gotta be kidding me, mister.
Massachusetts?
Paradise, Massachusetts is
a long way from home.
But it's been my home for 20 years.
In many ways, this town and I
grew up together.
I've appreciated the opportunity
to serve as your police chief
- and I tried never to forget...
- It's a sad day.
...that the trust
you so generously placed in me
had to be earned.
Not once,
but every day.
So, as I move on,
I just want to say
thank you.
So...
Before I start crying,
does anyone know a good joke?
So, this guy takes
his old dog to the vet
and he says, "Doc, it looks
like it hurts when he pees. "
Doc says, "How old is he?"
Guy says, "Twelve. "
Doc says, "He's peed enough. "
Not funny, huh?
Are you all right?
Going far?
Long way.
I don't see why you feel
the need to work.
I like it. It gives me
a sense of independence.
Is that new police chief
coming this week?
Yeah, from California.
That's a long away.
Why is Lou retiring anyway?
He's a relatively young man.
I don't know.
He said he's fed up with the job.
He's put his 20 years in.
Don't you have to be at the bank?
I can go to work when I want.
That'll look good on you.
Why don't you come back to bed?
I can't. I'm going to be late.
Sorry.
I've always wanted to drive
across country.Take the back roads.
I got nothing better to do.
What if you don't get the job?
Where are you?
Missouri, I think.
What's that noise?
I'm in a phone booth.
The phone in my room doesn't work.
It's raining.
You drinking?
Yes.
You need to be
carefuI of that.
I know.
Am I losing you, Jesse?
There's some danger of it, Jenn.
Tequila Sunrise.
Hi.
You come here often?
What's your sign?
Is there a hidden camera in here?
Gee, I was sure that would work.
My name's Sandy.
- And you are?
- Jesse.
I'm a student here.
I don't figure you for one.
Grad student.
Okay. I'm not in school.
-What do you do for a living,Jesse?
-I'm an insurance adjuster.
So, are you working on a case or
you have a thing for college girls?
- Both.
- I'm one.
- A case or college girl?
- Both.
And what do you do, Sandy?
I already told you,
I'm a student.
You're kind of old for me.
Everybody says that.
You want to go someplace?
That's a very nice offer, Sandy,
but I'm already going someplace.
I admire your spirit.
You know, just...
Take all the back roads,
get in the car and just drive.
I mean, I think it's great.
Fifty grand.
Lou.
It's the end of it.
Hasty, is there any other way?
No, there's no other way. Listen,
I just can't afford you anymore.
- We already picked your replacement so...
- You're just gonna have to pay him.
No, why would I?
The guy's pathetic, he's a loser.
He's just looking for a nice quiet place
to hide, and I'm gonna give it to him.
Yeah, well, he just might not be
the answer to that...
You know what? It's not your
problem. Don't worry about it.
Just forget about us,
forget about this town.
Hey.
Gonna miss you.
Go find what's at the end
of that rainbow, all right?
What time is it there?
10:45.
It's 7.;45 here.
That would be my guess.
-What are you wearing tomorrow?
-I don't know.
Wear your blue suit.
You look so handsome in it.
I wasn't telling you, Jesse.
I'm thinking about
going into therapy.
Well, do me a favor, Jenn.
If you see a shrink,
see a real shrink.
Not some idiot who reads your
aura and does crystal therapy.
I'm just so mixed up about things.
My career, and you, and me...
And Elliott.
I don't want to talk to you
when you're like this!
I made a mistake, but I don't see
why I should be singled out for it.
Everyone's goofed
off around here.
The Caine's a slack ship.The men
act like a pack of cutthroats,
the decks look like
a Singapore junk.
I take it, then, that you must
also strongly disapprove of leave.
Go ahead, Keith,
man to man.
Sir, I'm in no position
to approve or disapprove.
I only know that my conception of
a captain seems different from your own.
I'll take it
under advisement.
Since you feeI so bitter,
perhaps what's in the dispatch
will brighten your day.
As you can see, Keith,
I'm being relieved of command.
What are you looking at?
You're welcome.
Obviously, you know,
we think your resume is impressive
or you wouldn't be sitting here.
So this interview is
basically a formality.
But I am head of town council,
so I guess it's my job to ask.
We talked to your Captain...
- Cronjager.
And he speaks well of you, but...
He fired me for being
drunk on the job.
He said he thought it might
have something to do
with problems in your marriage.
I guess I did go off the deep end
for a bit, but I'm fine now.
So, it wasn't an ongoing thing,
you just went through a rough patch
in your marriage and you needed
a drink. I've been there myself.
You know, when a man like you with your
record applies for a job like this...
I just think you had a few
too many drinks, I mean...
Most of us would have done the same
thing under the circumstances.
I don't have a problem
here, do you, Lou?
No problem, Hasty.
You make sure you give
these to the kids.
I'm gonna miss you, Lou.
What's the new guy like?
He seemed nice,
-except he smelled like a brewery.
-You're kidding me.
Hi!
Hey, Jesse, this is Molly Crane.
Molly, this is Jesse Stone,
your new chief.
- Nice to meet you, Molly.
- And you.
This is Boomer.
Well, I was just packing up
a few things. I'll...
Don't let me run you out.
As a matter of fact,
I'd like to talk to you if I could.
Sure. Please.
Weird sitting here.
Is this a first-name department?
- Has been.
- Good.
- How you feel about retiring?
- Relieved.
- You didn't like being chief?
- Not really.
Pay's not worth the aggravation.
Tell me about the aggravation.
You, you're used to
a big force, big city.
Here, you're an employee
of the town.
And sometimes the
town and the police
don't exactly agree
on how things should get done.
That's exactly what I'm used to.
So, what're you going to do?
I was going to throw the fishing rod
in the back of the car and drive.
Never did that before.
Always wanted to.
Mr. Stone, it's your new boss.
Just press the lighted button.
Change your mind?
Listen, Jesse, we're having a little
fundraiser at our yacht club Saturday.
I think you should be there.
- I will be.
- Good.
Well, good luck.
Thank you, Lou.
Here's Lou Carson's badge and gun.
They belong to the department.
Thanks, but I got my own gun.
I will need a permit.
Yes, you will.
And I guess I'll need
some business cards.
Well, I think you
should get some.
What exactly do you do, Molly?
I'm a police officer.
Actually, most of the time,
I'm the dispatcher.
Who do you dispatch?
-Usually one of two people, small town.
-You know a good realtor?
I know who my boss would recommend.
I think I got a card someplace.
Officer Simpson just called. They have
a domestic dispute out on Sylvan Road.
I think you should be there.
Okay.
You know where Sylvan Road is?
No.
Thank you.
I don't think I smell like
a brewery. I was drinking Scotch.
- Jesse Stone.
- Luther Simpson.
Walk with me.
Carole Genest called us.
Said her ex-husband forced his way
into the house, threatened her.
- Who's the kid?
- Their daughter.
He's pretty belligerent. D'Angelo's
up there  trying to calm him down.
Don't let her come in.
Why don't you give me the
divorce? What do you want?
- You want money?
- You got money.
- So what! So what!
- Anthony D'Angelo. How are you doing?
- Any more kids in the house?
- There's a couple of kids upstairs.
- Who are you?
- You got kids, Anthony?
Yeah, I got three.
-Do what you can to make them feel safe.
-Okay.
Hey, buddy, I said, who are you?
I'm the new police chief, sir.
Oh, yeah. I heard about you.
Only good things, I hope.
Oh, you're a funny guy.
Does Mrs. Genest have
a restraining order on you, sir?
Yeah, so?
He's gonna kill me one day,
the bastard.
-Did he say he was going to kill you?
-Every time I see him.
-Can you people do anything about him?
-Yes, ma'am, we can.
Did he hit you or
in any way assault you?
No, not this time.
She's okay.
Did he force his way in?
Yeah, yeah, I tried to lock the
door, but he's still got a key.
- It's my house.
- Has he assaulted you in the past?
Sure, he's beat the crap out of me
a lot of times.
Well, we probably don't have
an assault charge here.
We may get forced entry
even though he had a key.
But obviously, we've got him for
violating the restraining order.
Restraining order don't mean crap,
and you know it.
Yes, sir, I know.
I just go to court with my lawyer,
they issue a new restraining order.
I am out of there in 20 minutes.
That's the way it usually works,
especially if you've got some money.
Which I do.
So...
I guess that means I get to come
in here and visit my wife
just as much as I please.
Is that true?
You just said there's nothing
you can do about it.
No, sir, I said the restraining
order probably wouldn't work.
Isn't that the same thing?
Not really.
If you come near
this woman again,
if anything happens to her,
or her kids,no matter what,
no matter whose fault it is,
I will kick you around this town
until you look like road kill.
And if you're annoying,
like you were today,
I just might shoot you.
Stay here with D'Angelo
until Mr. Genest leaves.
What if he comes back?
I don't think he'll come back.
Molly, can I get a cup of coffee?
If you make it.
Just because I'm the dispatcher
doesn't mean I can't do police work.
We need to talk.
I should have introduced myself earlier.
I'm Abby Taylor, the city attorney.
Jesse Stone.
- May I call you Jesse?
- Of course, Abby.
Whatever the circumstances
of your police work in Los Angeles,
this is a town where everyone's
civil liberties are important.
Now, I can certainly sympathize
with Carole Genest's situation,
but you cannot go around
beating people up.
- Can I ask you a question?
- Of course.
You asked if you could call me Jesse.
I said you could, but you didn't.
- Excuse me?
- You didn't use my name.
What does that have to do
with you assaulting Mr. Genest?
Just seemed odd to me.
Do you have anything to say on the matter
of your assault on Mr. Genest?
The restraining order wasn't working.
Think of me as implementing it.
You really need to take
this more seriously.
this more seriously, Jesse.
You really need to take
No, I don't, Abby.
You don't make it easy, Jesse.
Joe Genest should be kicked
in the gonads once a day.
It was necessary to
get his attention.
The town council is prepared
to go forward from here,
but they would like your assurance
that something like this
will not occur in the future.
- It might.
- You don't give an inch, do you?
Jesse.
Have you had much experience
with people like Mr. Genest?
People in South Central L.A.
would keep Joe Genest for a pet.
Are you married, Abby?
No.
I don't see what that has to do
with the issue before us.
Me, either.
Have you ever been married?
- Yes.
- But you're not married now?
No.
- Divorced?
- Yes.
Jesse, one of the rules of conversation
is that when asked a question,
you don't give a one-word answer.
Okay, want to have dinner with me?
Yes.
It's good.
Holster your weapon.
You might want to
get into the habit
of keeping your finger
outside the trigger guard.
If you're handling a suspect,
you might get a sympathetic
response and shoot somebody.
And you don't just stand there,
you shoot and move.
How'd you learn
to shoot like that?
Practice.
So, in a fight, front sight.
You hear I was drunk
at my job interview?
I did hear something about that.
- Small town.
I wouldn't have
hired me, would you?
Well, I don't know.
Any idea why Lou Carson retired?
I don't know.
Hello, you've reached Paradise
Realty. Please leave a message.
My name's Jesse Stone. I'm
calling about finding a residence.
You can reach me at the
police station. Thank you.
- I'll start with an egg.
- All righty.
One egg. Now, you don't
have to use eggs.
Paradise Police Station.
- Hey, Molly.
- Hey, Lou. Where are you?
I don't know.
Doesn't really matter.
This just doesn't
make any sense.
Maybe you'll be
surprised about Stone.
He's got more iron in him
than I was expecting.
Yeah, maybe I won't.
Boy, does this guy have baggage.
Listen, Molly, there's
something I want you to know.
I always enjoyed
working with you.
And I consider you my friend.
Thanks, Lou.
Keep in touch.
Bye, Molly.
What are you doing?
I don't think he'll
do that again.
Maybe not if you're around.
He hasn't bothered
me since that day.
How long are you going to
stick around here for?
I don't know.
I'm worried about Michelle.
She's older...
- How old is she?
- Fifteen.
- Tough age.
- Yeah.
She took the divorce really hard.
- She hates her dad.
- That's too bad.
- You think so?
- Fathers are important.
- You want some more coffee?
- Yes, thank you.
- Luther?
- Yes, ma'am.
You get the house as
part of the divorce?
Yeah, yeah.
He's supposed to pay me alimony,
but he never does.
Must be tough to keep
the payments up.
Well, I...
You know,I got to pay taxes quarterly,
but at least there's no mortgage.
- Well, that's good.
- Yeah.
Joe bought it for cash
when we got married.
What's he do?
He works in Boston.
He never shared his work with me.
My ex-husband has
a very bad temper.
I learned very early
not to question him.
Besides, I'm not very smart.
I never learned anything in
school. I didn't even graduate.
Taking care of me was
his job, right?
Well, I'll talk to him.
You know, you're going
to need to be careful.
Joe's mean. He's gonna
wanna get even.
Joe's a fake.
Sometimes for a minute he knows it
and he knows that I know it, too.
He isn't really tough.
And you are?
Yes, ma'am. I am.
I find dealing with cash
unbelievably tedious.
Yeah, but you're
pretty good at that.
Started as a teller,
worked my way up.
I hear you had a little run-in
with our new chief.
Yeah, the son of
a bitch blindsided me.
I hope your little personal and petty
problems with him don't get in our way.
He's the chief of police.
So what?
I get $1,114,905.
You wanna do a recount?
I'll take your count.
Okay, well, then, your share
of my eight percent...
$22,298.
Oh, that's the wrong
number, Hasty.
We're equal partners now.
Well, Joe, I don't
want to diminish
your very valuable contribution
to this little enterprise,
but there's no way in hell
you're getting half...
Lou Carson's dead.
What?
He had a terrible accident.
What an incredibly
stupid thing to do.
Don't worry, they're
never gonna find him.
He knew everything.
Come on, he was a danger to us.
- He never would have said a word.
- What difference does it make?
He's dead.
That makes you an accessory.
So...
From now on
I get half.
Thanks.
I wouldn't have figured you
for a beer drinker.
I'm not. I'm a Scotch
on the rocks drinker.
Just didn't want to get drunk
on our first date.
Do you get drunk?
I have trouble stopping
when I start.
Is that what happened
on the job interview?
Actually, I had way too much
the night before.
I just made the mistake of having
one in the morning to steady up.
Well, he hired you anyway, so
he must have seen something in you.
- Maybe.
- Why maybe?
I wouldn't have hired me.
What's your take on our boss?
My father told me to never trust
a man that smiles all the time.
That's good advice.
If you want a Scotch, go ahead.
I'm willing to risk
it if you are.
Did your ex-wife ever remarry?
No, but she's in another
guy's bed a lot.
And that hurts.
Maybe it would help
if you got even.
I think coffee and donuts
tend to certify one's copness.
Thanks for buying.
I'm trying to prove
I'm a regular guy.
Luther your real name?
My mother teaches Sunday school.
She's a very religious person.
Named me after
some religious guy.
Gym teacher called me Spider
when I was in the fourth grade
and that stuck for a while.
- I don't see you as a Spider.
- Well, what do you see me as?
Stop the car, Suitcase.
- What did you say?
- Stop the car.
No, after that.
Drive around the block a couple
of times, Suitcase.
You gonna run me out
of here or what?
No.
You come here, you smoke dope.
I chase you out, you come back.
It's a waste of my time and yours.
-You gonna kick me in the nuts?
-That would be difficult.
You know,
-you can't prove I'm smoking dope.
-Doesn't matter.
So, why don't you just
leave me alone, then?
-Why don't you go to school?
-School sucks.
So, I guess you just think it's
okay to push me around?
-Am I pushing you around, Michelle?
-How do you know my name?
I'm the police chief,
I know everything.
You know, I saw you going
into the Gray Gull last night.
Small town.
Aren't you a little old for her?
I don't know. Maybe I'll ask her.
Did you have a drink?
Yes, I did.
So how come that's okay
and smoking dope isn't?
It's legal, and smoking
dope is illegal.
- So that makes it right?
- Nope, just legal and illegal.
- Well, that sucks.
- A lot of things suck.
You said stuff was just legal or illegal.
Well,what about it being right or wrong?
I'm not in the right and wrong business.
I'm in the legal and illegal business.
- You just don't want to answer.
- No, I don't mind answering.
Actually, that was
part of my answer.
You and I both know that
sitting around here all day
smoking dope isn't the right thing
to do with your life.
Who the hell are you
to say what's right for me?
The guy you asked.
Most people don't have trouble
seeing what's right and wrong.
Doing it is sometimes complicated,
but knowing what's right
usually isn't so hard.
And chasing you out of here
is obviously not the right way
to help you do the right thing.
- So, why are you still here?
- Trying to do the right thing.
It has a living area.
It has a kitchen with a dining
area and a half bath.
- Mrs. Hathaway...
- Cissy.
I think I want a house.
Excuse me, Jesse,
I don't mean to offend you,
but within your budget range...
You know, it's
the people from Boston,
they keep coming up here
and driving the prices up.
Actually, there is
a place I could show you.
It's absolutely charming.
You have the ocean on both sides,
and it's extremely private.
Pretty isolated.
Where's the garage?
Well, there isn't one.
But you just park your car back
there and take this bridge.
Might be a drag if you're
carrying groceries.
This is it.
Floors are originals of the house.
You don't see craftsmanship
like that anymore.
And it's very reasonable.
Well within your budget range.
- You mean, it's cheap?
- Exactly.
I'll take it.
I think you're going to be
very happy here, Jesse.
You think so?
-Well, thanks, Skipper.
-D'Angelo, please,don't call me Skipper.
- Your appointment's here.
- I don't have an appointment.
- Jesse?
- Yeah.
I'm Captain Healey,
State Police, Homicide Commander.
Nice to meet you. Sit down.
I work out of Boston,
but I live up this way.
- I've been meaning to stop by.
- I'm glad you did.
- You like Scotch?
- I do.
- Want some pizza?
- No, thanks.
I like pizza, it don't like me.
So, I hear
- you're up from L.A., right?
- Right.
-That's a long way from Paradise.
-Long way.
You worked homicide?
Yeah.
I know Cronjager.
How's it going?
I don't drink
on the job.
Good night, Skipper.
You gonna lock up?
- I will.
- Thanks.
So, I hear you used
to play ball.
Double-A, tore up my shoulder,
and that was that.
The Phillies signed
e as a pitcher.
- And?
- And I wasn't good enough.
You miss it?
Every day.
Lou Carson's dead.
Went off the road,
drowned in his car.
There weren't any witnesses.
The local police aren't even
sure when it happened.
Their ME says he's been in
the water at least a few days.
Found alcohol in his blood.
Lou liked to drink.
Family?
Divorced, lived alone.
So nobody reported him missing.
If the fisherman hadn't seen
his car in the water...
You released it
to the press yet?
Not yet. I'm gonna hold it.
Take a look at it.
Make sure it was an accident.
- Doesn't sound right.
- Why?
No reason.
Anyway, I thought
you should know.
Welcome to Northeastern Bell.
If you have any problems...
- Hello.
- Hi.
- You okay?
Not really.
Broke up with Elliott.
I'm shocked.
Don't make fun of me, Jesse.
It's too easy.
I'm sorry.
You think I'm a dreadfuI fooI,
don't you, Jesse?
I think you do foolish things
sometimes, Jenn.
I don't think you're dreadful.
Have you met anyone?
Yes.
Do you love her?
Not yet.
I don't think
I belong here, though.
-You mean, you didn't get the job?
-No, I got the job.
I'm just not so sure
they should've hired me.
- Are you drinking?
- Not on the job.
I'll need you to drive me
into town to pick up my car.
I called the towing garage.I'll clean
up the paint before they get here.
Leave it alone.
Thank you. Sorry about your car.
- Your boss called.
- You don't like him, do you?
I think he's a son of a bitch.
Anyway, he wants you to meet him for
breakfast at the coffee shop in 15 minutes.
I already had breakfast.
- Molly, I know you and Lou were close.
- Still are.
Lou's dead.
He drowned. His car
went off the road.
- But I just spoke to him.
- When?
First day out.
You want to go home?
Take the day off?
Molly, I don't want you to talk
about this to anybody.
Even Simpson, D'Angelo.
I'm sorry.
Who do you think
did that to your car, Skipper?
Jesse.
-Jesse.
-Come in.Close the door behind you.
I want this to be between
just you and me.
I need a hat.
We got hats, Skipper.
How do I put this delicately?
I don't like them.
I'm used to navy blue.
Can you have one made up for me?
PPD, silver letters?
And maybe you could have them
embroider "Chief" on the back.
- I guess so.
- Good.
Who's gonna pay for it?
- I will.
- Okay.
This may come as
a complete shock to you,
but I've been hearing
good things about you.
No, I couldn't be happier about
the job you're doing.
Well, I was under the impression you didn't
like the way I handled Joe Genest.
Well, officially that's true. But off the
record,I think he got what he deserved.
-So you know him?
-Well, I know who he is.It's a small town.
You sure I can't bring
you anything, Chief?
- No, I already ate. Thanks.
- Thank you, Tammy.
I understand that Captain Healey
was in your office last night.
- Yes.
- How's he doing?
I don't know, he just stopped
by to introduce himself.
Oh, I see. What did
you guys talk about?
- Baseball, mostly.
- Baseball. Anything else?
Not really. Why?
Well, it's just that we like to handle
our own problems here in Paradise.
In fact, if you do have a problem,
Jesse,I'd like you to call me first.
I mean it, I don't care if it's
the middle of the night, you call me.
- Anytime?
- Anytime.
- Well, I appreciate that, Hasty.
- Sure.
- Thanks for the coffee.
- All right.
You seem to have made a decision
not to wear a uniform.
- Oh, well, actually I...
- It's okay, I don't mind.
I'm growing really
fond of you, Jesse.
- See you. Yeah.
- See you.
- I think I'm overdressed.
- I told you, small town.
But when I heard yacht club I was
thinking blue blazers and deck shoes.
Well, that's what Hasty's wearing.
The bow tie is his party trademark.
At Christmas, he has one
with red and green lights.
Sporty guy.
- Hi, Peter.
- Hi, Abby.
Jesse, this is Dr. Peter Perkins.
- I heard about you.
- Everybody says that.
-Peter has a very successful practice here.
-Really?
Jesse Stone.  Abby, could
I borrow Jesse for a dance?
- A short one.
- Come on.
Nice meeting you.
- So how's the house coming?
- It's charming.
- Do you like my dress?
- Yes, I do.
Can you tell that I'm not wearing
anything underneath it?
I wasn't sure.
Is that something you might be
interested in seeing?
Here's the deal.
I like men and I like sex.
And assuming you're interested,
we could have something very nice
and very uncomplicated
with nothing at stake.
Wow.
Hi. May I cut in?
That was short. By all means.
I didn't know that
you knew Cissy Hathaway.
Yeah.
She found me my house.
And how does she
stack up as a kisser?
There's better.
Will trouble find you
if I use the facilities?
Hard to say.
Jesse.
Scotch on the rocks your drink?
Yeah, I had a feeling.
Want to get some air?
Come on.
Cheers. You having a good time?
Your batteries are low.
There's a switch.
Women are kind of hard to figure,
aren't they?
Yes, they are.
Yeah, I guess you've had your share of
trying to figure them out. Sexual problems?
- Excuse me?
- In your marriage.
Sexual problems. I mean, it's usually sexual
problems that make a marriage hit a reef.
No, we didn't have
any sexual problems.
- No?
- No.
When we were dating,
she was hotter than Cleopatra.
That's probably
one of the reasons I married her.
When we were dating,
we did everything except it.
She said she didn't want
to cheapen the relationship.
Kept talking about
saving it for marriage.
Then when we got married,
she wasn't interested.
She'd lie back, close her
eyes and think of England.
-I guess marriage is different than dating.
-Yeah.
You ever wonder why
you weren't enough?
Yes.
Cissy seem frigid to you?
- Hard to say.
- Oh, come on, Jesse.
She embarrassed us both
out there on the dance floor.
She seem frigid to you then?
No.
How come she's frigid at home
and hot with other guys?
I'm a cop, Hasty.
That's a shrink question.
Funny thing is
I'm still in love with her.
Lou Carson's dead.
- What happened?
- Car accident.
He was looking forward so much
to his retirement.
Hell of a thing to happen
first day of his trip.
How do you know it happened
on the first day?
Well, it was just
an assumption I made.
- It's a good assumption.
- I was fond of Lou.
I was very fond of Lou.
-What do you do when you have groceries?
-Well, you carry them across the bridge.
It's charming.
-Boomer's not eating.
-It's just the new surroundings.
He'll be fine.
Any plans to furnish
it at some point?
That's a good idea.
There is a mattress
in the bedroom.
Do you have a box spring?
I just want to know
what I'm getting myself into.
That's Ozzie. The best
shortstop that ever lived.
- And that would be baseball?
- Yes.
Thank you.
Jesse, what's going on with you
and Joe Genest?
No shrugging. I asked you
a question. I expect an answer.
Are you afraid of him?
Joe is stupid and mean
and he doesn't like me.
On the other hand,
if I had to, I could shoot him just
as easily as if he were smart and kind.
Hi, Jesse. Are you there?
You can pick that
up if you want to.
You said you were
trying not to love me.
Are you succeeding?
Well, that was just
getting interesting.
Do you still love her?
I'm not a good basket to put
all your eggs in at the moment.
Am I too young for you?
Is that another way of saying
I'm too old for you?
Come here.
How old is he?
- Ten.
- Do you see that? Right there?
That's polycystic renal disease.
His kidneys are failing.
What can we do?
Well, nothing, I'm afraid. It's
often the kidneys that go first.
- Did you breed this dog?
- No. Why?
He's not been neutered.
Any particular reason why?
Somehow I didn't think Boomer
would be Boomer without testicles.
Oh, well, be that as it may,
the end won't be pretty.
I think you need to put him down.
It would be the right thing to do.
Paradise Women's Club.
Makes me blush.
Maybe it's evolved into
a powerful force for feminism.
And maybe pigs fly.
- Did you see that?
- What?
Did you see Cissy get all
wiggly listening to Joe?
I'm telling you,
I think there's something there.
I don't see it.
I think he's plonking her.
- Plonking?
- Yeah.
And you can tell this
just by looking?
I can. I am wise in these matters.
And why is that?
Because I am blessed with a penis.
Hey, Stone. How about a drink?
Hey. Sorry I couldn't say hi outside
the vet's, but I was in a rush.
You're not following me around,
are you, Joe?
- How're you doing, little lady?
- I'm fine.
Yes, you are.
What do you do, Joe?
- What?
- For a living?
I don't see how that's
any of your business.
I was sorry to hear
about Lou Carson.
What about him?
He was killed.
Where were you
when it happened?
I got an alibi.
How do you know
when he was killed?
Whenever it happened,
I didn't do it.
Do what?
I don't got to listen
to this crap.
How long have you
known about this?
How long?
Couple of days.
You may like to stir the pot
and play your stupid little games,
but Lou Carson was
a friend of mine.
And you should at least be honest
with someone who's sharing your bed.
Captain Healey.
It's Jesse. Sorry we've
been playing phone tag.
The lid's coming off
on Lou Carson's death.
Thanks for letting me know.
We're still calling it an accident.
Is there a reason we shouldn't?
I don't know. Maybe I just
like stirring the pot.
- Skipper?
- In a minute.
Listen,I need to talk to you,but I can't do it
on the phone.Can you come down here?
- I can.
- When?
- Today.
- Thanks.
Yeah.
D'Angelo.
What do you think?
It's a good hat.
Here's your receipt.
Did you tell Hasty Hathaway
that Captain Healey
was in my office
a couple of days ago?
Yeah.I saw him on the street,and he
was asking me how things were going.
It's a small town.
Well, here's an idea.
Don't do that.
What happens here stays here.
If it happens again,I'll have your badge
and gun in my drawer.Understood?
- Understood.
- Thanks for the hat.
You're welcome.
Suit!
Come on in. It's okay.
You're not in trouble.
-You practicing?
-Yes,I am.In a fight,front sight.
Sit down.
Jesse, can I ask you something?
I was looking at this report.
You arrested Joe Genest for
assault and battery six months ago.
- Yes, sir.
- Jesse.
Jesse, Joe beat up this guy bad.
Well, no charges were filed. Why?
That's the way Lou wanted it.
He said it was self-defense on Joe's
part, which was a load of crap.
Any idea why he might be
following me around?
It might have something to do with
you kicking him in the nuts.
I think he's plonking
Hasty's wife.
He is.
How do you know?
What do you know about
Cissy Hathaway?
- What do you mean?
- You know what I mean.
- I don't know anything about that.
- Am I missing something here?
I ask you about Cissy Hathaway,and you
look like you just swallowed a squirrel.
Suit...
How do you know?
I was plonking her
before Joe took my place.
Did I hear you call
Luther "Suitcase"?
- You did.
- Why?
Why not?
Do you ever give anybody
a straight answer?
- Change your mind about lunch?
- No.
- We going to a different place?
- Would you prefer I didn't ask?
- Yes.
- Can I ask you a question?
Why you following Joe Genest?
Coply intuition.
What's he doing?
I don't know.
- Can I ask you a question?
- Yes.
-What do you think's in the bag?
-Money.
-That's good police work, Officer Crane.
-Thank you.
Assuming you're right about the bag
and it's not full of clothes,
I think our friend
is laundering money.
So why is Hasty a son of a bitch?
Lou didn't retire.
Hasty forced him out.
Why?
I don't know.
Can you guess?
I don't want to.
I think Joe Genest killed Lou
and made it look like an accident.
Because Lou knew about this?
That would be a motive.
Unless Lou Carson's car could go
sideways,it wasn't an accident.
It was smashed in
on the passenger side.
So obviously not a suicide
drive off the cliff.
Traffic found
an abandoned rental truck in town.
Traces of paint on the front bumper
matched the paint on Lou Carson's car.
Rented under a phony name.
Driver's license didn't check out.
Anyway, we did pick up enough at
the scene to know he was pushed off.
His motor wasn't running.
You getting all this?
You got a suspect?
Not yet.
-How about you?
-I got a prospect.Guy named Joe Genest.
I know a guy named Joe Genest.
Bag man for Gino Fish, who is
a very prosperous businessman.
Drugs and gambling mostly.
He runs the South End and
the Back Bay. Why Joe Genest?
He's following me around.
And why would he do that?
'Cause he doesn't like me.
Jesse,
we've had Joe Genest
as a person of interest
in about five mob killings.
We got nowhere.
I'd be a little careful
if I were you.
- Where's Boomer?
- He's home.
I got some furniture.
Jesse, I think
that we're moving way too fast.
I think that I need some time.
I understand.
I'm sorry.
I got a surprise for you, Boomer.
Steak.
Hi. It's me. Call me.
So I'd be kind of like a hyphenate.
A pediatricianlmedical examiner.
Well, no offense, Doc,
I didn't know you were a pediatrician.
How about just medical examiner?
I haven't seen a cadaver
since med school.
And you'll probably never see one.
Hell, nothing ever happens here.
I can get you an extra 500 bucks
a month and a nice title.
- Sounds like a challenge.
- There's one other thing.
I want you to put down my dog.
Excuse me?
Jesse, I can't do that.
For me to euthanize your dog
would be completely unethical.
Why?
'Cause as a doctor,
I took an oath to do no harm.
I'm a people doctor,
not an animal doctor.
Why don't you have the vet do it?
Because I don't like her.
Look, if you could get
your mind around it,
I'd consider it a favor.
- Hey, Suit.
- Hi.
- You got a second?
- Sure.
Where's Boomer?
He's home.
Jesse, I got a problem.
I don't care about Cissy Hathaway.
No, it's not that.
Something's been bothering me.
I wasn't sure if I was
supposed to ask and...
Maybe I'm supposed to know.
See, the thing is...
Why do you call me "Suitcase"?
Why not?
That's not funny, Jesse.
I'm sorry.
It's after Harry "Suitcase" Simpson.
- The baseball player.
- Why "Suitcase"?
Because he was traded to a lot
of teams. He traveled a lot.
But I've lived here all my life.
Yeah, I know. Just seemed to fit.
How long you had him?
Since he was a pup.
I went on the Internet.
Found out how to do this.
You can find out nearly anything
on the Internet.
I'm sorry, Jesse.
Thank you, Doc.
Hi, Jesse. Doc Perkins
just told me about Boomer.
Call me when you can.
I guess Lou was on the take.
I think so.
You know, last night I was thinking.
About a year ago, Hasty kept coming
in and out of here as he pleased.
He used Lou's office...
Sorry, your office.
Hasty's white-collar. Doesn't
figure he'd order a murder.
Can you prove that
Joe Genest killed him?
I got some evidence, but no proof.
This happened on my watch.
I gotta make something happen.
Where's Boomer?
He's home.
- You got a cigarette?
- No.
- What, you don't smoke?
- You ever?
- No.
- How come?
- I was a jock.
I didn't want it
to affect my wind.
So, what are you doing here?
I was waiting for you.
I talked to your mom.
She worries about you.
She said you took the divorce really
hard, that you hate your dad.
Well, I do.
Well, that's too bad.
-Fathers are important.
-Look, I don't want another lecture.
I'm not lecturing. I'm sharing.
- We have something in common.
- You hate your dad?
No. But I've been through a divorce.
- You hate your ex-wife?
- Sometimes. But not all the time.
And I'm a better person when
I remember that I care about her.
Your dad's done some bad things.
Tell me about it.
To other people, too.
If something happens
and you need to talk,
let me know.
I'll meet you here.
You gotta watch
that drinking thing.
Oh, hey there, Chief,
you following me?
I asked you first.
So, how's Hasty's wife?
Excuse me?
What do you do, Joe?
Guy drives a nice car, pays cash
for his house. I get curious.
Maybe you should stay that way.
You've done some bad things, Joe.
So throw me in jail.
Not tonight.
When's the last time you had sex
with a woman?
None of your business.
Well, I think you should consider it.
'Cause it's going to
be the last time.
- Hello.
- Hi, Hasty.
Sorry to bother you in the middle
of the night, but you said anytime.
Listen, something's come up.
We have to talk.
- What's going on?
- Can it wait till morning?
- If you say so, boss.
- What's going on?
Right. I'll call you first
thing in the morning.
Fine.
The son of a bitch has landed.
-I thought you were gonna call me.
-Well, you said it was urgent.
I'm sorry, boss, you said anytime.
- What's going on?
- Want some coffee?
Coffee? No, I don't want coffee.
Lou Carson was murdered.
Murdered?
Well, I find that
hard to believe.
You know what? I actually...
I will have some coffee.
Molly, can we have another
cup of coffee?
- You told me it was a car accident.
- I was wrong.
-Newspapers called it a car accident.
-That's what the police gave them.
-But you remember this guy Joe Genest?
-Joe Genest?
Molly, close the door.
- You think Joe Genest killed Lou?
- I know it.
- How do you know it?
- I can't tell you.
Look, Hasty,
I know I owe you a lot but this...
All right. All right.
But this has to stay between us.
Yeah, of course, I understand.
Well, Healey found evidence
that Joe was at the scene.
Oh, he found it. Why hasn't
he arrested him, then?
Well,they don't have enough to make
a case.They don't have a motive yet but...
See, I think I do. J
oe works for the mob.
And I think he and Lou had some
kind of deal that went bad.
There's something else.
Joe's sleeping with your wife.
I think if he's arrested,
it's gonna come out.
No one else knows about this.
I appreciate that you came
to me first with this.
I'm sorry to be the one
to have to tell you.
- I'll walk you out.
- Yeah.
I got it.
- Hello.
- Jesse, this is Hasty. Listen.
This thing has really thrown me
for a loop,and I need to talk.
I understand. I'll come
to you, boss.
No, no. It's got to be
somewhere private.
I don't want everybody
to know about this.
You know where that
rusted ship is tied up?
- Yes.
- Tonight, 8:00.
- I'll be there.
- Good. Thanks.
He'll be there.
You got to talk to him in private
about what?
Anything you want to say
to me there, Hasty?
I don't think there is anything I could
say that'll make a difference,will it?
I work for the mob and I kill people.
Excuse me?
You asked what I do for a living.
Give me your gun.
No.
Put your hands behind your head.
Excuse me?
I'm not putting my hands behind
my head. I'm drinking coffee.
And you're gonna
shoot me anyway.
That's a good point.
Is he dead?
Yeah.
How do you know?
You just know.
Tragically, Joe's ambitions
exceeded his abilities.
And it's one way
to keep him away from my wife.
You all right?
Too soon to tell.
Oh, Hasty.
Yeah, I know.
I was growing really fond of you,too.
I'm sorry to put you through this.
This? This is nothing.
I just had to bury my dog.
What'd you do, Hasty?
See this in a movie?
You shoot Joe with the Chief's gun.
And then you use his on me.
Pretty much.
Well, the problem is you might have trouble
explaining why Joe was shot in the back.
Oh, right.
You're out of your league, Hasty.
Don't do this.
I don't wanna see you get hurt.
I'm the one with the gun.
Not the only one.
Don't move a muscle, Hasty.
Oh, hell. No.
Just put it down.
Did you get all that, Molly?
Tell the son of a bitch we got it all.
There's another one in his pocket.
I was ready, Jesse.
Sure you were, Suitcase.
Good God.
You should've done
something to stop it.