- I hate surprises.
- Ah, yes?
Yes.
You didn't care when
I surprised you with my promotion.
It was not a surprise, it was
deserved merit for my brilliant husband.
Maybe because of my brilliant wife.
You say that because you like of
me, because of my body.
I like to feel your body.
What and what are we to do?
Surprised.
Don't I notice, what does mean this?
The house.
Yes! Me tou to see, thank you.
- Also known as home, shrine, lodging.
- Yes.
Or if you prefer,
we can call ourselves of ours.
- Ours?
- Yes.
Where and that will get ourselves the money,
do we only have prai one weekend for us to change ourselves?
Yes, good...
Maybe with the key.
Oh my God, oh my God,
you these to play with me!
And a classic.
1920, good facade,
3 rooms, one has suite.
And the old owner left us
one balances new in the bottoms.
I think am with one
little of will of balancing.
I will have to show you
how to balance how it should be...
Thank you.
- I love you.
- I also love you.
We will enter.
- Mamma? Mamma?!
- Uh?
When and what does eat him it comes home?
- What did go he/she he/she drinks?
- When and what does the father go back home?
Uh... Today he/she drinks,
he/she was to do travel her during the night.
Because and what Courtney didn't take us?
Because it was spoken that could not go...
But, why don't say
does good morning suck, what good to see you?
Good morning sucks.
- He/she sucks, you have to get dressed!
- Candy, we have ourselves plenty time.
We leave
to be late to the school.
No, no, we don't leave
we delay ourselves to the school.
And better we go us or we go
to arrive the school late!
Bridgette, already know
to spell the words?
Yes mamma.
- Ei! Ei! Ei!, don't forget about the lancheiras,
we go, fast, feel a kiss.
- We go, diffuse in them.
- I am to go.
That no this dirties.
small Ei! How and what this everything?
I don't believe that already and Thursday.
Don't tell me, I don't have idea
of as and that this week passed.
I would like were here,
I want to say...
I am to have difficulties to find
the ideal dress for this night.
And you, did big
plans for this weekend?
Removing the trip of
Jim for Acapulco, not.
I think is going well coorer everything. Ok,
I have to turn off...
I have to see him/it
that will do of my life immediately.
Ah yes, which and his name?
His name, well, his name
and really bad, and Harry...
but it is never known, it can be "the such."
You have a new message.
First new message.
Linda, listens,
I need to tell you a thing...
I spoke to her serialize when he/she spoke in front
of the small ones in the other night and...
Me just...
I just want you to know about that.
it is please reminds you.
Rays leave, somebody this
to call, he/she waits for a little.
are you "?"
End of the messages.
If he/she leaves me a message, me
I will give answer the fastest possible.
Ei! I am me. I received your message,
I don't know when and that you left her, but...
It just ties me when you receive
mine, this well? Good-bye...
- Sra. Hanson?
- Yes.
- Linda Hanson?
- Uhum.
- I am Sheriff Railley.
-Yes.
I feel a lot to give him/her announces her:
His/her husband Jim?
- Yes.
- He was in a road accident.
He died at the place.
- When?
- Yesterday.
No! No, that and
impossible because I ended...
I have just heard his voice in the
tape recorder of calls, therefore...
Good, I feel my lady a lot.
Us... we didn't get ourselves
to come informs her earlier.
The other driver drove a camiao...
of inflatable products, with certainty
a risk that he assumed, was misled
It was in the fast road, in the mark of the 220 miles...
he died instantly,
I feel a lot for his/her loss...
Mrs.? Sra. Hanson? Mrs.?
Mrs., he/she has some thing
what can I make for itself?
- Can I link to anybody for itself?
- No.
Do let to leave me my card, this well?
If he/she has questions to do, call.
What was mamma?
Mamma?
What was?
- And on him it eats.
- Yes?!
Yes.
He suffered a very serious accident.
What accident type?
When and what does he go back home?
Him this well?
No dear, he left.
Well! I am impressed.
You already got
to set up this everything alone?
- Yes.
- It is really impressive.
Ei! And Annie, leave the message after the bip,
and I promise that later tie him/her.
Ei Annie am me...
please, it ties me as soon as
you receive this message, thank you.
Well, you two
they are to do this screamingly.
He/she eats him/it and better
in the puzzles.
He will help us.
- Dear Ei?
- Ei.
I think finally
I got fall asleep them.
Well, I treat of that.
No! No knives that,
they has just fallen asleep, clue...
I was to think in everything
what needed ourselves to do.
Tomorrow probably we will have to begin
to treat of the funereal ceremony.
It is then... you will have to see the
situation of the benefits of the insurance.
I am not prepared for that mother.
Nobody this prepared
for anything of this wanted.
But you had been surprised
with the all will be strong.
- You know, when I lost...
- I am not to think in serving in tray.
What tray of serving?
You know, the big in the top of the closet.
One of the relatives offered her.
I don't arrive there.
Jim, Jim made that for me.
Nobody wait that knives
everything in the first days, wanted.
Me, I am very tired,
I will lie down...
I will look for some sheets to the closet.
I will be here if you
you need me, wanted.
Mother?
Jim.
Which and the problem?
I don't know... me only... me only...
I only found strange.
What? What was?
Ok, I don't think so
and anything, and anything, and anything.
Mother, we are delayed ourselves, the
third time we will be punished ourselves.
We know ourselves how to begin with good
humor the day, do they remember the "good morning?"
- Good morning.
Good, I have to go,
meeting of morning Monday.
Hugs for all,
this well, I have to go.
I am to train the new assistant of it manages.
Catch your snacks,
we are ready to go.
You this well for... do you take them the school?
Yes.
Right.
- Girls, have fun at the school.
- Good-bye it eats.
These without problems in
to spell for the teacher?
Yes.
Ei, don't forget
of your lancheira.
- We are going Annie, he/she leaves the car!
- I am to go!
You don't have messages.
Shit!
- It was a travagem and so much.
- And, because it was, I was totally...
Yes, I was surprised.
Ah, I was totally distracted.
- Do we just go with more calm, hum?
- Clear.
We don't want that
is nobody hurt, no and?
I am to try to decide,
will it be that should call him?
The one that I feel really and that
I want to call for him...
but I also feel as
if it was to break the rules...
I think and better, if I wait.
What?
Did we talk us yesterday?
- Yes, we talked us everyday.
- No, I want to say...
- Did I leave you a message?
- Do I think no, because?
He/she waits one minute, it tolerates oh, I am the
what this to pass for a crisis, right?
- Are you sure that this well?
- Yes.
This everything well between you and Jim?
Yes, everything this
exactamente in the same.
Then, as it was your day?
- Mine was normal.
- It was annoying.
And, I am bored.
Boredom, hum?
Jim?
Jim... Jim?
What?
Lithium.
(Anti-depressive)
- Here this her.
- Hello wanted.
Did you get to rest?
What and what does happen?
Ei! How and what do sit down?
Why don't go up
and garments some clothes?
- Don't you want to arise for you dress yourself?
- Where, where, where are the small ones?
The small ones are very dear.
The small ones are well candy,
don't worry about the girls.
That no this well.
What and qu no this well?
No, this everything well,
necessary of to arise and to sleep more.
No! No, I don't need to sleep
plus, and I don't also need to wake up.
- Everything anger to be very dear.
- No mother, doesn't anger to be everything well.
- Some thing this really wrong one.
- Ready, this well.
Him no this died.
Hello he/she drinks.
Ei! Hello!
He/she excuses, I was not
awake when you rose.
- The grandmother told me to let to fall asleep.
- He/she doesn't drink, you can always wake up me.
It was only a dream.
- Balancing.
- Uhum.
I think her this sad one.
Well, I will speak to her.
Do drink?
Oh my God! Oh my God drinks!
Does he/she drink, what did happen you the face?
He/she drinks speech with me! As and that cut
the face, did make who you that drinks?
- Because?
- Because you have cuts for the face!
- He/she doesn't have cuts mamma.
- What and what these to say?
Her and perfect,
as a beautiful princess.
Oh God, comes here, he hugs me,
he/she will be everything well, it will be everything well.
Everything had been well,
everything had been well, everything had been right.
- Mamma?
- Yes.
Do I wonder how and what does eat him he/she died?
I don't know drinks, I was not there.
Then, as you know that he died?
You these well?
And does this go a mistake?
What do with "a mistake" mean?
He/she doesn't just die in one day and
the following day this everything well, and only.
- This no and a mistake.
- Ready mother, did you see him/it inside of the coffin?
- No! I didn't see him/it inside of the coffin,
but that doesn't mean...
Ready mother, somebody put
he/she longs for with this situation.
Beautiful? We needed ourselves to enter
inside of the church now, we go wanted.
No, you necessary of taking the children inside.
Why and that don't come inside with the...?
- He/she takes the children inside.
- He/she is going going, it takes the children inside.
Beautiful! Beautiful?
Hello Sra. Hanson.
Ok. I only want you to know that
this everything inside of the programmed.
I need him to open the coffin.
No! Roman no.
- I don't think so and a good idea.
- Open the coffin, porra.
- Open him/it, open him/it, open, open, open.
- I understand.
Sra. Hanson!
I implore him/her that gives up.
- No knife that with me.
- Sra. Hanson...
- A problem there is been, we will be discovered which and.
- The corpse...
- There was problem with the corpse.
- What does have with the corpse?
- There was mutilac.es
- What types of mutilac.es?
- Oh!! No!!
- Oh my God!
Leave!! Stop!! Leave!!
Release me! Come unfastened! No!
No! Leave me!
Jim left this world,
a dear person.
His friends talked about his kindness.
His/her smile, their graces, yours
helps and considerac.es to all in his/her circuit.
But his great devotion,
it was with the family.
His girls that he liked of
to hear to speak, and his/her lover marries, Linda.
- The Precious daughters, Megan and Bridgette...
- Mother?
What and?
Who and that?
- Who?
- There, that woman.
I don't know wanted.
- Beautiful?
- This everything well, everything well.
Our father, that these in the sky,
Sanctified is your name.
Come the us Your kingdom,
be made Your will.
Like this in the Earth as in the Sky.
Wait! No, please wait, wait!
- Excuse me.
- I only want to talk.
How and what do you know my husband?
I just thought that already
we had talked.
- Did we talk us?
- Yes, yesterday.
- Yesterday?
- Don't you remember?
No! I never met before
I get in all my life!
- Do I only want to go, ok?
- Please speak to me.
My condolences,
and for their daughters also.
Who and you? Please, not.
Lithium carbonate
Not to mix with anything
or to ingest with alcohol.
Dr. Norman Roth.
Dr. Norman Roth!
Mamma?
Why don't you go down the stairways
and will they talk with the grandmother and Annie?
No!
I am sure that will be graced.
What and what these the search mamma?
I need to talk
with a person, he/she drinks.
Why not
conversations with us?
He/she drinks, I adore to talk with you,
but this, this and adults' conversation.
Do I need a help, this well?
He/she goes drinks, please it goes there down.
Thank you he/she drinks, thank you this everything well.
I am the search.
PSYCHIATRISTS - PSYCHIATRY
Roth Norman MD
He/she called the
clinic of the Dr. Norman Roth.
The consultations happen in Salvador, of
Monday Friday of the 9:00 the 17:30...
You want tea or coffee or any
thing, do they want me to swallow some thing?
Maybe it is better to put
the children to sleep, hum?
- Oh yes.
- They were some steep days.
Hum... yes they were.
Ready girls!
We are going with the aunt Annie, we go there
upward and did we dress the pajamas, this well?
Can I read you one recounts?...
Can it be?
Among.
Good morning Mrs. Quinn.
Ei Annie.
- Hello Linda.
- Hello.
Am I it Dr. does Roth, remember?
No, don't I remember, what?
Annie?
- Ready girls, we go there upward...
- Mother! What and what does happen?
Wanted, please be not angry,
please be not angry with us.
Wait one second, Annie!
Annie, what and what these to do?
I am Dr. Roth, his/her family
he/she worries am gotten.
- What and what these to do?
- His/her family worries about herself.
- What and what these to do? Annie? Annie?
- What more we could do?
What and?
You only say him/it that and that happened
with the face of Bridgette?
Mother, I don't know him/it that and that
he/she happened with the face of Bridgette.
That that I wanted to say was not!
I would never make something like that,
she was hurt outside!
Stand back of me! Stop!
This to hurt me!
- Stop!
- Stand back of me!
I think he/she doesn't know
the one that this to do!
Drink!
He/she drinks, he/she drinks, this everything well, drinks,
I don't know him/it that and that they are me to do!
Stop! No, this everything very dear,
he/she excuses me, it excuses me!
Mom laments a lot!
Stop, mother! Mother!!
- Impossible! Release me.
- Excuse me.
- Mamma!! Mother!
Sr.? Sr.? Sr.?
She still didn't calm down
since it arrived...
obviously her never
it was interned previously.
Her husband died in a
car accident on Wednesday.
I informed her on Thursday.
Wou, wou, wou, wou,
wait one moment.
Wednesday?
This and strange, she appeared in the
my clinic on Tuesday...
He/she declared that him already
he/she was dead or... he/she would die.
She said that he would go
to die before the accident?
Yes.
You are sure that
was an accident?
Hello Linda.
Please no knife that, I only want
to go home with my girls.
Please no knife that.
Please Sr. I want to go home
to be with my girls.
We will have a long time for
to talk about that tomorrow.
Please no knife that.
Please no knife that,
please no, no knife that!
Everything had been well.
Jim?
What was?
- You these well?
- You will be all soaped.
He/she gives me one minute,
only one moment.
To hear beating of yours
heart and so good.
He/she waits oh,
ei, ei, ei, waits oh.
This everything well. Then!
- Do promise?
- I promise.
What was wanted,
he/she tells me that and that he/she happens...
I don't know, I don't know how to explain.
- I have to go, I have to work.
- He/she waits one minute...
just only one more minute.
I have to go, I am
late for the service, it loosens me.
Girls?
- Good morning sucks.
- Good morning.
Good morning sucks.
Ei...
Hello...
Oh... Oh, you are so beautiful,
did you know?
- Am I?
- You are.
Beautiful, they are both beautiful ones.
Wait one minute, ei, ei, he/she has a lot,
very taken care there, this well?
Don't play with scissors, me not
I want to see you to play for oh...
Mrs., you this to hinder him/it
- He/she promises me, right.
- My lady?
Feel one second!
- Just, he/she promises me, do you promise?
- I will try.
- Does he/she promise me also, This very dear one?
- This well.
Ok, here this, Behave.
Mrs., walk there, please.
PSYCHIATRISTS - PSYCHIATRY
Roth Norman MD
You have Sra. Webe and
plus three marked consultations.
Yes, this well. Treat of that for me.
Who and that?
- Sra. Stevenson?
- Steven...
- In what I do can help her?
- Linda Hanson.
Hello Linda, I am it Dr. Roth.
Do you know me?
Would he/she owe?
I wake up him this died,
I wake up and him this lives.
Different things happen with me
the the whole hour, that I don't get to explain.
Things that I did,
People that speak to me, people that
they know me, but that I never knew.
- People like me?
- Yes.
- I think a little complicated.
- Nor tell me.
And on the lithium flask?
I don't know, that, that,
I don't know, it was in some besiege I don't know.
Look! I don't get to explain, but
I thought that somebody was to try...
- ... to try you do drug her?
- Uhum.
- Who, and because?
- I don't know, you tell me.
- It was not me who it wrote prescriptions.
- But his/her name this in the flask.
Why and what does think I came here?
To receive some help.
Obviously you this to work
with some inconsistencies.
Oh yes...
I wake up each guile and I discover
that my husband died again.
That is going a little
haul of the inconsistency.
As and that he/she sits down...
During the moments
in what him this died?
What?
I want to say, that type
of emoc.es, they go by itself.
And excuse, resentment, do I diminish?
What and what this to try to say?
And very common to dream during the day,
to imagine that people are dead.
Don't I dream during the day, right?
I wake up and him this died.
Excepto today.
You have some antecedents
of mental diseases in his/her family?
No.
And on you same, and those episodes
of psychoses, loss of memory...
deceiving judgements...
I don't want him to die!
It was a car accident.
- No and crime to imagine something.
- I am not to imagine!
Him this died!
Good, and a little strange.
But the prescription of the
medicine and for his/her good.
Because?
Because probably and the best
thing for itself at this time.
help-there-to to be calmer.
You think gets
to visit me here tomorrow?
- Ei! He/she looks who this here!
- Hello Bob, Jim still this here?
Yes, like you never again
did you appear for here?
- Hello!
- I need to speak with you.
What was?
What does happen he/she?
I know that I walk to act of
strange way, but there is something strange.
- There is something very strange.
- And with the children?
No, no, no, they are well,
at least for the time being.
Can we talk in another place?
Only we just, caught the
girls and we are going to some besiege.
I am not able to, it goes you,
I am to work.
Please I really need
of you, we just can...
I have to go the a meeting of sales.
Does he/she excuse me, Jim?
They are your wait.
Do excuse, who and you?
I am Claire Frances,
he/she should be Jim's wife.
Yes, Linda.
I saw their pictures,
and a pleasure knows her.
Claire and the new... assistant of it manages.
His/her husband has been one
precious help in you finish them weeks.
Claire, and Sonny.
With license.
We talked each other later about that.
Girls?
Fast, it will rain
with fork, hurry.
I will collect the clothes
what done this extend outside, this well?
Bridgette no, Bridgette!
Bridgette no!
Ready, I am here,
I am here.
Megan are going to the hospital, fast.
- Mamma?
- I am here wanted.
This everything very dear, this everything well.
This everything very dear.
It continues mamma to bleed.
Anybody? anybody, please?
Dr. do Nolan, tell me the one what happened?
Yes, she crossed a glass door.
She has some allergy
what should know?
- Cordim, cordim.
-  I number 40 please.
Mrs., wait at the waiting room.
No lady, we will take care of her.
- Everything had been well.
- He/she will be everything well he/she drinks.
Her this well?
- She cut the face, only some cuts.
- You these well?
Yes.
She was to run for the back yard and
he/she crossed the glass window.
Ready.
This everything well, encourages you.
What and what these to do, mamma?
We go forget ourselves us of the
he/she would sicken for a mouthful.
It ties that you feel a better little.
She will be with
ugly scars forever?
I don't want to hear to speak
on the scars.
Because and what not?
To Jesus Christ's eyes
there are no scars.
I don't care with that the
other they tell you, this well?
Do you understand?
Because you are beautiful.
How a princess?
Yes, as a princess.
My two princesses.
I thought you
had you glued stickers?
Me clei.
I don't know, maybe,
maybe I thought had glued.
Christ, Linda.
What? What? These to blame me
because of the situation?
I asked for your mother to be
here while I am in they travel.
What? Because?
- Only to help, do you know?
- I don't need any help.
- To take care of the children!
He/she looks, you can rest.
Who knows,
some alone time for you.
For the one what? Time for me, for the one what?
What? For me to stop acting how a crazy one?
- Of the one what and what these to speak? I never said...
- You won't divorce the children.
I am a good mother.
Sunday / Monday / Tuesday / Wednesday / Thursday...
Ok. Hum.
Thursday. I discover that Jim died.
Monday. Alive Jim.
Funeral of Jim. Saturday!
And more...?
Lithium, on Saturday.
Excepto for today.
I know him/it Dr. Roth on Tuesday.
It is then I return her see him/it...
Saturday... Dr. Roth.
What this to happen?
CUTS OF BRIDGETTE??
Care! Care!
Mamma?
Tuesday
CUTS
I have to have absolute certainty, travel
it was on Wednesday. Wednesday...
THE ONE what?
He/she has a new message.
- When and what did he die?
- Yesterday.
Oh God.
Jim dies on Wednesday.
What and what these to do?
Jim, don't you go in that they travel, please?
I need to go, I waited
one year for this interview.
Haul of the plus, it can
to be good for us, do you know?
To give a time each other.
It can be a larger time
of what you made calculations.
It is if some thing
to happen you?
Some thing can happen with me
in my road for the work.
- Should I stop working?
- Do you want me to implore?
I implore, please, don't just go,
you have children and you have family.
Why tell that,
do you think I forgot of that?
- No, I know that you didn't forget...
- Because I didn't forget!
I noticed that, I didn't say
that you forgot...
- Fortunately, good.
- He/she just listens.
- Certain, just..
- You don't listen to me!
- He/she just listens to me!
- For! For!
He/she does me only a favor.
If tomorrow it goes Wednesday, please
does he/she wake up me before you leave?
- If tomorrow Wednesday goes?
- Just... I know that seems madness.
Just, please, does he/she wake up me, this well?
Jesus!
Do you promise me?!
- I promise.
- Good.
This well.
Oh, this bed of you accommodate and horrible.
Mother!
- He/she excuses me, Jim left, Jim left.
- Do you think him this here?
No, no, no, I remember, me
I remember everything, don't worry.
Thursday, Thursday, Thursday for the guile,
Thursday for the guile.
Everything well, everything well, right.
They lack two days.
Here and Monday, every day,
I don't remember. Shit! Shit!
- These well?
- Shit.
She appears... Sra. Claire, Sra. Claire.
Did we talk us?
We were us yesterday,
don't you remember?
(CLAIRE)
- Mother, I have to go.
- What?
You have to be with the girls, you had
the largest shock of your life yesterday.
Nor tell me.
He/she has some subject that
in the owe-millstones to talk?
Something on my husband?
To talk?
I think he/she ended of doing.
He will betray myself.
What?
He/she waits one minute, as
did you know, as you discovered?
I talked with her,
she told me everything.
- When?!
- Today.
Oh, wanted I feel a lot,
you still these in shock?
No!
I already went by the state
of shock there are already some days.
All this and bad, accident
and other woman, and a confusion.
I don't know if and that bad.
Maybe this had to have happened.
What and what do want to say?
He knows that he/she still didn't make anything.
The damage that the would cost us, the girls.
Maybe it didn't go enough,
therefore he decided to go behind something different.
You these to hear him/it
what these to say?
We were us friends of fourth Annie.
We were us room friends,
two girls...
My room friend was a liar.
We have of the it politicizes of the life insurance.
Now, in agreement with the insurance,
your daughters' education this solved.
And, with what it was left, you
you will also be well financially.
You know Linda...
I have to tell you,
of the "timming" in that all this was made.
"Timming!" What do you mean?
Jim passed to see me on Wednesday
for the guile, for me to formulate the insurance.
- Wednesday?
- Yes.
And he seemed very anxious, as if
he was not sure that would live.
And he spoke about you and
of the children, and he said that
He/she doesn't matter what happens, he wanted
to have the certainty that all you were well."
And you were witness of the accident.
I want to say, that no and problem.
The report of it polices confirmed
that everything was an accident, then...
I will put in clean plates to the central office,
and they will give you a check.
Beautiful view, no and?
Yes, a lot.
You and of the family?
I have two daughters, more my mother.
No and an important thing,
he/she happens with a lot of people.
They pass for here as well as you did,
he/she sees a house in the edge of a beautiful lake.
Some say for himself:
That beautiful place to resume the life.
I moved for here
after mine I divorce.
And good?
Yes and optimo...
As a life totally new.
Everything well, that and very nice of the
his/her part, I would like that for the Shepherd.
Ok, think well about the subject
and I tie him/her of turn, thank you.
Hello, I am Duan MacClein.
I know.
He/she fit.
- Hello wanted?
- Hello mother.
- One for you.
- Wohou!
- Thank you mamma.
- One for you. You are welcome.
Do you know him/it how much I love you, don't they know?
- Beautiful?
- Yes.
- I don't want to annoy you, but...
- What was? What?
I know that this and very difficult, but...
I really think that
we should think about the funeral, wanted.
- I am going with you.
- No, I already treated of everything.
- What?
- I already treated of all of the details.
Everything!
When and what leaning what will be made?
The funeral and tomorrow, this everything treaty.
- Saturday?
- Saturday.
Tao early?
Yes, so early.
You these well, done want?
Mother?
Uhum?
If I let to die him...
And the same thing that killing?
Wanted, Jim already this died.
Dear good night.
Girls, they can do
less noise, please?
- Hot Sunday.
- All the day.
Because you don't take the
children for walking?
You know, they be one
little of together time.
Have fun a little.
Yes, this well. And a good idea.
You want that eats him/it knife some
pancakes for the coffee of the guile?
- Yes!
Hello priest...
Beautiful...
There is how long.
I am afraid priest.
Some didn't diffuse. He/she ate!
Dutch presenter of
you moderated in Carolina's coast.
A hysterical woman declares...
to have gone by a terrible hurricane
that still had not happened.
Then the one what with she happened?
They hung her/it for being witch.
Two days later, the city
he/she completes was pulled by a hurricane.
And horrible.
We are going to the half of the century XX.
Boston 1918.
During the big it influences of the epidemics.
The priest said there are some
friends that it had been in the future.
He/she saw the two small children's graves.
When he was crazy, he/she threw us
two for not spreading the disease.
Oh my God.
The autopsy showed that the
children were never infected.
He committed suicide
one week later.
Who are those people,
because that happened?
See...
This world and full of...
inexplicable phenomena.
Nobody knows him/it because.
Some people find, that them
they suffer than the old ones call of...
Blessed for the
absenteeism of Judas.
The dangers of the little faith.
Little faith.
And the notion that the nature
of the horror this in the own back yard.
Same spiritually.
The people that lost their faiths
they are as empty cans.
They are more susceptiveis of they have their lives
taken by other larger forks than them own.
He/she resembles a curse more.
Or a miracle.
Because, but I don't believe in miracles.
Everyday ours
life can be a miracle.
I don't feel in that way, not for me.
Priest...
Something horrible this to happen.
I need itself, I need
of his/her help, I need a direction.
I need faith.
Faith, and just to have faith in
something hauls of you own.
Something that you are not able to
to feel, to smell or to play...
As hope... or love.
I believe that go
to leave that everything go leave.
Maybe you should try
to rescue that again everything.
But if it goes too late?
Never and late too much, to notice
the one that and important in your life...
to struggle for her.
I don't know for the that I should struggle.
Plate of 220 miles
It was in the fast road, lady,
in the mark of the 220 miles.
Sra. Hanson?
Mrs.?
Who are these people?
Because and what did they come?
And only an inexplicable phenomenon.
- Bridgette! No Bridgette!
- He/she won't be long a lot.
Open! Open! No!
Obviously you this
working with inconsistencies.
Mother! Mother.
Dangerous, I fear me.
I am Claire Frances...
His/her husband has been a help
enormous in those you finish weeks.
As if he/she sits down, during
the period in what him this died?
We don't want that nobody
be hurt, yes?
- I like than Jim does.
- Everything has a sense.
And the same thing that killing.
And as if he didn't exist.
220 miles
- Did you have fun?
- Yes, yes, we had a lot of fun.
That good.
He/she lets to help me you with that.
I will drink a beer.
Oh, beautiful girls.
Good night.
- Good night.
drink.
Ei! Because and that my girls no
do they give an extra-tight hug to the it eats?
This well, this well.
This 'because of what?
The mamma told us for
to give you an extra hug.
Hugs extra? He/she eats adores him
extra hugs, and kisses!
They are going to bed,
and brush the teeth.
Why don't Ei girls, say
to the it eats him/it how much you like him/it him?
- I like you eats.
- And Me also.
Well, thank you senhorinhas.
Won't you tell them?
- To tell them the one what?
- That like them a lot.
Do you really adore them, no and?
Of course adores.
Then he/she tells them.
The girls know him/it
how much do I adore them, no and?
Is there, no and?
I adore you more than any
another thing in the whole world.
The mamma also.
Plus than any thing.
I really love your mother...
I love her a lot.
Beautiful?!
What these to do outside?
Wanted, we will return inside.
How and what did we arrive to this point, Jim?
I feel the lack of you.
I feel the lack of us.
He/she continues her be us,
only and different now, and only that.
- Because? Because and what and different?
- I don't know him/it because!
- How did you hope went?
- In the way that be.
He/she looks at us. We are married,
a house, a mortgage, two children.
Why do have to speak of that now?
Why are not just going inside?
Because we are to be without time!
Care!
I feel a lot...
I feel a lot, even.
- What was?
- What?
La in my work.
Which work?
You wanted to tell me there something.
I had a dream
in that you will die.
It was only a dream...
Everything had run well.
- Hello.
- Annie, Annie that day and today?
And Wednesday, and Wednesday,
which and the problem?
Girls? Girls? Jim?! Jim?!
Jim?
Oh shit.
The girls are to go for school.
Hi, here and Jim Hanson, I am not able to
to assist his/her call at this time, but...
if he/she leaves a message, me
I tie him/her as soon as is possible...
Thank you for having called.
I have condic.es of solving
that quickly, without problems.
Thank you Doug.
Ei!
I have just arrived at the place.
It is very pleasant.
I badly can wait
that arrive here.
Jim? This everything well?
Yes...
He/she excuses me, I am not able to,
I cannot make this.
To do the one what? The interview?
Us.
Jim...
Jim?
Attempt, he/she assists Jim, he/she assists.
Hi! He/she called the residence of Hanson's.
You know what to do!
He/she listens, Linda...
I need to tell you a thing.
I was to speak to her serialize him/it that me... he/she said
the children's front in the other night, and...
Me just... I want you to know about that.
it is please reminds you always.
Rays leave! Somebody this to call, wait.
Telemovel of Linda
618-185-9354
"Are you?"
Beautiful!
- Jim!
- I love you dear.
I need to tell you a thing.
This everything well, I know on
her, I know about Claire.
- Do you know?
- Yes.
- I need to explain but...
- Wanted, wanted, he/she listens to me...
I thought that was that that
I wanted but no and, me only...
I want to put the things
better, does he/she know? Among us...
...cost what to cost.
I am you to see, I am you
to see, I am really behind you.
Oh these?
I will lean.
Thank you.
I get to see you wanted.
220 miles
Oh not.
Jim, do you love me?
Do you trust me?
of course yes.
Then he/she makes stocking returns now.
What? I am not to notice...
he/she "Makes stocking returns!"
Jim!
These well? Jim?
Jim?
Dear these well?
do you Get to hear me?
You these well?
Jim? Do you get to hear me?
He/she excuses, I let the telephone to fall.
I love you, we are going home.
This well, wait.
Ah, diffuses!
Oh not. Oh not. No!
Jim! Jim! He/she leaves the car!
Jim! He/she leaves the car!
Jesus!
Jim!
Jim leaves the car!
Jim! Jim! He/she leaves the car!
Dear!
No!
He/she sucks, they are here!
- Well, he/she drinks, the mamma must have fallen asleep.
- He/she sucks the guests are here.
I know, I heard.
He/she knows so well.
Why and that you don't go down,
am I already going in one second, this well?
This well.
They just believed in something for of
behind of them own, as hope, love.
Never and late too much, to notice
the one that and important in your life...
...to struggle for that.
Why don't I know should struggle.
Everyday of our life
they can be a miracle.