They say most of your brain
shuts down in cryo-sleep.
All but the primitive side...
...the animal side.
No wonder I'm still awake.
Transporting me with civilians.
Sounded like 40, 40-plus.
Heard an Arab voice.
Some hoodoo holy man.
Probably on his way to New Mecca.
But what route?
What route?
Smelled a woman.
Sweat, boots, tool belt, leather.
Prospector type.
Free settlers.
And they only take the back roads.
And here's my real problem:
Mr. Johns, blue-eyed devil.
Planning on taking me back to slam...
...only this time he picked a ghost lane.
A long time between stops.
A long time for something to go wrong.
Why did I fall on you?
He's dead.
Captain's dead.
I was looking right at him.
The chrono shows we are 22 weeks out.
So gravity was not supposed to
kick in for another 19--
-Why did I fall at all?
-Did you hear what I said?
Captain's dead.
1,550 millibars.
Dropping 20 mb per minute--Shit!
We're hemorrhaging air.
Something took a swipe at us.
Just tell me we're still
in the shipping lane.
Just show me all those stars.
Come on! Those big, bright--
What?
This is an emergency dispatch from
merchant vessel, Hunter Gratzner,
en route to the Tangiers system
with 40 commercial passengers on board.
We have been knocked out of our
shipping lane and are currently
entering the atmosphere of a planetary
body in the following position:
X-38-stroke-5
Y-95-stroke-8, Z-21--
Fry, where the hell's our comms?
Rate of descent beyond known limits.
Rate of descent beyond--
Hey, they trained you for this
Fry, right?
Deploy lower air brakes now.
-Deploy lower air brakes now.
-Center of gravity too far aft.
Recommend purging ballast now.
What the....
Was that a purge, Fry?
Too heavy in the ass!
Can't get my fucking nose down!
Crisis program selected Number 2 in
the system because it shows some oxygen.
Maximum terrain:
220 meters over mean surface...
...largely cinder and gypsum
with some evaporite deposits.
Fry, what the hell are you doing?
I gotta drop more load.
Look, I tried everything else.
I still got no horizon.
You gotta try everything twice 'cause
no way that we just flush out the--
Look,  If you know something I don't, get
your ass up here and take the chair or--.
Listen, company says we are responsible
for every single one of those people, Fry.
What, we both die
out of sheer fucking nobility?
Don't you touch that handle, Fry!
I'm not gonna die for them!
-Air lock doors not secure.
-Owens!
70 seconds, Fry! You still have
70 seconds to level this beast out!
-damnit! shit! SHIT!! SHIT!!!
-Air lock doors not secure--
Air lock doors not secure.
Air lock--
What the fuck is happening up there?
-Imam? ...Imam?
-...Zeke?
Somebody's gonna get hurt
one of these days.
It ain't gonna be me.
Here, Shazza.
So, I guess something went wrong.
I'm sorry.
Get it out of me!
Don't touch it!
Don't--Don't you touch that handle!
-Leave it alone.
-Get it out of him.
No, No, No.
It's too close to his heart.
There's some Anestaphine in the med-lock
in the back of the cabin.
Not anymore there's not.
Get out of here.
Everyone.
Teach me for flying coach.
Interesting.
Is anyone else
having difficulties breathing?
Yeah. I feel one lung short.
All of us.
I feel like I just ran or something.
There was talk of a scouting party looking
for other people, but--then we saw this.
What the bloody hell happened?
Could have been a meteor storm.
Might have been a rogue comet.
-I don't know.
-Well, I for one am thoroughly grateful.
This beast wasn't made
to land like this, but...
...I think you did well.
Actually, the only reason
we're alive is because of her.
Yes, I suppose you're right.
Thanks very much.
Yeah.
Thanks for saving our dicks.
No, really.
Thanks awfully.
Well done.
He just escaped from a maximum prison.
So, do we just keep him locked up forever?
Well, that would be my choice.
-Is he really that dangerous?
-Only around humans.
I'll bet the whole container's upside
down, it's all--it's all topsy-turvy.
Well, thank goodness
it's not a total loss.
Booze?
This is what you have to drink?
I'm gonna need a receipt for that.
For all of these. This is my personal stuff.
I don't suppose this will help you at all.
Unfortunately, it is not permitted.
Especially while on Hajj.
-You realize there's no water, don't you?
-All deserts have water.
-It only waits to be found.
-I hope you're right.
All the more for me then.
Motherfucker.
What the hell are these?
They're Maratha crow-bill war Picks
from Northern India. Very rare.
And this?
That's a hunting blow-dart pipe
from Northern Papua New Guinea.
And that's very, very rare,
since the tribe is now extinct.
'Cause they couldn't hunt shit with
these things, would be my guess.
Well then, what's the point, anyway?
I mean, If the man is gone, he's gone.
-Why should he bother us?
-Maybe to take what you got...
...Maybe to work your nerves.
Or maybe he'll just come back
and skull-fuck you in your sleep.
Sounds like a charmer.
For you.
There we go.
-Yeah?
-Yeah.
Imam! If we're looking for water,
we should leave soon.
Before nightfall, while it's cooler.
Ali.
Excuse me.
I think you should see this.
Three suns?
Bloody hell.
So much for your nightfall.
So much for my cocktail hour.
We take this as a good sign...
...a path, direction from Allah.
Blue sun, blue water.
Ever wondered why I'm an atheist?
It's a bit of a bad sign.
That's Riddick's direction.
I thought you found his restraints
over there. Towards sunset.
Right. Which means
he went towards sunrise.
Zeke.
Fully-loaded clip. Safety's on.
One shot if you spot him, okay?
Don't tell me you're going off, too.
What happens if Mr. Riddick spots us first?
There'll be no shots.
Quiet!
Seven stones to keep the devil at bay.
Sorry.
So, did you see anything?
No Riddick.
Trees...trees mean water.
You comfy up there?
Yes, well, its amazing how you can
do without the necessities of life,
-provided you have the little luxuries.
-Just keep your bloody eyes open.
I don't want that dog sneaking up
on my bloody ass.
Yes, well, you dig the graves.
I'll hold the fort, old boy--
-Christ!
-He'd probably get you right here...
...right under the jaw,
and you'd never even hear him coming.
-Because that's how good he is.
-Tell me something,
Did you run away from your parents
or did they run away from you?
It's a communal graveyard, perhaps.
Like the elephants of Earth.
He asks what could have killed
so many great things.
Is this whole planet dead?
Drink?
Probably shouldn't do this.
Dehydrates you even more.
You're probably right.
You know, you could've stayed back
at the ship. Probably should've.
We don't find water,
you know what happens.
I wanted to get away.
I've never seen a captain
so ready to leave her ship.
-I think we should keep moving.
-What did Owens mean...
...about not touching the handle?
This is between you and me, Carolyn.
I promise.
I'm not your captain.
During the landing when...
...things were at their worst,
Owens was at his best.
He's the one that stopped the docking pilot
from dumping the main cabin.
-Passengers.
-And the docking pilot being?
I guess I'm a little more glad
to be here than I thought.
Hassan! Suleiman!
Captain.
Is there anyone here?
There was water here.
Lights?
Lights on? ...
Okay.
They are saying, "God is great."
Yes.
This is the source of the water.
No darkness.
No lights because no darkness.
Hello, Mecca!
Tell me that was you just now.
What are you going on about?
He's been right here helping me.
Back of the ship.
That noise?
You trying to tell me
that was someone else?
No!
Oh, my God. I thought I was the only one
who got out of the crash alive.
It was just somebody else.
It was just somebody else from the crash!
Crikey, I thought it was him.
I thought it was Riddick.
No juice.
It looks like it's been laid up for years.
-But we might be able to adapt it to the--
-Shut up!
-Sorry, I thought I heard something.
-Like what?
Gunshots.
Dang!
Piece of shit!
What did you do to Zeke?
What did you do to him?
Just kill him. Just somebody
goddamn kill him before he--
So, where's the body?
Well, do you want to tell me
about the sounds?
Look, you told Johns you heard something.
That's fine.
You don't want to talk to me,
that's your choice. But, just so you know...
...there's a debate right now as to whether
we should just leave you here to die.
You mean the whispers?
What whispers?
The ones telling me to go for
the sweet spot just to the left of the spine.
Fourth lumbar down.
The abdominal aorta.
It's a metallic taste, human blood.
Copperish. If you cut it with
peppermint schnapps, that goes--
Do you want to shock me
with the truth now?
All you people are so scared of me.
Most days, I take that as a compliment.
But it ain't me
you got to worry about now.
Show me your eyes Riddick.
You'd have to come a lot closer for that.
Closer.
Where the hell can I get eyes like that?
-Gotta kill a few people.
-Okay. I can do it.
Then you gotta get sent to a slam where they
tell you you'll never see daylight again.
You dig up a doctor,
and you pay him 20 menthol Kools...
...to do a surgical shine job
on your eyeballs.
So you can see who's sneaking up
on you in the dark?
-Exactly.
-Leave!
Leave.
Cute kid.
Did I kill a few people?
Sure.
Did I kill Zeke?
No.
You got the wrong killer.
He's not in the hole.
We looked.
Look deeper.
They're hollow.
I'm in here!
I'm in here! I'm inside!
I thought I heard something.
Please! Can you hear me?
I'm in here!
I'm inside!
Oh my God. Help me.
Give me your goddamn hand.
I heard you, Fry. I heard you first.
-Fry, are you okay?
-Come on.
-What's down there? What is it?
-Did you find Zeke?
-Fry, Are you okay?
-You're all right.
-Fuck!
-Okay.
That was so fucking stupid!
I don't know what the fuck is in there...
...but whatever it is, it got Zeke,
and it nearly got me!--
Get it off me! Get it off me!
-Get it off me! Get if off me!
-Watch it! Watch your head!
Finally found something
worse than me, huh?
So here's the deal.
You work without chains,
without bit, and without shivs.
-You do what I say, when I say it.
-For what?
The honor of going back
to some asshole of a cell? Fuck you.
The truth is...
...is I'm tired of chasing you.
Are you saying you'd cut me loose?
I'm thinking you could have died
in the crash.
My recommendation: Do me.
Don't take the chance that I'll get
shiv-happy on your wanna-be ass.
Hey--
Ghost me, motherfucker.
That's what I would do to you.
I want you to remember this moment.
The way it could have gone and didn't.
Here.
-Take it easy.
-Fuck you!
Do we have a deal?
"I want you to remember this moment."
-Just one?
-For now.
So, you click your fingers
and he's one of us now.
I didn't say that.
But at least this way, I don't have
to worry about you all, ugh...
...falling asleep and not waking up.
-So, could I talk to him now?
-No.
Blast!
Paris P. Ogilvie.
Antiquities dealer, entrepreneur.
Richard B. Riddick.
Escaped convict...
...murderer.
Tha-That's a particularly good Shiraz.
It-It-It's a lovely drop.
It-It's very expensive.
By all means, please.
Help yourself.
All right, all right.
My turn.
There we are, we're gettin' there.
So--
We've got enough power for a sys-check
but we'll still need more cells.
How many are we talking about?
Ummm...Let's see, we got a 90-gig draw.
The other...
...ship takes 20-gig cells, so that'd be five.
Five total to launch.
Thirty-five kilos each.
Well, that's pretty heavy.
You know that old sand cat out there?
I might be able to get it going.
Yeah, do it if you can.
But if you need a hand...
...Where'd Riddick go?
Let's go.
You're missing the party.
Come on, boy.
"Missing the party. Come on."
All praises be Allah,
for his many blessings to us.
What?
It's the winner of the look-alike contest.
-Who were these people, anyway? Miners?
-No, looks like geologists.
You know, an advance team,
moves around from rock to rock.
Nice of them to leave so much stuff here.
Why did they leave their ship?
It's not a ship. It's a skiff,
and it's disposable really.
It's more like an emergency life raft, right?
Yeah, they probably had a big
drop ship take them off planet.
These people didn't leave.
Come on.
Whoever got Zeke, got them.
They're all dead.
You don't really think they left
with their clothes on the hooks...
-...Photos on the shelves?
-Maybe they had weight limits.
You don't know--
I know you don't prep your emergency ship
unless there's a fuckin' emergency.
-He's fuckin' right.
-Watch your mouth.
Hey, he's just saying what
we're all thinking.
So what happened?
Where are they?
Has anyone seen the little one? Ali?
Has anyone checked the coring room?
-Ali?
-Jack, wait, wait.
Ali? ...Ali?
Ali?
Imam?
Other buildings weren't secure.
So they ran here.
Heaviest doors.
Thought they'd be safe inside.
But they forgot to lock the cellar.
Whatever the fuck those things were,
they seem to stick to darkness.
So if we stick to daylight,
we should be alright, okay?
-Let's go.
-Twenty-two years ago.
What?
These coring samples are dated.
Last one's 22 years ago, this month.
OK, is there something special
about that, Carolyn?
I don't know.
There could be.
An eclipse.
You're not afraid of the dark, are you?
So we got to get the power cells.
-Shit, I've still gotta check
on the hull--
-and patch the--
-Wait on the power cells.
What, wait for what?
Until it's so dark, we can't even
-find our way back?
-You don't know when it's gonna happen,
-So let's not get over excited.
-Just get the fucking cells here Johns.
-What, What is the discussion?
-Maybe I should tell you how Riddick escaped.
-He can pilot?
-Yeah, he hijacked a prison transport.
Made a hell of a good run
before I tracked his ass down.
Okay, Okay, Maybe that's a good thing.
Maybe we can use him...
...to help us navigate or something.
He also figured out how to kill the pilot.
Look, you told me that we could trust him.
You said that we had a deal, Johns.