(PHONE RINGING)
GRACE: (GROGGILY) HeIIo?
You still asleep?
No, I´m not:::
Get up: l´m outside:
Why? What time is it?
lt´s time to go:
Come on, hurry up:
You´re late:
Hey:
Hi!
Sorry l´m late:
lt´s okay:
Good morning:
Morning:
Nice pj´s:
Let´s go:
We´re going:
l know that look:
You got to pee:
No, l don´t:
Yeah, okay: Yeah, l do:
Babe, we just left:
l know: l´m sorry:
We haven´t even been
six blocks:
Well, l got to go:
Okay:
l´ll be fast:
Can we go?
Yes:
You sure? Positive?
Yeah: Come on:
Gross:
Here: Hand me that water:
Grab the wheel:
Whoa, whoa:
Come on:
Yeah: That´s impressive:
Thank you:
(THUNDER RUMBLlNG)
(MO VE ALONG PLAYlNG ON RADlO)
l´m excited
for the girls to meet you:
l can´t wait to meet them:
Are your friends
gonna like me?
They´re gonna love you:
(GASPlNG) Look out!
(TlRES SCREECHlNG)
Oh, my God:
Oh, shit:
Did you hit him?
What the fuck
was that guy doing
in the road?
Did you hit him?
No: l don´t know:
l don´t know: Shit:
You okay?
Yeah: We almost killed him:
l´m gonna go see
if he´s okay:
What? Why?
Grace, we´re in
the middle of nowhere:
We can´t just leave
that guy out here:
We gotta see if he´s okay:
That guy is just
standing there, Jim:
He´s not even moving:
What kind of freak
just stands
in the middle of the road
and doesn´t even flinch?
Oh, man:
He´s coming over here:
l´m gonna go talk to him:
No, please: Let´s just
call somebody for help, okay?
Let´s go:
l don´t want to
pick up a stranger
out here:
All right: All right:
(ENGlNE STALLlNG)
What´s wrong?
Engine´s flooded:
Come on: He´s coming up here:
Come on:::
JlM: Fuck:
Come on, start! Come on!
(ENGlNE STARTlNG)
No signal:
This isn´t right:
l´m sure someone else
will come along:
Yeah: l hope so:
You know, l never did
a full 360 before:
First one:
Just keep your eyes
on the road:
l will:
(EXCLAlMlNG)
Man, raining out there
pretty hard, huh?
Yeah:
Hey, Doritos or Cheetos?
Cheetos:
Ding Dongs or Twinkies?
Ding Dongs:
Damn: Lady knows
her processed foods, huh?
Yeah:
Pump number seven:
Hey, there´s a guy broke down
a few miles back:
Can you send someone
with a tow, or:::
Yeah, that´s a no-can-do:
That´s Buford´s truck
out there:
Probably be back
around 7:00:
All right:
l´m gonna go
to the bathroom:
Good:
CLERK: Oh:
You need a key, ma´am:
And there you go:
l´m just joking with you:
Thanks:
That´s a car, ain´t it?
What?
442:
That´s a bad-ass
fuckin´ ride, man:
Regular little
pussy wagon, huh?
Right:
What do you drive?
Been fixing up this Camaro
in my back yard:
Guys want to take
a little break
from the drive,
you can come on over:
That´s all right:
We got to get
on the road, man:
l got a couple of donkeys
in the back yard:
Me and my cousin
raise those things:
l got kicked in the eye:
That´s why l got
a lazy eye and shit:
l tried to milk
that son of a bitch:
You can´t milk
a fucking donkey, though:
You know what l´m saying?
(STAMMERlNG) Yeah:
All right: Anyway:
(VEHlCLE APPROACHlNG)
(lNAUDlBLE)
l´m okay:
There you go:
Thanks:
Hi:
Hey:
You have a motel nearby?
There´s one in Tatum,
about 15 miles north of here:
Hey, l bet you he´s that guy
who was having car troubles:
Yeah: Hey, sorry
for taking off back there:
That was you?
Yeah:
(CHUCKLES)
Don´t worry about it:
l wouldn´t have
picked me up, either:
You still headed north?
Yeah:
Would you mind giving me
a ride to the motel?
Yeah, okay:
Yeah?
Yeah:
What´s going on?
This is the guy
we almost hit:
He can´t get a tow
until morning,
so l told him
we could give him a ride
to the motel:
JOHN: Hi:
l´m John Ryder:
Grace:
Nice to meet you, Grace:
(ROCK MUSIC PLAYING
ON IPOD)
So, where you from, man?
All over:
What do you do?
l´m between jobs: You know?
Yeah:
My dad changed jobs a lot
when l was a kid:
Yeah?
Yeah, he´s a salesman:
lt´s Ford trucks now,
but he´s sold
everything from Buicks
to farm equipment:
That´s probably what
l´ll end up doing, too:
Where you heading?
Lake Havasu: Spring break:
Sounds like fun:
Yeah:
l hope so:
She´s a good-looking girl:
Thank you:
How long
you been fuckin´ her?
Excuse me?
lt´s a simple question:
How long you been fucking
your wife?
l don´t have one:
Well, what´s with
the wedding ring, then?
lt helps strangers
think l´m trustworthy:
Aren´t you?
No:
Hey, hey, hey!
What the fuck
are you doing, man?
All right, you know what?
That´s it:
Ride´s over, pal:
Keep driving:
All right: Okay? Okay?
Look, we don´t want
any trouble, all right?
We just:::
What do you want?
We got money:
l don´t want your money:
What do you want?
You want the car?
l don´t want your car:
Come on, man:
What do you want, man?
Stop!
Hey, what are you doing?
Jim:
lf you fucking hurt her,
you´re a fucking dead man!
Jim:
l want you to stop me:
Don´t hurt her, all right?
Jim!
Then stop me:
(GASPlNG)
How? You´re the one
with the fuckin´ knife:
All you have to say
is four little words:
´´l want to die:´´
Say what?
Don´t say it:
For your sake, he better:
(CHUCKLES)
You want her to die?
No: No:
Say it!
Come on: l:::
l:::
Want:::
To:::
Die:
l don´t want to die!
Get his door! Get the door!
l´m going to kick
this motherfucker out!
Get the door!
(GRACE SCREAMS)
JlM: Get out of my car!
Fucking psycho fuck!
Fuck you, asshole!
You okay?
Yeah:
Hey, hey, come on:
lt´s okay:
Hey, come on:
We´re okay: lt´s okay, huh?
(SHUSHlNG)
lt´s okay:
We should call the cops:
Okay:
What is it? What is it?
My phone´s gone:
(RlNGlNG)
RADIO HOST: WeII, as we
come up on 4:00, I´ve got
something nice and meIIow
for aII you night owIs
out there:
Here´s a cIassic
from David SouI:
(DON´T GIVE UP ON US PLAYlNG)
Grace? Grace?
Morning:
Jim, l just wanna go home:
Come on:
We´ll stop in the next town,
we´ll get some food,
l´ll talk to the cops,
and we´ll be drinking beers
with your friends
by tonight:
Besides, we got one hell
of a story to tell:
Yeah, you just wanna
tell all my friends
you saved my life:
Yeah:
Let´s go eat:
Look at this:
lt is a beautiful day:
Yeah:
(CHUCKLES)
You ever think
about having kids?
Sometimes: l don´t know:
Yeah, l guess, eventually:
Oh, my God!
Pull up, pull up:
Shit!
We gotta warn these people:
(HORN HONKlNG)
Sir, you got to stop!
Hey! Hey!
The guy in the back
of your car is crazy!
He pulled a knife on us!
JlM: Stop the car, sir!
He´s dangerous:
Pull your car over!
The guy in the back
of your car is crazy:
He´s dangerous!
He has a knife!
Pull over! He tried to:::
Oh, shit!
GRACE: What?
(TRUCK HORN BLARlNG)
(COUGHlNG)
Grace:
GRACE: Okay:
JlM: Oh, fuck:
We´re fine:
You okay?
Mmm-hmm:
Yeah:
(PANTlNG)
(GROANS)
They didn´t stop!
We gotta walk:
Give me a minute:
All right:
Fuck!
How did he find us?
l don´t know:
Maybe he wasn´t
looking for us:
Maybe it was
just bad luck:
What about
those people?
lt´s gonna be okay:
No, it isn´t:
(VEHlCLE APPROACHlNG)
Hey:
Oh, God:
Hey!
Stop!
Stop: Stop!
Stop! Please!
Please!
Please stop!
Nobody stops for strangers:
Jim:
Oh, no:
You stay behind me:
He might still be inside:
Just stay here:
You don´t want to see this:
Why?
Just stay there: Please:
(RELIGIOUS PROGRAM
PLAYING ON RADIO)
What is it?
Don´t you come over here,
all right?
Just::: Please! Please!
Oh, sir! Sir!
(MAN GROANlNG)
(WHlMPERlNG)
Oh, Grace, Grace,
this guy´s really bleeding:
l think we got to
leave the knife in:
l don´t know:
What do we do?
Open the back door:
Can you clear it out?
We gotta get him
to a hospital:
Okay:
Come on, Grace!
Sir?
GRACE: Okay:
lt´s all right, sir:
Come on, pick him up:
Pick him up:
Come on, you gotta just:::
(MAN MUMBLlNG)
JlM: Sir?
Sir, stay with me,
all right?
l´m gonna get him
in the back seat:
l´ll get his legs in:
Okay, go on: Come on:
JlM: You gotta drive:
Sir, please:::
Oh, God:::
JlM: Grace!
Be with me in this darkness,
dear Lord:
We´re gonna get you help:
Okay, sir?
ls she okay?
No: She is not okay:
You sure she´s not okay?
She´s not okay:
Try not to move, sir: Please:
How could somebody do this?
You don´t just kill a family:
(CRASHlNG)
Grace:::
What the fuck?
What:::
Oh, my God: lt´s him! Fuck!
JlM: Just keep driving:
l´m driving: l´m driving:
What does he want?
l don´t know: We pushed him
out of a fucking car!
What do you think?
Yeah? What were we
supposed to do?
Let him kill us?
Can´t this thing go
any faster? Just drive!
l´m trying, okay?
Come on! Come on!
Come on:
l don´t wanna die out here:
(SCREAMS)
What do you think?
What´s he doing?
What do you think
he´s doing?
Where´d he go?
(MUMBLlNG)
Oh, shit:
We gotta get this guy
to a hospital, Grace:
Grace, go inside
and call the police,
all right? Get some towels:
l´m gonna stay here
with him:
Okay:
Sir, we´re gonna
get you some help:
Okay? Okay?
Can you call 91 1, please?
lt´s an emergency!
What´s going on?
Towels: l need towels:
Paper towels are
in the bathroom:
Where is your bathroom?
lt´s over there:
Thank you:
(GROANS)
(GASPlNG)
Sustain me in the darkness
which overwhelms me:
MARLENE: Torrance County
Sheriff´s Office:
Marlene, it´s Beth
down at El Dorado´s:
Oh, hi, Beth:
You better get Harlan
down here fast:
(FOOTSTEPS APPROACHlNG)
The Lord is my shepherd:
l shall not want:
Bless my family and friends
as l depart from them:
(MUMBLlNG PRAYERS)
(GROANlNG)
Sir:
l will fear no evil,
for thou art with me:
l will fear no evil:
Stop right there!
What?
Put your hands
behind your back!
Freeze!
Let me see your hands!
Get out of the car!
No, no, no:
We´re the ones
who called you! Tell him!
Quiet! Move:
No, no:::
You´re under arrest:
Come on, move!
No, you don´t understand:
You have to help
those people:
You have the right
to remain silent:
Anything you say can
and may be used against you
in a court of law:
l just saw him right there:
You have the right
to an attorney:
lf you cannot
afford an attorney:::
She didn´t do anything!
(CAR ENGlNE STARTlNG)
This guy you picked up,
he give you a name?
l told you,
he said his name
was John Ryder:
Sit in the chair, please:
Young lady, have a seat:
OFFICER: Where was
this gas station Iocated?
I don´t know:
God, I don´t even know
where I am:
Tatum:
We saw signs for Tatum:
Did anybody see you
pick this guy up?
Yeah, the cIerk
at the gas station saw him:
CIerk got a name?
I didn´t ask him his name:
I´m trying to heIp you:
Put your hands
through the opening:
Look at me:
l didn´t kill that family:
All right?
l was trying
to help that guy:
Come on:
Hey:
Hey, come on!
l don´t need to be
down here, man!
l was trying
to help that family!
l was trying to help them!
And I´m teIIing you
the truth, okay?
I opened the door,
Jim pushed him out of the car:
That´s it:
OFFICER ON RADIO: MarIene,
this is unit seven:::
MarIene, are you
gonna answer that?
Are::: Are you kidding?
Why are you
wasting your time
in here with me?
You shouId be out there
Iooking for him:
He is gonna kiII
more peopIe:
I´II be right back:
Come on, man,
you can´t leave me
down here like this!
(YELLlNG)
Hello?
l know somebody is in there:
I know that you can hear me!
Come on!
I didn´t do anything!
JlM: Hello?
Hello!
Grace!
Just let me talk to Grace:
l just want to talk to Grace:
(SlGHS)
(DOOR UNLOCKlNG)
(OFFICERS CHATTERING
ON POLICE RADIO)
(WHlMPERlNG)
Stupid redneck:
OFFICER 1 ON RADIO:
Torrance SO, SP-214:
It´s been reported
we´re not receiving
any transmissions
from Torrance SO:
PIease respond:
(DOOR OPENlNG)
Hello?
SP dispatch,
no, we´re going to scan
aII frequencies
in case we´re off channeI:
Sorry:
OFFICER 2:
Approach with caution:
You scream
like a little bitch:
Why are you doing this?
You´re a smart kid:
You can figure it out:
GRACE: Jim?
He´s down here!
(MUFFLED) He´s down here!
Jim?
One more word
and l´ll kill you both:
Where are you?
Jim!
Jim, answer me!
l´ve got a gun!
Grace!
Oh, thank God you´re okay:
Everybody´s dead:
Everybody upstairs:
(DOOR CLOSlNG)
Come on: Come on:
Get me out of here:
Okay, okay, okay:
Hold this:
Light: l need light:
Okay:
(GROANlNG)
(SlRENS WAlLlNG)
Come on:
You think they got him?
l think we need to go back:
Come on:
We´re not going back there:
We need to get help:
He killed the help:
Here: Give me the gun:
What?
Give me the gun:
Fine:
We should have gone home
when we had the chance:
Come on: Don´t blame this
on me, all right?
lt´s not my fault:
l´m not:
Yes, you are:
Well, why´d you have to
offer the guy a ride?
l didn´t offer him a ride!
He asked for one:
All right?
That stupid hick clerk
brought it up:
And you agreed!
Yeah! Yeah:
What else was l
supposed to do?
How was l supposed to know
he was a sick fuck lunatic?
You could have
just listened to me:
You okay?
Yeah:
OFFICER 1 ON RADIO: SP-172:
We´re gonna get a roadbIock
started down the road,
I guess, on that side:
OFFICER 2:
This is AIbuquerque SP:
Yes, this is
Officer Garcia:
Go ahead:
Gonna need
the coroner out here:
10-4:
Well:::
He´II show up
in 20 minutes: Out:
Roger:
OFFICER 3: Is that confirmed
they passed aIong
that suspect description
to Arizona DPS?
There´s another one
over here:
Right:
OFFICER 4:
Yeah, that is confirmed:
(FLlES BUZZlNG)
My goodness:
How old did you say
these kids are?
Early 20s:
The boy,
you said he was locked up
downstairs, right?
Yes, sir:
And the girl,
she was interrogated
inside here?
Yes, sir:
Then who the hell did that?
Get me air support now:
l want eyes in the sky:
Looks like we have
a third suspect:
Hello?
Jim?
What?
Come on,
we´ll get one of
these cars:
Jim, get down!
Oh, fuck:
ls there a way out?
No!
See him?
No:
He comes through
that door, he´s dead!
Twenty-one years old:
They didn´t do it, boys:
(CHUCKLlNG) College students:
They didn´t do this:
They didn´t:
You see him?
No, l don´t see him:
l don´t know
where he went:
Oh, God: Jim::: Jim:::
What?
There´s a cop:
lt´s the cop from the diner:
We got to talk to him:
No: No: No:
He thinks we did it:
Only chance we have
to get out of here:
(CHATTERlNG lNDlSTlNCTLY)
All right:
You take this, all right?
Okay:
All right?
l´m gonna go talk to him:
You just watch: Watch:
Okay:
Officer, please,
you don´t understand!
We´re all in danger here:
You aren´t going anywhere
this time, son:
Please, Officer!
This is SO-235:
l have the male suspect
in custody:
I repeat, I have
the maIe suspect in custody:
The female remains at large:
GRACE: Get off him:
State 531 :
We have a support unit
just minutes away:
Do you copy?
Come on: Get up:
Take it easy:
Let´s not go do
anything stupid:
Just stay calm:
l am calm:
Grace:
Hey! Just keep your hands
in the air, please:
Grace, you don´t need
to do this:
Jim, take it:
Sorry about this, man:
We have to
get out of here:
We got to go: Come on,
let´s get in the car:
Please, sir: Please:
JlM: Turn around, please, sir:
Okay: Okay:
Okay:
What the fuck
are you doing?
What am l supposed to do?
We have to get out of here:
l know,
but this is crazy:
l know:
Just go:::
Please get in the car, sir:
Listen: Just take it easy:
Just give me the gun:
No: You don´t understand:
We don´t have time
for this:
We have to
get out of here:
Grace, we got to go:
Come on, please just
get in the car: Get in:
(GASPS)
JlM: What did you do?
Freeze!
l didn´t do it!
JlM: Get in the car!
Get in the car!
We got to get out of here!
SO-236:
We have an officer down!
FemaIe suspect shot Edwards:
She took off
in a Torrance County
Sheriff´s vehicle!
What the fuck
happened back there?
lt must´ve been him!
He´s not going to stop, is he?
No:
He´s framing us:
No: No: lf he was doing that,
he would have stopped
when he killed the family:
Then what does he want?
l don´t know!
WOMAN ON POLICE RADIO:
Suspects armed
and considered dangerous:
OFFICER 1: Lieutenant, we are
in pursuit of the suspects
on Highway 285:
ESTERIDGE: Copy that:
They are armed and dangerous:
How Iong tiII
my air support is 10-97?
OFFICER 2: This is Air 2:
We´re on their 20,
but don´t have a visuaI:
Get on that thing
and tell them
that he´s back there
in the trailer park:
Get on that thing:
Hello?
Is this on?
Can anybody hear me?
Oh, shit!
Air 2 to base:
We´ve spotted the suspects:
We´re joining
ground pursuit:
This is bad:
ESTERIDGE: Grace Andrews
and Jim HaIsey:
This is
Lieutenant Esteridge
with the New Mexico
State Police Department:
How y´all doing?
Listen, we´re really
not too good, okay?
The guy that shot that cop
is back there
in the trailer park
that we just pulled out of,
off of that dirt road:
Well, now, you see,
l have an officer down,
and l have a witness
says that you did it:
So you´II puII
your car over:
lf you feel like
talking about it,
we can talk about it then:
Okay, what do we do?
Just tell him
that you didn´t do it:
Listen to me:
I did not shoot that cop!
Okay?
l didn´t shoot him,
we didn´t kill that family,
we haven´t done anything:
When are you gonna
believe us?
Now, now, now, you don´t
make the rules around here,
you see? l do:
So, why don´t you
just puII over
so we´II chat about it
before this thing gets
out of controI, okay?
We can´t: He´s close:
We can´t pull over here:
lt´s not safe:
Why don´t you
just puII the car over,
or l´ll have my men
help you do it?
We cannot pull over here!
You don´t understand!
OFFICER: Suspects are stiII
not stopping, sir:
l don´t give a rat´s cock bag
how you do it!
You wiII puII them over
and stop them right now!
Over!
OFFICER: Copy on that:
What the:::
Oh, my God!
Oh, shit!
l´m gonna pull over!
Okay! Okay! Okay!
Oh, fuck!
OFFICER: Lieutenant,
ground is firing on suspects:
Hold her steady!
Okay, we´re pulling over:
Please, just stop shooting!
Air 2 to ground,
you got another vehicIe
approaching fast from behind:
It´s a Iate-modeI
bIack Trans Am:
Oh, fuck!
What?
lt´s him, Jim:
Fuck!
ESTERIDGE:
Somebody taIk to me:
Have you puIIed over
the suspects yet?
What the fuck
is going on down there?
Fuck!
Oh, my God!
OFFICER: What´s going on
down there?
Fuck!
Son of a bitch!
You gotta be
five-finger fucking me!
Keep going!
Grace, l can´t go
any faster!
Just drive: Go:
l can´t go
any fuckin´ faster!
Oh, fuck:
(EXCLAlMS)
Where´s he going?
Come on: We got to go:
He might come back:
Where?
Jim:
Get your gun: Let´s go:
Okay:
All right:
We´re good:
Try to call home:
What´s wrong?
lt goes right to
the front desk:
Are you serious?
l should go find a payphone:
Call our folks,
see if we can get some help:
l´ll be back in 15 minutes:
Okay:
Hey:
l´m sorry
l got us into this:
WeII, what about
the Iovebirds?
Are you sure
you wouIdn´t Iike to see
a canary instead?
We have some very nice
canaries this week:
AII right:
AII right,
may I see them, pIease?
There we are:
Whoa, there:
Back in your giIded cage,
MeIanie DanieIs:
(GRACE GlGGLES)
You´re making me horny:
l´m fuckin´ horny, too!
(GASPlNG)
(GRUNTlNG)
l have a gun!
Jim?
Jim!
(TRUCK ENGlNE REVVlNG)
(MUFFLED YELLS)
Okay, l´ll get you:
(MUFFLED) Grace! Help me!
l´m here and l´m gonna
get you down:
l´m gonna get you down:
You´ve got to get me
out of here:
lt really hurts!
l know: Just hold still:
Just hold still:
Please stop him: Please!
Wait, wait, wait:
(REVVlNG ENGlNE)
(BOTH SCREAMlNG)
No!
Stop it!
You´re killing him!
(SCREAMlNG)
Turn it off!
No:
Turn the truck off!
These clutches
are tricky things:
Touchy, you know:
(SCREAMlNG)
One little slip, and:::
l will shoot you:
You shoot me,
my foot comes off the clutch:
Now, get in:
Get in!
Okay:
(REVVlNG ENGlNE)
(JlM SCREAMlNG)
Close the door:
(MOANlNG)
Turn it off:
Stop! Stop the truck!
Turn it off!
l can´t:
Yes, you can:
Just turn it off:
l can´t: l can´t:
You´re sick:
What do you want?
(REVVlNG ENGlNE)
(WHlMPERlNG)
Point it in my face:
Right here:
Do it:
(MUFFLED YELLS)
lt´s your chance, Grace,
your chance to kill a man
who´s gonna kill
your whiny fuckin´ boyfriend:
No! Don´t you say that!
Don´t say that to me!
l want to die:
Now pull the fuckin´ trigger:
State police!
(JlM YELLlNG)
Put the gun down!
This is the police!
Drop the gun now!
Don´t listen to them:
No: Stop: Please:
OFFlCER: Put the gun down!
Go ahead: You can do it!
Put it down!
Put the gun down!
Put the gun down now!
Put that gun down,
God damn it!
l can´t:::
(SCREAMlNG)
Please:
Please, don´t tease him:
Please,
just stop hurting him:
Please!
This is the police!
Put the gun down now!
No:
You useless waste!
No! No!
(SCREAMlNG)
No!
GRACE: (SOBBlNG) No!
Get your hands off of me!
OFFICER: Get up here!
Get up here!
Let´s go, man: This way!
(SIRENS WAILING)
(GRACE SCREAMING)
JOHN: I want to die:
(JIM SCREAMING)
GRACE: No!
Grace?
Grace, do you know
who this man is?
That´s the real John Ryder:
He´s been missing
since Tuesday:
Then who:::
We don´t know yet:
Now, we´ve run
his fingerprints
and mug shots
through every database
we´ve got,
and we´ve come up
with nothing:
This guy´s a ghost:
So, I need your heIp
here, Grace:
Is there anything
he toId you about himseIf?
No:
Anything at aII?
Open cell F!
Ryder, l need you to stand up
and put your hands
behind your back:
l need you to stand up,
put your hands
behind your back:
(CLEARS THROAT)
So, where are you from?
All over:
ls that so?
You´re a sick fuck,
aren´t ya?
The way you tortured
that young man:
l know
you enjoyed yourself:
l just can´t figure out
why you did it:
You knew
you´d get caught:
Why´d you do it?
Why not?
How many others
have you killed?
Hard to say:
You see,
here in the great state
of New Mexico,
we do have
the death penalty:
You don´t seem
too worried:
Should l be?
You comfy down there, John?
Are those cuffs
a little tight?
Yeah, a little tight:
Yeah, you see,
those are the new ones:
They stretch out after
you wear them for a while:
Let me see:
(EXCLAlMS lN PAlN)
Look at me:
You have yourself
a nice trip:
We´ll chat again real soon:
Maybe next time,
you´ll be better company:
Thanks:
Where are we going?
l´m taking you to Albuquerque
for trauma support:
l can release you
to your parents there:
OFFlCER: Step up:
03 X-ray,
we´re about 20 minutes out:
DISPATCHER:
Copy that, 03 X-ray:
OFFlCER: l get home,
l look at my paycheck:
lt´s so skinny:
l decide to take
another job:
So now
l´m delivering pizza:
What are you
getting your daughter
for her birthday?
She´s just turned five:
She wants to take me:::
Go to the mall,
get one of those big
customized teddy bears:
A customized teddy bear?
Come on:
Yeah:
lt´s just another way
they can charge:::
ESTERlDGE: Look, Grace:::
l wish l could have
stopped this
before it got
all out of control:
l know there´s
nothing that l can say
that´ll bring Jim back,
but l am sorry:
l truly am:
Get your own little pants,
your own little jacket:
Make your own
little teddy bear:
For real, you spent
100 bucks on a teddy bear?
Yeah, l know:
lt was hurting me:
Yeah, it´s 100 bucks:::
You know,
this week´s check,
it´s gone:
Stop moving:
What the fuck?
lt´s cool:::
Oh, shit!
Son of a bitch!
(GROANlNG)
My leg´s stuck:
03 X-ray:
l need a Code 3 backup
on Highway 19:
DISPATCHER: 10-4, 03 X-ray:
Grace, l want you
to run up over that hill
and wait there for help:
l´m done running:
Grace! Grace!
That´s not the answer:
You don´t know
what you´re doing:
Yes, l do:
Grace!
ESTERlDGE: Grace, be careful!
(EXCLAlMS)
Backup, now!
Let´s go!
03 X-ray: Where the hell
is my goddamn backup?
You better hurry:
(BANGlNG ON DOOR)
(GRUNTlNG)
Grace!
Go fuck yourself!
No!
(RlFLE COCKlNG)
Feels good, doesn´t it?
l don´t feel a thing: