Sue, you know l like you.
How long have you been
in this building?
12 years.
That long.
And we never had a
problem, right?
But you owe me 3 months
rent now.
You pay me 400 dollars
a month,
l could be renting it out
for 7, maybe 8.
l think it´s more than fair,
isn´t it?
Yes, it´s extremely fair,
Stanley.
l mean, l don´t care, but we´ve
got to get paid.
lt´s still a business,
not a charity.
Yes. l´ll get you the money by
Friday, Stanley, l promise.
Get it to me by the end of the
month. That´s more than 2 weeks.
Otherwise, l can´t carry you
anymore.
l appreciate that.
l´m familiar with all types of
legal paperwork,
and even though l have
no formal degree in law,
l can do any type of contract
and even file suits.
l have all the secreterial skills
that l think you would require
and l feel quite qualified
for the job.
Here´s my resume and
letter of recommendation.
You´ve taken Psychology
and Modern Dance.
Well, l have a BA in Psychology
from Columbia University.
l did take a few courses
in Modern Dance, but...
We´ll be in touch.
Thank you. My primary
background is law, though.
l worked for 12 years
for a law firm.
Okay, thank you very much.
What´s a beautiful young woman
like you doing by herself
on a Sunday morning?
Crossword puzzle.
My name is Willie.
Hello, Willie.
Will you show me your breasts?
Excuse me?
l´d love to see your breasts.
Well, it´ll cost you.
How much?
10 bucks.
l can´t afford it.
Well, that´s the going rate, even
with a senior citizens discount.
What´s a European capital,
6 letters, starts with a ´P´?
Prague. Or Paris with 2 ´R´s.
l think Prague works better.
Where are you going?
l´m going to get a coffee.
Would you get me a
Strawberry Mystic?
A Mystic?
Yeah, strawberry flavor. lt´s
75 cents. l´ll pay you back.
No, no.
Thank you.
Excuse me. You dropped a dollar.
Oh, thank you.
No problem.
You want a cigarette?
No, thank you.
You´re smart.
How can you tell? l mean,
we´ve only just met.
You don´t smoke.
Well, that doesn´t make
me smart.
lt just means l never
got in the habit.
That´s what l mean,
you´re smart.
Anything interesting in there?
Where?
The paper?
Oh, no, the usual crap.
Why do you read it?
Goes well with cigarettes
and coffee.
There you are.
Here, keep the change.
Well, it was nice to
speak to you.
Sue.
Ben.
Nice meeting you Ben. Would be
nice to chat some more.
Yeah well, you have a good day .
Do you live around here?
No, l live in Minnesota.
Minnesota?
That´s out in the Midwest.
Yeah, l know where
Minnesota is.
l´m sorry. New York brings out
the mean streak in me.
lt was nice meeting you.
Wait a sec, wait! Do you
have a pen?
Take it! You can throw
it out if you want.
l´ll give you a call, Sue.
ls everything all right?
Yeah, l´ll take some more
coffee, if you don´t mind.
All right.
Hey Eddie, listen to this.
The other night when
l was working,
there´s this guy sitting
in the back,
and he´s like, ´´hey babe,
we need some more coffee. ´´
and l´m like,
l don´t like it,
´cause l´m not his babe,
l´m not his anything.
But l go back there, start
pouring the coffee.
The next thing l know ,
he´s got his hand on my ass,
so l say to him...
Thank you.
So, l go to take some
other orders,
Then, maybe 10 minutes later,
same bozo wants a refill,
So, l´m thinking, he´s
learned his lesson.
So, l go back there.
Now his cup of coffee is up
against the wall,
all the way on the other
side of the table,
so l have to reach for it
to pour the coffee,
and as l´m reaching to
pour the coffee,
l can feel his hand smack up
between my legs,
l can feel him fingering
my pussy.
l´m like, ´´what? You think
just because l work
in an all-night diner, you can
just finger my pussy
any time you feel like it?´´
l fucking whacked him
right on his head.
He was on the floor on
his ass, it was beautiful.
´Cause, Eddie, baby, you´re
the only one for me.
You dress like a slut,
you talk like a slut,
what the hell do
you expect?
That´s all you have to
say to me
after everything l go through?
You changed, Eddie.
Where the hell are you going?
Good morning, l´m calling
in reference
to your ad in the ´´T imes. ´´
´´Medium-sized midtown legal
firm seeks office manager. ´´
Already? Yikes! Early bird
does get the worm, huh?
Thank you very much.
What do you think?
Oh, l quite like it.
lt´s complicated, but...
really quite simple.
l think l like it.
Yeah, l see what you mean.
These group shows are
so difficult.
They must be very difficult
to organize, l think.
Yes, certainly for
the curator...
Oh yes, for him especially.
Of course, yes.
l think, they did a good job,
l think. Don´t you?
Yeah, it´s curiously
coherent.
Oh, excuse me.
There you are Agnes.
Hello. Nice to see you.
Yeah, sure, go with Agnes.
See what l care.
lt´s a fucked up world,
if you ask me.
l didn´t ask you,
but you´re correct.
Men, all they wanna do is
jerk off in your face
and make you swallow
their cum.
Well, fuck them and fuck
their mothers.
lt´s true. You want a beer?
Thank you. Why not?
How´s everything?
Well, a couple of days ago my
grandmother died from pneumonia.
That sucks.
Well, that´s New York for you.
What are you gonna do?
Listen, you wanna go get
a cup of coffee?
lf l don´t have cof fee
first thing in the morning,
l just can´t do anything.
Especially in the winter.
ln the summer,
l don´t care.
Yeah, all right. But on
one condition.
What?
We go Dutch.
Fine by me.
l can´t stand it when somebody
buys you a coffee and
then they think they own you.
But this once, l´ll invite you.
lt´s fine, ´cause l don´t
like to pay.
Okay, cool.
Besides, this cold weather
makes my tits hurt.
Me too.
Hey, gringo! Can we get
some drinks here?
How can l help you, ladies?
l´ll have a double whisky in
a tall glass with some ice.
What kind of whisky?
´´Wild Turkey. ´´
How about you?
l´ll have a Johnnie Walker
on the rocks.
l love to drink in the morning.
As opposed to the rest
of the day?
As opposed to nothing.
So, why did you start talking
to me in the street?
You started talking to me.
Really?
So, what do you do?
l rob banks and video stores.
Anything to eat?
Yeah, l´ll have salad and
some bread.
How about you, ma´am?
Just go make the salad
and bring me back
a double whisky in
like 5 minutes.
Why video stores?
´Cause they´ve always
got cash.
Besides, l can pick up a
couple of videos,
watch them at home and then
l take them out
on Canal Street, sell them
for 5 bucks a pop.
So what do you do?
l´m between jobs at the moment.
l used to be a dental
assistant.
But then l lost my job when
Clinton got re-elected.
What does Clinton
getting re-elected
have to do with your work?
Nothing. But, you know,
that´s when it happened.
But l don´t care, cause people
stink from the mouth.
l haven´t had a cavity
in years.
As far as teeth are concerned,
l´ve been very fortunate.
l don´t ever go to doctors. lf l´m
in pain, l just drink it away.
l just lost my apartment and
l don´t even care, it´s a relief.
That´ll be 22 dollars
and 15 cents.
No, that´s all right. l´ll take
care of it.
Now, listen up, Billie-Joe,
or whatever your name is,
l got money, but the thing is,
do you really want me to pay?
No, no, l was gonna
invite you.
Folks like you are always
welcome.
That´s what l thought!
So, why don´t you go
to the cash register,
get me 50 bucks
and we´ll be on our way.
Thank you for coming.
No, thank you,
for having us.
Thanks for breakfast.
l got to get going,
l´ll see you later.
lt was my pleasure.
l live right here if you
wanna come up.
No, l´ve got things l gotta
take care of,
so l´ll see you later.
Okay. l live on the top floor,
end of the hall.
l´ll have the money in a week.
You´ve never had any problem
with me, l promise. Okay?
Okay.
Hello, Mom?
Mom, l miss you.
Mom, how are you?
Mom, don´t hang up.
Mom, please don´t hang up.
How´re you doing?
l´ll have a chocolate donut.
Something else?
Yeah, a cup of coffee.
Buck fifty.
Kind of empty tonight.
lt´s getting late.
Keep the change.
No, thanks.
l´m too worked up to sleep.
Well, l´m closing soon.
Why? What time is it?
Getting late. Midnight.
l didn´t know it´s that late.
You wanna go have a drink?
No, thanks, l gotta get
back to Brooklyn.
Right, yeah.
l don´t know what l
was thinking.
l gotta get up early, too.
Thanks.
You´re sure about this?
Yeah. lt´ll be nice to have
some company
and someone to help
with the rent.
Yeah, we´ll have fun. You got
anything to drink?
Sure, yeah.
Unfortunately, when
my boss died,
l didn´t get a reference at
the time, ´cause l thought
l was gonna go into a
different field, but l´m sure
l can get a reference from
one of his partners.
l was the boss´s right hand man,
so to speak, for a long time.
Then, when he died, the office
shut down very suddenly.
Hi.
l was thinking that maybe
you´d like to come over
and have a good time with
me and my girlfriend.
You mean like, ´´good time´´
good time? Or...
Yeah, a good time.
Sure, yeah, why not. l mean,
l´m not busy in the afternoon,
l don´t have anything to do.
l mean, in the evening
l get busy, but...
We were there 3 days,
you know,
when finally the helicopter
came to rescue me,
you know, gets cold up
in the mountains there.
That´s why they call me like
the lndiana Jones of New York.
Take off your coat.
lt´s cozy.
So, where´s your friend?
lsn´t there supposed to be
a third party to this party?
Don´t worry about it,
just relax.
Was that your friend?
Yeah.
Listen, what´s your name?
Lola.
Lola. Okay, Lola? Fine!
Your friend? l can´t do it.
Get rid of her or something.
l mean, l can´t...
Okay, all right.
Just don´t get crazy.
Don´t... crazy? Listen,
you don´t even know
about crazy, okay? l was
shot at, many times.
l´ve fucking killed people for
looking at me sideways.
l´d rather get shot at
than have to deal
with that, all right?
Believe me.
Okay.
Just can we do something
about that?
Yeah
Sue, something came up. l can
explain it to you later, but...
Listen, that´s okay, no, no,
forget what l said, cancel,
l was kidding you. Don´t you
know when l´m kidding?
Yeah, we got 7-Up, beer.
Save the 7-Up in case your
grandmother ever comes to visit.
Hi. There was a girl who
came out of there before,
that wasn´t you, was it?
Yeah.
You´re really beautiful.
But really old.
No, not at all.
My god, your skin is so soft.
Just took a bath.
So what, am l interrupting
something now?
No.
Here´s your beer.
Forget the beer.
Hey, Sue! What´s the matter?
Sue!
What did you say to her?
l kissed her.
One... two... you ain´t got
much, do ya?
Hi, gorgeous day, isn´t it?
How old is she?
lt´s a he.
Oh, sorry. How old is he?
1 4 months.
Oh. lt´s a gorgeous little
thing. Hi, aren´t you?
You´re a gorgeous little
thing, aren´t you?
He´s got beautiful eyes.
Come on, Max, you
wanna go home?
l just... l love the park.
l mean, because it´s so...
Jesus!
Well, fuck you!
l´m sorry, Lola.
l´ll see you around.
What are you gonna bet on?
The double.
Sounds good to me.
Do you want another?
Yeah.
Okay.
How are you today?
Do you need any
help in here?
No, we´re not hiring
right now.
Are you the owner?
l´m his daughter.
Oh, well, in that case,
l´ll have a Johnnie Walker.
On the rocks?
Yeah.
Bright and early
you be drinking.
Yeah.
Have you ever bartended?
Oh yeah, l´ve done
a lot of things.
Like what?
Waitressing, modelling. l ran a
law office for 12 years.
There´s a lot of law
offices in town.
Yeah, but nobody´s hiring.
l just need a job. l got
sick of it, anyway.
Can´t live on unemployment
forever.
Not in New York fucking City.
l know what you mean.
Do you like this job?
l don´t mind it. l´m working
my way through my Ph. D.
Really? What are you
studying?
Clinical Psychology.
The way l´m going, l´m
gonna need your services
pretty badly in about
2 months.
l hope not. l won´t be done
for another 2 years.
Oh, no, by then you´ll have to
fish me out of the morgue.
How much do l owe you?
lt´s on the house.
Thank you.
Hi, Minnesota.
How´re you doing, Sue?
All right.
lmagine seeing you here.
Where have you been?
l´m glad to see you.
Really?
Yeah, l was thinking
about you.
Oh really?
l am!
Lost my number?
l didn´t lose your number.
l was busy.
God, you´re incredible.
ln what sense?
You´re so passionate.
l feel like a teenager.
Jesus Christ!
Well, it´s been a long time
since l made love
with somebody l
really liked.
Do you make love to people
you don´t like?
Oh, yeah.
So, what happened
to Minnesota?
Minnesota´s just
a home base.
l write for airline magazines
and travel a lot.
And the wife and children
in Minneapolis come
to the airport all teary-eyed to
greet you when you come home?
The wife is remarried and
lives in Connecticut.
There are no children.
No kidding?
No kidding.
´Cause, you know,
we already fucked,
so you don´t have
to lie to me now.
l wouldn´t lie to you, Sue.
Well... cream and sugar?
No. Just black.
So, tell me about
your work.
l told you, it´s just
this and that.
l travel to a place,
l do some research,
l get the atmosphere, write
about it. That´s it.
Sounds so simple.
No. Believe it or not,
l used to be a boxer.
That was simple.
l mean, l never thought
l could write.
l can´t even spell.
The trick is, not to be
redundant, to keep it fresh.
l guess the most important
thing is to make
a good impression
on the editor.
Does that work?
l try.
l try to make everything a
little special, a little unique.
What about you?
Tell me about yourself.
Oh, nothing has happened
to me for years.
l go in and out of
the apartment,
l go up ten blocks,
down ten blocks,
l have sex with a lot of strangers
and l watch a lot of TV.
Your life is as interesting
as anyone´s.
Maybe more than most.
Why do you say that?
´Cause you´re yourself.
Because you choose.
So, l choose to be lonely?
Maybe.
Why?
l don´t know.
You never got married?
No. l have only accidental
people in my life, like you.
l´d hate to be thought of
as an accident.
Yeah, well...
l gotta get going. l got
a lot of work to do.
Yeah.
That´s why l came to New
York. To get something new.
Me too.
Something new,
something exciting.
l´m addicted to the city.
Sometimes l think l´d be
happier any other place.
But where else could you find
this level of noise?
l´ll see you real soon, Sue.
No, you won´t.
Hi, Sven.
Hello, Miss Sue.
How´re you doing?
Good.
How are you?
Okay.
Do you want some coffee or
something cold to drink?
Actually, coffee would be nice.
Do you want cream
and sugar? l forget.
Yeah, both.
Okay.
Here. How´s it going?
Good.
Yeah?
Yeah.
lt´s gonna be fixed.
Oh gosh, you´re a
genious, Sven.
What would l do
without you?
l don´t know.
You should still get
yourself a new set.
Okay. l´ll ask Santa.
He´s a good guy to ask.
Yeah.
Hello? Okay.
You Miss Sue?
Me Su Yan Sin, who you?
Sign here.
Hello? Yes, they´re
beautiful.
Jesus Christ!
Thank you.
Here´s to you.
So, you´re still trying to
impress your editor?
l´m still trying.
Flowers? Lunches?
Chocolate?
No, nothing like that.
You´ve been down to Mexico?
No. Why?
l had a job down there,
it was beautiful.
lt was fun. This place reminds
me of a place in Mexico.
l know something else fun.
What´s that? What are
you doing, Sue?
Getting comfortable.
Getting comfortable...
You´re getting more
than comfortable.
That´s all right.
l like this dress.
You do?
Yeah, l do.
You wanna dance?
No, l´d like to take you down
to Mexico some time.
What are you gonna do?
Sue... stop.
Sue... come on...
Sue, what are you doing?
You wanna dance?
Yeah.
You want me to dance?
You´re gonna regret it.
No.
You know why l wanna
dance with you?
l like to dance with you.
You still think l´m
an accident?
Yeah, but a good accident.
No, seriously.
Atall, handsome wonderful
accident.
You really do think l´m an
accident, don´t you?
Well, there´s good accidents
and there´s bad accidents.
You´re a tall, handsome,
good-kisser accident.
How´s that?
You think l´m just in this
for the sex?
Nothing wrong with that.
Come on, Ben, don´t be
a baby. Come on!
Sue, you know what?
Stop, all right? Stop.
There, that´s for the drinks.
l don´t need this.
Ben. Come on!
Hello, yes, l´d like to speak
to one of your hotel guests.
His name is Ben.
He´s about
32 or 34, l don´t know,
something like that.
He´s tall, he´s very
handsome, he´s...
No, l´m afraid l don´t know
his last name, but can´t you...
Okay, great, thank you,
fuck you, too.
We must be neighbours.
Yeah, l live down the street.
l´m Linda.
Sue.
Have you found a job yet?
No.
You´re quiet.
Yeah. l´m not that big
on conversation.
l only communicate
through sex.
Oh.
Oh. l´m not gay or anything.
Well, let´s see...
Have you seen any
movies lately?
No, l don´t go to the movies much.
Why not?
l don´t like to go alone and
it´s so expensive, you know .
You get the popcorn
and the soda.
Yeah, you don´t want to go to
the movies without popcorn.
And that´s 15 bucks
easy and...
You know, there´s a lot
of stuff on TV.
Although l don´t want to
watch too much and become
one of those automated zombies,
you know, no brain...
You must have friends?
No.
What do you mean, no?
Well, kind of lost touch,
you know.
Friends, family, kids. All go
their own ways, get jobs.
You´re not married?
No. l´ve resisted the
institution of marriage
and now it´s probably
too late,
and l´m too old and
set in my ways.
Nonsense.
Hello? Operator?
Could you connect me with
my mother in...
My mother, please.
What´s the number?
l can´t remember. lt´s some kind
of a facility in Seattle.
Portland. Portland. Sorry.
You´ll have to give me
the number.
You dial the area code and
then 5551212.
Operator?
Yes?
Don´t get off the line.
l just...
l just need somebody to
talk to for a minute.
You sound like a nice person.
Miss, we´re very busy
right now.
Yeah, l´m sure, l just...
l´ll be all right in a minute.
l just need someone to
talk to for a minute.
l´ll be all right
in a minute.
Operator, are you
still there?
Yes.
Where are you located?
l just need to talk,
to calm down.
l´ll be all right
in a minute.
Sorry, we cannot give out
that information.
Why not?
For security reasons.
Oh, l see.
l have to get off
now, Miss. l´m sure,
lif you get the number,
somebody will help you.
l´m sorry. l just...
My mother has Alzheimer´s.
My mother has Alzheimer´s
and l haven´t been able
to have a conversation
with her in years.
Operator? Operator?
Yes?
My mother was very beautiful.
l´m sorry, Miss.
You´re a very kind person,
operator, very kind.
lt´s very surprising.
Why is it surprising?
l don´t know. l always
think that
operators are just sort of like
machines, you know.
Thank you very much
for your kindness.
l´d love to work with children.
l feel quite qualified.
l have a BA from Columbia
in Psychology.
When did you graduate?
A little more than
ten years ago,
but during that time
l feel that
l´ve learned a lot of
other things
just from life in the city
and living here
and people that l´ve met.
lt´s just that right after
l graduated
l didn´t feel like pursuing
social work right away.
So, l did some other things.
But now l feel very
interested in it
and l´d like to give it a try.
Thank you very much.
lt´s quite all right.
Then what? What now?
Back home to New York.
Back to the same rut?
No! lt won´t be the same.
l´ve gone straight, honest.
Do you?
l came all the way across
the ocean for you.
Has it been on long?
About 5 minutes.
Thanks.
l told him l want to go
back to work.
He promised he´ll find
me something.
He wants me back.
That´s wonderful, Jack.
Things will be different
from now on.
Can l have some of
your popcorn?
Well, sure.
l can´t make it without you.
You don´t want to throw away
6 years just like that, do you.
You should have thought
lof that earlier.
Don´t send me away!
All right, l´ll go with you.
There´s a flight that leaves for
New York in the morning.
All right.
Let´s get going.
Not right now. l need some
time by myself.
l understand, l really do.
l´ll leave you alone, then.
Look, could you please
stop following me?
Hey, take it easy.
Look...
What´s the matter with you?
Just don´t follow me, okay?
We did what we did,
it was nice.
But just don´t follow me, okay?
Shit!
Hi.
l don´t want anything. l just
like to sit for a few minutes.
Sure.
Are you all right?
Yeah, sure. Thank you.
lt´s a nice dress.
You look great.
What is it?
l´m fine.
l´m going to California at
the end of the week.
lt´s gonna be quite
a change.
l thought you wanna
get your Ph. D. here.
No, UCLA.
Wow, that´s a long way off.
Yeah, it´s a good school,
though.
Yeah.
What is it?
ls there anything l can
help you with?
Sure... 1 ,200 dollars.
Does that sound like a good
deal or what?
l think l can swing it.
No! No!
Yeah.
Why are you so nice to me?
Because l like you.
You look like you´re going
through a hard time.
Well, let me think about it.
l still have a couple of weeks.
You should take it
now, Sue.
l´m gonna be gone at the
end of the week.
lt´s no big deal.
No, no.
What is it?
Oh, l´m okay.
l just had a little trouble
breathing for a second.
You should see a doctor.
No, l´m fine, really.
l´m fine.
l´m here through Sunday.
Okay, great.
l´ll see you then.
Bye.
What are you doing here?
l´ve been looking for you for days.
l can´t get involved with
anybody right now.
Why not?
Because l´ve just got
too many problems
and l just can´t get burnt
by somebody right now.
You really think l´m
gonna burn you?
Yes, l do, l really do.
l´ve been burnt by everybody,
all around me,
ever since the day l was born.
And l just...
l know it´s my fault,
lt´ my fault,
because l get too vulnerable,
it´s not their fault.
But l just... l just
can´t do it.
You´re not even here,
you travel all the time.
One minute you´re here,
one minute you´re gone.
lt´s just...
Sue, l´m not going to be
traveling forever.
lt´s your job.
lt´s been my job for the
past 4 years.
Exactly. And before?
Before l was a chef.
And chefs are nailed down?
l was, yes.
Come on, Sue! Come out here!
Please!
Before that, l ran a video
store for 3 years.
Before that, l was
in the army.
They trusted me... government,
come on.
Sue, it´s all right.
Things change.
My life doesn´t change.
Yes, your life can change.
No, it doesn´t change, that´s
the point. lt never changes.
lt will.
lt doesn´t.
l can´t have children. l´ve
taken a million drugs,
l´ve had a million abortions.
lt´s ridiculous.
l don´t care. Do you hear
me? l don´t care.
ls that true?
Yes, that´s true.
Yeah! Well, thank you
very much.
lt was really nice
meeting you.
Oh, ditto, ditto.
l can start whenever
you want.
All right. Well, l´ll talk to
the guys upstairs
and we´ll call you later.
Okay, thanks.
You left me your
number, right?
lt´s on my resume.
Okay.
Next!
Hi.
ls he nice?
He was really nice to me.
Good luck.
Thank you.
Hello, Miss Kallenowski.
Nice to meet you.
Come in and have a seat.
Oh, sure. Thank you.
Well, Miss Kallenowski.
Sue, if you don´t mind,
seems you have a lot of
experience and...
everything we require in one
of our employees.
So, congratulations, good to
have you aboard.
Thank you so much.
You won´t be sorry.
Beautiful day, isn´t
it, driver?
l said, beautiful day, isn´t it.
Can you hear me?
l mean for New York,
in this time of year.
l love this kind of weather.
l´m going to lunch with
a friend of mine.
He´s a writer. He´s
very interesting.
Well, writers by definition
are interesting
people, though, aren´t they?
l really like this guy.
When l´ve been feeling
good, l can´t imagine
why l was feeling bad
for so long.
l don´t know where the
desperation
comes from sometimes.
What´s his name?
Ben.
Ben what?
l don´t know. But he didn´t
ask my last name, either.
Why didn´t you ask him?
Ask him what?
For the rent money.
No. l told you, l got this job.
Why should he pay my rent?
Commitment. Love.
Sharing.
l mean, don´t get me wrong,
my offer still stands,
but if he´s the right guy,
then he´ll come through.
No, l couldn´t do that.
My number in Santa Monica.
Linda McNeil.
Call me if you need
anything, okay?
Okay, thanks.
My name´s Kallenowski.
lt was nice to know you,
Sue Kallenowski.
Likewise.
Could l have some sesame
noodles to go, please?
Sesame noodles and eggroll?
No, no eggroll. Just
sesame noodles.
What else? What
kind of soda?
No soda. Sesame noodles,
no eggroll, no soda.
Sesame noodle!
No soda! To go!
How much, please?
Watch where you´re walking,
you piece of shit!
What´s all that noise? Where
are you calling from?
l´m at the airport. l got
a job. l´m going to lndia.
lndia? When? Now?
ln 45 minutes.
Well.
lt happened all of a sudden.
l got this job.
Somebody else has
dropped out.
l had to make up my mind.
l needed time to get
ready and go.
Good luck, Ben.
Hello?
Don´t hang up, please.
All right, l´m... here.
l can´t just go without
talking to you.
l don´t have anything
to say.
Don´t be so cold!
l´m not cold.
lt´s not because l don´t
care about you, Sue.
Yeah, just not enough.
l´ll be back!
When?
ln about a month.
Look, you have a good time.
l really have to go now.
Send me a postcard, okay?
l will.
Yeah. You don´t even
know my last name.
Sure, l do.
Kallenowski. lt´s on
your mailbox.
Look, l´ll send you a postcard
from every city, l swear.
Okay. You do that.
Hey.
Hi.
What?
How much?
How much what?
What?
You think l´m a hooker?
Do l look like a hooker?
Okay, l´m sorry.
l look cheap and
decrepid and...?
l look like a hooker?
Forget it, forget it. l´m sorry.
lt´s all right.
No, no, wait, wait.
How much were you
thinking of?
l don´t know.
Well, how about 1 ,200 dollars
and you get the whole night?
Oh well, l was thinking
more like 20 dollars.
20 dollars? All right,
all right, okay.
Look, l´m just kidding. l´m
waiting for my boyfriend.
We´re going to see a play.
l´m sorry, really.
l´m sorry.
Hey...
Oh, no, no. lt´s okay .
Really?
Yeah, it´s okay. Just... could
you help me with my zipper?
lt´s hard.
l know, it´s hard.
Thank you.
l´m glad you´re not a hooker .
l´m glad you´re not, either.
Do you think l could
see you again?
Well, l actually do have a
sort of a boyfriend.
You sure?
Yeah, pretty sure.
You´re sweet. l have to go.
l´m sorry.
You sure?
Yeah, l really do.
You´re sweet.
Have a good time
in New York.
Have fun!
l will.
Sue, what are you
doing here?
l´m just finishing up this
stuff for Mr. Parker.
You didn´t get our notice?
What? No, l´m sorry.
l´m sorry. We don´t need your
services any longer.
At all?
No, l´m sorry.
Please, have your desk
cleaned out by 2 p.m.
Yes, yes, l know Friday is the
end of the month, Stanley ,
l´m not a fucking moron.
Hi, yeah, is Linda there?
No, do you know when
she´ll be in?
No, l don´t want to
leave a message.
l´ll call back, okay.
Yes?
What´s going on?
Who´re you?
Who do you think l am?
Damn it, man. Someone must
have given me
the wrong address.
l´m looking for Lola.
Are you from UPS?
No, l´m her ex-boyfriend.
And close that robe.
Oh, really?
Really.
What are you doing here?
What am l doing here?
l live here.
The real question is,
what are you doing here?
l´m looking for Lola.
Where´s Lola?
What the hell´s going
on here?
Lola has been gone
for weeks.
Where did she go?
l don´t know. l haven´t
heard from her.
Do you want something
to drink?
Atequilla, if you got it.
l have tequilla...
Sit down. lt will cost
you the same.
What do you mean?
l was joking.
What have you got there?
A knife.
Oh, l thought it was
gonna be a gun.
Ain´t you scared of letting in
people, just like that?
Especially guys who´d just
come out of jail?
No, l love violence.
You do.
Uh-huh.
Keep drinking.
l didn´t mean to kill
the conversation.
You didn´t kill nothing.
l come here to kill Lola.
The cheating bitch.
l was going to cut her
arms off.
lt sounds so exciting.
But Lola´s not here.
No, she´s not.
But l am.
You´re some woman, Sue,
you know.
ln a lot of ways you
remind me of Lola.
Really?
You even drink like her.
Thank you.
l´m just going to take
my watch off.
lt´s a gift from my mother.
l wouldn´t want anything
to happen to it when
my arm goes.
What do you mean?
lt´s a joke.
l get it.
You know, you came through
the door, l said to myself:
´´Now, there´s the man
for you.´´
And l have really
good instincts.
You know, Eddie, sex is
very important to me.
Lola never had any
complaints.
Yeah, well, Lola´s
not here.
Hi, Pedro, how´s it going?
l´m all right.
l´d like a chocolate donut
and a cup of coffee, please.
You still owe me 21 dollars.
Oh, gosh you´re right.
l´ll get it to you.
l´d appreciate if you
don´t smoke.
Okay. Then l´ll just have
a cup of coffee.
You can have it if you give
me 21 dollars and 75 cents.
l´d like another cup
of coffee, please.
Thank you.
Hello, Willie.
Hello, Miss...
Sue.
Sue. That´s a nice name.
Thank you.
How´s your wife?
She´s all right.
That feels nice.
l wish l was young, Sue.
l wish l knew you when
l was your age.
No, then we wouldn´t
be meeting like this.
Look, l have a lot of
advantages.
l can work long hours
in the office.
l can take work home. l´m
not married or anything.
so l can work on the
weekend. l can...
You sure, you...
l see, you already did.
Okay, yeah, no. lt´s great,
thank you.
Hi. Yeah, l saw your sign
in the window
that you´re looking
for a waitress.
Yeah, l am. l´ll give you
an application,
fill it out and bring
it back to me.
Thank you.
Welcome.
Would you like some
more coffee?
Sure.
Ma´am, may l have more
coffee, please?
How long does it take you to
fill a cup again? How long?
l´m sorry.
How´s everything?
Fine.
Mom? Mom, can you
hear me?
l just called see if you
were feeling any better.
l´m okay.
From time to time, l get a
little desperate, but l´m okay.
Don´t worry about me, though,
that´s the main thing.
Just don´t worry about me.
That´s the last thing
you should do.
Okay. Well, l just called
to say hi
and see if you were
feeling any better.
l miss you.
l´ll come down for Christmas,
it will bejust the two of us.
lt will be nice, okay?
Okay. Well, l love you.
Okay. Bye.
Oh, god.
Hello, Miss Sue.
Sven, what are you
doing here?
l brought you a new TV.
Oh, Sven.
What is all this stuff?
l got evicted.
Jesus.
ls there anything
l can do?
You really made my
day with the TV.
Can l have the same room
l had last night, please?
Thank you. Come on, let´s
get this show on the road.
Hi. l´d like a room for
the night, please.
50 bucks.
Okay.
That´s cash in advance.
l think l just have 47.
How much?
47. Two, three... 47.
All right.
l have some change.
All right, keep it, keep it.
Room 28, second floor.
You need help with that?
No, thanks.
Got a cigarette?
Yeah.
So, you´re new here, huh?
What´s your name?
Sue.
l´m Lisa.
Hi, nice to meet you.
Sorry. Sorry.
Hey, you got 50 cents or 75
cents for a cup of coffee?
Lola?
Yeah. l´m freezing, man.
Lola, don´t you remember me?
Come on, just like a dollar
or something.
l´ve been out for two weeks,
l´m fucking cold, man!
Lola, Lola! Come back
to the hotel with me!
Lola, come back to the hotel.
Excuse me?
What is it?
There is an old man,
that used to come here,
his name is Willie.
Do you know him?
Yeah, Willie.
l don´t see him. l haven´t seen
him in a really long time.
Do you know where he is?
Well, l can´t help you lady .
He stopped coming here.
When?
About a month.
Susan!
l´ve been looking for you
all over the place.
l must have called your
house 20 times.
When did you get back?
Two days ago.
How was it?
lt was great.
Good.
But l really missed you.
Where have you been?
l´ve been travelling.
Where to?
Nowhere far and
exciting like you.
l gotta go to work.
l´ll see you later.
Where are you working?
l´m temping.
l´ll walk you.
But tell me a little
bit about lndia.
Sue, lndia is a whole
other world.
l´ve travelled all over, but l´d
never been to the Far East.
lt made me realize how much
more there is out there.
How many more options we all
have, know what l mean?
lt just makes me
a little dizzy.
Have dinner with me tonight.
l´ve got so much l want
to tell you.
That´ll be great.
Eight o´clock sharp, your
phone´s gonna be ringing.
l´d love that.
Okay, l´ll see you later.
Not even one kiss?
Uhmm, tonight. l´m all dirty
and disgusting.
Ben, could l borrow a few
dollars, just to tide me over?
Of course, what do you need?
A hundred?
Are you all right, Sue?
Yeah.
You do like me a little bit,
don´t you, Ben?
You´re teasing me, right?
l wouldn´t do that.
Thanks. See you later .
Hello, operator?
l´d like to make this
a collect call, please.
For Miss Linda McNeill.
The name is Sue.
Thank you.
Hello?
Hi baby, it´s Sue.
l´m really sorry.
Sue, where are you?
l´m in a phone booth.
Okay. l´m gonna wire you
some money.
What´s your account number?
l don´t remember.
Listen Sue, l´m gonna
wire it to the Times Square
Station Post Office, okay.
You can pick it up
in the morning.
Okay.
Sue, l´m going to be over
in two weeks for Christmas.
Thank you baby.
l´m so sorry.
Are you all right?
lt´s just l haven´t spoken
to my mother
in a really long time.
And every time l call,
l have this fear
that she´s gonna be dead
and l won´t be able to speak
to her any more.
Yes, next?
Yeah, l´d like some sesame
noodles to go.
To stay or to go?
To go.
Sesame noodles, to go!
l´m sorry.
lt´s okay. What´s your name?
Sidney.
Where are you from?
New York.
Do you like it here?
Yeah. l´ve got to go, okay?
So, see you later.