Do you find me sadistic?
You know, Kiddo...
.
I'd like to believe...
you're aware enough, even now...
to know that there's nothing
sadistic in my actions.
At this moment,
.
this is me...
at my most masochistic.
Bill,
.
it's your baby...
Looked dead, didn't I?
Well, I wasn't.
But it wasn't from lack of trying,
I can tell you that.
Actually, Bill's last bullet
put me in a coma,
a coma I was to lie in
for four years.
When I woke up,
I went on what the movie
advertisements refer to as:
"A roaring ram page of revenge. "
I roared, and I rampaged,
and I got bloody satisfaction.
I've killed a hell of a lot of people
to get to this point,
but I have only one more,
the last one,
the one I'm driving to right now,
the only one left.
And when I arrive at my destination,
I am going to kill Bill.
Now,, the incident that happened
at the Two Pines Wedding Chapel,,
that put this whole
gory story into motion,,
has since become legend.
"Massacre at Two Pines. "
That's what the
newspapers called it.
The local TV news called it:
"The El Paso,
.
Texas Wedding Chapel Massacre. "
How it happened,, who was there,,
how many got killed
and who killed them...
changes depending on
who 's telling the story.
In actual fact,
.
the massacre didn't happen
during a wedding at all.
It was a wedding rehearsal.
Now, when we come to the part
where I say...
"You may kiss the bride, "
you may kiss the bride.
But don't stick
your tongue in her mouth.
This might be funny to your friends,
but it would be
embarrassing to your parents.
We'll try to restrain
ourselves, Reverend.
Y'all got a song?
How about "Love Me Tender "?
I can play that.
Sure.
"Love Me Tender " would be great.
Rufus, he's the man.
Rufus, who was that
you used to play for?
Rufus Thomas.
I was a Drell. I was a Drifter.
I was a Coaster.
I was part of the Gang.
I was a Bar-Kay.
If they come through Texas,
I played with them.
Rufus, he's the man.
Have I forgotten anything?
Um, oh yes, you forgot
the seating arrangements.
Thank you, Mother.
Now, the way we normally do this,
we have the bride's side,
and then we have the
groom's side.
But since the bride
ain't got nobody coming,
and the groom's got
far too many people coming...
Oh yeah, they're coming
all the way from Oklahoma.
Right.
Well, I don't see
no problem with...
the groom's side
sharing the bride's side.
- Do you, Mother?
-No, I don't have a problem with that.
But, honey, you know,
it would be good
if you had somebody come.
You know, as a sign of good faith.
Well, I don't have anybody...
except for Tommy and...
my friends.
You have no family?
Well, I'm working on changing that.
Mrs. Harmony,
we're all the family this
little angel's ever going to need.
I'm not feeling very well,
and this bitch
is starting to piss me off.
So while you all blather on,
I'm going to go outside
and get some air.
Okay.
Reverend, sorry, ah...
She's going to go out
and get some air.
Yeah, given her
delicate condition...
She just needs a few minutes
to get it together, she'll be okay.
all right.
Hello, Kiddo.
How did you find me?
I'm the man.
What are you doing here?
What am I doing?
Well,
a moment ago
I was playing my flute.
At this moment,
I'm looking at
the most beautiful bride...
these old eyes have ever seen.
Why are you here?
Last look.
Are you going to be nice?
I've never been nice
my whole life.
But I'll do my best to be sweet.
I always told you,
your sweet side is your best side.
I guess that's why...
you're the only one
who's ever seen it.
See you got a bun in the oven.
I'm knocked-up.
Jeez, Louise.
That young man of yours...
sure doesn't believe in
wasting time, does he?
Have you seen Tommy?
Big guy in the tux?
Yes.
Then I saw him.
I like his hair.
You promised you'd be nice.
No, I said I'd do my best,
that's hardly a prom ise.
But you're right.
What does your young man
do for a living?
He owns a used record store
here in El Paso.
Ah, music Iover, eh?
He's fond of m usic.
Aren't we all.
And what are you doing
for a J-O-B these days?
I work in the record store.
Ahh so.
It all suddenly seems so clear.
Do you like it?
Yeah, I like it a lot, smart-ass.
I get to listen to music all day,
talk about music all day.
It's really cool.
It's going to be a great environment
for my little girl to grow up in.
As opposed to
jetting around the world,
killing human beings,
and being paid vast sums of money?
Precisely.
Well, my old friend, to each his own.
However,
all cockblockery aside,
I am looking forward to
meeting your young man.
I happen to be
more or Iess particular...
whom my gal marries.
You want to come to the wedding?
Only if I can sit on the bride's side.
You'll find it a bit lonely on my side.
Your side always was a bit lonely,
but I wouldn't sit anywhere else.
You know,
I had the Ioveliest dream about you.
Oh, here's Tom my. Call me Arlene.
You must be Tommy.
Arlene's told me so much about you.
- Honey, you okay?
- Oh, I'm fine.
Tommy, I'd like you to
meet my father.
Oh, my God!
Oh, my God, this is great.
I'm so glad to meet you, sir.
Oh, Dad.
The name's Bill.
Well, it's great to
meet you, Bill.
Arlene told me you
couldn't make it.
Surprise.
That's my Pop for you.
AIways full of surprises.
Well, in the surprise department,
the apple doesn't fall
far from the tree.
- When did you get in?
- Just now.
Did you come
straight from Australia?
Of course.
Daddy, I told Tommy that you were
in Perth mining for silver and...
no one could reach you.
Lucky for us all,
that's not the case.
So...
what's this all about?
I've heard of wedding rehearsals,
but I don't believe
I've ever heard of...
a wedding dress rehearsal before.
We thought:
"Why pay so much money for a dress
you're only going to wear once? "
Especially when Arlene looks so
goddam n beautiful in it.
So, I think we're going to try to
get all the mileage we can out of it.
Isn't it supposed to be bad Iuck...
for the groom to see the bride
in her wedding dress...
before the ceremony?
Well, I guess I just
believe in living dangerously.
I know just what you mean.
Son.
- Some of us have places to be.
- Sure do.
Look, we got to go through this
one more time.
So, why don't you have a se...
Oh, my God. What am I thinking?
You should give her away.
Tommy, that's not exactly
Daddy's cup of tea.
I think Father would be
much more comfortable...
sitting with the rest of the guests.
Oh, really?
That's asking a lot.
Well, okay, we'll forget it.
But how about we go out to dinner
tonight and celebrate.
Only on the condition that
I pay for everything.
Deal. We got to do this now.
Can I watch?
Absolutely. Have a seat.
Which is the bride's side?
Right over here.
Mother, here we go.
Now, son, about them vows...
Bill,
I just wanted...
You don't owe me a damn thing.
If he's the man you want,
then go stand by him.
Do I look pretty?
Oh, yes.
Thank you.
Oh, good.
It's all much more simp...
What the hell?!
No! Bill!
You're telling me...
she cut her way through
88 bodyguards...
before she got to O-Ren?
No, there wasn't really 88 of them.
They just call themselves
"The Crazy 88. "
How come?
I don't know. I guess
they thought it sounded cool.
Anyhow,
they all fell under her Hanzo sword.
She's got a Hanzo sword?
He made one for her.
Didn't he swear a blood oath
to never make another sword?
It would appear he has broken it.
Them Japs sure know how to
hold a grudge, don't they?
Or maybe...
you just tend to
bring that out in people.
I know this is a ridiculous
question before I ask it,
but you haven't, by any chance,
kept up with your swordplay?
I...
I pawned that years ago.
You hocked a Hattori Hanzo sword?
Yep.
It was priceless.
Well, not in El Paso, it ain't.
In El Paso I got me $250 for it.
I'm a bouncer in a titty bar, Bill.
If she wants to fight with me,
all she's got to do is
come down to the club,
and start some shit,
and we'll be in a fight.
I know we haven't spoken
in some time.
And the last time we spoke
wasn't the most pleasant,
but you've got to get over
being mad at me...
and start becom ing
afraid of (BLEEP)...
because she is coming,
and she is coming to kill you.
And unless you accept my assistance,
I have no doubt she will succeed.
I don't dodge guilt,
and I don't Jew out of
paying my comeuppance.
Can't we just forget the past?
That woman...
deserves her revenge,
and we deserve to die.
But then again,
so does she.
So I guess...
we'll just see,
won't we?
Late again.
Budd, can't you tell time?
There ain't nobody in here, man.
- Is that Budd?!
- Yeah!
Tell him to get his
fucking ass back here!
Okay.
Budd, Larry would like
a word with you.
Take a hit. Be somebody, baby.
You looking for me?
I don't know what car wash
you worked before you came here,
that let you stroll in 20 m inutes Iate,
but it wasn't owned by me,
and I own a fucking car wash.
Do you want me to leave?
No, I don't want you to leave,
I want you to sit and wait.
Larry,
there ain't nobody out there, so...
"There's nobody out there, Larry. "
What's your point?
That you're not needed here?
My point is...
I'm the bouncer,
and there ain't nobody
out there to bounce.
You're saying that the reason...
that you're not doing the job
that I'm paying you to do...
is that you don't have a job to do?
- No...
- Is that what you're saying?
What are you trying to
convince me of exactly,
that you're as useless as
an asshole right here?
Well, guess what, Buddy,
I think you just
fucking convinced me.
Let's go to the calendar.
It's calendar time.
Calendar time for Buddy.
Okay, you working tomorrow?
Yeah.
No, you're not.
You don't even know
what fucking day you work.
Here. You're not working tomorrow,
you're working Wednesday.
Here you are. There you go.
- You working Thursday?
- Yeah.
I don't think so.
Friday?
I don't... there's your name.
- If you say so.
- There used to be your name, okay?
Saturday, there used to be your name.
So Monday you're going to...
Here, how about...
how about that?
Fucking with your cash
is the only thing...
you kids seem to understand. Okay?
Now, I want you to go home
till I call you.
Till I call you.
Before you leave, talk to Rocket.
She's got a job for you to do.
And...
the hat.
That fucking hat.
How many times have I told you,
don't wear that fucking hat here?
How many?
Well, customers wear hats.
Well, I'm not the boss
of the customers.
I'm the boss of you.
And I'm telling you...
that I want you to keep that
shit-kicker hat at home.
Yeah, Budd, honey,
the toilet is at it again.
There's shitty water
all over the floor.
Okay...
Rocket.
I'll clean it up.
Well, that gentled you down some,
didn't it?
Yep.
Ain't nobody a badass with a
double dose of rock salt...
dug deep in their tits.
Not having...
tits...
as fine...
or as big as yours,
I can't even imagine how bad
that shit must sting.
Yet,
I don't want to neither.
I win.
Bill?
Wrong brother, you hateful bitch.
- Budd.
-Bingo.
And to what do I owe
this dubious pleasure?
I just caught me the cowgirl
ain't never been caught.
Did you kill her?
Well, not yet I ain't.
I shot her full of rock salt.
She's so gentle right now,
I could perform her
coup de grace with a rock.
Anywho,
guess what I'm hold ing
in my hand right now.
What?
A brand spanking new
Hattori Hanzo sword.
And I'm here to tell you, Elle,
that's what I call sharp.
How much?
Oh, that's hard to say,
being that it's...
priceless and all.
What's the terms?
You get your bony ass down here
first thing in the morning...
with a m illion dollars
in folding cash,
and I'll give you...
the greatest sword
ever made by a man.
Now,, how do you like
the sound of that?
Sounds like we got a deal.
One condition.
What?
She must suffer to her last breath.
Well...
that, Elle, darling...
I can pretty much
damn well guarantee.
Then I'll see you
in the morning...
millionaire.
all right.
Wakey, wakey.
Eggs and bakey.
I'm done!
Get me out of this hole!
Good.
Whoa, look at those eyes.
This bitch is furious.
What did I tell you?
Is she the cutest little
blond pussy you ever saw?
Or,
is she the cutest little
blond pussy you ever saw?
I seen better.
You got anything to say?
White wom en call this
"the silent treatment, "
and we let them think
we don't like it.
You grab the feet,
I'll get the head.
Hey, hey. Hey!
Wiggle worm.
You see this?
You see it, don't you?
That's a can of Mace.
No.
You're going underneath
the ground tonight.
And that's all there is to it.
I want to bury you.
I was going to bury you...
with this.
But if you're going to
act like a horse's ass...
I'm going to spray
this whole goddam n can...
right in your eyeballs!
I'll burn them right out of
your fucking head.
Then you're going to be blind,
and burning,
and buried alive.
Now, what's it going to be, sister?
That's a wise decision.
This is for breaking
my brother's heart.
Once upon a time, in China,
some believe...
around the year
one double aught-three,
head priest of the
White Lotus Clan, Pai Mei was...
walking down a road...
contemplating
whatever it is that...
a man of Pai Mei's infinite
powers would contemplate,
which is another way of saying
"Who knows? ",
when a Shaolin monk
appeared on the road,
traveling in
the opposite direction.
As the monk
and the priest crossed paths,
Pai Mei,
in a practically unfathomable
display of generosity,
gave the monk
the slightest of nods.
The nod was not returned.
Now, was it the intention...
of the Shaolin monk
to insult Pai Mei,
or did he just fail to see
the generous social gesture?
The motives of the monk
remain unknown.
What is known...
were the consequences.
The next morning,
Pai Mei appeared at
the Shaolin temple...
and demanded of
the tem ple's head abbot...
that he offer Pai Mei his neck...
to repay the insult.
The abbot, at first,
tried to console Pai Mei,
only to find Pai Mei was...
inconsolable.
So began...
the Massacre of the Shaolin Temple...
and all 60 of the monks inside...
at the fists of the White Lotus.
And so began the legend...
of Pai Mei's Five-Point-Palm
Exploding-Heart Technique.
And what, pray tell,
is the Five-Point-Palm
Exploding-Heart Technique?
Quite simply,
the deadliest blow
in all of martial arts.
He hits you with his fingertips...
at five different
pressure points on your body...
and then lets you walk away.
But once you've taken five steps,
your heart explodes
inside your body...
and you fall to the floor, dead.
- Did he teach you that?
- No.
He teaches no one...
the Five-Point-Palm
Exploding-Heart Technique.
Now,
one of the things
I've always liked about you,
Kiddo,
is you appear wise
beyond your years.
So, allow me to impart
a word to the wise.
Whatever,
whatever Pai Mei says, obey.
If you flash him,
even for an instant,
a defiant eye,
he'll pluck it out.
And if you throw any
American sass his way,
he'll snap your back and your neck
like they were twigs.
And that will be the story of you.
He'll accept you as his student.
- What happened to you?
-Nothing.
- Get in a fight?
-Friendly contest.
Why did he accept me?
Because he's a very,
very, very old man.
And like all rotten bastards,
when they become old,
they get lonely.
Which has no effect
on their dispositions,
but it does teach them
the value of company.
Just seeing those steps again
makes me ache.
You're going to have
a lot of fun carrying...
buckets of water
up and down that fucker.
When will I see you again?
That's the title of my
favorite soul song of the '70s.
- What?
-Nothing.
When he tells me you're done.
When do you think that might be?
That, my dearest,
depends entirely on you.
Now remember,
no sarcasm, no backtalk.
At Ieast not for
the first year or so.
You're going to have to
let him warm up to you.
He hates Caucasians,
despises Americans,
and has nothing
but contempt for women.
So in your case...
it might take a little while.
Adios.