[Explosion]
YES, THE ATOMIC BOMB
IS TERRIBLE.
BUT MORE TERRIBLE STILL
ARE THE EFFECTS
OF ATOMIC MUTATION.
HELLO...
I'M LAWRENCE WOOLSEY,
AND I WANT TO WARN YOU ABOUT
SOMETHING THAT COULD HAPPEN,
SOMETHING THAT DOES HAPPEN
IN MY NEWEST MOTION PICTURE.
OBSERVE THE ANT,
A MINIATURE MARVEL OF
SOCIAL COOPERATION AND
PRODIGIOUS STRENGTH.
BUT, IF A MAN
AND AN ANT...
WERE EXPOSED TO RADIATION
SIMULTANEOUSLY,
THE RESULT WOULD BE
TERRIBLE, INDEED;
FOR THE RESULT
WOULD BE...
MANT.
[Screaming]
NO! NO! NO!
[Woman On Screen
Screaming]
DENNIS,
YOU'RE GONNA MISS IT.
I FEEL I SHOULD WARN YOU.
THE STORY OF "MANT!" IS
BASED ON SCIENTIFIC FACT,
ON THEORIES THAT HAVE APPEARED
IN NATIONAL MAGAZINES.
[Screaming]
[Woolsey]
YES, THESE TERRIBLE EVENTS
COULD HAPPEN...
IN YOUR TOWN,
IN YOUR HOME.
AND THEY WILL HAPPEN
IN THIS THEATER...
IN "ATOMO VISION," THE NEW
MOTION PICTURE MIRACLE...
THAT PUTS YOU
IN THE ACTION.
[Announcer]
LAWRENCE WOOLSEY,
THE MASTER OF MOVIE HORROR.
IN 1960,
HE HYPNOTIZED YOU.
LOOK. LOOK INTO THE EYES
OF DR. DIABLO.
[Woman Screaming]
YES, MASTER,
I WILL --
HUH?
IN 1961,
HE INSURED YOU AGAINST --
GENE, CUT IT!
WHERE AM I?
NOW, IN 1962,
HE EXTERMINATES YOU...
WITH "MANT!"
[Screaming]
[Scream]
YAAH!
GENE, GOD!
IT'S JUST ME...
THIS TIME.
[Indistinct Chatter]
LOOK, DENNIS.
NO NIGHTMARES, OKAY?
OR ELSE YOU CAN'T
SEE "MANT!"
LAWRENCE WOOLSEY?
HE'S COMING HERE?
THAT'S RIGHT.
TELL ALL YOUR
LITTLE FRIENDS.
WOW!
GENE, THAT COULDN'T
REALLY HAPPEN,
COULD IT,
WITH THE ANT?
IN FACT,
IT HAS HAPPENED...
UP IN TENNESSEE
ABOUT A YEAR AGO.
THIS POOR BASTARD GOT
TRAPPED IN AN URANIUM MINE
WITH A CLICK BEETLE.
HE COMBINED WITH IT.
WHAT?
IT WAS SIX FEET TALL.
THEY KILLED IT FINALLY,
BUT A LOT OF PEOPLE
WERE DEAF BY THEN
FROM THE CLICKING.
[Dennis]
THE POOR BASTARD!
DON'T CURSE, DENNIS.
HOW'S IT GOIN', KID?
SO MAYBE THE GIANT BUG SAW
HIS MOM AND DAD GET CRUSHED
BY A LITTLE KID,
THE GUTS AND EVERYTHING,
SO HE GOES LOOKING FOR
A KID HE CAN CRUSH.
REVENGE...
THAT'S WHAT INSECTS LIKE.
GENE.
GONNA GO DOWN AND
SHOOT SOME TREE FROGS.
WANNA COME?
YEAH, CAN WE?
NO.
NO THANKS, ANDY.
IT'S DISGUSTING.
YEAH,
DISGUSTING.
[TV]
* BRILL CREAM
BRILL CREAM *
HI, MOM.
HI!
WHOA! OH, GENE,
WHAT DID YOU TAKE HIM TO?
A GIANT BUG SHOW!
THE MOVIE WASN'T THAT SCARY BUT
THE COMING ATTRACTION WAS GREAT.
WELL, IT'S NOT REAL,
SWEETIE.
IT'S NOT?
NO, OF COURSE NOT.
THANKS A LOT.
HE CAN TAKE IT,
CAN'T YOU, SQUIRT?
YOU'RE THE SQUIRT!
OH!
MOM, I REALLY WANT
TO SEE THAT MOVIE.
WITH THE BUG?
YOU'RE GONNA GET
BAD DREAMS.
UH-UH, I PROMISE.
MM-HMM.
WE'LL SEE.
OH, YOU SHOULD'VE HEARD
HIS HEART BEAT!
YOU'RE SCARING HIM
HALF TO DEATH.
IN THIS BOX WE HAVE
TWO WHITE RATS.
[Audience Laughing]
ONE, TWO.
TWO WOMEN'S RATS THAT
THEY PUT IN THEIR HAIR.
MARTHA WASHINGTON.
YOU GOT THAT?
REMEMBER THAT.
OKAY.
BRING THE LADY BACK IN.
SHE DOESN'T KNOW A THING
ABOUT THIS SO FAR.
WE WANT TO SEE WHETHER
A WOMAN'S UNREASONING FEAR...
WILL PREVENT HER
FROM GETTING A PRIZE.
YOU COULD HAVE INVITED
THAT ANDY IN.
IN OUR HOUSE?
WELL,
HE IS YOUR AGE.
SO WHAT?
HE'S A JERK!
MAYBE HE KNOWS SOME KIDS
YOU WOULD LIKE.
IF YOU WANNA MAKE FRIENDS --
MOM, DON'T YOU GET IT?
OH, OUCH.
WE MOVE TO A TOWN,
EVERYBODY'S KNOWN EACH OTHER
SINCE NURSERY SCHOOL.
THE KIDS IN TOWN DON'T LIKE
THE KIDS FROM THE BASE.
MMM.
THEN WE MOVE AGAIN
ANYWAY.
SO WHAT'S THE POINT?
YOUR FATHER SAYS
WE MAY BE HERE FOR A FEW YEARS.
OH, DON'T PUT
A PLATE DOWN FOR HIM.
[TV]
WOULD YOU PUT YOUR HAND IN THERE
AND GET THE $10?
WHAT'S WRONG?
THEY SENT THEM OUT TODAY,
A LOT A GUYS FROM THE BASE.
[Sigh]
OUT WHERE?
I DON'T KNOW.
HE CALLED AND SAID IT
WAS SOME KIND OF EXERCISE,
SPECIAL OPS --
AW, SOMETHING.
THEY WON'T EVEN TELL THEM
FOR HOW LONG.
JUST HAD TO GO.
WELL, IT'S --
YEAH. SHH, SHH.
[TV]
$100 IN CASH IF YOU WILL
JUST PUT YOUR HAND IN THERE...
WHERE THOSE TWO RATS ARE.
ALL RIGHT, COME ON.
PUT YOUR HAND IN.
[Audience Laughing]
PUT IT IN.
[Lady]
WHAT IS IT?
[Audience Laughing]
THEY'RE WHITE RATS,
AREN'T THEY?
WHAT DID THEY STOP IT FOR?
[TV Announcer]
NBC NEWS BRINGS TO YOU FROM
THE WHITE HOUSE IN WASHINGTON...
AN ADDRESS BY PRESIDENT KENNEDY
DECLARED TO BE OFFICIALLY
OF THE HIGHEST NATIONAL URGENCY.
THE PRESIDENT
OF THE UNITED STATES.
[Kennedy]
GOOD EVENING,
MY FELLOW CITIZENS.
THIS GOVERNMENT,
AS PROMISED,
HAS MAINTAINED
THE CLOSEST SURVEILLANCE...
OF THE SOVIET MILITARY BUILDUP
ON THE ISLAND OF CUBA.
WITHIN THE PAST WEEK,
HEY, MOM.
UNMISTAKABLE EVIDENCE
HAS ESTABLISHED THE FACT...
THAT A SERIES OF
OFFENSIVE MISSILE SITES...
IS NOW IN PREPARATION
ON THAT IMPRISONED ISLAND.
SEVERAL OF THEM INCLUDE
MEDIUM-RANGE BALLISTIC MISSILES,
CAPABLE OF CARRYING
A NUCLEAR WARHEAD...
FOR A DISTANCE OF MORE THAN
1,000 NAUTICAL MILES.
EACH OF THESE MISSILES,
IN SHORT,
IS CAPABLE OF STRIKING
WASHINGTON D.C., CAPE CANAVERAL,
OR ANY OTHER CITY
IN THE SOUTHEASTERN PART
OF THE UNITED STATES.
- THEY'RE GONNA BOMB US?
- NO. SHH.
...A STRICT QUARANTINE ON ALL
OFFENSIVE MILITARY EQUIPMENT...
UNDER SHIPMENT TO CUBA
IS BEING INITIATED.
ALL SHIPS OF ANY KIND
BOUND FOR CUBA,
WHERE THEY'RE FOUND TO CONTAIN
CARGOES OF OFFENSIVE WEAPONS,
BE TURNED BACK.
WE WILL NOT PREMATURELY
OR UNNECESSARILY...
RISK THE COST OF
WORLDWIDE NUCLEAR WAR,
BUT NEITHER WILL WE SHRINK
FROM THAT RISK...
AT ANY TIME
IT MUST BE FACED.
GENE, IS DAD IN CUBA?
WELL,
HE'S ON A SHIP
OVER NEAR THERE.
THERE'S A BUNCH OF SHIPS
AND THEY'RE GONNA STOP
THE RUSSIANS...
FROM TAKING ANY MORE
WEAPONS IN THERE.
HOW?
IF A RUSSIAN SHIPS COMES
THEY MAKE THEM STOP,
AND THEY GO ON
AND SEARCH IT.
DOES DAD HAVE
TO GO ON TOO?
HE MIGHT.
WHAT IF THE RUSSIANS
DON'T LET THEM?
I DON'T KNOW.
I'M SCARED.
[Thunder]
EVERYBODY'S SCARED,
EVERYBODY IN THE WORLD.
YOU HAVE TO TRY
NOT BE, OKAY?
BUT YOU WANTED ME
TO BE SCARED OF "MANT!"
YOU SHOULD
GET SOME SLEEP.
OKAY, BUT CAN YOU
TURN THE RADIO ON?
[Radio]
...STEAMING TOWARDS
THE QUARANTINE POINT...
500 MILES OFF CUBA
IN THE ATLANTIC.
MEANWHILE, IN WASHINGTON,
ROUND-THE-CLOCK MEETINGS
ARE BEING HELD --
* THE LION SLEEPS TONIGHT *
* IN THE JUNGLE
THE QUIET JUNGLE *
* THE LION SLEEPS TONIGHT
HUP, HUP *
* OWIMOWEH, OWIMOWEH
OWIMOWEH, OWIMOWEH *
** ["Loco-Motion"]
* EVERYBODY'S DOIN'
A BRAND NEW DANCE NOW *
* COME ON, BABY
DO THE LOCO-MOTION *
HEY, LARRY.
LARRY! LOOK AT
THESE HEADLINES.
THIS KEY WEST IS ONLY
90 MILES FROM CUBA.
SHOULDN'T WE POSTPONE THIS
A FEW WEEKS?
YOU KIDDIN' ME?
THE TIMING'S PERFECT.
THIS WAR STUFF SPOOKS 'EM.
THEN WE COME IN... POW!
THE MAIN EVENT.
YEAH, RIGHT.
HANG WITH ME, BABY.
THIS GUY, SPECTOR --
WOW!
"MAN-I-GATOR,"
"ALI-MAN."
SPECTOR COMES TO THE PREVIEW,
HE CAN PICK UP A PHONE,
BOOK US INTO 50 THEATERS.
WELL, HE'D BETTER.
THIS CAME FROM THE LAB.
IF WE DON'T PAY UP
BY NEXT THURSDAY,
THEY'RE GONNA SUE US.
BOY, THIS BUSINESS
HAS CHANGED!
THEY USED TO SETTLE
THESE THINGS WITH VIOLENCE.
THAT'S CUTE.
HONEY?
HEY, BOY! MAKE SURE
YOU GET THE BUGS
OFF THAT WINDSHIELD.
I HATE BUGS.
"SHE-GATOR," "GATOR GAL,"
"GAL-I-GATOR"!
WHY DON'T YOU HOLD ONTO THAT.
I MAY NOT BE AROUND
THE NEXT TIME YOU NEED IT.
WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
I MEAN, WE'RE GOING
NOWHERE, LARRY.
MATTER OF FACT,
WE'RE THERE.
IF THIS PICTURE'S A FLOP,
I'M GONNA LOOK INTO REAL LIFE;
WHICH, AS WE KNOW,
LETS YOU OUT.
WAIT A MINUTE!
YOU'D LEAVE ME OVER MONEY?
IT'S NOT THE MONEY,
LARRY.
IT'S DUCKING THE PEOPLE
THAT ARE TRYING
TO COLLECT THE MONEY.
EXCUSE ME.
THAT'LL BE $2, SIR.
[Truck Horn Honking]
HERE.
THANKS.
HEY, AREN'T YOU
THAT GUY THAT MAKES
THEM SCARY MOVIES?
WELL, YES, I AM, RICHIE.
PLEASURE TO MEET YOU.
WHAT ARE YOU DOIN'
DOWN HERE?
WE'RE GOING TO KEY WEST.
PREVIEW MY NEW PICTURE.
I GOT A NEW PROCESS.
IT'S BIG.
DON'T WANT ANY OF THE BOYS
FROM THE STUDIOS COMIN' AROUND,
STEAL IT FROM ME.
WOW!
UH, COULD YOU --
THANKS,
MR. HITCHCOCK.
[Woman Laughing]
LISTEN, DON'T BE SURPRISED IF
WE GO ON A SURGICAL AIR STRIKE
BY 2400 HOURS.
BLOW 'EM UP! POW!
CUBA'S RADIOACTIVE
FOR NINE LIFETIMES.
YEAH, WHERE'D
YOU HEAR THAT?
MY DAD'S NAVY.
WE LIVE ON BASE.
OOH, I'M IMPRESSED!
WHAT'S YOUR DAD DO?
MOTOR POOL.
THEY STILL HEAR STUFF,
THOUGH.
MAYBE WE'RE ATTACKING CUBA
WITH JEEPS.
IT'S ONLY 90 MILES.
YEAH, WE PUT
PONTOONS ON 'EM.
HEY, SEE THAT KID
OVER THERE?
HIS DAD'S ON ONE
OF THE BLOCKADE SHIPS.
YEAH?
HEY!
TELL 'EM
ABOUT YOUR DAD.
UM, WELL,
HE SHIPPED OUT BUT
WE DIDN'T KNOW WHERE.
DID HE CALL YOU
FROM THERE?
THEY'RE NOT ALLOWED
'CAUSE OF SECURITY.
THAT'S TOUGH.
FACE-TO-FACE
WITH IVAN, MAN!
DAMN, GOT COLOR GUARD.
AH, MAN.
LOOK AT MICHELLE.
THINK IF THE BOMB
WERE ABOUT TO FALL,
SHE'D DO IT WITH ME?
[School Bell Ringing]
ASK HER.
NOW, YOUR RED MEAT
FOOD GROUP,
YOU WANT TO MAKE SURE
YOU HAVE THREE SERVINGS A DAY
TO SATISFY THIS FOOD GROUP.
BREAKFAST: HAVE BACON, SAUSAGE,
SOMETHING OF THIS NATURE.
LUNCH: A HAMBURGER, PORK
SANDWICH, SOMETHING LIKE THIS.
THEN DINNER --
[Air Raid Siren]
[Teacher]
OKAY, PEOPLE.
THIS MAY NOT BE A DRILL.
SINGLE FILE, QUICKLY.
ASSUME THE DUCK-AND-COVER
POSITION WITH YOUR HEAD DOWN.
NO TALKING.
SINGLE FILE.
LET'S MOVE!
OKAY, DUCK-AND-COVER
POSITION, HANDS BEHIND
THE BACK OF YOUR NECK.
NO TALKING.
EVERYBODY, HEADS DOWN.
THIS ISN'T REAL.
IF IT WAS REAL, THEY'D
USE DIFFERENT SIRENS.
HOW DO YOU KNOW?
MY FATHER.
[Teacher]
I SAID, "NO TALKING."
[Woman] NO, RIGHT NOW!
[Girl] NO,
I'M NOT GONNA DO THIS!
WE'RE NOT HAVING THIS
FROM YOU, YOUNG LADY!
THIS IS FOR YOUR PROTECTION!
YES, BUT IT ISN'T
ANY PROTECTION.
IT DOESN'T DO ANY GOOD!
KEEP YOUR HEADS DOWN.
IF YOU THINK
IT'S GONNA HELP...
TO PUT YOUR HANDS
BEHIND YOUR NECK WHEN THE
BOMB FALLS, YOU'RE WRONG!
YOUNG LADY, WE'VE HAD
JUST ABOUT ENOUGH OF THIS!
THAT GIRL'S A COMMUNIST!
HEADS DOWN, PEOPLE!
IF YOU DIE WHEN THE BOMB
FIRST FALLS, YOU'RE LUCKY,
'CAUSE IF NOT...
YOU'RE GONNA GET
RADIATION POISONING.
FIRST YOUR HAIR'S GONNA
FALL OUT, THEN BLEED
FROM YOUR INTESTINES.
YOU'RE GONNA START
THROWING UP, BUT YOU'RE NOT
THROWING UP FOOD.
YOU'RE THROWING UP
YOUR OWN ORGANS.
EEW!
YEAH, "EEW" IS RIGHT.
PRINCIPAL'S OFFICE,
LET'S GO.
BUT I WON'T HAVE
THE PROTECTION OF BEING ON
THE FLOOR IF THE BOMB FALLS.
I SAID, "LET'S GO!"
THEY DON'T TELL
YOU THE TRUTH!
THEY TELL YOU PUT YOUR HANDS
BEHIND YOUR NECK, AND THEY
KEEP BUILDING BOMBS.
WHAT IS THAT?
IT'S A MAN
IN THE BATHTUB.
HE'S LEANING OVER
AND SCRUBBING HIMSELF.
OH, GEEZ.
TOUGH. WHERE'D
YOU LEARN THAT FROM?
MY DAD SHOWED ME.
THAT IS
SO STUPID!
WHAT?
THAT TRICK HIS DAD TAUGHT HIM.
NEVER GIVE HIM A SPOON.
HEY, NAVY,
HAVE A SEAT.
GOOD MOVE.
MAN!
WHAT?
THIS SANDWICH!
MY FOLKS HAD A
FONDUE PARTY LAST NIGHT.
NOW I'VE GOT THIS SLICED,
SOLID FONDUE SANDWICH.
LOOK AT THAT!
YOUR FOLKS ARE HAVING
PARTIES DURING THIS?
WELL, THEY HAD IT
ALREADY MELTED.
ANY OF YOU GUYS GOING TO
THAT HORROR SHOW ON SATURDAY?
YEAH, IF THEY STILL HAVE IT.
IF THEY STILL
HAVE SATURDAY.
HEY, THAT'S DEEP.
I THINK IT'S CALLED "MANT!"
THE GUY WHO MADE IT WAS ON TV.
P.T.A.'S TRYING
TO BAN HIM.
TOUGH.
WHAT'S HIS NAME?
LAWRENCE WOOLSEY.
HE'S COMING IN PERSON.
HE'S GOT A NEW PROCESS.
WHAT'S THE PROCESS?
IT'S THINGS LIKE 3-D
OR WHEN STUFF
COMES OUT OF THE WALLS,
LIKE ON "ISLAND
OF THE FLESH EATERS."
THEY LOCKED THE THEATER
SO YOU COULDN'T GET OUT
IF YOU WERE SCARED.
YEAH, I HEARD
IN THIS ONE TOWN...
THE PROJECTOR GUY
GOT SO SCARED HE DIED.
THAT WAS A DIFFERENT MOVIE,
AND IT DIDN'T HAPPEN.
THAT WAS THE ONE
WHERE THEY HYPNOTIZE YOU:
"THE EYES OF
DOCTOR DIABLO."
HEY, NAVY HERE IS
A WALKING ENCYCLOPEDIA.
[Boys Chuckling]
MY NAME'S GENE.
THEY HYPNOTIZED YOU?
I DON'T KNOW.
THEY GUARANTEED THAT
YOU WOULDN'T REMEMBER.
THAT'D BE THE BEST SHOW
TO TAKE A GIRL TO.
SHE GETS REALLY SCARED
SO SHE GRABS ONTO YOUR ARM.
YOU KINDA SNEAK YOUR ARM
OVER IN THERE.
HEY, QUIT IT!
- YOUR ELBOW DOESN'T COUNT, MAN.
- SURE, IT COUNTS!
WHAT IS THERE, RULES?
[Bell Ringing]
HEY, NAVY!
WAIT UP!
WE MOVE EVERY YEAR,
SOMETIMES MORE.
YOU MOVE EVERY YEAR?
HOW MANY GYM SUITS
DO YOU HAVE?
I HAVE THREE WILDCATS,
TWO PIRATES, TWO COUGARS.
WOW!
YOU GOT A DATE
FOR THAT SHOW SATURDAY?
NO.
YOU OUGHTA GET ONE.
THIS IS A KINDA SPECIAL PLACE
YOU'RE IN HERE.
FLORIDA?
NO, KEY WEST.
IT'S LIKE
THE MAKE-OUT CAPITAL
OF THE WORLD.
IT'S LIKE THERE'S
SOMETHING IN THE AIR.
EVEN GROWN-UPS LIKE DOIN' IT.
GET A DATE FOR SATURDAY
AND SEE WHAT I MEAN.
I HAVEN'T MET ANYBODY.
JUST WALK UP AND ASK 'EM.
IT'S EASY. LIKE, "I'M TAKING
YOU TO A MONSTER MOVIE.
"DON'T WORRY ABOUT THE MONSTER
GETTIN' YOU. WORRY ABOUT ME.
DON'T BE LATE.
I WANNA GET MILK DUDS."
REALLY, LIKE THAT?
YEAH, 'CAUSE YOU'RE
IN CONTROL, MAN.
SHE LIKES THAT.
WHAT?
SHERRY, HI.
HELLO, STAN.
UH, THIS IS MY FRIEND GENE
FROM OUT AT THE BASE.
UH, GENE'S FATHER'S ON ONE
OF THOSE BLOCKADE SHIPS...
OFF OF CUBA.
OH, MY GOSH!
IS HE?
YOU MUST BE
SO WORRIED ABOUT HIM.
BUT, THAT'S WONDERFUL.
I THINK EVERYBODY'S
THINKING ABOUT "OUR BOYS,"
NOT THAT YOUR FATHER'S
A BOY OR ANYTHING.
WELL, HE'S FORTY.
I THINK PEOPLE NATURALLY
REFER TO THEM AS "OUR BOYS."
AND I THINK THERE SHOULD BE
A SPECIAL PRAYER MOMENT...
FOR ALL OF THEM
IN STUDY HALL.
SO DO I.
YEAH?
WELL, I GUESS
I'LL SEE YOU GUYS LATER.
BYE, STAN.
BYE.
HEY, YOU OKAY?
YEAH, I'M FINE.
THE LAST GUY
SHE WENT OUT WITH
IS IN REFORM SCHOOL.
YEAH?
YEAH, THIS GUY,
HARVEY STARKWEATHER,
REALLY BAD KID.
[Gene]
WOW!
I SEE THAT GIRL,
I JUST --
LISTEN, WE GOTTA GET
A DATE FOR YOU.
YOU WANNA COME OVER
AFTER SCHOOL?
UM, OKAY. SURE.
[Bell Ringing]
ALL RIGHT, BETTER HURRY,
YOU'RE GONNA BE LATE.
[Lenny Bruce On Record]
THE ENTERTAINMENT CAPITAL...
OF THIS COUNTRY
IS LAS VEGAS.
WHAT'S THE ATTRACTION
THAT ALL SUPPORT,
ALL OF THE MORALISTS,
ALL OF THE SENSORS,
ALL OF THE SENATORS?
ALL RIGHT, THIS PART HERE.
TITS AND ASS
IS THE ATTRACTION.
I BEG YOUR PARDON.
GIVE ME THE SECOND
BIGGEST ATTRACTION.
MORE TITS AND ASS.
THAT'S IT.
TIT'S AND ASS
AND ASS AND TITS.
DAMN, IT'S MY MOM!
[Mother]
STAN?
UH, WE'RE IN HERE, MOM.
THANK GOD YOU'RE HOME.
EVERYBODY IS SO CRAZY OUT THERE.
UH, MOM,
THIS IS GENE.
OH, HI, GENE.
GENE'S FROM ON BASE.
WHAT HAVE YOU HEARD
OVER THERE?
THEY DON'T TELL US MUCH.
THEY'RE SAYIN' ON THE RADIO
THAT THE WORLD IS
RIGHT ON THE BRINK,
AND THAT IS THE TERMS
THEY'RE PUTTIN' IT IN.
DO YOU KNOW THEY ARE USING
THE CASA MARINA HOTEL
FOR A BARRACKS?
I ALMOST COULDN'T
GET BACK HERE.
THEY GOT ARMY TRUCKS COMIN'
DOWN THE A-ONE-A
HOLDIN' EVERYBODY UP.
COOL!
LET'S GO LOOK.
STANLEY!
MOM, I'LL BE ALL RIGHT.
DON'T WORRY ABOUT IT.
ALL RIGHT, BUT YOU STAY WITHIN
17 MINUTES OF THIS HOUSE,
YOU UNDERSTAND?
AND IF YOU SEE THAT FLASH,
YOU DON'T LOOK.
YOU GET DOWN --
AND I PUT MY JACKET
OVER MY HEAD.
THEN GET HOME
AS FAST AS YOU CAN.
GENE, YOU JUST GET ON BACK
TO THE BASE THEN, ALL RIGHT?
YES, MA'AM.
ALL RIGHT.
MOM, DON'T WORRY.
DON'T WORRY.
HUH!
DAMN!
LET'S GO! MOVE OUT,
ON THE DOUBLE!
GO! GO! GO!
MOVE 'EM OUT!
[Stan]
WHAT'S THAT ONE?
THAT'S A MOBILE RADAR UNIT.
THAT ONE THERE?
THAT'S A
MISSILE LAUNCHER.
MAN, THAT LITTLE THING
CAN REACH CUBA?
THAT'S THE PLAN.
SEE RIGHT OVER THERE?
THAT'S WHERE I GOT ON TOP OF
DENISE ROGERS LAST SUMMER.
FELLOWS, WE NEED YOU
OUTTA THIS AREA.
GONNA PULL SOME TRUCKS
UP IN HERE.
UH, SURE.
MAN, WHAT'S THE DEAL?
WATCH IT!
[Indistinct Chatter]
OW!
IT'S A RIOT!
I KNOW.
IT'S TOUGH.
HEY, LOOK!
HEY, EXCUSE ME!
HEY, LET GO OF THAT!
[Indistinct Arguing]
BOTH OF YOU, STOP IT!
THAT'S MY
SHREDDED WHEAT!
IS THERE MORE IN THE BACK?
THERE'S NO MORE
SHREDDED WHEAT IN THE BACK.
IN THE WHOLE KEYS,
AND ONE OF YOU WILL HAVE TO
GO TO THE ATOMIC DESTRUCTION...
WITH NO DAMN
SHREDDED WHEAT.
WHAT DO YOU THINK
ABOUT THAT?
I THINK IT'S MY BOX --
HELLO, MR. ELROY.
HELLO, UH, SON.
[Elroy]
HEY!
[Translating From Russian]
YOU WILL HAVE YOUR ANSWER
IN DUE COARSE.
I'M PREPARED TO WAIT FOR MY
ANSWER UNTIL HELL FREEZES OVER,
IF THAT'S YOUR DECISION.
HE SAID "HELL."
THAT'S OKAY.
IT'S A CRISIS.
HE HAS BEEN WATCHING THIS
ALL AFTERNOON.
WILL YOU PLEASE
CONTINUE YOUR STATEMENT.
WHY DON'T YOU
TAKE HIM TO THE MOVIES?
THEY'VE GOT ONE OF
THOSE FLYING PROFESSOR
PICTURES.
YOU COULD GO SEE A MOVIE
WITHOUT A MONSTER FOR ONCE.
NO MONSTERS?
NO!
HELL.
- WHERE DID HE GET THAT FROM?
- THE U.N.!
WE HAVE NO TIME TO LOSE.
WE HAVE TO FIND
UNCLE CEDRIC BEFORE
HE GETS INTO MORE TROUBLE.
WHAT DOES UNCLE CEDRIC
LOOK LIKE?
HE'S A SHOPPING CART,
CHROMIUM FINISH,
AND HIS RIGHT FRONT WHEEL,
IT'S SORT OF WOBBLY.
A SHOPPING CART?
YES!
[Woman]
HE WASN'T ALWAYS
A SHOPPING CART.
HE HAD A SPELL PUT ON HIM
AND IT'S ALL MY FAULT BECAUSE --
[Man #2]
ALL RIGHT, STICK 'EM UP,
BOTH OF YOUSE.
GIMME YOUSE PURSE.
[Squeaking]
OOH!
ALL RIGHT!
HOLD IT RIGHT THERE!
UNCLE CEDRIC!
[Squeaking]
YOU SEE,
HE LIKES YOU.
CAN WE GO HOME YET?
UH-HUH.
[Man]
THEY'RE PLAYING THIS THING
ON SATURDAY...
UNLESS YOU PEOPLE STOP THEM!
ASK THE PEOPLE WHO RUN
THIS THEATER.
ASK 'EM WHY THEY'RE SELLING
THIS TOWN'S KIDS, YOUR KIDS,
DOWN THE RIVER.
LOOK AT THIS!
MONSTERS TAKING WOMEN AND --
WAIT A MINUTE!
HAVE YOU SEEN THE MOVIE?
NO, I HAVEN'T, MISS.
UH-HUH.
I HAVEN'T TAKEN A TOUR
OF THE SEWER, BUT I KNOW
WHAT'S DOWN THERE.
[Man]
THIS GUY, WOOLSEY,
HIS PICTURES ARE ALL THE SAME,
A CHEAP THRILL FOR A BUNCH
OF HOP-HEADED TEENAGERS.
WHAT ABOUT LETTING PEOPLE
MAKE THEIR OWN DECISIONS?
YEAH.
SURE, LET THE KIDS SEE IT.
THEY'LL WAKE UP SCREAMING
EVERY NIGHT.
LET THEM FORGET ABOUT CHURCH,
SCHOOL AND --
OH MAN, COME ON!
SURE, AND LET THE FELLAS
AT THE BASE COME TOO.
JUST WHEN THIS COUNTRY
NEEDS TO BE STRONG.
ARE YOU SAYIN'
THESE PEOPLE ARE COMMIES?
IT'S NOT ABOUT POLITICS!
HOLD ON A MINUTE.
IT'S HIM!
I'M LAWRENCE WOOLSEY.
WHO ARE YOU FELLAS?
WE'RE FROM CITIZENS
FOR DECENT ENTERTAINMENT.
I'VE NEVER HEARD
OF YOUR ORGANIZATION.
YOU'RE GONNA HEAR.
I DON'T THINK YOU'RE BEING
VERY FAIR TO MY MOVIE.
THEY WERE FAIR TO YOUR MOVIE
IN LITTLE ROCK, PAL.
LOOK WHAT IT GOT 'EM.
FULL-SCALE PANIC.
PEOPLE TERRIFIED!
[Woman]
LET HIM FINISH!
THANKS. I DON'T HAVE
A BIG SPEECH TO MAKE,
BUT I WAS UNDER THE IMPRESSION
THAT KEY WEST WAS
A PRETTY SOPHISTICATED PLACE,
NOT LIKE COMING
TO SOME HICK TOWN.
[Boy] NAH, DO YOUR WORST.
I WOULD LIKE TO HAND OUT
SOME FREE PASSES SO PEOPLE
CAN DECIDE FOR THEMSELVES...
IF THIS MOVIE
IS REALLY SO TERRIBLE.
THAT'S FAIR.
IT'S TRUE THAT MY MOVIES SHOW
THINGS THAT OTHERS WON'T SHOW,
THINGS THAT SOME PEOPLE SAY
ARE SHOCKING,
THINGS THAT SOME PEOPLE
ARE SCARED TO EVEN IMAGINE.
BUT IS THAT REALLY
MORE TERRIBLE THAN THE WORLD
WE LIVE IN EVERY DAY?
THAT'S A REAL PRETTY
SPEECH, PAL.
DOES THAT
HELP YOU SLEEP NIGHTS...
WHILE YOU'RE TURNING KIDS
INTO HOODLUMS?
I SLEEP LIKE A BABY, MY FRIEND.
WE GONNA GET
FREE PASSES?
HERE YOU GO, SONNY.
HERE. MAYBE YOU TWO
COULD DECIDE FOR YOURSELVES.
THANKS, BUT THAT'S NOT
THE WAY WE GET OUR KICKS.
[Man]
WHAT ABOUT
THE FIRST AMENDMENT?
THERE'S NO FIRST AMENDMENT
TO THE TEN COMMANDMENTS, PAL.
HERB DENNING.
I KNEW IT!
STAN, BEFORE WE GO OUT
ON SATURDAY,
THERE'S SOMETHING
I HAVE TO TALK TO YOU ABOUT.
SURE.
YOU KNOW, FOR A WHILE
I WAS SEEING THIS OLDER BOY,
HARVEY STARKWEATHER.
I HEARD THAT.
IT WAS A MISTAKE.
I SEE THAT NOW,
ALTHOUGH IN SOME WAYS
HE WAS A VERY GOOD PERSON.
HE WAS REALLY SENSITIVE.
DID YOU KNOW
HE WRITES POEMS?
REALLY?
YEAH. I COULD TELL YOU ONE
IF YOU'D LIKE TO HEAR IT.
YEAH, UH, SOMETIME.
OKAY.
ANYWAY, HE USED TO GET HIMSELF
INVOLVED IN THINGS, LIKE
HOLDING UP LIQUOR STORES.
IT'S OVER NOW, ALTHOUGH
HE DID TEACH ME A LOT.
WHAT ABOUT?
WELL, ABOUT MY BODY,
MY DESIRES,
ABOUT BEING A WOMAN.
HE WAS VERY GOOD FOR ME.
[Jet Engine Roaring]
STAN?
YOU DON'T THINK
THEY'RE GONNA SHOOT OFF
THOSE MISSILES, DO YOU?
NO, I DON'T --
BECAUSE HARVEY
WAS ALWAYS SAYING...
THAT THE WHOLE WORLD'S GONNA
BLOW UP ANYWAY, SO WE SHOULD
JUST DO WHATEVER WE WANT.
THAT'S CRAZY.
I KNOW.
THIS WRITER IN NEW YORK
THAT HARVEY SENT HIS POEMS TO...
SAID THAT HARVEY WAS AN
EXAMPLE OF A COMPLETE PRIMITIVE.
I COULD'VE TOLD HIM THAT.
I DON'T THINK THEY'LL
SET THE MISSILES OFF.
KENNEDY AND KHRUSHCHEV
ARE PROBABLY WORKING THIS
WHOLE THING OUT RIGHT NOW.
IT'S ON THIS HIGH LEVEL.
[Sherry] IT MAKES MORE SENSE
WHEN YOU EXPLAIN IT, STAN.
WE'LL HAVE A GOOD TIME
ON SATURDAY.
ONE THING I THOUGHT WE MIGHT DO,
THEY'RE SHOWING THIS MOVIE
AT THE STRAND WHERE THIS GUY --
THAT SOUNDS NICE, STAN.
BUT IN MALLORY SQUARE
THEY'RE HAVING A SPECIAL
EXHIBIT ON CORAL,
LITTLE ANIMALS AND THINGS
PEOPLE MAKE OUT OF IT.
THAT SOUNDS GREAT.
OKAY.
SO, I'LL SEE YOU THERE
ABOUT 1:00.
ALL RIGHT.
* AH-OOH
WAIT AND SEE *
* MY BOYFRIEND'S BACK AND
YOU'RE GONNA BE IN TROUBLE *
[Bell Ringing]
[Sigh]
HI.
HELLO.
UH,
MY NAME'S GENE.
I SAW YOU IN THAT
AIR RAID DRILL YESTERDAY.
YEAH, THE WHOLE WORLD DID.
WHAT DID THEY DO
TO YOU?
DETENTION FOR A WEEK.
WOW!
THEY PUT GANDHI AWAY
FOR A YEAR.
I DON'T KNOW
THAT MANY PEOPLE HERE.
UH-HUH.
YOU'RE NOT ONE OF THOSE GUYS
BY THE TETHERBALL, ARE YOU?
NO, I JUST
MET THEM.
I MEAN, I JUST
MOVED HERE THIS YEAR.
I'VE LIVED HERE ALL MY LIFE.
YOU HAVEN'T MISSED MUCH.
I THOUGHT PEOPLE WERE
SUPPOSED TO LIKE IT HERE.
[Sigh]
IT'S SUPPOSED TO BE THE MOST
WONDERFUL PLACE ON EARTH.
THE BEAUTIFUL CORAL REEF!
THE BEAUTIFUL HIBISCUS FLOWER!
BLAH, BLAH, BLAH.
IF IT'S SUCH A WONDERFUL PLACE,
HOW COME THE NEGRO KIDS HAVE
TO GO TO A DIFFERENT SCHOOL?
I DON'T KNOW.
I GUESS THEY DO THAT --
IT'S BECAUSE THEY'RE NOT REALLY
SUPPOSED TO BE PEOPLE,
NEITHER ARE THE RUSSIANS.
IF THEY'RE NOT REAL,
JUST GO AHEAD AND KILL THEM,
SEND IN THE NAVY.
MY DAD DOESN'T WANT
TO KILL ANYONE.
WHO'S YOUR DAD?
HE'S ON ONE OF
THOSE SHIPS...
OVER BY CUBA.
[Sigh]
I'M SORRY,
I DIDN'T --
THAT'S OKAY.
YOU MUST BE
WORRIED ABOUT HIM.
WELL, I HOPE
HE'S ALL RIGHT.
THANKS.
** [Humming]
TELL ME YOUR NAME.
I'M NOT MAD.
I JUST WANNA KNOW YOUR NAME.
STAN.
STAN, YOU'RE GONNA HAVE
TO GIVE ME SOME ANSWERS.
IF YOU DON'T, THEN I'M
GONNA HAVE TO HURT YA!
WHAT'S THAT
GONNA SOLVE?
IT'S NOT GONNA SOLVE
ANYTHING,
JUST MORE PAIN.
ANSWERS?
ABOUT YOURSELF AND SHERRY.
YOU GOIN' OUT WITH HER?
WELL, WE WERE GONNA LOOK
AT SOME CORAL ON SATURDAY.
CORAL?
SHE LIKES CORAL.
ALL THOSE LITTLE ANIMALS
GIVIN' UP THEIR BODIES TO MAKE
SOMETHIN' PINK FOR SHERRY.
[Sigh]
YOU CAN'T DO IT, STAN.
YOU CAN'T DO ANYTHING
WITH HER.
AND YOU CAN'T TELL HER
WE HAD THIS LITTLE TALK...
BECAUSE THE FACT THAT
THINGS LIKE THIS HAVE TO HAPPEN,
IT'S CRAZY, YOU KNOW?
WELL, UH, MAYBE IT DOESN'T
HAVE TO HAPPEN.
NO, STAN, IT DOES.
IT'S LIKE I ONCE WROTE
IN A POEM:
DESTINY...
IT'S LIKE A CRAZY RIVER...
WHERE YOU SEE
DIFFERENT PEOPLE'S BOATS...
THAT THEY HAVE
GOING BY ON IT.
BUT TOMORROW,
TOMORROW'S A KNIFE.
TOMORROW'S A BIG KNIFE.
YOU GET IT?
UH... SORT OF.
IT'S ABSTRACT, STAN.
[Sigh]
MR. WOOLSEY?
HELLO, SON.
GOOD TO SEE YOU.
COMIN' TO THE SHOW
SATURDAY?
SURE.
I WAS HERE THE OTHER NIGHT
WHEN YOU GOT HERE.
UH-HUH.
YOU KNOW THOSE TWO GUYS
WHO WERE YELLING AT YOU
ABOUT YOUR MOVIE?
OH, YEAH. WE GET SOME OF
THOSE PEOPLE IN EVERY TOWN.
SOMETIMES IT'S A CHURCH GROUP,
SOMETIMES THE P.T.A.
THEY MEAN WELL, BUT --
ONE OF THOSE GUYS
WAS HERB DENNING.
HE WAS IN
"THE BRAIN LEECHES."
HE PLAYED THE THIRD MAN
AT LUNCH COUNTER.
MMM.
JUST CRUISE IT
AROUND TOWN FOR A FEW HOURS:
SCHOOLS, NAVY BASE.
YOU SEE, SON,
HERB TURNED AGAINST ME.
OKAY, HE DIDN'T TURN AGAINST ME.
HE'S STILL WORKING FOR ME.
WHAT'S YOUR NAME?
GENE LOOMIS.
YOU'RE VERY OBSERVANT, GENE.
THAT'S A GOOD HABIT.
HI, HOW YA DOIN'?
SATURDAY NIGHT, RIGHT HERE.
BIG SHOW.
DON'T MISS IT.
HERB'S AN INTERESTING GUY.
HE USED TO BE KIND OF, UH,
WELL, DISHONEST:
SHAKEDOWN ARTIST, STRONG ARM.
SOMEONE SENT HIM TO COLLECT
MONEY FROM ME JUST WHEN
I NEEDED AN INEXPENSIVE ACTOR.
ISN'T IT FUN
TO KNOW THESE THINGS
ABOUT YOUR FAVORITE STARS?
HE'S PRETTY GOOD.
BOB'S EVEN BETTER.
THAT OTHER GUY?
BUT HE GOT HIMSELF ON THE
STUPID BLACKLIST. THAT'S
WHY HE'S WORKIN' FOR ME.
THEY'RE BOTH GOOD.
IT'S JUST HARD TO GET PEOPLE
AROUND HERE STIRRED UP.
COULD BE THIS
BOMB BUSINESS.
I DON'T HAVE TO TELL ANYONE
THOSE GUYS WORK FOR YOU.
YOU WANT A PASS
FOR THE SHOW SATURDAY?
I'VE ALREADY GOT ONE.
WHAT DO YOU WANT?
TO HELP YOU OUT.
YOU MUST HAVE
A LOT TO DO.
[Sigh]
OKAY, YOU'RE WITH THE SHOW
FOR AN HOUR.
THERE YOU ARE.
WHAT IS ALL THIS?
IT'S A SECRET.
CAN YOU KEEP A SECRET?
I ALREADY AM.
RIGHT!
THESE ARE A LITTLE SURPRISE
FOR THE AUDIENCE RIGGED
TO THE SEAT CUSHION.
FEEL THAT.
[Electrical Currents
Crackling]
AAH!
GIVING IT TO THE PEOPLE
RIGHT WHERE THEY NEED IT MOST.
COOL.
MR. WOOLSEY,
THIS IS A NATIONAL CRISIS
THAT'S GOING ON.
IF YOU START
VIBRATING THE THEATER
AND SCARING PEOPLE --
WHAT IS THAT?
CONELRAD, THE
CIVIL DEFENSE CHANNEL.
THEY'RE TIED STRAIGHT IN TO
THE DISTANT EARLY WARNING.
IF THERE'S AN ATTACK,
THEY WILL BROADCAST ON THIS
WAVELENGTH A FULL 90 SECONDS
BEFORE WE HAVE LOCAL SIRENS.
I REALLY WISH YOU'D --
ANYWAY, YOU SEE
WHAT I'M SAYING.
THE COUNTRY IS ON RED ALERT.
PEOPLE ARE ALREADY SCARED.
EXACTLY!
WHAT A PERFECT TIME TO OPEN
A NEW HORROR MOVIE.
THINK OF IT, MY FRIEND.
MILLIONS OF PEOPLE...
LOOKING OVER THEIR SHOULDER
WAITING FOR GOD'S
OTHER SHOE TO DROP,
NEVER KNOWING IF EACH KISS,
EACH SUNSET,
[Crunch]
EACH MALTED MILK BALL
MIGHT BE THEIR LAST.
PLEASE.
WE'RE HALFWAY HOME.
WE'LL FILL THIS PLACE.
WHAT'S CAPACITY HERE?
FIVE HUNDRED DOWN HERE AND
A HUNDRED IN THE BALCONY.
THAT'S ALL FOR THE BALCONY?
SAFETY RESTRICTIONS,
TERMITES, THE TROPICS.
WHATEVER, WE'LL FILL IT.
THE YOKELS
ARE ON PINS AND NEEDLES.
MR. WOOLSEY,
PEOPLE IN KEY WEST
ARE NOT YOKELS.
THEN THEY SHOULDN'T HAVE
ANY PROBLEM WITH IT.
I'M GLAD
YOU SPOKE UP.
WHAT A JERK!
OH, I KINDA LIKE HIM.
YOU KNOW WHERE WE CAN FIND
A HARDWARE STORE?
YEAH, I'LL SHOW YA.
I DIDN'T THINK ANYBODY'D
RECOGNIZE HERB.
YOU SPEND YOUR WHOLE LIFE
SITTIN' IN MONSTER MOVIES?
A LOT, YEAH.
SOMEBODY LIKE HERB
OR VINCENT PRICE,
IT'S LIKE
THEY'RE MY FRIENDS.
THAT'S A STRANGE GROUP.
WHAT ARE YOUR
REAL FRIENDS LIKE?
I DON'T HAVE TOO MANY.
MY DAD'S IN THE NAVY,
SO WE MOVE ALL THE TIME.
OH, MAN! FIVE HUNDRED
NEW KIDS A YEAR?
THAT'S SCARY.
ONE TIME WE MOVED.
THIS WAS TO THE BIG TOWN,
HATFIELD, MISSOURI.
I WAS PETRIFIED
OF THOSE GUYS.
REALLY?
OH, YEAH.
BUT SEE, NOW I GET
MY REVENGE.
I GET TO SCARE EVERYBODY ELSE,
BUT IT'S FOR THEIR OWN GOOD.
PEOPLE GO LIKE THIS
AT THE SCARY PARTS.
THEY'RE NOT GETTIN' THE
WHOLE BENEFIT. YOU GOTTA
KEEP YOUR EYES OPEN.
WHAT'S THE BENEFIT?
OKAY, LIKE, UH...
A ZILLION YEARS AGO
A GUY'S LIVIN' IN A CAVE.
HE GOES OUT ONE DAY. BAM!
HE GETS CHASED BY A MAMMOTH.
HE'S SCARED TO DEATH
BUT HE GETS AWAY.
WHEN IT'S ALL OVER WITH,
HE FEELS GREAT.
YEAH, 'CAUSE
HE'S STILL LIVING.
BUT HE KNOWS HE IS,
AND HE FEELS IT.
SO HE GOES HOME,
BACK TO THE CAVE,
FIRST THING HE DOES,
HE DOES A DRAWING
OF THE MAMMOTH.
AND HE THINKS...
PEOPLE ARE COMIN'
TO SEE THIS!
LET'S MAKE IT GOOD!
LET'S MAKE THE TEETH REAL LONG
AND THE EYES REAL MEAN!
[Roaring]
BOOM!
THE FIRST MONSTER MOVIE.
THAT'S PROBABLY WHY
I STILL DO IT.
MAKE THE TEETH
AS BIG AS YOU WANT,
THEN KILL IT OFF.
EVERYTHING'S OKAY.
THE LIGHTS COME UP.
[Sigh]
YOU SEE,
THE PEOPLE COME INTO YOUR CAVE
WITH THE 200-YEAR-OLD CARPET.
THE GUY TEARS
YOUR TICKET IN HALF.
IT'S TOO LATE TO TURN BACK NOW.
THE WATER FOUNTAIN'S
ALL BOOBY-TRAPPED AND READY,
THE STUFF LAID OUT
ON THE CANDY COUNTER.
THEN YOU COME OVER HERE
TO WHERE IT'S DARK.
COULD BE ANYTHING IN THERE!
AND YOU SAY...
"HERE I AM!
WHAT HAVE YOU GOT FOR ME?"
HEY, LARRY.
WHERE DO YOU WANT ME
TO PUT THIS THING?
PUT IT NEXT TO THE AX
ON THE FLOOR UP THERE, SWEETS.
WHAT AX?
ISN'T THAT --
RUTH CORDAY.
SHE'S SOMETHIN', HUH?
SHE'S GOT THAT...
BEARING.
ALL THE REAL STARS
HAVE THAT,
WHETHER THEY'RE MOVIN'
BIG EQUIPMENT...
[Clicking]
OR WHATEVER.
THEY GOT IT.
[Sigh]
YEAH.
HEY, DON'T!
DON'T TOUCH THAT PART.
I'LL GET THAT LATER.
JUST LEAVE IT.
IS ALL THIS
STUFF YOURS?
YEAH!
"ATOMO VISION,"
"RUMBLE RAMA."
IT TAKES A LOT MORE
TO SCARE PEOPLE THESE DAYS.
TOO MUCH COMPETITION.
GIVE ME THEM PLIERS,
WILL YA, KID?
NOW THEY GOT BOMBS THAT'LL
KILL A HALF A MILLION PEOPLE.
NOBODY'S HAD A
GOOD NIGHT'S SLEEP IN YEARS.
SO, YOU GOTTA HAVE
A GIMMICK, YOU KNOW?
SOMETHIN' A LITTLE EXTRA.
HEY, THAT THING'S LIVE!
I'M SORRY!
I'D BETTER GO.
UM, I'LL SEE YOU SATURDAY.
YEAH, GOD WILLING.
[Electrical Current
Crackling]
[Ringing]
HELLO?
SHERRY, IT'S STAN.
HELLO, STAN.
UM, LISTEN, UH...
I'M NOT GONNA BE ABLE
TO GO WITH YOU ON SATURDAY.
OH, NO?
HOW COME?
WELL, UH,
COACH BURNETT CALLED,
AND THEY WANT GUYS TO PUT
SANDBAGS UP IN FRONT OF
THE ALL-PURPOSE ROOM...
IN CASE THERE'S
A MISSILE ATTACK.
OH, STAN,
THE ALL-PURPOSE ROOM?
YEAH, 'CAUSE IT
FACES SOUTH.
THEY THINK IT'S GONNA TAKE
ALL DAY, UNFORTUNATELY.
I'M SORRY.
[Sigh]
I UNDERSTAND.
THAT'S IMPORTANT.
SO, WE'LL JUST
DO IT NEXT WEEKEND.
UH, YEAH.
I'LL SEE YOU AT SCHOOL.
BYE, STAN.
* JOHNNY ANGEL
JOHNNY ANGEL *
HEY, SHERRY.
DWIGHT, YOU LITTLE BRAT.
GO BACK
AND KNOCK FIRST.
UH-UH.
YOU WEREN'T SUPPOSED TO WRITE
TO THAT GUY IN JAIL!
GIMME THOSE!
BOY, THESE ARE DIRTY.
HIS POEMS DON'T RHYME.
THEY'RE NOT SUPPOSED TO RHYME.
I'M GONNA SHOW MOM.
YOU ARE NOT!
WHAT DO YOU WANT?
YOU TO TAKE ME TO THE
HORROR MOVIE SATURDAY.
IT'S GOT A GUY
THAT TURNS INTO AN ANT.
SOME PEOPLE
THROW UP AT IT.
HOW WONDERFUL!
OKAY.
OKAY, OKAY.
NEAT!
THIS ONE'S REAL HOT!
BETTER HOLD ONTO IT.
[Sighing]
** ["The Great Pretender"
Performed By The Platters]
* OH YES *
[Man]
WE SHOULD'VE
ELECTED NIXON.
HE PUT THOSE BOMBS
IN RUSSIA.
* I'M THE GREAT PRETENDER *
THIS WHOLE THING
WOULD BE OVER.
* PRETENDING
THAT I'M DOING WELL *
BLOW EACH OTHER UP.
* MY NEED IS SUCH *
THEY DON'T EVEN
HAVE RELIGION.
* I PRETEND TOO MUCH *
HOW YA DOIN'?
* I'M LONELY
BUT NO ONE CAN TELL *
WE'RE DOIN' FINE, MY FRIEND.
EXCEPT FOR THIS BIG TRUCK LOAD
OF SOCIOPATHOLOGY...
THAT'S JUST ABOUT TO BE DUMPED
OUT HERE ON DUVAL STREET.
WE'RE JUST DANDY.
SOCIO WHAT?
THIS SO-CALLED MONSTER MOVIE
THAT'S COMING ON SATURDAY.
I NEVER HEARD
ABOUT THAT.
MAYBE IT'S TIME YOU TOOK
A GOOD LOOK AT WHAT'S GOING ON
IN YOUR OWN TOWN, MISTER.
WAKE UP AND SMELL THE COFFEE.
SMELL THE WRECKAGE
OF YOUNG MINDS.
GAG ON IT.
WHAT'S YOUR NAME, FRIEND?
HARVEY.
DO YOU KNOW THEY LET
CHILDREN SEE THESE THINGS?
WHAT'S THE MESSAGE
THEY PUT OUT?
THAT ATOMIC POWER
IS NOTHING BUT TROUBLE?
AND IT'S ALL RIGHT FOR
MUTATIONS TO RIP THE CLOTHES
OFF OF YOUNG WOMEN?
THAT'S WHAT THEY TEACH
THE YOUNGSTERS, HARV.
THAT'S A LONG WAY FROM
GEORGE WASHINGTON AND
THE CHERRY TREE, ISN'T IT?
YEAH.
THIS IS OUR
ORGANIZATION, HARV:
CITIZENS FOR
DECENT ENTERTAINMENT.
GEE, CAN I KEEP THIS?
SURE. KEEP IT
AND READ IT, HARV.
YEAH, I WILL.
HARV, I DON'T THINK YOU'LL MIND
IF I TAKE THIS BACK FROM YOU.
YOU MUST GET CAUGHT
PRETTY OFTEN, HARV.
YOU EVER DO ANY TIME?
YEAH, OPA-LOCKA
BOYS' REFORMATORY.
I JUST GOT OUT.
I DID SEVEN MONTHS.
NOT LONG ENOUGH.
YOU DIDN'T LEARN VERY MUCH.
IT WAS SUPPOSED
TO BE A YEAR,
BUT, YOU SEE, I WRITE POEMS,
AND THIS GUY IN NEW YORK
GOT ME OUT EARLY.
POEMS?
YEAH, YOU WANNA
HEAR ONE?
I DON'T THINK SO, HARV.
YOU GUYS REALLY
FROM THAT, UH --
IT'S A FUNNY WORLD, HARV.
ALMOST NOBODY'S
WHAT THEY SEEM TO BE.
AND THE ONES THAT ARE,
YOU REALLY HAVE
TO WATCH OUT FOR.
CAN WE GIVE YOU
SOME ADVICE?
GET YOURSELF
A SQUARE JOB, HARV.
YOU'RE NOT VERY GOOD
AT THIS.
HOLD 'IM.
AND AT ONE HOUR, TWENTY-EIGHT
MINUTES, "THE END" COMES UP,
COUNT FIVE,
HOUSE LIGHTS UP.
THOSE DOORS OPEN.
THAT'S THE TIMETABLE.
THOSE ARE THE FACTS.
THAT'S NOT
THE WHOLE STORY.
I KNOW SOME OF YOU HAVE
NEVER BEEN IN THE MOTION
PICTURE BUSINESS BEFORE,
AND SOME OF YOU HAVE BEEN
AT IT A LONG TIME.
BUT I WANT ALL OF YOU
TO LOOK AT THE FACES OUT HERE...
DURING THIS PICTURE.
THERE'S GONNA BE ROOM IN THEIR
HEADS FOR ONLY ONE THOUGHT:
DON'T LET IT GET ME.
THEY KNOW WE CAN'T HURT 'EM,
BUT THEY'RE STILL GONNA BE
SCARED HALF TO DEATH.
AND ALL OF YOU,
WHEN YOU THREAD THE PROJECTOR,
WHEN YOU TEAR THE TICKETS,
WHEN YOU SELL
THE JUJUBES,
YOU'RE ALL A PART OF IT.
AND JUST WHEN IT GETS THE WORST,
WHEN THEY'RE SITTING THERE...
AND THEIR HEARTS ARE GOING
LIKE TRAPPED ANIMALS
OUT HERE IN THE DARK,
WE SAVE THEM.
AND THEY SAY,
"HEY, IT'S ALL RIGHT!
THANK GOD! HEY,
CAN I SEE THAT AGAIN?"
P.S., NO, THEY CAN'T.
WE CLEAR BETWEEN SHOWS.
THAT WAS WONDERFUL, LARRY.
I'M ALL A-TREMBLE.
THANKS.
WHERE ARE THE GUYS
APPLYING FOR THE JOB?
ONLY ONE SHOWED UP.
I SENT HIM TO TRY
THE SUIT ON.
ONLY ONE?
HOW MANY PEOPLE
ARE GONNA WANT TO DRESS UP
IN A RUBBER "MANT" SUIT?
HEY, NOT BAD.
LAWRENCE WOOLSEY.
HARVEY STARKWEATHER.
TAKE YOUR HEAD OFF.
WHAT KIND OF JOB EXACTLY --
IT'S JUST
A ONE-DAY THING.
SOME OF IT'S
RUNNING ELECTRICAL STUFF,
SWITCHES AND THINGS
BACK HERE BEHIND THE SCREEN.
BUT THE OTHER PART,
YOU HAVE TO SCARE PEOPLE!
REALLY SHAKE 'EM UP.
THINK YOU COULD DO THAT?
YEAH, I COULD DO THAT
REAL WELL.
GOOD.
BECAUSE, WHEN YOU
PUT THE SUIT ON,
WHEN YOU HIT THESE SWITCHES,
THOSE PEOPLE --
THIS IS WHERE
I CAME IN.
THOSE PEOPLE OUT THERE
IN THE DARK --
[Mother]
FRED! OH, MY GOD!
[Dad]
SHH. YOU'LL WAKE
THE KIDS UP.
ARE YOU KIDDING?
I'LL WAKE THEM UP RIGHT NOW.
NO, HONEY.
I WOULD HAVE CALLED YOU
TO SAY IT WAS OVER,
BUT THEY WANT
TO KEEP A LID ON IT.
DAD?
[Explosion]
[Thunder Rumbling]
[Sighing]
[Rattling Noise]
[Woman]
SEE THE NURSE
BEFORE THE SHOW.
[Radio]
MAJOR RUDOLPH ANDERSON, A NAVY
PILOT FROM SOUTH CAROLINA,
WAS SHOT DOWN BY A RUSSIAN
MISSILE OVER CUBA EARLIER TODAY
AND IS PRESUMED DEAD.
ANDERSON, THE FIRST-KNOWN
CASUALTY OF THE SHOWDOWN,
WAS ONE OF THE PILOTS
WHOSE RECONNAISSANCE...
FIRST REVEALED THE PRESENCE
OF SOVIET MISSILES IN CUBA.
I HOPE THIS THING CLOSES
FASTER THAN IT OPENS.
THIRTY SECONDS.
ALL RIGHT,
LET'S ADD IT UP.
OFFICE TO STAIRWELL,
FIFTY-EIGHT SECONDS.
STAIRWELL TO SHELTER,
ELEVEN SECONDS.
ZERO HOUR CHECKLIST,
FIFTEEN SECONDS.
CHECK AIR-INTAKE LEVEL,
EIGHT SECONDS.
AUTOMATIC DOOR,
TWENTY-EIGHT SECONDS.
SIXTEEN AND FIVE IS
TWENTY-ONE, TWENTY-TWO --
STAN, HOW'S IT GOING?
HEY, ANY OF YOU GUYS
SEEN GENE?
SO!
SHERRY!
NEAT!
SO THIS IS HOW YOU'RE SPENDING
YOUR DAY, NOT SANDBAGGIN'
THE ALL-PURPOSE ROOM.
DOWN HERE AT
THE MONSTER SHOW?
NO!
SEE, I --
THAT'S VERY IMMATURE,
STAN.
WHO'S THAT?
THAT'S NOBODY.
I'M TELLING ANYWAY.
SHERRY, WAIT.
THE ALL-PURPOSE ROOM?
OH, MAN.
SIGN HERE, PLEASE.
WHAT ARE
THESE THINGS FOR?
IT'S A RELEASE FORM.
IT SAYS IT'S NOT OUR FAULT IF
THE MOVIE SCARES YOU TO DEATH.
WOW!
IT'S NOT A JOKE. WE'VE HAD
TEN-YEAR-OLD KIDS HAVING
HEART ATTACKS AT THIS MOVIE.
THEY'RE RECOVERING, BUT WE
CAN'T BE EXPOSED LEGALLY.
NOW, IF YOU DON'T SIGN --
BUT, WE'RE NOT SCARED,
ARE WE, DENNIS?
NO.
NURSE!
I CUT MY ELBOW!
THAT LOOKS TERRIBLE.
NEXT!
SIGN HERE, PLEASE.
HEY, LOOK IT!
- SANDRA!
- HI!
I DIDN'T KNOW YOU LIKED
MONSTER MOVIES.
I'M HERE
WITH MY PARENTS.
HERE SHE IS.
WHOA!
OH, GOD!
THAT'S DISGUSTING.
I KNOW, RHONDA.
WELL, THE POINT ISN'T
WHETHER WE LIKE IT OR NOT.
NO.
IF WE START LETTING THEM
TELL US WHAT MOVIES WE CAN SEE,
OR WHAT MUSIC
WE CAN LISTEN TO, THEN --
I KNOW, JACK.
OH! UM...
OKAY, WELL, WE'LL, UH --
WE'LL SEE YOU LATER.
OKAY, YEAH.
BYE.
THOSE TWO FOR REAL?
'COURSE THEY'RE REAL.
THEY'RE MY PARENTS.
THEY'RE GREAT,
YOU KNOW.
DON'T BE SCARED.
WHAT ACTUALLY HAPPENS
IN THIS?
IT'S JUST A MOVIE.
RIGHT, I JUST HEARD
THEY HAD SOME OTHER THINGS.
WELL, THERE'S SOME STUFF
TO MAKE IT SCARIER.
WHEN THE GUY IN THE MOVIE SAYS,
"YOU DON'T UNDERSTAND.
MY WIFE IS IN THERE.
MY GOD, LOOK OUT,"
THAT'S CUE NUMBER FIVE.
TURN ONE UP TO FOUR,
TWO UP TO THREE.
UH-HUH.
FOR CUE NUMBER SIX,
ONE GOES TO FIVE,
TWO GOES TO SEVEN,
BUT YOU NEVER EVER
TURN ONE ABOVE SIX.
RIGHT.
NOW THIS STUFF
OVER HERE.
THE GUY'S GONNA SAY:
"STAY DOWN LOW AND DON'T LOOK.
THOSE ARE ATOMIC WEAPONS."
BIP, BIP,
BIP, BIP, BIP.
OKAY.
YOU'RE NOT A
BAD-LOOKIN' KID.
YOU EVER DONE
ANY ACTING?
HOW DO YOU DO IT?
NEVER MIND.
GO PUT YOUR COSTUME ON.
DO YOU LIKE POETRY?
JUST THE MAN
I WAS LOOKING FOR.
THAT'S SOME AUDIENCE.
THEY'RE PRACTICALLY
TEARING THE PLACE TO SHREDS.
I WOULD LIKE TO BE
PAID IN CASH AS SOON
AS THE SHOW IS IN.
AS A MATTER OF FACT,
I'D LIKE TO BE PAID IN CASH
FOR BOTH SHOWS.
MR. WOOLSEY, WE'VE NEVER
SHORTED ANYONE, REALLY!
YOU SHOULD
LEARN HOW.
THE ROAR OF THE CROWD.
HI!
HOW ARE YA?
GOOD TO SEE YA.
ENJOY THE SHOW.
NO RUNNING.
GOOD TO SEE YA.
[Chanting]
WE WANT "MANT!"
DOWN HERE LOOKS GOOD.
[Cheering]
HELLO, I'M
LAWRENCE WOOLSEY.
THE FEELING AT THIS
ATOMIC TEST SITE
IS AN ANXIOUS ONE,
BUT THEN, YOU'RE ABOUT TO SEE
FOR YOURSELVES WHAT I MEAN.
MY TERRIFYING NEW PROCESS,
"ATOMO VISION,"
PUTS YOU, THE AUDIENCE,
AT GROUND ZERO,
NOT A SAFE PLACE
TO BE.
BUT TODAY, THERE IS
NO SAFE PLACE TO BE.
[Explosion]
HOW WE DOING,
NURSE?
JUST TOO DAZZLED BY
SHOW BUSINESS TO SPEAK.
THAT'S THE STUFF.
HEY, WOOLEY?
MR. SPECTOR!
HEY, HOW'S IT GOING?
SENSATIONAL!
RUTH, THIS IS MR. SPECTOR
FROM MEGALOPOLITAN THEATERS.
Enchant.
I'M UP HERE.
OH.
HELLO, MR. SPECTOR.
HOW ARE YOU, HAROLD?
HOW ARE THE NUMBERS?
IT'S HOWARD.
WE'RE SOLD OUT.
FANTASTIC. WHAT DID I TELL YA?
I WOULDN'T HAVE TO WEAR
THIS UNIFORM ANYMORE.
THE QUESTION IS HOW THE PICTURE
WILL PLAY WITH AN AUDIENCE.
THAT'S WHAT I'LL BE WATCHING.
[Radio: Indistinct]
[Mr. Spector]
WHAT THE HELL IS THAT?
WAR NEWS.
OH, YOU GOT
A BET ON IT?
WHEN YOU SEE WHAT
I'VE GOT COOKED UP!
[Chuckle]
WAIT'LL YOU SEE
THE FEELERS ON THIS THING.
I'M SURE IT'S WONDERFUL.
I'M SORRY. THAT'S ALL
THE BALCONY CAN SAFELY HOLD.
THERE'S A FEW SEATS
IN FRONT.
OH, MAN!
[Woman On Screen]
IT ALL STARTED OUT
SO INNOCENTLY...
WITH ONE OF THOSE DENTAL
CHECKUPS YOU'RE SUPPOSED
TO GET EVERY SIX MONTHS.
BILL AND I ALWAYS
THOUGHT IF YOU JUST DO
WHAT YOU'RE SUPPOSED TO,
THEN LIFE
WORKS OUT FOR YOU.
POPCORN?
HOW WRONG WE WERE.
[Man]
YOU'RE LUCKY
TO BE ALIVE, BILL.
I WISH I WAS DEAD.
HOW COULD SUCH A THING
HAPPEN, DR. GRABOW?
X RAYS, CAROLE,
A FORM OF RADIATION.
AN ANT MUST'VE BITTEN
BILL WHEN HE WAS HAVING
HIS TEETH X-RAYED.
I'VE BEEN MEANING TO HAVE
THE OFFICE FUMIGATED, BUT
I'VE BEEN TOO DARN BUSY!
ANYWAY, THE ANT'S SALIVA
MUST HAVE GOTTEN INTO
BILL'S BLOODSTREAM...
AND GONE STRAIGHT
TO HIS BRAIN
JUST AS THE RADIATION,
WHICH IS MEASURED IN
UNITS CALLED ROENTGENS,
WAS RELEASED.
AND THAT'S HOW
HE BECAME A --
"MANT!"
[Audience Gasping]
OH, BILL.
HE'S IN A BIOLOGICAL
NO-MAN'S-LAND...
GENE?
SOMEWHERE BETWEEN THE
INSECT KINGDOM AND OUR OWN.
IS IT REVERSIBLE?
I'M AFRAID NOT,
CAROLE.
EXCUSE ME.
ONCE A RADIOACTIVE EVENT
HAS TAKEN PLACE --
I'LL ALWAYS BE THIS THING!
DON'T SAY THAT, DARLING.
YOU'RE STILL BILL, MY BILL.
SO WHERE WERE YOU?
I WASN'T TRYING
TO GET OUT OF ANYTHING.
I HAD A DATE WITH SHERRY.
WE WERE GOING TO LOOK
AT CORAL ANIMALS.
MM-HMM. SO?
WHAT HAPPENED?
HARVEY STARKWEATHER.
HE BASICALLY SAID
HE'D KILL ME.
NOW SHE'S HERE
WITH HER BROTHER AND
SHE WANTS TO KILL ME!
TELL THE TRUTH, HONEY.
IF I LOOKED LIKE THIS
WHEN WE FIRST MET --
I WOULD'VE BEEN AFRAID, BILL.
I WOULD'VE BEEN VERY AFRAID.
CAN I SIT WITH YOU GUYS
AT LEAST?
SURE.
HEY, ISN'T THAT
THAT "BAN THE BOMB" GIRL
YOU'RE WITH?
WE'RE JUST
SITTING TOGETHER.
YOU HOUND!
BY THE WAY, I DID GET
YOUR X RAYS BACK, BILL.
I DON'T 'SPOSE IT MAKES
MUCH DIFFERENCE TO YOU NOW,
BUT YOU DIDN'T HAVE A CAVITY!
[Knocking]
COME IN.
WELCOME, DOCTOR.
[Bill]
WHO'S THIS GUY?
I TOOK THE LIBERTY OF
INVITING DR. FLANKEN HERE.
HE'S WITH THE OFFICE OF
UNFORESEEN ATOMIC EVENTS
IN WASHINGTON.
[Geiger Counter Clicking]
YOUNG MAN, I'M AFRAID
YOU'VE SUFFERED SOME
OF THE WORST...
OF WHAT OUR MIGHTY
LITTLE FRIEND, THE ATOM,
HAS TO OFFER.
IT CAN POWER A CITY...
OR LEVEL IT.
[Carole]
HOW CAN IT CAUSE THIS?
[Dr. Flanken]
HUMAN INSECT MUTATION
IS FAR FROM AN EXACT SCIENCE.
BUT THERE ARE SOME THINGS
WE DO KNOW.
YOU'LL CONTINUE TO
METAMORPHOSE... OR CHANGE,
TAKING ON MORE
ANT-LIKE CHARACTERISTICS.
AND... YOU'LL GROW,
BECOME BIGGER.
I'M SORRY, BILL!
SORRY?
DO YOU THINK THIS IS
SOME PICNIC FOR ME?
[Laughing]
[Bill]
DID YOU HEAR
WHAT I JUST SAID?
PICNIC! GET IT?
ANTS... PICNIC.
[Laughing]
WHAT AM I, ALONE HERE?
THAT'S FUNNY!
ISN'T IT FUNNY, DOCTOR?
[Carole]
DOCTOR, WATCH OUT!
WHAT'S HAPPENING TO HIM?
[Dr. Flanken]
HE'S ALL RIGHT.
ANY ANT WOULD REACT
TO A SMALL DOSE IN THE SAME WAY.
YOU'RE JUST SEEING IT IN A
MAGNIFIED... OR LARGER FORM.
OH, BILL.
[Bill]
THANKS, DOC.
I NEEDED THAT.
[Carole]
WE SAID WE WOULD TRY
AND LIVE A NORMAL LIFE,
BUT WE WERE KIDDING OURSELVES.
[Bill]
CRUMBS! HOW LONG
CAN I EXIST ON CRUMBS?
I'M HUNGRY!
I'LL SHOW YOU!
GO, MY BROTHERS AND SISTERS!
GO!
YOU'RE FREE!
FREE!
NO, BILL.
[Cackling]
BEHOLD THE
GREAT EMANCIPATOR!
AND NOW,
TO GO DOWNTOWN.
NO, BILL,
YOU MUSTN'T.
I'LL CALL DR. GRABOW.
GET AWAY FROM
THE TELEPHONE, CAROLE.
DON'T MAKE ME USE THIS.
[Scream]
[Screaming]
GOTCHA!
OH, BILL, IF YOU COULD JUST
LISTEN TO THE MAN IN YOU
AND PUT THE INSECT ASIDE.
INSECTICIDE?
WHERE?
NO! NO, I MEAN --
DOCTOR, HE BELONGS
IN A HOSPITAL, NOT IN A PRISON.
WHERE WOULD YOU HAVE ME
SEND HIM, A FUNNY FARM
OR AN ANT FARM?
HOW COULD YOU BE
SO CRUEL?
HOW COULD YOU NOT LOVE ME
NOW THAT I'M THE ONLY
REAL MAN IN YOUR LIFE?
[Audience Screaming]
JUST KIDDING,
BILL.
[Dr. Flanken]
ELECTRICITY
PLUS ATOMIC ENERGY.
NOW HE'LL GROW
AT AN ACCELERATED...
OR SPEEDED UP RATE.
[Growling]
OH! OH!
[Scream]
[Grabow Groaning]
ARE YOU
ALL RIGHT?
I HOPE SO.
WE'LL HAVE TO HAVE
THAT BITE LOOKED AT.
UH-HUH.
GOOD LORD, HE'S
BECOMING HUGE!
WHO CAN POSSIBLY STOP HIM
THE WAY HE -- LOOK OUT!
[Loud Rumbling]
HE'S BREAKING THROUGH
THE ROOF!
[Screaming]
[TV]
THE AMERICAN BLOCKADE
HAS INTERCEPTED ONE SHIP,
THE SOVIET CARGO VESSEL
MARUCLA, WHICH WAS BOARDED
BY ARMED SAILORS...
FROM TWO U.S. DESTROYERS
THIS MORNING.
THAT INSPECTION WAS
DESCRIBED AS TENSE BUT
NO WEAPONS WERE FOUND.
TODAY, AN ANXIOUS WORLD
HOLDS ITS BREATH WAITING
FOR THE NEXT CONFRONTATION,
WAITING FOR
THE NEXT RUMOR OF WAR.
THE PRESIDENTIAL PRESS
SECRETARY, PIERRE SALINGER,
HAS SCHEDULED A STATEMENT.
SHERRY.
OH, HELLO,
UM --
GENE.
GENE. YES.
I HOPE YOU AND YOUR FRIEND
STAN ARE ENJOYING THE SHOW.
I'LL HAVE A HERSHEY BAR
AND POPCORN, PLEASE.
COULD I TALK TO YOU
FOR A MINUTE?
WHAT ABOUT?
ABOUT STAN. THIS
WASN'T HIS FAULT TODAY.
HE REALLY WANTED TO GO SEE
THE CORAL WITH YOU.
I FIND THAT HARD TO BELIEVE.
WELL, IT WASN'T
THE CORAL SO MUCH.
SEE, STAN LIKES YOU.
HE REALLY LIKES YOU.
HE CERTAINLY HAS
A STRANGE WAY OF SHOWING IT.
HE WAS PROBABLY AFRAID
THAT YOU'D THINK IT WAS
CHILDISH TO, UM --
TO BE HERE?
I DO.
YEAH, WELL,
HE WAS GONNA GO WITH YOU.
BUT THEN HE REMEMBERED
HE SAID HE'D GO TO THIS MOVIE
WITH ME AND MY LITTLE BROTHER.
YOU SEE, STAN KIND OF
CALMS DENNIS DOWN...
WHEN HE GETS SCARED.
HE'S LIKE
AN UNCLE TO HIM.
TO YOUR BROTHER?
SURE. AND HE KNEW
DENNIS WAS REALLY
LOOKING FORWARD TO IT.
AND HE SAID:
"I CAN'T DO IT. I CAN'T
LET THE LITTLE GUY DOWN."
THAT'S SWEET OF HIM,
THINKING ABOUT A LITTLE BOY.
WE'RE MISSING IT.
GO AWAY, DWIGHT.
I'M TELLING.
THAT'S THE KIND OF GUY
STAN IS.
HE JUST THOUGHT WITH...
OUR DAD BEING OUT THERE,
HE DIDN'T WANT DENNIS
BEING ALONE IN HERE.
AND WITH YOU LIVING
ON THE BASE AND
BEING LESS ADVANTAGED --
OH...
THAT IS MOVING.
I KNOW.
[Growling]
HOLD YOUR FIRE!
WHAT IN CREATION
DO YOU CALL THAT THING?
BILL.
BILL, THIS IS
GENERAL ANKRUM.
SURRENDER NOW.
COME DOWN OFF THAT BUILDING.
[General]
WE'VE GOT SUGAR FOR YOU.
[Growling]
MEN, FIRE YOUR
D.D.T. MISSILES.
[Audience Screaming]
[Radio]
...MAJOR CITIES,
RESORT AREAS.
IT'S ALL GONNA BE LOOKING
LIKE THE SURFACE OF THE MOON.
PEOPLE SHOULD
BE PREPARED TO --
[Garbled]
THIS IS IT!
[General]
A DIRECT HIT.
IT DIDN'T EVEN STUN IT.
SHERRY!
STAN, GENE EXPLAINED
EVERYTHING TO ME.
I'M SO SORRY.
I DIDN'T REALIZE.
[General]
THERE'S ONLY ONE THING LEFT,
ATOMIC WEAPONS.
"ZERO HOUR CHECKLIST."
FISH FOOD!
QUICKLY!
IT'S HEADED FOR
THAT MOVIE THEATER.
IT? DON'T YOU UNDERSTAND?
HE'S NOT A MONSTER,
HE'S A SHOE SALESMAN!
WOULD YOU LET THAT
FIT YOU IN A PUMP?
A REAL GENERAL
WOULDN'T SAY THAT.
SHUT UP.
** [Twist]
[Growling]
[Scream]
LOOK OUT BEHIND YOU.
IT CAME OUT
OF THE SCREEN!
DON'T WORRY, DENNIS.
IT'S JUST SOME GUY
IN A SUIT, OKAY?
LOOK OUT! THERE,
IN THE TENTH ROW!
IT'S IN THE THEATER.
HOW COULD THIS HAPPEN?
[Man]
LOOK OUT!
HE LOOKS MAD,
DOESN'T HE?
RUN FOR YOUR LIVES!
DON'T LET
IT GET YOU!
OH, NO! HE'S GOT
AHOLD OF SOMEONE!
RUN! RUN!
JESUS, WHAT THE HELL'S
HE DOIN' TO THAT KID?
YOU'RE SUPPOSED TO
SCARE HIM, YOU IDIOT HICK!
[Gasping]
[Cheering]
HEY, COME BACK!
[Man]
WAIT! IT'S LEAVING.
IT'S GOING OUTSIDE.
THANK GOD!
OH, WHAT WAS IT?
SEE WHAT HE'S PUTTING BACK?
THE SHOWMANSHIP.
THIS, TO MY MIND,
IS WHAT'S BEEN MISSING!
[Cheering, Whistling]
[Carole]
DO YOU REALLY THINK THESE ATOMIC
THINGS WILL CHANGE BILL BACK?
THAT KID IS NOT LAYING
A HAND ON ME, LARRY.
THERE ARE LIMITS.
OKAY, OKAY,
I'LL TALK TO HIM.
GREAT STUFF.
STOP!
DON'T SHOOT!
STAN?
IN HERE.
WHAT HAPPENED?
THAT GUY WAS CRAZY!
I DON'T KNOW, MAN,
BUT I SCARED HIM AWAY WITH THIS.
LOOK AT THIS.
IT'S A FALLOUT SHELTER.
WE'VE GOT ONE AT HOME.
SEE THIS? IT PURIFIES
THE AIR SO YOU DON'T
BREATHE IN THE FALLOUT.
WHAT'S THIS THING FOR?
[Click]
NOTHING.
AND THIS BIKE?
GENERATOR. TO RUN THE
LIGHTS AND EVERYTHING.
THERE'S A SHOWER AND BOOKS
IF YOU GET REALLY BORED.
THERE'S NO PHONE!
OH! RIGHT.
WH--
WHO? WHAT
ARE YOU DOING IN HERE?
GET OUT!
THE DOOR IS CLOSING!
HURRY UP! HURRY UP!
IT'S HAPPENING!
THIS IS IT!
THE BOMB'S EXPLODING!
LET ME OUT!
LET ME IN!
WE'RE LOCKED IN.
[Rumbling]
LISTEN.
WAS THAT... IT?
WAS THAT
REALLY IT?
UH, I DON'T KNOW.
[Rumbling]
I CAN'T FIND HIM ANYWHERE.
HE WENT OUT THIS DOOR
AND I WAS SCARED AND --
OKAY.
I LOVE YOU.
BYE.
WHY IS THIS TERRIBLE
THING HAPPENING?
I HAVE BEEN OVER AND
OVER IN IT MY MIND AND
I CAN'T FIND AN ANSWER.
ALL NIGHT
I LIE AWAKE THINKING.
WHY? WHY DOES
IT HAVE TO HAPPEN?
YOU'RE A DOCTOR.
TELL ME.
I WISH I KNEW, CAROLE.
I WISH I KNEW.
WROTE THIS TOO,
DID YA?
YEAH.
EXCUSE ME A MINUTE.
IT'S NOT FAIR!
IT'S SUPPOSED TO BE
FOR ME!
HEY, YOU SEE THAT KID
IN THE ANT SUIT?
THE RUSSIANS HAVE ATTACKED.
THE BOMBS ARE FALLING.
YOU SAW THIS ON TV?
NO. IT WENT OUT.
THEY MUST'VE HIT
THE TV STATIONS FIRST.
AND THEN EVERYTHING
STARTED SHAKING
FROM THE BLAST WAVES!
MY GOD.
IT'S NOT THE RUSSIANS.
IT'S "RUMBLE RAMA."
WHAT?
THAT STUPID KID I HIRED,
HE PROBABLY TURNED ALL
MY STUFF UP WAY TOO HIGH.
DID YOU HEAR
ANY AIR RAID SIRENS?
NO, BUT --
WHAT ABOUT YOUR RADIO,
YOUR CONELRAD?
MY RADIO.
MY RADIO IS, IS --
IS IN MY OFFICE.
WELL, UM --
WELL, I, UH,
I GUESS EVERYTHING IS --
WAIT A MINUTE.
THERE ARE TWO KIDS IN THERE!
MY FALLOUT SHELTER!
LET 'EM OUT.
I CAN'T.
IT'S ON A TIME LOCK.
IT WON'T OPEN FOR MONTHS.
IT'S NOT MY FAULT.
IS THERE FOOD?
YES, BUT --
I FORGOT TO SET
THE AIR-INTAKE BLOWER.
THE WHICH?
IT BRINGS THE AIR IN.
THERE'S NO AIR
IN THERE?
THERE WON'T BE SOON.
DANDY.
WELL, WE'LL HAVE TO POP
THIS OFF RIGHT HERE.
FIND CROWBARS AND HAMMERS.
SURE.
THEY GUARANTEED
IT COULDN'T BE OPENED.
WHO?
THE PEOPLE
WHO SOLD IT TO ME.
BOY, AM I
IN THE WRONG BUSINESS.
GENE?
YEAH?
WHAT IF WE'RE THE ONLY ONES
THAT MADE IT INTO ONE
OF THESE THINGS IN TIME?
THEN --
THEN WE'D BE THE ONLY PEOPLE
IN THE WHOLE WORLD.
IT'S LIKE WE'RE --
LIKE WE'RE WHAT?
ADAM AND EVE.
I MEAN, IF THERE ARE STILL
GONNA BE PEOPLE AFTERWARDS --
BABIES.
WELL... YEAH.
THEN MAYBE THEY WILL BE
THE ONES THAT'LL LIVE HERE
WITHOUT BLOWING IT UP.
IT'S OUR RESPONSIBILITY
TO CARRY ON.
THAT'S RIGHT.
ARE YOU SCARED?
YEAH.
ME TOO.
MOM!
YES. YOU OKAY?
GENE AND "MANT" WENT OUT
THE DOOR WITH... WITH HIM!
UH... HI. UH,
ARE YOU GENE'S MOM?
YEAH.
BUT HOW CAN THIS BE
A FREE SPEECH ISSUE?
I DON'T KNOW.
THAT ANT CAN'T HURT YOU,
SO DON'T BE SCARED.
ANTS.
AMERICAN MOVIES.
WHERE IS HE?
YOU SEE, UH, GENE AND THIS
GIRL SANDRA GOT STUCK IN A --
SANDRA?
MY SANDRA?
GOOD LORD!
BILL,
PUT THAT DOWN!
HEY, QUIT IT,
YOU GUYS!
WHOA, YOUNG MAN.
I WANT YOU TO WAIT
FOR ME RIGHT HERE.
DON'T YOU MOVE.
DON'T MOVE!
[Banging]
THERE'S
SOMETHING ALIVE.
THEY WANT TO GET IN.
WE HAVE TO LET THEM IN!
BUT THE RADIATION.
THAT DOESN'T MATTER!
SANDRA?
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
OH, RHONDA!
MOM!
OH, MY GOD!
ARE YOU OKAY?
LOOKS LIKE
HE'S DOIN' OKAY TO ME.
THANK YOU.
WE THOUGHT EVERYONE ELSE
WAS DEAD.
YOU WERE ACTING LIKE EVERYONE
WAS DEAD. YOUR LITTLE BROTHER
HAS BEEN TERRIFIED!
NO, MOM --
EXCUSE ME!
EXCUSE ME, EXCUSE ME.
STAN, DO YOU REALLY HAVE
ONE OF THOSE SHELTERS
AT YOUR HOUSE?
YEAH, DOWN
IN THE BASEMENT.
HE USUALLY DOESN'T
EVEN MEET PEOPLE.
IS THE BOY MILITARY?
OH, GOD.
WELL, IT'S ROUGH, KID.
BUT ON THE PLUS SIDE
THE WORLD'S STILL HERE.
[Rumbling]
NO, NO, NO!
IT'S JUST THAT STUPID KID.
HE'S GOING CRAZY
WITH MY STUFF.
WHERE'D HE GO?
IT LOST US.
[Screaming]
THERE HE IS!
STOP HIM!
SOMEONE STOP HIM!
- HE'S GOT THAT WOMAN!
- SHE'S A NURSE!
WHERE'S HE TAKING HER?
- AFTER HIM!
- BUT IT'S SO --
SO WHAT? DO YOU KNOW
WHAT SOMETHING LIKE THAT
WILL DO TO A HUMAN WOMAN?
I TOLD LARRY I'M
NOT DOING THIS!
DON'T PUT A HAND ON ME.
COME ON!
PUT ME DOWN!
BEAUTIFUL, BEAUTIFUL!
YOU'RE NOT EVEN GOING
THE RIGHT WAY, YOU JERK!
YOU'RE SUPPOSED
TO GO OUT THE LOBBY!
HEY, WHAT'RE YOU --
PUT ME DOWN, YOU MORON!
[Screaming]
THAT WOOLSEY'S
A GENIUS.
[Chuckling]
YOU CAN'T DROP AN ATOMIC BOMB
ON CHICAGO!
WE'VE EVACUATED THE
CIVILIANS TO A SAFE PLACE.
[Flanken]
SAFE FROM FALLOUT,
FROM RADIATION POISONING?
NO MORE SCREAMIN'
OR I'LL CUT YOU!
THERE THEY ARE.
[Flanken]
HE'S JUST A BUG,
A BIG BUG.
HE'S GOT A KNIFE!
AND IT'S A BIG KNIFE.
GIVE ME THE MONEY FAST!
[General]
A MILLION DOLLARS WORTH
OF RADAR CAN'T TRACK IT.
ENOUGH FIRE POWER
TO WIPE OUT A REGIMENT
CAN'T EVEN SCRATCH IT.
COME ON, SHERRY.
YOU'RE COMIN' WITH ME!
WE'RE GOING FAR AWAY.
PLEASE DON'T HURT HER!
COME ON!
WE BELONG OUT THERE.
IT'S LIKE A POEM I WROTE:
THE ROAD, THE SACRED PAVEMENT.
WE ARE THE TRAFFIC.
WE ARE WHAT WE TRAFFIC IN.
AND THE TRUCK STOPS HERE.
IT'S NO SKIN OFF MY ASPHALT.
IT'S JUST A LINE,
JUST A YELLOW LINE.
NO!
MY SOCKS ARE RED
AND I'M READY TO RIDE.
WHAT DOES SHE SEE
IN THAT GUY?
HOLD IT, SON.
WE'LL CALL THE POLICE.
GIVE ME THE POLICE.
[Rumbling]
IT'S STILL SHAKING.
FEEL IT?
HELP ME, SOMEBODY!
HELP!
SOMEBODY HELP ME!
STOP!
ONCE WE SO CLEVERLY LET THAT
ATOMIC GENIE OUT OF ITS BOTTLE,
THERE IS NO PUTTING IT BACK,
GENTLEMEN.
[Woolsey]
WOW, THAT THING'S
READY TO DROP.
WE GOTTA GET EVERYBODY
OFF OF THERE.
DO WE TURN OFF
THE MOVIE?
THEN THEY STOMP.
COME ON!
IT'S A
DIFFERENT WORLD NOW...
FROM THE ONE WE KNEW
ONLY A FEW SHORT YEARS AGO.
WHAT'S GOING ON?
WE'RE GONNA HAVE TO GET A LITTLE
AHEAD OF THE PICTURE HERE.
MAKE SURE
THE AISLES ARE CLEAR.
OPEN THE BACK DOORS,
WILL YA, HON?
KID, HEAT UP NUMBER TWO
FOR ME, WILL YA?
WHY WOULD YOU WANT TO EXAMINE ME
NOW WHEN BILL IS OUT THERE...
CLEAR THE AISLES.
TAKE YOUR SEATS.
I SAW THAT.
AND THE
ARMY'S SENDING MISSILES?
YOUR APPOINTMENT IS TODAY.
PEOPLE ALWAYS FIND A REASON
TO PUT IT OFF.
THAT'S THE THING PEOPLE
LIKE TO DO.
UM, YES, BUT AFTER
EVERYTHING THAT'S HAPPENED,
MAYBE YOU --
MAYBE I'M WHAT?
UNFIT TO WORK ON PEOPLE'S
PRECIOUS LITTLE TEETH?
[Shouting]
WHY ARE YOU KEEPING
YOUR HAND --
BECAUSE IT'S NOT MY HAND.
IT'S NOT A HAND AT ALL!
NOT SINCE BILL BIT ME!
[Scream]
[Explosion]
[Screaming]
JESUS!
THIS IS IT!
[Screaming]
HEY! HEY, LOOK!
IT'S STILL HERE.
I DON'T BELIEVE IT.
IT'S ALL STILL HERE.
IT'S ALL RIGHT.
WHAT THE HELL
ARE YOU DOIN'?
THEY HAD THE ATOMIC BOMB!
I THOUGHT THE WORLD
WAS GONNA END.
MAN, I'M SEEIN' THIS TWICE!
GUYS, LET'S GO.
NO TRIPPING.
NURSE, THIS GUY FAINTED.
YOU'RE RIGHT.
EVERYBODY, LET'S GO.
OUT THAT DOOR.
[Engine Revving]
[Sherry]
HARVEY, WATCH OUT!
[Honking]
STAY BACK, STAY BACK!
SHERRY?
STAN!
OH, THANK GOD YOU GOT HERE.
I WAS SO SCARED!
YOU WERE WONDERFUL!
I WAS?
DENNIS? DENNIS?
HE WAS DOWN HERE!
DENNIS?
[Creaking]
MOM!
HELP.
DENNIS!
OHH!
[Quietly]
DENNIS, HOLD OUT
YOUR HAND.
GIVE ME YOUR HAND.
COME ON.
[Creaking]
OKAY. THAT'S IT.
COME ON.
NICE AND SLOWLY.
COME ON. COME ON.
REACH FOR ME.
[Gasp]
GENE!
THAT'S IT.
[Screaming]
MOM! GENE!
HELP ME!
GENE, PULL ME UP.
PLEASE!
[Mom]
PULL HIM UP, OKAY?
OHH!
PULL ME UP!
[Dennis]
IT'S BURNING.
NO, IT'S NOT.
THERE'S NO FIRE
IN THERE.
NO, I TURNED IT OFF.
FOLKS, WE WON'T BE HAVING
A SECOND SHOW TODAY.
YOU'RE KIDDING!
WHAT?
WE WILL BE GIVING YOU A FREE
PASS TO A FUTURE PRESENTATION.
MY SON'S BEEN
WAITING THREE WEEKS
TO SEE THIS MOVIE!
YOU TELL HIM
HE CAN'T SEE THIS MOVIE!
HEY, WOOLSEY!
THIS CROWD IS
TURNING INTO A MOB.
CONGRATULATIONS.
LET ME ASK YOU SOMETHING.
EXCUSE ME.
DO YOU OWN THAT PROCESS?
YEP. IT'S SOMETHING
I'VE BEEN WORKING ON.
SOME OF IT'S STAGE LIGHTING,
SOME MAGIC SHOW STUFF.
BUT THE BIG STUDIOS,
NONE OF THEM HAVE
ANYTHING LIKE IT.
YOU KNOW WHY?
THEY'RE DINOSAURS!
NO VISION.
THEY WERE SCARED,
WEREN'T THEY?
TERRIFIED.
MIGHT EVEN WANT TO
TONE IT DOWN A LITTLE.
SURE.
NORMALLY YOU CAN LET THE
PEOPLE LEAVE THE THEATER
AT THEIR OWN PACE.
EASIER ON THE CARPETS,
YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN?
ALSO, I'M STILL CONCERNED
ABOUT THAT BOMB THING.
LITTLE QUESTION
OF TASTE?
NO, NO.
BUT YOUR YOUNGER PATRONS,
YOU COULD HAVE
SOME SEAT WETNESS.
THIS I SEE AS A DRAWBACK.
RIGHT. HEY.
YOU KNOW WHAT
WOULDN'T BE BAD?
GHOSTS. THEY COME
THROUGH THE SCREEN,
FLY OVER THE AUDIENCE.
GHOSTS THAT
DRIP BLOOD!
DRIP IT ON
THE AUDIENCE.
THAT WAS MY THOUGHT.
I CAN SEE IT ALL NOW.
"BLOOD-O-SCOPE," "BLEED-O-RAMA."
YOU WRECKED
MY THEATER.
I DID NOT!
HE DID.
SHERRY!
IT WAS GREAT,
MR. WOOLSEY.
IT'S KINDA HARD TO BELIEVE
THAT YOU'RE A GROWN-UP.
NO KIDDING.
YOU THINK GROWN-UPS KNOW
WHAT THEY'RE DOING?
THAT'S A HUSTLE, KID.
GROWN-UPS ARE MAKING
IT UP AS THEY GO ALONG
JUST LIKE YOU DO.
YOU REMEMBER THAT,
YOU'LL BE FINE.
THAT'S BEAUTIFUL,
MR. WOOLSEY.
NO TROUBLE.
NURSE.
BUT HE --
WILL YOU STOP WORRYING?
THE INSURANCE WILL COVER IT.
IN FACT, I'D LEAVE
THE BALCONY OUT. I'D PUT
TWO MORE SCREENS UP THERE.
THE SOUND LEAKS,
AND PEOPLE WILL HEAR TWO
PICTURES FOR THE PRICE OF ONE.
THE WAVE OF THE FUTURE!
[Gene] I'LL CALL YOU.
[Sandra]
I'LL CALL YOU TOO.
[Mom] NICE TO MEET YOU.
[Rhonda]
YES, GOOD-BYE.
[TV]
THE ANNOUNCEMENT CAME
IN A COMMUNIQUE...
FROM CHAIRMAN KHRUSHCHEV
TO PRESIDENT KENNEDY,
SAYING THAT THE SOVIETS WOULD
DISMANTLE THE MISSILES ON CUBA,
AND RETURN THEM
TO THE SOVIET UNION.
QUOTING, "TO
GIVE REASSURANCE...
GENE, DENNIS!
"TO ALL PEOPLE
WHO CRAVE PEACE,
COME IN HERE!
"AND TO REASSURE
THE AMERICAN PEOPLE,
"ALL OF WHOM, I AM CERTAIN
ALSO WANT PEACE...
IT'S OVER.
AS DO THE PEOPLE
OF THE SOVIET UNION."
THE PENTAGON SAID THAT THE
AMERICAN NAVAL QUARANTINE
OF CUBA WOULD BE ENDED.
THE SHIPS WOULD BE RETURNING
TO THEIR HOME PORTS
BY THE END OF THE WEEK.
AND SO A SIGH OF RELIEF
AROUND THE WORLD...
AS TWO OF THE GREAT POWERS
PULL BACK FROM
THE NUCLEAR ABYSS.
AMAZING! YOU WON'T
BELIEVE THE KIND OF INK
WE'RE GETTING.
LOOK. "HORROR STUNT
SAVES PATRONS' LIVES."
WHERE?
OH, DOWN THERE.
WELL, WE'RE UP
AGAINST THIS CUBA THING.
ANYWAY, SPECTOR'S GETTING
US INTO 60 THEATERS.
HOW DO YOU LIKE THE CAR?
IT'S GREAT.
WELL, WE'RE OFF
TO THE OPENING.
CLEVELAND.
CONGRATULATIONS.
EXACTLY.
HONEY?
SO, NOW, YOU TWO,
WAS THAT YOUR FIRST DATE?
AH... YEAH.
HARD TO TOP.
YOU GUYS'LL DO IT,
THOUGH.
WELL...
BETTER BE ROLLING.
UH, KEEP
YOUR EYES OPEN.
I WILL.
BYE.
[Honking]
KEEP YOUR EYES OPEN
FOR WHAT?
THE SCARY PARTS.
OH.
NICE KIDS.
THAT WOULDN'T BE BAD,
HAVE A COUPLE KIDS.
WE HAVE TO BE MARRIED
FOR THAT, LARRY.
YEAH, I KNOW.
BOY, YOU ARE
THE SHOCK EXPERT.
THINK ABOUT IT.
YOU SEE THE LOOK ON THOSE TWO?
IT'S LIKE THEIR WHOLE LIFE
GOT CALLED OFF AND THEN,
"NO, WAIT A SECOND, SORRY,"
IT'S ON AGAIN.
THAT'S HOW
EVERYBODY LOOKS NOW.
PEOPLE ARE WALKIN' AROUND,
[Sigh]
THEY MADE IT. SAFE.
UH-HUH.
HOW LONG DO YOU GIVE THAT?
COUPLE WEEKS, COUPLE YEARS,
THEN BANG,
SOMEBODY ELSE COMES ALONG
WITH ANOTHER WAY
FOR THE WORLD TO END.
ONLY THIS TIME
THEY MEAN IT.
AT LEAST THOSE TWO
GOT A JUMP ON IT.
HUH?
THEY'VE SEEN
THE COMING ATTRACTIONS.
[Laughing]
** ["The Lion Sleeps Tonight"]
* IN THE JUNGLE
THE MIGHTY JUNGLE *
* THE LION
SLEEPS TONIGHT *
* IN THE JUNGLE
THE QUIET JUNGLE *
* THE LION SLEEPS TONIGHT
HUP, HUP *
* OWIMOWEH, OWIMOWEH
OWIMOWEH, OWIMOWEH *
OWIMOWEH, OWIMOWEH **
OH, BILL!