Attention.
At ease, gentlemen. Be seated, please.
As you've all probably noticed,
we're currently headed north.
Tomorrow morning at 0500 hours, we will
be taking a position at Yankee Station.
That means we're back in business.
We'll be flying sorties over North Vietnam
to take out enemy supply lines,
which means we have to cross over
into Laos.
This mission is classified.
No cards and letters to sweethearts.
No phone calls to family back home.
- Is that understood?
Yes, sir.
No one can know.
No one except Charlie
when we kick his ass.
For survival
in the jungle environment,
the smart soldier must understand
that nature is not a force against him.
He has to make nature work for him
by utilizing the ample natural provisions
at his disposal.
Is this a double feature?
For God's sake, just lean your head back
and open your mouth.
What is this?
Hell, the boys back home
don't know anything about the jungle.
In the jungle,
your best friend is your knife.
Oh, look at...
Now he's getting serious.
Cut the leaf, man. Here it goes.
Come on, baby, cut. Cut.
Where is the salt and pepper shaker
for that leaf?
Chew it, boy! Chew it!
Leaf good. Me like leaf.
Maintain a constant state
of readiness...
What did he do, sit in an anthill?
Look at him.
And then, when
the rescue helicopter appears, make sure...
Honestly,
it's right above your head!
Jeez. Shake it, Pops.
He's got a nice ass for a sailor,
I'll tell you that.
I don't mean that in a weird way.
God bless America.
Are you a smart soldier?
I mean, I just thought we'd be assisting
some South Vietnamese generals
against a few infiltrators. Whole thing
would be done in three, four weeks.
You picked the wrong time
- to enlist, Dengler.
- I know.
No, but I just wanted to fly so badly,
and everybody, they were telling me
all about the fantastic massage parlors
and the go-go girls, everything, and...
And what did I get? Goddamn one night?
- One night in Saigon. That's me.
- Yeah, and that didn't go so well.
Gentlemen, next please.
Okay.
Hey, are there any mosquito nets?
What you see is what you get.
- Okay. Okay. I see plastic.
- Yes, sir.
I see plastic there and how about...
Are you able to give me two slices
of that plastic, please?
- Sir?
- And maybe six foot by three foot,
you put a zipper in the middle,
- and I crawl inside...
- What you're describing
is a sauna, not a mosquito net.
Not a mosquito net,
but it holds off the bugs.
And you put some netting on it
so I can breathe through at night time.
- You got it, sir.
- Yes?
- Absolutely, sir.
- Okay.
Now, look here. Look at this.
I have my boot on your table.
- Why do I have my boot on your table?
- I don't know, sir.
Okay, this is why. Look at this.
Can you create a flap for me
in the tongue here
so I could hide my American passport
inside of here should I need it?
You know what, sir? Since you're my only
customer today, it would be my pleasure.
Thank you.
So, Charlie got his shit together.
Now we have heavy antiaircraft fire
around Mugia Pass.
Change direction and altitude
every seven seconds
so the radar of the enemy gun
cannot lock onto you.
Your secondary target will be
the intersection of 121 and 90.
That's the Ho Chi Minh Trail.
That's right, Spook, inside Laos.
Now, one more thing.
They've been using your radios
to lure our rescue teams into ambush.
Now, don't get me wrong.
You go down, you use that radio.
But if they're hot on your trail,
you scrap it.
You scrap anything
that they can use against you.
Now, this is Flight Lieutenant Dengler's
first mission.
Yes, sir.
You're gonna be Spook's
wingman. You think you can handle that?
I could not ask for a better man, sir.
But, please,
- could I ask you a question, sir?
Go ahead.
You know, Spook is such
a goddamn daredevil,
could you please order him not to
try too hard to die for his country,
but rather to let the son-of-a-bitch
on the other side die for his instead?
Okay. All right, boys.
- You all set?
Yes, sir.
Anything else?
No, sir.
- Okay. Let's go, go, go!
Radar Kilo, 6195, position four.
Radar Yankee, 67279,
position two.
- Heads against the wall. Come on.
- Come on, Diet.
Come here.
This is what we would do as kids
when we were out for mischief.
It would keep us out of trouble.
But we would usually pee right now.
- Can we pee?
- I don't really have to.
I'm not gonna.
But this will keep us safe. Okay, fellas?
Stay out of trouble.
Come back in one piece. Good luck.
- Come back, boys.
- You, too.
Boys, get set to change
the altitude again. On my mark.
- Now.
- Roger.
Gentlemen, do you notice
the coastline down there?
Welcome to North Vietnam.
It's pretty boring.
Boys, we got too much
cloud cover.
Climbing again 280 west.
We're heading into Laos.
Target in sight.
Lessard, roll in.
Rolling.
Farkas, roll in.
Dengler, roll in.
Rolling in.
I'm hit. I'm hit!
Dieter, you're losing altitude!
Pull it up!
Dieter, pull up!
Dengler, get out of there!
Dieter, bail out!
I'm not gonna bail out!
Oh, come on.
Come on.
Come on, search planes.
Where are you? Where have you gone?
Come on.
God, how can it get this hot?
Hey. Hey.
I need to go to the bathroom.
I need...
Yeah. I need to take a shit.
Hey. Hey.
I need to take a shit.
Oh, shit.
Hey. Hey.
Does nobody listen to me?
Why doesn't anybody listen around here?
Why don't you listen to me?
I said I needed the bathroom
and now I've shit myself.
Why doesn't anybody listen around here?
I've shit my pants.
They can't hear us.
They can't see us through the treetops.
It's not my fault. I didn't signal them.
Don't ever, ever do that again!
You better just shoot me right away!
Don't you ever do that again!
This is unusual.
You American pilots normally attack us
earlier in the day. Sit.
No English.
German.
Why don't you admit
that you are an American?
Yes.
I am an American citizen,
and I love my country.
But why are you in this war against us?
I never wanted to go to war.
I never wanted to go to...
I saw enough as a child.
I only wanted to fly.
Then you should sign this.
"Condemning the imperialistic aggression
"of the corrupt and debased political
establishment of the United States..."
What else would you call it?
"...against innocent children
and the peace loving working classes."
No, I cannot sign this. I cannot sign it.
If you sign this, we would be your friends.
- You could be released in two weeks if...
- I cannot sign this.
- It's against my...
- Your what?
I mean, what is in here?
What isn't here?
I love America. America gave me wings.
I will not sign it, absolutely not.
No way.
Your choice.
The quick have their sleepwalkers,
and so do the dead.
Hey.
- Hey. Hey.
Hey, there. Who's that? Hello.
Hey, you American?
- What?
He's American.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah, I'm American.
My name is Dieter. I'm a U.S. Navy pilot.
And originally I was born in Germany...
Be quiet.
...but I am a U.S. citizen now.
Quiet.
- What?
- Who's that?
Quiet.
Why? I'm whispering.
- Little Hitler's coming.
- Who?
- Little Hitler.
- Who's that?
Who's Little Hitler?
Okay.
Now, what the hell is this?
The Middle Ages?
Hey, listen. Don't mess with
these guys. You'll regret it.
- Hi. Dieter Dengler.
- All right, let's go. Give it over.
Who won the World Series?
- The World Series?
- Yeah.
- I don't know...
- Hey, man, the guy don't like baseball?
You don't like baseball?
- No, I don't know. I don't follow baseball.
- I'm Yik Chiu Tuo.
- Yik Chiu Tuo?
- They call me Y.C.
- Okay, Y.C.
- Y.C.
Hi, I'm Dieter Dengler.
- Dieter Dengler.
- Yeah.
We all flew together for Air America.
Yeah, I'm world champion of bad luck.
But I tell you something, I'm undefeatable.
Hi. Phisit.
- Phisit.
- My name is Phisit.
- Dieter. Dieter.
- Yeah.
Procet Kam Phong Kit.
- What?
- Procet.
- Okay.
What was that?
- Procet.
- It's okay.
Okay.
- That was actually Procet... Got that?
- Right.
- But you need to call him Procet.
- Okay, Procet.
That's what we call him.
He's also Air America.
- Also got shot down flying supplies...
- Okay, okay.
...to royalist villages,
- just like the rest of us.
- And when was that?
Two... No, two and a half year ago now.
- Two and a half years ago?
- Oh, yeah.
I had no idea that we were here
for that long.
Yeah, been here a lot longer
than people know.
- Duane Martin.
- Duane Martin. I'm Dieter Dengler.
United States Air Force. I was shot down
about a year and a half ago.
- Okay.
- And when this war starts,
we'll be here a lot longer
than we already have.
Well, you see...
How many more times you think
I'm gonna have to say,
like I been saying and saying and saying
and saying again,
that we will never go to war
in Vietnam, man?
No, they just...
- They, no...
Because any day now... Listen.
They will what?
- Yeah, Christmas come every day.
- They...
They will release us, man.
They will let us go any day now.
- No, you see...
- Gene, by the way.
- Gene.
- But listen.
It's... The trick to it is it's actually Eugene.
- Okay, Eugene.
- Eugene DeBruin from
- Eugene, Oregon.
- Okay.
- How do you like that?
- Yeah.
See how that works out? Name, name...
Jesus Christ, not this Oregon shit, again.
I've heard this over 2,000 goddamn times.
- Eugene from Eugene.
- Oh, yeah, right. Eugene from Eugene.
- You know what? You know what? Listen.
- Yeah.
What you really need to know is
you see this man here?
Take a good look at him. He, he...
Listen now, he shits in his pants
every night without fail, man.
Trust me.
And you know the only thing that he
thinks is worth complaining about?
You know what that is?
- This man right here.
- Right.
- Eugene from Eugene.
- From Eugene.
Okay.
Dieter.
Take a careful look to your right.
You see that guy there?
We call him Little Hitler
for a very good reason.
He is the worst.
This one we call Jumbo.
Oh, wow.
That's the first smile I've seen
since I was shot down.
Yeah. He's, in fact,
one of the only truly nice guys here.
This is Nook the Rook right here.
He's also very much not a nice guy.
- What is his problem?
- It's all right. Just keep going.
His problem is he's Crazy Horse.
That's what we call him.
And he is a bastard. Keep going.
And I just cannot stand him.
- That's Walkie Talkie.
- Walkie Talkie?
We call him that 'cause he does not speak.
Never, never.
Hey, do yourself a favor, Kraut.
Keep your head down
and your mouth shut.
That's your best chance of surviving.
So there is a war.
There is a war.
All right. So tell me about
the peace talks, man. Geneva?
There's got to be peace talks, man.
Shut up, Gene.
There is no goddamn conference.
When are you gonna get that
through your skull?
Secret talks, man.
I'm just talking about secret talks.
Forget it.
We're not getting out.
No, no, no, there was a honcho
on the outside,
he said I would not be here too long.
They tell that to everyone
to get them to sign.
No, I did not sign. No.
Anyway, nice having met you.
What do you mean, met?
Well, my friends,
you can rot in here if you like,
but I'm gonna scram this very night.
This hut, it ain't no prison.
Scram. I like that. I like that.
Listen, listen, my friend,
you cannot escape.
If you try to escape,
you'll screw up our release.
Look, I don't give a shit about our release
or whatever you think is gonna happen.
But without water, you won't survive
more than two days out there.
And without water,
your tracks will be visible for even more.
The jungle is the prison. Don't you get it?
Hey, when does the rainy season start?
Five months, maybe six.
I can't wait that long.
Hey, listen, let's say you do survive
the jungle and lack of water,
whatever you find, snakes and animals
and shit are out there,
you won't make it out of camp.
There's six guards posted during the day.
Yeah.
That is during the day.
I'm going at night.
Why, what happens at night?
No.
I'm shitting my intestines out.
Again.
I'm sorry, I can't help it.
You just shit right on my hand again, man.
- Sorry.
- That makes it 2,207 times and counting.
Leave the guy alone, okay?
There ain't no alone, brother.
Does anybody have a nail?
What are you gonna do with a nail?
You're gonna stab all the lousy guards
to death with a nail?
What kind of plane you fly off of?
- Procet has got a shard of glass, man.
- No, that's no good.
I have porcupine needle.
No.
I've got a hammer and a socket wrench
stuffed up my ass.
There's no nails.
This whole prison's made
of bamboo and rattan.
Damn it.
I know where there's a nail.
Okay.
I'm gonna make my move.
So all of you scatter in
all directions, okay? Go.
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
What makes you think you're not crazy
for thinking that'll work, man?
Eugene's right.
It'll attract too much attention.
Oh, for God's sake, that's what I want.
Please.
You trust me? Please.
Duane, head to the outhouse.
Y.C., go to the top right. Okay?
Gene, please come on. No, no, no.
Gene, Phisit, Procet,
head towards the gate.
Move as fast as you can.
Get their attention, that's what I need.
Go, go, go, go. Go, go.
Hey, Jumbo, Jumbo. Hey, no, no, no.
Can I borrow some of the toothpaste?
Let me get some of that. That's good.
I felt so like having a good smile,
you know?
Like you have. You got a good smile, too.
Okay.
Y.C., when I hit it, you make a noise.
Cough or something.
I love it.
I love it. I love it.
Give me some slack.
Let's see.
Oh, God. Oh, God, that was an easy one.
You see, I apprenticed as a tool
and die maker in Germany.
There was no aviation at the time
and I wanted to learn something useful
that would help me repair planes.
And, boy, are those years coming in handy
in unexpected ways now.
There's only one brand
that I cannot handle,
that is Smith and Wesson.
I think with practice, I can open these up
in maybe two, three seconds flat.
But listen, everybody keep one cuff
on a wrist at all times,
so that if the guards come checking,
we can put them on again quickly.
No, they don't check us at night.
They think we can't get out of these.
They think it's impossible.
Show me how you did that.
It's so simple. Okay.
All you do, insert the nail.
There's a cuff and a spring.
They both have teeth.
You push down on the spring,
disengage the teeth like that.
You see? This is what happens inside.
- And the cuffs release.
Wow.
Hands free.
Get away.
No, no, no, no, no. Let him.
He's our friend, Malay.
Let him do it. It's the best way
to heal sores around here.
Okay.
Hey,
that cuff thing, that's good, real good.
Yeah. Thanks.
Hey, Duane,
do you know where we are?
I mean, you have any idea?
No. But my guess
is that this here's still Laos.
And the guards, they're...
- Laotian.
...Laotian?
- Yeah.
- Yeah, but the camp is Vietcong,
there's no question.
Look, I know what you're thinking,
but jungles on these mountains
is a nightmare.
Besides, you'd end up in Vietnam.
- No, but if we can get to Thailand...
- Yeah.
If we can make it to the Mekong River...
Yeah, the Big Muddy.
If you could, you would, right?
Yeah. We can.
- Hey, why not? We can.
- Yeah.
Just stop talking about it. Okay?
Just quiet. Excuse me.
- Hey, Gene.
- Yeah.
Which of you guys knows most
about the country?
Oh, that would be Phisit,
but he doesn't talk to us.
What do you mean?
You see, Phisit is pissed about...
About...
He's pissed about something.
We don't even remember
what he's pissed about.
Hey!
Hey, come back!
I can't believe that bastard shot you.
I know. I didn't even pull down
my flight suit.
Hey, look, when I was standing
it looked like...
We're gonna get even one day.
Howdy.
Americali.
- Americali.
- Americali. Americali. Americali.
Two years ago a parcel came through.
Yeah.
He puts it on display on really bad days.
The bacon label still looks greasy.
Does it still have a scent on it?
Oh, you bet.
Can I get a sniff?
Oh, no, you may not.
You may not. That is my sniff.
Man, that is my sniff.
Hey.
How'd you ever end up a pilot?
I always... I always wanted to be one.
I was
five years old, or something, in a little
town, Wildberg, in the Black Forest,
and it was just bombed to ashes,
you know?
No clear reason,
just these senseless attacks.
But I remember I was in the attic
with my brother.
We were looking out,
and we see this fighter plane,
beautiful, coming right at us.
And it's firing from its wings,
and I see the machine gun,
it's flashing and it
goes flying past the house.
It's so close. I mean,
it's feet away from the house.
And the canopy was open.
And this pilot,
he had his goggles up on his helmet.
And I could see his eyes.
And he was looking at me.
Right at me.
He's looking right at me.
And as he turns to go, he's starting back,
he's looking right at me still.
And the thing is,
from that moment on, little Dieter,
he needed to fly.
You're a strange bird, Dieter.
Guy tries to kill you and you want his job.
Yeah.
God, we need the rain.
We need the rain to come quicker.
See, here's what I can see,
you still need to understand.
- No, I understand.
- You wanna talk about the rain again, we...
Listen, now. Listen.
We will be released
by the time the rain comes
like I have told you before...
- Stop telling me.
- I don't wanna have to keep telling you.
- Then stop telling me.
- They will release us.
You understand?
And here's what I'm starting to think,
that maybe you're trying
not to understand.
If you try and escape, we,
we will be killed,
we who you leave behind.
- It's not just me, we all try to escape.
- Taking off. We who have been here
for two years.
Two years before you showed up.
I don't want to escape alone.
We escape together.
Wait, wait.
Why would the guards spend all this time
cutting bamboo and wood
to build a watchtower
if we weren't meant
to be here for a while?
- Exactly.
- Two years.
- Exactly. Why would they do that if they...
- Listen. Listen to me.
...didn't plan to hold us a long time?
- Listen. Here's what it all comes down to.
I am not, I'm not gonna let you do that.
No, no, no.
You know what I am gonna do?
I am gonna scream.
That's right. I think
I'm gonna scream my head off.
'Cause see,
I would much rather they shoot you,
than me, or any of us. You understand?
Yeah.
You understand?
You've been warned.
Haven't you?
Hey, hey, hey, hey.
This is for shaving.
Howdy.
- Man, I can't get over it.
- What, this?
No, that girl, you know?
She smiled at me.
And when she smiled,
man, did I wish there was no war.
Really.
- I thought you were engaged.
- Oh, yeah, I am.
We got engaged the day before I left.
Marina, she is a wonderful girl.
So smart, you know?
She studies marine biology.
But I hope that she's waiting for me.
- I'm sure she is.
- Yeah, well, she said she would,
but, you know, women can be funny
and go looking for another man...
Duane, you okay?
- Yeah.
- Y.C.?
Yik Chiu Tuo, okay.
Okay. Gene?
Phisit? Procet?
Yeah.
Happy birthday to you.
Happy birthday, dear Dieter.
It is May the 22nd?
Happy birthday.
- Thank you.
- Happy birthday, Dieter.
What kind of champagne is this?
You just got to keep thinking protein,
lots of protein.
It's not bad.
Squished insect larva.
Protein.
Mmm.
Oh, this is a good year, this one.
Yeah, my favorite.
So, listen, guys.
Thank you so much.
And it is my birthday, yes,
but I would like
to give you some presents.
Okay. Now, look.
I have taken these cartridge shells
and I have made a knife of each one.
Okay.
Now, I'm sorry, but I have to keep one
for myself. Okay?
Duane, you're first.
Right.
Phisit.
Left or right?
Y.C.
Easy money, pal.
Gene.
- Procet, it is yours. Okay.
- I don't care about the knife.
This is for Crazy Horse.
No, no, no. Crazy Horse is mine.
My Crazy Horse. Mine.
Now listen, we must collect the rice
and hide it.
But we must dry it because it rots
too quickly if we don't dry it, okay?
What? Hide it? You wanna hide it?
- Yeah, yeah.
- We can eat it now.
- No, no.
- We eat it now.
Look, look, look, I've created
a secret compartment here for the rice.
It is at the bottom of my crap container.
So I don't think the guards
- are gonna want to check that.
- Crazy. This is...
Why are you hiding it now?
For our escape.
You have a plan.
Yes.
Now, have you noticed
that the guards when they are called
to the kitchen hut for chow time,
they always leave
their rifles behind, always?
So we have a few minutes
before they return for their rifles.
We go out through the hut,
we grab their guns,
- we surprise them.
- No.
- And we surprise... We surprise them...
- Crazy.
...and we surround them, okay?
Then we take the guards as prisoners.
We take over the camp.
Think about it, okay?
We hold it down for a few days
until we can signal our aircraft
to pick us up.
- Dieter, quick.
- Okay.
They'll call mess any second.
Quick, quick.