Highway Patrolman
Rojas, come here at once!
I haven't got all day!
What classes do you have today?
Law. Self-defence.
Criminal psychology. Weaponry
This letter authorises you
to work for me
Show it to your tutors tomorrow
Sir, this will affect my marks
Report to my office in 15 minutes
Guerrero, come here at once!
Come with me
Cadet, help the ladies
Open the door
But I was right there
You were lucky
I had to cut the grass
and wash the car
I found condoms
in the glove compartment
- You're having me on
- I swear it's true
- Sorry, Sergeant. A tyre burst
- You'll pay for a new one
Two volunteers to change the wheel.
Guerrero and Leyva!
Who can give me the essence
of today's lesson?
You're the most stupid class
I've ever had!
Let's see if Cadet Rojas can
enlighten his illustrious colleagues
Three reasons to stop vehicles -
One, highway patrol violations
Two, mechanical defects
- Three...
- Stop thrashing about, Rojas
What is the essence
of today's lesson?
Well, it seems that whatever
the circumstances...
...they've always broken the law
Exactly!
They've always broken the law
When you follow a vehicle...
...stop it first,
then decide what they have done
- What have you learnt today?
- They've always broken the law!
Your rifle
Your pistol
Your badge
Cadet Pedro Rojas!
The National Highway Patrol...
...expects you to honour it...
...and maintain
the spirit of the service
Cake, Isabel?
I hope you like it
Congratulations, brother
Where's Dad?
You know he's tied up with work
You're lucky to have passed
I'd have failed if it wasn't for Pedro
Don't tell anyone
Mother, Dad hasn't spoken to me
in a year!
Don't be upset.
He wanted you to study medicine
You're the first
to have finished his studies
No matter what Dad thinks,
I'm proud of my brother...
...the patrolman
Your first assignment...
...is Sector Four
of the Northern Z one, Highway 82
You've been highly recommended.
I expect an ex emplary performance
Report to Lieutenant Perez.
He will allocate a car to you
You get number 27, Rojas
Our best car, because
they say you are a good driver
Thank you, Lieutenant
I'm warning you...
...one scratch
and I'll knock the shit out of you
- Congratulations
- Thank you, Lieutenant
May I see your licence?
You're putting lives at risk, driving the
wrong way down a one-way street
What is your explanation?
I'm late for work
and my boss wants to fire me
My mother is ill, my father beats me
and my dog has died
You should leave earlier
to get to work on time
I could impound your car
for three days
Here is your licence
I'll overlook it this time
Everything is all right. Right?
Have a nice day
Buy our iguanas!
Pedro, they've assigned us
to look after hell
Even buzzards are at a loss here
- What would you like?
- Ice cold beers
The beers have all gone, lads
There is only tequila
- What about those gringos?
- They brought their own beer
No beer. Bring tequila then
What do you reckon?
Beer
No, thank you
German, the best
Mexican beer is best
You've never been
to an Oktoberfest...
Can't you see we're busy?
I'll leave them there
How do they expect us
to make money here?
Meet our quotas
Check trucks and permits
Dealers smuggle drugs
in truckloads of explosives
Don't mess with them,
they're really dangerous
We mustn't be afraid of them
It's poison!
- What's wrong?
- No front bumper
It was stolen last night
- Open the back
- I've nothing but canned goods
Nothing but canned goods?
Take this ball
Shoes for your son. A bathing suit
I'm impounding this merchandise.
Follow me to the police station
I'm only making a living
Thanks for remembering my children
Getting permission was difficult
God will know how to thank you
It takes so little to make them happy,
doesn't it?
May I have a cigarette?
"S ONS OF TH E ARMY"
Come to our restaurant, El Famlllar
Try our dellclous clllaqulles
In green sauce...
...and our succulent
luevos rancleros
If you're so weary, stay at home
instead of sucking travellers' blood
Article 70 - trucks are not
public transport. Licence, please
How am I supposed to take
my workers to the fields?
In a limousine?
It's obvious that
you come from the city
Leave him alone, Señorita Griselda
- Griselda...
- Don't you like my name?
It's unusual, but I like it
What now? Because I am not
going to give you money
You'll breakfast with your workers.
I've not eaten since yesterday
You want to have breakfast?
Do you know Pancho Villa Street?
Do you know where the plaza is?
My house is two blocks
from the plaza. Number 115
I'll be waiting there... in an hour
Don't be late
Is Señorita Griselda in?
We've been waiting for you.
You are two hours late
Lots of work?
Highway problems, Señor Marcos
Never mind. You can come here
whenever you like
Why haven't the service station
robbers been caught yet?
That's a matter
for the municipal police, not us
Well consider this your home
Please help me with my sleeve
I hope I won't make it worse
What happened to your face?
When I was a boy, some friends
threw me through a window
With such friends,
I'd hate to meet your enemies
Life in the capital, Señorita Griselda
How do you like it in Mapimi?
It's lovely
They say that God was born
in Mapimi
- An egg?
- Yes please, Señorita Griselda
All my friends call me Z eldita
You're dead tired
Zanaida, prepare the guest room
for the officer
It's not necessary, Señor Marcos
Patrolmen never rest. Always looking
down the barrel of a gun
- True?
- True... Z eldita
Father, weren't you going
to do something?
No, I've got no plans
You asked me to remind you
of something
Oh yes...
I was going to change
the flowers on your mother's grave
I'll come to the door with you
- What about Father?
- He's very tired and his leg hurts
Tell him I miss him very much
Let's get going, my love
I need money for irrigating the ranch
A patrolman's salary
isn't big enough for that
Open the door for me
I know how to do it
- Put it on the floor
- OK
You know a patrolman's salary
is barely enough to get by on
Somehow we must have
more money here
Don't drool on me
Don't worry, all women
are the same. She'll get over it
A wedding ring is a tightening noose
I just washed it
It's dirty here
- How goes it, Anibal?
- A promise is a debt
- How much?
- Half. And check the oil in my car
What are you doing?
Get rid of that banger
It's fine. I just need
to change the plugs
- Change the car
- The car's fine
Rojas. Report to the Commandant
What have you done?
Who knows
You're worn out
Come for some fun at the Oasis
after your shift
No. Thanks all the same, Anibal
What's happening, Rojas?
I hear you aren't fulfilling your quota
for tickets. Is there a problem?
The road is deserted.
There's almost no traffic
Officer Guerrero
seems to have no problem
- I'm not interested in him
- But I am, Rojas!
Because of your poor performance
I am assigning you to Route 44
- The pig route?
- Precisely
If you don't manage
to fulfil your duties there...
...I'll have to suspend you.
Understand?
- Yes, sir
- Dismissed
I think one is dead
Did you ask for the permits?
He has the vet's examination papers
but no health permits
I'll check. Confiscate the dead pig
Sorry, but without health permits
I can't allow you to go any further
All the Health Department red tape...
The pigs will die of old age
before I get permits
I have Doctor Matanzas' certificate...
...and a donation
to your department's retirement fund
We appreciate your donation
But you can't leave without permits
Every time they change the officer,
the bribe goes up
I'm not informed about that
I'll inform you. There you are
Please stamp my permit
Even stones bleed out here,
don't they?
- What's this?
- The dead pig
They're not going to eat it!
The poor people
haven't got much else
What are you drinking? I'll pay
Looking for company?
I'm married
Everyone here is married
Buy us a drink
Waiter!
A round of drinks for the ladies
Not like that. Dance slowly
Come on. Get up and go. Time's up
- Out, Pepe
- Pedro... Pedro Rojas
Come and see me soon, Pedro.
I like you
Officer Pedro Rojas
Emilio. Are you paying a visit?
- What time do you call this?
- It's only five in the morning.
Don't try to be funny, you fool.
Where have you been?
Don't yell, you'll wake your father
Since when have you cared?
I'll do what I please in my house
We'll see about that.
No one makes a fool of me
I'm warning you, Pedro
It's my house...
...and no one makes a fool of me
I'm warning you, Pedro!
Just you wait and see
Where have you been, Pedro?
I'm talking to you
If you do this again you won't live
to see another day, I swear it
And if you give me
a venereal disease...
...I'll serve your balls for breakfast
You're making money at last,
Pedro dear
You should have said
you were working
Come on. We must get there first
Car 27, reporting from the accident
on Highway 27
There's another one inside
- How goes it, Anibal?
- Fine
It's a good job we got here first.
Those vultures never leave a thing
How about this? Nice, eh?
It's for you to keep, Pedro
I'm going after them
Car 27...
...reporting a suspicious yellow
Gremlin without number plates
Stop immediately!
Take it easy, boss.
We don't want to end up full of holes
You're drunk. Get out of the car!
Hold on, calm down
Don't muck about with me.
Show me your licence!
Take it easy, just give me a moment.
Don't upset me
Give us a ticket quickly.
We're in a hurry
Simon, show him your licence
Goodbye, copper!
Car 27, Code 44
I've been shot in the leg
Car 27, Offlcer Rojas,
report your posltlon
Pedro. Wake up, man
I must speak to you, boy
- Father?
- Yes. Don't you recognise me?
Dad, I'm happy to see you
Those men almost killed you
I wasn't careful enough
It won't happen again
You'll end up crippled, like me
All because of those damn cops who
blew my knee off in the 1962 strike
I'll be all right, you'll see
Reconsider all this, son.
Come and work with me
Is that why you came?
You almost lost your life.
Don't keep disobeying me!
Father, I'm a patrolman
and I always will be
After this you insist on remaining
a petty taker of bribes?
Please don't treat me like this
We'll meet again, Pedro
In another life
Father, don't leave me here
Help me!
When you grow up,
you'll work like Daddy, Lucerito
Pedro, please.
Don't start giving her ideas
So being a patrolman
means nothing?
Don't get upset
You know your public service work
gets very little recognition
Dad came to insult me, too
Your father?
Your father...
...has died
While you were in hospital
You had such a fever
We couldn't break the news to you
I'll put the baby to bed
Eat
What did they do to you?
Don't touch me there.
It hurts like hell
It's a dangerous job, isn't it?
Your job is dangerous too
Maribel, why do you do this?
What do you mean "why"?
Why are you a cop?
You can't compare jobs
No? What do you know?
I have two children
My husband left me two years ago
Do you think I do it for fun?
No, not that
Get the hell out of here
I never want to see you again
Maribel, I didn't mean to offend you
Fuck off! I don't want to see you
Damn leg!
Are you all right? What happened?
- I hit a truck
- You were chasing it?
No, I shifted to first
instead of reverse
Well you did a thorough job
Do you think it's funny?
This vehicle is public property
and you are responsible for it
You must pay for the repairs
In the meantime, use this car
No objections or you'll keep it
Pull over! That's an order!
- Let's see how brave you are now
- Don't kill me!
Why should I stain my hands
with your blood?
Your cellmates can rape you
I'm Ramon Lopez Perez,
son of the state governor
- Bullshit! I'll knock that out of you
- I swear! I'm Ramon Lopez Perez!
I'm taking you in. Your friends can
wait for the pick-up truck
Eliseo, call my father at the mansion
I'll call my uncle at the police too
- Why not call the President?
- I know him, too
I swear I'm Ramon Lopez Perez
My uncle will fix that creep
Stop crying, sissy. You're all right
You've really screwed things up,
Pedro
First you crash your car. Then you
rough up the Governor's son
He deserved a bigger beating
than he got
Sure, but you know
these little rich boys
They're made of porcelain
You can't touch them.
Daddy is someone
- It was a misunderstanding
- Control your animals
Don't you insult me!
Navarro, sort this creep out
- Just try that again!
- Clear off, you brat!
Rojas, come to my office
Never draw a gun on a minor
It's the first thing we teach you!
So what happened?
I'm on report. I must go and see
Doctor Bolaños in Torreon
Rojas, car 27 is ready
Assign it to someone else.
I've got used to 112
You're joking.
This car is a death-trap
No. The 112 engine
is more powerful
Pedro, take 27. It's a better car
Like this gun, it's better
Smith and Wesson automatic.
You can't compare it to your gun
What's the difference?
They both kill
Are you sure
you didn't hate your father?
He was very strict but I loved him
And you still like women?
Absolutely
Doctor, be frank
Do you think there is
something wrong with me?
Officer Rojas, take these pills
If they don't work
I'll prescribe stronger ones
Señor Peña, your bus
is in no condition to be driven
Give us a break. We're not going far
Think of the kids.
They're all mentally retarded
Besides I was going
to give you a big tip
It's not a question of money. You're
responsible for the children's safety
Car 19, this is 112. Over
White caravan, licence 471 O VE,
coming your way
Driver was smoking a joint
We'll collect off tlem.
Tlanks, Pedro.!
Be careful, they look like smugglers.
Keep radio contact. I'll join you
There's a campsite up there
It's for girls
but I'm sure they'll admit you
God bless you, Officer. You're kind
Have a drink on me
Drive carefully, Señor Peña
What are you looking at?
Get inside
Car 19, I've spotted them.
I'm moving to intercept
Car 19. I'm bellnd tle wllte caravan
Tlere's no danger, I'm stopplng llm
Calling car 19. 112 won't start
Relax, Pedro. Flx It and tlen follow
I'v e swltcled on my warnlng llglts
Don't do it, Anibal. Wait for me
Tley'v e slot out my wlndscreen.!
Tlose bastards won't get away.!
Anibal, back off!
Tley're armed to tle teetl.!
Tley're gettlng away.!
Now tley'v e stopped.
Wlere tle lell are you, Pedro?
Take cover. I'm almost with you
I can't hear you, Anibal!
Speak clearly, I can't hear you!
Where are you, brother? Hold on!
What happened to you?
What have they done to you?
Where was God
when they did this to you?
What would you like, gentlemen?
A bottle of tequila
I'm sorry, we serve only cocktails
Tequila, or I'll knock the shit
out of you!
Sorry.
We've just come from a funeral
Please make an exception
in this case
Thirty years in the service...
...and I can't get used to this
To Anibal, Pedro.
We must never forget him
I'm going to look for those gringos.
They're going to pay
Don't waste your time.
They're out of the country by now
Learn from what happened
and forget the whole thing
But be sure to remember
your friend Anibal...
...who died doing his duty
Tle Wllte House las stated...
...tlat drug smuggllng
from Mexlco Is up 30%
Turn off that television!
And bring another bottle of tequila
And another glass
Salud, Sergeant
Buy our iguanas!
Why aren't you at school?
We don't want to go
Don't you know it's illegal
to sell iguanas on the highway?
- Where did you get them?
- The mountains
You don't want to go to prison?
Tell me where your school is then
It's up there
You don't want to go?
Well I'm taking you up there
right now
Take your hands off the car
You think it's funny?
Officer, we have a big problem.
A rabid dog, over in the corral
- What happened to her?
- The dog bit her
Take her to the clinic at once!
Don't follow me,
it might be dangerous
You have a problem, too?
It's my daughter,
these children's mother
As long as it's not another dog
You must pay for killing my chicken
You fool
Can you take my grandson?
They left my daughter here
this afternoon
- Maribel?
- Do you know her?
Then help her. She can't stay here
Maribel, what's wrong with you?
It's Pedro. Don't you recognise me?
Maribel, what did they do to you?
I'm all right, don't worry
- I'm freezing
- Put my coat on
- Put that animal away
- It's only an iguana, Pedro
Careful, there's another somewhere
Don't be a sissy
I'll take you to the bar but you must
tell me who is giving you the drugs
- What's it to you?
- I'm not mucking about
Me neither.
Stop acting like Tarzan's mother
You can't change things
- What are they for?
- Pills. For my nerves
Let me help you
Keep out of my problems
Let me buy you something to eat
at least
- If you like
- Two portions of cllclarrón
Come and see me sometime
Emilio, listen. I need some now
Emilio, I'm dying. Let's go inside
- Who was that cop?
- A customer, like all the others
Car 27, report your posltlon
Can you tell me the time?
Come on, can't you afford a watch?
It's very late
Pedro, breakfast is ready
What are you doing?
I'm just checking Anibal's gun
You can't forget, can you?
I couldn't save his life
Be careful, that's all I ask
I'm your wife
But I don't want to be your widow
Get out, wltl your lands up.!
Where are you going?
I'm taking my brother to work
in Nuevo Laredo tomorrow
- What's your job?
- I'm a journalist...
- Show me your press card
- It's at home in Browns ville
Journalist?
Don't you mean smuggler?
- Open the boot
- I haven't got the key
You travel light
Maybe your heavy bags
are elsewhere?
On your knees, you bastard!
Drop your trousers
Why? This is abuse by the police
What have we got here?
Where did you get this stuff?
They'll kill us if we squeal
That's not my problem
What about the helicopter
beyond the mountains?
It's the distributors, foreigners
We take their drugs across for them
- When are they due back?
- In two days, stuff for Los Organos
Please don't kill me.
For my children's sake
We haven't done anything
Clear off
The car?
- Can I come in?
- Yes
Finished?
A few moments ago
Want to cover yourself?
Don't you like me like this?
Take this money. And the drugs
Go and dry out at your mother's
Who are you to order me about?
A patrolman
Obey me or go to jail
Pedro, there is no cure for me
I am going to die
Then die at home
I don't want to find you dead
in this crappy place
Hold me
Pack and I'll take you to the bus
Hug your mother and the kids for me
Tell me if you need anything
Call me through HQ
when you get home
Enough of that, we're off now
Rojas, we're out of work. You
haven't wrecked your car in months
Check the points
while I see the Commandant
I've received a report
from the police
They stopped two men
on the highway
They said a patrolman confiscated
their drugs then let them go
Do you know anything about this?
The police are very naive
I'm sure it's just a yarn.
The drugs have been hidden
- You don't know anything?
- Absolutely nothing
I'll tell them to make further enquiries
You may go now
Be careful, lad. I'll be keeping
a close eye on you. Understand?
Emilio!
It's Pedro Rojas of the PN DC
All I want to know is
who the guys in the helicopter were
Come and get me, if you can!
Emilio, I'm Maribel's friend
Let's drop our guns and make a deal
Just come and get me!
I only wanted to talk to you, that's all
Fuck!
I'll tell him at once
Central Office congratulates you,
Rojas
He was a drug trafficker.
He deserved it
- I only wanted to detain him
- That you did. Congratulations
However, I must suspend you
for 30 days during the investigation
Why?
It's routine,
when there's been a death
The police insist
that weekly deliveries were 15 kilos
They accuse me
of concealing the drugs?
You know how they are.
They suspect everybody
I'm resigning, Commandant
The Highway Patrol rewards
its most effective personnel, Rojas
We must be tough. You have
a great future in the Corporation
I don't give a damn. I'm going home
Stupid little boys
Most don't even make it this far
- What's wrong with the baby?
- Who knows, Dad
Don't forget to tell Venancio
to repair the cow pasture fence
Drive carefully. Don't hurt the boys
Buy me the afternoon edition
of "The Voice of the North"
And don't forget my change
- Is that all?
- No. My kiss
What's so funny?
What a nice surprise
Maribel, you have a visitor
Pedro, I'm surprised to see you
I couldn't come before, what with
quitting the service and everything
I can imagine.
I went to Headquarters a month ago
Invite the officer for a cup of tea
We'd invite you to eat
but there isn't enough
I'm glad to see you looking well
But for how long?
Pedro, live with us.
We'll be very happy
No, I can't leave my family,
my daughter
So I'll have to go back to the bar
No, please don't
How am I supposed to feed
my family?
You promised to give me money,
or have you forgotten?
If you don't want to live here
and I can't work... What then?
What the hell am I supposed to do?
Are you going to support me
or what?
Yes. I'll give you money every month
Thanks, Pedro
You're great
Maribel, the child!
Buy our iguanas!
PAYI NG TAX ES
IS PARTICI PATI NG