We all grow up looking for
somebody to believe in.
For me it was my father.
He was my hero.
The day after my 12th birthday I found out
my father killed people for a living.
He was a made member of the Mafia.
When I saw my father shot dead
outside of our house
I remember thinking
he probably deserved it.
And years later, when I got the chance,
I joined the marines
looking for something new
to believe in.
That lasted until February of 1991.
Just outside Kuwait City
and the Iraqi border.
Fuck!
Let me guess - you're from the government
and here to help me.
Get on your feet, tough guy.
I tell you, you're a helluva good marine.
Commendations, medals...
Made sergeant 26 months ago.
Pretty good.
And then you assault an MP
and you steal the colonel's jeep.
Why?
The colonel is a prick.
Something like yourself.
Tough guy, ain't he?
Smart, too.
Like your friends.
Friends? What friends are those?
Alright, let's see what you're looking at here.
Bad conduct discharge,
forfeiture of all paid allowances,
confinement, 2 to 3 years
at hard labor.
You've really put yourself up the creek,
old buddy.
Maybe I've got a paddle for ya.
Wanna hear more?
Not particularly.
You know this guy,
Manny Matello?
Hey, Rocco,
make me a Cosmopolitan.
Manny Matello was the
mafia boss
my father and my uncle Joe
had worked for.
I swear on Saint
fucking Anthony
if you put too much cranberry juice
in it this time,
I'm gonna kill your whole
fucking family.
You hear me?
Hey, Rocco?
Tell me, am I gonna
be lucky tonight?
The shooters were a couple of zips
working for a guy named
Luciano Reggio.
Now Reggio is a major
drug trafficker.
He's also liaison between
the Gambinos in New York
and the Sicilian mob.
In fact, New York sent Reggio down
to whack Manny Matello.
Take over the family.
Imagine that, huh?
A goddamn immigrant
running the old neighbourhood.
Do you remember a guy
named Willy Dolan?
Used to run a little book
for Manny Matello.
Sure, I knew Willy.
We grew up together.
Nice guy.
Just looking to buy a house
for his wife and kid.
87 thousand.
The market's changed.
The price is a 100 now.
It took me six months to put
87 grand together.
Now you want a hundred?
You tell me you're gonna
sell me a house for 87 grand,
now you want a hundred.
What's with the quibbling,
Junior? Why are
we quibbling?
Price is a hundred grand.
No quibble.
You know what? You're a fucking
pain in the ass to do business with,
you one-legged motherfucker.
- One-legged?
- I'm taking my money and going home.
You've got a problem with
my leg now, huh?
You don't even know how much money
I'm saving you out of mortgage.
That's how fucking stupid you are.
How do you like my leg now?
Tryin to chisel me, huh?
Stealing money out of my pocket?
Like the cocksucker you are!
That's right - I fucking spit on you!
Fucking piece of shit.
What's this, Willy?
What's this?
You motherfucker.
Willy was working for us.
And we're gonna miss Willy.
We had some things
that we were working on
and there are things we gotta
keep working on.
Which is why we're talking
to you,
tough guy.
Now you wanna be
a good citizen
and help us out here?
Hey, you wanna let me
out of here?
I'd like to get back to my cell.
Please.
Ok, so you don't care about
truth, justice
and the American way.
What about Joey Marcucci?
Care about him?
He's family, isn't he?
Yeah, he's my cousin.
Another ignorant dirtbag.
But we can't choose our
family, can we?
What exactly do you want me to do?
I don't want you to do anything for me.
But I'm gonna give you a chance
to do something
for your cousin Joey,
the dirtbag.
Because Joey doesn't like the idea
this guy taking over the family business.
I mean, sooner or later
these guys will kill each other,
they are gonna sit down and
make some kind of a deal.
Well I want you to be there,
because I want Reggio.
Do you understand me,
tough guy?
I want Reggio.
You give me Reggio,
I give you your cousin Joey.
I vowed a long time ago
I was never gonna become
what my father was.
Now I was going home to
become something he was.
My mother died giving birth
to my brother Vincent.
After my father was killed,
me and Vincent
went to live with my uncle Joe,
my aunt Tina and my cousin Joey.
Me, Vincent and Joey, we
were more than cousins.
We were brothers.
- Your father got killed?
- Don't make a big deal of it.
Vincent, slow down.
Even if it doesn't make you taller,
it makes you fat.
Go fuck your hand.
Look at Joey.
How's the steamfitters?
It's great, man.
My back hurts all the time,
throbbing.
My legs feel like somebody
beat them with a hammer.
Remind me to thank you
in like a hundred years.
You ain't 10th and Wolf,
where you're from?
I'm a friend of Ricky's.
You know Ricky?
Ricky Jerk-Off?
That's what we call him round here,
Ricky Jerk-Off.
You know why?
- Why?
- Well cuz he's a jerk-off.
Go get us a pack of
smokes, will ya?
What am I, your bitch?
I'm buying.
Watch my purse.
Let me tell you something
about Ricky Jerk-Off.
Hey, Marcucci,
you're talking to my girl.
I ain't your girl.
I just met ya.
Shut your face.
Hi, Ricky Jerk-Off,
what's going on?
Tommy, this is between me
and your prick-face cousin over here.
Is this a jerk-off convention?
Fuck you, Marcucci.
Tommy, I'm coming!
Let go of me!
Come on, Vincent!
Get off me.
Tommy, you're making a
mess over here.
We're gonna have to pay
for all that stuff we broke.
How much do you think three
tables and a booth cost?
Shit, I broke my chain,
I lost my St. Chris.
You sent me for the cigarettes
on purpose, didn't you?
- Shut up.
- That ain't right.
You don't think I'm tough?
- Come on, me and you. Right now.
- Shut up, Vince.
Come on, Joey. Tell him I can
kick his fucking ass.
Not in your wildest dreams, Vincent.
How's my eye?
Let me see.
Fucking yin and yang douchebags.
It's Manny.
Joey, come here.
Manny!
- What do you think he wants?
- Shut up.
Listen to me, son.
It's your father, Joey.
He's gone.
Uncle Joe was killed the same way
my father was.
Left for dead like an animal
in the street.
Tommy, get yourself cleaned up.
Go home and take your brother.
Your aunt's gonna need ya.
Now go on. Good boys.
We're all gonna miss him.
He was a good husband.
A good friend.
Thank you for everything, Manny.
Thank you.
Aunt Tina, is Joey home?
What the hell do you think you're looking at?!
Ain't you got no decency?!
Toilet's busted. Take a walk.
Move, I've gotta pee.
Get outta here before I kick
the shit out of you.
Yeah, you and what army?
Back in, I'll knock your teeth
down your throat.
Loser!
Okay.
You wanna know
or you don't wanna know?
You're old enough to decide.
You either deal with these things
or you don't.
I wanna know.
You're your father's son.
His blood.
It's not my place,
unless you give it up.
So,
tell me what to do.
Why is he giving him that newspaper?
Oh, is he gonna let him
read the obituary?
How are you holding up?
Okay, I guess.
Poor Joey.
- You guys should go home.
- We're not leaving you, Joey.
- Go home.
- I wanna talk about this.
Can we talk about this, please?
He killed my father, Tommy.
What do you want me to do?
You want me to go to the cops?
Ask him to say he's sorry?
All we know is what Manny told us.
Maybe Manny's wrong.
I'm not saying that he is.
But you do this right now, you'll
kill somebody
you're gonna live with that
for the rest of your life.
What, do you think
Manny got it wrong?
You know something I don't?
Go home.
Benedetto?
Joey, what...?
Joey!
Tommy?
Oh, God.
He's bleeding pretty bad, Joey.
What are we gonna do?
I don't want him to die.
He's not gonna die, Vincent.
Oh, God.
Look Vincent, I need you to do
something for me, alright?
I'm gonna get him to the hospital,
but I need you to do something.
What am I saying to you, Vincent?
Listen to me! What did I say?
- I gotta do something.
- I need you to get rid of the gun.
Break it up into little pieces,
throw it in the river
and dump the car, alright Vincent?
What did I just say?
Break it into pieces
and throw it in the river.
And dump the car, Vincent.
Vincent, I need you to get it together.
I can't, I'm sorry, Joey...
Come on, Tommy.
Joey, don't let him die!
He's not gonna die, Vincent!
Look at me!
Tommy,I'm not... Look at me!
I'm not going anywhere. Alright?
I'm right here.
Don't leave me, Joey.
Stay awake.
No, no!
Don't leave me, Joey!
I'm right here, Tommy!
Don't you let him die!
We have this. Please.
Tommy, I'm right here!
It had been years since
I've been on that corner.
But as the bus pulled away,
I'd felt like i never left.
Horvath and Thornton would have
given me the money
to live anywhere.
But I went home,
to aunt Tina's.
I was worried about Vincent.
Come here.
You know Joey don't live here no more.
He's got a condo over on Market.
- Where are they now?
- Probably at the club.
Vincent's the manager.
Vincent's working for Joey?
What happened to steamfitters?
He quit.
Didn't he tell you?
When did he do that?
About a year ago.
You like my new shoes?
Vincent got them for me.
He's a good boy, that Vincent.
I'm so glad you're home, Tommy.
We need you around here.
...Stinger missiles, C4,
RPG's, everything.
What's an RPG?
Are you a complete fucking nitwit?
I just told you 3 minutes
ago what an RPG is.
- I forgot.
- Rocket propelled grenade.
RPG - tattoo it on your
fucking forehead.
- Hi, Joey.
- Hi, Brandy. How you're doing?
- You've got a minute for me?
- Yeah, absolutely. Come in.
I'm telling you, this guy is like a
fucking weapon supermarket.
Can I stab you?
Cops found Willy's car
down by the river.
Yeah? What did they say?
Nothing.
They asked me if I knew anything
and they gave me back the car.
- Have a drink.
- I'm good.
Have a drink.
I need to know, Joey.
I need to know if Willy's dead.
I'm not gonna do anything.
I'm not gonna go crazy,
I just need to know
so that I can move on.
What makes you think I
know anything, Brandy?
Don't fuck with me, Joey.
You know I've got
the kid to think of.
Joey, for three weeks
it's like I'm living in mud.
I can't do anything,
I can't get out of bed
in the morning.
I know you for a long time,
and you need to
understand something.
Whatever I tell you,
I would only be guessing.
Ok. He's dead?
Why?
Why would somebody do that?
What did he do?
I don't know.
Ok, I want whoever did it
dead or in jail.
I want their kids to be
without their father.
I wanna know who did it.
I can't help you there, Brandy.
Fine, I'll find out
by myself.
- Settle down.
- Fuck you! Settle down.
Okay, fine.
Go. Go.
But where?
What are you gonna do?
You're gonna go to the cops?
When was the last time they helped
anybody from 10th and Wolf?
So you can't do that,
so what - you're gonna
go after whoever done
this yourself?
Then you die and your
kid ends up
in some foster home.
You want that?
I've got a seven year old kid
I can't feed no more.
What am I gonna do?
It's alright.
You want a job?
What?
A job. You want a job?
I'm not much of a dancer.
You think I'd put you up
on one of those stages?
No, we're looking for a bartender.
I don't know how to
bartend either.
Well good. That means you
don't know how to steal yet.
Vincent, come here.
Meet me in the back.
Brandy is your new bartender.
Stupid me. I didn't even
know I needed one.
- How you've beenBrandy?
- Good, Vin. Thanks.
Give her the good shifts and
give her a grand up front.
- Okay?
- Yeah.
And forget about that other
stuff that we talked about.
That way nobody wins.
I gotta get this.
Yeah, hallo?
Am I speaking with
Joseph Marcucci?
Yeah, you got him.
Who is this?
The Joseph Marcucci who resides
at The Dorchester, 226 Market Square?
Who is this?
My name is Simon Liebowitz, sir, and
I work for the Board of Health.
The Board of Health?
Who is this?
Simon Liebowitz.
Yeah, I heard you the first time.
What the fuck do you want?
There's no need to be
rude, Mr. Marcucci.
Tell me about the rats.
Rats?
Okay, you don't know
about the rats.
You couldn't have missed them.
What fucking rats?
The condominium where you
reside has been quarantined
due to an outbreak of rats.
- Rats?
- Yes.
Yes. Big, fat, stinky rats
concentrated in your
bedroom area.
You need to be more careful who
you sleep with, Mr. Marcucci.
Who the fuck is this?
Leibowitz!
Simon Leibowitz!
Vincent, get out here!
We've got a big,
fat, fucking rat.
He still has this jacket.
Come here.
They told us we were going in there
to get a monster
who has killed thousands
of his own people.
And just before we
got the son of a bitch...
- They make a deal?
- They make a deal.
Jesus.
They lied to us and people died.
A lot of their guys and some of ours.
Some of my buddies.
So I got drunk that night
and beat the shit out of an MP
and I stole the colonel's jeep
and I went after Saddam myself.
Get out of here.
I swear to God.
And I'd have got him too,
If I didn't drive 30 miles
in the wrong direction.
Jeep ran out of gas just
outside Kuwait City.
That's my Tommy right there.
For friends and family.
It's good to see you, Tommy.
I just got the call.
Who's this?
It's my brother Tommy.
How you're doing?
Army guy.
Actually it's the marines.
There's a little bit of difference.
One is pussies,
one is not.
Hey, give us a minute, will you?
What you gotta be a jerk for?
Who called?
Rocco.
They want to arrange a meet.
Why don't I save us
both a little time
and I can tell you to go fuck yourself...
Reggio, Joey.
They wanna meet.
Rocco is the one who set Manny up.
Hey, I think we should meet.
Well...
Hold up, guys.
Stay there, Rocco.
- Did you invite them in here?
- A talk, Joey. A talk.
Who's the grease ball ?
That's Reggio's nephew.
Take it easy.
Fuck these ginzo motherfuckers.
Tell your uncle I refuse to talk
with any grease ball,
moustached, foreign motherfucker.
Do you want me to say it again?
I'll say it again.
Rocco?
Let me ask you something.
How does it feel to betray
a life-long friend?
I mean, how does your life
like fucking the Judas?
I'm just wondering.
Tell your uncle:
I see him, I put a knife in his kidney.
Drop by anytime, guys.
Monday scumbag nights.
Drinks are half price.
Bring a friend, you know?
- What's the matter with you?
They were ready to share, you asshole.
We can make a lot of money with Reggio.
You better get off your
high fucking horse
because if there's an all-out war
here's a bulletin - they win.
They're looking to play this thing smart.
Why don't we?
I wish there was something I didn't know.
You're a fucking asshole,
you know that?
- Hello?
- It's me. Give me Horvath.
What?
You dangled Joey
out there to hook me
but you helped Vincent
back in case you needed
to twist the screws, didn't you?
Everybody needs a whole card.
I can't do this.
- I want out.
- Nah.
It's too late for that.
No, I want out.
I can't do this.
- Deal's off.
- Hold on.
Deal's off.
Hold on a second.
I just want you to listen
to something, alright?
"- Is it 500? How's 500?
- It's un-negotiable."
"Come on Vincent, I can't. I can't."
"Thousand a week, Sid."
"That's the number Joey gave you,
that's what you gotta pay."
"Otherwise I'll come back with a
hammer and drive nails in your head."
"And plus we gotta
wreck the joint, too."
Alright, that's enough.
It's called extortion.
And your little brother Vincent
is in it up to his eyeballs
thanks to your cousin Joey.
Family.
I don't give a damn
about those cheap thugs.
I want Reggio.
If I'm gonna get him,
I need it on tape.
You gotta wear a wire.
Wire?
You didn't say anything
about wearing a wire.
I'm saying it now!
You're gonna wear a wire.
Look, you'd better straighten
out your loyalties, tough guy.
Who's it gonna be?
Reggio or your brother Vincent?
I want a guarantee Vincent walks
and you go easy on Joey.
Your guarantee is my word.
We're going to lunch.
Joey has to meet Reggio
and you gotta get yourself in there.
Wear the wire, and we'll
stick to our end of the bargain.
We know Reggio is setting up a heroin pipeline
coming from the Golden Triangle through Sicily.
We need to know how it's arriving and how the distribution is.
That's a microrecorder.
You tape it underneath your privates.
Chances are they search
you - they won't look there.
Just make sure your
dick faces whoever is talking
and do everything you can
to keep them out of areas with noise.
Yeah.
What's with the door locked?
Some marine thing or something?
I was taking a nap.
Dinner's over.
What's going on with her and Joey?
He don't come by, he don't call.
Her and Manny was like
a whole two years
after uncle Joey died.
I take care of her, make sure she's
got enough money and all of that.
You wanna hear something?
I've got around 128,216 dollars in the bank.
You picked the right time to come home.
What?
How long have you been working for Joey?
I don't wanna hear...
- You could have wrote me.
- Tommy, I don't wanna hear it.
It's everything we said
we didn't want, Vincent.
No, it's everything YOU said.
And then you said goodbye and
ran off to join the marines.
- What did you fucking do, Tommy?
- Hey, watch your mouth.
Let me bust my ass 8 hours a day
for a lousy 300 dollars a week.
Sorry Tommy, no can do.
You're in over your head.
- Stop it!
- You stop it!
Yeah.
What? Now?
Tell them you're eating now.
I'm eating now.
I gotta go.
Alright, I'll go with you.
I'm not a fucking baby!
He didn't even call for you.
I'm sorry, I didn't mean to curse.
Will you save me a plate?
I'll be back later.
Smile, please.
Tommy, I'm sorry.
Get those puppies shiny.
Junior has a thing about clean glasses.
Who's Junior?
He owns the drive with Joey
stay as far the fuck away from him
as humanly fucking possible.
Say I said that and I'll call you a liar,
make sure your ass is canned.
Yeah, I've got it asshole!
Give me a Crown Royal on the rocks.
Vincent's brother Tommy, right?
Yeah.
Army?
The marines.
Brandy Brenner.
You and me and Joey were in the
7th and 8th grade together at Sacred Heart.
Yeah. How's it going?
Wow. You're really a bad liar...
- Is that right?
- Big time.
Sorry?
- Rock'n'roll. You're new here?
- Yeah.
It's a shot of rockin' rye
and a bottle of rolling rock.
Rock and Roll.
Yeah.
Learn something new every day, huh?
Hey that's a nice haircut.
Where did you get it, the army?
Marines.
Well Semper Fi, motherfucker.
Hey, Semper Fi.
Always faithful.
Yeah, that's what it means.
Semper fucking Fi!
9.50 for the drinks.
Are you gonna jump up on the pole?
Bartenders don't dance.
Are you gonna show me your tits?
It's 9.50.
I'm sorry, maybe one of
us is in the wrong place.
Hey, buddy.
What's the problem?
You got any medals?
- Hey.
- It's alright.
Let me ask you something.
We send our boys over there,
they kill a bunch of Arabs
that don't mean anything to us
and then we pick up and leave
before we take out the
scumbag we went in there for.
- Now what's that about?
- I don't know.
Like a thief in the night
they take away our heart and our soul.
We give them the best that we've got.
My kids are dead,
and Saddam is still alive.
I don't...
understand...
Yeah, yeah.
I was just kidding about the dancing.
You're new, so
I just tried to make you feel at home.
Keep the change.
I've got to talk to you for two minutes.
You got it?
- Can i kill ya?
- Very funny.
You're a very, very funny guy.
Listen, listen...
Listen to me.
What's your Sunday look like?
What? After church?
I've got a guy who wants to sell us a tank.
- A what?
- A tank.
- A tank?
- Yeah, big fucking tank.
I don't think so, Jimmy.
Where will we park it?
- I don't know. Behind the club?
- No, I don't think so.
Thanks for thinking
about things, though.
It's a good idea, no? Joe?
Hey, how you're doing?
You see those titties?
I paid for those titties.
Do you know how much doe
that brings in for me?
- You paid for those titties?
- Yeah.
Three times over.
I'm thinking we should
take this meeting, Joey.
We can't take on the
whole fucking Mafia.
What Mafia?
Vincent, the mafia in this city is gone.
They're all dead or in jail.
Do you know what elmatta means?
It means "How much
time do I get off my sentence?"
Get out of here!
Take care of that.
Get off the stage!
Jesus fucking Christ, Jimmy!
How many times have I gotta tell ya?
No beating up the customers.
- I ain't doing nothing.
- He's crazy.
Should've left him out of it, Joey.
I don't speak for Vincent.
You let me down, Joey.
I let you down?
Well I guess it's not the first time.
Did you tell me to go home that night?
Did you tell me to go home?
You didn't shoot me, Joey.
You saved me.
You still left.
So, we're taking the meeting,
or commiting suicide?
Would you shut up?
No, Vincent, I mean really...
You should take the meeting.
Really? Why is that?
What's this Reggio need from you?
They need me to keep quiet.
After they killed Manny,
they thought the transition
would go smooth, but
they didn't bank on us.
They didn't bank on me.
This ain't Palermo, this is my city.
They can't afford a war,
but this is what they'll get, Tommy.
It's stupid.
Stupid.
You know what they need.
That's a good piece of intelligence.
But it's only worth
what you make of it.
You let them think they're using you,
you get next to Reggio,
you be a good soldier,
when the time is right you
cut the head off. No war.
Nobody dies for Reggio.
That's what I've been
trying to tell him the whole time.
Yeah, but you couldn't because you
didn't graduate from 5th grade.
Shut up.
I was busting your balls.
You know, I know you love
him more than me.
What is that? Don't say that.
No, I know that.
If you were in a dark alley,
you'd rather have him there, not me.
It's alright.
There's nothing I can do about it.
I just want you all to know
that the world could crumble
and I would die
trying to be in that alley with you all.
You're drunk, Vincent.
Maybe I'm a little drunk.
I'm still here
waiting to be in that alley.
I'm sorry.
God, you're beautiful.
I'm sorry, you've got to excuse me,
I've got to take a piss.
I'm sorry - a leak.
Tell him I said
thanks for everything.
You're welcome.
Could you get me another drink?
She's off duty.
Drink mine.
I'll see you tomorrow.
She's a good looking girl.
Yeah, she's a good looking girl.
I'm Junior, who are you?
I'm Brandy, I started tonight.
Dancing?
Bartending.
It's a nice car. Is this yours?
Yeah.
It's in my spot.
Sorry.
You're parking in the back
with the rest of the girls.
- Got me?
- Yeah.
You're a real fucking
looker, you know that?
What brought you here, Brandy?
I'm a friend of Joey's.
I'm gonna try parking in the back next time.
Brandy, could you do me a favor?
Tommy doesn't have a car. I was wondering
if you can give him a ride down to the diner?
- Yeah, sure. Yeah.
- Thanks.
- See you down there.
- Are you coming?
Yeah, I'll meet you there.
- She's okay.
- Yeah, that's what you said about Willy.
Willy's okay.
Turns out Willy was a rat.
Forgive me if I question your judgement.
Yeah, but you didn't know he
was a rat until after you killed him.
That somehow makes a difference?
How do you know she's not a rat too
like her scumbag husband?
You go near her, I'll cut off
your other leg, Junior.
How are we doing, Junior?
- We're doing great, Joe.
- Good.
It's bad enough I made
the poor girl a widow,
I don't want to make
the kid an orphan too.
Yeah.
So how long is cousin Tom here for?
Tommy's okay.
Is there anybody
around here not okay?
That's what I'd like to know.
Just stay away from Brandy.
Thanks.
Are you hungry?
No, I gotta get home to my kid.
My neighbor's watching him.
Out to the left, three seats back.
Where you sat in the 8th grade.
Used to piss me off because
you sat by the window, and I didn't.
You should know how cold it was
by the window in the winter.
What did you say to that guy?
The guy in the bar.
I told him the best thing
a marine could hope for
is to die for his buddies.
That's probably what happened to his son.
Is that true?
That's what they told us.
How was it over there in Kuwait?
It was hot and sandy.
It's the desert, right?
Who knew.
I saw the three of you in there
the night Joey's father was killed.
You and Vincent and Joey.
It was a fight.
You looked like the three musketeers.
The only thing missing were
the big swords and the costumes
and stuff.
That was the night I told
Willy I was pregnant.
He's gone, you know?
Yeah.
It's good to see you.
Hallo?
Joey?
Rise and shine, buddy boy,
we're taking the meet.
Start this thing all over again,
me, you and Vincent.
Ten minutes, don't be late.
Back it up. Guys, we're
coming through here.
- Alex, are we good?
- Yeah.
I've got one leg and
I'm here on time.
They take this kind of thing as an insult.
That's what it was meant for.
Nice suit. Italian?
Hey, Smiley, how you're doing?
Buon giorno, Giuseppe.
Joey, my name is Joey.
Scusa.
Capisci Siciliano?
No, I speak English.
I speak American.
Me too. I'm from Carnasi.
I don't give a shit where you come from.
No. We're getting off to a bad start here.
Either you tell me what's on your mind
or I'm gonna go buy myself a rack of lamb
and me and my friends are gonna
have ourselves a little barbecue.
Giuseppe, we talk like men, no?
Not like a bulldog in the gutter.
The bulldog - very ugly.
So you shoot me in the head,
than Sipio shoot you in the head.
And what do you get?
We've got a big headache.
That's funny.
- Ain't that funny?
- Yeah, it's funny.
I make you laugh.
Yeah, a laugh.
That's good.
So let's talk business.
Hey, one thing.
This Rocco betrayed his friend.
I don't work with someone like that.
Either he goes or I go.
You have a problem?
We'll fix it.
What the hell is that noise?
It's a meat grinder.
Everything is drowned out. What happened?
Sipio killed Rocco.
Why?
Reggio told him to.
Okay. Why?
I don't know.
He just told him to shoot him?
Yup.
And you have no idea why?
You know, I didn't ask.
That's very helpful.
You've got to get me something I can use.
Come on, do us proud, tough guy.
Thank you, Jimmy.
I've got a winner.