[ radio tuning ]
MAN ON RADIO: ...have decided
to withhold comment
pending further investigation.
Officials at NASA
released a joint statement
with the National Weather Service
this afternoon
saying they're monitoring what's
being called a celestial event
moving over the southwestern
part of the country.
No details are available
at the present time,
but they did say
that the atmosphere
would be producing
extreme weather systems
in response to increased
magnetic activity from space.
RON:
Yeah, Angel's talented.
Did you see her
in "Wick Dipper V"?
I don't think so.
Is it new?
Fairly new.
She did some fine ball work
in that.
That's nice.
And she told me she was honored
to have you as a coach.
Coach. [ chuckles ]
[ sighs ]
I think our makeup girl
has a little crush on you.
Please. This bus ride
is nauseating enough.
Oh, fuck off.
Ron's twice the man you are.
[ scoffs ]
Hey, when we get up
to the cabins,
I want to show you something
I've been working on.
You found a new way
to hold a boom.
[ laughs ]
Come on.
I'm just a sound guy
like you're just a black man.
No, I think
I'm on to something.
It's gonna revolutionize
the industry.
Viva la revolución.
[ sighs ]
Cynical bastard.
Where's your joy?
Hey, pop.
How much longer?
About 45 minutes,
give or take.
I'd like to drop you all off
and get back down
before the snowstorm hits.
[ gasps ]
Ooh, snowball fights.
The radio says
it's to be a whopper.
Biggest since 1938.
Yeah, what were you --
like, 60 then?
Come on.
Leave the guy alone.
Yeah, I was talking to you.
[ chuckles ]
Anyone know
when we're getting paid?
Same as always, hon --
Half up front
and half when we wrap.
Jim said there will be checks
when we arrive.
Thank God.
I could really use
that 6 grand.
$6,000?
She's making $6,000?
What has she done?
Maybe 100, 150 movies?
She's just a beginner.
Oh.
That is so unfair.
JIM:
Yeah, we're almost there.
What?
We're doing it here because
I want to get this thing done
without all the agents
and boyfriends
looking over my shoulder
every fucking minute.
Don't worry.
We'll get it made.
I said, "we'll get it mad--"
Hello? Fuck.
Jack?
End of the line.
Get me
to a shower immediately.
Ooh,
it's so pretty here.
ROCK: That's everything.
Thanks, pal.
Benjamin Franklin?
Well, thank you.
So, you folks
are making a picture, eh?
Yeah.
Oh, I sure do love the movies.
Is it a thriller?
Yeah, thrills aplenty.
Wait till I tell mother.
[ laughs ]
Listen, now,
I'll never hear the end of it
if I don't get
the details right.
Mind me asking?
By all means.
Your cock is 9 inches.
That right?
9 3/4.
Oh!
I owe her $10.
I'm sorry.
Well, no harm done.
I'll be back to pick you all up
on Sunday...
unless, of course,
the roads are snowed in,
In which case, you'll have to
wait a day or two till it melts.
But there's plenty of food
in there in the pantry.
Oh, and I started the generator
before I came
and picked you folks up,
so, uh, your rooms should be
nice and toasty by now.
LANCE: Hey, pops.
Are we the only ones
on the mountain?
Uh, nope.
There's a feller that lives
over on the other side.
Uh, name's Mohtz.
Comes down for supplies
and whatnot every few months.
Pretty much keeps to himself.
He, uh [sighs]
He's been there ever since
he came back from Vietnam.
- Mm.
What's that?
Oh, uh, that's
an old communications tower.
Now, this whole mountain was
used by the army as a lookout
after Pearl Harbor...
making sure
no japs come a-calling.
Okay, people,
grab a cabin and pretty up.
I want to do Ron and Wanda's
first scene before dinner.
We're setting up
in the main cabin.
Good luck, folks.
Stay warm.
Hey, maybe we can roast
some marshmallows -- uh!
Hey!
ROCK:
Roast that, nerd boy.
Oh!
Ooh!
Oh, excuse me.
I have the luggage.
Um, is there anything else
that you need, Mr. Jeremy?
Oh, no, thank you, uh...
Laura.
Laura. I'm sorry.
So many names over the years,
you know.
Historic years.
Yeah, some would say
prehistoric.
That's just awful.
Raw talent like yours
is ageless.
And anyone
who says otherwise --
They can
just shut the hell up.
Why, thank you, Laura.
So, uh, how long have you been
working in hard-Core?
A few years.
I used to do makeup
for the Olsen twins,
and one of them told me
about a film
called "Lord of the Cock Rings"
that needed a makeup person.....
Gilligan...
You and the Skipper here
take the bunks.
Sure thing.
I don't mind
taking the top.
RON: Appreciate it.
Ahh!
Hey, you guys think Wanda
is as cute as I do?
I don't know.
I'm kind of digging her.
She's a sweet kid.
You think
she'd go out with me?
Dude.
She's gonna blow you
in an hour and a half...
and me.
It's totally different.
MAN ON RADIO:
It is 10 minutes after the hour,
and they still don't know
what that thing is in the sky,
so if I were you,
I'd stay indoors, folks.
Z97 FM.
[ door opens ]
[ chuckles ]
Your room
looks just like mine.
Kind of cozy, huh?
This is just like camp.
What's that?
Lidocaine.
Stubble always hurts
when I'm getting my pussy eaten.
So I spray it on
right before a scene.
Now,
that's using your noodle.
Thanks.
But I'm sure you have some
of your own tricks of the trade.
Yeah.
I've got a great one.
So, if I'm doing this video
where I have to lick
a guy's asshole,
I hit myself in the head
with a piece of wood
five times really hard
right there.
What does that do?
It disables
the olfactory bulb
in my limbic system.
I can't smell anything
for 12 straight hours.
Mm-hmm.
So I ask the director
to make sure
all my ass-licking scenes
are in the same day.
Cool.
It works.
[ chuckles ]
[ knock on door ]
Come in.
[ shivering ]
Hey. Hey.
Okay,
what's the matter?
Been put out to pasture, Ron.
[ chuckles ]
What are you talking about?
I never should have come here.
I mean, I don't know
what I was thinking.
I guess I was hoping maybe
I could fill in for somebody,
or maybe they'd add a scene
just because...
Because I was here.
[ sighs ]
Pretty deluded, huh?
Not at all.
[ sighs ]
I'm the worst kind of diva --
an out-of-work one.
Truth is, I don't belong
in hard-core anymore.
You know, there's no room
for a woman my age.
Do you remember the first film
we ever did together?
Um...
"Women in Love," 1979.
I played your fiancée.
Right.
28 years later,
I'm here to tell you
that the years have made you
only more beautiful.
Right.
What you're lacking
is confidence,
and that is a shame.
Ronny, do you know how tough
it is to be confident
when half the girls on the set
call you mom?
That shouldn't matter.
How you feel --
that's what matters.
Look at me.
I don't look like a porn star,
except for my...cock.
But I play the fool,
and I get the joke.
I'm in on it.
And that makes it kind of hip.
And I try to bring a
different character into
every role that I play,
And that gives me confidence.
But I can't suck
my own dick anymore.
Oh, sweetie, I'm sorry.
With the added weight
and the back pains,
all I can do is kiss the tip.
[ both laugh ]
That's more like it.
Let me tell you something,
Veronica.
You have
something really special
that I have found
very hard to resist.
Thanks, Ronny.
You know, I do wish
Jim would put me in the movie.
I think I've got
a few surprises left.
What are you waiting for?
Why don't you go talk to him?
I guess maybe
he just needs to be persuaded.
Maybe he needs
your secret weapon.
Maybe I'll show him.
Attagirl.
Remember,
you are a porn star.
Show him what porn stars
are made of.
[ sighs ]
Thank you, Ronny.
[ wind howling ]
[ clears throat ]
Hey, there, coach.
Shouldn't you be running lines
with Wanda or something?
She knows her lines.
I know her lines.
Don't start with me, Veronica.
We've been through this.
Yeah, I know.
We've talked and talked.
But I just don't think talking
is getting us anywhere.
Do you?
Huh?
[ chuckles ]
Oh.
Whatever.
I've fucked them all.
But if you think you can make
a case, the floor is yours.
I prefer the desk.
Come on.
Give it to me.
[ gasps ]
Oh.
Oh. That's it.
Hold it right there.
What?
Oh.
Oh, what are you doing?
Oh, what I was trained to do,
what I was born to do.
But how? We're not even moving.
You're massaging.
They're called kegels, jimbo --
muscles in the vagina.
Every woman has them,
but I know how to move them.
Ah, ah, ah.
Like a concert pianist
moving their fingers.
You like it, don't you?
Yeah, it's good.
Oh, God damn. I'm gonna shoot.
I'm gonna shoot.
No, you're not.
What?!
Let it go.
I'm gonna cream.
No. Not till you put me
in the movie.
Oh, I can't handle this.
Please, I'm ready. Please.
Put me in the movie.
[ grunting ]
Okay, you're in.
You're in the movie.
First scene?
Okay, you're in.
Please.
Ahhhh.
[ laughs ]
[ sighs ]
See you on set.
Points.
JIM:
We're going in 20 minutes.
Lance, Rock,
I need you in makeup.
Laura is set up in her cabin.
Jonah,
you almost ready?
Almost.
Hey, Poindexter.
I'm paying you to hold the boom,
not play video games.
Put your toys away.
Jawohl, herr director.
What's that you working on
anyway?
Ah.
Program I designed.
Nothing special,
Except that it might change
the world as we know it.
Well, what's it do?
Ah.
"what's it do?" he asks.
Sit down, sit down.
I think you're gonna like this.
This is
a neuro-tactile simulator.
A what?
It's a neuro-tact--
It's a doohickey.
And so, now all you have to do
is answer one simple question.
Shoot.
If you could fuck anyone
in any orifice,
who would it be,
and how would you do it?
Oh, that's easy.
Anna Nicole Smith's tits
when they were alive.
Ah. No, see,
I need an orifice.
Paris Hilton in the mouth.
Paris Hilton.
Paris...Hilton.
Now, I'll need you to put
your big buddy inside that thing
before I run the program.
Hold on there, partner.
I don't want to fuck
with my livelihood.
You do fuck
with your livelihood.
T.J.:
It's perfectly safe.
It's been tested
many, many times.
Well...
And cleaned.
Okay.
[ whirring ]
Oh!
Holy shit!
Oh, this is great.
Ahh. Ah, so, this
is what it would feel like.
Pretty good, huh?
Hold on a second,
Einstein.
You expect us to believe
he's fucking Paris Hilton.
In the mouth.
If you want her in the ass,
I have to change the settings
and pick up some brownie mix.
Oh, not yet.
[ sighs ]
T.J.:
It's the real thing, boys.
See, I've got 2,000 celebrities
in my database.
I organized the data
consisting of three-dimensional
measurements, fluid content,
skin tone, and muscle strength,
all of which is available
on the internet,
and then I wrote a program
to send the information
to that thing,
which is nothing more than
a bunch of moving sponges,
mineral oil,
and an adjustable aperture.
So, for all intents
and purposes...
I'm fucking Paris Hilton.
In the mouth.
[ owl hooting ]
JIM: Let's do it again,
for christ sakes.
"Wet Dream Girls" scene one,
take five.
And...action.
VERONICA: So...
Are you gonna be
our new manager?
It looks that way, yes.
In the meantime,
may I audition your pussy?
Okay.
Yeah.
[ laughing ]
Hey, hey, hey, hey.
Uh, hold on.
Hold on.
Hold on a second.
Just wait. Wait.
Damn it.
Hey, old man, what the fuck
is wrong with you?
I just need
about maybe 20 minutes.
I need a little bit of air,
that's all.
Are you okay, Ron?
Yeah, yeah.
I'm fine, I'm fine.
Okay, that's lunch.
Back in 20.
Ron, get your shit together.
This movie's getting made
with or without you.
[ sighs ]
[ owl hooting ]
You all right?
I miss the good old days,
Jonah.
You know, the sets,
the lights,
when a script had
an actual story line
and wasn't
some fuck-film knockoff
of whatever
the current hit was.
You weren't moved
by "Schindler's Fist"?
We were given actual trailers
to hang out in.
Is that right?
We were treated like stars.
Hell, we were stars.
Now I feel like some schmuck
caught on tape
in some dumb-ass reality show.
Well, back to the grind,
as it were.
Yep.
Tell Jim I'm gonna be
in the truck getting
his filters, will you?
All right.
- All right.
[ urinating ]
Hey, Jonah!
Shooting star.
All right, ready to go?
Yeah.
As ready as I'll ever be.
I thought so, too,
But if it smells bad,
it's probably not cancer.
Okay, let's do this before the
next fucking century, please.
Ron, are you with us now?
Yeah.
I feel a lot better.
Let's go.
That's more like it.
Jonah?
Okay.
Ready.
Okay, places...And roll --
T.J.: Hold on.
I hear wind.
Good for you.
Roll tape.
Speed.
And...action.
[ moaning ]
Yeah.
Oh, yeah.
[ laughs ]
ooh.
Yeah.
Oh, God.
You're gonna pass this audition
with flying colors,
you know that?
Yeah.
Ohh.
Do you like it?
Hmm?
JIM: Okay, Ron, Veronica,
doggy style.
Jonah, let's get a two-shot
from in front of her.
Oh, that's it.
Yeah, fuck me from behind.
I can't wait to.
I'm gonna roll you
like a carpet,
ride you like a Harley, and
flip you like a cheese omelet.
You sweet talker, you.
Now, what did Lee strasberg
used to say?
Breath,
character, focus.
Breathe, yeah.
- You ready?
How long is it gonna take
to relight?
Ready.
Okay, Ron,
take off your sweater.
RON:
I'm not wearing a sweater.
Okay, and action.
Oh, yeah.
You like that?
Keep going.
That's it.
Oh. Oh, you're gonna pass
this audition.
You're the best yet.
Yes. Fuck me.
- That's it, Honey.
Oh, baby.
Yeah.
Great. Great.
- Yeah, fuck me.
Yeah.
Do I get the job, huh?
Oh.
Great.
[ grunting ]
Careful, tiger.
Oh! Oh!
Ooh.
[ grunting continues ]
Something's wrong
with Ronny!
Oh!
Fuck!
What is it, Jonah?
Is she okay?
Oh, she's hemorrhaging badly.
Well, do something.
We're losing time.
Check her purse.
Maybe there's a tampon in there.
Oh, this is just perfect!
God damn it, I can't believe
this is happening to me.
Shut the fuck up, will you?
There you go.
We're gonna need
a bigger tampon.
Fuck.
Hurry, T.J.
All right,
that should hold it.
Let's put her on the couch.
W-where's Ron?
Over there.
Holy shit.
What the hell?
Correct me if I'm wrong,
but he's missing his dick.
[ panting ]
You know what I'm saying?
I don't see his dick.
What the fuck did you just say?
Ron, can you hear me.
It's cold.
Get a blanket.
There you go.
Hang in there.
Hey, Jonah, remember when
I fucked that girl that time?
I don't understand.
Where the fuck is his dick?
How the hell should I know?
Well, it just didn't get up
and walk away.
T.J.:
Actually, it did.
Camera's been rolling
all this time.
I checked the playback.
Now, watch Ron.
See how he's trying to get
our attention?
He had a pretty good reason.
Look.
Look at his dick.
Okay, well,
what about her?
The bleeding's stopped.
She's just in shock.
Well, did you check her snatch?
Maybe it's gone, too.
How the fuck
is a snatch gonna run away?
Well, pardon me, but I'm
still trying to understand
how a dick did it,
because I didn't think
that they could!
I wonder where it went.
ANGEL: Ohh. Yeah.
Oh, so good.
Oh, yes.
Oh!
Give it to me.
Hmm?
Oh.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, yeah.
Slap that ass.
Oh, yeah.
Give it to me.
Fuck me.
Shit.
[ sighs ]
Harder.
Fuck me harder.
Give it to me, baby.
Yeah.
Just like that.
Fuck me.
Fuck me harder.
[ sniffs ]
[ screams ]
[ Angel gagging, clattering ]
Angel, I'm trying to do
my homework.
Could you please rehearse
somewhere else?
[ sighs ]
[ gagging,
clattering continues ]
Oh.
Gosh. Okay.
It's just
that I've got a midterm.
[ gagging continues, slurping ]
[ gasps ]
Gin!
- Shit.
That's three in a row.
Yeah, thanks.
I didn't realize that.
[ crying ]
Don't you think
Ron has the cutest mustache?
[ door opens ]
There's a dick
in Angel's mouth!
Yeah?
[ panting ]
No, no, you don't under--
It's not attached
to anyone!
[ door closes ]
[ door opens ]
Oh, I-I'm sorry.
I was just putting on my...
Oh, ahh.
Oh, oh.
Oh, yeah.
[ moaning ]
[ gasps ]
Holy shit.
Oh, my God.
Jesus!
Now, that's what I call
giving head.
You insensitive creep!
Come on, man.
Okay, okay.
Keep your panties on.
You're saying
a disembodied dick did this?
Do you think
I'd make that up?
What should we do?
We got to do something
with this body.
There's a dumpster out back.
He's a human being,
not a fucking pizza box.
We could pack him in the snow
Until we can get an ambulance
up here.
Now, how do you propose
we do that?
There are no phone lines
up here,
And my cell
doesn't get a signal.
It doesn't matter.
No one's coming up and down
this mountain any time soon.
Not in this storm.
We'll pack him in the snow
until it blows over.
Come on.
- Jonah, I, uh...
I can't touch dead bodies.
I'm about a minute away
from passing out as it is.
I didn't even like the guy.
Fine.
Take him around the side.
I don't want to be stepping
on him.
[ Wanda crying ]
You can't just leave.
- Watch me.
You'll never make it
down the mountain.
I'll take my chance
with the mountain.
I won't take my chances
with a killer dick.
Coward!
[ engine turns over ]
You got to be
fucking kidding me.
Somebody help here.
- Oh, my God.
Oh, my God.
- Help.
[ speaking indistinctly ]
We need some help.
She's dead. A dick went through
the back of her head.
There's a hole in it.
She's dead, Angel's dead.
Shut up. Shut up.
Now, what happened?
I know you're gonna think
I'm crazy.
I just saw a disembodied dick
in Angel's mouth.
It was choking her,
and it killed her.
It went through her head.
The dick went through her head.
You should have seen
the size of the hole. The
thing's got to be huge.
Okay, let's just calm down
a bit. Now, where's rock?
He left in your "Z."
Motherfuck!
Hey, what about
the makeup girl?
Uh, Linda...Lorna --
uh, Laura.
LANCE: She was with us,
but I don't know.
Hey.
Are you okay?
I'm fine.
Why?
What happened to Veronica?
Nothing.
She's just sleeping.
Is she dead?
What happened?
Would you just stop it?
It's --
T.J., what's going on here?
[ horn honking ]
Nothing is.
Hey, that's my "Z."
[ honking continues ]
[ growling ]
Jonah.
- No!
Jonah's out there.
Remember?
Fuck Jonah.
He's probably already dead.
It's the dick.
The only dick I see is you.
Lance!
Oh, great.
Fuck me?!
Fuck you.
I should throw your sorry ass
out there.
I'm sorry.
I -- I didn't mean to...
[ rhythmic pounding on door ]
LANCE: Holy shit.
That's the dick.
[ pounding continues ]
Wait a minute.
S...
O...
S.
You telling me
it knows Morse Code?
If it does,
I'm ready for death,
But I think
somebody's out there.
WANDA: Who is he?
Look at his jacket.
I'm assuming
this is our neighbor
from the other side
of the mountain -- Mohtz.
Jesus, he must have walked
all the way here.
It's amazing
he's not dead.
He's close.
Get him to a chair.
This is insane.
Even if he is this guy,
look at him.
He's probably
some Vietnam lunatic.
What do you want us to do,
huh?
Send him home
with a goody bag?
Don't we have enough shit
to deal with?
Besides, we don't have
enough food for him.
Oh,
there's plenty...
Especially now
that we lost Angel and Rock.
Wait.
We're
missing somebody.
Where's Ron?
I want to get off this mountain
as much as you do, okay?
But this blizzard
is forcing us to stay here.
So, why can't
we just continue working and --
Working?!
You're out of your fucking mind.
Hey, 19-year-old,
I don't care how hung you are.
If you talk to me like that
again,
you've made
your last fuck film.
Look, he's right.
The picture is
not our priority right now.
Hey, speak for yourself.
If I don't get
this film made,
I'm gonna lose
some limbs here.
Man, if you don't shut up,
you're gonna lose them
a lot sooner.
What about
the communications tower?
Maybe we can go over there
and radio for help.
In this weather?
No, it's way too far.
Well, what's-his-face made
it from the other side
of the mountain.
I think
it's stopped snowing.
Yeah, but the
temperature's dropped,
what, 20 degrees since then.
It's suicide,
but be my guest.
What are you gonna do
about Ron's dick?
I mean, are we safe in here?
Guess we'll find out.
What does it want?
Why don't you ask it?
Maybe it talks, too.
You know, when I went to
the truck to get those filters,
I saw something in the sky.
Ron saw it, too.
It's almost like
a shooting star.
And I saw a really bright light
just outside that door.
I could see it from my cabin,
but I just thought
it was one of yours.
I don't have lights
that bright.
What did Ron say about it?
Nothing, but
he was acting kind of strange
when I got back from the truck.
Why?
Maybe nothing.
Maybe everything.
I have a theory.
It's a little way-out.
But I saw a dick scurry
out of a tail pipe today,
so I'm willing to consider
just about everything.
Well, go on.
The shooting star,
the bright light,
Ron acts weird,
and his dick takes off running.
And killing.
Mm.
Yes, I haven't forgotten that.
And killing.
What if that shooting star
was some alien life-form
that invaded Ron
and took control of his dick?
Give me a fucking break!
I don't know.
I'm just riffing here.
But it seems to be only natural
that if an alien
wanted to take over the planet,
it would need to seed it.
A dick.
Well, not just any dick.
One that had access to
as many vaginas as possible
and could penetrate them
as deeply
as someone like Ron could.
Maybe it even knows who's
capable of conceiving right now
and sees anyone who isn't
as a threat.
So, you're saying
it scouted Ron?
I don't know.
I'm tired.
But maybe it did.
Hey, Mr. "X files,"
why just the dick?
Why not all of Ron?
Women don't usually fuck dicks
that aren't attached to men.
Unless
they're battery-operated.
I don't really think it's
interested in wooing anybody.
It just wants to replicate.
And it clearly doesn't mind
using force.
To the alien, everything
but the dick is baggage.
We got to kill it.
No.
I just mean...Can't we trap it
or something?
Maybe it's just scared.
You didn't see
what that thing did to Angel.
It was horrible.
So, how are we gonna do it?
MOHTZ:
I'll kill it for you.
It's a death machine...
Smart.
You've got to outthink it.
Never saw one that big, though.
You've seen them before?
One.
Well, care to elaborate,
old-timer?
No.
Then what the hell
are you doing here?
I saw that streak of light
from my cabin on the other side.
The shooting star.
You can call it
whatever you want to, but...
...that's not what it is.
What are we doing
listening to this guy?
He probably thinks he's
in the jungle, for christ sakes.
Why don't you just shut up?
So, you know what it was?
Your man there already knows.
So it's a martian?
Sweetheart, I don't have
its mailing address or anything,
but I can tell you one thing --
it's not
from this godforsaken planet.
You said
you know how to kill it.
How?
Whatever it was,
whatever it's gonna be,
right now it's a dick.
Brilliant.
And, therefore, subject
to the physiology of one.
Bright boy.
Oh.
Of course.
It seems to kill
during an act of penetration,
meaning it's erect.
But, okay --
but what about after that?
If it's a dick, it needs
a refractory period, right?
So, what?
So that's when it's spent.
That's when it's vulnerable.
I just call it a rest period.
So, we just need to get it
to blow its load.
But then what?
Circumcise it to oblivion
with an ax.
Should have one in your shed.
How are we gonna get it
to come?
She's a porn star.
She can fuck it.
Hey!
- Fuck you!
No one's fucking it.
At least no one human.
Come again.
I'll set up
the neuro-tactile simulator.
Good.
The what?
We'll explain later.
Right now
we need to get that ax.
Someone has to go to the shed
and get it.
Choose.
There's only four.
What about him?
The man's frostbitten.
And he volunteered to kill it.
Who's gonna go first?
Hail Mary, full of Grace.
Oh, fuck that!
I'm not going out there
with that thing on the loose.
Stop calling it a thing.
It's got a name -- Ron.
It's Ron Jeremy.
Hey, weird girl, I don't care
if it's Ron McDonald.
I'm staying right here.
Give me a reason.
JIM: Okay. Okay.
Okay.
I'll give you 50 bucks
if you go out there for me.
No, thanks.
- $200? $1,000?
$1,000? $1,000.
Anyone?
Bundle up.
Fine.
If any of you think you're
working in fuck films again...
At least give me
something to protect myself.
Well, there's a shovel
out there.
That's all I had when I was
waiting for you to let me in.
MOHTZ: If I were you,
I'd hold a tight asshole.
Couldn't get any tighter.
Okay...
Whatever the fuck you are.
You want me?
Here I am.
Just going to the shed...
...to get the ax that's gonna
bobbit you back to outer space.
Yeah?
[ echoing ] Hey!
I could help you.
I produce movies.
I know a lot of women,
do some pretty kinky shit
for a little coke.
What do you say?
Ah, fuck you.
[ whirring ]
[ whirring stops ]
So, it's a trap, huh?
T.J.:
It's a simulated vagina.
They're all traps.
Nope, no issues there.
JONAH:
Lance, come here for a sec.
Hold it right there.
Think we'll make it
out of here?
Your guess
is as good as mine.
This is my first adult film.
All my friends
said not to do it.
They said I'd get aids.
I told them
everyone gets tested now.
T.J.: Jonah,
come take a look at this.
That's my light meter.
Ah.
It was your light meter.
Walk away.
[ beeping ]
Good.
Now, walk back but faster.
[ beeping ]
How about that?
Part boom guy, part MacGyver.
You made a motion sensor
out of a light meter?
It's not such a stretch
if you think about it.
I mean, what is light
but electromagnetic motion?
I just recalibrated
the sensitivity
and installed an audio
trip for the beep from
one of my microphones.
This is for the kitchen?
For the kitchen, yes.
Now we'll know if it's near.
See? No surprises.
Good job.
[ Wanda crying ]
Wanda, you okay?
[ sobbing ]
Oh, sweet.
You, my friend, are gonna get me
the fuck out of here.
It's empty.
God damn it.
[ door closes ]
What the fuck?
[ knock on door ]
[ door opens ]
Hey, Wanda.
Don't worry.
We're gonna make it.
That's more than we can say
for Angel and Ron.
Even Rock
didn't deserve to die.
Well, you haven't known him
long enough.
[ laughs ]
That's more like it.
I love your laugh.
It's like...
I don't know, like music.
Really?
This may sound
kind of stupid and all,
But, on the bus over here,
I was writing a song for you.
You were?
You want to hear it?
Yeah.
# I know
a pretty girl named Wanda #
# she's someone
that I'm awfully fond-a #
Well,
that's all I got so far.
When we get home,
safe and sound,
if it's okay with you,
I'd like to call you up
on the phone
and ask you
for a proper date.
I'd like that.
Oh. [ chuckles ]
I want to see you.
Yeah, I think I saw a flashlight
in the cabinet.
Oh, yeah, here it is.
Thanks.
Hey, there doesn't seem to be
a switch on this thing.
Well, how are you
supposed to turn it on?
I think
you probably have to suck it.
[ slashing ]
[ gasps ]
Okay.
Let's do this.
T.J., put your stuff
in the kitchen.
Mohtz, I got a chair in there
for you.
It could be a long night.
Laura...
I'm gonna need
the panties you have on.
Uh...
Okay.
Fellas.
JIM:
Sweetheart, I make porn.
I don't see what makes
your change purse so special.
You're pretty proud of yourself
there, aren't you?
Well, it might not
make millions,
but it just might save
our lives.
This will do.
How do you know
it's gonna show?
It'll show.
I'm going to watch over
the women here.
Good.
Sure looks like they need you.
Wake me up when it's over.
Where are Lance and Wanda?
I saw them
going to the bathroom together.
Hey, party time.
[ laughs ]
Fine.
Let's leave them alone.
Hey, Jonah, I don't think
I'm ready for this.
I'm feeling a little jumpy.
Yeah.
I could use a drink.
Abracadabra.
[ simulator rattling ]
# home, home on the range #
# where the... #
Where the what?
Ah, I forgot the rest of it.
Come on, man.
Don't bogart the whiskey.
T.J.: It makes sense.
What?
Why it's here,
why it chose earth.
We practically
broadcast commercials.
English.
Think of all
the satellite signals
we send out into space
on a daily basis.
Billions of them,
each one saying,
"uh, hey, folks, earth here."
Now, of all the broadcasting
that goes on on the planet,
50% of it
has got to be porn, right?
I mean,
that's probably conservative.
And of that 50%, half of it's
got to feature Ron Jeremy.
They were just looking
for a familiar face.
Well, not a face.
That tattoo there on your arm
is airborne?
182nd.
Gulf war.
Hmm.
405th infantry.
Outside Da Nang.
Whole platoon got wiped out,
but it wasn't Charlie.
You're shitting me.
Friendly fire
killed your whole platoon?
No, no, not exactly.
Uh...
[ sighs ]
One night me and the C.O.
were pulling guard duty,
and we're sharing a joint --
Thai stick.
I'm really stoned,
and all of a sudden,
we see this streak of light.
Zoom! Waaa!
And it looked like it lands
maybe, oh, about 2 klicks
northeast of camp.
So, the C.O. says,
"I'm gonna check it out."
"go ahead, cap, man."
more doobie for me, you know.
So, off he goes.
And, uh, it could have been
10 minutes or 2 hours.
I don't know.
I was stoned.
But he comes back, and
I notice he's acting weird.
But now, oh.
Oh, now, no problem,
It's just the Thai stick
kicking in.
Well, man, pretty soon
he starts jumping around
like his pants are on fire.
I'm not shitting you,
you know.
And he --
off comes his pants.
Rips them off.
He rips his skivvies off.
Now I got my C.O.
standing there in front of me
butt naked
from the waist down.
And then something happened,
man, that, uh...
boot camp
did not prepare me for.
Ahh.
This guy's pecker, his dick,
ripped itself off his body
and headed for the tent.
So, the C.O.'s
screaming like hell.
Pretty soon I can't hear him
because the screams
are now coming from the tent.
Want to know
what hell sounds like?
I think it sounds like...
30 men getting massacred
by a dick.
So, uh, I went over and hid
behind a rock for about an hour
and had to listen to my...
my whole platoon
being murdered.
And I heard one guy
get a shot off,
but then I heard him
getting killed.
So, after it stopped...
I very cautiously,
believe me,
crept into the tent to get
a radio to get some air support,
and...
I see the dick
lying there on a sleeping bag.
And it looks like
it's looking back at me.
But it looked, you know,
fucking weak, man.
And it was like in this,
uh, you know, shriveled --
what kind of period is that
you call it?
A refractory period.
Yeah, yeah.
And, you know, I could have
killed it right then,
but I was so stoned
I was afraid I'd miss.
And on the other hand, I knew
it was just a matter of time
before it would be, you know,
back in action again.
So, without taking my eyes
off of it,
I get a radio, and I have them
chopper in two Saigon whores.
So, for the next half-hour,
I'm holding my weapon
on this dick.
Now, I figured
it won't know I'm stoned,
so he won't jump me,
you know.
So, chopper arrived
just in time, thank God,
Because now the dick
was getting big and hard.
So I tell the two whores, "look,
hey, I'll do anything, man.
"I take you to the states,
anything,
if you just lie down there
and spread your legs for me."
Well I guess "States"
was the magic word,
because you never saw
two whores
take their panties off
so quick in your life.
Now, the dick
must have smelled dinner
because -- Choo! --
It makes
a beeline for the whores.
So, I watch.
And I wait.
And I watch.
Finally...finally, man,
it blew its load.
I grabbed it,
and I went outside,
and I threw it in a bunker.
God, Jesus Christ, man!
About 10 seconds later,
out runs about 15 gooks.
And I could have nailed
every one of them,
but, no,
I made a priority decision.
Threw in a grenade.
Fire in the hole!
Fa-foom!
Well, guess what.
Now it's raining dick.
Yeah, raining dick.
I crawled
into a whiskey bottle
when I got back to the States,
and I've been there
ever since.
[ keys clacking ]
[ beep ]
Okay.
This thing's ready for action.
Good.
What about you?
Well, I'm certainly drunk.
Good enough.
Hey, if this thing manages to
get out of the kitchen somehow,
the women in that room
are sitting ducks.
Jim's in there.
[ scoffs ]
Right.
Rest easy, friend.
Man and machine
are on the job.
But just in case,
seal us in from the outside.
Good luck.
[ pounding ]
[ ticking ]
[ simulator whirring ]
[ slow beeping ]
[ beeping continues ]
It moves like an inchworm.
Like a 9-inch worm.
Here we go.
Come to uma.
Come on.
[ whirring ]
When I get out of here,
I'd like to try that.
Okay.
Almost there.
Almost.
And...
Oh, shit.
No, no, no, no, no.
No, no!
- What's wrong?
It's crashing.
There's nothing I can do.
Damn it!
- Pull it out.
No, I can't do that.
Pull it out, fucker!
- No.
God damn it,
I said pull it out,
you fucking
cocksucking pussy!
Kill the fucker!
Shit, I fucking missed!
Jesus, hurry up again
before it gets...
[ growling ]
No, no, no.
We keep forgetting
it's Ron Jeremy's dick!
[ growling ]
[ gasping ]
Kill it!
It's on your neck.
I know that.
Kill it!
I can't do that.
Chop
my motherfucking head off!
Aah!
Oh, my God, somebody get me
out of here...please!
Please, Jonah, Jim, anybody.
Please, get me out of here!
Get me the fuck out of here
right now, please!
Open the goddamn the door!
What's going on?
Hurry, God damn it!
Oh, my God.
Get me the fuck out of here!
You trying to get us killed?
Back off.
[ screams ]
[ all scream ]
What's happening?
Must be the generator.
It's been working overtime.
Could be out of gas.
Where the fuck
are we gonna get gas?
We're gonna freeze to death.
I got an extra 5-gallon gas can
in my truck.
I'll do it.
Oh, you will?
When did you grow balls?
Well, someone's got to stay
and protect them.
If that thing
gets through this door,
I'm gonna be too busy
shitting in my pants.
Okay, let's go.
[ knock on door ]
T.J.: Guys?
Guys, I'm okay now.
You can open the door.
What the hell?
Seriously, guys, I'm fine.
Come on, please open the door.
I'm stuck in here.
No.
- What?
I don't think
that's T.J. talking.
Who is it?
It's that thing.
Must be...animating him
or something.
Come on, guys.
Open the door.
It's in his ass.
It's running him
from his ass.
What do you want from us?
I want you to open the door.
Who are you?
Open the door.
Fuck you.
You will not survive.
[ engine idling ]
What the hell?
Son of a bitch!
I'm gonna be sick.
[ gagging ]
[ panting ]
[ whimpers ]
[ screams ]
[ whooshing ]
Come on! Come on!
[ groans ]
[ snow crunching ]
[ gasping ]
[ laughs ]
[ cracking ]
huh?!
This isn't over.
We just need to keep warm
until the snow melts.
They know we're out here.
Someone will come get us.
Who are you
trying to convince?
No.
No, take it.
I went to boot camp in Alaska.
You learn to ignore the cold.
Boy, you know, it's really cold
when you can see the heat.
You mean your breath.
No.
Over there.
Where?
It's coming from the floor.
Hand me a flashlight.
I'll be damned.
What is it?
Must be
an underground passageway.
There's a ladder that comes
right up to the floor here.
Got to be 10 degrees warmer
down there, too.
Where does it go?
I don't know.
What did that bus driver say?
We're on an old army base,
right?
Right.
I wonder if these cabins
are connected.
And maybe...
- We could get
to the radio control tower.
I said maybe.
And even if we did,
we don't know if it still works.
But at least
we won't freeze to death
Or be sitting ducks
for that thing.
It's not a thing.
Yes, it is.
Now, listen to me.
Ron's dead.
You can go around to the side of
the cabin and see for yourself.
I know you dug him.
And that may be his dick out
there, but it's a mass murderer.
What about Veronica?
We can't just leave her here
all alone.
Get my light Meter
off the kitchen table.
Okay, we're ready.
Help me.
Grab her leg.
I got it. It's good.
I got it. Ready?
Mm-hmm.
Got her?
Yeah.
Radio tower
should be this way.
Let's go.
Hold up.
How much further?
[ grunts ]
I don't know.
Maybe 100, 200 yards.
[ beeping ]
What's that?
Maybe nothing.
Stand still.
[ rapid beeping ]
Shit.
- What?
Something's coming.
It's a rat.
Strange.
Looks kind of dead.
[ beeping continues ]
Let's go.
This has to be it.
Get her.
Come on.
Got her?
Get her up, get her up.
[ grunting ]
Let's get over here.
I got her.
[ whirring ]
All right.
Here goes nothing.
Mayday, mayday.
If anyone can hear me,
there are three of us
on top of lookout mountain.
One of us is seriously injured,
and we're stuck in the snow.
Six others are dead.
We're being stalked by a d--
[ whirring stops ]
Are you
out of your fucking mind?
You just killed us.
VERONICA: Maybe not.
How long you been awake?
I heard your mayday call.
Ohh.
Who's in me?
You have a tampon.
You were hemorrhaging.
[ pounding ]
What is that?
It's Ron's dick...
minus Ron.
What?!
Is Ron okay?
Not really.
He's dead.
[ gasps ] Oh!
Oh, my God.
[ sobbing ]
Oh, Ron.
[ pounding stops ]
[ pounding continues ]
Kids, did I ever tell you
what I can do with my kegels?
Your what?
They don't call it a trap
for nothing.
But I call it my c-clamp.
Trust me.
I can stop a bullet with it.
The banging stopped.
Do you think he went away?
It's probably got a headache.
But...
I can bring him back.
No.
Ron could never resist me.
Yeah, well,
he almost killed you last time.
But this time
I'll be ready for him.
No...
No.
Go on, now.
In a few days,
We'll meet at the burgundy room
and have drinks.
We'll laugh about this,
okay?
[ sobbing ]
Go on.
[ crashing ]
aah!
Anybody see it?
I do.
Sweet mother of God.
Jonah...Get it!
Hit it!
Jonah!
[ coughing ]
Enough.
If there's any part of Ron
left in you,
this is what you want.
Smell good?
Oh.
You bet your ass it does.
That's it.
Get it and come.
[ growling ]
[ gasps ]
Ooh.
Good.
Yeah, good.
How about
a little massage now?
Uh-huh.
That's it.
Oh! Good.
Here you go, baby.
Come on.
[ panting ]
come on.
[ grunting ]
Ooh!
It wants to come.
How do you know?
Can't fuck a guy
2,000 times
And not know
a thing like that.
Go on.
Kill it.
Okay. Ooh!
What are you doing?
Oh, I'm clamping down
its head,
preventing it from coming.
It's gonna explode.
I thought
you were gonna kill it.
I'm gonna kill it.
But I'm checking out, too.
What? Why?
Because the world's
no place for senior citizens.
You're 47.
Yeah, but in porn star years,
it's more like 103.
And I...am...a porn star.
Get out of here.
Oh, my God.
It's gonna explode.
Veronica, let it come.
Go on.
Hurry!
[ grunting ]
[ gasps ]
[ drops falling ]
Where are we?
Toolshed.
How?
Snow melted enough for me to
carry you down the mountain...
thanks to that.
Rain.
Not rain.
Ron.
[ yoni's "let the devil know"
plays ]
# you talk of sinners
taking down society #
# guys like Howard Stern
talking about pornography #
# your solution
is to take away our liberty #
# to decide what we choose
on radio or the TV #
# I don't know where you think
you have the right #
# to compel everyone
to see the light #
# it's not your place,
nor responsibility #
# ask the many more
who do agree with me #
# I'll take you
to every London avenue #
# so you can try to see #
# there's always gonna be #
# sinners who will tell you
with a laugh #
"please let the devil know #
# I send my best
and say hello" #
# can't you understand
that you're acting like Iran? #
# justifying, overriding
all the freedoms of the land #
# like you, I believe kids
should never have to see #
# hookers, drugs, and booze #
# but there
is still the right to choose #
# as long as what I do
does not affect your day #
# mind your own, and
we shall both be on our way #
# your meaning may be pure,
so it goes #
# but good intentions
pave the road to down below #
# I'll take you
to every London avenue #
# so you can try to see #
# there's always gonna be #
# sinners who will tell you
with a laugh #
"please let the devil know #
# I send my best
and say hello" #
# the way to spot
the ultimate hypocrisy #
# find the one who's
screaming loudest, "blasphemy" #
# and how two fellas
hooking up must be sick #
# then you find him with
his mouth chock-full of #
# I'll take you
to every London avenue #
# so you can try to see #
# there's always gonna be #
# sinners who will tell you
with a laugh #
"please let the devil know #
# I send my best
and say hello" #
# I'll take you
to every London avenue #
# so you can try to see #
# there's always gonna be #
# sinners who will tell you
with a laugh #
"please let the devil know #
# I send my best and say #
# I send my best
and say hello" #
[ intro to "do the kegel"
plays ]
# there's an exercise
that every woman needs #
# it's the kegel,
the pelvic squeeze #
# it's great at any age #
# let's make it all the rage #
# it's good for you, it's fun,
and it's a Breeze #
# you can do it in the bank
or on the bus #
# you can do it
with the minimum of fuss #
# find the muscle you'd locate
when you don't want to urinate #
# and squeeze,
squeeze, squeeze #
# do the kegel #
# the pelvic squeeze #
# come on with me, ladies,
and kegel, please #
# you'll Adore
your pelvic floor #
# when you squeeze,
squeeze, squeeze #
# and relax #
# you can kegel when
you're talking on the phone #
# we can kegel together
or alone #
# but when you're
with your lover #
# this trick is like no other #
# it's guaranteed to make
your Honey Moan #
# oh, baby, do the kegel #
# the pelvic squeeze #
# come on, ladies,
and kegel, please #
# you'll Adore
your pelvic floor #
# when you squeeze,
squeeze, squeeze #
# and squeeze some more #
# and relax #
# now here's
the really motivating bit #
# a kegel will put pressure
on your clit #
# and once you've had a baby #
# no time for saying maybe #
# take my advice #
# making kegeling a habit #
# a habit #
# squeeze, squeeze, squeeze #
# a healthy habit #
# now, it isn't just the girls
I want to tell #
# guys, this news
is pretty cool for you as well #
# 'cause when you're lovin'
with your lady #
# and she cries,
"no, don't stop, baby" #
# you'll be glad you know
this muscle really well #
# and so will we #
# do the kegel #
# the pelvic squeeze #
# come on, everybody,
and kegel, please #
# you'll Adore
your pelvic floor #
# when you squeeze,
squeeze, squeeze #
# do the kegel #
# do the pelvic squeeze #
# come on, everybody,
and kegel with me #
# you'll Adore
your pelvic floor #
# when you squeeze,
squeeze, squeeze #
# and then squeeze some more #
# a healthy habit #
# and relax #
# very healthy habit #
# squeeze, squeeze, squeeze,
and squeeze some more #
# and relax #
# squeeze, squeeze, squeeze #
# you'll Adore
your pelvic floor #
Mm.
MAN: Do you kegel
when you google?
# you'll Adore
your pelvic floor #
# a healthy habit #
# and squeeze some more #
# you'll Adore
your pelvic floor #
# a very healthy habit #
Subtitles by LeapinLar