I keep hearing this melody in my ears…
Frosty the Snowman
was a jolly, happy soul
With a corncob pipe and a button
nose, and two eyes made out of coal
There must have been some magic
in that old felt hat they found
For when they placed in on his head…
- Dude!
- What?
Don't put the magic hat on the snowman.
- Why?
- 'Cause if you do, he's gonna come to life.
Cool!
No it's not cool! My
sister - in, in Minnesota -
put a hat on a snowman
and it tried to kill her!
- Fuck him, let's do it anyway.
- Yeah.
There must have been some magic
in that old felt hat they found
For when they placed in on his head…
Oh my God! Frosty killed Kenny!
Dude, I told you not to put that
fuckin' hat on Frosty's fuckin' head!
Now, didn't I?!
Well, I'm sorry, Mr.
Rocket fucking Scientist!
What are we s'posed to do now?
I don't know what we're s'posed
to…wait. I bet he can help us
Who?
Ho ho ho, ho.
Save us! Save us!
Fuckin' save us! Save us!
Whoa-whoa. Now, tell me
what happened, slowly.
Okay. We were just
building a snowman…
and all of a sudden…it came to life…
I told him. I said, 'Don't put
the magic hat…on the snowman'
and he did it anyways…and…and
then he killed our friend, Kenny,
and now he's gonna kill everybody!
Did he look kind of like this?
- Yeah, kind of like that…
- Mm-hm, exactly
You know, ah-I don't think
that was the real Santa Claus.
Oh, no shit, Sherlock!
You know, thanks to you
there's not gonna be any Christmas,
and there's no one left to help us.
Oh, Christ!
Jesus!
Jesus, we beseech thee
in this time of need…
OK. Fucking Frosty, he fuckin' killed…
Dude! This is Jesus! You don't
say 'fuck' in front of Jesus!
is that so?
Go, Jesus!
Our Savior!
- That sucked.
- I'm sure glad that's over with.
Yeah. But you know, I
learned something today.
Yeah, don't put the magic hat on Frosty!
No. I learned about the
true Spirit of Christmas.
Really?
Yeh. Christmas isn't
about Frosty or Santa…
You're right. It's about Jesus.
- No, it's not even about Jesus, either.
- Well, then, what's it all about?
Presents.
You see? Presents!
Hey, man. Let's go home. I know
where my parents hide my presents!
- Cool!
- Yeah!
…sooo heee waves goodbye,
saying, 'Don't you cry,
I'll be back again someday.
Subtitles created by Lux Aeterna
Requiem_for_my_dreams@pathfinder.gr