My town is probably
a lot like yours.
You know, plenty of manicured
lawns and Volvos on the outside.
And some very special friends
on the inside.
Not to mention the never-ending
search for enlightenment.
Businessmen begging
for their promotions.
I-- I'd kill for it.
Whoo! Yeah!
While the jocks
and cool kids
look after
those less popular.
It can be quite touching.
Or not... depending on
your perspective.
I mean, everyone has
their breaking point, right?
Meet mine.
No, I don't think
we're dysfunctional.
You don't?
I mean,
we have our quirks,
but what family doesn't?
Your family, Mr. Burnett--
Jack-- Why don't you call me
Jack, Rachel?
Oh.
You can't call her Rachel.
- Why not?
- Because she's our therapist.
Here we go.
It's fine.
You can call me Rachel.
Absolutely not.
You deserve respect.
Call her "Doctor."
- She's not a doctor.
- What?
- How do you know that?
- Googled her.
You're not a doctor?
Well, I have my master's,
but not my PhD.
No PhD?
- That's just great.
- What does it matter?
We're supposed to tell her
every intimate detail
about our family life.
Yeah, like how
fucked up we are.
- Kelly--
- She comes highly recommended.
I assure you
I'm very qualified.
Might as well be talking
to the plumber.
Why are we even here?
Because your father said
we were on the verge
of a nervous breakdown.
- I did not say that.
- Yes, you did!
Actually, it was
an "emotional breakdown"--
- Shut it.
- Shut up.
I bet we're the first
family to ever be fired
by their therapist.
♪ I think you're
full of it ♪
♪ You're always talking shit ♪
♪ I'm getting closer
to losing it losing it ♪
♪ Every dirty look
I'll make a picture book ♪
♪ With all the pictures of your
stupid face stupid face ♪
♪ I ♪
♪ Will be fine ♪
♪ When you ♪
♪ Shut the fuck up
you're bringing me down ♪
♪ What the what
are you talking about? ♪
- ♪ Shut the fuck up ♪
- ♪ 'Cause you know ♪
♪ I don't really
give a damn anymore ♪
♪ Oh, oh, oh, oh ♪
♪ Such a fuck-up
you've done it again ♪
♪ What the hell what the hell
were you thinking? ♪
♪ I've had enough
I don't care ♪
♪ I don't care anymore ♪
♪ I'd like to
follow you someday ♪
♪ And when you look
the other way ♪
♪ Tie you up tie you up
to a hot air balloon ♪
♪ Watch you float
watch you float ♪
♪ All the way to the moon ♪
♪ I'll be walking on air
that day ♪
♪ 'Cause there's no air
in outer spa-- ♪
♪ A-a-a-a-a-ace ♪
- ♪ La-Ia-Ia ♪
- ♪ Shut the fuck up ♪
- ♪ La-Ia-Ia-Ia-Ia-Ia ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah ♪
♪ La-la la-la-la-la ♪
Ah.
Nice.
Yeah, good.
Yeah, come on.
Good.
Yeah.
Shit!
Not a chance, Jack.
( click }
Nice job.
Damn it.
But, mother, I think we
should have the AIDS triathlon
at least two weeks after
Bicycling for Breast Cancer.
Be-- no-- but--
Because everyone's
gonna be exhausted.
- Cut your ear again, Dad?
- Very observant.
Grandma's not really coming to
live with us, is she?
- No.
- Uh, yes, she is.
No, I'm back.
Right, what about a marathon
for manic depression?
Or, uh,
sculling for scoliosis.
Shut up, Jack.
Rollerblading
for rectal itch?
Luging for lumbago?
Yes, I know that
they're rude.
Good, mm-hmm.
Well, I just can't
wait to see you.
Leave this under
my pillow again,
and I'll shove it
up your ass.
I'm just trying to help.
I don't need
your fucking help.
Don't talk to
your brother that way.
Is that my blouse?
Yeah, you gave it to me,
remember?
Uh, I think it shows a little
too much nipple.
Bunnie.
Well, if you want
every boy in school
thinking you're
a little slut...
- which you may be.
- Fine.
- Oh, my God.
- Kelly--
There's your blouse back.
She's definitely
a little slut.
I hate school.
I hate it almost as much
as I hate that old bitch.
That's no way to talk
about your mother.
I was talking
about Grandma.
Oh, well, that's no way
to talk about her, either.
Oh, please, you hate her
almost as much as I do.
I don't hate her.
You hate her almost
as much as--
I do not hate anybody.
God said, "Honor your
father and your mother--"
- Shut up, Eric.
- Please shut up.
I'm driving.
Honor thy father--
get in the back.
Wait, um...
what is this for?
Oh... oh, God.
Well, maybe it ought to be
200 a plate, then.
What'?!
Pancreatic cancer
kills that many?
That's great!
No, let me get right on it.
Yeah, okay,
I'll call you later.
What?
Ha! You're so bad.
Okay, bye.
Reminder to self--
call Grace,
check pancreatic cancer
death rate.
If accurate,
up per-plate fee.
Aah!
Aah! Aah!
Come here!
Aah!
- Oh, shit.
- What?
That doorknob
was made in Italy.
Oh.
I'm sorry.
I mean, the window
I can fix.
But the doorknob...
it's irreplaceable.
Oh, I'm--
Babe, I just--
I don't know.
I was just so... into it.
How's it going,
Mr. Burnett?
♪ You're tripping every time
you take a step ♪
♪ You light the wrong end
of your cigarette... ♪
♪ It's love
it's love it's love ♪
Mr. Burnett?
Huh?
Your ear is bleeding.
Oh.
Nina.
Is that the best
you can do?
What are you--
what are-- what are you--
Oh, this is gonna
be fun, Jack.
Working together?
You mean, we're--
Firing people together.
Um...
Yeah.
That.
Nina? She's back?
I hired her yesterday.
The company's
hemorrhaging money, Jack.
You and Nina will stem
the flow of blood.
You'll get your raise,
your own Secretary.
You're the best boss ever,
Mr. Burnett.
Of course,
a position like this
comes with a certain amount
of responsibility, Jack!
You can definitely
count on me, Harv.
Your first priority
will be cutting costs.
Fantastic.
Yeah! Ohh!
Good, yeah.
- Yeah!
- Ohh!
Oh, I like that.
- Stop!
- Oh! Mmm.
- Hammer time.
- Ohh.
Yeah.
Oh! Oh!
- Watch your head, baby.
- Ohh! ohh!
Ohh! Yeah!
Ooh! Yeah!
- Let's ring the bell, baby.
- No.
No, no, ring my bell.
- Ring the bell, baby.
- Don't ring the bell.
Ohh! Ohh!
Ding! Whoo!
Ding!
Oh!
Oh, shit.
Bunnie?
You rushed it.
Sorry, Reverend.
Everything all right?
You know those guys I told you
about-- Andy and Roy?
Andy Porter--
religious club.
I joined.
Excellent.
Shit.
Hey, Jack...
- How is she?
- She's, um--
I don't know.
Cops said someone
broke into the house.
She might've been raped,
for God's sake.
Raped?
Is she conscious?
Mr. Burnett?
Oh, Doctor.
- We've had some complications.
- Oh, complications.
She's confused,
short-term memory loss.
- Confused, short-term...
- Yes.
Short-term memory loss?
Yes, quite a mess,
actually.
Bunnie?
Jack?
You remember me.
Oh, of course I remember you,
snookie-pie.
You haven't called me
that in awhile.
I haven't'?
Mmm.
What?
Nothing.
Do you feel up to
seeing Eric and Kelly?
Sure.
Who are Eric and Kelly?
She doesn't
remember either of us?
She only remembers up until
we first got married.
Shouldn't we go in there
and at least see her?
What's the point if she doesn't
even know who we are?
Maybe you guys
should just let her rest.
Yeah, Simon's right.
That's probably the best thing
for her now.
I wonder if she
can bake again.
Well, you always said
how good her
fudge brownies used to be.
If she decides
to whip up a batch,
send them over
to the church.
You guys were out shooting
again, weren't you?
Your boy has a God-given
talent, Mr. Burnett.
- What, killing and maiming?
- Dad--
Eric, you're weird
enough as it is
without being some kind of
gun nut to top it off.
- Dad, hey.
- Josh, what are you doing here?
How's Mrs. Burnett?
She's got amnesia.
- Amnesia.
- That's the good news.
Short-term memory loss.
She should probably
get it back soon.
And that's the bad news.
Kelly, you know what?
I've just about had it.
I'm fed up to here-- I only
wanted to be fed up to here.
What's the problem, Dad?
Simon, do you mind
taking the kids home?
- Seriously.
- I can do it.
Great, why don't you pick off
a couple of deer on your way?
- I'll take them.
- Thanks, Josh.
Come on.
Your son's very talented,
Mr. Burnett.
Yeah.
You should come out
and watch him sometime.
I'll pray for your wife.
You do that.
Gun-toting nut job.
I really gotta thank you
for coming out.
I can't tell you
how much it means to me.
Oh, hey, man,
it's the least I could do.
- It's amazing, right?
- What's that?
In a world full of
racial bullshit,
here's a black man
and a white man,
and, uh, we've just
risen above all this crap
to actually be able to
call each other "brother."
Uh, you know,
I don't mean "brutha,“
like maybe one of those
ghetto black guys.
I can say "black guy" to you,
I don't have to say--
I understand,
I know what you mean.
Yeah, you know-- sorry.
- Ah, hell.
- it's all right.
I love you, buddy,
really, l-- really.
Um, I was gonna get a cup of
joe, if you want to join me.
You know what?
I need to get home.
- Oh, all right.
- Yeah, yeah.
Well, I--
I love you, buddy,
I do, yeah.
Couldn't ask for
a better neighbor.
- All right.
Right on, I'll holler
at you later, then...
My man.
Paging Dr. Bender,
paging Dr. Bender, please.
Hi, Bunnie.
How are you feeling?
Good.
How are you?
Me? I'm-- I'm fine.
It's nice
to see you again.
You don't have any idea
who I am, do you?
Mm-mm.
Hold on.
What about now?
Not a clue, sorry.
No, no, don't be sorry.
Just, um--
- You get some rest.
- Mmm.
Just great.
License and registration.
Here you go.
You know your car
registration's expired?
No.
Is this vehicle yours, sir?
No, I stole it.
- Step out, please.
- Oh, come on, that was--
Sir, I need you to
step out of the car.
- Ohh!
- Oh, I'm sorry.
- Freeze! Right there!
- Hey, take it easy!
What are you doing?
- He looks black.
- Right.
- He stank black.
Okay.
Yeah.
Motherfucker
tastes black.
Is he delicious, cuz?
Don't ask me
no shit like that!
We should cut this
motherfucker open
and see if he's black
through and through.
I say you cut
this motherfucker--
Whoa, he just woke up.
Wake up.
What's up... my brother?
You ain't
my brother, cuz.
Right, sorry.
What the fuck
you in here for, huh?
I really don't know.
Where the hell was you at
when they picked you up?
I was in my car.
His car, shh.
Okay, shit, what kind of
car you drive, huh?
Um, I drive a Jag.
- Oh, Jag!
- Oh, big shit.
But you don't know why you in
here, though, huh?
Simon Krebs.
Yeah, that's me.
- You made bail.
- Deepak...
- Later, guys.
- Search this motherfucker!
What's in your
pockets, nigga?
Shit, what kind of fuckin' name
is Simon Krebs?
What kind of name
is that for a black man?
I don't know, but I know crabs
are supposed to
make your dick itch
or something.
Do you really buy that
some guy busted in here
and attacked Mom?
Uh... why else would
the window be broken?
Give me some.
That was, uh, nice of Josh
to show up like that.
Um, yeah, I guess.
- Do you think Mom blows Dad?
- What?!
Maybe if she did, they wouldn't
be getting a divorce.
They're not
getting a divorce.
Sure they are.
But maybe a little oral sex
would spice up--
Shut up!
You're disgusting.
What, there's nothing
wrong with it.
Yes, there is.
They talk about it
on TV all the time.
The Bible forbids it.
Yeah?
Tell me, where does it say
“no blow jobs"
in the Bible, Eric?
I couldn't tell you,
I don't know the exact--
But I know it's in there.
What do you think
the word is on rim jobs?
Jesus Christ, Kelly!
Why do you do this?
What, what do I do?
You say stuff just to
piss people off, why?
Because when people
are mad,
it shows you
who they really are.
- Really?
- Yeah.
Okay, then who am I?
You're a Bible-thumping
hypocrite
who really doesn't know shit
about the Scriptures.
Fuck you.
Heh.
That's the first real thing
you've said to me in months.
She was pretty.
She's still pretty.
I got a promotion today.
Really?
That's good.
You guys really look like you
used to be in love back then.
Yeah.
Why do you think
she hates me so much?
She doesn't hate you.
You think she's
gonna be okay?
Don't know.
I hope so.
Is Eric upstairs?
- Yeah.
- Hmm.
You know, you probably shouldn't
have called him a weirdo.
Yeah, heh.
Even though he is.
Ah, what the hell
are you doing?
- Nothing.
- Nothing?
You call pointing a gun
at somebody "nothing"?
- Give me the gun.
- it's not even loaded.
Goddamn it, Eric,
give me the gun!
If anyone's
seen Bobby Overmeir,
will they please report
to the principal's office.
You need some help?
Um...
Yeah, sure, yeah.
They can be
kind of tricky.
Yeah, uh--
- it's, um, 15-1-36.
- I know--
I know it already.
My locker's here,
so, I mean, I've seen it.
- Cool.
- Yeah.
Thanks, that's awesome.
I need to
get some stuff.
Praise the Lord!
Yeah, yeah, prai--
Uh, praise the Lord.
We got something.
Right now?
Yeah, right now.
Unless you want to
hang out with the skank.
What the hell, man?
Can't you see I'm busy?
- And God said unto thee...
- Let go of me!
“Smite the sinner!"
- Come on, man!
- Are you crazy?
Hey, piss on him.
What?
You want to get stoned
in the house of the Lord?
What the hell's your problem?
It's a bathroom!
Do it!
Whatcha doin', a-holes?
You know, you shouldn't
interfere with God's work.
God told you to put Johnson's
head in the urinal?
Yeah.
Whispered it
right into my ear.
Hmm.
Then God's as big a dick
as you are, Porter.
Gentlemen!
Have any of you seen
Bobby Overmeir?
Coach is looking for him.
What's a Bobby Overmeir?
Oh, you know--
star football player,
National Merit scholar,
all-around great kid.
Everything you're not,
Mr. Stukey.
Never hoped to be,
Vice Principal Carnes.
Get to class.
It was after Benedict Arnold was
cleared at the court-martial
that Washington issued
a reprimand,
when Benedict Arnold
almost gave up what?
Miss Burnett?
Uh...
I'm not sure
about that one.
Hmm.
And that would be because
you weren't listening?
you're so incredibly boring.
You, out.
Mitzy, do you know
the answer?
Um, West Point?
Thank you.
So, I'd say you owe me one.
You can...
spank me later.
Sp-- spank?
I am a connoisseur
of spanking!
Your parents must be
so proud, Mr. Stukey.
Oh, my gosh.
Anything look
familiar at all?
- In here, not so much.
- No?
Well, um...
I like it, though.
- Heh heh.
- Yeah.
It's pretty.
Yeah.
We have a cat?
Bunnie, seriously,
we need to talk, I--
Yeah, I know,
but it can wait.
Didn't the doctors
tell you?
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah, I have a little
bit of memory loss.
Yeah, like not remembering your
children and where you live--
But you know what, the idea of
having children
is starting to feel
really familiar to me.
That's a relief.
What's with this
belt buckle?
Honey, there are other things
we need to talk about
- other than your memory loss.
- That's great.
Let's talk about
the good things first.
Um--
Mmm.
Look, I know you don't
want me to lie--
- Wrong.
- You want me to lie?
Jack, just say that
everything is wonderful,
and if you say it enough,
it will be.
Who always
used to say that?
Your mother.
Oh, yeah.
Last thing I remember--
She and I weren't--
we weren't talking.
Tell me that we're
still not talking.
I gotta take this--
get off, get off.
It's Harv, it's Harv.
Harv, yeah, I just got her
back from the hospital.
Jack, what is it?
Are we talking?
She's moving in in two weeks,
you figure it out.
Ohh.
I'm sorry.
That's okay.
Oh, no, no,
no, it isn't.
Is all that stuff mine?
Sure as hell ain't mine.
Ohh.
I invited her, didn't I?
Uh, are we still
doing the lying thing?
Yeah.
Okay.
I invited her.
This is good.
I need to go to work.
We'll talk more later.
- Morning, Barbara.
- Good morning.
Morning, Alicia,
is there anything I--
Eunice, what's going on?
Up yours, Jack.
- What are you doing--
- How's the wife?
Wow, what did you--
- Still having memory problems?
- What?
Bet you like her
better that way.
Why was--
She's a new woman,
so to speak.
- Did you fire...
- Hmm?
Eunice?
- No, she quit.
- Because... ?
Her department's
quarterly profits are down,
and her managerial
skills suck.
You told her that?
Didn't I tell you
this would be fun?
Anybody in here?
It's okay.
- I missed you.
- I missed you, too.
♪ Trying to stop
all of the lyin' ♪
♪ 'Cause I'm tired of
your denyin' ♪
♪ That you have those
feelings for me ♪
♪ But instead you
just ignore me ♪
♪ Now you told me
a little secret ♪
♪ Gotta love me
gotta show it ♪
♪ When are you gonna
face your temptation? ♪
♪ Everyone's got their
own expectation... ♪
I knew Delbo
was a dyke.
Are you
gonna report it?
Why should I give a shit?
It's weird about
Overmeir, huh?
Totally.
It's so unlike him
to just split like that.
You think?
Wouldn't know.
'Cause I heard you two hooked up
at Wailer's party last week.
Heh, whatever.
Oh, we gotta go.
I'll catch you guys later.
Hey-
Want a better look?
Here.
Thanks.
It's, uh, kind of
weird looking.
No shit.
You're Eric's sister, right?
You're Delbo's bitch,
right?
I was in
one of the stalls
while you guys
were going at it.
I got a nice shot.
I'm not her bitch.
Eric talks about you
sometimes.
Yeah?
What does he say--
That I'm the gimp
at the locker next to his?
Something like that.
Actually, he said
you were nice.
Really?
Yeah.
But why would you care
what Eric thinks?
I don't.
What?
You're straight.
- No, I'm not.
- Bullshit.
- Fuck you.
- No, I don't think so.
I think you want
to fuck my brother.
Yeah?
Sorry.
Not my brand.
I'd rather eat pussy
than suck cock any day.
Well, how do you know
if you never tried?
Uhh!
Ask the Lord
for forgiveness.
Fuck you!
- Give me your pot!
- I don't have any!
Lying to me is like
lying to the Lord.
Now, give me your pot!
I knew it.
See?
You probably feel
better already.
Ohh!
Come on, get him off,
get him off!
- Get him off me!
- Son of a bitch!
Uhh! Fuck!
Oh, fuck!
Ohh, my God!
Holy shit! Fuck!
Oh, my God!
Holy shit!
Uhh!
Fuck.
Is he dead?
Come on, let's get
out of here.
Where are you guys going?
Give me some fucking help!
Fuck!
He's not breathing!
Your hair is broken.
That's great.
Mohawk's a bit retro,
don't you think?
Like you'd fuckin' know.
I know you shouldn't
have spit on me.
We're just doing
God's work.
That's bullshit-- you're using
God as an excuse
to beat up on people--
you're fanatics.
I know he doesn't
like dope dealers.
I'm not a fucking dealer--
that's my personal stash, man.
It's still a sin.
Dude, I need to sit down.
Where does it say
in the Bible
that smoking pot is a sin?
It doesn't actually talk about
marijuana in the Bible because--
because it wasn't
around back then.
How do you know
God doesn't like it?
Look, why didn't you
just leave me here?
Because killing
is a sin, too.
You should check out what your
buddy Andy does with my weed.
I was defending God.
And losing.
You didn't see
the other guy.
I bet he looked
much worse.
- Kitty--
- Kelly.
Kelly-- Kelly, would you pass
the salad, please?
- You hate salad.
- I do?
You used to like it when
we first got married.
So, why don't I
like it now?
You had it at one of
your charity things
and got sick on it.
At least,
you said you did.
Charity thing?
That's what you do.
You put on functions
for charity with Grandma.
Really? I do?
Do I get paid?
No.
You sort of do charity
for charity's sake.
Kelly.
She doesn't even
remember my name, Dad.
I'm-- I'm trying,
darling, I really am.
I'm sorry, it's just--
Everything is just
so damned hazy.
Maybe if we tried to do some
things together as a family,
that would help
to bring things back.
Yeah, that'll work.
Kelly.
She doesn't
need the attitude.
The town carnival
is tomorrow.
Really?
I love a carnival!
- I don't?
- Not really, no.
What do I like?
- Diseases.
- Mm.
Yeah, you like
diseases a lot.
Yeah, diseases.
- That's your thing.
- Mm-hmm.
You do that a lot.
With Grandma and stuff.
Oh, Nina called.
She said she wanted to see
how I was doing.
Nothing's going on.
I-- I didn't say
that there was.
I'm surprised
you remember Nina.
Your memory seems
to be getting better.
That's good.
I'm thinking maybe
we should...
go see some kind
of therapist.
As a-- as a family.
We don't do well
with therapists.
My mother-- did she
buy us this house?
She bought it for you.
I let her?
- Yes.
- Why?
Because we couldn't afford this
neighborhood otherwise.
I couldn't afford
this neighborhood.
We've let her buy us a lot of
things, haven't we?
Yes.
Bunnie.
I'll be right there.
Is Mom coming, or--
Oh, there she is.
She's wearing
my blouse.
Nice tits, Mom.
You look beautiful, dear.
♪ You, You never
believe me ♪
Oh, this looks like
it's gonna be so much fun.
♪ We all ♪
♪ Radia-diate ♪
Dude, that's so sick.
Where'd you learn
to shoot like that?
I don't know.
No, no, I'll take
two of those.
Who's your sister with?
No clue.
She seems to know you.
Your sister's not the
friendliest chick in the world,
is she?
Eric.
Reverend.
Who's your friend?
This is Paul Stukey.
- Nice to meet you, Paul.
- Pleasure.
Wax, I wax it.
Wax holds it up.
Uh-huh.
We'd better get going.
Um, Reverend.
Uh, see you, Reverend.
Yep-
60 bucks? You said 80.
Told you.
Let's get out of here.
So, how much did you
really hang out with Overmeir?
How'd you know about that?
He wrote about it
on his blog.
I didn't know
he had one.
Yeah, he wrote
really bad poetry.
Yeah, he read me some.
We were
at this party,
and he really started
laying on the moves,
like trying
to kiss me and shit.
There was no way.
So, I told him I'd give him
a quick B.J. if he laid off.
Really?
Yeah.
We were headed up
to his bedroom.
The loser
got so excited,
halfway up the stairs,
he creams himself,
and I get home in time
to watch Rachael Ray.
You cold?
I'm fine.
- Oh, that's a first.
- What?
You're smiling.
Oh, yeah.
Is that better?
I'm serious,
you haven't smiled once
since I came home
from the hospital.
Well... I was
worried about you.
I know, but I'm gonna
be fine.
I'm even starting
to remember some things.
♪ Springtime sunshine ♪
♪ Will always be around ♪
♪ As long as good times ♪
♪ Will never fade ♪
♪ But I'm escaping... ♪
Hmm, whoa.
Are you still
afraid of heights?
Well, yeah, when it, um--
When I look down
or up or--
- Ha ha!
- Wow.
- That's ridiculous.
- He must really like you.
What happened
to your nose?
Uh, vigorous picking.
Hmm, one of your
better traits, I'm sure.
I remember us being in love.
S-- something's
happening here.
I remember when you couldn't
keep your hands off me,
no matter where we were.
Yeah, Bunnie,
but, um... something's wrong.
Very wrong.
What's this guy--
oh, Jesus.
- Tell me.
- Ohh.
Honey, tell me what
happened to us.
No, I--
You know what, um...
Can't you see that
something's going--
Yeah, you don't even want to
kiss me anymore.
But, Bunnie, I'm having--
there's some sort of
major malfunction
going on down here.
I think
I'm gonna be sick.
What are you--
Jesus, Bunnie.
Oh, wait-- but--
You know, you used to love it
when I'd do this.
In front of
all kinds of people.
Yeah, but l-- Bunnie!
Bunnie, Bunnie.
Dude.
So gross.
Maybe their marriage
will survive.
You think that Mom's
having a nervous breakdown?
No, I just think she's nuts.
Were you nuts when you
ripped off your blouse?
Yeah, that was different.
How about giving blow jobs
to any guy that asks?
Does that mean you're nuts?
No, it means
I'm generous.
Hmm.
You know I don't
really do that.
Yeah, I know,
I know you don't.
You just want people
to think that you do.
Good morning.
- Uh...
- Good morning.
Uh... heh.
Can we ask you a question?
Does it have anything
to do with yesterday?
Yes.
Then no, you can't.
Did anybody get the paper?
- No.
- Nope.
Fine, let's get
ready to go, okay?
Hi.
Josh.
I'm surprised
you remember my name.
Oh, little things are
starting to come back to me.
- SO, you're feeling better?
- Much.
Good, I just thought
I'd do something for Bobby.
Oh, sure, sure, sure.
Do you smell that?
Yeah, a little.
You know, Dad and I have been
praying for you.
Well, thanks.
Josh.
Time to go for church.
I swear, Reverend.
It wasn't
what you think!
Look at me and swear
to the Almighty.
I swear.
You wouldn't lie to me right
beside the house of the Lord?
No.
You use your faith
as a guise
to hide your evil.
Give it to me.
Now.
Get out of my sight.
Not bad.
Thank you
for coming, dear.
You're welcome,
can we go home now?
No.
- Morning, Mrs. Burnett.
- Morning.
What are you doing here?
Oh, I'll see you inside.
Nice to see you got
all spruced up.
I did it all
for you and God.
Dude, I can't stop thinking
about your sister.
- Forget it.
- Why?
- You're dead, Stukey!
- Up yours, Porter.
You ratted me out.
Dude, you almost
killed me.
What the hell are you
doing with him, Eric?
Um...
We're friends.
Then ye shall reap
what thou sows.
What a dick.
We're friends?
Yeah.
Thank you, Jesus,
thank you.
Ha ha ha ha ha!
Mmm.
♪ Ridi, pagliaccio ♪
♪ Sul tuo amore
infranto ♪
♪ Ridi del duol ♪
♪ Che t'avvelena ♪
♪ Il cor ♪
Fuck you laughin' at?
Excuse me?
Fuck is
your problem, Jack?
Jack?
Do we know each other?
Man, fuck off, huh?!
Do that.
Hey-
Josh-- hey, hey.
- I need to talk to you.
- What's the matter?
- I need help.
- Is there a problem?
I can't talk
about it right now.
What's the problem,
what is it?
Can we talk about it
tonight, okay?
- Tonight? With me?
- Please.
I can't--
Josh, I can't.
7:30, please... please.
Lookout Park,
7:30, okay?
Okay.
You okay?
- Morning, Barbara.
- Morning.
You want to come?
Excuse me?
Lunch?
Not really hungry.
You and Bunnie finally
having sex again?
Oh, I don't--
I don't think--
You know, I think
about us sometimes.
She knew, Nina.
Knew what?
Nothing ever happened.
Well, I told her
it might.
We probably should've had
our little bump and grind.
That way, the two of you
would've got over it by now.
Keep those
profit margins up, Jack.
You and Nina--
doing a terrific job.
Thanks, Harv.
What are you doing?
- I got fired.
- What? Why?
Ask Nina.
Sit tight,
I'm gonna handle this.
I knew you had balls, but you
can't fire Alicia like that.
You're so busy
looking at her tits,
you didn't even know
if she could type.
Know what I'm gonna do?
I'm gonna hire her back.
Yeah?
You'll have to hire yourself
back first, won't you?
What?
Harv finally came
to the conclusion
that one hatchet person was
more than enough.
I just saw him!
He was just telling me what
a great job I'm doing.
See how quickly
you get to see him again.
Harv?
Harv, I know
you're in there.
Open the goddamn door!
Son of a bitch.
Ow!
Don't have time
to talk now, Jack.
Make the time, Harv.
It wasn't personal.
Fuck you!
And that is personal.
If we're not gonna
discuss this civilly--
You're a dick, Harv!
I'm gonna have
to call security
if you don't get
hold of yourself.
Thank you.
What--
Son of a bitch!
Yeah, yeah, and you're boning
Nina, too, aren't you?
- Did she tell you that?
- She didn't have to!
I still got
the dildo, Harv.
And I bet I could take it
into a lab
and get your DNA off it, too.
What's your DNA doing
on a dildo, Harv?
It's a...
prostate problem.
Quack, quack, quack,
quack, quack, quack.
Yeah.
You diggin' it, dude?
That's good, good.
I gotta show you
something.
Yeah.
Oh, shit.
Where'd you get that?
Reverend Diggs.
Bullshit.
He-- he wants me
to enter
this U.S. target-
shooting contest.
Says it's my
God-given gift.
Is it loaded?
Nah.
It's-- it's heavy.
Switch with me, man.
- Here.
- Yeah.
I gotta take a piss.
You do that.
Ohh, yeah.
All right.
There's all these ants.
Look, I'm gonna
pee on the ants.
Do you think God
really gives a shit
whether you can shoot
this thing or not?
Fuck!
Eric?
Eric, man, are you okay?
Oh, fuck, oh.
Hey, man.
Oh, hey.
Oh, shit.
Eric, hey man,
are you all right?
What am I gonna do?
- Blow me-- ha ha ha ha ha!
- Fuck!
Shit, dude!
Fuck you, dude!
You were freakin' out
so bad.
Dude, I thought
you were fuckin' dead!
No.
I'm high.
No, I'm fine, Mom, really.
Yes, I got your check,
thank you.
Still divorcing Jack?
No! What--
I mean, we're fine,
we're fine.
Well, I don't think
it's a mistake.
I'm not being
belligerent, Mom.
Oh, come on!
She said
she's in love with me.
Delbo?
Shit, get out!
What, you don't think someone
could love me 'cause of this?
Oh, stop being
a drama queen.
So, what'd you say?
I told her I was in love
with somebody else.
Cool.
Who?
Does it matter?
I'm going to her apartment
tonight to break it off.
Yeah, I think that's
the right thing.
Well, you're coming with me.
- What? No.
- Yeah, dude.
No, there's no way
I'm doing that.
- Seriously, broheim.
- That's not my thing.
Like, I don't do confrontation,
I don't do that shit.
My old man
doesn't like me.
Bullshit.
He like Kelly?
Yeah, he likes her.
I guess it's understandable.
In a way, he's kind of got more
control over her.
Well, my pops
always says...
that being in control
is always having a plan "B."
Reverend Diggs
says that...
religion should give you
all the control you need.
Yeah, but what the fuck
else is he gonna say?
Whatever this is about--
Listen to me, okay?
Okay, no, no, no, no,
you listen to me.
I don't remember what
happened between us.
But whatever it was,
it will never happen again.
- Do you understand?
- I love you.
And you love me, too.
'Cause what we did,
we couldn't do unless--
I-- I don't love you.
But what about
what me and you--
- You get out of this car.
- You can't--
- Go on, get out right now.
- NO, no.
You get out of
this car right now!
You love me.
I'm sick,
this is sick.
Say it!
Say that you love me.
Do you understand that?
Get out of the car.
Go on, get out
of this car now.
Conversation's over,
go home.
Close that door.
Here I go--
close that door, now.
This is the house
right here,
but ain't nobody out there,
it's dead as hell.
The motherfucker from jail
is following this
white bitch over here
to this house, cuz.
Simon.
What the hell is going on
between you and Josh?
- Nothing.
- What do you mean, nothing?
Don't lie to me!
- Well, I don't really know.
- What?
- Okay? I don't know.
- Bullshit!
These mothers
is crazy, cuz.
Where'd you find
this fool anyway?
Google's a wonderful
thing, dawg.
Ah! Ah, shit!
- Shit! Shit!
- Simon--
- Simon.
- Shit! Shit!
- You ready to do this shit?
- You ready?
- Let's roll.
- Creep low, creep low.
Simon, what's happening?
What's happening-- I'll tell
you, your wife here--
We almost had an accident.
Remember us, homeboy?!
I don't like them
fuckin' things!
How the fuck else I'm gonna
get 'em in the house?
What's wrong with you?
Why you always talkin' shit,
nigga, always talkin' shit.
Fellas, I don't know
what you're after,
- but there's a brand-new XBox--
- Shut up!
Take whatever you want!
Shut up, white boy,
before I bust a cap
on you right now!
He's just trying
to explain--
Who said you could talk?
Sit your ass down on the couch!
Oreo-lookin' motherfucker!
Sit down!
Why'd you have
to bring her?
- What do you want?
- Hmm?
Money, apologies,
a passing grade
in history?
Excuse me?
You're not here
to blackmail me?
No, she's not.
Fine, then why
is she here?
I want an "A" in history.
What?
I refuse to be blackmailed by
a lowlife student
who doesn't even know
who Benedict Arnold was.
Look who's talking
about lowlifes.
At least I've never tried to
steal another woman's woman.
She--
She doesn't care
about the "A."
She was just joking.
I'll give you a "C", but this
all stays between us.
I want a "B."
- C-plus.
- B-minus.
- Fine.
- Okay, great.
Let's go.
No, you... tell her
what you came for.
No, come on, let's go.
Okay, she doesn't
love me.
She has a crush
on my brother Eric.
No, I don't.
You don't?
No, I'm--
I'm gay, and I love you.
Well...
that's just...
fan-fucking-tastic.
Are you--
are you serious?
Yeah.
Kind of wish I wasn't.
Where'd she go?
Yeah-- oh.
Hey, you--
Where do you keep
your jewels and shit?
- The jewels?
- Yeah, the jewels.
- I can't remember.
- I don't know.
Y'all got jewels, and neither
one of you know where they at?
Well, it's kind of
complicated,
because we weren't
getting along for awhile--
Where are the fucking
jewels, cuz?!
- I would tell you--
- I'm countin' to three,
and I'm gonna blow
your fuckin'--
What the fuck
are you doin', man?
Give me this shit!
You just gonna snatch
my piece, cuz?
- You're damn right!
- Fuck you, cuz.
I gotta get this--
it's my mama.
Mrs. Johnson?
Shh!
Hey, Mama! Hey!
Hey, nigga, tell Mrs. Johnson
I say what--
Uh-huh?
Yeah, I know.
Thomas Jefferson,
yeah, yeah.
Right, no,
it's due Friday.
Huh? I know.
I couldn't believe it.
You said we might be
related-- that's crazy!
Heh! Okay.
I love you, too,
Mama, mwah!
All right,
okay, bye, bye.
Love my mama, ha ha!
What-- I got a book report
for school.
You're in school?
Hell yeah, my nigga is
a straight-A student.
Trey!
And his old man's
a dentist out in Cali.
Shut up!
Please, man!
You hate when I talk
about your daddy.
Now, listen,
you're gonna tell me
where you keep your jewels,
all right?
Or I'm gonna beat the fuck out
of you, you hear me?!
I'm gonna bust your
fuckin' head wide open!
I'm not fuckin' playin'!
They're in
the master bathroom.
Uh, go under the sink.
They're in a douche bag.
You ever think about
doing yourself?
All the time.
- How would you do it?
- How?
With my hand,
how else am I gonna do it?
Would you, like,
choke yourself?
I don't want to choke it,
bro, I mean--
I want to... stroke it.
Nah, I--
I mean, you know--
You ever think about--
about doing yourself?
Oh.
No.
You?
Nah.
Why do you look
so familiar?
I jacked you before
or something?
This would be
my first jacking.
That nigga knew
right where it was at.
How the hell do you know where
my wife hides her jewelry?
I think he knows where
she hides a lot of things.
Hey, go grab that.
Hey, cuz!
We got a visitor.
Nina?
Mm, ugh-- what is
going on here, Jack?
A little get-together,
that's all, ha ha!
Bitch, get on the couch!
What you think we doin'--
we got guns and shit.
What is she doing here?
I don't know-- what are you
doing here, Nina?
You got me fired, asshole.
- You got me fired first.
- Oh!
You got fired?!
Look what else I got, cuz.
- Well...
- Jack!
She got transferred
into the--
Ohh! Ohh! Ohh!
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, oh yeah, yeah.
Oh, yeah, I like that.
Stop!
Hammer time.
Ohh! Yeah.
Ohh-- Let's ring
the bell, baby.
- No.
- Come on, ring my bell.
Ding! Ding!
Whoo!
Ohh! Ohh! Ding! Whoo!
Ding!
Oh!
it's not like
it sounds, man.
You know, they alter
them tapes all the time.
Simon, cuz--
the ding-dong man!
A nerd name,
but it gets the--
- We're done.
- Jack-- Jack, please!
If we make it through this
alive, we're done-- done.
- Sit your ass down.
- Fuck off.
You were supposed
to be my friend.
Sit your ass down.
You see, actually, Jack,
all of your pseudo-liberal,
ain't-it-great-being-friends-
with-the-black-folk-
next-door shit...
never really cut it with me.
Oh.
So you fucked my wife
to get back at me?
And if you think
I was the only one--
Well, yeah.
- Only one?
- Oh, yeah, yeah.
Yeah, ask her who else, hmm?
Ask her.
What the fuck
is he talking about?
Yeah, what am I
talking about?
Josh.
So, you think
your sister's home?
Tsk, forget about it, dude,
it's weird.
You're weird.
No, man, that's weird.
Nice parking job.
Ha ha.
Yeah.
I think that's
Josh's dad's car.
Veronica, what the hell
are you doing?!
I read your
space things, you know!
Myspace?
All you kids-- what
a bunch of narcissistic,
whining little scumbags!
Especially you.
Oh, really?
What does that
make you, then?
Broken-hearted.
Bullshit.
I'm out of here.
Fine, go-- take your
girlfriend with you!
- I'm not her girlfriend!
- Right, we got it, Kelly.
You'll give it up
for any asshole
because you can't have
real feelings for anyone.
I have real feelings.
Yeah? For who?
I'm out of here.
Mitzy!
Eric, run!
- Trey, shut that down!
- Can't go, either.
- Let's rush 'em.
- What? What?
- Shit!
- He's not so tough.
His father's a dentist,
for God's sake.
- Yeah.
- Come to think of it...
you ain't really no blacker
than I am, are you, boy?
He doesn't even
have a gun.
Oh, shit.
What you call this, huh?
He gets one of us,
the others take him down.
You talkin' real crazy
right now.
No, I'm not,
I don't think so.
- I don't think so, either.
- Ouch!
( gunshot }
Oh, shit!
They shootin' at me!
Oh, shit! My ankle.
- Eric.
- Oh, my God.
Yo, we gotta bounce, cuz.
- Did you get 'em?
- I couldn't get 'em.
Man, they had guns
and everything.
Dodging bullets and shit.
Just get the shit
and let's go, man.
Get on the goddamn couch!
We're not playin', man!
- This shit never happened.
- You's a freak.
- I gotta get my gun.
- Dude, forget the gun!
We gotta get
the fuck out of here.
Watch out!
I'll go first.
- Right there!
- Where? Where?
Ohh!
Man, you shot my shit!
- I'm sorry!
- You can't even shoot!
No, I should probably be
the one to go first.
- Bunnie, would you--
- Oh, shit!
Oh, crap!
Jesus!
Oh, my God!
- I'm Simon.
- Nina.
You know, maybe she
doesn't even mean it.
You know, maybe she just needs
time to think about it.
Know what I mean?
Yeah, it doesn't even
matter anymore.
Don't say that-- whoa.
Shit!
What the fuck?!
- What the hell is this comin'?
- What is this?
What's up, homeboys?
Back your ass up.
- Son of a bitch!
- Back the hell up!
Fuckers!
No!
Oh, shit!
What the fuck?
Ohh, you broke my wallet.
You're insane!
Whoa.
Doesn't that kind of
look like Overmeir?
Yeah, just kind of
a bloated Overmeir.
Yeah, with, like,
a stretched-out neck.
Eric?
I'm all right.
Jack...
I don't want
the rubber chicken again.
Let's go with
the roast beef.
Roast beef's too expensive.
We'll go with the chicken.
Oh, my mother just walked in--
let me call you back.
Heh heh.
Another job interview?
Yep-
Your ear's bleeding.
How the hell does he always
cut himself like that?
Nice to have you
here, Ilene.
Good luck, honey.
He's never gonna get a job.
Oh, you are wearing
your mother's blouse.
L-- I gave that
to her, Mom.
You can see--
it's fine, Mom.
She looks really
beautiful in it.
What is a hero?
A hero is someone that you'd
want to be like,
someone that you
look up to.
Especially if they're hanging in
a tree outside your house.
Bobby Overmeir was
that kind of kid.
Even in death,
Bobby was able
to tackle
a no-good gang banger.
And there's another
hero here today,
one who saved many lives
the night that Bobby's
poor body was discovered.
That's Josh Krebs.
Josh,
come up here, son.
It's loaded.
It's beautiful.
You deserve it.
On your way home,
stop at a range,
try that baby out.
What the hell
are you doing?
You gave him a gun?
Yes.
Are you insane?
After what our family's
been through?
Please-- Eric,
just give me the gun.
- Give me the gun, Eric.
- it's up to me.
- Give me the fucking gun!
- No! Okay?
This is the only thing
that I'm good at.
The only thing you're good at
is being an idiot.
Jack.
What? Look.
How dare you talk
to him that way?
“How dare you"?
You want to do “how dare you"?
How about... how dare you do
what you did to me?
Jack, a lot of things
are starting to come back to me.
A lot of things--
I didn't sleep with Josh.
He wanted to,
but I didn't.
That's a relief,
I feel a lot better.
Well, I don't.
This has always
been about you
and the career that
you didn't have
and the money that
you didn't make
and the fact
that my mother
bought us that
fucking house!
Let me talk to him--
Jack.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, Kel.
You're dead, Stukey!
Andy!
Everything pretty much
happened in a rush after that.
There was a funeral,
and the Krebs decided
to move across town.
Don't you forget
I paid for this house.
Yes, I won't forget that.
But you put it in my name,
and that makes it
legally mine.
Fine-- why would I want to stay
in a place that I'm not wanted?
It's not that
you're not wanted.
But, actually,
And I'll tell you why.
Because you're
a very selfish woman,
and you've always
used your money
to manipulate
anyone you can,
but especially me!
Grandma never knew
what hit her.
It's time.
Ladies
and gentlemen,
I'd like to introduce you
to a real hero tonight,
a young man we can all
be proud of.
So, what exactly
happened that day?
I'm not even sure myself.
Eric Burnett.
It was pure instinct,
I guess.
The reverend probably would've
called it divine intervention.
Also in the audience,
we're very lucky to have with
us... two other heroes.
Others might've
called it blind luck.
Either way, even Dad
would have to admit--
It was a hell of a shot.
Jack Burnett and his very
brave wife Bunnie--
Eric's father and mother.
Let's face it.
The fact that this family
is still together
is almost as much of a miracle
as those two bullets colliding.
I mean, my mom and dad
will never have
the perfect marriage...
maybe not even close.
But they're still here.
We all are.
That must say something.
I don't know.
Maybe it takes
almost losing someone
before you know how much
you're going to miss them.
Hey, I'm sure we'll
still have our moments.
I mean, you have
parents, right?
The man's entitled
to his opinion.
Even though he's wrong.
♪ I think you're crazy ♪
♪ I think you're lazy ♪
♪ I'm getting closer
to losing it losing it ♪
♪ You keep complaining ♪
♪ You keep on blaming ♪
♪ I'm getting closer
to losing it losing it ♪
♪ I ♪
♪ Will be fine ♪
♪ If you ♪
♪ Shut the fuck up
you're bringing me down ♪
♪ What the what
are you talking about? ♪
♪ 'Cause you know I don't
really give a damn anymore ♪
♪ Oh, oh, oh, oh ♪
♪ Such a fuck-up
you've done it again ♪
♪ What the hell what the hell
were you thinking? ♪
♪ I've had enough
I don't care ♪
♪ I don't care anymore ♪
♪ I think you're
full of it ♪
♪ You're always talking shit ♪
♪ I'm getting closer
to losing it losing it ♪
♪ Every dirty look
I'll make a picture book ♪
♪ With all the pictures of your
stupid face stupid face ♪
♪ I ♪
♪ Will be fine ♪
♪ When you ♪
♪ Shut the fuck up
you're bringing me down ♪
♪ What the what
are you talking about? ♪
- ♪ Shut the fuck up ♪
- ♪ 'Cause you know ♪
♪ I don't really
give a damn anymore ♪
♪ Oh, oh, oh, oh ♪
♪ Such a fuck-up
you've done it again ♪
♪ What the hell what the hell
were you thinking? ♪
♪ I've had enough
I don't care ♪
♪ I don't care anymore ♪
♪ I'd like to
follow you someday ♪
♪ And when you look
the other way ♪
♪ Tie you up tie you up
to a hot air balloon ♪
♪ Watch you float
watch you float ♪
♪ All the way to the moon ♪
♪ I'll be walking on air
that day ♪
♪ 'Cause there's no air
in outer spa-- ♪
♪ A-a-a-a-a-ace ♪
♪ La-la-la ♪
- ♪ La-la-la-la-la-la ♪
- ♪ Shut the fuck up ♪
♪ La-la-la-la-la-la ♪
♪ La-la
la-la-la-la ♪
♪ Shut the fuck up
you're bringing me down ♪
♪ What the what
are you talking about? ♪
- ♪ Shut the fuck up ♪
- ♪ 'Cause you know ♪
♪ I don't really
give a damn anymore ♪
♪ Oh, oh, oh, oh ♪
♪ Such a fuck-up
you've done it again ♪
♪ What the hell what the hell
were you thinking? ♪
♪ I've had enough
I don't care ♪
♪ I don't care anymore ♪
♪ Oh, oh ♪
- ♪ Shut the fuck up ♪
- ♪ Yeah-eah-eah ♪
♪ Yeah-eah ♪