Aah!
Girl, quiet.
You'll wake up the dead.
It was a nightmare.
Enough about nightmares.
You've got to be on your way
before the house is
up for breakfast.
Look alive, girl.
You'll never be hired
looking cow-eyed.
I write this note.
I told your mother
I'd do what I could,
and now I done it.
Put your hat over your face.
Your mug's been in the papers.
You can't tell them the truth,
or they'll send you packing.
and God hates a liar,
so just keep your mouth shut.
You hear me?
Keep your mouth shut.
Well, hurry now.
Go on.
Can't you talk?
Oh, Lorraine,
of course she can talk.
Will you let me eat sweets?
Lorraine.
She gets far too
many sweets as it is.
Her father cannot say no.
Will you paint with me
and read me stories?
Of course she will,
won't you, Alice?
Oh, yes, ma'am.
Has Trevor got one of
his famous smiles for Alice?
LORRAINE: Our nanny
walked out on us.
Well, not quite,
but she did leave us in a pickle.
We need to find a
replacement quickly.
We're going on a big boat!
That's right, dear.
Tomorrow we get on a
big boat for New York.
Would you like Alice
to come with us?
I don't know.
Well, of course you do.
What about you, Trevor?
Do you like Alice? Hmm?
Maybe you should hold him.
I'd like him to get used to you
before we sail.
You're supposed
to hold his head.
Uh, the note said
that you've had
experience with babies.
I mean, that's imperative.
Oh, yes, ma'am.
I got experience.
I love children.
I-- It's just nervous, that's all.
Ohh, well, there's no need
to be nervous around us.
We're just regular people.
The most important thing
is that you give our
children loving care.
Oh, my heavens, what
a lucky girl you are.
You'll be sailing on the Titanic.
Is the crew in order?
Aye, it's a fine bunch, sir.
I know quite a few of them.
Most come from the same
neighbourhood here in southampton,
but these 900 men never
sailed together as a crew before,
so there's a bit of confusion.
Still, all in all, they're as proud
a bunch as I've ever seen.
Indeed, to serve
aboard this vessel.
Uh, also, Captain, well,
to serve under you.
Well, thank you, Mr. Lowe.
There's always a bit of
apprehension on a maiden voyage,
but I have the greatest faith
in all of my officers and men,
including yourself, sir.
Now I'm afraid I must face
the most perilous
part of the voyage--
meeting all of those reporters.
We have here the largest movable
manmade structure in the world.
A supership, if you will.
11 stories high.
5 city blocks long.
A boat this big, it has to
be slower than Lusitania.
Does the Lusitania
have a library,
a swimming pool,
turkish baths?
We're offering luxury.
A colossal showcase.
And I can assure you, young man,
that this ship will give the
Lusitania a run for her money.
Is it your vision, Mr. Ismay,
or the owner's?
Well, in all fairness
to J.P. Morgan,
may I remind you that my father
founded the white star line.
Now, I, as managing director,
intend to bring it
into the 20th century.
Ah, here he is our Captain.
Captain Smith, is it true
you're retiring after this voyage?
That's true.
Will you be writing a book
about your adventures?
Well, it'd be a very
short book, I'm afraid.
I haven't had much adventure.
What about wrecks, accidents?
Well, there've been winter squalls
and storms and fog,
but I've never had any...
adventure worth writing about,
certainly not recording
for posterity.
I'm afraid that I enjoy
uneventful sea voyages.
Like the one you're
embarking on, sir?
Exactly.
Shipbuilding has become
such an art now
that disaster is...
unthinkable.
My job has become, um...
Uh, effortless.
Thank you.
Effortless.
Gentlemen, might I point
out the dining room.
Oh, yes, please.
For your information,
we are stocked with
75,000 pounds of fresh meat...
11,000 pounds of fresh fish...
and 1,120 pounds of
marmalades and jams.
And of course,
stock of the finest libations.
Cognac-- oh, one moment.
Yes, "Sandeman Port, 1870."
Very good.
Thank you.
And we have-- uh, not there!
Those chairs should go
on the private promenade outside.
Uh, they should be a darker green.
They will be repainted
before the next sailing,
you can be sure of that.
We have seen to every detail.
What about lifeboats?
We have complied
with the statutes
of the british board of trade.
But, gentlemen, we
have here the largest,
most beautiful, and
technically perfect ship
in the history of mankind.
We're not going
to need lifeboats.
I thank you for your attention,
now first Officer Murdock here
will take you on a
short tour of the bridge.
Good day to you.
- Good day. Thank you.
- This way, gentlemen.
[ police whistle blowing ]
Oh! Aah!
Bugger!
[ blowing whistle ]
[ ragtime piano music ]
[ loud conversations ]
Tot of rum here, mate.
Here, take me cap, lad.
Keep your head in your booze
and your wits about you.
[ exhales ]
You in trouble, lad?
Nothing serious, thank you.
Ahem.
Drinks on me, chaps.
Here.
I worked for this.
Worked and saved.
Say farewell to
bloomin' England.
I'm set for Niagara Falls.
That's in America.
You see her out there?
See who?
The Titanic.
Biggest ship ever made.
Just walk right outside
that door there.
Here, look at this.
See that?
[ chuckles ]
That's...
that's me ticket
to a new life, eh?
No more coal dust
for Merriam Dickle.
America!
On the biggest ship
I've ever dreamed.
Imagine, Merriam Dickie...
sailing with some of the
richest people in the world.
Ha ha ha ha!
[ chuckles ]
Well, you're right about that.
John Jacob Astor himself
wil be on that boat.
That's a fact.
All the money and jewels on board.
Priceless paintings.
A thief could have himself
a high old time.
Did you ever see
a diamond tiara?
Can't say I have.
Of course, the trick is
getting the booty off the boat.
Strings of pearls.
Oh, yes, sir.
A thief could have himself
a grand old time.
Mmm.
I'll be calling it a day.
Man's got to get his sleep.
OK, but I owe you one.
No. Just the tiara.
You be careful.
Hey. Heh.
Merriam Dickie...
on the same ship
as John Jacob Astor.
[ laughing ]
That's the joke on it, eh, lad?
Here...
to-- to the Titanic!
Titanic.
Ha ha.
# ...beyond joy #
# The queen and king #
# Me mother nor me father #
# Won't I have a
clue where I'll be #
# Across the sea... #
Come on, Dickie.
You can't sleep here,
now, can you?
Aye, my brother
has got me a job,
a whole new life
for Merriam Dickie. Yes. Yes.
Wake up.
I'll take you back to
your boardinghouse.
[ snoring ]
Dickie.
[ carriage passing ]
Titanic.
And my thanks it is
to you, Mr. Dickie.
Maybe I'll say good-bye to
bloomin' England myself.
Nigal...
Yes, sir?
Get the bags.
Yes, sir.
Bye!
...or ye shall die, sinners!
Repend of your wickedness!
Repend or ye shall die, sinners!
I hear shrieks
and cries
and moaning!
You shall sink in the dark waters
and never be heard of again!
Mrs. Paradine.
Isabella.
We're both going on the Titanic.
It must be fate.
I don't believe in fate...
Mr. Park.
Please excuse me.
And death shall cover thee!
Thou shal sink deep in the ocean
like a stone!
Yes, Miss?
Ludwigsen.
A lovely little lady
traveling alone, are you?
Uh, she's a convert
traveling with the group.
My husband here is
Black Billy Jack,
and he's big enough to take
you on, and a few more like you,
so don't go bullying us
because of our religion.
We're no simps.
Now, Clarinda.
Uh, I be a Blacksmith, sir.
That's where my
nickname comes from.
Not from my nature.
Excuse me, I'm looking
for the men's quarters.
Well, look what
the cat dragged in.
I don't think I caught
your name, chum.
Ahem.
Merriam Dickie.
Dickie, you say?
Heh heh heh heh.
Well, Mr. Dickie,
I don't suppose you'll be
traveling with these converts.
No, I'm traveling alone.
Well, run along, then, chum.
I'll catch up with you later.
Miss Ludwigsen,
if you'll step this way.
The Steward down the corridor
will give you a cabin,
Mr. and Mrs. Jack...
All the little... Jacks.
I'm told we'll have crisp nights
but clear skies straight across--
why, Mr. Park.
Henry! Good to see you, Henry.
Well, likewise, I'm sure, sir.
You will see many familiar faces.
Many of the regulars
have joined us, sir.
Mr. Wynn Park across
the hall from you--
real gentleman.
I have crossed the
Atlantic 6 times with him.
Generous man, if you
know what I mean.
I must ask for another stateroom.
Mrs. Paradine, this one is exquisite.
Every detail--
Please see what
you can arrange.
Mrs. Paradine,
everything is booked solid.
It's impossible.
I can't stay here.
Please.
Any room at all.
Just far from this one.
Yes, of course. Ahem.
Thank you.
[ horn blowing ]
[ cheering ]
WOMAN: Mrs. Paradine.
Excuse me.
Oh, you poor darling.
We heard that you
were in London.
Your poor dear Aunt Grace.
How sad for you her passing.
Well, I took matters
into my own hands
As soon as I realized that
you were sailing with us.
You can dine at our
table, of course.
And no moments alone,
I'll see to that.
And my granddaughter Lulu,
she'll keep you company,
and my baby Charlie.
Lulu, don't slump.
It's so lovely to see you.
Don't look now.
That's the infamous Molly Brown.
Her husband made a fortune
in silver and gold mines.
But they say he tried
to shoot her twice.
It was a terrible scandal.
She's crude, but one
can't ignore her.
She's far too rich.
Oh, the strausses.
They own Macy's
department store.
Jewish.
Oh, and Benjamin Guggenheim.
Ha.
Most people are content
to bring back souvenirs of
the eiffel tower from Paris.
He's bringing back his mistress.
Well, he's not sitting
at our table. Huh.
Oh, the Wideners.
Al, Lulu, the-- the-- the Wideners.
AL: For heaven's sake,
how are you, old man?
Tugs all fast.
Take her out, Robert.
When do we get
on the boat, Mommy?
Oh, we're on the boat, darling.
Looks like a hotel to me.
- Ha ha ha ha.
See?
See there, little darling?
Wave to all the people.
Good-bye to England.
Good-bye, England.
MAN: Here, now!
I've been robbed!
I've been robbed! Here! Here!
Me life! It's me life!
You can't do this to me!
Me life is on that ship!
Here, get off me!
You can't go!
[ ship's horn blows ]
Is, uh, something wrong, Miss?
I left my family
back in Denmark.
I may never see them again.
I brought my mother's
nightcap from the clothesline.
It's all I have of her.
Well, more than I have of mine.
I look for a better life.
Yeah, me, too.
Oh, my heart is divided.
Yeah, well, it's better
you don't have a heart.
An emigrant must have courage.
You have to keep
thinking of that,
to be grateful to be on
this beautiful ship.
This is nothing.
Steerage.
Now, up there in first class,
they got gold mirrors
and crystal chandeliers.
What is this first class?
We'll all get to America
at the same time.
Yeah, but they get there in style.
That's where I plan
to do business,
there in first class.
It don't take courage,
it takes smarts.
Throw that bit of
raggedy cap away.
Let go of the past.
Hey!
Uh, this gate is locked.
Well, now, that is
the idea, isn't it?
Steerage can't mingle
amongst the other passengers.
Why?
Yank immigration laws, on
account of infectious diseases.
Well, I'm not asking
you to kiss me.
Ha ha.
Just let me through.
I'm not about to lose my
stripes on the first day out.
I just want a look around.
Nobody will know the difference.
In that suit?
What's wrong with
my bloody suit?
# I gave my love a cherry #
# What had no stone #
Come on, let's go.
# I gave my love a chicken #
- # That had no bone #
- Trevor's cold, Alice.
Please, it's cold out here.
# I gave my love-- #
It's night, Alice.
Trevor needs his supper.
You're supposed to take care of us.
Stop whining.
Come on, Alice.
Excuse-- excuse, please,
these children.
Did you see Mrs. Astor?
Mrs. Astor?
Mrs. John Jacob Astor?
You don't know who
John Jacob Astor is?
The richest man in the world?
I think I know you.
Were you in Cairo last month
with the Hendersons' baby?
I never been to Cairo.
Oh, Mrs. Astor.
Your cape.
You'll catch cold.
And in your condition...
it's chilly out here.
You can't be too careful.
You're right, Miss Miller.
I keep telling my wife that.
Now promise me you
will eat a good dinner.
They say a body
needs these things
they've discovered
called Vitamins.
She eats like a bird, you know.
She's eating for two now, and
she's not getting her Vitamins.
Ha ha ha ha ha.
Just a few more moments,
John, please,
before we have to walk
into the dining room.
I have to be calm-- ha--
and regal when they
all start to gossip.
Come, my dear.
[ music plays ]
[ laughing ]
Mr. Astor, Mrs. Astor.
Mother Foley, the Astors.
Ah!
I should think they would
be dining in their stateroom.
I mean, the nerve, They must
have boarded at Cherbourg.
Mr. Astor is a frequent
passenger on the white star line.
But not with her.
I know the real Mrs. Astor,
the first Mrs. Astor.
They say she's expecting.
Well, she could have a
litter of little Astors,
but she will never be
accepted in polite society.
Ah, the hell with polite society.
They got each other
and the U.S. Mint.
Oh, excuse me.
Captain Smith.
Ah, how may I
assist you, madam?
It's about Lulu.
Uh, your daughter?
Oh-- ha-- actually,
my granddaughter.
We are always mistaken.
Captain, I was wondering,
perhaps you might know of
some nice gentleman on board
who might be of some
company to Lulu,
someone dignified,
substantial.
Someone like yourself, only--
only, uh, younger.
No, no, no, no, not younger.
Lulu is so incomplete.
Uh, an older man
would be helpful.
No, I-- I meant someone...
Well-to-do. Wealthier.
Exactly. The trip to
europe was disastrous.
All the men are
foreigners, fortune hunters.
Well, I promise you,
I will keep my eyes open.
Oh, thank you, Captain.
Another bottle, sir?
I'd like it before we get to
New York, if you don't mind.
[ laughter ]
Good health!
This is my third crossing
with the captain,
and last time I even
sat at his table.
25 years, is it?
With the white star line, yes.
The world's greatest ship and
the world's greatest captain.
Here's to a rip-roarin'
maiden voyage for us Titanic.
Well, since it is my last voyage,
I was hoping for
something a little calmer.
How fast are we going, Captain?
I have a wager on
with Allison here.
I say we're traveling
in excess of 20 knots.
If you will excuse me.
Captain Smith doesn't
like to talk about speed,
but I think it's safe to say that
Mr. Allison owes you some money.
Ohh.
Now, Mrs. Brown, would you
care for some more oysters?
Ooh! Don't mind if I do.
They're delicious.
Big and fat and juicy.
Oh, and some more-- some
more wine, please?
Lafite-Rothschild.
We don't get wine
like this in Denver.
Boy, you built some
rowboat here, Mr. Ismay.
Well, I'm glad you're
impressed, Mrs. Brown.
Yes, I was determined to
create a ship for the 20th century.
One must be a visionary.
Now, may I recommend
the pressed pheasant,
or perhaps the, uh, poularde
poche a l'estragon.
Ha ha. No skinny little
poularde for me.
I'm havin' roast mutton,
agneau et mouton.
You speak french?
I hired a french tutor.
He pulled a cork from a champagne
bottle and put it in my mouth--
The cork, not the bottle.
He said it'd force me to hold
my mouth open when I talk.
Well, I told him most people
preferred me with my mouth shut.
- Ha ha ha ha.
We are forgetting Mrs. Paradine.
All this festivity.
Poor darling. Her dear Aunt
Grace passed recently in London.
All those months
alone in London,
taking care of the burial
and your aunt's affairs.
I supposed things were... jumbled.
We promised your husband
that we'd watch over you
on the voyage home.
That's very kind of you.
The Paradines have the most
beautiful estate on the Hudson,
and their little girl is a dream.
Miss Foley, could I have
the pleasure of a dance?
Oh, well, Lulu would love
to dance, Mr. Park,
as long as it isn't that
abominable turkey trot.
One wonders what the
world is coming to sometimes.
Posture, Lulu.
Such a charming man,
and so very handsome.
Our little Lulu could do worse.
Our little Lulu couldn't
do any better.
He's shrewd-- ha ha-- intelligent.
And loaded.
A marriage made in heaven.
You must long to dance, too
a young woman like you.
It's so sad you're stuck in
black for the whole crossing.
It doesn't domuch for your...
delicate complexion.
I suppose your aunt's
husband is grieving.
The marriage only lasted
a year, Mrs. Foley.
I don't know where
Mr. Santilese is now.
Why, she gave up everything
for that Scoundrel.
Well, what can you
expect? An italian.
He was after her
inheritance. I said so.
Poor woman.
On the contrary, Mrs. Foley.
My aunt had no regrets.
In fact, just before she died,
she told me it was a glorious year.
No matter what the price,
it was worth a lifetime.
Would you excuse me?
I have such a terrible headache.
Oh, poor lady.
Let me help you to your room.
No, no, please. Please,
continue with your dinner.
Isabella, wait.
Go back to your dancing
partner, Mr. Park.
You're jealous.
Now you know how I feel.
You can imagine what's been
happening to me all these years.
Eddie Paradine has everything
your family's ever wanted for you--
money and a pedigree.
He's a kind man,
a gentleman, a good husband.
Oh, your marriage must
have pleased your father
and your mother.
My parents are both dead now,
and the past is the past,
irretrievable.
It's been with me every
moment of every day.
Don't you think it's
been the same for me?
Oh, Bella.
Oh, Bella...
I'm married, Wynn.
I never expected to see you again.
You broke my heart.
What do you think of me brood?
Nice children.
Nice wife, too.
I wouldn't be much without 'em.
You planning to have pups yourself?
Ha! Me? No. No, no.
I wouldn't be so good at it,
uh, raising pups, I mean.
Damn!
"Crew only."
There has to be another way up.
I might as well be in prison.
What's out there, Mr. Boxhall?
Looks like a freighter.
Yes, sir.
The Rappahannock
on opposite course.
She's morseing us.
She's warning us of icebergs
and heavy ice pack ahead.
Where are the other Binoculars?
They only gave us one
pair for the bridge.
Mr. Boxhall, I will not
have my officers
passing around one
bloody pair of glasses.
Now take the ones
from the crow's nest.
The lookouts won't like this.
I'm not concerned
with what they like.
They'll manage well enough
until we reach New York.
J.J., you sure you won't
join us for another hand?
No, no.
Nightcap and then to bed.
I promised my wife.
I forgot. You're a Newlywed.
What's the matter,
never seen a woman
smoke a cigar before?
Well, no.
I mean, not a lady, anyway.
Not like you.
Well, get used to it.
Woman's emancipation.
We can smoke cigars.
We can tell you men
how to run the world.
Hell, we'll probably
have a woman president
in the next 100 years.
Unfortunately,
I don't think I'll be
around to see that.
Well, I hope I won't.
Can I buy you another drink?
Some brew on me.
Whatever he's drinking.
I come into a bit
of money recently.
I'll share my good fortune.
Well, thank you, young man.
You, uh, down in your cups?
You might say that.
I've remarried recently.
Hmm. Well, that'll do it.
Ha ha! No, no.
I'm happily married.
I'm only worried
about the reception
my new wife received
tonight in the dining room.
She's very young.
People can be cruel.
Yeah, well...
bunch of stiffs,
full of themselves
and all their money.
Mmm.
Some tugboat, eh?
Yes. It's a thing of beauty.
Have you been to America before?
No. No. Looking forward to it.
Yeah, I might go into
a bit of business.
You ever hear of this chap
called, um, Mack Sennett?
Got hisself a moving-picture company.
Calls it keystone.
Up-and-coming sort of thing.
Let me give you a bit of advice.
I always find investors
for my projects.
It's better to use another
fellow's money.
Yeah. Well said.
I can drink to that.
I believe in using the
other fellow's money, too.
Actually, I'm thinking
more about, um...
acting in the keystone company.
Might do a bit of shakespeare.
Well, I'm sure you'll
do well in America,
Whatever you decide at,
young fellow like yourself.
Yeah, well, nice to meet you.
Oh!
Clumsy.
So sorry.
My wife will think I'm a sot.
I'll have this cleaned for you.
I've got connections
in the laundry.
Don't worry about it.
Good evening to you,
and I will watch for you
in the moving pictures.
Another brandy, man,
and make it a double.
Yes, sir.
[ moaning ]
[ baby crying ]
No!
[ moaning ]
Alice, wake up.
You're having a nightmare.
My baby.
He was dead in the water.
Dead.
It's only a dream, Alice.
You don't have a baby, Alice.
That's right, Lorraine.
Now go back to sleep.
Mummy's here, sweetness.
We don't want to
frighten the children,
now, do we?
The ice. There was
ice and a shipwreck,
and he was out there
in the freezing water.
Oh, dear, now. The baby.
Alice, please.
Shh. There now, honey.
Oh. Shh.
What is it?
A bad dream, appearently.
She's very...
nervous.
His night garment's on backwards.
We stop at Queenstown tomorrow.
I think it's best for all of us
if Alice gets off there, in Ireland.
My baby.
My poor little baby.
Are you lost, Mr. Dickie?
Oh... you.
Look, I know I'm not
supposed to be up here,
but an acquaintance of mine
invited me up for a drink.
Oh, son, let me give you
a piece of advice.
Take it from your old da.
You're holding
Mr. John Jacob Astor's Billfold.
I saw you life it in the bar.
You didn't realize that,
now, did you, Mr. Dickie?
John Jacob Astor?
I don't know what
you're talking about.
I'm trying to be
your friend here, son.
Everybody needs a friend.
I told you--
You put the bit on
the great man hisself.
I just want to keep you
out of trouble, that's all.
A nice young chap like you.
There's a good boy.
The best.
You don't want to get
caught on your first night out
stealing Billfolds,
especially one
belonging to Mr. Astor.
It's all there.
I'll tell him I found it
laying on the floor
by the bar.
Must have dropped it, eh?
You're not going to report me?
Of course not.
I helped you before, didn't I?
The time to be picking Billfolds
is the last night out.
Men get all their moola
out of the safe.
Now, I'm sure we can
work out something
that'll be good for the both of us.
You're a talented lad, you are.
I could see that right away.
Quick and slick with
your hands, you are.
What's your name, son?
Your real name.
Well, it don't really
matter now, does it?
Don't be so prickly.
I can't help if I worry a bit
about the real Mr. Merriam Dickie.
You didn't ax the fellow, did you?
Of course not.
He passed out... drunk.
[ laughing ]
Drunk as a skunk, eh, Dickie?
I can see you and I
are going to get along really well.
[ laughing ]
All passengers
disembarking in Ireland
must proceed to the boat deck.
We have landed in Queenstown.
ALICE: Please, sir!
No! Don't make me go.
I beg you.
You've been fairly treated.
I've given you plenty of money
for your boat fare back to England.
Oh, you're kind people,
you have to understand.
I'm just a young girl
alone in the world.
Please, Miss, you've upset my wife.
All this talk about your baby.
I couldn't help it.
See, I had a baby what died.
Your baby died?
Where's your husband?
There's no husband, sir.
Anyway, he ran off.
I can't go back to England.
Don't cry. Here.
Will you promise to keep
these things to yourself?
It would only upset my wife.
Yes, sir,
I promise.
It would also help
if you could get through
the children's supper
wihtout spilling soup.
Well, I'm nervous,
but I'll do better now.
If I give you this chance,
you won't let me down?
My word, sir.
I give you my word.
And I thank you
for the opportunity
to stay on this ship.
I do, sir.
I thank my lucky stars.
Hello and goodbye to Ireland.
The emerald isle,
so green and beautiful.
Makes me wonder if I
should just stop here.
Close to home--
is that what you're thinking?
No. I try not to think of them--
my mother,
my little brother and sisters.
Their life is so hard.
I try to think of the future only,
like you.
No. No, not like me.
You don't want to be like me.
Anyway, you'll send for
your family someday.
Yes. How do you know that?
You don't know me.
Well, I know that you're good,
a good person.
Maybe the only good
person I've ever known.
[ morse code signal beeping ]
So, uh...
which is which, then, eh?
Oh. Green's where I've been.
Yellow's where I want to go.
Right. You know, uh, Phillips,
you're probably the only bloke
that took the ad seriously.
"Join the Marconi company
see the world."
Hey, well, here we are.
Yeah, like hell. See the world?
How are we suppose to
see the world, Phillips,
stuck in this bloody Brom closet?
Wynn Park.
I'm expecting a Marconi-Gram.
Oh, yes, sir, Mr. Park.
There's so many messages
coming and going.
There we are.
There you are, sir.
I'll be expecting several others.
I'd like them delivered immediately.
Right, sir.
Smooth sailing all the way.
I hope so.
Hoo.
Cheers, governor.
It's a double eagle.
It's a $20 piece.
Look at that.
Tin mines.
Didn't that wire say tin mines?
Uh-huh. You split that with me?
Right.
- Ahh.
- Oh-ho-ho.
Hey?
"Please forgive me. I was a bore."
Oh, Wynn.
A red dress?
Do you see that, a red dress?
It can't be. She's in mourning.
She appears to have recovered.
Pomme Duchesse.
Where I come from,
we call a spud a spud.
she's not sittng here.
I won't have it.
This is a disgrace.
Hazel.
It's only been a few months
since her Aunt Grace passed away.
She ought to show some respect,
even though her aunt was... fast.
Mrs. Paradine.
You feeling better?
I am, Mr. Ismay, thank you.
I feel queasy.
Mr. Park?
Oh, he had urgent business.
I understand the
Bolivian government
has given him permission
to open some tin mines.
That's dangerous.
That-- that Zapata fellow.
That's Mexico, my dear.
It's the same thing.
Oh, here he is.
I knew he wouldn't disappoint us.
Evening. I'm sorry I'm late.
So, it's mining, is it?
Takes perseverance.
Me and my man, we never
gave up when others did.
Our little Johnny mine
turned out to be
the richest gold vein in the world.
Of course, it didn't
exactly buy us happiness.
Well, money doesn't always
get us what we want.
You unlucky in love, Mr. Park?
My family tree is missing
a few branches.
I set out to prove to
a young lady's parents
that I was worthy of her,
and she married someone else.
Mr. Park, you could have
any woman in the world.
Except the one I want.
You'll be going there,
Mr. Park, to Bolivia?
Yes.
As soon as we land in New York.
Oh, you can come to
our Lulu's birthday party.
I mean, one little week.
The Bolivian government can wait.
[ orchestra playing a tango ]
Mrs. Paradine.
Will you tango?
I thought you'd never ask, Mr. Park.
My dear...
are you forgetting?
You are in mourning.
I've mourned enough.
Oh, my. I feel absolutely faint.
Dancing the tango?
We haven't even finished
the first course.
They're just skipping to dessert.
My.
[ music ends ]
[ knock on door ]
Wynn-- oh.
I beg your pardon, ma'am?
Excuse me, I thought Mr. Par--
Oh, I believe he went up
for an early breakfast.
Mrs. Paradine, I have
wonderful news for you.
I have managed to convince
the Countess of Rothes
that she absolutely must
take this stateroom.
Her servants have
packed all her things,
so, here I am ready to move you.
Move me?
Well, you weren't happy in this suite,
and it's my job to make you happy.
Ah, yes, well,
that won't be necessary.
I'm quite happy here now.
Yes, but I've arranged for it.
The Countess of Rothes--
it took a great deal of maneuvering.
I-- I've changed my mind.
I'm completely comfortable here.
Thank you.
Yes, but what do I tell
the Countess of Rothes?
MAN: Very smooth.
I slept like a baby last night.
Excuse me.
Bad news, Captain?
Um, no, Mr. Strauss,
just, uh...
Routine.
You and Mrs. Strauss
enjoy your breakfast.
CAPTAIN: Mr. Ismay.
Ah, yes, what is it?
A message from the ship Baltic
regarding ice conditions.
I'm told that you've been
discussing operation of the ship
with my crew.
Yes, with regard to our speed.
It's certainly within my
prepogative as chairman.
Things are running smoothly--
the machinery is bearing the test,
the boilers are running well.
The ship is steady,
and with power to spare.
We can beat the olympic's record
and be in New York on Tuesday.
I see absolutely no purpose
in arriving a day early.
Yes, and I see no
purpose in meandering,
keeping to a schedule
devised for inferior vessels.
But there are basic...
safety procedures nonetheless.
I want this ship to perform
to its full potential.
Well...
in future, if there's any discussion
about the operation of this ship,
it must be cleared with me first.
This may be my last crossing...
but I am still the captain.
Wynn?
Good morning.
You couldn't sleep?
No.
Me, neither.
And I was up thinking about you--
your life...
and your daughter...
Claire.
She's such a tomboy.
Hates fancy clothers.
She's very bright, curious.
She loves dogs.
She loves horses. She rides
for hours with her father.
What are we going to do?
All those years I've
wondered about you--
where you were and
what you were doing.
And now you're here.
With you.
For 4 days.
[ footsteps and children's voices ]
You're it! Ha!
Oh.
Osa, what you going
to do in America?
I'm going to Minnesota
with the other converts
to build a new life.
Oh, I want to do good in
this world, Mr. Dickie.
Do good?
I want to be a teacher or a nurse,
have children of my own.
And raise them to be good souls
and to help their fellow man,
like Mrs. Jack teaches her children.
Oh, the Jacks have been so kind to me.
What's your dream?
My dream?
Yeah.
You have a dream.
I can see it in your eyes.
You know something, Osa?
I do have a dream.
Have you ever seen one
of those moving pictures?
Moving pictures?
Yeah. I saw one at a
carnival peep show once.
I put my eye to the hole in the box,
and there was people in there--
moving.
Oh, I mean, they wasn't
really in there,
but it was like they was.
There was this beauty,
Mary Pickford.
That's my dream.
Mary Pickford?
No, no, not her.
I mean, my dream is
to be a part of it,
part of the moving pictures.
Well...
then you must work for
it and make it happen.
No, stupid pipe dream.
Anyway...
you could be in
the moving pictures.
I mean, you're-- you're much
prettier than Mary Pickford.
Well...
moving pictures sound nice,
but I'm not looking
for pictures in a box.
What you looking for?
God.
CHILD: Osa, Osa.
CHILD 2: Can't catch us.
CAPTAIN: They say we're at
the dawn of a new age.
The fires below are sending
50,000 horsepower to the propellers.
Who knows what kind of progress
we'll see in the next 100 years?
Soon we'll be flying across
the Atlantic in airplanes.
But nothing will ever
be like this again--
Nothing like the Titanic,
a boat this big and powerful...
and so beautiful.
There's a rumor we'll be
landing a day early.
Only rumors.
Captain Smith...
could we bribe you
to take your time,
to meander off course a little?
I know what you mean.
I suppose I will miss all of this.
There's a magic to it.
I enjoy it most right here
behind the wheel.
It's almost sacred.
May I steer it?
Oh, you're right.
It is magical.
I can feel the power
beneath my feet.
Are you sure that you
know the way to New York?
Ha ha! No, I don't.
Maybe I'll just turn it
around and go back to England.
How does that sound?
It's not fair.
She's a married lady.
Well, what do you expect?
A man loses his head
when a woman throws herself at him.
But he danced with me.
Well, it wouldn't have hurt for
you to throw yourself a little, Lulu.
Get your shoulders back.
You're going to get a hump.
[ Orchestra playing ]
Most of them don't bother to
leave their jewels with the purser.
They want to wear them.
Come on...
I'll show you.
Hey.
Room service.
WOMAN: Wrong room.
What did I tell you?
[ laughs ]
Wait, wait, wait.
Lookie here.
What do you say?
A diamond tiara.
Go ahead.
Try it on for size.
Shh, shh, shh, shh.
We case out all the staterooms,
find out where they keep them,
and, then, on the last night out...
We strike.
That's right, my friend.
There'll be confusion in the morning.
How do we get it off the boat?
The loot never leaves the ship.
Mr. Astor's loo.
In the plumbing.
We lay low and go about our business
until the ship is fitted out,
ready to sail again.
I've got a plumber friend here.
He's agreed to carry it
all off in his tool kit.
I don't know.
You don't know what?
Well, how do I trust you?
[ chuckles ]
Is that my buddy?
Trust me?
How do you know
I wouldn't turn you in this minute
if I got the urge?
Hey, don't try to blackmail me.
I could tell 'em a few things meself.
I've worked for the white
star line for 12 years.
I'm a trusted employee.
Who do you think they're
going to believe--
me...
or Mr. Dickie,
who isn't Mr. Dickie at all?
[ woman laughs ]
Come on, boy.
Better get out of here.
The tiara.
Oh, God.
What if--
Shh.
WOMAN: I was playing the piano.
[ whispering ] Not a word.
I was watching you from the
hallway, waiting for your father.
Wrong door.
Yes, wrong door.
It's the next one.
I've never been in such
a grand house before,
and there you were-- you were--
you were playing the piano.
Chopin.
I didn't know what it was.
I only knew it was the
most beautiful music.
And the sun was coming
through the windows,
and everything was golden,
and the sun and you...
the dress.
Dressing gown--
and it was yellow, it wasn't golden.
Anyway, the door was
supposed to have been closed.
[ woman clears throat ]
MAN: Oh, yes.
MAN: There we are.
[ drops keys ]
[ laughing ]
The lady lost her key.
It was see-through,
your dressing gown.
It was not.
Yes, it was. When you stood up,
I could see you through it.
I thought I was going to die.
We found your room.
Mm-hmm.
Well?
Can you get the key in the lock?
Can you?
I'm trying.
Can you get the key
in the lock? Can you?
Hurry up, son.
It's not good to be
seen up here together.
All right.
Mr. Dickie...
we're going to make a killing.
[ giggles ]
Look at you.
Where have you been?
Eh, first class,
Hobobbing with the rick folk.
A real dandy, all right.
If only Mary Pickle
could see you now.
Pickford. Mary Pickford.
You look beautiful.
But, Osa, men aren't
supposed to look beautiful.
Why?
Take me word. I'm not
beautiful, not in any way.
You are beautiful to me.
I don't know,
maybe something has rubbed
off of you and onto me.
Ohh...
I didn't want to remember this.
[ scottish accent ] She's a
thoroughbred, Mr. Lightoller.
I'd swear there was a boat
drill scheduled for this morning.
Well, if I know the captain,
we'll skip it.
Some fool's gone and set it
for the same time as
the Sunday service,
and the captain surely
won't miss saying devotions.
MAN: Chief Bell!
Hear, Mr. Chairman.
Don't look so shocked,
Mr. Lightoller.
I frequently check in the boiler rooms.
Tell me, uh...
How many boilers are currently lit?
24 of the 29 are in service.
That's, uh, 80%, is it?
84, and the propellers are
at 75 revolutions per minute.
And our speed?
21 1/2 knots, sir.
Have the men light 2 additional boilers.
I have no order from the captain.
You have my orders, Chief.
I want us at 22 1/2 knots by noon.
Carry on.
Mmm...
Oh.
[ chuckles ]
Oh. What day is this?
Sunday.
Everyone's at church
service except us.
We're the sinners.
Mmm...
You knew I was sailing
on the Titanic, didn't you?
Yes.
It wasn't fate at all.
You planned it that way.
Yes.
But it isn't enough.
God, I want to be with you always.
Come to Bolivia.
Oh, I--
I know I have no right
to ask, but come with me.
- Wynn...
- Come with me.
I don't know.
I just don't know.
Does it have to end?
Ohh...
They that go down to the sea in ships
and do business in the great waters,
they cry out to the Lord...
in their trouble,
and he bringeth them
out of their distresses.
In Psalms 107, verse 29,
"He maketh the storm a calm..."
"so that the waves
there of... are stilled."
"So he bringeth them
unto their desired haven."
- That girl sets my hair on end.
- Shh!
Amen.
ALL: Amen.
[ tapping morse code ]
[ beeping ]
Got the messauber here.
She's reporting
heavy pack ice ahead.
Large bergs...
and field ice.
Huh.
Right. Well, uh, I'll
run it up to the bridge.
Actually, not now.
It's 20 minutes to 5:00.
Let's clear through some
of this backlog first, eh?
Right. Fine.
[ piano playing ]
You know, you must come visit
me sometime in Denver, Captain.
I'm-- I'm having' a
huge party in June.
Well, I expect that in June
I shall be in Hampstead
making up for all the
gardening I've been missing
for the last 40 years.
I'd... like to spend a little time
with my wife and daughter.
Oh...
Lovely.
I understand.
My husband J.J. is
ambitious and-- and smart.
But he's more comportable
in Leadville.
Myself... I want to be more civilized.
I guess that's why we've
gone our separate ways.
Tell me something, Captain Smith.
Won't you miss the sea?
I suppose I shall.
But just between you and me,
sometimes being on a ship
is like being in jail...
with the possibility of drowning.
- Ha ha ha!
Well, you've just got 3 more days.
Yes, only 3 more days
Then you're a free man.
Lorraine, don't run. You're spill it.
Whoop!
What's going on here?
Now, look what a mess you made.
You seem to have your
hands full. I'm Marge Miller.
What's your name?
Her name is Alice.
Lorraine. Shh!
Now, come along.
Bye.
Mrs. Paradine.
Oh, hello.
You look happy.
I am.
I think I am.
Mrs. Astor--
Oh, please call me Madeleine.
Madeleine, may I talk to you?
I feel like I'm going to burst.
Of course.
Shall we?
What was it like when
Mr. Astor got his divorce?
It was painful.
For everyone.
I felt terribly guilty.
But we've embarked
on a new adventure.
I try not to look back.
Are you... contemplating divorce?
I have a young daughter.
I could never leave my daughter.
Oh, but surely you could arrange
something with your husband.
He would never let her go.
I couldn't hurt him, either.
In a way, I feel indebted to him.
He helped me at a
terrible time in my life.
He was-- he was my knight
in shining armor.
You're in love with
Mr. Park, aren't you?
Yes.
I have loved him for many years.
These things seem like
they can never work out,
but somehow they do.
Life is so short, Isabella.
There's hardly any time, is there?
Anything important?
Another ice warning, sir.
It's from the Coronia.
Hmm. Post the coordinates.
I will, sir.
Remarkably cold tonight, is it not?
Yes, it is.
I've sent word to take care
with the fresh water supply.
It'll be below freezing
during the night.
Not much wind.
A flat calm.
In 24 years, I've never
seen so calm a sea.
Hmm.
"Low, low..."
"Breathe and blow,
"wind from the western sea.
"Over the rolling waters go,
"come from the dying moon...
and blow."
Sir.
Upon my word, I have
not thought of that verse
since I was a cabin boy.
Love of the ocean brought
me to the sea as a lad,
and there's still...
wonder in it.
Ah...
Are we not a bit fast?
Uh, Mr. Ismay, sir.
He seems intent on breaking records.
He was in the boiler room today.
I'm going below. Keep sharp.
The first sign of any... haziness,
we'll need to slow down.
I'll deal with Mr. Ismay
in the morning.
Yes, sir.
Captain Moore...
white patches ahead.
That'll mean ice.
Stop the engines!
Stop down the boilers!
Go into position for the night!
[ bell clangs ]
[ lively music ]
Dance with us!
- Come on, dance!
- Dance!
Come on. The children are
saying for you to dance!
Come on, boy!
No shame in having some joy.
No, no. I-- I don't know how.
I'll show you.
Right now upstairs
the wine is flowing,
and the jewels are sparkling.
The stars are jewels.
We're all the same under the stars.
I'd get them for you if I could.
All them stars.
There's so much out there
just waiting for us to scoop it up.
I promised you a tiara,
and Jamie Purse is
gonna get you one.
Who is Jamie Purse?
Oh... yeah.
I forgot.
Um...
Jamie Purse is my real name.
But... Mr. Dickie?
Uh, that was...
just the name on the ticket.
How did you get the ticket?
You're not a thief.
Um... fact is, I-- I found it.
You're right.
I'm not a thief.
I just seized the opportunity.
If you'll excuse me...
I don't mean to interrupt, madam,
but, uh, me and Mr. Dickie
have an appointment
with the ship's purser.
I got to go.
The purser.
Don't go with him.
I have to.
Haven't you ever had to do things...
been forced to do things?
I try to stay true to myself,
if that is what you mean.
You're so bloody good.
Always on the straight and narrow.
Well, that's not the way
the world works.
Look, maybe I'm not so great,
but I can change.
I wouldn't mind a
piece of her myself.
You want to get
smashed in the face?
You do, and you'll end up
in the ship's brig,
you silly bugger.
Now... I'm having a jar
with the purser in his office.
Perfect time for you to life
the key out of his pocket.
Magic hands like yours...
no problem.
Understand?
All right!
You just stay away from her.
You hear me?
She's too good for the likes of you.
[ snickering ]
And me.
[ bell clangs 4 times ]
4 bells.
10:00.
Ocean's as smooth as a mill pond.
Water's like oil.
I was saying the same
to the captain.
He left word to be called
if conditions become doubtful.
Good night, Mr. Murdock.
Yes. Right.
Good night, Mr. Lightoller.
It's cold out tonight.
Aye. By the smell of it,
there's ice about.
You smell it before you get to it.
Of course, I wouldn't
tell the Bigwigs that.
They think you're stupid.
But you know what I say.
We're the eyes of this here ship.
Well, don't expect no respect.
What I expect is
some proper glasses.
I've got good eyesight,
but I can't see in the dark.
Well, I asked again just tonight.
They would like to
have bit me head off.
I'm through with the bloomin' sea.
After this one, I'll go back home,
make an honest woman of me Linda.
There's a ship.
Off the southeast.
That looks like a big passenger liner,
maybe 10 miles away.
No.
She's something like ourselves--
a small freighter.
Not that far.
Any other ships in the vicinity?
The closest one's the, uh, Titanic.
Can't be the Titanic.
She's closer to us in size.
That must be a freighter...
or a fishing boat.
Maybe.
Have evans radio the Titanic.
Tell them we've stopped
for the night...
surrounded by ice.
Yes, sir.
Phillips.
I'll never get through all these.
Yes, ma'am?
I wish to send a wire.
Right, then.
Address at the top.
My husband is at
our home on the Hudson.
This has to go out immediately.
Do you understand?
Yes, ma'am. The thing of it is--
We're bogged down here right now.
The wireless broke down last night
and wasn't back in commission
until 5:00 this morning.
We've got quite a backlog, ma'am.
Please. This has to
go out immediately.
You have to send it
right away before I...
Before, ma'am?
Before I lose my strength.
Before I change my mind.
Please, just send it.
Well, uh, don't worry, ma'am.
It's very urgent.
Promise me.
We'll do the best we can, eh?
[ whistles ]
Some bloody bloke's going
to get the shock of his life.
[ incoming telegraph ]
Shut up.
Shut up. You're jamming me.
Damn freighter Californian.
Stopped for the night
on account of ice.
They keep interrupting.
Bloody Titanic wants me to shut up?
Well, the same to you, Bucko.
I can't get
Mrs. Paradine's message out.
Poor lady.
Can I offer you a fag, chief?
Aye, thanks, Jack.
It's me prize.
Tobaccy from the East Indies.
Keeps it next to me heart.
It's me treasure.
Ow. That hurt.
Are there really angels, Mama?
Of course there are angels...
watching over you and your
sister and your brothers.
Over all of us.
And over this ship to
make sure we're safe.
Ohh, you're a mass of snarls,
Miss Ophelia Jack.
You need one of them angels
down here to brush it out.
It doesn't look right,
young girl like you alone in the world
talking to that Hooligan.
We are all God's children.
You said so yourself.
Chap like that cause
you nothing but pain.
There. Here we are.
You're almost an angel yourself.
We're off to bed now, Osa.
Sweet dreams, Osa.
Sweet dreams.
You say your prayers, Osa.
God will keep you from harm.
And all the angels, too, Mama.
And all the angels, too.
Hello, miss.
What- what? No! What are you--
Your boyfriend's not around
to protect you, right?
Let me go!
No!
I beg you. Let me go.
Aah!
You're a piece, you are.
I had my eye on you from the start.
Let me go! Let me go!
You're going nowhere.
I knew from the first
time I laid eyes on you
that you were no saint.
22 1/2 knots.
What are we doing?
It's not a race.
We have our orders, Mr. Boxhall.
Hope Mr. Astor won't be
playing cards too late.
I hate to go to bed alone.
I put a nice warm bottle
under the covers, ma'am.
It'll be very comfy.
Finished?
Mm-hmm.
I was talking to the Allisons' nanny.
Such a strange bird, she is.
I've been racking my brain
trying to remember
where I know here from.
Her name is Alice.
That's what the little girl said.
Alice.
Oh, Mrs. Astor, I must
go get your husband.
It just came to me.
Alice Cleaver, that's who she is.
What are you talking about?
Um, nothing.
Nothing that concerns you.
Who is Alice Cleaver?
Not in your condition.
I'll speak with Mr. Astor.
He'll know what's do be done.
You boys keep playing like this,
you're going to pay for my trip.
[ laughing ]
And tomorrow night, poker.
You must excuse me
for just a moment.
We'll wait.
He's the one with the money.
Is something wrong with my wife?
Oh, no, no. She's safe in bed.
Well, what is it, then?
You must go have a word
with Mr. Allison, sir.
You must warn him.
What are you babbling about?
The nanny. I recognize her, sir.
Alice Cleaver.
She was convicted about 3 years ago
for... for murdering her baby.
Where did you hear all this rubbish?
It was in the paper.
They let her out of prison.
Said she was deranged at the time
on account of the baby's
father deserting her.
They granted her leniency,
which is no excuse if you ask me.
Her little child--
It's after 11:00.
I can't go wake them up now.
But she's in charge of
the Allison children, sir,
and she's a murderer.
Perhaps you're mistaken.
At any rate,
nothing will happen tonight.
I will talk with
Mr. Allison in the morning.
I'm sure he won't mind
your waking him up
under the circumstances.
In the morning, Miss Miller.
I will speak with
Mr. Allison in the morning.
But she--
she threw him from a train.
Her baby boy.
A touch of haze on the horizon.
There's ice ahead!
Is someone there?
Yes. What do you see?
Ice! Dead ahead!
A berg less than a mile away!
Thank you.
Iceberg right ahead.
Hard astarboard, Mr. Hitchens.
Hard astarboard.
Helm is hard over, sir.
Full speed astern!
Turn!
[ bell rings ]
There's an iceberg ahead.
Come on.
Turn, you whore, turn.
What's taking her so long?
Turn!
We're going to hit the bloody thing!
We hit it, man!
Oh, no! We're dead!
[ gasps ]
What was that?
I think we hit something.
It felt like a hit.
Hey! What's happening?
[ alarm blares ]
Close the damps now.
Move, quickly!
We can't allow water into the boiler!
Aah!
I'm, uh, I'm closing
the watertight doors.
Note the time and enter it into the log.
Clear the bolts from the door!
Heave!
Shut down the boiler!
OFFICER: Captain on the bridge.
We've struck something,
Mr. Murdock?
An iceberg, sir.
I hard astarboarded and
ran the engines full astern,
but it was too close.
I'm afraid she's hit it.
Dearest God.
I closed the watertight doors,
rung the warning bell.
Sir, do you hear me?
Impossible.
This cannot have happened.
Do you hear what they're saying?
We hit an iceberg.
That grinding noise we heard?
Perhaps we lost a propeller.
Good.
It gives us more time for bridge.
The boat's stopped cold.
Ah, a few hours, we'll be
back on our way again.
Anybody want a souvenir?
Isabella.
Did you see it, the iceberg?
I've done a terrible thing.
What?
I sent Eddie a wireless.
Yes?
I can't give you up.
I won't.
I've told him all about us,
and I've told him I'm going
to Bolivia with you.
Bella...
Oh, Bella.
All right.
Calm down.
Show's over, folks.
Come on, let's get back
to our bridge game.
After all, this tin tub's unsinkable.
[ crystal shatters ]