THE SECRET OF MOONACRE
Colonel George Herbert Merryweather...
...ashes to ashes...
...dust to dust...
[IN MEMORY OF ELIZA JANE MERRYWEATHER]
...Aah, Miss Merryweather...
This being the last will and testament of
Colonel George Herbert Merryweather of London.
...he...he...lost it all?
... including the house?
No!
...No, Papa can't have been in London...
...why, he wrote to me and said that
he was coming home,
he wouldn't arrive and not...
...Aah, well...
Your father did leave you this book...
...as your inheritance...
"The Ancient Chronicle of Moonacre Valley"
I know it is hard...
but you know I... I'm sure that your father did ...
...did love you...
...he just... um,
...and...and you know, everybody does have to go out on their own at some point in their ...
...lifes.
Miss Heliotrop, I'm fine!
Really!
Yes...
"Once upon a perfect time...
...many hundred's of years ago...
...when the old magic called Moonacre Valley...
... there was a young woman whose skin glint as pale as the star...
...and whose heart was as pure as a meteorite's...
...such was her bravery and goodness...
...she was beloved by nature ...
...as if she was their daughter...
...one fateful night...
...the moon blessed her,
with an extraordinary gift...
...with a tinge of the magic of the valley...
...forever!
The moon power!
...from that day forward...
...she was known...
...as the Moon Princess!
Two ancient families lived in harmony at the edge of the valley.
Sharing nature's bounty.
Daughter to the De Noir clan ...
... the Moon Princess,was deeply in love and was to be marry to Sir Wolf Merryweather.
Her father...
...Sir William De Noir...
...blessed the union by presenting the couple with a rare black lion.
For my daughter's bridegroom!
Thank you, father!
In turn, Sir Wolf gave his bride a unicorn.
Litter from the wild white horses of the sea.
Only an animal of such beauty and purity,could be the companion of the Moon Princess.
Her heart overflowing with happiness!
The Moon Princess revealed the magical power's to both families...
This was found deep in the heart of the ocean...
This pearl was given to us...
... by mother nature herself!
Promising untold riches to us all...
...look!
They have a unique power!
They can revealed the truth...
... in man's heart!
Legend told of their unique powers'...
.. so strong the pearls will grant every wish.
Both good and evil!
Good bye...
You be Miss Maria Merryweather then?!
My man?
Quick!
Madame...
Get on with you!
Good bye...
...yes, yes, yes...
Miss Heliotrop?
Maria...
When your dear mother died...
I promised her faithfully that I'll take care of you...
... so I'm not going to abandon you now!
If you're going to live with your uncle...
or in the middle of the country-side...
... then I shall be there with you.
Where are my charcoal tablets?
All these're doing nothing for my indigestion ....
How can I possibly go live in the country?
It's like a camp-site!
Maria...there's only one thing that can save us now.
Clever girl...
French...
...needles point.
What's happening?
Have we arrive?
Is he deaf or something?
The man obviously a half wit.
Who are they?
What do they want?
Don't worry, my dear...
... Sir Benjamin will protect us, I'm sure!
Miss...
Welcome to Moonacre!
Unfortunate circumstances...
There we are...nothing to be done...
I'm pleased to meet you, uncle ...
Miss Heliotrop...
Oh...Sir Benjamin...
Oh... what a journey we had!!!
Not one hour from this very door we were accosted by...
.. a bunch of ruffians...
-Madame, please!
-It...
Tell me your fascinating story some other time if I may...
His name is Wrolf.
There are those who find him alarming...
He can killed in an instant.
But you're a Merryweather.
He very probably won't harm you.
Miss Heliotrop, your room is over there to the right...
Oh...thank you, Sir Benjamin.
Well, come along Maria.
I'm sure that your room... will be next to mine...
No, Maria's room is up in the tower.
But...I'm kind...
Have to let you inspect the room first before you turn your nose at whatever it is.
Good night, uncle!
Charmed, I'm sure...
What on earth is this?
Oh, no!
...no, I think not...
Young lady...
We're taking breakfast in here...
Where did you get this from?
Oh... um, papa left it to me...
Well, he've no right to...
This belong here.
But... that's mine!!
Miss Heliotrop!
Help!
Help, tell him he can't take my father book from me!
Maria!
Good question!
Why don't you just speak...
That he can't just go and...
Maria!
Don't worry.
I'm sure that he's just keeping it safe somewhere for you .
Sit down. Have your porridge.
Miss...
There be your breakfast, Miss...
Maria, you really must try this delicious aumelette.
Hum...um... a dish best enjoy in silence, I'm told.
Uncle, when can you return my father book to me?
Now...
You certainly have a very, very good cook, Sir Benjamin.
Have you... have you had her long?
Madame... no woman have settled in this house for years !
And believe me the silence has been blissful.
Now... I must say...this country food is
doing wonder for my trapped wind!
Madame, please... can't a man enjoy
a meal in his own home in silence.
Well, do tell us uncle...
Why did you invite such irritating and noisy females...
...into your nice quiet house?
I love to know.
My useless brother dies in debt
and it fall on me to take you in.
The man was a... cowardly
good for nothing.
Sir Benjamin!!
How dare you say that?
My father was a Colonel!
Yes.
And he died in debt owing money
to half the regiment.
He fought for his country!
And got himself killed in a backstreet gambling den.
Borrowed money once too many times
from the wrong sort of money lenders.
He wouldn't take money from me, would he?
Oh no...
Damn, all his pride...
You're a Merryweather, Maria...
And this is where you belong.
Here, at Moonacre.
There we are...
Nothing else to be done.
Library private and my study-prohibited.
...and in here...
...the East wing, closed...
...the West wing, out of bound...
There we are...
-And here..
-Uncle, about that attack yesterday...
Can't something be done?
Yes... keep your little nose out.
I beg your pardon?
Just keep out of the forest.
But why? Who are they?
They're a band of ruffians in the woods.
The De Noir clan.
You mean like the "De Noir" from the story book?
No, no, no... these're real enough.
Poachers, bandits, plunderers, robbers...
Ladies...
This should suits your need.
And these will be your classroom.
(Speaking French)
Digweed...
Bring me my whip.
You weren't expecting me to...
She can't ride, can she?
Oh... Sir Benjamin, it's a matter of fact that a lady should never be allow to sit on a horse!
...they're unstable and they're vicious creatures...
I think Sir Benjamin it might be a
approciate moment for me to retire.
Take care!
Come...Maria...
Every Merryweather ride.
It's in the blood.
This is Peririco...she's a little feisty but she's a loyal stead.
Just hold out your hand...
I give you my words...
It'll stay attach to you, Miss....
You see, Miss?
She knows...
-You're getting on well with Peririco...
-Yes, uncle.
We should be heading back.
It's getting late.
Uncle, I'm really enjoying this.
Could I stay out a little longer?
As long as you promise to stay within the Moonacre boundary.
Remember...
I can only vouch for your safety if you stayed out of the forest.
I could be home before long...
And Peririco will take good care of me.
Very well.
Goodbye uncle!
What's so special about the forest anyway?
You stay here.
...oh, little baby...
Who did this to you?
One catch two captives.
What do you want?
Let's go. Catch an animal that comes that get you coming to help!
I know who you are!
You're bandits and plunderers!
You!
You're coming with us now!
My father's just dying to make your acquaintance.
It's the demon dog!
Thank you, you obedient doggy!
Come on, little one...
Let me take you home.
Robin, it's your father!
What did I do to deserve such a prize filth for a son?
I hope Peririco gave you an
educational tour of the estate.
I have a wounded hare ...
That young lady is a rare Moonacre rabbit.
By far the more beautiful, brave and serene creature.
And as you've brought her in from the wilds, she's now your responsibility.
And with your knowledge of animal, I very
much doubt it will live to see the morning.
Keep out of the forest child!
Maria?
Goodness gracious!
Look at your...
...dress!
Maria, there's something alive on your body!
Miss Heliotrop, please calm down!
This is a Moonacre rabbit ...
A beautiful, brave and serene creature.
I intend to look after it.
And I'm going to call her Serena.
Uncle?
I really think you and I have some matter to discuss.
There is some very strange things going on in this house...
First of, who always keep my dress and leave the biscuits in my room?
The stars on my ceiling moves.
There's a mysterious white horse outside...
This place is falling apart, things appear to move, the piano plays music on its own!
I mean I have never even seen the kitchen...
So where on earth does all this foods comes from?
Do you ever stop asking questions?
Uncle, I ...
Sit down, my dear...
Wrolf?
Where are we going?
Wrolf?!
Marmaduke Scarlet...chef of all chefs...
At your service, little Princess.
How do you do that?
Get me some sherbet, will you?
...chop, chop...
I'm not actually really sure where your sherbet is...
Never you mind...I'll get it...
Are you the one who leaves the milk and biscuits for me?
This past few days,
it all comes back to me.
Scarlet please, will you stop
yourself for just one moment?
Surely somebody in this household must be able to answer my questions.
Dear Princess, a little bit of magic...
...has come back to the valley.
You obviously haven't finish reading the book.
The book?
But my uncle took it away from me.
...in the library?
...you'll find a slim volumes,  secret doors and private lockers...
Perhaps a piece of...
Stargazer pie for your study.
[SECRET DOORS and PRIVATE LOCKERS]
The Moon Princess truly believe in the goodness of all...
But the men soon fail of the greed that was in their heart.
Each desperate to claim the power of the pearls for himself....
We are the chosen ones!
These pearls stay with the De Noir clan forever!
Father?
Come! Be with me.
Let Moonacre be your home and be your family.
Speak true!
WIth the power of these pearls I can claim the valley for myself.
...no...
Together...I mean together we could rule the valley..
These pearls belong's to no man...
...they belong's to nature!
Give it to me!!
No! Give them to me!!!
No no no!!!
I beg of you... please!!!
You cannot let your heart be rule by greed!
Betrayed by those she love the most...
The Moon Princess unleashed the power bestowed upon her ...
...and cast a terrifying curse over them all...
Hear me!!!!
You've go against the nature...
...you shall suffer for it!
Nature will wreak her revenge and put a curse upon this valley.
One day...
...a pure heart will walk among you...
...if she can't lift the curse...
...when the 5000 moon rises from the sea...
...this valley shall be plunge into eternal darkness!!!!
The moon pearls vanished that day...
...and where to find them remain a secret.
Marmaduke...the house...the valley...it's all...
Cursed!
Oh yes!
Take a look around you...
Everything's falling apart...
Ever since that terrible day...
...the two families have been totally consumed...
...with pride...
...and blind hatred.
And the only person who can break this curse...
... is a true Moon Princess!
The Moon Princess?
...but...
...she lives hundred of years ago.
The legend tells...of a little white horse...
A mystical companion to protect her...
...a magical creature...
Invisible so they say...to anyone...
...except a true Moon Princess.
You mean...
...I'm suppose to be this...
...I'm suppose to undo this curse?
Everyone knows the legend.
Peace will never be restored...
...until the pearls are return to the sea and the families reunited!
This is all madness!
Time is slipping away...
...5,000 moons...
...to set it right.
Stop! stop...I don't want to hear another word!
You are all insane!!
Three hundreds and eighty-four years...
...times thirteen for the moon's per annum.
...plus
....seven moons for this year...
that's...
that makes...
Four thousand nine hundred and ninety-nine.
Oh Serena, the very next moon arrival will be the 5,000 moons...
Everyone knows the legend...
These pearls belong's to no man...
They belong's to nature!
5,000 moons to set it right!!
You're a Merryweather...
You're the chosen one!
Keep out of the forest child.!
I've to get out of this remote place, Serena!
I don't want anything more to do with this!
Miss Heliotrope will take good care of you...
...Maria....
...Maria...
Who are you?
...you look...just like the lady in the painting...
Come along.
Oh, do come in!!
You naughty hedgehodge!
In my favourite chair again!
You cheeky monkey!
Be nice and still...
...don't make any sudden movement.
Then she won't be so scare!
I will try!
Oh! I was talking to the snake.
I rescued as many injured creatures as I can.
And do you the L embroide and brought all those strange dresses in my room?
Yes, I am.
My name is Loveday.
....our time is nearly spent right here....
the moon shall not be our forever.
You saw something, didn't you?
Didn't you? Tell me what you saw.
I've to leave!
No no no no...
Stay with me!
I've frightened you, haven't I?
You see, I'm not use to visitor.
And I do so much just want to be friend.
It's no use you know...your father...
...he tried to run away too.
But there is nowhere to hide.
He send you here because he loved you.
Because Moonacre is where you belong.
You and I are the same.
Except...
Except?
Where I failed you might succeed.
What about my uncle?
Sir Benjamin...can't he help?
Never, ever mention that man to me again, do you understand?
Your past is behing you...
Your future await you if you want it...
You decides.
I want to help...
I just don't know what I'm suppose to do to begin.
Find the pearls!
Noboby knows where they are.
Each family blames the other for taking them.
They are both to blame.
The De Noir took the casket then we must have the key...
The key!
Now for the casket...
You have to take me there.
-Where?
-To the De Noir...
You've to take me to where they live...
There it is!
Loveday...are you alright?
I'm sorry! I can never go back there!
Loveday!
Father, I could pad and place a scythe and nailed it under their roof.
Don't go near Moonacre...that house is damned!
No...the word is...
...she is about to meet her downfall.
How kind of you to join us, Moon Princess.
Oh...Oh, and what is this?
She has brought us the lost key, gentleman!
Wasn't it terrible of the De Noir to have the moon pearls hidden uphere all the time...haven't we?
Well, it's true isn't it?
Your ancestors stole them!
My ancestors?!
Well, perhaps Princess...
...I should introduce you...
Maria Merryweather...the last Moon Princess.
Sir William...
The very first De Noir...
The pearls casket!
And you so very kindly brought us the key.
You've hidden them!!
They were never there, girl!
Your filthy Merryweather family took them!
Before he...picked up the box!
They stole the pearls...
But soon...
...the final moon will rise...
...and the thieving Merryweather will be punished!
I'm glad that we have you here...
There's nothing anyone can do to stop it!
At last the entire valley will be ours!
And the De Noir, will finally feast upon revenge!!
Leave me alone, you ogre!
You know, for someone in your predicament, I admired your spirit!
Witch!
Hey! Lock her in!
Welcome to your new house!!
Hope you make friend with the roaches!
Guard, watch her...she's slippery.
Where is that girl?
Unbelievable!
Absolutely irresponsible!
Oh, this dress...
Come back here, you witch!!!
The girl have escaped!
Princess!
What're you going to do now?
She won't find her way out of the forest.
-She can't have come this far...
-Let's find north!
Go Robin, find her!
I want her killed!
I want her to stop the curse.
Their death is our victory!
Stupid girl...should have stay where you are...
Robin!
This way!
Oh...Wrolf!!
Quickly! Can you find the way home?
That demon dog can't protect you forever!
Now that be Miss Maria home, sir.
Uncle Benjamin... Miss Heliotrop!
I'm really sorry!
Where are your...where are...
Miss Heliotrop!
I'm perfectly alright... yes.
But where are your clothes, my dear one?
How dare you come home in this manner and at this hour?
I'm sorry but you don't know what happen, I was...
I was...in the forest and...
In the forest?
-Didn't I expressively forbid you to go to the forest?
-Yes.
But...listen, I've so much to tell you!
Go upstairs this instance and tidy yourself up!
...but...
Just do as you're told!
You're not my father!
Maria!
Maria, open this door!
Listen...
It maybe possible that I was livid upon sight earlier..
The point is you were gone for such a long time.
I mean you didn't even tell us!
...I...
We!
Miss Heliotrop is beside herself with worried...
Maria...
I know that...
...given that woman and I normally don't see eye to eye ...
...it wouldn't be untrue to say...
I'm glad that you're back.
Who put this back on the wall?!
Digweed? Digweed!! Come and take this away!
Seems there won't be any stars left tonight, Serena...
The Moon is getting closer and closer...
...what're we going to do?
How could you leave me like that?!
...in the forest...
This belong to the first ever Moon Princess...
...forgive me?
Fit's you like a glove!
Oh Loveday, this is all hopeless..
What?
I'm as faraway from actually finding the pearls as ever...
Perhaps it's here somewhere...hidden.
Come on, come with me.
Where?
Downstairs? Oh no no, I'm not going downstairs...
Isn't it bad luck for the groom to see the dress?
I wanted you to see me just as I am before the wedding.
And what does that means?
Benjamin...
I've to tell you something...
Something I should've told you a long, long time ago...
My darling... whatever is it?...hum?
I am not who you think I am.
I'm a De Noir.
A De Noir?
I was brought up to despise the Merryweather but later then I met you and that change everything...
You tricked me!
No!
You pretended to love me!
And all these times you were plotting behind my back, trying to find those ridiculous pearls.
It was your father that sent you, wasn't it?
No...
By marrying you, I lost his love forever.
But Benjamin, don't you see?
Our love could bring our families back together!
Can put an end to this dreadful curse!
Curse ...no, don't give me that nonsense!!
And you filled this house with your De Noir flowers!!
No no please...you do not understand...
Doesn't love change everything?
No...my dear...
...but hate does.
So...
... you missed your chance to bring the families together.
He broke my heart ...
I think he broke his heart too..
But he let me be lost forever.
It must have been quite a shock for him...
I mean...
Maybe if you've waited for him to calm down...
Perhaps apologize?
Oh me apologize?!
You don't understand, do you?
I'm starting to understand one thing.
The real curse of this valley...
...is pride!
Digweed, stop!
But that'll be the master wishes!
I'll be back.
Exactly!
Miss Maria,tell me more about this curse!
There she is...
Each time when a new Moon Princess arrives...
...so does this picture.
But look at it...look at it!
Digweed...you can move now...
Oh...thank goodness!
Can't you see?!
There, look!
She's showing us!
She took the pearls!
Maria...
...are you telling us...
...that the Moon Princess herself took the Moon pearls?!
Yes!
Yes and she's showing me where she hid them!
But where? Where did she put them?
They're in the trees somewhere...out in the forest.
...well, that's a help...
No, I saw what was nearby...
I think I'll know again if I saw it.
...hum, what?
What?
There's only one person who has walked the woods his whole life...
Someone who has it in his blood...
Robin?!
Impossible!
He's an arrogant so and so!
I never ever wanted to see him again!
It's a point of honour.
...it's a matter of...
...pride?!
[BENJAMIN]  [LOVEDAY]
Good luck, little Princess!!!
Bye!
Wait...wait...
No, Miss Heliotrop...
No, you won't stop me!
This is my home and I'm going to fight for it!
No, no no.... I know you've to do this.
I'm beginning to understand a little...
I believe in you!
-Bye...
-Bye, miss.
But be careful!
I will!
That will be the post, sir...
Loveday?
Princess!
Giving yourself up?! How good of you?
...the grand trapper...trapped!
Let me down, you little witch!!
Certainly...
No no no, no don't you dare!!
Oh...my foot...
Thank you darling Serena...
...off you go...
Please!
Wait!
I'm really swelling, I can feel my head hurting!
Oh no...it was like that before...
-I would let you down if you do one thing for me.
-What?
Just promise you'll listen!
Say "I promised"!
Just say it!
I promised!
Alright, you beat me, let me down!
Very well...
What about him?
You're a De Noir...
... he'll very probably will hurt you.
...I'm listening...
Miss De Noir...
Sir Benjamin...
-Well...
Benjamin?
I'm here...
-I believe apologies are in order...
-Yes, they're...
Afetr all one's behaviour have not been... as it might.
That's right...
I'm sorry...
Yes, you should be...
Beg your pardon?
It shall be easy to forgive you... but
Forgive me?!
What on earth are you talking about?
Don't play games with me, Benjamin Merryweather!
You asked me here!
-It was you who asked to see me!
-What!
...Maria...
Maria...
Where the devil is that girl?
-Goodbye!
-Robin, please!
I promised I'll listen to you...
...and I have!
Robin, you've to help me, you have to!!
You're a Merryweather!
-Right now I want to kill you...
-Kill me and the whole valley dies with me.
You and me can solve it and we only have until moon rise.
Tonight!
I'm still listening...
She's back in the forest...
...and this time...
...she won't be leaving...
They are armed men out there whose express aim it is to do her harm!
I would've never agree...
...I didn't know, you see...
I must go to her...
Oh, don't be a fool. I'll go.
I know the forest.
If you'll forgive me...
I believe I know exactly where Maria will be.
-You do?
-How do you?
I'm a superb chef, madame...
...it follows that I should possesed a truly superb nose.
In my youth ...when I would roamed
those woods...I could tracked anything that moved...
... plus she told me where she was going...
What was that?
False trails...
What would you do with one of my ribbon in your pocket?
There are in the trees, that is very distinctive...
...it has massive roots twisting around a big dark colour...
I know where that is.
Suppose for a moment I do this to help you out...
...and suppose we actually manage to find the pearls...what then?
...well...we...
...returned the pearls to the sea and then we go....
You know my father is coming after you?
It's just a matter of finding them before he find's me...
Miss De Noir, it's highly dangerous out there, this is no mission for a woman!
Perhaps you should have told that to Maria.
...as a matter of fact I did.
...frequently...
Wait!!
...that will be another female for the party...
Madame...you're not required on this expedition.
...oh...that's better!
-That'll be your wind...
-Enough...Digweed...
I've been taking care of Maria since she was a baby.
And I intend to protect her now!
I know which way to go!
Come on!
Marmaduke?
Marmaduke, you blithering ex-hunter, what are you doing?
Sorry, sir...
It appears...my power's out here... are not they're in the kitchen...
Just shows us where to go, would you?!
I notice the house is falling down...
sad to see the place is in such a state of disrepair..
If you're so fond of it, why did you run away from it?
You took everything I held dearly and ripped it away from me...
How could I stay?
Run far, did you?
No, not very far...
But then you never came to look for me, did you?
He spent months on horseback, scout the entire county, searching for you ...
Marmaduke?
-Are you leading this expedition or not?
-Yes, sir. Yes.
Hum...strawberry...
...this way!
I think we might have a greater chance of finding her, if we divide and
spread the arc a little wider.
-It should be clear over the next hill... we're not far now.
-Wrolf
Wrolf!!!
Wrolf?
Robin?
Robin?!
Wrolf?
Wrolf...
Wrolf!!
Let's go boy!
Oh, this is pretty...
...isn't it enough for one member of my family to betray me...
...now I find the half-brother is a traitor too?
I will take care of this Princess...myself...once and for all!
Wrolf?
This is the place!
Where are the pearls?!
Listen! The moon will kill us all!
Wrolf, we have to find Maria!
Wrolf!!
You! How could you betray me like that?!
I will not let you take her, father.
Put the knife down, boy ...
Father please, you've to listen to what Maria has to say!
Traitor! You're nothing to me now...
Go!
I know where to find you again!
Back to where it all began...
In here...
Where did they go?
Robin, look at this!
Where are they...
It's her. It must be.
Where...where did you put them?
The pearls!
Open the door!
Robin, let's go!
It's so dark here...
Moon pearls...we need your power now...shows us the way!
Suddenly seems...very quiet...
That will be the absence of the ladies then, sir.
Sir Benjamin!!
We're lost!
Maria!
Robin, come on!
Don't you see?
She's showing us the way!
De Noir!
Merryweather!
Good evening!
Your niece has failed!
If you harm, hurt her...in any way...
Stop!
-Uncle, no! No!
-Father, we got them!!
Look!
Give me the pearls!
Those damn pearls! They brought nothing but harm and grieve!
No, uncle...it's not the pearls but the greed in our heart which brings us such misery.
Father!
Why do you have so much hatred in your heart?
My daughter!
Don't you want to be free of this darkness imprisoning you?
It's he! It's he!
Father!
Benjamin!
Look!
The 5,000 moons.
The curse is coming true!
If you can sacrifice your pride,
we can saved our families....
...we can saved the valley!
You first...
No, no...after you...
I must do this myself!
At the 5,000 moons...
I ...
Maria Merryweather, Moon Princess of Moonacre...
....to remove the curse that had darken this valley...
Take back what is yours!
No!
Maria!
Oh, my sweet child... you're alive!
Uncle!
Were you worried, Robin?
No...I could've done that...
You're the true Moon Princess!
Oh... nasty!
That will be a black lion male, sir...
It's alright, uncle.
It's just Wrolf...
Please forgive my stubborn pride!
Loveday...
-Stop right there! I'll finish her right now!
-No, stop... you idiot!
Maria! I'm here!
I've come to save you!
...Is there...
...going to be a wedding?
...Oh, my...
Mr. Dogweed?!
Well, there we are then...
...nothing to be done!
(The Ancient Chronicles of Moonacre Valley)