AIRLINE DISASTER
Translation: Pix
Good afternoon.
I'm Glenn Russell,
and is an honor to announce the trip
Starquest's inaugural program.
It offers the best
Aerodynamic design
to reduce
Fuel consumption;
computerized controls
sophisticated
and what we believe to be the experience
more pleasant to fly today.
And now, at this point, I would like to
present chief pilot Joseph Franklin
Bill Alexander and his copilot.
Thank you very much!
-Joe, Joe!
The Starquest boasts
be totally
automatic since the
takeoff to landing.
Are you afraid of this plan to replace it,
that replace all pilots?
No, no. We love to fly.
Also, you always
will need pilots.
Who will point when you
are flying over the Grand Canyon?
And here you are.
Calm down!
Sorry ... was reflex.
Reflection?
Great reflection. You will
it is our security?
No.
Something special?
Paperwork. Diplomatic thing.
None of your business ... whoever.
Okay, you two are good.
-Thanks, man.
"Sure.
Take care.
That sucks you should
stop at the limit, Gina.
Yes, well ...
I feel that the Secret Service
get me out of my field
sending to the safety
the President's brother.
-So the ball will never get me.
-Actually, it would be the right field.
Is.
There you are
Take care.
Thank you.
Hello?
Hi, dear. You watching?
Hi! No, nothing in the news yet.
Just some pretty pictures of the plane.
Gwen is looking at the conference
press onto YouTube.
What the ...?
43rd
Hey! Look at the verbiage, young lady.
I really wanted to be here.
I wish we were there, too.
No, you do not.
-Yeah, right.
Oh, man. I still can not find.
Hey Gwen, prepare to go to school.
Joe, I gotta go.
I love you. Take care of everything, and I
I'll be back for the weekend.
-Right. I love you.
-Bye.
This was a TV interview today.
Joe, you got the look on the radio.
Someone stole all
our equipment.
Let us, Joe. Forget the crap
flight old-fashioned.
This is not fly, Billy.
This is videogame.
Joe, you're a grouchy,
grizzled, old Gaga.
Just sit back and enjoy
your retirement.
Counting the minutes. Counting the minutes
until he can retire away from you
with my wife, children, in a
beach in Barbados. And without Billy.
It looks delicious. Okay,
Let us prepare.
-Hydraulic ...
-Adjusted.
Emergency-Lights ...
-Prepared.
E-key phone ...
-Disabled.
66th
Anti-Ice System ...
And no. This should be disabled,
and is disabled.
I know how to fly this thing.
Do not worry, right?
Ladies and gentlemen,
're number one for takeoff.
Make sure your belts
Security is tight
, and their chairs are upright
, and in the locked position.
Time to shake. Remember,
five minutes in and out.
-Molly? Molly ...?
Where's your ...?
Go kids!
Children go, run!
No. Run! No, no!
No, no!
You bastard!
-Remember ...
-No!
If you cause a problem,
will be much worse for their children.
"Come on.
-Go!
Come on.
Anda ... Come on!
Freeze!
No!
Down!
Tie the children!
No!
-No!
-Hey!
Do not forget ...
You are hurting my arm!
-Mother ...
-No!
Stay down, guys, look ...
We have problems.
Damn!
Go, go, go, go!
Hey, go! Go!
Mama ...
Quiet!
Shoot him!
103rd
No!
Calm down, Fred!
Yes.
Melville. What? Damn!
Make sure the residents were there.
I'm heading.
-Let me know so I have something new.
-Right.
FBI agent Melville ...
Julius Reed, the Secret Service.
What is the situation?
The maid of Franklin,
Molly, is dead.
We seek fingerprints, and we
begin to investigate the neighborhood.
Great. There is something that
can help me with this?
What about the surveillance system?
Already there?
That surveillance system?
-Go children, run!
6-We install monitoring cameras.
-So should show everything that happened.
-No!
Beauty. The way these
guys are heads down,
we have to search to try
get a photo for identification.
Yes, sir, Director.
I understand that you need
inform the President.
Yes, sir. Send details as soon
we have more to continue.
Yes, sir ... Yes, sir;
we find them.
Let's find them.
Fortunately, they are still alive.
Expert!
You're late!
-Come on.
-Shut up!
Mom!
Mommy!
No! No!
"Come on, its useless!
Mother!
-Where are we going?
Mother! Mom!
-Freeze!
Mom! Help!
Gwen! Michael!
No! Mom!
Got it?
You what?
What do you want?
What do you want? What you ...
Morning Edition.
Right. Let's leave it
ready for your photo.
Come, get up!
Talk to me!
Strip.
No. No. .. No!
No.
Look at me, tell the truth!
-Get in!
-Hi. Babies, I'm here.
Mom! Mother! "
-You're right.
"Oh, no.
I have, I have it.
Lord ... sir.
Lord ... I'm sorry, sir,
but it was only the announcement that
could use your cell phone.
The seat belt warning
Security remains connected.
Is it? Sorry.
No problem.
Lord?
-Jennifer, right?
-I need to sit down, sir.
I need to show you something.
Oh, my God.
What the hell is that?
My agents called me.
The pilot's family was kidnapped.
You need to go get it and
bring it back to talk to me.
"Who are you?
-I'm just an analyst with the FBI, right?
They knew I was on vacation, they know
I'm on that flight. So I contacted.
So, if you can get him and bring him
back, I'll be here, right?
Hey, princess.
It's Jen. She is alone?
-I think so.
"She can bring us champagne?
You're a figure ...
Have you worked?
Joe has ... has something very
important that I need to show you.
Sure, Nate. Go ahead
unlock the door, let it go.
Yes, sir.
Sit.
And tadpoles as well.
As you can see today's newspaper.
Ladies and gentlemen.
Ladies and gentlemen, please.
First, to cooperate ...
nobody will get hurt.
Secondly, we are all
heavily armed, and you do not.
Without heroes, and nobody dies.
Then just sit ...
enjoy complimentary peanuts,
and not annoy my brothers.
Thirdly ... are not
terrorists, this is not a jihad.
Our demands are very simple, all
want to go home late at night.
So be good sheep, do
I say, and nobody dies.
My brothers will come from the booth
to collect their phones.
Remember, your cooperation
guarantees that no one gets hurt.
That  ...
Submit only the
nice men and women.
And finally, for
security guard ...
No heroes, and nobody will
die. Remember that.
196th
Coast 8-5-Heavy,
what is the emergency?
He has a gun
pointed at his face.
Now ... open the door.
Então é a sua filha.
Wait a minute! Right?
Wait a little, slowly.
Pane ... bassline,
central section has a blue button.
Good boy.
Come on. Come on.
Hello. Hello? Forget
Static bad on the phone.
Here is the Agent
Special Gina Vitale.
I'm in the middle of a
emergency.
-Mrs. President.
-Good morning, Ms. President.
Thank you. Please
okay, someone begins.
Who's down?
Nathan Polansky. He
is one of the browsers.
They shot him.
And who the hell are "they"?
Our guess, of Aryan Brotherhood.
The guy in the cockpit or
has a mole on the eye
or tattoo a teardrop-shaped.
-Does Joe know about Annette?
-He knows, Frank ... He already knows.
How?
The guy in the booth
Joe gave a cell phone.
He spoke with one of
Our staff on site.
DeToro, contact the Starquest.
I have to talk to Joe before
making any decisions.
Yes, Mrs. President.
What is the nearest airport that
they could land, military or civilian?
Well, probably are
on the South Carolina now.
There are six airports
main, and not know, thirty,
forty airports
aviation in general.
We have five bases
Air Force in South Carolina
But only two commercially
behave the Starquest.
-And the military?
-We are well.
What? Well, get it.
We have a Secret Service agent
assigned to his brother.
Sure, Agent Vitale.
You're on speaker
with the president.
What can you tell us?
Has at least ten of them
board. They are all armed.
They have control of
plane. They had been shot
fired, but it seems
the plane was not affected.
-Are you in a safe place?
"Yes, yes.
I did this by compartments
below the plane.
Vitale're saying
can walk freely around?
Yes, ma'am.
Let's take the forms
Complete aircraft.
Okay, so Vitale, the
know about electronics?
'll learn much more about that.
Sure, it might be useful.
His complete obedience
avoid any victim today.
Madam, the companions
arrived, and we have contact.
I'll put them on speaker.
Bravo, Tango-one, you're in
speaker and speaking with the boss.
Our call sign
will be Bravo-Tango-6.
Roger, Six.
In waiting.
Bravo-Tango-1
Here is President Franklin.
Tell me what you see and what it means.
The plane seems to still be piloted
by a competent crew.
I do not see any evidence of
mechanical problems with the aircraft.
I want you to put your
sister on the line for me.
Think it is easy to catch
e. .. the phone?
ATC, here is the Coasteira
8-5-Heavy.
Could open a channel
to the White House,
so that we could
communicate to Ms. President?
Mrs. President, here is the Starquest.
Mrs. President, is really an honor.
Let me talk to Joe.
I want to hear his voice.
Here is Captain Joe Franklin
Mrs. President.
Do whatever is necessary.
Very noble.
Sure, you have my
attention. Whatever?
Ten of my Aryan Brothers are arrested
stupid government charges
a federal penitentiary
the state of New Jersey.
I want his release
immediately and unconditionally.
Names?
Ask the Director.
Know that our policy is
not negotiate with terrorists.
Yes, I knew it would be a game.
But Joe here, and his family,
have been generous enough in
give me an insurance policy.
I see.
Know what I want.
Empty fuel.
Okay, okay.
6, here is one. The Starquest is
draining fuel.
6, this is Bravo-Tango-2.
Just lost
Bravo-Tango-3 for the emptying
fuel.
6, here are two. She is going
to a population center.
The pilot came out?
Sorry, ma'am. We have
visuals on a ramp.
Vitale, go pro side panel.
Yes.
We need you to replace
manually dump fuel.
I am here ... what
I'm looking for?
Find something that says "Dump
fuel emergency "
"Release of fuel,"
something.
Looks like a Christmas tree.
The whole thing lit up.
I do not ... wait.
Wait a minute.
What about "release
fuel emergency "?
Probably it is.
Listen. Need to press
this button and hold it.
299th
Ready.
The agent stopped Vitale
emptying of fuel.
The fuel is not draining.
He stopped being emptied.
"I did not tell him to stop.
"I did not quit, never stopped!
Is not responding.
I think all this will
let us expel it.
Mrs. President ... we have only
90 minutes of fuel.
You know what to do.
How long before
accordance with clear images
enough to pass
by the NCIC and CODIS?
I have a clue about Karl Hitler.
Have nothing. If I had changed
legally in prison
five years would be a penalty
ten years for bank robbery.
An armed bank robbery to help
finance the Aryan Brotherhood.
Arians? Great.
Heavily armed psychopaths.
He checked the address it here?
The parole agent
said it is up to date.
We will make sure
he is still there.
Tell Terry to mount a
mobile team in five minutes,
and talk to bring
plenty of ammunition.
So it was great.
They came running ...
Take him out.
Now look, Snake.
Mother! "
Honey.
Here, here, look at me.
Right.
So, good job.
Hey, hear that?
Where do you think is going?
-See our guests ..?
No, it will not.
327th
Sit.
Run as fast as possible on the road.
Get help to us, right?
Harry?
330th
Why me?
How about "because I told you so"?
Come on!
-Damn!
-Mommy, Mommy!
Damn!
Because I had to do this?
Do not worry, Snake.
Let's get them.
-No!
Drop-it, bitch!
-Stop it!
-If you move, you will die.
Okay, go with Dad.
Come on!
Hey, kid!
I'm your sister!
Now that I have your attention,
let me tell you something.
And believe me,
I'm talking about pretty serious.
Next time ...
will be in her head.
Sure, you have five seconds
get back here, or already was!
A!
Two!
Three!
Do not!
Get him!
"You okay?
-I want to go home!
Here.
Move over, kids!
Bravo-Tango-1
stay far away and firm.
In the current trajectory, how long will
before they fly over the Atlantic,
know, far from the populated areas?
About twenty minutes.
Well, if the plane is on autopilot,
we can not assume it, get it back?
We can not attempt to override
the whole pattern of his flight?
Well, it's self.
There is no signal to be blocked.
There is another option.
We are working on
an emergency system
named "Kitty Hawk"
it allows us to take control
in flight and redirect it.
To be more specific,
is an unfolding
the vehicle program
unmanned aerial.
We are doing some testing
Preliminary adaptation
this technology for use in
civil aircraft compromised.
Right then, as
time for the satellite?
We are now working on it.
Ten, fifteen minutes?
Hey, Willie, already found
that security?
I'm still looking.
Well .. start to shoot people
until that bastard appear.
You! You're the security officer?
"You look like a porthole. You is it?
-No.
Hell, you're so ...
Shut up! Shut up!
378th
Hey, Willie, now what?
Was he safe?
-Fuck you!
-What?
-Hey!
Want to help me here?
I do not know where he is.
You do not need it.
Where does this go?
Where will this lead?
I. .. downstairs.
Cargo compartment.
C'mon.
I know that is where the agent
Security is hiding.
I'm feeling.
What do you ..?!
Okay, dear.
We have a problem.
We lost the autopilot.
They're obviously taking
difficulty controlling the aircraft.
And we can not
take control?
Not yet.
We'll have to leave Joe
do your job.
Joe?
The man up there, Bill.
I have total confidence in Joe.
Okay, let's go.
Come on!
We will get well soon
near those buildings.
Come on, Billy, get it!
-I can not handle it!
"Come on, Billy! Raise it!
It's happening again!
I think the rotating stabilizers
are functioning again.
This autopilot broke down.
I do not think we'll retrieve it.
Do not worry about the pilot
Automatic. You got me here.
While on board, I am
the control of the aircraft, right?
What happened to the pilot
automatic, gentlemen?
I do not know.
Give me a hand.
You're the security officer?
No.
A cop?
Who are you?
Only the right person at
wrong place at the wrong time.
That's it.
Are you okay?
No.
Just ... hold on tight.
Buster!
-Idiot!
-No!
Stop, stop!
424th
Damn!
-Robert will kill you ...
-Shut up!
Willie is dead, man.
Really?
That should be simple and enjoyable
As Robert said!
Yes, well, not Robert
is simple and enjoyable.
Is she?
Who killed Willie?
Yes, of course it is.
432nd
Cursed Willie. Leaving
be killed by a whore.
Come on. Let's say that Robert
found the security guard.
I do not ...
Tell you.
Here is the special agent
Vitale, 2-9-4-8-3.
Yes, I'm still in season.
You can put me on hold,
but keep writing
and I will continue talking
in ... Thank you.
One of the kidnappers
is dead. I am using
his phone ... Perhaps
can get a signal.
You know what ... 'll
send his number.
Maybe you could get an address.
But ... Hello?
Yes!
Agent Vitale, is in
back in with the president.
Agent Vitale, what's the latest?
Some passengers were killed.
From their side, there is a low.
confirm my original estimate
ten hijackers.
Can contact
with the security guard?
Agent Vitale?
God.
The governor of Carolina
South wants to activate
units of
Air National Guard
with orders to shoot down the plane,
cross the airspace of its cities.
-And the idiot wants to be president.
-Yes.
If the order to shoot
is a given, it will come to me.
-Let this clear.
"I will tell you.
We learned that his brother
has control of the aircraft.
Mrs. President, we confirm
ten Aryan Brotherhood in Fairton.
Why are they in prison?
They fired for about an arsenal
five, trying to get some weapons.
We lost three ATF agents.
How are we with the satellite?
We have an uplink to
alive, but the integrity
data with
ailerons was compromised.
Committed to?
There is a flaw in
somewhere in the system
causing
communication problems
between the cockpit and the servants who
are controlling the ailerons.
If the failures continue, I fear that
we may lose control of the aircraft.
We have a connection with the Starquest.
Okay, turn it on.
Mrs. President ... How are
my brothers Aryans?
We are talking to
director. How are you, Joe?
I'm fine, Mrs. President. So
as in Ice Fishing Point George.
475th
We are isolating the ten brothers.
Isolating or releasing
For now, we are isolating them.
478th
Isolating ...
This is what the isolation buying ...
But damn!
So you're thinking of
play in the water below?
Bill will redirect this flight for us
lead to all East Coast cities.
If we play down and rains will
debris throughout the east coast.
Bill, make a new plan
flight for me, could you?
Now!
Do not mess with me.
What is our next step?
Okay, let's go get something to
to focus on Point George.
Why is that?
Because they never ice fished Point
George. So something is happening there.
We're with him.
Lord, that combines with a truck
image we have a camera of a bank
in the area where the kidnappers
the van disappeared.
And they are stationed in
front of the house of Karl Hitler.
What a surprise.
The best approach is to use the bank
and then take the truck to cover.
That still leaves the
front windows.
Collins, you will monitor and
warn you if see any movement.
Let's break down doors and shoot them
before they can react.
Today, nobody dies
only the bad, right?
Taken control of the airplane.
Although the statute of
passenger safety
is unknown, there
various speculations for ...
First team to go and
be in a position now.
You will not end?
Damn it, man. Damn day long.
Mrs. President, the satellite has
and a lock is loading.
508th
How long will it take?
-Five minutes.
Well, let's go. Where,
what is the closest runway?
Charleston. We
take them to Charleston.
No.
Merritt is a better choice.
It is a military base, not civilian.
Let's take them Merritt then.
-Do this.
Bill? What is this?
We seem
on fire below.
We'll have to come down
and take a look.
No, nobody will leave.
Whether we burn?
I imagine that a plane so advanced
has some way to deal with fire.
-I should go there to see.
"Nobody is going anywhere!
Mrs. President, Kitty Hawk
ready for your command.
How long will it take to get it?
-Just sort.
Come on.
Here is General Dillard.
We are ready
to take flight.
Again, the bird fly.
Kitty Hawk has a grip
hand with Starquest.
Bill ... are you doing this?
What's happening?
I think the autopilot again.
I'm setting a
vector of 142.3 to 27,000 feet.
Sure, the place still Merritt
docking closer?
It is close now, but I think
we can still do that.
It is as if the plane took control
of itself, except it is erratic.
The flaps are turned down.
At this air speed?
I know, I know. He will rip
wings right out.
But why the hell
is he doing this?
Someone can take the
control of the plane out?
No, not that I know ...
-Robert!
Correct me if I'm wrong,
but it seems that such sudden breakdown
is taking us to the
nearest airport.
Okay, let's go.
Come on, raise it.
Something is not right.
She is not responding.
We're going too fast.
We are fighting to hold on to it.
What ... You have control or not?
Telemetry is all wrong.
It is not responding to input,
she is not responding.
It's coming fast
and too low!
Bravo-Tango-6,
here is Bravo-Tango-1.
Starquest going
straight to the city.
Will have to let it go,
Let Joe take it!
Three minutes to landing.
Okay, c'mon, c'mon.
Lift it.
Come on, Billy.
Lift it!
The engines are kicking.
Jesus, the landing gear going down.
Because someone is lowering it.
I recommend abortion, sir.
Here is Bravo-Tango-2. Wings
Starquest are swinging a lot.
Cason, let it go!
Forget it.
That's an order!
Kitty Hawk, here is Cason NSA
you must abort. Again, it should abort!
Climb. Climb it, climb it.
Upload it!
Let's stop!
We will not stop!
Reduce power!
Bring the landing gear
up!
See those buildings?
Come on!
His ... great ... beautiful ... whale!
This is Bravo-Tango-2. The Starquest
is flying straight and level.
Mrs. President,
knows better than that.
I know I tried to take
control of this
plan somehow
and this will cost you.
DJ, open the door.
Is up.
What the hell was that?!
Find the security officer.
Any other agent
safety, stand up.
How about three of us give a ride?
Mrs. President,
Secret Service reports that
the first lady and her
children are in shelter.
Her mother is safe. Locate
his sister. She is out of the country.
Thank you.
Take that.
Still no sign of
movement in the window.
Helicopters in position
and waiting.
Tell them that they are ready
jumping up and enter.
Come on. Come on, come on!
Come before. Be ready to
come quickly to the smoke.
Come on! Come on!
Do not let them use
the hostages as shields.
That, my ass is that
bulletproof, bitch!
595th
Clean!
Clean! We have a runner!
I thought I heard something funny.
Let me see your hands.
That was me. I
to go to the bathroom.
Ruth!
Sarco-1, the suspect is fleeing
a white cargo van.
Go ahead and keep eye contact.
Come on!
Damn! Damn!
Do not shoot! I repeat, do not shoot.
We need the target alive.
Lord, and if he
say where hostages are
and tell them to be
move, or shoot them?
Can you bring the target to a
quick stop without killing it?
Affirmative.
Dammit!
Damn!
Oh no, not you.
It, bring it!
Damn!
You know ... you and my ex-wife
have similar qualities.
Perhaps when all this is done,
We can get a little bit?
"I do not have it.
-Claro.
You have two choices.
Can open the folder or ...
What's your choice?
Here! Take it, right?
Take it!
This poses a problem.
What we are doing
about it, Robert?
It is part of a plan that you have not had
privilege of knowing yet, Ralph.
Make sure that
I'm not bothered.
I said, I do not have the key!
The guy on the other side has the key!
This may hurt a little.
Damn!
Bastard!
Yes, sir, I will return.
The guys toast.
Were burned in the disaster.
Great.
Some good news?
I took it from his pocket
one of the boys.
We can get some
SIM card information.
I have the record.
-Where?
Point-George.
Okay, let's go.
The SIM card seems
still be legible.
Let's see ...
It has a text message
posted at 9:30 this morning:
"Delivery on the way."
642nd
Locate your destination.
Lord, have another
message text here.
Sent soon after his fall.
Only says: "Problem."
Okay, let's hurry.
We are running out of time.
Your current position leads to Alexandria
Virginia, directly to DC.
If I had to bring down the plane,
where would be the best place?
Find a safe place
Mrs. President.
We have the Phoenix System.
-What is it?
Laser-launched satellite.
This is a five-megawatt laser spatial
which vaporizes the metal contact.
Can focus on a target with precision
less than a foot in diameter.
We had almost 90% successful
reduction targets.
The laser detonates the
fuel in the wings,
virtually disintegrating the
plane, leaving few traces.
If you do, I do it in an area
uninhabited, so think of these areas.
Yes, ma'am.
Well, let's start organizing
the National Guard,
hospitals and service
Search and Rescue.
Yes, Mrs. President.
I have already said the key.
-Stay with me.
-I do not have the key.
-I have not.
You can survive it.
Marsha ... Marsha.
What are you doing?
666th
Hey!
Stay with me.
Okay, okay.
She's back.
Vitale agent, you are
back to President Franklin.
It's the money!
How well "the money"?
Securities, worth of bonds.
Vitale, we have no control
aircraft. I may have to bring him down.
Give me more time, Mrs. President. I will
try to take him down from here.
-Do not have much time.
-I know.
Drugs.
Mrs. President, this is a list of
SAT for special circumstances.
His agent Vitale is on board,
security officer
but so are two messengers.
Let me guess ...
are moving cash.
One hundred and fifty million
dollars in bonds.
TJ, I want you to know
policies of the rich.
Of course I want to download and 100 of those.
-What is going chief?
-Forget it, do what I say.
What are you doing
out of place?
"Who are you?
-I am a passenger.
It is you who is causing
all these problems?
Secret Service.
It's the nanny's sister's president,
that pretty.
But it will be with
the family when you die.
But I found
trunk of the family.
"You know where my suitcase is.
"I know and you do not.
You're just a bank robber.
It's just the money.
It's a lot of money.
Damn ...
And you were already dead.
You must be kidding.
Robert, what's the plan?
Wait, leave here in a minute.
Stay away from the door, princess.
ENGINE DAMAGED
Just lost
engine power.
Really?
We could not have lost the engine.
If not we land
now we will fall.
-Do it!
-Hold on, hold on.
6, this is Bravo Tango 2.
The charge exploded and it seems
the motor was with her.
See any further damage,
something more superficial?
Negative, try to get close to
see the damage, but walk quickly.
I guess I can not continue
flying more.
Tango Bravo 2 if it was
pilot could fly this plane?
I did not want.
Okay, let me be
clear. If you shoot,
The 716th
I do not think that it is in
the air for long.
Mrs. President, reached an information
the next 60 seconds.
Were seen six miles.
Lady?
We can use this fire to
bring them to a controlled area?
Mrs. President, this aircraft
was equipped with guard
722nd
and a missile defense system.
What is the chance he
keep giving it the shape?
Currently unknown.
Bravo-Tango-two, here is Franklin,
is authorized to bring the plane down.
Roger, Bravo-Tango-6.
Zorro-3, Zorro-3.
Locked-defense system.
-What was that?
June 2 is here, the missiles
were eliminated.
Firing again.
The missile is moving.
What happened?
Bravo-Tango-two, has to abort
the mission immediately.
Understood in June, mission aborted.
They have a laser?
-How far are?
-They are coming.
Get me the White House.
Yes, Madam.
We gotta go.
Come on.
Come on, come on.
President, we
waiting for their orders.
Proceed.
Pro floor to the ground!
Do not mess ...
We are not stabilized,
're falling.
746th
6, here is 2, Bravo-Tango-1
just explode.
The laser-worked.
-Are you listening?
"No pro airplane.
-What happened?
Tango-Bravo 2, continue.
Shot him.
-Turn off it, unplug it!
Turn off-the laser.
She can not die.
There is nothing to descend.
Fly without the engine.
-Damn!
-Over, okay?
Let me get off the plane to which
these people do not have to die.
-Let me think.
-Does not have to think about anything.
It takes just 5 minutes to land
and nobody will give a hero.
Guys, we ran out of time.
Do something, do it!
What's the plan?
-I will talk with my brother.
-All right.
-Me, Joe.
-I am a little busy now.
Do not want to be thick but
can go straight to the point,
I appreciate it.
Remember when we fish the bay?
-What beautiful memories.
-Thanks.
See you there.
This nonsense will not happen
and my brothers will not be released.
All-or hurt themselves.
-Sure, DC will not accept it.
Well, put the table,
we arrived for dinner.
-Hey, that's my sister.
-Fuck your sister.
-The search continues ...
-I do not believe they shot the plane.
-We have reports that ...
"You know what that means.
Sorry, lady.
Sorry. I pity you,
soon as we begin to know ourselves.
Do not move.
3 hostages got down here
and I'll kill them all!
FBI, right?
Not the loss, I can not
keep this plane.
Is dropping.
Can I fly a plane alone.
Okay?
I lost GPS.
-They are very bad?
We flew blind, and nearly out of fuel.
Mrs. President, the plane is
DC airspace.
President, I have two
waiting in line.
-Joe.
'We have control of the airplane again.
Actually we do not need because we have
map, satellite or anything else.
But ... we landed in Dallas.
-Sure, and your family is safe.
Thanks, Harriet.
We lost communication.
Are you okay?
Yes I am better than Ben, lodge
this baby and get back home.
-How?
The old-fashioned.
Let's take it and plant it on the track.
Navigate the brands.
Gina was very kind to me
say what you see there.
The Lincoln Memorial at 2:00
approximately 3 km.
The Washington Monument
11.00, five kilometers.
That, slowly, slowly.
Let's try the next port.
We can not give back
these conditions.
Your browser does not work
levels are not certain.
Never be able to land this thing,
we can not keep it that way.
Sure. Gina, I can
give a glass of water.
By half, please.
All right, brother?
We hope so.
Thank you.
Capital right, 1:00.
National Park
left side. 09:00.
-The wheels are falling.
-You have to give me good news.
Joe can not land this plane.
We're running out of fuel.
Never succeed.
Gina, I think it would be
a good idea to sit down.
Never succeed.
Between this and the street prostitutes,
the only thing that keeps me
trying to land this plane.
They're going straight to
building capital.
I was so scared.
Are you okay?
Yes.
Hey buddy.
Do not you ever fly again.