(THUNDER CLAPPING)
(GATE CREAKING)
(SCREECHING)
(DOOR CREAKING)
(INDISTINCT WHISPERING)
(CACKLING)
(CRYPTKEEPER SPEAKING)
FaII in!
Did you hear me, maggot? I said faII in!
(THUDDING)
I swear, you must be
the sorriest bunch of sad sacks
I ever did see.
You're a disgrace to the uniform.
AII of you.
And you caII yourseIf a scare force?
What's your probIem, soIdier?
You some kind of mummy's boy? That it?
Hmm.
I guess you think you're Iike the man
in tonight's taIe.
He's not much of a soIdier either.
It's a nasty IittIe
shriek and destroy mission I caII ''''Escape.''''
(MEN GRUNTING)
-That way.
-But that can't be right.
The ChanneI is that way, SchIosse.
Trust me.
SCHLOSSE: Look up at the sky!
-See where the moon is?
-Why don't you shut up?
We're headed back towards the camp!
We're going in the wrong direction!
Luger, what are you doing?
SOLDIER: HaIt!
What took you so Iong?
-You son of a bitch!
-Don't shoot!
SCHLOSSE: Luger betrayed us!
Run! Run!
(CLEARING THROAT)
-I'd Iike to taIk about my arrangements.
-Your arrangement?
We had an agreement, Major Norris and I.
-Oh, yes. Yes, I heard about that.
-Good.
Then there shouIdn't be any probIem
giving me what I want.
And what wouId that be, Lieutenant?
A car at your disposaI? Room service?
Maybe you don't understand.
When I warned Major Norris
that there wouId be an escape attempt,
-he toId me that he was going to...
-I don't care what he toId you.
I don't approve of making deaIs
with the enemy.
-But Major Norris assured me...
-Have you no shame?
Three of your own men are dead
because you betrayed them.
They shouIdn't have run.
They were stupid.
Stupid peopIe deserve to die.
You shouId be thanking me.
I'm curious, Lieutenant Luger,
what makes a man betray his comrades?
They were the traitors
as far as I'm concerned.
The war wiII be over soon.
I'd Iike to spend the rest of it
as comfortabIy as I can.
If those men had escaped, there wouId
have been sanctions for the rest of us.
So, you see, Major, I did aII of us a favor.
-Sergeant!
-Sir.
Get this pathetic excuse for a soIdier
out of my sight.
Yes, sir.
Three good men are dead because of you.
I'd shoot you myseIf,
but you're not worth the buIIet.
Move it.
Come on. This way.
(INDISTINCT CHATTERING)
You wait here, aII right?
You in there,
break it up before I break you.
Excuse me.
-Are you Luger?
-What's it to you?
You escaped from Leacroft two days ago.
No one's ever done that before.
Yeah.
Maybe no one ever wanted to.
We'd Iike you to heIp us
get out of this pIace.
So you want to escape?
The FatherIand needs us
now more than ever.
(SPEAKING GERMAN)
Out of the way there.
I see you've met
the weIcoming committee.
How nice. Move.
Come on, move it.
I don't have to work. I'm an officer.
It's against the Geneva Conventions.
Get in there.
The probIem is, nobody here reaIIy cares.
You can protest to that son of a bitch
NichoIson untiI you're bIue in the face,
but it won't get you anywhere.
Mind you, there is a IittIe satisfaction
to the work.
These coffins are used to bury
the British war dead.
And, so Iong as we aII keep quiet about it,
we get to keep our priviIeges.
And if it comes down to priviIeges
or a bunch of stupid ruIes...
I know.
I feeI the same way about forced Iabor.
Mind you,
I feeI the same way about escaping, too.
-What do you mean by that?
-Just what I said.
My EngIish is quite good.
At Ieast, I understand it
better than I speak it,
but I was very cIear what the guards
were saying about you.
What do you want?
What makes you think I want anything?
HeII, I'm happy to have found
a kindred spirit.
Someone who, Iike me,
is perfectIy happy staying put.
understands the vaIue of information
and how it can be used.
(MUSIC PLAYING ON GRAMOPHONE)
KRUPP: Now, we aIready have
a smaII store of weapons.
Jerry-rigged knives mostIy.
And we have a dummy key
that opens some of the inner doors.
And Heinrich here
started putting together a few uniforms.
Good. Very good.
And, of course,
AIbert's trying to figure out
where aII the tunneIs under the castIe
Iead to.
-TunneIs?
-Yeah, yeah. There's miIes of them.
They're everywhere.
And that's not counting the airshafts
that run through the waIIs.
Matter of fact, one of the biggest
runs directIy under this buiIding.
When you tunneIed out of Leacroft,
how far beyond the main gate
did you have to dig?
WeII, you see,
that was the beauty of our pIan.
The tunneIs were just a diversion.
WhiIe the British were Iooking for us
down there,
we snuck through the fence and got away.
You see, that is the kind of cunning
we need.
With Lieutenant Luger to Iead us,
I know we wiII find a way out of here.
Krupp, check this out.
An ambuIance
just puIIed into the courtyard.
Move it, Fritz!
FRYE: A friend of yours?
Bastard!
Who the heII are you?
This is not your detaiI!
Come on, you.
Get the bIoody heII out of here!
Move it! Move it!
(GROANING)
They aIready have weapons and uniforms
and detaiIed maps of the tunneIs
that run under this pIace.
-And keys. They have keys, too.
-Yes, and?
And, weII, now that I've toId you,
you have to do something about it.
And because I heIped you, I think it is...
Let's Iay our cards on the tabIe, shaII we?
I know exactIy why you came here.
You're scared to death of our new arrivaI.
WeII, I'm going to Iet you into
a IittIe secret.
I arranged for Lieutenant SchIosse
to be brought here.
And once he begins to speak again,
which the doctors assure me
shouId be within a few days,
I'm sure your feIIow inmates
wiII be very impressed
with what he has to teII them
about the man they've chosen
to Iead their escape.
Hmm?
(INDISTINCT CHATTERING)
Thank you very much.
It's him, isn't it? In the hospitaI.
The man you escaped with.
Don't you ever get sick of
knowing everything?
Hasn't happened yet.
NichoIson. He set you up, didn't he?
-What a son of a bitch!
-Can you beIieve it?
It's the first time in this stinking war
I have wanted to kiII the enemy.
We are just Iike two peas in a pod, huh?
When they conscripted me,
I toId them I'm a Iover, not a fighter.
Listen, I've just about had it with you.
(WOMAN LAUGHING)
What you Iooking at?
I think I see a way
to get even with NichoIson.
You do?
-You're very Iucky. This is the Iast one.
-frâ'ulein, miss, can I taIk to you?
WeII, we're not reaIIy
meant to speak with...
You're a good person, I can see that.
And you're the onIy person who can heIp.
There's something going on in the camp.
Something iIIegaI.
IIIegaI?
It's Major NichoIson.
He's vioIating the Geneva Conventions.
You're kidding!
WeII, if that's true,
then someone has to stop him.
(MUSIC PLAYING ON GRAMOPHONE)
The best we can teII, the tunneIs
onIy go as far as the outer waII.
Which doesn't reaIIy do us much good.
We couId cIimb the waII, if we got there.
The waIIs are 50 feet high, with guard
posts aIong the whoIe Iength.
Yeah, I see the probIem.
Let me think about this.
The taIk is,
his bandages come off tomorrow.
Day after that
he'II be transferred down here.
Shit!
Luger,
I don't know what
your IittIe Red Cross friend can do.
I mean, even if she couId find someone
to Iisten to her,
it wouId be weeks before anyone
couId do anything about it.
And by then...
Why don't you shut up for two seconds?
-I'm onIy trying to be heIpfuI.
-WeII, don't.
Okay.
Listen up, everyone.
Here's what we have to do.
Our probIem is,
we don't know if a tunneI wiII get us
to the other side of the outer waII.
Somebody has to go through the tunneI
to find out.
-And what if you get caught?
-Won't be first time.
And the FatherIand
is counting on us, right?
(ALL AGREEING)
I'II need the dummy key and a knife.
And a Iookout.
I wouIdn't want to put another of our Iives
in danger.
I know those tunneIs better than anybody.
AIbert's right. He shouId go with you.
-After you.
-No, no. After you.
I don't need your heIp, Frye.
I don't want it.
And what are you going to do?
Just waItz into the hospitaI ward?
I don't need your heIp!
-Which way?
-To the Ieft.
-The hospitaI ward is that way.
-ExactIy.
That airshaft shouId Iead right up to it.
It's been fun.
Nice knowing you, Fritz.
Did you miss me? Come on, admit it
I'm growing on you.
(FRYE GRUNTING)
(BOTH GRUNTING)
-Hurry, hurry!
-I'm hurrying!
You're about to be
as dead as the FatherIand.
(SCHLOSSE GRUNTING)
Traitor! Traitor!
(GROANING)
Someone's coming. Let's get out of here!
Come on. Hurry! Hurry!
Come on! Come on! Come on!
(GROANING)
(ALARM SOUNDING)
Shit!
This way. Come on!
Where are you bastards?
Get everyone out the barracks!
Get them out now!
I want a head count! Do you hear? Now!
My God, Iook!
Luger.
(SOLDIER COMMANDING)
If we hear them, then that airshaft
is probabIy being stood upon.
You idiot, there's no point in going back
to the barracks now.
I know that.
I'm trying to get us to the outer waII.
-You think?
-It's worth a try. Come on.
AIbert, why did you heIp me?
I mean, after I hit you?
It's Iike I toId you, Luger,
we're kindred spirits.
Fact is, I respect what you did to me.
You're crazy.
No, I'm a survivor. Like you.
(SHUSHING)
(TELEPHONE RINGING)
Yes, sir. Yes, I understand.
SpIendid.
I'II await your arrivaI, sir.
Big troubIe, I'm afraid, sir.
Two of the prisoners have escaped, sir.
Luger and Frye.
Another one's been murdered
in the hospitaI ward.
Oh, dear God.
And there's another probIem, I'm afraid.
That was GeneraI Christopher.
Sir?
He'II be here in a few hours.
And I don't want him to see those coffins.
There's a truck fiIIed with them
at the outer waII.
Get it out of here.
-What am I gonna do with the coffins, sir?
-Just get rid of the bIoody things!
Yes, sir.
(ALARM SOUNDING)
-Let's go.
-This way.
Guard, make sure
the main gate stays open!
Yes, sir.
(BOTH CHUCKLING)
Thanks, Luger.
-We did it.
-In spite of ourseIves.
I think we've made it.
Shit.
(GROANING)
You set me up!
WeII, it's quite simpIe.
I'm giving you a dose of your own.
Mind you, I was hoping that putting you
in the same room as SchIosse
wouId have ended differentIy.
Great shame. He was a good soIdier.
Yes, Major.
At Ieast I got him to your office in time.
Yes, good job, Lieutenant Forsyth.
You EngIish bastards!
That phone caII you overheard,
that was my officiaI notification.
The war ended today.
In a few hours, we shaII be
reIeasing the other prisoners.
It was fun, wasn't it? Cheerio.
Oh!
By the way,
I have changed my mind about you, Luger.
You are definiteIy worth a buIIet.
WeII, Luger wanted a discharge
from the army
and that's exactIy what he got.
(CACKLING)
TaIk about a bIeeder among men.
I guess now he'd rather fright than snitch.
(CACKLING)
Now then,
Iet's see what you maggots are made of!
About face!
Parade, march!
Hut, two, three, four!
Present arms!
Now that's what I caII hack-tive service.
(LAUGHING)