Be careful!
It might be dangerous.
Take it easy! Take it easy!
You'll be fine. Just fine
A basic rule in journalism is to always thank
the person you interview
for any exclusive or secret revealed.
I have to admit that this one
...is the hardest interview
I've ever done in my career.
But nothing's impossible
for Miranda Tovar.
You know?
Being a prostitute is as hard
as being a reporter.
Something you want to add?
Well.
In that case we'll leave this interview here.
I hope I see you again some day.
See you in hell, Senator Davis.
"The Wild Reporter"
I told you as soon as
you knock at the right doors
you would start climbing
your way to success.
Sister, I'm so happy
you'll live here with me.
It smells like something burned.
I think it is you.
You're crazy!
- Yes, it is you.
Listen, soon I'll stop
being a reporter.
I will become the director
of The Publisher.
I think you should keep like this,
doing a good job and everything
else will just come along.
No sister, in this life
nothing comes by its own.
I'm a woman who sets goals
and get there, at any cost.
Any!
Hello! I'm home.
How are you, sweetie?
You are so pretty.
Hi Miranda, how are you?
Her boss is very happy,
for her article about immigration.
Oh really? Congratulations.
- Thank you.
Well, I'm leaving now.
I have to get ready.
I'm meeting my boss later on.
Sweetie.
I missed you.
There's no turning back.
You'll have to suck it up.
Come on, chief.
You know I'm the best
qualified for this case.
Give me this investigation.
No Jose Luis.
You think you can choose
your cases as you wish?
When you're chief of this department
you can do whatever you want.
All right, fine!
And, what am I going to do now?
Arrest bums?
No, something better.
You're going to take care
of a drug dealing business
going on in a stripper club.
But boss, this.
I want you to be in charge.
That's it.
"The Pamperers"?
Don't you speak Spanish?
"The Pamperers".
What exactly you want me
to develop in this interview?
The article you wrote about
Senator Davis's life was a hit.
By the way, do you know what
happened to Senator Davis?
No.
His car exploded. He's dead.
But, what happened? When?
This morning. And that interview
we published today.
couldn't have been more timely.
The edition sold out.
It's a tragedy!
We all will die some day,
won't we?
Besides no one liked him much.
Now let's get into business.
I want that article about
the life of a stripper.
Mr. Gabriel, but... I think.
No buts! I want you to disguise
as a stripper.
I want it to be from
a woman's point of view
who's in the need of strip tease
to make money.
Are you asking me to turn
into a stripper?
Just imagine the headlines.
Strip tease! Out of pleasure,
need or money?
The life of a stripper.
Special report by Miranda Tovar.
Of course I won't strip.
Of course you will strip.
You're the one who came here
looking for a job.
But it this really necessary?
Listen. I have my hands
in many things right now.
All I can offer you is a job
as a dancer.
And besides dancing,
you also have to strip.
I need to see the merchandise
you may offer in my business.
If you're not interested
don't waste my time.
Very good!
Talent my ass!
I won't allow you to talk that way
about Miranda. She's my sister.
I'm sure she got the job
by sleeping with someone.
Shame on you!
How could you say that?
I'm sorry, baby. Forgive me.
How do you dare to judge her
like that without knowing her?
Right. I'm an idiot.
Please forgive me.
She suffered a lot with dad's death
and mom's schizophrenia.
I want to make it up for
all the years we were apart.
Right. It won't happen again.
I promise.
You could be the show sensation.
What was your name again?
Well, never mind.
My name is Miranda.
- I'm Shakis.
Now I present to you, the only
the sensational, the red-hot.
Miranda, the wild woman!
If I had half of what you have
more than enough.
I could keep my husband.
You're hired.
"The Pamperers".
This is your work place.
Girls.
Please come here.
Welcome the latest acquisition
of "The Pamperers".
Welcome. I'm Candy.
- Hi!
Shall we go?
Go where?
I forgot. It's beach day!
Every two days we go to the beach
and have fun getting a tan.
Moron, can't you see
where you step?
I'm very sorry.
It was an accident.
Accident! Can't you open
your eyes wide before you walk?
You're too cute to
have that temper.
I'm sure you don't even have
a boyfriend. It's a shame.
Lots of meat but not hungry.
What's wrong with you?
- That's none of your business!
You are crazy.
- Yeah right.
Look at this mess.
Miranda. Good company you got there.
Who's your friend?
My friend?
I don't know this moron.
He just walked over me.
- I'm sorry.
Do you like walking over people?
Wouldn't you like to walk over me?
No, thanks.
What's his problem?
Would you like my phone number?
Very kind.
We'll see each other again.
Men. Who can understand them?
Who understands men?
Are you sure you put them here?
Please, don't get started.
I know where I put
my blue boxers.
They're my favorite.
They're not here.
I know that because
I've looked everywhere.
What's wrong with you?
You're acting worse than a child.
You lose everything
and then you try
to blame it all on me.
You're not the same woman.
Ever since your sister moved in
you haven't been the same.
Will you start with that again?
Yes, because you're different!
This place is turning into a hell.
And you know what?
I hate your sister!
I hate her, Raquel!
It doesn't matter to my family
whether I'm a secretary or a stripper.
I'm doing this out of need.
We all say the same thing.
But after a while you get used
to easy money, to presents
and you go on sinking in debts,
until it's impossible to stop.
You do this for love or pleasure?
Miranda.
You know, this sounds like an interview.
I'm saving to pay for my studies.
I know this won't be forever.
Candy, come with us
to the bathroom.
We'll talk later.
By the way, that swimsuit
looks great on you.
You will pay for this!
Hey, give me that.
Give me back my top.
Someone should teach
you good manners.
I'm telling you to give
me back my top.
But I asked you for that
report last month.
Don't you know the competition
is getting all the market?
Senator Davis' interview
was a hit.
That was good. Scandal, death,
that's what sell news papers.
But we can't rest now.
Miranda is working on that.
She'll hand it over by...
Make sure she hands it in today.
Scandal. Violence.
Those are the ingredients that
makes people to buy our paper.
Your position is at stake here.
I'll call the police if you don't
give me back that top.
I'm so scared.
I would like to see that.
May I answer that?
- Get out of here, moron!
Hello? Yes, I'm on that.
Today? All right.
Some prince? Poor boy!
He has no idea of your temper.
Give me that.
You're wild, but there's a huge
emptiness of love in your eyes.
Didn't you say you don't know him?
Girls, you're impossible.
You're easier than the rule of one.
You're a great kisser. Miranda.
By the way, my name is Jose Luis.
Go away!
Let's go.
Heavy hand but nice lips.
Miranda. What a woman!
Hello?
Are you sure?
Okay, I'm on my way.
Please forgive me.
I know it's not an excuse,
but all of a sudden our life has
changed after Miranda moved in.
She has been through a lot.
She has no one else.
After dad passed away.
our mother was confined
in a mental institution.
She had many foster parents.
Life hasn't been easy for her.
And now she's happy at last.
You never told me.
Dad killed himself and that made
our mother to lose her mind.
Miranda was taken to
an adoption house.
I couldn't obtain her custody
because I couldn't support her.
Stop crying.
Please forgive me.
Forgive me.
I am an idiot.
Listen, don't cry anymore.
I promise I'll change my
attitude toward her.
Don't listen to her.
She has always been jealous of
those prettier than her.
Your family knows you're a stripper?
Are you out of your mind?
My mom thinks I'm a receptionist.
If she finds out she'll go nuts.
Poor mom. Do you have a family?
No. I don't have anyone.
Today is my lucky day.
This looks like a crime.
Heels.
Me, these shoes? No way.
At least not this kind of shoes.
I came here to work as a dancer,
not as a prostitute.
Oh, dear! This is not the
Convent of Charity.
And believe me, when you see
all that money in front of your nose,
you'll put all those baths
of purity aside.
Fine. So, do you have
a more screaming color?
Something like bright green.
I knew it.
No one can resist the money.
You're not here to decide.
You're here to obey.
All right.
I know I'm here to obey, chief.
But I specialized in plots.
I'll say it again.
The decision was made.
And I'm asking you to keep
away from Senator Davis' case.
I was told you've been
sneaking around.
I found something out.
What are you talking about?
It was not an accident.
I think he was murdered.
Really? And who murdered him?
I suspect it was a woman.
A woman?
That's what men come
to see in this club.
To watch the exotic dance.
Your sensuality and horniness.
Come here.
Between you and me.
No one knows how to dance with
that pole better than me.
What's so special about it?
It's just going once or twice
around the pole and that's it.
Miranda! You're being
very disrespectful.
Please God, let this I just heard not be an
advance of my punishment at the Last Judgment.
Listen, when you're up here
with all those thirsty men
looking at you with lust,
you have to seduce them
with your lure.
You have to picture yourself
making love with that pole.
An as intensity goes up,
you have to get more into it.
Remember, the more
you heat your audience,
the more money they'll pay.
So you'll get more money.
They'll get thirstier
and they'll buy more drinks!
You're a thief!
Give me back my purse!
Sweetie.
Thank you for being so understanding.
You know I would do anything
for you, sweetie.
We're the only family Miranda has.
Okay, stop worrying.
Every thing will change.
Today I work part shift but if they
ask me to stay longer I will.
We need the extra money.
Miranda could collaborate
a little bit, don't you think?
Sweetie!
I'm sorry.
Don't start, come on.
I have to work.
Stay a little longer.
Okay, that's it.
I'll call you later. Bye.
You won't accuse me
of something I didn't do.
Listen, darling. You better calm down
if you don't want me to teach you
a lesson so you know where
your place is in here.
Time out, girls!
What's going on, Casilda?
This prick stole my glow
case that I use in my make-up.
I didn't steal anything.
I'm sure you did it when
you were alone on the beach.
Stupid! You're a bastard!
- Casilda! Calm down.
Listen, this is not a market.
Don't you see this is
a high class club?
And I won't allow you to fight
like two vulgar greengrocers.
I want my glows back.
I have a set of glows I got from
the flea market in Los Angeles.
You will look stunning.
But if you fight.
I'll kick your asses out of here.
The two of you.
You know I do what I promise.
I knew you were into something.
What is this?
Oh dear! Life is full of surprises.
What is your game?
We're going to find out right away.
Leave my recorder alone!
I couldn't find the glows I got
from Hollywood, but I got these
in another flea market.
They're as good as the others.
Is something wrong?
- Nothing!
We were just talking girl's stuff.
You know, I'm an expert in that.
Now put this on so you see
what shades these glows have.
Be careful. I'll be watching you.
My God.
What were you talking about?
I don't know if I should tell you.
I think I shouldn't.
Come on!
We shouldn't have secrets.
You're right.
She told terrible things about you.
Your lack of humanity, your abuses.
and specially your drinking problem.
Me, a drunk!
I may be gay. I may be a bitch.
but never a drunk!
Take it easy.
I should go home. I have to get
ready for my first night.
I swear I didn't believe any
of what she said to me.
Especially that thing about
your problem with stomach gases.
Bye.
Gases. me?
Fabian.
Miranda.
I think this is yours.
Yes, they are.
Why do you have them?
I don't know. They just were
in the laundry the other day.
I'm sorry, but there's a problem
with the shower's faucet.
And I have to take a shower
before I go to work.
Are you going to work at nights?
A special report. You know how
a reporter's life is.
Would you help me?
Okay, let's go.
It was nothing.
- Oh, my!
Apparently the screw was loose.
Really?
- Yes.
You know, I'm crazy about you.
Darling, I'm back!
Miranda?
I don't know why Fabian
can't get along with you,
when both are so messy.
Miranda! Miranda!
Yes, what is it?
I'm very happy that you're with us.
And Fabian is happy too.
Could you wait until I finish
showering for us to talk?
Are you telling me you're ashamed,
of your sister seeing you naked?
Have you see Fabian?
Sure, a while ago.
Didn't you see him?
I swear I don't like that Miranda
woman at all.
I don't think she's a bad person.
I know what it is. You're jealous.
Me, jealous? Of her? Come on!
Admit it. Clients will die when
they see Miranda dancing.
You're going to lose some clients.
Over her? Oh, come on, Candy!
She can't even dance.
She may have a great body,
but she's too silly.
Clients like boldness, sensuality,
and she's harder than a board.
Anyway, you shouldn't mess with her.
She declared war on me already.
But I'll find out what she's up to.
I'm telling you she had
a tape recorder in her purse.
A tape recorder! What for?
How would I know!
But I have to find out.
Girls.
Shakis! Darling!
The glows look great on me.
You were right. They are better
than those from Hollywood.
As I was saying,
girls.
I want to introduce a very dear
and special person.
He is Mister Sugar.
Pleased to meet you.
He will be honoring us
with his presence.
So tonight I want your total
cooperation, okay?
I know I'm not perfect.
I have my flaws.
Like people say, breed crows and
they will gouge your eyes out.
I've been like a mother to you.
You're ungrateful.
That's all I got to say to you.
You're a poisonous viper!
Me, a drunk! Never!
Let's go.
Damn Miranda. She shouldn't
have messed with me.
I'm so happy for you.
Will you come back late?
- I don't know.
I have to do this report.
And what is it about?
About the night life in the city.
Okay, but don't forget your cell phone
in case you need anything.
All right.
Fine. I love you, bye.
What do you say?
Shall we wrap this up?
No.
- Please don't say that.
You'll have to wait until tomorrow.
I want to make you mine now.
We'll do it tomorrow
all the times you want.
You drive me crazy.
Of course it was that stupid of Miranda
to put those ideas in Shakis' head.
You can't be certain.
You know how Shakis is.
He must be "on his days".
Right, don't listen to her.
You know he likes drama.
He must have fought
with his "husband".
I'm going to teach that woman
how to respect me.
Well, sister, see you later.
Do you have batteries in your phone?
- Yes. Bye.
Is something wrong?
There is. But I don't know
if I should ask you.
After all who am I to get
in your personal life?
You're my sister. You may
ask me whatever you want.
I never thought you and Fabian
would like wild sex.
What are you talking about?
Come on!
With me you don't have to pretend.
I had a boyfriend who also
liked that stuff.
I don't understand.
- What do you mean?
Come on Raquel, I mean that
huge bite on Fabian's chest.
He was watering the
garden without a shirt.
I went there to give him some
clothes that were in my laundry.
And I saw the mark.
It must be nice to be able to do all
the crazy things with your husband.
Yes, but.
There's nothing to be ashamed of.
It's the most natural thing, to vent
your carnal desires with your husband.
Well, I'm off to work now.
I'm going to earn my bread
with my forehead's sweat.
What's wrong with you?
I'm furious! I'm not feeling well.
You know, you should
calm down a little.
Everything is that bastard
woman's fault.
But she won't laugh at me.
You'll see.
I think you're overreacting.
You know Shakis is a drama queen.
But I don't have to pay
for that slut's mistakes.
You better calm down.
You don't have insurance,
you can't afford getting sick.
That slut is dangerous.
I'm sure she's a witch or something.
I've always been Shakis' best girl.
You know sometimes Shakis is like
a little boy with a new toy,
but after a while he will get bored
and he'll find someone else.
Well, I'm going to take her
out of the way for good.
Stop talking like that.
You're freaking me out.
Now let's forget about all this and
grab something to eat. I'm starving.
You're right. At least I have the lead
in this business.
That's the one I like to hear.
Now leave the drama for the soap operas.
Do you have any glows?
I must be looking really bad.
All this because of that stupid...
I don't have any.
Please hurry, I'm starving.
Now, with great pleasure.
I want to present to you.
The unique, the hottest.
Miranda, the wild!
But wasn't it her first time?
Come on, they all say the same.
We all are stripper in disguise.
Hey, don't fart without a notice!
Dear, why are you so quiet?
Is there something bothering you?
No, no, nothing.
I told you I'll change my
attitude toward your sister.
In fact, we talked a lot this afternoon.
You know. Yes?
Also, have you forgotten we didn't finish
something this morning? Remember?
Yes, I saw the mark on his chest.
Get out!
What's the matter?
Get out of here!
When you feel like telling me the truth,
then you may come back.
I think you're losing your mind.
Miranda told me the truth.
Listen, I'm telling you the truth.
This girl is a goddess.
She'll be great for business.
I'm so envious. Good envy.
But you know that girl
is hotter than me.
Darling, you don't have to be jealous.
She's a woman, and you know
I don't like women.
Besides, you and I are
not officially dating,
just friends with rights.
It's a shame you're in Los Angeles.
Do you miss me?
Really? A lot?
Me too dear.
I miss you too.
Like a real beast.
I just want to hug you.
Listen, when you get back here make sure you
bring your friends so they see our new acquisition.
They're going to die!
I don't understand how being so hot
she's not working in Hollywood,
or in any of those Latin soap operas.
Daddy, I wish you were here.
And you better behave, okay?
Don't forget I know a lot of people.
Alright.
I have to go now.
There are some birds watching.
Walls can hear.
There are ears flying around.
if you know what I mean.
Alright.
Do you love me?
A lot?
Tell me you miss me.
Okay, I love you, bye.
Bye, darling, bye.
Shouldn't you be dancing, baby?
Shakis, I want to clear things up with you.
I never lie.
And I believe you. I just want
you to accept my apologies.
I was a real prick on the beach.
I shouldn't have done what I did.
And then what happened
to you on stage.
Please, I don't want to talk about it.
Someone played a joke on me.
Have you been in this business
for a long time?
It's my first night.
What a debut!
I guessed so.
You must come here very often.
I'm no saint.
I've came a couple of times with friends,
but I'm not a vicious person either.
What are you looking at?
You're beautiful. I love you.
But you don't know me.
And I'm not about making out
with strangers.
You're right. I'm Jose Luis Duran.
I'm a police detective.
Why are you telling me that?
First because this morning
you needed a cop.
Well, here I am.
And second, because we heard there's
a drug dealing business going on here.
Do you know anything?
I don't know if I should tell you.
Trust me.
Alright, listen.
There's a girl, her name is Casilda.
She has something to do with it.
She threatened me because I busted
her selling that crap to a client.
No one can know I told you.
They would kill me.
Thank you, gorgeous.
Don't worry, I won't say a word.
Shakis. I can't believe you.
How could you believe
in that slut instead of me?
Life has taught me well.
But you trust me.
You trusted me.
But you're like a...
Like a mother to you.
I wouldn't dare to betray you.
What I am, what I know,
I owe to you.
That's why it hurts so much.
Because there's nothing
worse than treason.
Do you remember when I?
When with my own hands
I made your first dress you wore here.
With these hands!
Remember?
Shakis. How could I forget it?
It was the dress you were wearing
the day you met your boyfriend.
I never said that,
please believe me.
I've learned people change.
It's a rule of life.
But I haven't changed!
Believe me.
Stop it! Now, get back to work.
It's a great night.
I feel the pain a mother feels when
her children turn their backs on her.
But I have to stop crying now.
I don't want to ruin my make-up.
A lot of men out there are waiting
for me, and Shakis must shine.
Always.
I must go.
Now stop crying.
The show must go on.
Miranda! Why are you
getting home so late?
Yes, it's a little late.
What are you doing here?
Raquel is acting very strange.
She kicked me out of the bedroom.
Oh, Fabian.
It's okay. She'll be fine tomorrow.
Take a seat.
What is it?
I don't know if I should tell you.
Tell me what?
My sister is cheating on you.
Are you kidding me?
You're a good man. You don't
deserve her treason.
That's why I couldn't hold it
anymore and I kissed you.
Because it's not fair that you
give her all your love and she...
While she is screwing
with another man.
Stop kidding me Miranda.
Don't be a fool!
These flowers were in her car.
And she will deny it.
And you will get hurt.
We have to bust her to set her up.
Wait. Take it easy. Stay with me.
Calm down.
They're like my daughters, detective.
I can't believe what you're telling me.
It will be just a preventive questioning.
We haven't found any evidence,
but there's an accusation
against her.
Shakis, could you wait until tomorrow?
I'm exhausted. I want to rest.
I feel sorry for you Casilda.
To screw your future just like that.
Don't you know about shame?
No! Wait.
What is all this about?
I'm innocent!
I haven't done anything.
My sister is shameless,
and a fool.
You're the best lover
in the world.
Don't stop.
Fabian wait.
Hello?
No, boss. I don't sleep.
Yes. I'll deliver it right now
before closure.
I have to go.
- No, where?
I have to work.
No.
Don't leave me like this.
Miranda!
Miranda?
- Yes, boss.
You should see her.
She looks like she was
taken out of a soap opera.
I don't care.
The fact is that the bosses
are very pleased how fast
we put two and two together.
You think that woman
will lead us to something?
We'll find out right now.
Why did he cheat on me?
I gave him everything!
Because that's how men are.
They're trash, worse than beasts.
Not Fabian. He never failed me.
He always gave me all his love.
Oh sister. You have got so
much to learn about men.
All they want is to fulfill
their instincts, like animals.
That mark on Fabian's chest
must have an explanation.
Of course it does.
Fabian has a lover and he's
planning to escape with her.
No, Fabian is my husband.
He can't do that to me.
Raquel! Don't even think
about confronting him.
He has to explain to me.
No. He will deny it.
and he'll find a way to make
you think you're the one to blame.
What am I going to do?
Bust him. Ruin him.
Today I was going to tell him.
I'm pregnant.
Me and Fabian will have a child.
Senator Davis. You drove me crazy
since I interviewed you.
You're so beautiful, Miranda.
And you so stupid in trusting me.
It is a spectacular night,
filled with stars and dreams.
The low passions of the night become the
accomplice of an urgent need to survive
Mixed with broken wings
of fame aspirations.
The night has been born and from the hell's
core, like if coming out from the Avernus
Someone dances at the
rhythm of an exotic music.
A dancer who we'll call Pamela.
very soon, Pamela will take
all her clothes off.
But shame and she don't speak
the same language anymore.
Like every night, Pamela will be naked
with her legs and her hopes
opened and unprotected
to the lust of the highest bidder.
Inside this strippers cabaret
that hides in the moonlight.
Why am I thinking about him?
If this gets into the press' ears,
it will be the end of this place.
Where will then the executives
of this city shelter.
so they can admire the perfection
of women's bodies?
But, is Casilda involved in
that drug thing?
I don't know.
But I've always thought that
tragedies never come alone.
This is really a big problem.
Thank you for letting me
enjoy this moment with you.
I love you.
Promise me you won't leave me.
How could I? You're the best
thing that have ever happened to me.
Where are you going?
Do you want to make love?
Even the question is silly.
Handsome!
No!!!
Could that be possible?
I won't lie to you. Your visit
has brightened my day, detective.
Are you married?
The reason of my call
is strictly professional.
I understand.
Do you want something to drink?
No, thanks.
I need to talk to Miranda.
And you say this is
strictly professional?
That's right.
Fine.
In all this tragedy something
good had to happen, Miranda.
Explain yourself Shakis. I don't get it.
That hottie. The police guy.
He wants to see you.
He told me it's work,
but I know men.
and I can see lust
and desire in his eyes for you.
Oh girl, I wish I was you.
Don't say such things.
I'm going to let him in.
And if he tries to abuse you.
Just enjoy it!!!
Come on in.
- Thanks.
I know you're going to think
that I'm crazy, and that's right.
I haven't thought of anything
else but your eyes.
And your lips.
I'm crazy about you, Miranda.
I don't know if this is craziness
or love at the first sight.
You look great. Will you be
working extra hours today?
What do you care?
Do you want to know so you
can "organize" your schedule?
I've never felt this way before.
Thanks. But you have to leave.
I'll be back soon.
Senator Davis take me. I'm yours.
I'll make you enjoy me until you die.
Miranda, you're so beautiful.
What are you doing with that?
That's mine. You shouldn't.
Why are you sneaking in my things?
Is this yours too?
You're an idiot!
Why did you do it?
You're a murderer.
You killed Senator Davis!
Wait here.
- No!!!
Raquel, please!
Stop talking to me like that.
I talk to you the way I want!
I do as I please!
You're cynical.
- I may be. Now, have a good day.
Who might she be
cheating on me with?
I have to find out
who's my husband's lover.
I'm going to give her a lesson.
What's going on, Miranda?
I'll tell you later.
That man is after me.
What?
Detective! What a big gun!
Why all this violence?
Women can be silly.
- Really.
If that man was chasing me
with that big gun.
I would surrender
without resistance.
The things you got to see!
Freeze!
Miranda please.
Don't do any stupid thing
you might regret later.
Leave me alone, moron!
Please Miranda. I love you. I'll help you.
And we'll get out of this one.
Whatever the problem is we can work it out.
Love doesn't exist, you bastard.
Even though you could've made
me believe in it again.
Miranda!
I hope you understand.
Look, I understand, but I just want to
know if you're going to lend me that money.
Tell me who Raquel's lover is.
I'm in a hurry.
I can't talk right now
I have to run to cover that news.
I'm going.
- No!
There's something I got to tell you.
All right.
You're a too big temptation to me.
I want you out of my house.
As soon as you get back from
your sudden trip I want you out.
I truly love your sister Raquel.
I want to make that clear.
Whatever. Let's go to the bank
so you lend me that money.
It's a shame.
Doubt will never let you be happy.
Miranda is my husband's lover.
I can't believe it.
I feel so dirty.
Don't worry,
everything will be just fine.
You're right. Everyone has to
fight for happiness at any cost.
That's right. Shall we go now?
Yes, I'm really in a hurry.
Why, why?
Miranda! Fabian!
What's going on?
She just left, with my husband.
Miranda, is your sister?
- Yes.
Get up please.
I am going after them.
Now get back in the house.
We're going after them.
Stop!
Stop her!
Miranda!
She told me you were cheating on me
and that you were going to leave me.
Sweetie. She told me you
were the one cheating on me.
I wouldn't dare!
I know my love.
I'm sorry.
Her condition is very serious.
I don't think she's going to make it.
Are you her sister?
- Yes, doctor.
Did you know your sister escaped
from a mental institution?
Miranda?
- Yes.
Being raped by her own father
generated serious problems.
That got worse when he died.
What? She was confined when
she was little but,
I never knew she got back in.
We did some research and we found out
that she escaped eight months ago.
She's very dangerous because
of her obsessions.
What are you talking about?
An urge to have control over men to
destroy them, physically and mentally.
I forgive you Miranda.
If I knew about all this before
I would have helped her.
She would be alive.
Stop torturing yourself.
Everything will be just fine.
But if we have a girl, we're going
to name her after her, Miranda.
Casilda, please forgive me.
It's okay.
Stop it, I saw him first.
Don't forget that if you
don't buy, don't bother.
I'm still sad about poor Miranda.
It will always be a sad episode
in the story of this night club.
"The Pamperers"
But the show must go on.
So go and get ready.
Are you in a hurry? You may
"relax" a little if you want.
No thanks, I got to go.
Men!
Here.
- What is this?
Read it. There's something
that will interest you.
Okay. Thanks again.
I'm sorry for all the trouble.
Bye.
I really would marry that guy.
Would he be a jealous man?
But of course, all men are jealous.
The biggest danger for a stripper is not
to show the most intimate parts of her body,
but to fall in love.
Because up there on stage she may not only
lose her clothes, she may also lose her heart.
But that's life. An exotic dance is where
passion, lust and money can end with love.
Subtitles by LeapinLar