"The Beacon"
- Do not forget to download the tank
the guest bathroom, ma'am ...
All the secrets ...
are revealed with a simple ...
- It seems that all is well.
- I will leave to speak.
I wait outside.
- Thanks, Mr. Butters.
- Then the bathroom work?
- And do you think? Renting
is better than expected.
- It's great, because of its location.
- It's close to campus
the room is huge.
- Yes, but only has one.
- It's a big change.
- We go back there to visit.
Maybe at birthdays.
- We return
whenever you want.
- Okay, I'm ready. Please
Let me be ready, Paul.
- I'll talk to Butters.
- Okay.
- We'll be fine here, dear.
- Mr. Butters? My wife likes,
but I have some doubts.
- I'll be fine.
- No, Einstein,
it goes in the bathroom.
- See? It is written "potty."
- Is there, where is the toilet.
- Thanks.
"You found a great apartment.
- And was not even looking.
It was pure luck.
- Look at little sister ...
... There he is.
- Now back to work, guys.
- Hello, Mr. Shaw.
planning to give some spied?
- I am an astronomer.
- I get it.
- He likes to admire "celestial bodies"?
- Yeah, sure.
- "The Road to Heaven" astronomer? A
My wife loves these things.
- She is a Cancer.
- Sure it is.
- Ei, forgive me for that.
I pretended not to embarrass.
- No problem.
Women live
expose her breasts.
- You move here?
- I am helping my sister.
- I'll love
tranquiIo a building.
- Cool! Then I will come to visit
frequently. My name is Christina.
- I Will Tyler.
Nice to meet you.
- My friends tell me Ty.
-Ty?
- It is, as "tie" in English.
- O "tie"?
- I dajas without words.
- Why do not you think about it
depues answer me?
- Okay.
- Nice to meet you, Ty.
- The pleasure was mine.
- Beware!
"Excuse me.
- Honey, are you okay?
- Yes.
- Paul? Paul?
- Danny ...
- Danny, are you?
- No lie!
Come back here!
- Let go!
- Paul?
- Hey, sleepyhead.
Sleep well?
- Yes. I think our
neighbors are fighting.
- Okay.
- We should not do anything?
- No way.
Let's take our coffee. Voila!
- And if you have a child?
- Then you are making pancakes.
-Paul!
- One of the advantages of big city
is that we need not get us.
- Mainly when there
nothing to worry about.
- Are you using tie!
- Yes. The chancellor wants
go meet the Faculty.
- The I want to impress.
- How am I?
- Looks like you're wearing a costume.
- This is what all
teachers elegant ...
... Use this season.
- Is it true?
- You will have to get me out of
penalty area after school.
- Be good to
other children, right?
- Oh, be careful in the bathroom.
The mirror broke.
- Poor ...
- I cut.
- Bacon ... bacon ...
Where he hid the bacon?
- In the second shelf
behind the butter.
- Very funny!
- I love you too.
- Oh and let you otherwise.
- Maybe you want to use it again.
- Paul?
- Thank you, sir.
- It is a pleasure to work here.
- Welcome.
- Professor Paul?
- Professor Pau, the astronomer?
- Yes. Could you help?
I'm trying
find my office.
- I got this plane, but ...
- No offense.
We do this trick at all.
- It's room 1516.
- It's around here. I'll show you.
- I am Simon Valencia.
- I miss his presentation
this morning.
- Actually, nobody told me
you were here.
- Well, it's a pleasure to meet you now.
- Then, Astronomy? Fascinating!
I study Cultural Anthropology ...
- Comparative Theology
Morphology and Folklore.
- All "locologias."
- Yes! You are very funny.
- You will take the class
Astronomy too?
- You think it should?
Maybe even help me with my thesis ...
... Astrological Methodologies
Contemporary.
- After all, astronomers and astrologers
trying to do the same thing.
- You think so?
"Sure.
- Watching the stars
and try to understand God's face.
- What makes astronomers
in the largest "voyeurs."
- You see? You're funny.
It's here.
- Well, thank you, Simon.
It was a pleasure to meet you.
- Thank you, Professor Paul.
The pleasure was mine.
- You should not go to your class?
- I am student.
I am an assistant professor.
- I teach these "locologias."
We will share this office.
- The Department of Anthropology
had no more space ...
... then I spent here.
- Professor Paul, which seemed
carpooling too?
- Permission!
- I saw that!
- Do not just follow me in the street
now haunts me in my house!
- Come on, Miss Carver!
She is not stalking.
- I do not remember having directed
word, Mr. Tyler.
- At his age, no doubt.
- I have only 32!
- Maybe counted in dog years.
- Sorry, I was taking photos.
Do not even know who you are.
- She is Vanessa Carver.
- Ex-atriz, today is the resident diva
Edifício of Beacon.
- Well, I did not offend.
- My husband and I moved
here. I am ...
- A rat stock photography.
- Mr. Butters should send spray
the building.
- Then you better be careful, "Mrs. Spider."
- Pests!
- She did one of those novels
passing night.
- You know, those full of sex and scandal?
She quickly makes friends, right?
- I think it is far from dying
suffocated by his own vomit.
- Oh God!
- I'm Will Tyler.
- And I Bryn Shaw.
- I met her sister.
- I know!
- You're the kind of ...
"My friends call me Ty."
- And I bet you want to cause
a good impression, right?
- I have a job for you.
Come!
- Then, Bryn, always take pictures
when you move into a new place?
- Well ... yes.
- I think so.
- I always do.
- It is cocnocer the new place?
Have more control? It's smart.
- What do you do, Will?
- Work on "KIein, Horstman & Enos."
- Legal?
- No, it is an investment bank.
- I am a foreign insurance analyst.
- Monitoring the Stock Market
Singapore.
- That is, basically ...
... an elegant way of saying
I'm stuck
the night shift.
- These photos are yours?
- Yes, take a few years ago.
- I think now you have
some newer.
- Yes, I think so.
- Will, could you bring me that box?
- White and black?
- I like things
the old fashioned way.
- The black and white is not a
bad way to see the world.
- Look around ...
As the call?
- Mrs. Spider.
- Mrs. Spider!
- What is it?
- Do not know.
- A shadow maybe, the mechanism?
- No, that's an arm.
- And that's a face. It's a ...
-No.
- It's a boy!
- No, it can be.
- Hello?
- You must help me!
Following me!
- Who? Who is followed?
- We got it! Here was
that the thief entered and left.
- He was to be behind the car radios.
- There is a building block ...
... where all the cars stolen
the garage.
- I will send repair this door
and install a safety lock.
- Excellent.
- And you sir? There is something else you
or your spouse wish to report?
- We are not married.
- Really?
- Sorry.
- I like to go
my department.
- The accompany.
- The hero, the salvos!
- It is "the winner" official.
To the victor, the salvos.
- And is not no hero!
- I know.
- Third, please.
- I'm sure the police
find the man.
- You must be new in town.
- Is sure to be right?
- Yes. Nothing a bath
warm and long no cure.
- Thanks.
- Excuse me, what is your name?
- Vanessa Carver.
- Paul Shaw.
- Nice, Paul Shaw.
- Hello?
- Bryn? Dear?
- I'm here!
- You took pictures!
- Yes, some things.
- Nothing important.
- And how did it go?
- This was an excellent idea.
- It occurred to me suddenly.
- Then, she was pretty?
- Who?
-Who?
- Your damsel in distress.
It was pretty?
- No, she was a witch.
Calva, three teeth.
- You're lying!
- She had an eye on
middle of the forehead.
- One of the things
I love you.
- Today I met a friend of Christine.
Will Tyler. He is handsome.
- Should fall in love
and have babies.
- And you think that Chrissy?
- I think he will.
- Today he saved me
a horrible woman in the hall.
- Vanessa.
- Vanessa?
- Yes, it's an actress or model or something.
- So, back to the woman
you saved today. What is your name?
- In the midst of confusion
I forgot to ask.
- Danny!
- Danny! Danny!
- Find a focus, girls.
That.
- Smile.
- Fingers stretched.
- The kids call him
"Surfing in the elevator."
- They get on the roof of the elevator
and jump from one to another.
- And where are the parents?
Where are the parents?
- They are drunk? Drugged?
This is dangerous!
- I mean, look at these pictures!
"No!
"No, look! This guy ...
"It's not Daniel.
- Not Daniel.
- I know it's not Daniel!
- You think that's the point?
- And is not it?
-No.
- Okay, Bryn.
No problem.
- No problem.
- I'm having dreams again.
- You told Paul?
"No, he is with his new job.
- Two classes per week
for repeaters in Science.
- Three years ago,
it rained bids.
- He should not blame yourself.
"He did not do it.
- I do not blame.
- Professor Paul!
I brought donuts.
- I hope you enjoy.
- Hello, darling.
Are you okay?
- I told you not to go out!
- Please, no! No! No!
- Look at me!
Look at me when I'm talking about!
- Look into my eyes!
"Please, Dad!
- Look at me!
- Now you'll see!
I'll give you a lesson!
-Paul!
-Bryn, what happens?
- He was beating
I heard the blows and screams!
- And I could not ...
- What? Who?
- You are Mr. Shaw?
- Yes, Paul Shaw.
- Bryn, who is going?
Are you okay?
- Yes.
- I Karasic official.
- This is the official Ford.
- Mr. Shaw.
- His wife says he
witnessed aggression.
- I saw the children get there!
- I heard screaming,
and then I heard the shots ...
... and now let us
go there ...
- You did not understand ...
"Please, Mr. Butters.
- Mr. Butters, you can open
the door and show us?
- Police!
- I saw him coming here, Paul.
It's true.
- No one lives here for months!
- The apartment is empty.
- Maybe these people fled as
I call my wife to you.
- And how they could get?
- Change the locks whenever
a tenant moves out.
- I hold the keys
in a chest down.
- Who lived here?
- The Nash family.
They moved six months ago.
- Why?
- There was an accident.
Their son was playing ...
- In the elevator?
- The boy slipped, fell down.
It was terrible.
- I saw him.
- Damn, how many types of
shampoo can be?
- No one should underestimate
the imprtancia a good shampoo.
- One bottle can last for weeks.
- Much more than a few
of my relationships.
- I think I can
with commitment.
- Well, lets see what is
most important to you.
- A good body? Resilience?
- The elasticity provided
is welcome.
- Most men
I prefer easy.
- I prefer not sting the eyes.
"Oh, you're the sensitive!
- Here.
- "Makes brushing."
It is not for you.
... "Balance", "fruity" ...
- How about this?
- "Bold"?
I think it's an excellent choice.
- And you are doing here.
These harassing me?
- I still have my way to work.
- Oh, yeah. Bryn told me
you work at night
in a bank.
- That must be exciting.
- I used to be. Now I would like
more time for me.
- Maybe we can get
agreement on that.
- Where is your cart?
- Oh, you better
Go look.
- Or I'll walk
to your car.
- Hello, Bryn.
Oh, Hello.
- I'm coming.
- Something does not smell right here,
Indeed, Bobby?
- A false alarm
never smells good.
- Why?
- It's just a hunch.
- You know that woman
not told us everything.
- Let, Kit remember what
happened the last time.
- Believe me.
Your psychiatrist would say the same.
- And who said the officers?
- Is upset,
and gave us a sermon.
- I was told that Bryn
under psychiatric treatment?
- Yes. The officer said that as
half of the city ...
... following treatment.
- Bitch!
- The building superintendent, Mr. Butters,
I try to calm things down.
- Bryn told me that you showed
photos of the child.
- Yes, I asked him to forget it.
She did not want to mess.
- You said you are having
dreams again?
- Here you go.
"Shoot the spider"
- Hey, son! Let me take you out
a photo. Come here!
- Mom, I'm going to lose
"Shoot the spider!
- Only one more to the album!
- Now smile!
That!
- Look at the sky.
A picture for Dad!
"Mom!
- I know, you're going to lose
"Shoot the chandelier."
- Okay! Done.
- Now you can go.
- Look at me, Mom!
Look at me!
- Thanks.
- He's coming.
- I'm dreaming, right?
You Ronnie Nash, right?
- What is happening?
- It was just a dream.
- Everything? Are you calling me
it was all a dream?
- There was no child
in the elevator.
It's just ...
... I believe that these
mixing your feelings.
- No, you do not understand ...
"No, I understand, yes.
- When Danny disappeared,
I listened to mourn your
all the time.
- Disarming the whole house.
- And then the child who
followed in the shopping ...
- I scared!
- I thought it was Danny.
- It seemed so
Danny ...
- He was identical to it, Paul!
-Bryn, nor seemed ...
- It was like, yeah.
- He did not looked like Danny!
- Dr. Kirke warned us that we could
move feel guilty.
- And I want you to call her tomorrow ...
... recommended for you
any doctor in the city.
- Paul, why are you doing this?
- Bryn, Bryn.
- We lost our son.
We lost Danny.
- And so,
I almost lost you you ...
... and I will not let it happen again.
I will not let it happen!
- You understand?
- Is that I have fear.
- Of what?
- I should be attending,
was my responsibility!
- I have so much fear that Danny hates me!
God! The hate me?
- Our son hates me!
- Please do not hate me!
- He does not hate you, dear.
- He can not hate you.
- I love you.
- Oh, my God!
- You know, appear to rescue
is becoming a habit.
- Very gallant.
"Well, I'm new in town.
- Where do you ride?
- How about Colorado?
- I have not ski.
- Sorry, I have
snow covers.
- Then you can leave in the middle.
- I must settle accounts
to my agent.
- Why? Have you done?
- I intend to make the mother
of a teenager in a commercial ...
- Perhaps I have mother's face
of a teenager?
- How are you?
Thirty? Thirty-one?
- You are an amazing man
perpicaz.
- Astronomers are
very observant.
- I'll have to kiss you again.
- I hate when I have reason.
- Not true!
- Here is a report of
Polícia of Peccadillo County.
- How did you get?
- Still I have some
friends in the Department.
- Our "Ms. False Alarm"
Bryn Shaw, has a history.
- She had a son.
- "He"?
- Yes, he disappeared.
About three years will
next Halloween.
- It was given as drowning,
but never found the body.
- It must have been hard for her
and husband, then?
- So call us now
to report abuse of a child ...
.. Who happened also is dead?
- It sounds like remorse.
"Kit, do not do this.
- Do what?
My job?
- You're not a detective.
You came back to wear the uniform
for a reason.
- Something stinks here.
- If you mess up again
familiia other suffer.
- And I think you can not
live with it.
- Where are you?
- Oh, you crazy lady!
- Gossip run.
- Well, people in this building
care should check their own lives.
- So, you're not mad?
- Totally. From head to toe.
With certainty.
- Well, I think the madness
is underestimated.
- Thanks.
- Pass.
- In fact,
I need to do me a favor.
- Going to speak well
me your sister?
- Okay.
-Mr. Butters, occurred again.
"You shook the handle?
- Yes, the shaken, the turn, rolled her.
So I gave a little dance.
- Well, let's fix that bathroom
before you suffer under others!
"Please send emails
Nash, Rev. 418, a :....
Rev. B 2533 Gibson Street "
- Mr. Nash? My name is Bryn Shaw.
I live in the Beacon Building y. ..
- Mr. Nash? Mr. Nash?
- Mr. Nash?
- Sorry for the inconvenience ...
... but wanted to ask
about Ronnie.
- You know about the game?
Surfing in the elevator?
- A neighbor said she heard screams
coming from your apartment ...
... and noise, as if someone
was being beaten,
and need to know ...
- Mr. Nash?
- Mr. Nash, I just wanted to know ...
- You hit your child?
- Ronnie was running
you, Mr. Nash?
So he was hiding
in the elevator?
- Mr. Nash, I need to know.
- What was your child doing
in the elevator shaft?
- Mr. Nash!
"He is coming"
- Call the police a
public phone ...
... and said she was worried
by a friend.
- I do not know how
could explain it.
- They will find it, right?
And will take care of it?
- If, yes.
- You want to call Christina
or your husband?
- No, please. Because neither
I know how to explain.
- My God!
dying alone and so!
- It's hard to believe that
whole family died.
- What do you mean, the whole family?
- The child, parent, and now the mother.
All dead.
- No, Ronnie's father was there.
- Bryn, do not play well.
- Why lie, Will?
It was he who opened the door.
- I do not know where it went.
Not know how ...
... he came out of that bathroom.
- Jim Nash died.
- It happened here, just a week
after the death of his son.
- Mr. Nash took the sewing kit
his wife, took out a scissor ...
... I get the screw
connects the two parts ...
... And one of the sheets,
he cut his own throat.
- No way.
- Thank you, Lieutenant.
- Lt. Hutton adopted
Beacon Building ...
... after what happened.
- It's a good place.
- People come, live,
build their lives.
- Most.
- If the majority.
- Take me to bed.
- I'm not mistaken.
Not this time.
- Mail, Professor Paul!
- Department of Science Festival?
- Yes, I do every semester.
- For students and
teachers have
opportunity ...
... fun together.
- It will be Halloween.
"Yes, that's the good part.
- Because it is a folk tradition?
"No, women in disguise.
- They're hot.
As I was told.
- Bryn hates Halloween.
- Look, I know this ...
- Hey, we need to take
a normal life, remember?
- Even so, sorry.
- You look very handsome.
- Hey, buddy.
- Reinforcements!
- You look fantastic.
- Thanks for the invitation.
- Interesting costume for
a financial analyst.
- And the scientist says
Dress magician!
- What?
- I remembered something I said
on women in disguise.
- ... That particular issue, no ...
- Thanks.
- Well, I like everything
related to the holidays.
- I know ...
- Darling.
- Thanks, dear.
- Sure.
- Look at them.
- ... collision with a Ford,
and only got ...
- Better go rescue them.
- Ah, no, no. Stay here
and make your contacts ...
... Share with your colleagues.
I'll take care of that.
- Are you sure?
- Claro. Abracadabra!
- Esses is my point:
everything is cyclical.
... The earth revolves around the sun,
blood flows through our body.
... the water evaporates, returns as rain
and evaporated again.
- As my patience.
- So if we have physical cyclic
why not a cyclical paraphysical?
- Type something supernatural?
- No, no, everything belongs
the natural world ...
- Nothing can be "supernatural."
Maybe out of the ordinary ...
... unusual. We die
we become pure consciousness, o. ..
- Ghosts?
- Spirits, more precisely.
- Or "soul" if you
parateológico brain.
- Ghosts are different
dealing with minor cycles.
- Why are not talking?
I'll give you a ride.
- I think I was annoying.
- Maybe a little anxious.
- Professor Valencia
I'm Bryn Shaw. I am the ...
- The wife of Paul! Should have
recognized by the holder portrait!
- He looks pretty
- Really?
- You said that ghosts
cycles occupy less ...
- You ... you think
they exist?
- I think it always pays
worth asking.
Why?
- You saw the two appearances?
- The child, several times.
The father, only once.
- In the apartment of the mother?
- Yes. It was very strange ...
... had several scissors
hung on the walls.
- They were open, so?
- Yes, exactly.
- The scissors is a cross
to ward off evil spirits.
- I think it worked.
- The cross is a symbol of faith.
- If you need more of them
because they do not think enough.
- I think the boy was
seeking help from her mother ...
... and the father followed him.
- As I said, it appears that
Nash dominated the life of your child.
- Your spirit can follow
dominate in death.
- So, you think of me?
- Was I lying about?
- Could be disrupted.
- The disturbance can cause
chemical changes in the brain.
- The ghosts are
a symptom of the imbalance ...
... disturbance or leaves it
attuned to their world?
- How I can release the child?
- And because he thinks I should try?
- Because it's just a kid ...
lost, scared.
- Parent, no. Appearances
suicide are dangerous.
- There is so much hatred.
- For many years, suicide
was considered a mortal sin.
- The suicide could not be buried
on holy ground nor enter into Heaven.
- They were buried at night,
secret, at the crossroads ...
... where criminals and witches
were buried.
- Look.
- Literally nailed
the drawer with stakes ...
... Not to be lifted.
- Like vampires.
- There came
the vampire myth.
- As a vampire, it was believed
the ghost of a suicide ...
could take
a corporeal form.
- Corporal? You mean ...?
- Meat. A reminder of life
that was wasted.
- Everyone dies.
- Death is inevitable:
self-destruction, no.
- Neither indifference.
- It mantedrá away from father?
- I promise.
- Please, just tell me
and free the child.
- Both are imprisoned in a cycle
of abuse and guilt.
- Break the cycle before he arrives
at its most traumatic.
- That would be the fall of the boy.
- But be careful not
reinforce the trauma ...
... or be trapped forever.
- Simon?
- If I break the cycle and assist
the boy to make the passage ...
... He could ...?
- What?
- He could take a message?
- Someone was mixing
came with the medication.
- It's good to be alive.
- Hello, Mrs. Shaw.
- Hello, Paul.
- Bryn?
- I'm tired.
- It was so embarrassing
occurred in the elevator last night.
- I do not suppose you told
your wife about me.
- "About You" would be
exaggerate the situation.
- Poor Lancelot! She forced you
to sleep on the couch?
- Vamos! I did not know
I was a secret.
- Nothing important, at least.
- What do you mean?
- Discretion should be mandatory
for someone in your field.
- Looks like someone was
research on the Internet.
- It was good to flirt with a star
decadent, but not with depraved.
- I was not flirting with you.
- Just need someone
I may go to work.
- Sign.
- If I break the cycle and assist
the boy to make the passage ...
- He could take a message?
- Tell ...
... I'm very sorry.
- Tell him I love,
I love him so much ...
- Tell him to give
my life ...
... my life
just to see him again.
... Just for a moment ...
Just to see him again.
- Tell him I'm sorry!
I'm so sorry! I'm so sorry!
- Professor, I got information
about our ghost hunt.
- Still not investigate
the story of his building.
- In cases of apparitions,
Most importantly is the place ...
... but in this case it is necessary ...
... since we have the luxury of knowing
when they started
the INDICATED ...
- What are you talking about?
- Instead investigate
such as expelling a ghost.
.. ruling out a formal exorcism ...
... since the Catholic Church
was more selective ...
... from that movie
with green vomit.
- Simon ...
- But it is much folklore
less elitist.
- Then, if we
a piece of clothing ...
Nash
or your child ...
... could make a thread
giving 7 knots ...
... and burn. Hence the ghost
would be forced to return ...
- What ghost?
- Ops!
- You've been talking to
my wife about ghosts?
- James and Ronald Nash.
- Find some newspapers
they say that ...
- Enough! For that!
- My wife is
under medical treatment.
- She is sick, and need not
your leave it worse.
- But she seek.
- And you did not see
I was disturbed?
- You are a tremendous desatre.
- Nothing I say will change.
- No one here?
- The job ends at 5.
- We raised videos on the Internet,
we do photo shoots.
- It's not pornography.
- No need to justify yourself.
"I do not. The Porn pay more.
- In addition, so do not need
take off my clothes ...
... to which I sometimes
forced in Hollywood.
- Why did you come here, Paul?
- I came to apologize.
- Really?
- I know how it feels to be
caught in a difficult situation.
... listening to others
judging.
- I had no right.
- It is very noble of you.
- Not really understand
the grace of all this ...
... but that should not affect
the way I treat you.
- You do not understand grace is this?
"No, I do not understand.
- Vanessa ...
- You understand the grace, Paul.
Grace is to have control.
- I did not come here for that.
- No? I have asked you
apologies in the building.
- I'm going.
- Too late. I'm stuck.
- I can leave here, Paul.
- Paul! Paul, wait!
- Paul, please!
- I can not let go, Paul!
I'm helpless!
- Paul?
- Why are you doing this?
- You said you understand how
it feels to be trapped.
Who caught you?
- Nobody.
I was not talking about me.
- I am prey.
I can not let go.
- I am helpless, Paul.
- Wives are false.
Toys for the camera.
- To be imprisoned is just ...
- An illusion.
- Where were you?
- What happened?
Where is Bryn?
- I came to visit Ty,
but stop by here before.
- She was lying in the bath
babbling about Danny ...
... and a guy named Ronnie.
- I gave him sedatives and lay down.
- I was afraid that
was hurt.
- You did the right thing.
- I know.
But it should have been me.
- Sorry you had
to bother.
- It will not happen again.
- You can not leave you alone.
Bryn What is happening is ...
- What is happening Bryn!
How could I forget?
- Do not be selfish!
- I lost my son.
- My son disappeared
and probably dead.
- And I can not even mourn for him.
- I can show my pain ...
... I stay calm
and support ...
... but lose
my wife also.
- Listen, I know ...
- No!
- You do not know.
- You stayed with us
3 weeks after
the first attempt.
- I live 3 years ago
counting pills, hiding scissors ...
... Knives hiding, hiding ...
- Your anger?
- Well, she should have
better care, right?
- I said it once.
- But that's what you think, Paul.
- That she did not care.
"No, I do not think so.
- But sometimes I like to ...
... to take care of itself.
- And also me.
- She is in a limbo, Paul.
She is trapped.
- You have no idea of power
that gives a person
being trapped.
- You know, when my girlfriend started
to talk about being cornered ...
... was usually because they had
made some stupidity.
- You're really angry, right Paul?
- You must learn to hide
better.
- Ground floor, please.
- We need to know
Health Insurance Plan ...
... or the person being
responsible for paying the bill.
- We can see that count?
- No, sir. I need it now.
- Put my name.
Paul Shaw.
- After we solve the rest.
She is from the family.
- Bryn, we go home.
- I can not.
- They will call us ...
if anything changes.
- I do not know what is real,
since we moved there.
- But what happened to Chrissy
is real, and I stay with her.
- And I need you by my side.
- And the department
and everything else?
- Everything went wrong, I do not know why.
I know we have a contract ...
- No matter the contract.
- We were better, Bryn.
We felt better ...
... But the move,
we started a. ..
- Get out of there.
- How?
- Let's get out of there.
- Let's stay in the apartment
Christina.
- We will stay in his apartment
is closer to the hospital ...
... we stay with it.
We will be moving today.
- Okay? I go to school ...
... find someone to take
my classes for a few days.
- You go home and pack your bags.
- I love you.
Not survive without you.
- Everything will be fine.
- We're going.
- Thanks, Mr. Director.
I appreciate that.
- I'm sure if Mr
Thanks.
- Paul!
- I cut, Mr. Director.
Ty, you're doing here?
- I knew what happened to Chrissy.
- I went to the hospital,
but let me see her.
- Karasic.
- You received the call
the hospital, sir?
- I knew you were doing
Bryn questions about Shaw and her husband.
- Yes, sir.
- As we make a visit.
- No family
can have such bad luck.
- I will call my partner.
We find there.
- Only allow relatives.
- Call your department,
but nobody answers.
- We were with her.
- I came here because
do not know what to do.
- Professor Paul?
- Simon!
- I should not have ...
"Who is this?
- Paul!
- Who is this?
- Calm down, man!
- This is James Nash.
- James Nash! He committed suicide.
- When? When was that?
- About six or seven months, after
that his son fell into the elevator shaft.
- I saw him.
- When we moved
the building, I saw it.
- You see it?
- In the parking lot ...
... was behind a woman
a neighbor.
- No way!
- I saw him.
- He appeared to you, also to Bryn,
and that other neighboring ...
- It's the one who is asking for help.
- The child's dominant
dangerous.
- Your wife is in danger.
- Ronnie?
- She wanted to break the ICFI
and Iiberar the child ...
... but hate the child was
I believe in the cycle.
- I told her that
not to mess with suicide.
- Suicide? No, the child's death
was accidental. He fell, right?
- And if the leap?
- To escape from the father?
- What difference would it?
- In an appearance? You have no idea.
- Explicame.
- Ronnie? Ronnie?
- Ronnie?
- Please let me help.
- I also had a son.
His name was ...
... was ...
- His name is Daniel.
- Mama?
- Danny?
- Look at me, Mom!
Look at me!
- Okay, honey. Okay.
- No! No!
- No, Danny!
- Ronnie ...
- He is coming! He is coming!
- No! Please!
Please open!
- Suicides were fixed
stakes in their graves ...
... with a stone on the face
or chains around his head.
- Chains around his head?
- That they will not be lifted.
- You said Bryn
was under medical care.
- Please tell me she
not suicidal.
- Why?
- Creatures with her
is dealing, Nash and his son ...
... only know the anguish.
- And the only way they
to reduce your pain ...
... is seducing other
to follow suit.
- Ronnie?
- Ronnie, I will not hurt.
- You did?
- Do not serve.
- Let me talk
with Danny again.
- No, no.
- Danny ... you're there, Danny?
- He is coming.
- Danny?
- Look at me.
- No! No!
- No, Danny! No!
- No! Again no, please!
- Please let me wake up!
- Let me wake up!
- Find sometHing in the records!
- Before Building
Beacon was the Beacon Hotel.
- And, before that, was
Hosted by the Beacon Street.
- And that has to do with us?
- Before that, he was the street corner
Beacon Avenue to Church!
- A crossroads! Where victims
suicide were buried.
- Then The Beacon
is on a graveyard?
- A deposit of bodies.
- Then, when the child
committed suicide ...?
- The trigger that.
- God helps those who mess with that!
- Hello, darling.
- Paul and I are going ...
... and I would like you
do the same, Ms. Carver.
- Considering all that we share,
you should call me Vanessa.
- That's ...
- That's disgusting.
- Really?
- I think it's very sexy.
- I know someone who also believes it.
- Paul? Paul?
- Almost there.
- It was very easy.
To control ...
... coarse convince
that I was helpless.
- Paul would not do that,
the no ...
- Not what?
- He does not leave me alone.
- Ah, my dear, people like us
are always alone.
- These wrong.
- Fast!
We do not have much time!
- Paul, does not open!
- Stay in the car!
- Do not turn off.
- Paul, does not open!
- Did you see that ...? Caramba!
- He does not want to go up.
Something is happening!
- Call the police! Go through the basement.
4O9 apartment.
- What will I say?
- Tell my wife is in danger.
- And who are you?
- Came from the university ...
... when we reached the parking lot
try taking the elevator ...
... and saw a child
just not a child.
- Really?
- And you think you saw?
- Are the Shaw!
- Okay. Stay calm.
- Damn, Bob!
- Kit?
- You were a good man!
- How could you be so selfish
to lose against someone like me?
- What happened between you two ...
We can fix it.
- We forget.
We can forget you.
- Impossible, Bryn.
You do not want to forget.
- You do not want to forget ...
- ... us.
- Kit .. Kit ..
- This is not anything right!
- And, Bryn?
Do not look delicious?
- You can not be ...
- Dead? Ah, my dear,
we are all dead here.
- Son, I think it's time to go.
- It's all the building!
- God! Is the entire building.
- Son, you're talking about?
- Officer, who knows about this place?
Knows how many suicides occurred here?
- Many.
- Bobby, respond! Bobby!
- What the hell?!
- Kit ..
- Bobby, respond!
- Bobby? Answers!
- He can not hear you ...
- He does not know that you are here.
- Let me alone!
Let me alone!
- Honey, you cried unto
we came to you.
- The only thing I think is
to complete your life.
- We are butterflies
attracted by your light.
- You're all I have, dear.
- You are our beacon (beacon).
- Not true! Not true!
- Vives distraught
your husband betrayed you ...
... and you ... you lost
your son ...
... forever.
- Where do you think that you, boy?
- You think you know about us?
- Come to us ...
- Police!
- I want to see Danny ...
- I want to see Danny again ...
Once again, please ...
- Yes, dear ...
... have exactly what you want.
- All we had.
- Drive a stake into his grave.
- He's coming.
- You can not save it, Paul.
Now it is ours.
- Vanessa?
- Are you one of them! You are ...
"Say, Paul! A ghost.
- Dressed in a body
a body that feels.
- But that was what
all were looking for here.
- Bryn is what you want.
- No!
- No pain, no joy ...
... no reason to scream
but we are crying ...
... forever.
- Let her out of here, please.
- No, we then need.
- Why?
"Because she still feels.
- And, at the time
in which she cut ...
... at that moment of agony delicious
We feel with her.
- And you condemn her for that?
- I would condemn a
fraction of the time.
- I do not really feel anything?
- So this is just for me.
- I lied when I said
that prison is an illusion.
- She is already ours.
You no longer need.
- No need to go there.
- I love her.
- Poor Lancelot.
- Boy! Sal!
- Get out of where you are!
- Drive a stake
- Drive a stake into his grave.
- Tyler.
- She is ours now, Paul!
"We trust you.
- You gave back
and lost.
- You can bring me back?
- No, son.
- You just gonna die.
- Bryn, no! No!
- Danny! I want to see Danny!
- I want to see Danny!
- You can not! He was!
- He died!
- Stop!
- Calm down, Kit
Calm down.
- Your weapon, Officer.
- I found
my partner?
- I'm not crazy!
- We came together!
I'm not crazy!
Here again ...!
- Quiet. Let
find your companion.
- Those damned detectives me
treated as if he were crazy.
- I thought he was going to kill her.
- Do not worry.
- All is well.
We take care of you.
- I love you.
- What am I doing here?
- Sorry.
- I'm so sorry.
- I would give my life to change this.
- To go back.
- Everything will be fine.
DinleyinFonetik olarak okuyun
Sözlük - Ayrýntýlý sözlüðü görüntüleGoogle Translate'i kullanabileceðim yerler:AramalarVideolarE-postaTelefonSohbetÝþletmeGoogle Translate HakkýndaAnýnda çeviriyi kapatGizlilikYardým
©2010Ýþletme AraçlarÇevirmen Araç SetiGoogle Translate HakkýndaBlogGizlilikYardým
>