MAN: It's a beautiful day.
["BLESSED ASSURANCE" PLAYS]
It's a beautiful day.
It's God's good day.
You know, standing up for God,
it's not an easy thing.
Nobody said it was easy.
It is not easy.
But Jesus, Jesus saved my life.
He saved my life.
I relate it to David,
the psalmist, who said:
Thou hast picked me up
from the dunghill
and placed my feet
on a solid rock.
And Jesus,
Jesus, he lifted me up
from a horrible pit as well,
and he washed my heart clean,
and he cleaned me up
from all my sins
and all the evil that I did.
I'm all cleaned up,
and it's a wonderful feeling.
It is wonderful.
And he gave me this message.
He gave me this message to give to you today.
And today, he says:
Go, ye, unto all the world
and spread the gospel,
for he who believes
and is baptized will be saved.
Amen. Amen.
# Blessed assurance #
# Jesus is mine #
BILL: As you are buried
with him in baptism,
so you are raised
with him by faith
in our Lord, Jesus Christ.
[ALL LAUGHING]
Amen, sister.
# Purchase of God #
[SOBS THEN LAUGHING]
# Born of his spirit #
# Washed in his blood #
[MAN LAUGHING]
# This is my story #
[SPEAKS INDISTINCTLY]
# This is my song #
Hallelujah.
# Praising my savior #
# All the day long #
BILL: Our Lord, Jesus Christ.
# This is my story #
# This is my song #
[GASPS THEN WHOOPS]
Again!
# All the day long #
- Corinne?
- Yes.
As you are buried with him
through baptism...
Hallelujah.
... so you are raised with him by
faith in our Lord, Jesus Christ.
# Burst on my sight #
# Angels descending #
# Bring from above #
# Echoes of mercy #
# Whispers of love #
# This is my story
This is my song #
WOMAN:
Corinne. You've got chores to do.
CORINNE: He taught them
how to swim and dive.
[PIG SQUEALING]
# Praising my savior##
CW: Hey, honey.
Oh, please,
you're a lot of help.
[LAUGHS]
I was hoping for a little help
myself. I got this problem, lady.
Oh, yeah? Somehow your
problems become my problems.
Shoo. I got a runt in the oven.
I've got work to do.
- You do?
- Yeah, I do.
- Me too.
- Ha, ha.
- Mm. That tickle?
- Stop it, don't tickle there.
[LAUGHING]
- I told you don't do that.
- Careful, honey. Careful, honey.
Careful, honey.
Ooh. Ooh, ooh.
Ha-ha-ha.
CW: Hop on there, squirt.
There you go.
And get that other one. There you go.
Now, arms real straight.
Now, pick her up
and walk. Look at that.
Oh, boy. I got you.
- You're like a gigantic monster girl.
- Yeah.
Going into town to
cause damage. Ha, ha.
Big trouble.
[CORINNE GROWLS]
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
[DOOR OPENS]
Hello.
Good afternoon, ma'am.
Let me introduce myself.
Name's Bobbie Lee Moore,
Syracuse Accordion Company.
I'd like to show you an instrument to
bring magic into your little one's life.
How'd you like
to play the squeezebox?
This here is the Titano
Palmer-Hughes Grand.
It has all the features
of a full-size accordion.
Forty-one full-length black
and mother-of-pearl keys,
all your sharps,
all your flats.
[PLAYING]
Now it's your turn.
KATHLEEN: I'm sorry, but
she's not really musical.
I wouldn't wanna
waste your time.
Not to contradict you, but maybe
she hasn't found her instrument.
[PLAYING "MARY HAD
A LITTLE LAMB"]
[PLAYING "YANKEE DOODLE"]
SALESMAN: Wow.
Look at the way you squeeze that box.
What do you think of
the Titano Palmer-Hughes Grand?
It's practically
bigger than she is.
She can barely
stand up straight.
[SIGHS]
SALESMAN:
Okay.
[GASPS THEN GROANING]
Mama.
KATHLEEN: Oh, darling.
- I love you. I love you.
Everything is going
to be all right.
[SOBBING]
We'll see you in church
on Sunday?
Yes, ma'am.
PASTOR BUD: Oh, it's hot today
here in Vacation Bible School.
Just nod your head
if you're hot today. Yes?
Do you know the Lamb of God?
Do you know that he is knocking
at the door of your heart?
So gentle the way he does it.
Just... so soft.
Gently. Tap, tap, tap.
Can you hear it?
[PASTOR BUD
TAPPING MICROPHONE]
Can you hear him there?
Jesus is a gentleman, children.
He's not gonna come barging into
your heart without an invitation.
Won't you open the door
for Jesus?
Want you to take
that chain off your door
and lift up that latch
and open that up.
Who's there? It's Jesus.
And he's waiting for you, children.
You're welcome here, dear Lord.
All right, let us
bow our heads and pray.
With everyone's eyes closed now,
no one looking around,
raise your hand
if you made a decision today.
Yes, Pastor Bud,
I opened the door.
I didn't leave Jesus out in the cold.
I wanna go to heaven.
[CHILD SNORTS]
No pig snorting, please.
Little children, this is the time
now to make the decision.
I see you. Does anyone else
think this is the...?
I see you, dear.
Is there anybody else today
who will raise your hand and say:
"This is my day."
To say, "I've been saved."
I see you, dear child.
I see you, sweetheart.
I see you, I see you.
Tim, Corinne, Shelly.
I'll speak to you up here.
Everyone else, as you head out,
do be careful on those steps.
Won't you?
Happy summer.
["HOW GREAT THOU ART" PLAYS]
Now,
I want you to know
what a great day it is
in heaven right now.
Do you know why?
Because we asked Jesus
into our heart?
Hearts, moron.
Because you made
the best decision of your lives.
Put your hands together.
You've made the best
decision of your lives.
Don't be ashamed
of Jesus, children,
and he won't be ashamed of you.
I want you to tell your mama
and your papa
that your names have
been written in the book of life.
[KATHLEEN SIGHS]
Oh, Kathleen, Kathleen.
All right.
Is it hot enough for you?
I might join my girls
at the pool this afternoon.
Oh, Bathsheba bathing, well...
You like to swim, Pastor Bud?
Oh, I never learned to swim, I...
His power is perfected
in my weakness in that way.
I used to be a lifeguard.
- You didn't.
- I could teach you.
- No.
- I could.
I could teach you,
yes, I could.
PASTOR BUD: No, I would
just sink like a stone.
You know, the baptism tank,
that's as deep as I could go.
KATHLEEN: Ha-ha-ha.
PASTOR BUD: Never mind about that.
Corinne has some wonderful
news to share with you.
- Really, sweetheart?
- And Kathleen?
- Yes.
- I know this has not been
an easy time since you
lost your baby, I know that.
But the Lord can make good
things come out of tragedy.
Your family will be strong now with
God at the center. You know that.
All right, you tell your mama
the good news.
Bye.
Come on, Pookie.
Come on, Wendy.
Let's go swimming, huh?
Okay, so,
what's the wonderful news?
Hm?
What is it?
- She got saved today.
- Saved from what?
I just raised my hand,
that's all.
Pastor Bud says Jesus knocks on
our heart, but we don't listen.
Maybe he should try
the doorbell instead.
KATHLEEN: Sally saw you.
CW: What? Sally saw me what?
- What, what? What did Sally see?
KATHLEEN: I can't trust you.
CW: You can't trust me?
KATHLEEN:
You're making me crazy, all right?
You're making me crazy. I am home.
I am the one who's home here.
I'm taking care of these children.
I'm in this crap house.
CW: I'm the one who's out working,
buying your wigs and your car
and your other crap. So, what
is the issue? What did I do?
KATHLEEN: I have made every house
that we have lived in a home.
CW:
Yeah, well, are we...?
KATHLEEN:
Follow around all your crap.
CW:
Yeah, yeah, it's all about me.
What?
CW: All alone.
Yeah, you made us a house, sure, sure.
CW: What is the problem?
What do you want me to say?
KATHLEEN:
Right now, what isn't the problem?
Yeah.
You see how big that guy was?
Jesus Christ.
- Hey, guys, I'll catch you in a second.
- All right.
Hey. You're the writer,
aren't you?
- I write. I mean...
- Yeah, you're Corinne Walker, right?
- Yeah.
I was just on my way to practice.
Do you know The Renegades?
Uh, of course.
Everyone knows The Renegades.
I'm Ethan.
I know.
So, what are you doing?
Um, I'm waiting for my sister
to finish practice.
I meant, what are you writing?
Oh.
Some words and thoughts.
- Thoughts on what?
- Mm, disappointment.
Oh.
We should
write a song together.
For The Renegades?
Sure. Yeah. But, um...
I'm not musical.
Maybe you haven't found
your instrument yet.
[VEHICLE APPROACHING]
[DOOR OPENS]
[WHISPERING]
Tell her she looks pretty.
Just tell her you love her.
Where you going, wildcat?
- Hm? Where do you think you're...?
- Move it.
- No. Mm-mm.
You're gonna have
to get through me.
Ow!
That hurt.
Oh! Don't you dare.
Give me. Give that to me or I'm
gonna kill you. Give me that.
Mine.
[KATHLEEN SOBS]
- Damn it!
- Oops.
# I was anything but free
I was any... #
- What'd you say, free or me?
- Free.
- Free, okay.
- Free, yeah.
# I was anything but free #
# As far as I could see ##
[IMITATING DRUMS]
Do the drum solo right there
and come back.
I like The Renegades.
I've been to concerts.
- I love your music.
- Thanks.
WENDY: Corrine.
I'm the only freshman
to make it on varsity.
Ah.
You're looking at the first guy out in dodge ball.
It's like, every time...
- It's instant. It's...
- Me too.
- I'm always out first. Every single time.
- Yeah?
Knew there's a reason
I loved you so much.
I heard what you said.
You said "I love you."
No, I said I liked her
so much, because...
Yeah, okay.
Get lost, Wendy.
Yeah, Wendy.
Go shoot some hoops or something.
No, I run track.
Well, I'm a track monster.
Ew, that's gross.
You guys are disgusting.
Ew.
You guys are full of shit.
All right.
Harmonize with me.
Come on, come on.
# I went walking down the road #
# The road for the blind #
# For a long, long time #
I got you. I got you.
I got you.
# I walked alone #
[BOTH GRUNTING]
# Down that lonely road #
# No place to go #
# I was the sea #
# As cold as I could be #
# I was anything but free ##
ETHAN:
# I could show you how to fly #
# Charge you by the night #
# I could take you for a ride #
# A jog around my mind #
# You turn the other way #
# I can tell you're afraid #
# Put up your guard #
# It's all up to you #
# It's all up to you ##
[AUDIENCE CHEERING
AND APPLAUDING]
[FLY BUZZING]
[ETHAN PANTING
AND MOANING]
[PIG GRUNTING]
[SNORTING]
Oh, honey.
MAN: # Every time I see
your smile I run to you #
# Every time I hear your voice #
[INAUDIBLE DIALOGUE]
# I dream of you #
Hey, honey.
# Lady, lady, lady, lady #
[CROWD APPLAUDING]
# I'm gonna let you
Be my girlfriend #
# Maybe, maybe, maybe, maybe #
[CROWD WHISTLING
AND CHEERING]
[SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY]
# Because when you're there #
[SOBBING]
# I just don't care
I'm here for you ##
Break it.
[SIGHS THEN GRUNTING]
Oh, damn it.
Fuck.
- Thought you wanted to be a rock star.
- I did, yeah.
A different kind though, huh?
Whoo!
ETHAN: Abigator, did you
help Mommy with her hair?
[CRYING]
Oh, it's okay.
- See? She hates me.
CORINNE: She doesn't hate you.
I work too much.
You see? Right there.
Wendy told me the Jesus
people are in town.
Her friends get high
and go talk to them.
Oh. Jesus freaks
in Ellenville, huh?
[GIGGLES]
[CHUCKLES]
You know, I haven't opened
a Bible since I was a kid.
Listen, I told you
things would get better.
And they will.
Just wanna
get some practice time in.
And if I didn't have a baby
to take care of, I'd write a novel,
but this is our life.
At least we have Abby-Fat-Legs.
Ooh, ooh.
You little pork butt.
Look at you. Pbbt. Mwah.
- Aah.
- Ow.
This is for Abby-Fat-Legs.
Right here.
# Traded my guitar
For a chubby baby #
# Work with them stones
Bring home that gravy #
# Hair once on my head
Moved down to my chest #
# You sit at home all day long #
# With a baby
Sucking on your breast ##
[CRYING]
CORINNE: Shh.
She needs her own space.
Get a cooler and put her in there.
Just use it as a playpen.
CORINNE:
Mike, I need that cooler.
Not that one, take that one.
That one.
ABIGAIL:
Mama.
[CRYING]
This is a nice bed, huh?
Yeah. Yeah.
This is the last gig
Abby and I are coming to.
MAN 1: Yo, what up?
MAN 2: Look here.
[CAR HORN HONKING]
MAN 1: What's going on, man?
MAN 2: Party time.
Check out my poopy pants, yeah.
MAN 1: Suck it, bitch!
- We're The Renegades!
- Suck it!
ETHAN:
Hey, dickhead!
You wanna get us pulled over?
My kid's in the bus.
- Fucking cut it out!
MAN 2: Hey!
Hey, fucking cut it out!
MIKE: Oh, no.
ETHAN: Oh, shit!
Ethan.
[CORINNE SHRIEKS]
[MIKE GRUNTING]
MIKE: Where are my drums?
ETHAN: Let's go.
[CORINNE SHOUTS
INDISTINCTLY]
CORINNE:
Abby! Where's...?
Grab the cooler.
ETHAN:
Go, get out.
CORINNE:
Abby!
ETHAN:
You got the cooler?
CORINNE:
Abby!
Ethan! Where is she?
Where is she?
Abby!
ETHAN:
Where's the cooler?!
God!
God, please!
[PANTING]
God saved her, Corinne.
God saved us.
Okay, let's find out
what God has to say.
Well? Read it.
"I will dash your infants
against the rocks."
What?
It's right there.
That's fucked up.
Let's start from the beginning.
[YELLS]
[ALL CHEERING
AND APPLAUDING]
BILL: Praise God.
NED: Praise God.
BILL:
Hallelujah.
This is one fish the Lord has been
trying to hook for a long time.
[MEN LAUGHING]
Oh, yeah, that was wild,
you know?
I was just so... Ooh.
I was thinking about
the baby in my womb
- and how far God's brought me.
BILL: Praise God.
And my big old happy family.
Aah! What is that?
BILL: They're all God's creatures, Corinne.
They're all God's creatures.
I've been trying to get her in this lake.
She says, "Ooh, not in this ucky lake."
It's not sanitary."
[ALL APPLAUDING]
Come over here.
Newly. Newly.
[SHRIEKS THEN SCREAMS]
Hold on. I'm getting out of here.
Yuck, yuck, yuck.
CONGREGATION:
# Then sings my soul #
# My savior God to thee #
# How great thou art #
# How great thou art ##
- Thank you, Jesus.
- How you guys doing?
MAN 1: Hallelujah.
- How are you? Praise God.
[ALL CHEERING]
MAN 1: Praise God.
- Praise the Lord.
Another Sunday
and the saints have gathered.
ALL:
Amen!
BILL: Do not neglect the
assembling of yourselves
as is the habit of some,
but all the more
as the day draws near.
Hebrews 10:25.
And we have assembled ourselves
here today, brothers and sisters,
in God's cathedral.
- So beautiful.
BILL: In the splendor of his creation.
Mm.
Martin Luther says
that God writes the gospel
not in the Bible alone,
but also in the trees.
Yeah? In the flowers,
- in the clouds, in the stars.
MAN 2: Hallelujah.
BILL: Don't they proclaim
the name of God?
Amen.
BILL: Amen. Amen.
- Amen.
Now, you all know
about Nancy and Al, right?
- Yeah.
- Uh...
Nancy has decided to take
the kids and move to Buffalo.
It's devastating.
They come in for counseling?
I met with them a few times,
but the damage had already been done.
Their marriage was weakened
by, um, sexual, um, issues.
What kind of sexual issues?
I don't wanna go into that right now.
Brothers, God has put it on my heart to
speak freely with you tonight, okay?
You need to attend
to your wives' needs.
We've got a set of tapes.
Christ-Like Sex
by Dr. Frank Barnes.
MAN [ON RECORDING]: When it comes
to satisfying your wife, brothers,
clitoral stimulation
is part of God's plan.
You'll find the clitoris located
toward the top of her labia,
but below the pubic bone.
Let her be your guide
to what feels good.
- Amen.
- She will indicate this
with body movements
and various sounds.
It is advisable to apply
one tablespoon of oil or lotion.
Direct contact without lubrication
won't please your bride.
Okay.
That's pretty right on.
That's it?
There's more. Um...
There's seven tapes.
[PLAYING "NEARER MY GOD
TO THEE"]
# Nearer, my God to thee #
[MUMBLING INDISTINCTLY]
# Nearer to thee #
# Even when it be #
# A cross #
# That raiseth me #
[COUGHS]
# Still all my song #
# Shall be ##
ETHAN:
God bless you, Mama.
[BOTH CHUCKLE]
[LAUGHS]
- Stay for lunch.
- I can't. Ned's waiting for his lunch.
It's daytime.
So? Who cares?
What about you?
How many times a week?
- A week?
- Mm-hm.
Like once a week.
- Honey...
- Maybe.
Maybe?
Honey, you...
You cannot let sexual
chemistry burn out.
- You cannot.
- What if it does?
You have to spice it up.
Show him how much
you admire him.
I like to draw Ned's penis.
No, no.
- It's beautiful. It's beautiful. It's art.
- Ha-ha-ha!
I'm drawing Ned's.
And you're gonna draw Ethan's.
Listen to me.
He is gonna be so flattered.
Ned loves looking
at his penis drawings.
And he has such a...
[SPEAKING IN
FOREIGN LANGUAGE]
Ah...
- I call it Shamu. Stop it.
- Ha-ha-ha.
They're so weird.
It's God's design.
Yeah, but it's
a strange design.
Listen, the human body
is beautiful, period.
It...
It brings glory to God.
[SIGHS]
Shamu.
[LAUGHING]
- What?
- Ouch. Ouch.
Listen, nothing a little olive
oil can't take care of.
Let me see yours.
It's a little crooked.
Well...
it's long.
Okay.
Hi.
- Wendy.
- Hi.
Hi.
- What did you do to your hair?
- Yeah, I fucked myself with Sun-In.
But it's cool because
I have Mom's wig.
Uh, listen, Rich kicked me out.
And I don't really have
anywhere to go.
So...
Sleep over?
Your girls are gorgeous.
Hey, you could be
a beauty queen.
You could be Miss USA.
We're all beautiful
in God's eyes.
- Hold it down in the front.
- I am holding it down.
Man looks at the outward appearance,
but God looks at the heart. Right?
GIRLS:
Mm-hm.
We pray for you every day.
Don't we, girls?
GIRLS:
Yeah.
We ask God
to open Aunt Wendy's eyes
and to save her from hell.
Thank you.
I really... I really appreciate that.
[CHANTING IN
UNINTELLIGIBLE LANGUAGE]
What was that?
It's the gift of tongues.
It's a prayer language.
- A prayer language?
- Uh-huh.
That's beautiful. What...?
How does it work?
Scripture says, he who speaks
in tongues edifies himself.
[SIGHS]
It builds me up.
It's like charging my battery.
Can you do it
any time you want?
Any time I'm in the spirit.
So do you know
what you're saying?
I have no idea.
- You don't?
- No, I...
I just know it's what God
wants me to say.
It's so holy.
You sounded like an angel.
What does it feel like?
What does it feels like when...?
Uh...
It settles things in your spirit.
I want it.
You get everything.
You do. I want it.
[SIGHS]
It's gotta... It's what...
That's what I need.
That's exactly what I need.
I want it. I'm gonna get it.
I wanna get it. Ha-ha-ha.
Daddy, veggie burger?
Uh...
It looks delicious.
Jesus, you could feed this
to the geese.
ETHAN: They are very high in protein.
- Yeah, I bet.
ETHAN:
Very low in cholesterol.
- Get used to the taste.
CORINNE: Good for you.
- Yeah, not anymore.
CORINNE: Cheese.
What's good for me
is seeing my girls.
Isn't he sweet?
I am so pissed off
at that stinking asshole.
- If I see him, I'm gonna crack him.
- Daddy, Daddy, Dad.
- Your vocabulary.
- Sorry.
I'm ticked off at Rich and the
way he's done my Wendybug.
Thank you.
CW: You're better off without him.
- I know.
Corinne will help you
get back on your feet.
What do you say, squirt?
Why is Aunt Wendy so nice
when she doesn't know Jesus?
Well, because, hon, it's not enough to
just be nice or just do good things.
A man is justified by faith
apart from works of the law.
God will justify
those circumcised by faith.
What's "circus sized"?
That's when you get cut off
from the circus.
WENDY: I'm nice to you
because I love you.
So that's it. I love you.
I don't have to have a reason.
Kids are the best things
in life.
Losing your baby brother,
heh, that destroyed my marriage.
God, I regret that.
Ease off the clutch
and press the gas.
Ease and press.
It's like making love,
you know?
Come on, rev it up.
You can do it.
[ENGINE STARTS]
- You can do it.
- Oh.
Oh, oh, oh.
Okay.
[SIGHING]
Satan's doing
a real number on you,
but you know what?
I'm gonna bind him.
- Okay.
- I'm gonna bind him right now.
- Satan, you have no power over us.
- No, you don't.
We are children of God, Satan,
and we reject your fiery darts.
- We reject your lies.
- Yes.
We denounce you.
You're a fallen angel doomed to hell
- forever and ever.
- Amen.
Get thee behind us, Satan.
Get thee behind us.
Yeah, get lost, Bub!
Get lost!
Bub?
Bub. Yes.
You know, Satan is Beelzebub.
The Lord of the Flies.
The book.
Get lost, Bub.
That's great.
[SIREN WAILING]
Oh, no.
- What do I do? What do I do?
- Pull over. Pull over.
It's not Satan, but it's just as bad.
Pull over.
Another very important
driving lesson:
Charm the cop.
[IN FOREIGN ACCENT] Hello,
Mr. Policia. Hello. Oh.
What a beautiful mustache
you have. It's so manly.
Very beautiful.
- You're a long way from home, ma'am.
- Yes, I am, but I so loving America.
I'm stopping you for doing
15 miles an hour over the limit.
- That's a direct threat to your safety.
- I had a wedgie.
- A what?
- A wedgie.
Do you know what this is,
the wedgie?
My underwear inside
my pooskie-nooskie.
Oh, my...
Oh, it split my kaka in half.
Backwards, forward.
I was squirming, my friend,
not know what to do.
- License and registration, please.
CORINNE: Yes, sir.
Shoot. Take this. Here it is.
- And where's my registration?
- Here.
It's a learner's permit, sir.
Keep your mind on the road,
Miss Miller.
You know, the Bible says
we need to keep our minds
set on things above.
But I can do that
and concentrate on the road
at the same time, and I will.
And I hope your problem
got solved, ma'am.
Oh. Thank you, yes.
Everything down there very beautiful.
I just pluck it out.
Okay.
CORINNE: Thank you.
ANNIKA: Very deep caverns there.
- Bye-bye.
CORINNE: Thank you, sir.
- Thank you.
ANNIKA: Bye-bye.
A wedgie?
[IN NORMAL VOICE]
Yes, I had a wedgie.
I'm gonna give you a wedgie.
[LAUGHING]
Stop. Stop.
[PLAYING "I'VE GOT
A RIVER OF LIFE"]
# I've got a river of life
Flowin' out of me #
# Makes the lame to walk
And the blind to see #
# Opens the prison doors
Sets the captives free #
# I've got a river of life
Flowin' out of me #
ALL: # Spring up, O well
Within my soul #
# Spring up, O well
And make me whole #
And give to me #
# That life abundantly ##
[ALL CHEERING
AND APPLAUDING]
I like that.
That one always makes me
wanna dance for the Lord.
[ALL CHUCKLING]
Uh, listen, before we start,
I wanna welcome, uh...
Sorry, where did she go?
Corinne's sister, Wendy.
Let's give a warm welcome.
[ALL APPLAUDING]
Uh, now, let's give
a hot hand clap for Jesus.
[ALL WHOOPING
AND APPLAUDING]
Listen, before we start,
I wanna, uh...
I wanna open up the floor
to the body of believers.
If anybody has anything
they wanna share.
Anything that's on their hearts.
To edify the saints. Anybody?
No?
Okay.
CORINNE:
Yeah, um...
I was praying with a sister
for her rebellious child
and, um...
after we asked God for help,
we thanked him
for answering our prayers
because he will answer it,
you know?
As we're told in Thess...
Thess... Thess...
My, that is a tongue twister.
In, uh, Thessalonians, um...
Hold on.
As we're told in Thessalonians,
uh, you know,
God wants us to come to him
with all our needs and all our desires.
If you want the Ganders
to have a winning season.
If you want it, you know...
It'll take a miracle.
But I'll pray anyway.
And then I'll thank him when
they choke in the fourth quarter
like they always do.
But that's faith, isn't it?
Isn't that what makes us
different from the world?
That we believe
even though we don't see?
Faith is the substance
of things hoped for,
- the evidence of things not seen.
- You can sit down now.
- That's what it says in Hebrews, right?
- Thank you.
Uh, I see you have been
hitting your Bible studies.
God bless you.
Power of the holy word.
Uh, I don't know
who you were praying with.
And you know what?
I don't have to know.
It's okay, but I just wanna say, if
that woman wants to come to me directly
uh, or any of the elders
of the church,
we'd be privileged to sit down
and pray with her, okay?
Um, does anybody have a burden
on their heart they wanna share?
Ned, go ahead.
- What's on your mind, brother?
NED: Uh, a couple things.
Sister?
Yeah. I'm sorry.
You came very close
to preaching just now.
We have to be so careful not to appear
as though we're teaching the men.
- No. I didn't mean to.
- I know. I know.
And you were so sincere
and I know your heart.
And I know you wanna
submit to God in all ways.
- Of course, that's all I wanna do.
- I know. I know.
- Okay, of course.
- Good.
Okay.
Hmm. Come on.
Come on, Holy Spirit.
Come on.
I will love you, Father God.
Oh, Holy Spirit.
Thank you, Lord.
Oh. Father God.
Come on in.
Come on.
[SPEAKING GIBBERISH]
Come on, Lord.
Come on, Holy Spirit.
Just wash down on me, Lord.
Just...
# Come in thy strength
And thy power #
Get thee behind me.
# Come in thine own
Gentle way ##
[EXHALES DEEPLY]
[SPEAKS GIBBERISH
THEN GROANS]
Try later.
- Wend?
- Yep.
I have a system.
Okay, what's your system?
- Look at the edges.
- Right.
- Half.
- Mm-hm.
- Right.
- Thirds.
- Oh.
- Look.
- Okay.
Okay, okay, okay.
Half.
Half, thirds.
I'm doing it with the wrist.
Half. Ow. Ha-ha-ha.
I'm doing the towels.
LILY:
Hi, Brownie. Hi, Spotty.
What you doing, Spotty?
What you doing, Brownie?
Mm. Are you hungry?
Are you hungry?
You have a stomachache?
You say "yes."
You say "no."
- Oh, my God. What is this?
- My undies.
- Ha-ha-ha. What is this?
- Why?
How do you...? What is...?
How do you wear this?
What is this? Ha, ha!
- How do you fold this thing? Ha, ha!
- Half. Half.
- Thirds.
- Okay.
Okay, half. Half.
We're going into
origami territory.
Hold on, what could this be?
[FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING]
ETHAN: Hey, Lily,
what are you doing?
What are you...?
Hey. Come on.
Come on, honey.
Come on.
Wendy!
Hey!
- Okay, okay.
- Get that out of my house!
CORINNE: What is this?
- Give it to me.
Do you see this?
- Look at me, hon.
- No, no, no.
We're answerable to God.
I'm not giving it back.
It's not yours. It's not mine.
I don't use that.
Who has drugs
but doesn't use them?
- I'm holding it. I'm a safe house.
- We gave you a safe house.
Come on.
Don't look at me like that.
- Come here. You put it in your mouth?
- No.
- You sure? Drink.
LILY: Mm-hm.
ETHAN:
Let's do it.
CORINNE:
Drink, okay? Drink.
- What are you doing?
CORINNE: Face.
- Get right with God, Wendy.
- Shit.
It's not for me!
What? Peace, righteousness?
Eternal life?
Which one is not for you?
I don't want your life, Corinne.
I'll take my fucked-up one instead.
Scrub, scrub.
[ENGINE STARTS]
[TRUCK PULLS AWAY]
[PLAYING "HOLY HOLY HOLY"]