- YOU HAVE IT?
- GIVE ME.
- NOT UNTIL I SEE IT.
- NOW.
I HAVE TO...GET RID OF IT.
- I'VE MET TOO MANY CHARLATANS
SINCE OUR ARRIVAL HERE,
AND MANY KNIGHTS
HAVE BEEN TRICKED
INTO TAKING FALSE RELICS
TO THE HOLY SEE.
I WON'T BE ONE OF THEM.
STAY HERE, SIR RAYMOND.
STAND GUARD.
- YES, SIR.
- IT'S IN THERE.
- IF THIS IS A GENUINE
PIECE OF THE CROSS,
THEN IT IS NOT
FOR US TO TOUCH.
- COULD IT BE?
- VENI, VENI
SANCTE SPIRITUS...
...AMEN.
THE BLOOD OF CHRIST!
- WE HAVE A DEAL.
- GOOD.
TAKE IT AWAY.
QUICK.
- BLESS YOU, MY SON.
- WELL, IS IT?
- IT IS A TRUE RELIC.
A REAL PIECE
OF THE LORD'S CROSS.
- YOU COULD FEEL THE HOLY
SPIRIT POURING FROM IT.
- WE HAVE
FINALLY SOMETHING
TO MAKE THIS CRUSADE
WORTH THE FIGHT.
LET'S GO.
- WORD HAS SPREAD ABOUT
OUR FIND, SIR GREGORY.
- AND THEY SAY
A PIECE OF THE CRUCIFIX
IS AS PRECIOUS
AS THE HOLY GRAIL.
- I SAW SOME RED FACES
IN TANCRED'S COURT
WHEN HE HEARD THE NEWS.
HE FEELS HE WAS BEATEN
TO THE ULTIMATE PRIZE.
- WELL,
AS WELL HE MIGHT.
WHEN WE BRING
THIS BEFORE THE HOLY SEE,
THERE'LL BE PRAISE INDEED.
YOU'LL BE A HERO.
- A HERO?
I'M MORE CONCERNED AT
HOW THESE NIGHTS GROW COLDER.
- THE WEATHER IS TURNING.
PERHAPS NOW IS THE BEST TIME
FOR US TO LEAVE.
- WHEN WAS THE BEST
TIME TO ARRIVE?
- THE CRUSADE WAS
WORTH ALL THE SACRIFICE.
DON'T YOU THINK, BROTHER GEORGE?
- OF COURSE.
- THINK OF ALL
THE GLORY YOU'D HAVE MISSED
HAD WE ARRIVED ANY LATER.
- WHAT GLORY WAS THERE
IN THIS BLOODSHED?
- PERHAPS YOU FORGET
IT WAS THE GLORY OF GOD.
- GOD HAD NO WISH FOR THIS.
THIS WAS THE GREED OF MAN.
- BE CAREFUL
WHAT YOU SAY, MY LORD.
THAT COULD BE
CONSTRUED AS BLASPHEMY.
- YOU WERE AT THE COUNCIL
OF CLERMONT, AS WAS I.
EMPEROR KOMNENOS
ASKED FOR OUR HELP,
AND WE WERE
READY TO GIVE IT.
- CLERMONT WAS
A COUNCIL OF WARMONGERS.
I SEE THAT NOW.
- YOU NEEDN'T SPILL TEARS
OVER THOSE WHO HAVE SLAIN.
THEY DESERVE WHAT THEY GOT.
AND NOW WE HAVE
THE KINGDOM OF HEAVEN.
AS IT SHOULD BE.
- WHAT WOULD
YOU SPILL TEARS OVER?
- I SPILL THEM
OVER SLEEPING ALONE.
- FOR ME, IT'S SPENDING
ANOTHER NIGHT IN THIS COLD CAMP
WHILE MY LANDS ARE
PROBABLY BEING PLUNDERED
BY THE THIEVING BASTARDS
I LEFT TO LOOK AFTER THEM.
WHEN CAN THE REST OF US
SEE THIS TREASURE?
- AN ARTIFACT
OF THIS MAGNITUDE
SHOULD ONLY BE FOR THE EYES
OF THE HOLY FATHER HIMSELF.
HE SHALL DECIDE WHO
IS FIT TO GAZE UPON IT.
I'VE DECIDED IT'S TIME.
TOMORROW,
WE LEAVE FOR JAFFA.
FROM THERE,
WE TAKE A SHIP TO ROME.
WE PRESENT OUR GIFT,
AND THEN...
FINALLY...WE GO HOME.
- YES!
THAT'S A SIGN
FOR MORE MEAD, LADS.
- THIS FOR
YOUR THANKS, CAPTAIN.
- I THINK WE'LL HAVE A SMOOTH
PASSAGE FOR YOU, MY LORD.
OH, OOPS.
YOUR BACKSIDE'S TOO USED TO
FINE WINES AND LAZY HORSES, EH?
- AND MY BLADE IS
USED TO INSOLENT TONGUES.
- OH, I'M SURE IT IS.
AND ME, BEING A GOD-FEARING MAN,
WOULDN'T HAVE IT ANY OTHER WAY.
FATHER.
- IT'S BROTHER.
- CAREFUL THERE.
- YES, MY LORD.
- WHAT HAVE WE HERE?
- I'M SORRY, CAPTAIN.
I'M AFRAID THAT'S
NOT FOR YOUR EYES.
- MAYBE NOW YOU'D ALLOW ME
TO BRING YOU A CLEAN TUNIC.
YOU SMELL WORSE
THAN THE CAPTAIN.
- YOU KNOW MY VOW.
NOT UNTIL
I REACH MY OWN BED.
- AT LEAST NOW I CAN
FINALLY SEE THAT HAPPENING.
I CAN'T WAIT
TO GET BACK HOME.
- ME TOO.
AND THEN WE SHOULD TALK
ABOUT YOUR STATUS AS SQUIRE.
I'M SURE YOUR FATHER
WOULD BE PROUD TO KNOW
HOW BRAVELY YOU
FOUGHT ALONGSIDE ME.
YOU FOUGHT AS A KNIGHT.
I WONDER WHAT
THE GIRLS BACK HOME
WOULD SAY ABOUT SIR PAUL.
- THE GOSPEL IS TAKEN
FROM MARK, CHAPTER FOUR,
BEGINNING
WITH THE 39TH VERSE.
ET EXSURGENS COMMINATUS
EST VENTO
ET DIXIT
MARI TACE OBMUTESCE...
- DID YOU SEE IT?
THE RELIC.
- NO, I WAS OUTSIDE.
- WHY SUCH SECRECY?
- WE'RE TRYING
TO PRESERVE ITS SANCTITY.
- PRESERVE?
PRESERVE IT FROM WHO?
AREN'T WE HONORABLE KNIGHTS?
- WE'LL SEE IT SOON ENOUGH.
- ...QUIA ET VENTUS
ET MARE OBOEDIUNT EI.
IN NOMINE PATRI, ET FILII,
ET SPIRITUS SANCTI. AMEN.
- CAPTAIN!
THE WATER IS RUINED TOO!
- WHAT IN GOD'S NAME?
- WHAT IS IT?
WHAT'S GOING ON?
- HERE. TASTE.
- OH, IT'S SALT WATER.
- ALL OF IT IS.
BUT THE WATER
WAS FRESH LAST NIGHT.
- A WAVE MUST'VE WASHED OVER
AND SPOILED IT.
- IMPOSSIBLE!
EVEN THE BARRELS THAT
WEREN'T OPEN ARE RUINED!
AND THIS?
- BUT WE ATE WELL
LAST NIGHT.
- IT'S ALL INFESTED.
WE HAVE NOTHING.
THIS DOESN'T HAPPEN.
MY MEN ARE TALKING--
WHISPERING EVIL THINGS.
THEY TALK OF A CURSE--
AN EVIL YOU
HAVE BROUGHT UPON US.
- AR--I UNDERSTAND
YOUR CREW'S CONCERN,
AND OBVIOUSLY THERE HAS
BEEN SOME MISFORTUNE HERE.
BUT NOT A CURSE.
WE ARE CRUSADERS.
WE FOUGHT
WITH GOD ON OUR SIDE.
THEN WHY IS GOD PUNISHING US?
MAYBE YOUR PRECIOUS WAR
WAS LESS THAN HOLY.
- CAPTAIN!
STARBOARD!
- HEY, HEY,
HARD TO PORT!
WE HAVE TO RIDE OUT
THIS SQUALL.
STOW THE SAILS!
THEY'LL BE RIPPED TO PIECES!
- WHAT CAN WE DO TO HELP?
- YOU CAN HELP BY
KEEPING OUT OF OUR WAY.
GET BELOW DECKS
AND TIE EVERYTHING DOWN,
INCLUDING YOURSELVES.
AND YOU CAN PRAY
FOR OUR LIVES!
- AHH!
- AH!
- THANK GOD.
WHERE'S THE CREW?
- SWEPT OVERBOARD.
- THE IMPORTANT THING IS
THAT WE SURVIVED.
- IT WAS THE WILL OF GOD.
- OH, I MUST'VE BLACKED OUT.
I DON'T REMEMBER MUCH ELSE.
- NEVER SEEN A STORM
LIKE THIS BEFORE.
- IT RAGED FOR TWO HOURS
OR MORE, AND THEN SILENCE.
- AND THEN THIS DAMNED FOG.
- NOT ONLY ARE
WE NOW OFF COURSE,
WE HAVE NO MEANS
TO FIND A PORT.
- THAT TEMPEST COULD'VE BLOWN US
ANYWHERE IN CHRISTENDOM.
- LAND!
- WHERE'S THE SHIP?
- WELL, LET'S
NOT STAND AROUND HERE.
WE'LL CATCH OUR DEATH
FROM THE COLD.
THERE MIGHT BE
WARMTH AND FOOD FURTHER ON.
- I THINK WE SHOULD
STOP AND PRAY FOR GUIDANCE.
- OR WE COULD CONTINUE
WALKING AND FIND SOME.
- I WONDER WHY THE CRUSADE
HAS STRENGTHENED THE FAITH
OF EVERYBODY EXCEPT YOU.
- WELL, MAYBE I WAS THE ONLY
ONE FIGHTING WITH MY EYES OPEN.
SHH, SHH, SHH.
LISTEN, WHAT'S THAT?
STAY.
GUARD THE RELIQUARY.
COME ON.
- IF YOU INSIST.
- BLITHERING BARBARIANS!
- ROBERT!
NO, NO!
- AH!
AH!
AH.
- AH! AH.
- BANDITS.
- AH!
- THE TURKS
ARE ON OUR SIDE.
- AH--UGH.
- YOU FIGHT LIKE A KING.
- YOU KNEEL WHEN
YOU SPEAK TO A KNIGHT, DOG.
- SIR ROBERT!
CRUSADES ARE OVER.
SURELY THAT MEANS THAT
WE CAN ALL BE FRIENDS NOW.
- MY THOUGHTS TOO.
WE HAVE BEEN HUNTING
THESE...BANDITS
EVER SINCE THEY PILLAGED
SEVERAL MOSQUES.
WHEN THEY ATTACKED
THESE PILGRIMS,
WE COULD NOT STAND ASIDE IDLY
AS AN INJUSTICE WAS COMMITTED.
- YOU LIE.
- IT IS TRUE, MY LORD.
THE TURKS
FOUGHT TO SAVE US.
WE ARE THE ONLY TWO
WHO SURVIVED.
- THE TURK'S NAME
IS HASAN.
MY WIFE, SAFA.
OUR FRIEND, ALEM.
- YOU WILL BE
REWARDED FOR YOUR--
- WE DID NOT DO IT
FOR A REWARD.
AND AS I SEE IT,
YOU SAVED MY LIFE.
TWICE.
THE FIRST IS MY REWARD.
AND THE SECOND...A DEBT
OF HONOR THAT I OWE YOU.
WE WILL TRAVEL
THESE LANDS WITH YOU
UNTIL I CAN
REPAY SUCH A DEBT.
- YOU CAN'T SERIOUSLY WANT
THESE SAVAGES TO TRAVEL WITH US.
- FIND BROTHER GEORGE.
TELL HIM TO TEND TO THE WOUND.
THESE PILGRIMS WILL TRAVEL
WITH US UNTIL THEY FIND SAFETY.
SHH, SHH, SHH, SHH.
- PERHAPS YOU ARE A MAN OF PEACE
AS WELL AS A MAN OF WAR.
- AH, SIR ROBERT...
I TAKE IT YOU
NO LONGER DISAPPROVE
NOW WE HAVE HORSES?
- WOULD YOU LISTEN
TO ME IF I DID?
OF COURSE NOT.
- WHAT TREASURE
DO YOU CARRY?
- IT IS A GIFT
FOR THE HOLY FATHER.
- A TROPHY
FROM THE CRUSADES?
ANIMALS SENSE THINGS
WE CANNOT.
REAL POWER
FROM PERCEIVED POWER.
REAL VICTORY
FROM PERCEIVED VICTORY.
I FEAR THIS CRUSADE
WILL NOT BE THE LAST.
- AFTER WHAT I'VE WITNESSED,
I HOPE YOU'RE WRONG.
- I WONDER WHY YOU ARE
SO KEEN TO RETURN HOME.
DID YOU NOT FIND
THE GLORY YOU SOUGHT?
- THERE WAS NO GLORY.
- FIGHTING FOR GOD
IS GLORY ENOUGH.
- I USED TO THINK SO.
- AND NOW?
- MAN BEGETS THE EVILS
OF THIS WORLD.
NOT GOD.
- AND IS YOUR LOSS OF FAITH
THE REASON YOU DRESS
LIKE A FILTHY PIG?
I ONCE LED
100 MEN-AT-ARMS.
WHAT YOU SEE HERE...
IS ALL THAT'S LEFT.
TO WASH MY HANDS
OF THAT BLOOD...
WOULD BE LIKE PONTIUS PILATE
WASHING HIS HANDS.
I'M NOT YET READY
FOR MY ABSOLUTION.
- ALL OF THIS IS
THE BYZANTINE EMPIRE...
YOUR SHIP BEACHED HERE.
FROM HERE, WE SHOULD
GO INTO CONSTANTINOPLE,
AND FROM THERE,
YOU CAN CARRY ON TO ROME.
- THAT IS A LONG WAY AROUND.
WHY NOT GO WEST?
- BECAUSE THAT WAY, YOU WOULD
HAVE TO CROSS THE SEA TWICE.
AND...
AFTER YOUR
RECENT EXPERIENCE,
I THOUGHT MAYBE YOU
WOULD PREFER TO STAY DRY.
- SO WE
FOLLOW YOU BLINDLY?
- YOU CAN TAKE YOUR
OWN BLIND PATH IF YOU PREFER.
- CAREFUL HOW YOU SPEAK TO ME.
- WHY SHOULD SHE
WATCH HER MOUTH
AROUND SUCH
AN UNGALLANT KNIGHT?
- A KNIGHT WHO HAS A SERF
LIKE YOU UNDER HIS PROTECTION.
YOU SHOULD BE
THANKFUL FOR THAT.
I CAN LOOK AFTER MYSELF.
- YOU HAVE COURAGE.
IT IS A FINE
QUALITY TO HAVE.
- SOMETHING I INHERITED
FROM MY FATHER.
HE WAS A BLACKSMITH.
HE TAUGHT ME HOW TO SURVIVE
IN AN UNJUST WORLD.
- THE WORLD IS
NOT UNJUST, MY CHILD.
GOD IS EVERYWHERE.
- I DON'T BELIEVE IN GOD.
- THAT IS BLASPHEMY.
- IF THERE IS A GOD,
WHY DID HE
KILL MY FATHER...
AND HAVE ME INDENTURED
TO A SPOILED LORD
WHO DRAGGED ME
HALFWAY AROUND THE WORLD
ON A PILGRIMAGE
I HAVE NO BELIEF IN?
WHERE'S THE SENSE
IN THAT?
- THERE ARE PUNISHMENTS
FOR WHAT YOU'VE JUST SAID.
- YOUR GOD PUNISHES THOSE
WHO DO NOT BELIEVE?
ALLAH SUBHAN-ALLAH
IS MORE MERCIFUL THAN THAT.
- DON'T GET ME
STARTED ON YOU, HEATHEN!
- THERE ARE NO ARGUMENTS
IN THIS CAMP.
WE'RE ALL FRIENDS HERE.
I THINK NOW WOULD BE
A GOOD TIME FOR US TO SLEEP.
MY KNIGHTS WILL KEEP WATCH.
- I'M AFRAID THAT'S
ALL WE COULD SPARE.
BUT IT'S NICE AND WARM.
AND MAKE SURE IT DOESN'T PUT
YOU TO SLEEP LIKE THE LAST TIME.
- THANK YOU.
COLD'S BITING WORSE
THAN EVER TONIGHT.
- NO SIGN?
- NO.
- THE RELIC WAS SAFE.
- WHY WOULD THIEVES
NOT TAKE IT?
- WE TRACKED
THE KNIGHT'S FOOTSTEPS.
THEY JUST VANISH.
- MUST'VE BEEN AN AMBUSH.
- YOU MISHEARD ME,
I SAID THEY VANISH.
HE DID NOT
TAKE ANOTHER STEP.
THIS IS NOT
THE WORK OF...NORMAL MEN.
- THE HASHSHASHIN
WALK THESE LANDS.
THEY ARE MURDERERS
AND THIEVES.
- EVEN THE HASHSHASHIN
LEAVE A TRACE.
- THEN IT IS
THE DEVIL'S WORK.
- THERE IS
NO MORE WE CAN DO.
WE MUST LEAVE THIS PLACE
AND MOVE ON.
- YOU SHOULD PLACE A BRIDLE
OVER THE FRIAR'S MOUTH.
HE'S SCARING THE OTHERS WITH
ALL THIS TALK OF THE DEVIL.
- IS HE SCARING YOU?
- IF GOD DOESN'T EXIST,
THEN NEITHER DOES THE DEVIL.
I'M ONLY AFRAID OF
THE EVIL IN MEN'S HEARTS.
NOT IN THEIR MINDS.
YOU KNOW I DON'T BELIEVE.
AND I DON'T THINK
YOU DO EITHER, MY LORD.
- OH, NOW YOU KNOW
WHAT I THINK?
- IT WAS A COMPLIMENT.
YOU'RE NOT LIKE THE OTHERS.
- CUT THEM DOWN.
CUT THEM DOWN.
- THIS IS EVIL,
I TELL YOU.
- NOW IS NOT THE TIME
FOR SCAREMONGERING!
- THE FOOD ON THE BOAT,
THE STORM, THE BANDITS,
AND NOW THIS--IT'S THE
DEVIL'S WORK, AND YOU KNOW IT.
SATAN IS TRYING
TO DESTROY THE CROSS!
- KEEP YOUR VOICE DOWN.
WHAT DO YOU SUGGEST I DO?
BURY THEM BOTH.
- I AGREE
WITH YOUR PRIEST.
THIS PLACE IS...EVIL.
- WE SHOULD LEAVE HERE.
- WAIT, WAIT.
NOBODY LEAVES UNTIL
THE DEAD ARE BURIED.
- I AM A NATIVE
TO THIS LAND.
NO, NOT JUST A NATIVE.
MORE THAN A NATIVE.
I KNOW THIS LAND
CORNER FROM CORNER.
AND YET,
IN ALL MY LIFE,
I HAVE NEVER SEEN THINGS
LIKE THIS BEFORE.
MAYBE YOUR PRIEST
IS RIGHT.
MAYBE THERE IS EVIL
IN THIS PLACE.
AH!
- BROTHER GEORGE.
- WHAT'S HAPPENING?
- BLESS US NOW.
- I HAVE MIXED THE HERB
IN THE WATER TO NUMB THE PAIN.
YOUR LEG
DOESN'T LOOK GOOD.
IT WILL NEED BINDING.
- THE CROSS OF CHRIST?
PART OF IT, YES.
- NOW I UNDERSTAND
WHY BAD LUCK FOLLOWS YOU.
YOURS IS A PRIZE EVIL
FINDS WORTHY OF DESTRUCTION.
- ALL THE MORE REASON
TO GET IT SAFELY TO ROME.
SIR ROBERT, I WANT YOU
TO GUARD THE RELIQUARY.
MAKE SURE
NO ONE TOUCHES IT.
- THANK YOU.
- SOMETHING PUZZLES ME.
YOU'RE CARRYING
A RELIC THAT YOU BELIEVE
TO BE A PIECE
OF CHRIST'S CROSS.
AND YOU ACCEPT
THAT TO BE REAL?
AS MUSLIMS?
- THE KORAN SPEAKS
OF JESUS AS A PROPHET.
- YOU BELIEVE IN HIM TOO?
- OF COURSE.
ALTHOUGH
THERE IS SOME DEBATE
AS TO WHETHER
HE DIED ON THE CROSS.
- I DON'T UNDERSTAND WHY
YOU FIGHT FOR SIMILAR BELIEFS.
IT DOESN'T MAKE ANY SENSE.
- WE ARE NOT FIGHTING NOW.
- AND YOU?
YOU DON'T
BELIEVE IN ANYTHING.
SO IS THE CASKET EMPTY?
OR DOES IT JUST
CONTAIN A PIECE OF WOOD?
- MAYBE THERE WAS
A MAN CALLED JESUS.
I CAN BELIEVE THAT.
BUT AS THE SON OF GOD?
OR EVEN AS
THE PROPHET OF GOD?
NO.
IT'S JUST A STORY.
- THEN THAT
IS YOUR OWN BELIEF.
I WONDER...
WHO IS RIGHT?
MM. EH.
- EVERYONE,
GRAB A TORCH.
ROBERT!
- THEY'RE GETTING CLOSER.
- ROBERT!
- EH, EH, EH.
- OH!
- HA! HA!
- HAY-YA!
- AH!
- ARE THEY GONE?
- I THINK SO.
AND SO ARE THE HORSES.
- ROBERT?
ROBERT, CAN YOU HEAR ME?
- AH.
- WE NEED A HEALER.
- SAFA!
- AH!
- LOOK!
- AH, HE'S IN FEVER.
I NEED COLD WATER
AND PLANTS.
ALEM, BRING BORAGE
AND MOUNTAIN BALM.
THERE MIGHT
BE MORE INSIDE.
- IS YOUR PRIZE
WORTH THIS SACRIFICE?
- WE CAN'T ALLOW
ANY DARK FORCES TO WIN.
- I AGREE.
OUR GODS
MAY BE DIFFERENT,
BUT OUR ENEMY
IS THE SAME.
WHAT DO YOU SUGGEST?
- WE NEED TO FIND
SOME WISE COUNSEL.
SOME HOLY GROUND.
- THERE IS A--
A MONASTERY NORTH OF HERE.
A DAY'S MARCH ON FOOT.
IS--IS THAT SACRED ENOUGH?
THANK YOU, HASAN.
- HIS FEVER IS EASING.
YOU HAVE
A PRECIOUS SKILL.
- CAN YOU SPEAK?
- I, UH...
- YOUR NAME WOULD BE
A GOOD PLACE TO START.
- PAUL.
- SQUIRE PAUL?
- SOON TO BE A KNIGHT...
WHEN WE RETURN HOME.
- LIKE SIR GREGORY.
- THE MEN ARE STARVING.
AND MY STOMACH
IS COMPLAINING TOO.
- THERE'S PRECIOUS LITTLE
TO HUNT DOWN HERE.
IT WILL HAVE TO COMPLAIN
A LITTLE LONGER.
- LOOK, WE CANNOT
AFFORD TO BE WEAK...
IF WE ARE
ATTACKED AGAIN.
- THAT KIND OF TALK
CAUSES PANIC, ARTHUR.
- OUR FORTUNE HAS CHANGED.
A FARM.
- GREETINGS.
I AM SIR GREGORY.
- YOU'RE A LONG WAY
FROM THE WAR, MY LORD.
- WE ARE
HEADING TO ROME.
- THEN YOU'RE A LONG WAY
FROM ROME, MY LORD.
WE...WE HAVE
TRAVELED FAR WITHOUT FOOD.
WE ARE VERY HUNGRY.
IF YOU HAVE ANY TO SPARE,
WE WOULD BE MOST GRATEFUL.
- FOR YOU.
NOT FOR THEM.
- THEY ARE OUR FRIENDS.
HAVEN'T YOU HEARD?
THE WAR IS OVER.
AS A KNIGHT,
I VOUCH FOR THEM.
- SO DO I.
- ALL RIGHT.
COME IN.
- YOU ARE MOST KIND.
- GUARD
THE RELIQUARY.
- EXCELLENT.
THIS STEW
IS FIT FOR A KING.
- WE'VE HAD A HARD ROAD
SINCE WE WERE SHIPWRECKED HERE.
THIS IS A HOSTILE LAND.
- NO.
SINCE MY WIFE DIED,
MY DAUGHTER AND I
HAVE NEVER HAD
MUCH TROUBLE LIVING HERE.
DURING THE WAR, CRUSADERS
OCCASIONALLY PASSED THROUGH.
BUT NOW THERE
IS ONLY PILGRIMS.
THIS LAND IS ENJOYING
TIME OF PEACE.
SOME MORE SOUP?
- I DON'T BELIEVE THAT.
- I SWEAR.
WHEN HE WAS THROWN
FROM THE CATAPULT,
WE THOUGHT HIS BONES
WOULD SNAP IN TWO.
AND WHEN HE
SURFACED FROM THE LAKE,
HIS FACE WAS
AS WHITE AS YOURS.
A YOUNG MAN
SHOULD TALK TO A LADY.
- SIR GREGORY TOLD ME I'M
TO BE KNIGHTED WHEN WE RETURN.
MAYBE YOU WOULD CARE TO SEE
ENGLAND WHEN I'M KNIGHTED.
THEN YOU CAN SEE MY LANCE.
- WHAT?
WHAT DID I SAY?
- INSIDE.
INSIDE, ALL OF YOU!
QUICKLY, RUN!
- WHAT IS IT?
- SOMETHING'S COMING.
SOMETHING'S COMING.
- RUN!
- INSIDE!
- QUICKLY!
- WHAT?
- LOCUSTS!
- YOU HAVE BROUGHT
A PLAGUE WITH YOU.
- QUICK!
GO QUICK!
GO, GO, NOW!
OH, OH!
- IT'S CLEAR.
- THERE CAN BE NO DOUBT
SATAN IS TRYING
TO STOP YOU FROM
DELIVERING YOUR PRIZE.
- THEN WE BETTER
REACH THE MONASTERY...
BEFORE THE DEVIL
REACHES US.
SO STILL...
YOU'RE NOT SWAYED
BY RELIGION?
- I THINK THAT
THE RELIC THAT YOU CARRY
IS NOTHING BUT A CURSE,
AND YOU SHOULD LET
THE MONKS DEAL WITH IT.
THE POPE HAS MORE THAN
ENOUGH POWER AND WEALTH,
SO WHY GIVE HIM MORE?
- I SEEK FORGIVENESS.
- I THOUGHT ALL CRUSADERS WERE
GRANTED REMISSION OF THEIR SINS.
- OH, I DON'T SEEK
FORGIVENESS FROM GOD.
I SEEK IT FROM MYSELF.
- WHAT BRINGS KNIGHTS
OF THE CRUSADE
TO OUR HUMBLE MONASTERY?
- WE NEED SHELTER.
WE HAVE WOUNDED...
AND SOMETHING EVIL
IS STALKING US.
- EVIL?
A WOMAN.
- SHE IS WITH ME.
- THE TURKS CANNOT ENTER.
- THEY ARE GOOD PEOPLE.
THEY ARE OUR FRIENDS.
- THE TURKS WILL BE HAPPY
TO SLEEP UNDER THE STARS.
- LET ME BRING YOU TO SPEAK
WITH OUR ABBOT.
BUT YOUR WEAPONS
MUST STAY HERE.
WE DO NOT ALLOW THEM
IN THE HOUSE OF GOD EITHER.
- TAKE THE WOUNDED
TO A PRIVATE CHAMBER.
WHAT HAVE YOU BROUGHT?
- A SACRED RELIC FROM
THE HOLY LANDS.
IT'S WHY WE NEED TO SPEAK
WITH YOUR ABBOT.
- WHERE AM I?
- SIR ROBERT,
YOU'RE AWAKE AT LAST.
- WHAT HAPPENED?
- YOU WERE BURNING
WITH A FEVER,
BUT YOU'RE SAFE
IN A MONASTERY.
- MY BROTHERS WOKE ME
TO SAY
YOU CARRY SOMETHING
OF GREAT IMPORTANCE.
- WE CARRY A GIFT
FOR THE HOLY FATHER.
- WE HAVE SEEN MANY PILGRIMS
AND KNIGHTS PASS BY.
MANY EAGER TO MAKE
A NAME FOR THEMSELVES
BY BRINGING TRINKETS
OF UNIMAGINABLE WORTHLESSNESS.
- WE HAVE A PIECE
OF THE TRUE CROSS.
- SO I HAVE SEEN BEFORE.
- TELL ME, FATHER,
HAVE THESE TRAVELERS
YOU SPEAK OF BEEN PURSUED
BY MALICIOUS FORCES
INTENT ON DESTROYING
THEIR RELIC?
SINCE WE LEFT THE HOLY LAND,
WE'VE BEEN STRUCK BY TEMPESTS,
SHIPWRECKED,
MEMBERS OF OUR PARTY
HAVE BEEN BUTCHERED
IN THE FOREST.
BIRDS HAVE BEEN STRUCK DEAD
IN THE SKY.
WE'VE BEEN ATTACKED BY WOLVES
AND A PLAGUE OF LOCUSTS
AND ALL BECAUSE WE CARRY...
THIS.
AND YOU BELIEVE THIS
TO BE PART OF THE CRUCIFIX?
- WE DO.
- IT IS TRUE.
BEHOLD!
FROM THE CROSS OUR SAVIOR
WAS CRUCIFIED UPON!
AND IT WEEPS HIS BLOOD!
"IESYS NAZARENYS
REX IYDAEORYM.
JESUS NAZARENE,
KING OF THE JEWS."
THIS TRULY IS PART
OF THE CRUCIFIX.
THE INSCRIPTION WAS PLACED
ABOVE CHRIST'S HEAD.
PUT THERE TO MOCK HIM.
THIS RELIC--
BUT THIS RELIC IS TAINTED
BY THIS CURSED INSCRIPTION.
DARK FORCES ARE NOT TRYING
TO STOP YOU.
THE RELIC IS ATTRACTING EVIL
TO YOU,
DRAWING IT LIKE A MOTH
TO A FLAME.
- WELL, THEN--
THEN WE MUST DESTROY IT.
- IT IS SACRILEGE TO DESTROY
A SACRED RELIC.
- WELL, IF IT IS THE LETTERS
THAT ARE CURSED,
WHY NOT TRY TO REMOVE THEM?
- TRY THIS.
- THAT CANNOT BE.
- CAN WE BURY IT
IN THE MONASTERY?
- COMING HERE HAS NOT
IMPROVED OUR SITUATION.
- BEHIND YOU!
- THERE'S ONE BEHIND YOU
ON THE TABLE!
- IT'S BOLTED FROM INSIDE...
LIKE A FORT.
YOU WILL ALL ROT IN HELL.
- YOU KILLED HIM.
- THE MONKS WERE POSSESSED.
THE RELIC IS DRAWING
EVIL TOWARDS US.
- THEN WE MUST DESTROY IT
BEFORE IT KILLS US ALL.
- NO!
IMPOSSIBLE.
IT'S NOT EVEN WARM.
- IT IS MADNESS TO DESTROY
A RELIGIOUS ARTIFACT.
- EVEN ONE SO EVIL?
- YOU SAW THE BLOOD.
THAT IS BLOOD OF OUR SAVIOR.
BLOOD THAT MUST NOT
BE TAINTED.
THERE ARE POWERS IN ROME
THAT CAN DEAL WITH THIS.
- WE WILL NEVER MAKE IT.
- HE'S RIGHT.
AND EVEN IF WE DID,
THE EVIL IT DRAWS TO US
WILL DESTROY EVERYTHING BEFORE
WE EVEN REACHED ROME.
- THEN LEAVE IT HERE.
- FOR OTHERS TO FIND
AND BE SLAUGHTERED?
NO.
WE HAVE A RESPONSIBILITY
TO KEEP OTHERS SAFE.
THAT IS THE CODE
WE SWORE ALLEGIANCE TO.
THAT IS THE KNIGHT'S CODE.
WHAT SAY YOU,
SIR ROBERT?
ROBERT, ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
- NEVER FELT BETTER.
- WE CANNOT DESTROY IT.
WE CANNOT LEAVE IT
AND WE CANNOT TAKE IT.
YOU HAVE PUT US IN A PUZZLE
THAT WE CANNOT SOLVE.
- WE HAVE NO CHOICE
BUT TO TAKE THE DAMNED THING.
- IF IT CAN WORK ITS EVIL
HERE ON HOLY GROUND,
WHERE CAN WE TAKE IT
THAT IT'S SAFE?
- IT DIDN'T WORK
IN JERUSALEM.
AT LEAST NOT TO THIS EXTENT.
- THE POWER OF THE HOLY LAND
MIGHT BE ENOUGH
TO CONTAIN THE EVIL.
- WE MUST RETURN TO JERUSALEM.
- HEAD BACK?
- I DON'T SEE ANY OTHER WAY.
- THANK YOU.
- FOR WHAT?
- HOW MANY MORE TIMES
WILL YOU SAVE MY LIFE?
- AHH.
HOW MANY MORE TIMES WILL
I PUT YOUR LIFE IN DANGER?
PERHAPS YOU SHOULD GO HOME.
HASAN AND BROTHER GEORGE
CAN ACCOMPANY YOU.
THE EVIL WON'T
FOLLOW YOU THERE.
- AND RETURN TO WHAT?
I HAVE NO HOME.
MY FATHER'S FORGE
WAS TAKEN BECAUSE
HE COULD NOT PAY HIS TAXES.
IT WAS HIS LIFE.
- PERHAPS IF WE RETURN
TOGETHER,
YOU COULD FIND A HOME.
THANK YOU FOR YOUR HELP
LAST NIGHT.
IT'S BEEN A TERRIBLE LOSS
FOR BOTH OF US.
I CONSIDER YOUR DEBT
TO BE REPAID.
- BAH.
MERELY A TIMELY ENTRANCE.
A FOOL COULD BREAK
OPEN A DOOR.
I'VE YET TO ACTUALLY
SAVE YOUR LIFE.
- YOU HAVE A BEAUTIFUL WIFE
TO CONSIDER, MY FRIEND.
I HAVE NONE.
- NO...LADY WAITING AT HOME?
I WAS MARRIED ONCE
IN MY YOUTH.
- AND WHAT HAPPENED?
- SHE DIED IN CHILDBIRTH
ALONG WITH THE CHILD.
- I THINK YOU SHOULD REST,
MY FRIEND.
- SPARE ME YOUR PITY.
- DON'T MOVE.
DON'T EVEN BREATHE.
- DO WE NOT HAVE
ENOUGH PROBLEMS
WITHOUT FIGHTING
AMONGST OURSELVES?
- THE FOOL'S AFFLICTED
WITH MADNESS!
HE OFFENDED ME.
- AND HOW WOULD THAT BE,
SIR ROBERT?
- I DON'T LIKE
THE LOOK OF HIM.
AND AS FOR YOU...
LAY A FINGER ON ME AGAIN
AND YOU WILL BLEED, WHORE.
AND YOU WILL NOT STOP ME.
- I WILL NOT NEED TO.
SHE CAN FIGHT HER OWN BATTLES.
- WHAT'S GOT INTO YOU?
- HIS SKIN IS BURNING.
- THE FEVER WAS CLEARING.
WHAT WAS THAT?
- A SPLINTER?
- HE'S BEEN POISONED
BY A SPLINTER FROM THE RELIC.
IT'S WORKING INTO HIS BODY.
- WHAT CAN WE DO?
- IT'S BEYOND MY KNOWLEDGE
TO CURE HIM.
LET ME GO!
- WE'LL HAVE TO BUILD
A STRETCHER.
- A FOULNESS AFFLICTS HIM.
SOMETHING WICKED COMES NEAR.
THE STORM, THE PLAGUE...
IT'S GETTING WORSE.
A DEMON STRENGTHENS
AND DRAWS CLOSER.
- DID HE HURT YOU?
- NO.
- NOW HAVE SAFA TAKE
A LOOK AT THAT
AND THEN STAY CLOSE BY.
- I DON'T LIKE THE LOOK OF IT.
- SIR ROBERT'S CONDITION
IS DETERIORATING.
TO STOP NOW WOULD BE
TO CONDEMN HIM TO DEATH.
- THEN WE GO ON.
- THE DEMON HAS FOUND US.
I DON'T FEAR YOU, DEMON.
I HAVE THE POWER OF GOD
ON MY SIDE.
CHRIST IS MY SAVIOR,
AND IN HIS NAME
I CAST YOU TO THE PIT
OF HELL WHERE YOU BELONG.
BEELZEBUB,
EATER OF THE DEAD,
BE GONE BACK TO HELL!
UGH!
- DIE BY MY BLADE.
- IN THE NAME OF THE FATHER,
HIS SON, AND THE HOLY SPIRIT,
I CONDEMN YOU.
- SAFA!
- GET THEM OFF ME.
HELP ME!
- THE DEMON HAS FOUND IT.
- DID YOU KILL IT?
- THE HOLY SYMBOL DREW
ITS BLOOD, BUT...
I DON'T THINK IT KILLED IT.
IT HAS BOUGHT US
A LITTLE MORE TIME THOUGH.
WE MUST DESTROY
THE RELIC BEFORE--
BEFORE THE BEAST RETURNS,
ELSE...
WE ALL DIE THIS NIGHT.
ARE YOU SURE THIS IS WISE?
- WE HAVE NO WAY
OF DESTROYING THE RELIC.
WE MUST BURY IT,
SO NO ONE ELSE HAS
THE MISFORTUNE OF FINDING IT.
AND THEN WE RETURN LATER,
BETTER PREPARED.
- RETURN?
- WITH AN ARMY FROM JERUSALEM.
200 MEN TO FIGHT THAT DEMON.
- 200, 500, 1,000!
WHAT DIFFERENCE DOES IT MAKE?
- WHAT DO YOU SUGGEST?
- SIEGE WEAPONS.
MY FATHER HELPED BUILD
SOME ONCE.
A MACHINE OF WAR WILL
BE POWERFUL ENOUGH
TO SLAY THE BEAST.
- YOU MAY BE CORRECT
TO A POINT.
IT IS HELL SPAWN.
MORTAL WEAPONS CANNOT KILL IT.
- THE FEVER GROWS WORSE.
- HE NEEDS TO DIE.
- NO!
HE'S A KNIGHT.
HE FOUGHT WITH HONOR.
HE DOESN'T DESERVE
AN INGLORIOUS DEATH.
- THEN WE MUST KEEP
THAT DOG ON A LEASH.
- LET'S LEAVE THIS PLACE
AND PUT THIS NIGHTMARE
BEHIND US.
ROBERT.
ROBERT, YOU NEED TO EAT.
ROBERT, I KNOW YOU'RE
INSIDE THERE.
I KNOW YOU CAN HEAR ME.
DON'T LET THIS THING
CONTROL YOU.
FIGHT THIS THING.
YOU WILL DIE HERE.
YOUR SOUL WILL ROT IN HELL.
- YOU ARE A KNIGHT!
- YOUR SPIRITS ARE DEAD.
- YOU ARE A CRUSADER.
- HOW IS HE?
- HE NEEDS AN EXORCIST.
- MORE IMPORTANTLY,
WE NEED FOOD.
THAT WAS THE LAST.
- WE HAVE PASSED
NO ANIMALS FOR DAYS.
AND STILL IT'S A DAY'S RIDE
TO THE NEAREST TOWN.
- HAVE NO FEAR.
THE EVIL IS BEHIND US.
ALLAH SUBHANAHU WA-TA'ALA
IS GUIDING US ALONG
A SAFE PATH.
OR PERHAPS IT IS CHRIST,
PEACE BE UPON HIM.
IF WE BOTH PRAY,
SURELY SOMEONE
WILL BE LISTENING.
EITHER WAY,
WE WALK AS BROTHERS.
WE WILL SURVIVE.
- FATHER, FORGIVE ME FOR
ALL MY SINS.
- SORRY.
CAN I PRAY WITH YOU?
- OF COURSE.
I THOUGHT YOU DOUBTED.
- I SAW THAT DEMON
WITH MY OWN EYES.
FROM WHICHEVER HELL IT CAME,
I SAW IT.
THAT MEANS THAT THERE
IS A HELL.
- THEN...THERE MUST
BE A HEAVEN.
- SIR ROBERT?
- AHH!
- MAY THAT BE THE LAST
OF THE DEMON SPAWN.
- AT DAWN, WE GO DOWN.
MAKE SURE HE'S DEAD.
- WE'RE BEING WATCHED.
- IT'S JUST YOUR IMAGINATION.
- THIS VALLEY IS PERFECT
FOR AN AMBUSH.
- DOES THAT MEAN
WE HAVE WILLINGLY
WALKED INTO A TRAP?
- WE'RE JUMPING AT SHADOWS.
HE'S NOT HERE.
COME ON.
- IT CANNOT BE.
RUN!
- OUR PROBLEMS
ARE FAR FROM OVER.
- CAREFUL.
DON'T TOUCH IT.
- IS THIS REALLY
CHRIST'S BLOOD?
- IT IS.
- WHY DOES IT CONTINUE
TO BLEED?
- FOR ALL THE PAIN
THAT CHRIST ENDURED.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
- IF IT'S GOING
TO KEEP TURNING UP
EVERYWHERE WE ARE,
THEN WE MAY AS WELL
CONTINUE TO CARRY IT.
AT LEAST THIS WAY WE KNOW
WHERE IT IS.
LET'S GO.
- WHAT IS IT?
- I CAN'T DO THIS ANYMORE.
- YOU CAN.
YOU CAN.
IT THRIVES ON OUR DESPAIR.
STAY STRONG.
- MY FRIEND...
YOU SHOULD TAKE
A LOOK AT THESE.
- LOOKS LIKE THEY WERE
IN A SIEGE.
- THIS WAS NO WAR BETWEEN MEN.
- THESE WERE FIGHTING MEN
HEADING FOR THE HOLY LAND.
- WELL, THEY FOUND HELL
RIGHT HERE.
- THESE TRACKS ARE ALMOST
TWO DAYS OLD.
- THAT'S BEFORE
WE WERE SHIPWRECKED.
FRIAR GEORGE THOUGHT
THAT IT HAD BEEN
DRAWN TOWARDS US.
BUILDING ITS POWER
TO CONFRONT US.
WON'T BE LONG BEFORE IT
FINDS US AGAIN.
- WHERE'S REBECCA?
- REBECCA?
- MY CHILDHOOD WAS SPENT
IN A PLACE LIKE THIS.
THE BEATING HEART
OF THE COMMUNITY.
MY FATHER TAUGHT ME
EVERYTHING I KNOW.
THE CRAFT,
HOW TO USE THE FORGE,
THE RIGHT TIME
TO STRIKE THE STEEL.
SPARE ME!
- YOU ARE SAFE.
- I HAVE SEEN THE DEVIL.
THE FACE OF DEATH.
THE REAPER,
SHE DID THIS!
SHE DID ALL OF THIS!
- ENOUGH.
YOU ARE SAFE.
- YOU.
YOU TURKS.
YOU TURKS BROUGHT IT HERE.
- I SAID YOU ARE SAFE.
- WHAT'S GOING ON?
- A SURVIVOR.
- A KNIGHT?
A KNIGHT HAS COME
TO DELIVER US FROM EVIL.
SAVE US, SIR.
SAVE OUR SOULS.
- SHH.
WHAT'S YOUR NAME?
- MY LADY.
SIMON, MY LADY.
- AND WHAT HAPPENED HERE?
- I WAS A FIGHTER.
1 OF 100 MEN ON OUR WAY
TO SEEK NEW LIFE IN JERUSALEM.
THEN--THEN THE WAR ENDED,
BUT WE CONTINUED.
CONTINUED TO FIND THAT NEW LIFE
IN THE HOLY LANDS.
WE ARRIVED AHEAD OF--
AHEAD OF TALES ABOUT
THAT DEMON WHO--
WHO FED FROM THE DEAD
OF THE CRUSADES
AS IT WAS SEARCHING
FOR SOMETHING.
IT HUNTED US FOR SPORT.
HUNDREDS OF OUR MEN.
MANY MORE FROM THE TOWN
WERE ALL CUT DOWN.
OUR STEEL IS USELESS!
- YOU SAY IT HUNTED
FOR SPORT?
- IT TORMENTED ITS VICTIMS
LIKE A CAT WOULD.
IT CHASED THEM DOWN BEFORE
SLAUGHTERING THEM.
IT ENJOYED THE SLAYING.
- IF HUNDREDS OF WARRIORS COULD
NOT STOP THIS MONSTER,
THEN WHAT CHANCE HAVE WE?
- WE NEED A MIRACLE.
- I KNOW WE CAN DO THIS.
WE JUST NEED TIME.
- TIME?
THERE IS NO TIME.
- BUT...WE HAD WEAPONS
TO KILL IT.
THOUGH WE HAD NO TIME
TO DEPLOY THEM.
- WEAPONS?
WHAT WEAPONS?
- HERE.
COME.
LOOK HERE.
SEE?
WE HAD THE WEAPONS
TO KILL THE BEAST.
- PERHAPS NOW WE CAN MAKE
A STAND.
- BUT STEEL WILL NOT EVEN
SCRATCH ITS HIDE.
- SIMON?
- NEVER!
TWO DIED TO KILL ONE MAN.
WHAT CHANCE HAVE WE AGAINST
THE DEMON NOW?
WE SHOULD RUN.
- WE TRIED THAT.
- WELL, THEN WE TRY HARDER.
AND IF THERE IS A GOD,
THEN WE PRAY
THAT HE SAVES US.
- "IF"?
YOU'VE FOUND FAITH ONLY
TO LOSE IT NOW?
- THOSE WEAPONS ARE NOT GOING
TO BE POWERFUL ENOUGH,
AND THEY WERE OUR ONLY HOPE.
- NO.
THERE IS ANOTHER.
WHAT BETTER WEAPON THAN
THE BLOOD OF CHRIST?
- AND IF THIS DOESN'T WORK?
THEN WE NEED SOMETHING
TO BUY US SOME TIME.
THE BEAST CAN APPEAR
WHEREVER WE ARE.
IT'LL COME HERE.
WHEN IT REACHES HERE,
WE FIRE.
CAN'T MISS AT THAT RANGE.
- WHAT WAS IT LIKE,
JERUSALEM?
- IT WAS LIKE THIS.
WAR TORN.
FRIGHTENING.
THAT'S WHEN THE DREAMS STARTED.
- DREAMS?
- AHH, DREAMS OF BATTLE.
FIGHTING.
ALWAYS VERY VIVID.
THEN WHEN WE GOT HERE
AND FOUND THE RELIC...
I HAD DREAMS OF THE DEMON.
- YOU HAD PREMONITIONS?
- I DON'T KNOW.
MAYBE THAT'S HOW
THE DEMON KNEW
WE WERE TAKING THE RELIC
OUT OF THE HOLY LAND.
IT WAS USING ME.
NOW I JUST DREAM OF RETURNING
TO MY LAND
AND FINDING SOMEONE
TO SHARE IT WITH ME.
- AND INSTEAD
YOU MET AN INDENTURED SLAVE.
- NO.
I MET AT WOMAN WHO JUST DIDN'T
KNOW SHE WAS FREE.
IT'S COMING.
WHERE IS IT?
WHAT'S HAPPENING?
- RUN!
RUN!
GO!
FIRE!
THE RELIC!
THROW ME THE RELIC!
WE DID IT.