# I wonder why the hell
I stay in this town #
# Ain't much to do
when the sun goes down #
# But think about what I'll do
when I'm with you #
# Still don't know
why you went away #
# When black and white
turns into gray #
# Life is cold but I was warm
when I kissed you #
# When I'm with you my heart
pounds like rain #
# When I'm with you,
I'm immune to pain #
I feel no restraint #
# When I'm with you #
# And I don't know how
I'm gonna live this way #
# Eternity burned out that day #
# And I don't know how I'm gonna
spend my life without you #
# And the church bells are
ringing all across the world #
# And prophesies
go unfulfilled #
# Cause they always told me I
would spend my life with you #
# I won't say Adieu #
# How much more time
will I have to wait #
# You left me
in a restless state #
# I'll walk around like I'm in
a trance 'til I'm with you #
# I wonder where on earth
you could have gone #
# Feel like a siren
that somebody left on #
# Screaming out into the night
that I miss you #
# When I'm with you,
I feel warm inside #
time and space divide #
# When I'm with you,
I am so alive #
# When I'm with you #
# And I don't know how
I'm gonna live this way #
# Eternity burned out that day #
# And I don't know how I'm gonna
spend my life without you #
# And the church bells are
ringing all across the world #
# And prophesies
go unfulfilled #
# Cause they always told me
I would spend my life with you #
# I won't say Adieu #
# Adieu #
Hello Ma'am!
Beautiful day isn't it?
Go to hell.
Hey dude!
Can you spare some change?
No!
Love the hair though!
Fuck!
I can't wear the shirt I wanted.
It's too small.
It looks like my tits
are gonna pop out.
Sarah!
I just don't think that would
look very good in the pictures.
Yes but we have to leave
in fifteen minutes.
Don't pressure me.
I told you,
I don't want to be pressured!
I know. I know. But do you
have to wear your hair like this?
Like what?
Can't you just fix it a little?
I did already!
Hey all!
Sarah...
Look what I got for you.
Pearls!
Aren't they pretty?
I found them on the subway
but you can borrow them trom me.
You know -
something old, something new,
something borrowed,
something blue!
Do you have something blue?
No.
Hello Mama!
- Sarah.
You look sparkling today!
Oh, really.
Well, thank you Kyle.
Aren't you excited about
your son getting married?
More nervous I guess.
I'm the best man you know.
I know that Kyle.
Oh, you must be so proud of him.
Look how beautiful he is!
Kyle, can you get her
to finish please?
Me and mama have to get
some flowers from the deli.
Are you sure you don't want
anything in particular?
Maybe some nice tulips?
I guess not. Let's go.
Get something blue!
Sarah - come on!
Quickly!
Come on!
Yes, it seems to fit alright.
Thanks Danny.
Hey hurry up guys!
It's our turn!
Ok, let's go.
Come on!
Shit, I can't get it on.
Ok wait, let me help you.
OK, look like you are putting it on
so mommy can take a picture.
Marcel. Sarah -
I now pronounce you,
husband and wife.
You may kiss or embrace.
Right over here.
Come on!
I can't believe that you made us
come all the way out here!
Stop it Danny!
I told you, I want to get
some nice pictures.
Kyle stand right here.
Stand beside him.
Danny over here.
Sarah next to me.
Come on!
Hold this like so.
Ready?
Smile!
OK now with just Sarah please.
Oh, come on!
Can you please just relax and smile,
and look at the camera.
How about a picture of the Groom
and the Best Man?
Stole a kiss!
What about Sarah throwing
her wedding bouquet away?
Finally. I can't wait
to get ride of this thing!
Alright.
I got it. I got it.
I wonder what this means...
I guess I better get a divorce...
very quickly.
Let's hope immigration
never sees those photos!
It made my mom so excitied...
to be able to tell all
her friends that I got married.
She wants those pictures!
She's too much!
- I know
I don't want
all my friends at home
to hear that I got married
to some guy.
That's disgusting!
Well you did!
Cheers!
Kyle, how come Sarah
agreed to this?
She's getting the apartment.
She's getting your apartment?
She was supposed to move out,
so that Kyle could move in with me.
But now I'm moving out.
But where are you going to live?
I don't know yet, mama.
Yes but unless I get a Greencard
I will have to move
back to Europe as well.
There's something
I'd like to say.
I'm the Best Man. I'm supposed
to say something, right?
I met Marcel a year
and three months ago today.
I'd just moved to New York,
and one night I walked into a bar...
And there he was.
My heart almost stopped
when I saw him.
I just knew...
Marcel, ever since that day -
I have loved you more
than anyone has ever loved.
Everyday you make me so happy.
Marcel -
Je t'aime pourtourjours.
Do you wanna marry me?
Yes Kyle! Yes.
I love you too so very much!
There's nothing I want more.
You do realize
I thought you were a treak?
when?
when we met.
Really?
I thought I was charming...
Freakishly charming
I would say...
I don't mean to stare at you,
but you have gorgeous eyes.
Thank you.
Is that your boytriend
standing over there?
No.
Do you have a boyfriend?
Do you want one?
That depends who's asking.
I'm Kyle.
what?
Kyle!
Like... Kyle.
Oh, I'm Marcel.
where are you from?
France.
vacation?
School.
Acting school.
But I'm almost finished.
I love you.
what?
Nothing.
I'm sorry.
I thought you said...
I did.
I'm sorry.
I don't mean to sound crazy.
Normally I wouldn't...
But I just can't
take my eyes off you.
That's OK, I noticed you too.
So, um, what kind of a boyfriend
are you looking for?
Oh, I don't know.
No seriously, if you could have
anyone in here, who'd you pick?
Come on, tell me.
would it be my triend Ben?
Probably not.
OK, so who?
Maybe him.
OK, let me go see
if he's available.
Excuse me! I was just wondering,
do you have a boyfriend?
Cause my friend over there
thinks you're cute.
Sorry, he was taken.
You're gonna have
to pick someone else.
You're crazy!
Come on.
Him!
Oh sorry.
Strippers are off limits.
Maybe you then.
well now we're
getting somewhere...
Hi boys!
Hello mama!
I just don't understand
why you two don't move to Europe
and just get married
to each other.
And you Marcel, you would not
have to go through all this charade.
Merci mama.
But we want to live here.
I just don't understand it...
So where's your wife tonight?
Oh, I don't know.
She said she was going
to play some pool with Danny.
Not ready to consummate
the marriage yet, huh?
No, we decided that could wait.
I told her you would be willing
to take on her marriage duties.
At least for the wedding night.
Sure, I'll entertain the groom
while the wife's playing pool.
No problem at all.
Fuck you asshole!
who do you think you are?
I don't do that shit!
Get back here.
I want my money back!
Fuck you motherfucker! You're lucky
I don't call the cops on you.
Thank you.
Sorry I'm late.
Did you just get off?
Oh, just about ten minutes ago.
Bye Kyle!
Bye.
I'm sorry I was late baby, but we'll
still make the show if we hurry.
It's not that.
what then?
Guess who just called?
who?
My sister.
April?
Yeah.
well?
She says she wants
to be friends again.
She says she regrets
everything that happened...
So?
I don't know.
You're not ready to forgive?
I know it's been over a year
but it's been a good year.
And I really haven't
missed her at all.
You tell him to go fuck himself!
That fucking superior
son-of-a-bitch!
This has nothing to do with Marcel.
I think you need help.
Professional help, 'cause I
can't take care of you anymore.
Not mentally,
and not financially.
Believe me,
I don't want your charity!
I can't even bring
my boyfriend over to visit
because I never know how
and when you'll be acting up.
well, no need to worry
about that anymore.
And part of me feels she doesn't
deserve my friendship again.
She is your sister.
And part of me feels
she's my sister.
And don't worry about
yourmoney. You'll get it back.
Yeah, whatever.
Besides,
I don't want your hooking money.
Fuck you.
I told you, I don't do that.
April, I know.
It's none of your
fucking business what I do.
She said she's not
tuming tricks anymore.
Maybe you should
give her a chance.
Family is very important, you know.
Sometimes, family is all you've got.
Get out of
my fucking life already.
For once and for fucking all!
Fine. I'll be back to get the rest
of this stuff this afternoon.
I don't need her any more.
I got my family right here.
Yes I know baby,
but maybe she needs you.
Hey, this is good stuff.
Yeah.
Real good.
You think we should help them?
Yeah, probably.
I still can't believe our luck
getting this apartment.
Isn't that crazy?
Just across the hall.
It's great your landlord
likes you so much -
He probably could've gotten
much more for this place.
I know.
And this is definitely the easiest
move I have ever had.
And the most exciting...
Are you sure you are ready
for us living together?
I've never been
more sure of anything.
Their constant lovy-doviness
makes me wanna shoot myself.
I mean I love them
and all but,
God am I happy not to have
to look at that every day.
I mean praise the lord
for my own apartment!
Only in New York.
what?
Only in this crazy town
would someone marry for a lease.
You know what else is crazy?
when I told my mom,
She said that she would have
given me money for a broker's fee.
It wouldn't have helped though.
why not?
well you still don't have
a credit history.
Oh sure I do,
it's just not very good.
Nice!
They are handmade trom France.
Gorgeous.
You know,
this place is just perfect!
And with Sarah living
down the hall,
she and I are practically
living together
without having to live together.
God knows that
was getting on my nerves.
She's so peculiar.
Maybe you'll find me
peculiar too...
I always have.
You can never leave me.
Hi.
How are you?
Good.
Something to drink?
Oh, Ice-tea please.
Coming right up.
And Marcel?
Are you still together?
Yeah.
He says hi.
we just moved in together.
And you got married?
well engaged.
we exchanged rings.
Congratulations.
Thanks.
And you?
Anyone new in your life?
Oh, well these two!
Yeah, I noticed
they look bigger!
I had to get rid
of the old ones,
I had too much
scar tissue building up.
Oh, I'm sorry.
You know Kyle,
it was us against the world.
Ever since mom's suicide.
we always knew that no matter what,
we could count on each other.
Do you think
we could be best friends again?
I would like that.
I'm a different person
now, Kyle.
And I'm really sorry
about everything.
Me too.
I'm sorry too.
No, I understand.
I can't say that I want this though,
especially considering all
the things you told me about her.
Don't let her know that you know.
Sarah, try to smile OK?
I wasn't even thinking about that,
it's more the other things.
She's obviously
not the most responsible person.
I'm happy you found each other
again, I just didn't expect this.
It's only for a couple of days.
Her rent is way overdue and she's
got to be out of that place now.
Sure.
She gives me
that feeling again though.
what feeling?
I don't know...
Baby, she loves you.
Now smile!
Hi all!
Hey girl!
Did everything go OK?
Yes.
Kyle, can you help me
with my things?
I dumped all the furniture,
but Gina's downstairs in her
mother's car and it's stuffed.
Of course.
Oh thank you so much for everything.
I know, my life's just insane!
Marcel, how are you?
Good.
Hi, I'm April.
Sarah.
Nice to meet you.
I've heard so much about you...
what does she mean?
You didn't tell anyone about...?
Of course not.
She means the other thing.
I can't believe
all the cool stuff you got.
when did you buy all this?
Kyle?
Yeah?
I missed you.
Kyle, aren't you
coming to bed soon?
Yeah honey, just a minute.
Can't you stay in here and we can
talk all night like we used to?
we'll talk tomorrow.
Good night.
That is nuts!
Hey baby!
I already ate since I didn't
hear back from you.
Oh that's OK,
April and I got pizza.
we're going to put an ad online
for band members,
so we can start our band again.
Isn't that exciting?
I thought we were going
to look at that sofa tonight?
Oh, let's do that later.
We want to get this done.
Besides as long as April's staying
in here, what's the point, right?
Yeah.
I'm fine sleeping on the floor.
Baby I got a surprise for you!
What is it?
Over here.
I'll be right back.
what is it?
Oh baby...
I remember when we took this.
Thank you.
we should put it up.
Ok, ready?
Smile.
I love holding you.
I love feeling your heartbeat.
I love looking into your eyes.
I love your body.
Your nose...
Your lips...
I love you.
I know it's too early to say
that after just six days...
but I'm just crazy about you.
I can't imagine life
without you now.
Hearing you say that
just fills my heart.
How can I describe
how happy you make me?
I really, truly feel that...
My God. what can I say
I've already said too much?
You haven't said too much.
what do you want?
we got a letter
from immigration today -
They moved up our interview.
It's already next Friday.
Are you serious?
They can't just do that.
well they can, they did.
Shit, we haven't even
started rehearsing yet.
we have to do it everyday.
No!
Sarah remember
that guitar you wanted?
Yeah.
It cost about two-fifty right?
Uh-huh.
If we pass, I'll buy it for you.
But we have to work really hard.
Deal.
Come back in an hour.
I don't wear makeup.
Even if I was straight
I wouldn't wear makeup.
My sister for example,
is very straight
and she doesn't wear makeup.
Ever!
The thing is though
we want to look professional.
we want to look like we have our
shit together so we come across...
like responsible,
totally normal people.
I'm a musician.
I live in the East village!
Do you think
it would look totally normal -
To have me go in there
looking like a lawyer?
Fat chance.
Look, if I'm going to be able
to go through with this,
I have to go as myself.
Fine. No makeup.
But can you at least wear a dress
so you look a little bit
more feminine?
I don't have any.
I will get you one.
Listen it can be totally hip.
Totally you.
I don't wear dresses.
Please! I will get you
something that you like
and then you can keep it.
How about you buy the dress
and then after the interview...
I return it and keep the money?
Fine.
But the ring has to go back too
and I wont let you
keep the money for that.
I just hope K-mart
will take it back.
It does look a little bent.
I think Sarah's right.
You should let her be herself.
It's important that she feels
as comfortable as possible right?
The thing is that
we don't look like a couple.
I look like a decent citizen and she
looks like a lesbian street hustler.
well that's the woman
you married.
I know, but can't she be
just a little more cooperative?
It's just for a couple of hours.
well you are the actor.
You've got to be more like her.
I mean fuck respectability,
the important thing is you
come across as a couple right?
Hi guys!
I'm gonna take a nap.
Can you please let Gina in when she
comes over? We're going out later.
How's the job search going?
I got a few leads.
Nice guys.
But how long is she staying?
I don't know, she's in
a lot of trouble right now.
Sarah how and when
did you and Marcel meet?
we met at Thanksgiving.
Two years ago.
I know she's your sister, but she's
not even looking for a place.
Marcel... Smile.
Tell me about Sarah's family.
well I've only met
your brother James.
Sarah, what's Marcel's
mother's name?
Fuck off!
I just wanna play pool
and get drunk.
Sarah the interview
is in two days.
what's Marcel's mother's name?
I can't think about this all
the time. It's driving me crazy!
I'm not gonna be able to do it!
what's Marcel's mother's name?
Marie.
wrong!
The correct answer is Catherine.
Now smile.
Hey! Hey!
Stole a kiss.
Yeah, I got a bigger size.
You know I'm a big girl.
I have to keep massaging them
though. They're really hard!
She has to save
some money up first.
For deposit and all that.
No fucking way!
Are you kidding me?
So why isn't she working?
well it's tough to go back to a
regular job after making so much money
Do you even realize
how crazy this logic is?
She's not comfortable
prostituting anymore...
Shhh...
That's great.
I'm happy she stopped.
But then she gets
kicked out of her apartment...
Because she gets a boob job
instead of paying her rent.
And then she just
moves in with us.
It's temporary.
She's been lying around here
for almost two months,
and she hasn't even
looked for a place.
Because she doesn't
have any money.
wanna get a job.
Because it's too hard for her
to work an entire day...
and barely make what
she used to in half an hour!
Do you want to push my sister
back into working the streets?
I want her to move out.
You're such an asshole.
Kyle what about us?
I couldn't help but
overhear this conversation.
Marcel is just a bit
stressed right now
because of his
interview tomorrow.
well he should know that
I'm here as your guest.
You've overstayed your welcome.
Kyle, tell him I can stay.
Kyle and I
make these decisions together.
You're the one pushing him around,
making decisions for the both of you.
Look, both Kyle and I are working
our asses off waiting tables.
I know that you're used
to having him cover over your ass...
but I will certainly not
be taken advantage of any longer.
Kyle!
How can you allow this?
Marcel...
This slobbering around...
Occupying the entire
living room with your shit!
using our phone, eating our food,
leaving your dirty dishes...
Don't talk to her like that!
Fine.
I'm out of here.
But when I come back, I want to know
the date she's moving out,
and it better be within a week!
She doesn't have
anywhere else to go.
I can't stand this
living situation any longer.
How can you be so selfish?
If I'm selfish it's for us.
She's my sister...
That's what scares me so...
That blood is thicker
than water.
that you will
choose her over me.
I don't wanna choose.
why should I have to choose?
I want both my boyfriend
and my sister in my life.
I deserve to have both.
# Flying high like a dove #
# You and me in the night heat #
# All the angels above #
# what's the color of love. #
Shh! we can't be this loud.
It's really late.
we have to practice
for the concert.
And rehearsal with Tommy
is tomorrow.
I know. I can't believe
he got us a gig already.
we have to work really hard.
As long as Marcel will allow it.
Don't say things like that.
If you kick him out,
you and I can stay here together.
April!
what?
I know he'd prefer if I
was out of your life completely.
April, please.
what?
Can't you just try
and make friends with him?
He's the one going postal on me!
And he's so possessive of you.
You do know that?
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry too.
You know when I hear
your keys in the door
my whole heart
just bursts with love.
My baby's home!
It's the two most amazing
seconds of my day.
Baby, I love you!
Do you realize that this
was our first fight ever?
That is just crazy.
I know.
Let's never fight again.
Deal.
I guess I'm under
a lot of stress.
I'm sorry for being
so mean to April.
It's okay, I know she drives
a lot of people crazy,
but she's leaving soon.
Promise?
Promise.
So baby, are you
ready for tomorrow?
I think so.
I just hope Sarah will be OK.
She's so nervous.
It will go wonderful.
You just have to wait.
Have a seat.
Sorry, it's going to take longer.
The process is always like this...
They might be watching us.
Try to look like you're in love.
I'm trying!
Do you see any?
Any what?
Cameras?
No they must have
hidden them very well.
I can't believe they
have us wait this long...
we had a ten o'clock appointment.
It's already one!
I know.
I hate immigration.
Immigration is fucked up.
Shhh!
Marcel Colard!
Okay honey it's us.
Let's do it.
I love you.
I love you too, sugar muffin.
Repeat after me.
I swear to tell the truth,
the whole truth,
and nothing but the truth.
So help me God.
I swear to tell the truth,
the whole truth,
and nothing but the truth.
So help me God.
Sit down.
when's your husbands birthday?
June 22.
when's your wife's birthday?
July 5.
we're both cancers!
where does your husband work?
He works at the
Madison Square Cafe.
Cafe Blanc is the name
of the corporation,
but the restaurant is called
Madison Square Cafe.
How much is your husband making?
Oh, he takes home
about five hundred a week.
Really?
I know it says in that letter
from my boss
that I make
seven hundred a week...
but I work
in an outdoor restaurant,
and with the weather
we've been having so far,
five hundred is really all
that I've been making.
where does your wife work?
Marvin's records.
why does it say here
that your single in this paper?
I know that I filled out the paperwork
saying that I was married but...
maybe because I asked them to
take out the higher single rate,
they fucked it up.
Screwed it up.
what was your
taxable income last year?
About 25 thousand?
Really?
No! Honey, it was much higher
than that, maybe 35?
I did the taxes
and I can't even remember.
Sarah has no clue
about our finances.
So what other proof do
you two have that you're together?
well we have our joint apartment lease.
Joint bank account.
we have some pictures.
who's that?
Oh that's our friend Danny.
He's responsible for us getting
together in the first place.
who's that?
That is Sarah's friend Megan,
and that is my mother.
what's your husband's
mother's name?
Catherine.
why didn't your parents
make it to the wedding?
well they couldn't get away.
They have a farm.
But we're going to go home to
Arizona for Christmas this year.
And Sarah is going to teach
me horseback riding.
So you'd say that your parents
approve of the marriage?
Oh yes, of course! My mother,
she wants for me what I want.
She's really cool.
well I guess you wont mind
my calling her then, will ya?
No, of course not.
well write down the number.
Hello!
Its an answering machine.
Do you have another number?
No, I don't.
well... do you have any other
proof that you're together?
I don't know.
Bills maybe?
well I asked the phone company
to put both our names on bill
but they wouldn't.
well, what about
more bank accounts?
Look, we have one
bank account, okay?
That's all that we need.
we've only been married
for a little while
and we don't
have everything joint yet!
These things happen gradually.
Here.
Yeah, I think you
should have that checked out.
well I already made
an appointment with...
we passed!
we passed! we passed!
# What's the color of love #
# What's the case
of my heartbeat #
# Call the angels above #
# What's the color of love #
# Flying high like a dove #
# You and me in the night heat #
# All the angels above #
# What's the color of love #
Hi everybody.
we're The Inertia Kiss.
It's great to see so many
of you out here tonight.
This is our first live gig ever.
I'm Kyle.
Over here is April.
Hi!
And this is Tommy.
And now we're going to do
a song that's very special to me.
I wrote it to my baby.
For our two year anniversary.
# We had a chance
in a million to one #
# Driving the corvette
down the road on the run #
# Oh, running in the night.
Oh, running in the night #
# Me and my boyfriend #
# Why should we care
for the powers that be? #
# Always gonna do
anything to be free. #
# Oh, running in the night.
Oh, running in the night #
# me and my boyfriend. #
# I could never be lonely #
# I'm together with you #
# Gonna run away.
Where he goes I will stay #
# 'Cause he's my boyfriend.
Boyfriend #
# Day by day
love is coming my way #
# 'Cause he's my boyfriend.
Boyfriend #
# He's my boyfriend #
# Maybe it's fair to say
I live like a fool #
# What else could I do
when ever love makes the rules #
# Oh, running in the night.
Oh, running in the night #
# Me and my boyfriend #
# Why should we plan
what tomorrow will bring #
# Why believing that it
could change anything #
# Oh, running in the night.
Oh, running in the night #
# Me and my boyfriend #
# I could never be lonely #
# I'm together with you. #
# Gonna run away.
Where he goes I will stay #
# 'Cause he's my boyfriend.
Boyfriend #
# Day by day
love is coming my way #
# 'Cause he's my boyfriend.
Boyfriend #
I really think you should let go
of your anger on that line
and start breaking down there.
That would be a stronger choice
and you would show your range.
Oh my God! Did you see that?
what was he wearing?
Hey baby! Hey Jenny!
How are you?
Hi!
Honey what are you doing home?
we have to write some
cover letters to music agents.
But I'm rehearsing
for my audition.
You weren't supposed to be back
until after four.
we'll be in the bedroom.
we won't disturb you.
Please we need privacy.
we talked about this.
No we didn't. You told me
not to come home until four.
I never agreed to it.
You can't tell me what to do.
I live here too.
Baby, I'll make it up to you.
Leave now and come back at four.
You can't tell him what to do.
He pays rent too.
Yeah.
well you don't,
so stay out of this.
I moved out didn't I?
Finally.
Marcel, we're not leaving.
Come on. You know
how important this is to me!
April has an appointment later!
And we have to get
these letters done today.
Yeah.
This is ridiculous.
Stay out of it!
No you stay out of here.
And we'll stay out of there!
# Gonna run away.
Where he goes I will stay #
# 'Cause he's my boyfriend.
Boyfriend #
# Day by day... #
why do you put up
with that shit?
He's not always like that.
# He's my boyfriend #
There's a lot of
scar tissue build up.
Your body is definitely
rejecting them.
I'm afraid you need
to have them removed.
Goodbye April.
I decided to go back
to being a boy.
Really?
If I can't have breasts,
what kind of woman am I gonna be?
Besides, I wasn't ever sure if
I wanted to go through with it.
Gina still regrets
having cut it off.
Have you really
thought it through?
This isn't the first time
you've tried this.
Are you sure you can
be happy as a boy?
I have to.
I'm gonna get on
male hormones instead.
And the doctor says
I can get fake testicles.
wow. I'm so used
to you being April now.
It'll be for good this time.
I'm gonna have my breasts
removed in a couple of weeks.
And I'll be Cole again.
Hey. I'll always love you.
No matter what you do.
I know.
what the fuck?
what is she doing in our bed?
Sleeping. It got late.
Come to bed.
I've been shooting
since seven this morning.
I can't deal
with this right now.
I want her out of our bed.
That's fine.
I can sleep on the sofa.
I thought you moved out.
Here's twenty dollars for a cab.
Don't insult me!
I don't need your money.
April is staying.
Does she have to be
in our fucking bed too?
I mean come on!
You're a selfish
fucking asshole!
Kyle, I don't know what you're doing
with him and I'll never understand it.
I"m sorry that I find it
disturbing to have prostitutes
between my clean sheets.
How dare you?
Don't say shit like that
to my sister!
You have no idea
what she's been going through!
I didn't say it to her.
It was a general statement.
Besides you know
she's doing it again.
why do you destroy things
between us like this?
why do you let her destroy
things between us like this?
Goodnight Kyle.
I'll see you tomorrow.
April!
I hate you.
I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
I'm sorry, too.
I love you.
I love you, too.
# I've been to Greece
I've been to Paris #
# I've seen Brazil and Mexico #
# I've sensed a blooming tree
of cherries #
# And watched ten thousand
flowers grow #
# Every day my world
is full of colors. #
# Colors. #
# Red or green or blue
til I met you #
# What's the color of love #
# What's the case
with my heartbeat #
# Call the angels above #
# What's the color of love #
# Flying high like a dove #
# You and me
and the night heat #
# All the angels above #
# What's the color of love #
# Red #
# Orange #
# Yellow #
# Green #
# Blue #
# Purple #
# uh oh. Uh oh.
Uh oh. Uh oh. #
# What's the color?
What's the color #
# What's the color of love #
# What's the case
of my heartbeat #
# Call the angels above #
# What's the color of love #
I just wished we hadn't
messed up that last song.
I know!
Kyle came in really late there.
Congratulations guys
the show is wonderful!
I took some great pictures.
Thank you.
You looked great tonightApril.
I guess I'll wait for you
at the bar with the others.
Great show!
Thanks.
As I was saying you
came in really late there.
But it's okay,
I covered for you!
Please come home.
I can't we're on a flow.
It sounds like you're
having a party.
we're just taking
a little break.
You've been writing
for two days straight.
Isn't it cool?
Baby I miss you.
I thought we could spend
some time together.
Just you and me
like normal couples do.
well we're working.
Besides you're busy with your play
and the short film...
and if you get that part
you'll be in L.A. for months.
The more reason for us
to spend time together.
It's not a competition you know.
It's two a. m.
Baby, please come home
to sleep tonight.
You can go back
to work in the morning.
I gotta go!
Look I'll talk to you
tomorrow after work.
Je t'aime pour toujours.
God, isn't his boytriend
so annoying.
Yeah, that's why
I don't do relationships.
Yeah, that and the fact
that no one wants you.
Bitch.
Thanks guys.
I'll talk to you soon. Bye.
Good night Ben!
You just hate all my friends.
I don't hate Ben,
I just don't see why you would
invite him along to the movies.
This was our first night off
together in two weeks.
Ben is my friend.
And he was lonely tonight.
But you don't want me
to have any friends.
why aren't we important to you?
what do you mean?
we. You and me.
why aren't we more important to you?
Is it so strange to want to spend
some time alone with your boytriend?
I find it very strange
that you don't seem to care.
Of course I care.
It doesn't seem like it.
I care!
You spend three times as much time
with April as you do with me.
we're working together.
Besides we have to get our demo
ready for that manager.
why do you bring April up anyway?
Everything is not her fault you know.
I'm not so sure.
what's that supposed to mean?
I don't know.
You seem so different now.
The more time you spend
with her the less...
I don't wanna hear any shit
about my sister!
I got the part.
You got the part?
I'm flying to LAThursday.
we start rehearsals Monday.
So soon!
wow that's amazing!
Congratulations, baby.
So how long will you be gone?
A month.
So April could stay here
while you're gone right?
It's going to be really tough for her
now that she's changing sex again.
It's just temporarily of course,
she wouldn't dream of sticking around
while you're back.
Do you promise me that she
will be gone before I come home?
Of course!
Oh thank you baby.
Let me call her
and tell her the good news.
You know, it will be
really hard to go.
why?
It'll be fun won't it?
It's hard because you seem
so indifferent about it.
No, baby, of course not.
And I miss you already.
But listen. I'll just focus
on my work while your gone...
And when you get back,
I'll have several new songs
to play you.
So Kyle told me
you're gonna be a man again.
Yep.
Implants come out tomorrow.
So you're not really
a woman then?
what?
On the inside.
It's not that simple.
well its too bad.
what?
I never got a chance
to play with them.
You wanna touch them?
Go ahead.
They're kinda hard
trom the scar tissue though.
well they look good.
I know.
I'm gonna miss them.
Yeah you're right.
They feel fake.
Oh, it's okay.
I'm sure you'll make
a good looking man too.
Of course.
Not that you'll care.
No I'm already married to one.
Right.
That one.
You know Marcel didn't seem
too happy before he left for LA.
I think something's
going on with Kyle.
well you know that's life.
Nothing lasts forever.
Are you serious?
They might break up?
I always thought they'd
be the ones to prove
that gay relationships
can last forever.
well, I for one never thought
they were right for each other.
Your tum.
They don't know when
the shooting will start now.
Apparently they lost
some of the financing,
it might be another week.
Listen, honey,
I'm not happy here.
I miss you terribly.
Do you?
Are you sure?
Of course I'm sure.
where's April?
Look I gotta go.
Sarah just arrived.
I love you too.
Bye.
Cole is in the bedroom sleeping.
They gave him a lot of drugs.
Really?
Is he gonna use them all?
Her chest is all fucked up.
They say they can restore it though.
His chest.
I don't get it.
I thought all trannys were
supposed to be certain
they were bom the wrong sex
in order to go through with all of that.
well some probably are
but Cole never was.
This isn't the first time
he's gone back to being a boy.
Really?
Anyway, he needs
a lot of support right now.
Luckily Marcel isn't home.
You know...
I'm feeling really sad.
why?
Because you miss him?
No.
Because I don't miss him.
I so hope it works out
with you two.
He can be so egocentric.
It's all about him.
Actors!
I know.
You look great.
I'm not ready for a photo shoot.
we really need those new
promo shots of you.
And it's time you start
leaving the house.
Are you sure I look okay?
Of course!
Just stop tweezing those eyebrows.
Yeah, you should be talking!
Cole, can I ask you something?
If it's about you know who,
you know what I think.
It was so good.
It was supposed to last forever.
You know Kyle,
it's better to have
loved and lost...
than to spend the rest of your life
with a controlling, self serving SOB.
# When you weren't around
I was okay #
# I used to have time
formyfriends all day #
# When you weren't around
I was alright #
# I need sometime
alone tonight #
# So what will you do
if I leave you here alone #
# How will you feel
if I won't be coming home #
# Cause I got myself to save
so I might be gone #
# if you call on me tonight #
# Between love and goodbye #
# I won't be living
in the middle this time #
# Between love and goodbye #
# I got a heart of gold
you'll never find #
I called and I called,
where were you last night?
I was around.
Your cell was off.
And I called you at home three times.
Why didn't you call me back?
Where wereyou last night?
I was home.
So didn't you hear me
on the answering machine?
No, I did.
But you didn't pick up?
I didn't feel like talking
to anyone last night.
Kyle?
Yes.
You screen me out?
Me, your boyfriend,
you didn't pick up when I called?
Marcel...
No you told me many many times
no matter what
you would always love me.
I just need a little time.
No.
Just a little time...
No way.
No!
To figure things out!
what things?
what?
You wanna take a break
is that what you're saying?
I don't really know what I want.
Just... Please don't make
this harder than it has to be.
I'm already miserable as it is
being away trom home...
But you see this as
a great opportunity to break up.
I'm not breaking up.
I just need some time alone, okay?
Let's just not talk for a while.
Let's just figure this out.
You can't pretend
you didn't see this coming.
I'm not pretending.
# The thought of
losing you tonight #
# Makes me wanna
stay and fight #
# But I can't touch
what you believe #
# Should I leave #
# Between love and goodbye #
# I won't be living
in the middle this time #
# Between love and goodbye #
# I got a heart of gold
you'll never find. #
# Between love and goodbye #
what the...?
I think Cole and I are going
to go over to my place.
Right Cole?
Sure.
I tried not to call either
so that you would miss me.
But you didn't,
so I had to come home.
They cut my best scenes anyway.
My agent wasn't very happy
about it though
but I couldn't
stay away any longer.
So you're saying you want me
to give our relationship another chance?
No.
No?
No I want you, us,
to give it several new chances,
Unlimited tries.
what I want is for us
to never give up. Never.
But to keep adjusting,
and trying and fixing...
And loving.
Forever!
To never give up!
That's what I want.
Baby you're crying.
Kyle, what's wrong?
Please tell me.
whatever it is
we can fix it together.
Something happened.
what?
It's okay.
I forgive you.
No.
No, it's not okay.
How can you just
forgive me like that?
I was away.
You felt lonely and horny.
These things happen sometimes.
Have these things
happened to you?
No.
Marcel this is really important.
The fact that you don't seem
to care that I did,
tells me that you
probably did too.
Once.
You did?
Oh God I promised myself
I'd never tell you this...
but, last spring,
while you were away in Ohio...
I met this guy at the Phoenix.
Yeah?
Nothing really happened.
There was just this...
strong attraction,
and then we kind of
left together.
I mean, we were both
going in the same direction.
Did you have sex with him?
No, definitely not.
I don't know why,
I went upstairs with him.
It was just so exciting.
And I only stayed
for a little bit.
But you didn't sleep with him?
No.
Of course not.
He just...
sucked me off a little.
Did you suck him off a little?
I guess...
a little.
How could you?
I don't know.
I didn't mean to.
And it meant nothing.
And I felt so guilty
about it ever since.
we were so happy together then.
I know.
It had nothing to do with you.
And it didn't mean
I loved you any less.
It just kind of happened.
Has it happened again?
No.
Definitely not.
Please, it meant nothing.
It meant everything.
Lea will be here any minute,
so you have to go
as soon as she comes okay?
How do I look?
You could fix
your hair a little.
whatever. It's not like
it's a date anyway.
I met her at a poetry reading.
She's just coming over
for some mac and cheese.
Look, Marcel, just stay out
of his face for a while okay?
whatever you do,
don't try to contront him
or make him change his mind.
You know you can be
a little bit obsessive.
Not attractive.
Just give him some space.
And some time.
You know you shouldn't
have come home like that.
And you shouldn't have
told him about the cheating.
Big mistake.
I know.
Oh.
Time to go.
I do hope it works out
between you.
You shouldn't have
told him about the cheating.
Hi.
Come on in.
# Although we know
it isn't right #
# It didn't stop us
from making a scene tonight. #
# I should've seen that you were
making your way outta here #
# It's not the first time,
but it's the last #
# I guarantee you'll be trying
to win me back #
# If you could get out
of that mirror #
# You're a born loser,
you're out of your mind #
and I was so blind #
# You're a born loser, loser #
# You're losing me
for good this time #
# You run around
telling all your friends #
# My little secrets,
I told you in confidence #
# And all the stories
are making a star out of me #
# You got the act
and drama down #
# You turn them all against me
in this town #
# Am I the only one who sees? #
# You're a born loser,
you're out of your mind #
and I was so blind #
# You're a born loser #
# You're losing me
for good this time #
# You 're gonna lose me #
# You're a born loser #
# You're born a loser #
# You're a born loser,
you're out of your mind #
and I was so blind #
# You're a born loser #
# You're losing me
for good this time #
You once told me that the most loving
couple of seconds of your day,
is when you hear my keys in the door
and you realize that I am home.
Your baby's home.
Do you remember that?
Now you're telling me you don't wanna
hear my keys in the door anymore?
That you don't want
me to come home?
Ever again?
I mean it's just...
I just don't get it!
It's so crazy. It's so ludicrous
that it's impossible to...
You're telling me that...
I'm telling you that
I don't love you anymore.
No. Kyle how can you
not love me anymore?
You used to love me
so much that...
Right Marcel.
Used to.
Get it?
Try to understand,
I don't love you anymore.
we stopped having fun together
and it's time to move on.
You asked me to marry you!
You can't decide it's over
because we're not having fun.
I mean come on!
we can change that.
How?
well, we can go to therapy to...
To find out...
That's ridiculous.
That's so fucking stupid!
Listen, there are so many,
many things that we can do...
spend more time
together, for one,
go away together, perhaps?
The important thing is that
we can fix this together!
For the longest time I gave away all
my power to you, and you took it.
I'm not about
to redo that mistake.
Are those your word or April's?
His name is Cole.
And no I can speak for myself.
Marcel it's time to face the facts.
It's over.
No it's not. Stop saying that.
we can fight this!
I don't know which part of this
you don't understand.
I don't want to.
And that is that.
I'm an artist.
And I have to follow my heart.
And my heart tells me,
it's over.
well, my heart
tells me that it's not.
I don't know why
you're acting so surprised.
Honey -
Life sucks.
You win some,
you lose some.
I always used to debate...
Am I in love?
This feels like love, right?
Is this real love?
I've only known you for a week.
Not even a week.
But now I know
what real love feels like.
I told you.
As soon as our eyes met,
I just knew.
Hey how do you
say that in French?
Say what?
I love you.
Je t'aime.
J'taime.
Forever?
Pour toujours.
Je t'taime, Marcel.
I wrote him a love letter,
like you told me, saying goodbye.
And I didn't give it to him.
I hid it in one of his books.
Maybe one day he will find it,
and realize how much he misses me.
You know, Jenny,
sometimes I think
it would've been better
if he had died
when he still loved me.
Then it would've been forever
like he promised.
Marcel, it's really important
to turn inwards in times of crisis.
All the answers are inside.
You're gonna feel
so much better after this.
It's all in the breathing!
So when are you moving out?
well I thought I'd just keep staying
with Cole in the living room for now,
and you can keep the bedroom.
That's not going to happen.
If you're breaking up with me,
then you're out of here.
And your brother too.
I can't live like this.
well, I'm sorry, but you really
don't have a choice.
So you're going to bring home
your boytriends, and I mine?
If you have a problem with that,
why don't you move out?
First you break up with me,
then you tell me
to move out of my own apartment.
It's mine as much as its yours.
whose name is not on the lease?
Technically it's all mine.
That was just so you and Sarah
could both be on the lease.
we moved in here together.
I found this place.
You made one phone call
to your landlord.
I worked hard to get it.
You didn't do shit.
The point is;
you're breaking up with me.
I will get the money together
by the first to buy you out
of your share of the furniture.
Maybe you can move in with Ben
until you find a place.
And what about Cole?
Oh, now I'm responsible
for your brother too?
Your white trash family sure knows how
to take advantage of people.
why don't you just pack your little bags
and go back to France, huh?
You're single.
I don't see what's
keeping you in New York.
You're not wanted here anymore.
You wanna buy me out?
Most of this stuff here is mine.
Oh that's right,
you don't have any money...
and I don't belive your brother
had an income
since he stopped prostituting.
Again.
You just want me to give you
everything, is that it?
You're an asshole.
And I'm not moving out.
No. You're the asshole
and I'm talking to you.
Can you believe
he threatened Kyle with a knife?
I mean the guy is losing it.
How do you feel, Kyle?
Are you sure
this is it for you two?
I mean, I thought you were just taking
some time to figure things out.
You two had a good thing going.
They did not have
a good thing going.
whatever they had it wasn't love
because love is about
respecting each other.
If Marcel ever loved Kyle,
he wouldn't treat his triends
and his family so poorly.
He's a user.
He used you
and he used Kyle.
Maybe Marcel and I
used each other.
How did he use you, Kyle?
Look, Marcel's
not a good person.
Kyle has no interest in getting
back together with him.
Or even talking with him.
If Marcel has anything to say to Kyle,
it needs to go through you.
we're done with him!
So how about you two
move into Danny's room
and Danny moves in with Marcel?
what?
I told you,
you have to move out soon.
You're getting on my nerves.
It's out of the question.
we're not giving up
that apartment.
It's Kyle's apartment
just as much as yours.
I won't help you take him to court.
I just won't!
So let's solve this.
I can't live with Danny.
Come on we all agreed to this!
He's such a slob!
Marcel!
It was your idea.
I changed my mind.
You know it wasn't easy
convincing Kyle.
He feels like it's
letting you win.
I'm not happy about the terms.
Besides if we do this,
I need to discuss it with Kyle.
He won't speak to you.
Then there is no deal.
Oh hi Kyle.
I made dinner for us.
I thought we should sit down
for a meal, and talk things out.
I think we owe it to ourselves.
Kyle?
Please?
I'm not hungry.
Kyle, we need to talk.
If we're going to do this apartment
switch, we need to discuss the details.
Sarah told me you said no to it.
If you changed your mind,
it can go through her.
No it can't.
I need to talk to you.
Look, this is
really hard for me.
I think it would be easier if we
were able to part as friends.
Just go.
I really don't think we have anything else
to say to each other.
Ever.
Je t'aime pour toujours.
Yeah, yeah, yeah...
I know you seem to think so.
I did come across
your little note, by the way.
Dear Kyle...
I am crying as
I sit here writing this.
How could this happen
between us?
Your beautiful eyes that used
to be filled with so much love,
are now completely cold.
And then it goes on to say...
well you should know...
You wrote it.
It's more of the same
pathetic, needy shit really.
No wonder your mother
put her head into that oven.
I used to think that was
a strange thing for a mother to do.
Abandon a four and
a six-year old like that.
But hey! It's all really
quite clear to me now.
In fact your mother was probably the only
sane person in your family.
Get the fuck out of my room.
Now.
Stop obsessing about him.
I'm not obsessing,
I just don't understand...
It doesn't matter Marcel.
You have to move on.
But he...
I think he's made it very clear that he's
not interested right now.
You have to let it go.
I can't!
You have to!
Come on.
He's never gonna come around if you
make yourself so available and needy.
Date...
Fuck around...
like all the other gay boys do.
You have to move on Marcel.
Oh hi!
Rob this is my roommate, Kyle.
Kyle, this is Rob.
Rob, sit down
while I make us a drink.
Ciao.
How you doing?
Oh, don't worry about him.
He's just a little upset,
because his name is not on the lease,
and if he doesn't move out,
I will have his things thrown out
on the street and change the locks.
Sorry.
Don't be.
If he does,
I'll have him arrested.
You see, according to
New York State law...
you can't kick a person out of a place,
who's lived there over a month.
So both me, and my
brother Cole, are staying.
I can't believe I didn't dump
this guy a long time ago though.
But, you know what?
Rob... is it?
Now that I did, I can't
tell you how right it feels.
You see, Marcel is really
a selfish, pathetic creep.
would you like
some tresh lemon, Rob?
You see the problem with Kyle...
is that he will never
be happy with anyone,
as long as lets his
fucking brother run his life.
If there was ever a selfish person
in our relationship,
It was Cole.
Cole was right about you
the whole time.
You're just a mean,
petty son-of-a-bitch.
I guess this is what happens
when you invite homeless, unemployed,
ex-transsexual prostitutes
into your home.
They turn your loved ones
against you.
I was wrong.
I never loved you.
If you don't leave,
I will take you both
to housing court.
You can't! Sarah says I have
equal rights to this place.
Sarah is his wife!
who's also on the lease.
And she says we can stay.
Your wife?
whatever.
Drinks are ready.
Let's go.
Goodnight, Kyle!
Oh my God...
I love you lips...
You got such a gorgeous body...
You have to leave now.
what?
we're finished.
I want you to go.
what's wrong?
we just got going...
I can tell you liked it.
Just leave.
You treak!
who do you think you are,
treating me like this?
There were plenty of guys
I could've gone home with.
Good. Go find yourself
someone else to fuck.
what kind of game
are you playing anyway?
Your right it was just a game.
All pretend.
You can't satisfy me one bit.
Cocksucker!
You wish.
You have to get back at him.
I really don't feel
like having sex with anybody.
Especially not with you
in the same room.
So why don't you make
that one little phone call?
It'll all be over.
You tell him I'm this close
to having him deported.
Kyle! You are a sweet,
wonderful person,
How can you
even think of doing that?
He'd only have himself to blame.
Kyle!
what?
He cheated on me,
and he didn't tell me
about it for a year.
Is that what this is about?
Among other things.
You've seen the way
he's been acting up lately,
and I'm not gonna let him
get that apartment for nothing.
Come on!
Everything isn't
black and white, you know.
There are ways to solve this.
I know.
One phone call.
You're stupid to believe that
he would do that Sarah!
Nobody would ever do that.
Even if he would do it to me,
he couldn't possibly do it to you.
Please, Kyle,
we can still solve this.
I'll kick Danny out.
You and Cole can have this apartment.
I'll move in with Marcel.
Kick me out?
You can't kick me out.
My name's on the lease!
Only because my name
had to be on Marcel's lease.
You know very well
this is my apartment!
But, where am I gonna go?
You're not going anywhere.
It's too late Sarah.
Marcel's not gonna get away
with his little games.
Not this time.
Please! Kyle for my sake.
I can get jail time for this!
Nothing will happen to you,
if you cooperate.
You don't know that!
They may say that now,
but I already lied
to immigration under oath.
That's a federal offense!
Listen we're gonna do this with
or without you.
You're so stupid Sarah.
Please.
For my sake, don't call!
I'll try to keep you out of it.
You can't keep me out of it,
I'm married to him!
This is so fucked up!
He's been asking for this.
Are you gonna cooperate?
No, Kyle!
You're fucked up!
I got the number at my place.
Let's go.
Kyle!
Kyle. No, Kyle, please.
Please, Kyle, just wait...
Sure I can hold.
Kyle.
Kyle, please don't.
Yes.
My name is Kyle Thomas.
I'd like to report
a case of immigration traud.
His name is Marcel Collard.
How could you?
And you, Sarah, how could you?
Don't you dare blame me.
You guys are all fucked up!
Come on Sarah,
you know the freak deserved it.
How could you do
something so cruel?
You underestimated me.
I thought more of you than that.
You cheated on me!
And you on me!
well, it's done.
Call them back.
Tell them it was a mistake.
Just get the fuck out
of my room.
No.
This, in fact,
is my living room.
Get the fuck out of my room.
Don't you touch me again
or I'll kill you.
Get the fuck out of here now!
You better watch it.
Fuck!
I'm gonna fucking kill you!
what the fuck?
How dare you
threaten my brother?
I'm gonna call the cops
and have you arrested!
Bleeding a little are we?
Je t'aime Marcel.
Pour toujours.
# I wonderwhy the hell
I stayin this town #
# Ain't much to do
when the sun goes down #
# But think about what I'll do
when I'm with you. #
# Still don't know
why you went away #
# When black and white
turns into grey #
# Life is cold but I was warm
when I kissed you. #
Mr. Kyle Thomas
has already been here.
Filed charges against you.
For harassment and assault.
So what?
Is it his word against mine?
No, not exactly.
He didn't show up with five stitches
and a report from the E.R.
we'll have him
arrested for this.
Oh.
# Eternity burned out that day #
# And I don't know how
I'm gonna spend my life without you. #
# And the church bells
are ringing all across the world #
# And prophesies
go unfulfilled #
# Cause they always told me
I would spend my life with you #
# I won't say adieu #
I don't know about this Cole,
Do you think I even
have a case against him?
Of course.
That's why they want you
to come back and testify again.
The way he behaved
was totally unacceptable.
Threatening you with a knife!
Threatening to kill you!
The cops saw the bruises you had.
He's gonna have to pay.
Mr. Thomas, stand up.
And please turn around.
You're under arrest
for assault and battery.
You have the right
to remain silent.
Anything you say can and will
be held against you in a court of law.
You have the right
to an attomey.
If you can't afford one,
we'll provide one for you.
No, you can't do this.
You understand your rights?
- Yes.
It's the other way around.
# When I'm with you
my heart pounds like rain #
I'm immune to pain #
# When I'm with you
I feel no restraint #
# When I'm with you #
# And I don't know how
I'm gonna live this way #
# Eternity burned out that day #
# And I don't know how
I'm gonna spend my life without you #
I just got out.
I'm not allowed to go
back to the apartment.
Luckily Ben was home.
It looks like Marcel won
this little battle after all.
# And they always told me
I would spend my life with you #
# I won't say adieu #
You may have gotten rid of Kyle,
but your not getting rid of me.
And I'm your new roommate until
immigration picks you up
and puts you on
that plane to France.
It wont be long now.
You put domestic violence
on your charges against Kyle
You stupid fuck!
This whole thing is messed up.
My advice to you,
just hang tight.
Immigration is
completely backed up.
They weren't able to give them
the case number. Right?
Chances are they'll never be able
to put this thing together.
# Eternity burned out that day #
# And I don't know... #
He says if I move out,
he'll pay you for your share
of the furniture and the security deposit.
I told him to keep dreaming.
Ben says we can
stay here for a while.
He could use
the extra rent money.
No way.
we can't let Marcel win.
when immigration picks him up
the apartment will be ours.
I just have to stick it out
a little while longer.
Let's not.
You're gonna let the asshole
get away with this?
I can't fucking believe this!
Look you got what you wanted,
Marcel and I will never
get back together now.
You won.
The D.A. has agreed to
let him off with a waming
if he agrees to assault charges.
And if he stays out of trouble,
he wont get a record.
Okay.
Sounds good.
Here's the paperwork
where Kyle signs off
on the apartment
and everything in it.
Great. Here's the
money order for the fumiture.
we're all set then.
would you please tell Kyle
that I would like to speak with him?
For some closure?
Not in this lifetime.
well, congratulations
on the apartment.
Congratulations on Kyle.
You did good.
Please,
You did it yourself.
So when I broke up with Julie,
she got so vengeful,
She called my job
and told them I was stealing.
And I got fired.
But if that hadn't happened, I would've
never gotten the job at the cafe.
And I wouldn't have been there
when Sarah came in for the poetry reading.
what she's saying is that
you never really know
what's waiting for you in life.
That's the beauty of it!
It is pretty exciting.
My life is completely open
to anything now.
I mean, who knows
who I will spend my next Christmas with?
or who I'll meet
a year from now?
where I will live
ten years trom now?
Life is pretty dam exciting
if one looks at all the possibilities.
You know there will always
be sunshine after it rains.
For something new to start
something old has to end.
Anything is possible.
Anything can happen.
Then there is still hope.
Of course!
Then there will always
be hope...
# Yes I rememberlove, #
# Yes I remember love, #
# So beautiful #
# Now I know how hard
this breakup was #
# Cause I remember love #
# The true meaning of #
# I remember... #
# I remember... Love #
Marcel Colard?
Are you Marcel Colard?
Yes, that's me.
United States Citizenship
and Immigration service...
we're conducting an
investigation because we have
strong reason to believe
that you've lied to the US govemment.
what?
why? Because somebody called
and told you some crazy story?
No we've got more than that,
witnesses, photographs,
letters, love notes,
All indicating that you've
engaged in marriage fraud
in order to gain admittance
into the United States.
we need you
to come with us, sir.
what the fuck did you do?
It's better this way.
Should we move back in?
Okay the hearing is set
in three weeks,
So call my office next week,
set up an appointment,
so we can
go over strategy, okay?
# Cause I remember love
so beautiful #
# Now I know my heart
is breakable #
# Yes I remember love #
# The true meaning of #
# I remember... #
You need you
to come with us sir.
# Love... #
# Oh, I've been losing faith
each time I fall #
No.
Marcel!
# But I still believe
love conquers all #
NO!
No! No!
Kyle! No! No!
# Now I know my heart
is breakable #
# But I remember love #
# The true meaning of #
# I remember... #
# I remember love
the true meaning of #
# I remember... #
# Yes, I remember so beautiful #
# Now I know my heart
is breakable #
# When we see your face
as I hear your voice #
# I remember... #
# Love #
# When you weren't around
I was OK #
# I used to have time
for my friends all day #
# When you weren't around
I was alright #
# I need some time
alone tonight #
# So what will yo do
if I leave you here alone? #
# And how will you feel
if I won't be coming home? #
# Cause I got myself to save #
# So I might be gone
if you call on me tonight #
# Between love and goodbye #
# I won't be living
in the middle this time #
# Between love and goodbye #
# I got a heart of gold
you'll never find #
# When you weren't around
I was myself #
# I never had to think
of anyone else #
# When you weren't around
I always knew #
# Just where my life
was going to #
# So I can't create
what we haven't seen #
# But I can't escape
living in a dream #
# And my fear
is at it's height #
# So I might fall far
like the stars in heaven tonight #
# Between love and goodbye #
# I won't be living
in the middle this time #
# Between love and goodbye #
# I got a heart of gold
you'll never find #
# The thought of
losing you tonight #
# Makes me wanna
stay and fight #
# But I can't touch
what you believe #
# Should I leave? #
# Between love and goodbye #
# I won't be living
in the middle this time #
# Between love and goodbye #
# I got a heart of gold
you'll never find #
# Between love and goodbye #
# I got a heart of gold
you'll never find #
# Between love and goodbye #