WARNING: The film contains images of sex and
extreme violence. ONLY for adults.
Translated by Alexus
BDRip Ressync: amiable
Damn, damn, damn!
Ian, please ... Calm down!
Stay calm? The car're locked!
My dad will be pissed if I go without the car!
Relax, try again tomorrow
with the spare key.
Damn!
Do not think you will
break the car window!
Get out my face!
What the fuck you looking at?
Stop looking at my girlfriend, its tail!
-Ian, please!
You want to fuck it is?
Do not even think about it!
You know she's hot
too much for you as a dwarf.
Then go home
and beat a wank ...
No, please
No!
No, please!
Please do not!
No, please, please ... No!
Ian!
Hey, I have no time to lose ...
I have about 10 people
waiting to see this place.
And I just get money.
You have money?
-Lights
The lights are on here ... I think.
Hey, let's sign the damn contract
Or what?
Hello, my name is Mark of the Screen Actors Guild
... I am the actress of "The Human Centipede"
He said that is not available ...
... is in London
recording a movie.
Thank you for your interest
I hope to help in the future. Goodbye.
Stop crying
If Dad is not going to punish
Oh ... my God!
You shit again?
you pig
I called and Dr.Sebring
he is waiting for you! ...
Get up!
Hello Martin
Martin
Sit here with us.
Well ....
Martin here is your medicine
Martin, I came here because
his mother very concerned.
He did not talk to a centipede ...
made up of 12 people!
What does that mean?
Let's see ...
-The centipede can be considered
a phallic symbol ...
... animals are very aggressive
and their bites are very painful.
Perhaps it is connecting
the pain of the bite of a centipede ...
with years of psychological abuse
and sexually by her father.
I miss my husband.
And you are the reason
he's in jail!
Sometimes people get
problems because of these abuses
... mutilate their own genitals
Sorry, I gotta go.
There is nothing to worry about.
I'm sure it will pass.
Martin
Good boy.
I decided that we have to kill us
This song is me
crazy!
I no longer take any more!
He no longer supports the music!
Come on, tell them.
Be a man like your father!
I want to say something retarded?
I hear my music as I want!
Kill both of us!
I beg you!
Shut up and fuck, old!
What the hell? ...
I will listen to so high that
I'll leave you deaf, ok its tail? ...
If you bother me again
I go down and break your neck, damn it!
Dwarf fag, I'll listen to the cd
so high that I will break down the walls.
Cock sucker you moron!
The lips of B to C
and anus from A to B.
intersect in a circle
between the border between the skin and mucosa
Anus and mouth and from A to B
and from B to C
... Connecting the grafts
incisions of the jaw
Ingestion of A. .. goes to B
... EC performs the excretion
the human centipede
We'll dinner when we get there?
No!
Wow
What are all these numbers?
It was one of the most
stupid I did.
Valerie is the face of the club.
Is anyone there?
It has a dwarf masturbating.
You're drunk!
- No, I'm serious!
Hello, here is Ariadne
Creative Management
You wanted information of an actress
of Human Centipede for a hearing
... I just spoke with Ms. Yennie
and she is excited
... and eager to be part
the cast of the new Tarantino movie
Call me as soon as possible to
7134990913. Thank you. Goodbye
Damn!
It's just a movie!
The Human Centipede is a fucking movie!
He wants to sew us!
He wants to sew the mouth to the tail!
stop crying and swallow
everything that excites Dad
What is this?
100% of medical accuracy "?
The mouth to the anus?
A single digestive system
This is the movie perverted
you always say?
I want it out of my house!
Damn!
Swallow it, bitch ... Swallow
feed it! ... feed her
This was great!
You know what? ...
Her pussy is cheirosinha!
How's up, Doc?
Oh, I prefer the retarded boy
... but it gives to the expense.
I know a place specialized
these things.
Oh yes, she's good, right?
What do you charge to give the tail?
Dear ... $ 50.
Jesus! ... Who the hell are you?
What the fuck have you done?
I'm getting ... keep looking!
Stay there looking ... you pervert!
Go away!
Before I leave the car and
the thing for you to get ugly
No, please ... please.
Martin?
I am ... Dr. Sebring!
So ...
This is where you work?
This is not right, Martin.
What are you doing ... is wrong.
Martin ... I can help.
but you must give me the gun.
Imagine what his father would say
Martin! Martin no, no ...
Please ...
... I will not tell anyone.
Please!
No. .. I will not tell anyone.
Fuck it!
Son of a bitch!
Somebody help me!
Hello Martin. I am Ariadne.
I called to confirm that Mrs. Yenni
will arrive at London airport at 06 h
I hope that your driver is there
And I hope that everything goes right to the test
Thank you. Goodbye.
I can not believe that you will work
in a Quentin Tarantino.
My agents are very happy.
Would not it be better to call him
to say that I'm on my way?
Have you seen The Human Centipede?
I was interested in the film
the medical aspect of the matter.
If you were a surgeon, actually
could do that.
Very scary.
It was hard work ... I demanded, in the contract
one hour massage per night.
You know ... Why do not require?
Oh, and we all had to
take a shower before ...
... to stay near the butt of the other.
You will not smell anything, you know?
I'm allergic to germs.
Oh!
There seems to Tarantino's car
Do you have an umbrella?
This rain will ruin the hair.
okay.
Please!
Please! ...
... Please do not hurt me!
... I do what you want.
Hi, is the Mark of the Screen Actors Guild
again ...
... Please forget the previous message
Fortunately we got a date on the agenda
... and our customer is excited
to test for Mr. Tarantino.
I hope to confirm
that's all right.
Please call me as soon as possible
this phone number.
Thank you,
Hope to see you soon. Goodbye
Subtitles by Alexus.