Hello?
Hello!
What happened?
Nothing, a woman answered,
but she hung up.
There was a weird tone,
it sounded like a recording.
Give me more coins.
- That's all that's left.
- Give them to me.
Why spend what little we have
left on that telephone, Reina?
How are we supposed to let them
know we're here, huh?
Hello!
Hello, it's Reina.
It's Reina,
I'll call back later.
Why didn't you tell them
we were here?
You could've
given them this address.
I'll call them back later.
With what? We ran
out of coins.
I don't know,
someone will lend us a phone,
or we'll come up with an idea.
What idea?
You and your damn ideas!
Did you forget all this shit
was your idea?
Right, because
you never have any ideas.
Sure, just look where you
brought us.
Or was this rat hole
a part of your plan?
What were you expecting,
a suite at the Hilton?
No, but I thought we'd be
staying with your cousin.
New York is already too big
for you, Marlon.
You should've
stayed in Medellin eating shit.
Of course.
As if we're not screwed
and eating shit here too.
Yeah, but it's American shit,
so it's different.
What are we going to do?
Tell me, Reina,
what are we going to do?
Why don't you just kill
yourself, Marlon?
Don't you go out on the street,
Marlon Cruz!
Brooklyn, New York
Hey! Let go!
Did you find it?
Yeah, here it is.
What's the matter?
You went looking for dessert,
didn't you?
No, you saw me drop it.
Come, let's go take a walk.
I'll tell my father
we're going out.
Hey, didn't you promise
to teach me how to play pool?
No dessert?
Dad... I'm going out
for a bit.
It's very hot.
Be very careful, dear.
This neighborhood is full
of potheads now.
Yes, sir.
Nice! It's good.
You're learning.
Of course, with such an awesome
teacher, how could I not?
- Really?
- Yeah.
You like it? Yeah?
I spoke with Fabiola.
What's that tramp
telling you now?
She said she can get us in.
Come on.
You know that's all bullshit.
Aren't we supposed to go
to the embassy first?
You know,
fill out some forms,
go here, there,
do this and that?
Yes, but they are never going
to give us a visa.
Or at least not to me.
It doesn't hurt to try.
I'll ask you the same questions
Fabiola asked me.
Do you have a credit card?
Do you have a bank account?
- No.
- Do you have a steady job?
- What about property?
- A house? A car?
- No... I don't! I wish!
An uncle in the government,
secretary of any darn thing?
I wish I did!
See? You have nothing.
With nothing,
they won't give you a visa.
No, but I have you.
But having me
won't get you a visa.
But why New York?
Why so far away?
Because that's where it's at.
Look at the pictures my cousin
Gloria sent me.
She says we can
stay with her if we want to.
Come here...
Where were you hiding
those pictures?
Keep your hands to yourself
and sit down, would you?
Can you imagine me and you
living in a little apartment...
with a big tub we can get into
every night and make love?
Why don't we start now?
You know all this is yours...
but once we get there.
But why?
Let's go slowly.
No... let's come slowly.
I'd better get home.
But we were
just getting started.
That's just the point.
Hey, Giovanny, a thief!
Grab him, grab him!
Get him,
throw him out of here!
Get that rat out of here!
I don't allow thieves
in here; kick him out!
Wait, hold on!
Out!
Let go!
Come inside, Giovanny.
I'm not a thief!
There she is...
- Hi.
- What's up man.
Look.
Look how pretty
it is there when it snows.
Rather than that fucking mud pit
we get here every time it rains.
You should stop
looking at those pictures.
Oh, relax, just calm down.
I'm perfectly calm.
No, no, don't worry about them,
just give them to me; thank you.
Well, well.
I have the vouchers
and the passports
with visas for Guatemala
for those who paid.
The group is leaving
on the scheduled date
with those who've paid.
Those who haven't will have to
wait until we plan another trip.
But when
does this group leave?
No "buts," we're serious
people here,
and what
we say is what we do.
The tickets include the flights
from Medellin to Panama
and from Panama to Guatemala.
In Guatemala,
if anybody asks,
you just say you're there
for a week's vacation.
You shouldn't need
to make up anything else.
There, you will be greeted
by our representative
and once you get
settled at the resort,
he'll explain how you'll take
the fluvial route to Mexico.
From there,
a first-class surface transport
will take you to the border.
From there it's a hop,
skip, and a jump
and then you'll
start seeing signs saying:
"Welcome to the United States."
Excuse me, one question:
"fluvial, " what is that?
Fluvial! By river!
By river!
Ah, Okay...
And now, one little tip
for when you're there.
There, my dears,
anybody wearing a uniform
is an official of some sort,
and remember... the last
thing you people need
is any kind
of official for anything.
So, when you're there and you
see some guy in a uniform,
and he's coming towards you, you
walk in the opposite direction.
Do you understand?
Now, it's $3,000, per person,
"by next week."
If not,
"So sorry, babies, no fly."
All right, questions?
Damn it, Marlon,
we have to figure out a way
to get that money somehow.
- That's a lot of money, Reina.
- So?
We'll never come up
with that kind of money.
There's only three ways to raise
that kind of money:
working, gambling, or stealing.
Here you go, sweetheart,
Miguel Correa?
Right here!
Here you are... black, black
like you're wearing now, yes.
Cristina Beltran,
here you go.
Please, dad,
give me that job.
I know this city better
than you do.
I'm going
to tell you something.
Everything I've done
in my life has been
so that you can get a good
education and build a career.
Not so you can drive
a taxi.
But wasn't
that how you started?
And now you've got
four taxis.
Look how well you're doing.
That was different, son,
I started at the bottom.
But for you it's different,
thanks to what I've done.
Now it's time for you
to go to the University.
Mateo, sit up straight,
like I told you.
Don't you
want to go to college, Marlon?
You know, our contact there
is making some progress.
They told me
just the other day,
when the strike
is over, you can start.
That's just it, Mom.
In the meantime,
I'd like to earn a few pesos.
- Marlon, I said no!
- Why not?
How come Juancho's
family gave him work?
That's Juancho's family,
not this one!
Do you know
how many of my drivers
have been mugged
this week?
- Mom told you to say that!
- Nobody has told me anything.
Besides, I don't have
any free taxis,
they're all
working double shift..
I don't want to talk about this
again, understood?
Mateo, pick up your spoon
and eat properly.
You're hungry, aren't you?
You know you just can't enter
a place like a madman
and steal food
without permission.
Are you Colombian?
Colombian just like you.
Giovanny, go and see if you can
find something for a fever.
But ma'am, didn't you see
he was trying to steal food?
Go on, look at him,
what harm can he do to me?
He barely has enough strength
to lift up the spoon.
Where have you been
that you smell so bad?
- I got lost.
- Patricia!
Do you think we're in a position
to feed everyone in this city?
Pastor, stop nagging.
This boy is sick, and look
how cold it is out here.
help me
get him into the basement.
Help you? What nerve!
You fag! I told you I don't want
to see you anywhere around here.
All right, come with me, son.
Come on... come on,
finish it inside.
Patricia, this is the last
time I'll tell you!
This bum is not setting foot in
my restaurant! That's final!
Sit down here.
You know,
you got a pretty face, kid.
- Here you go, Patricia.
- Thank you.
- I'll bring some water.
- Yeah, okay.
And bring some blankets
so we can cover up this boy.
- Okay.
- Ma'am, is this "Queen"?
Yes, this is Jackson Heights,
Queens.
- Here you go.
- Thank you, son.
So Reina should be here,
nearby.
Reina...
On the front of Reina's hostel
it says "Queen."
"Queen" or "Queens?"'
Like Reina, but in English.
- I have to go.
- No, lay down, get some rest,
try to sleep.
Do you have any idea
how many hostels
there are in Queens?
Lock it.
- What?
- Lock the damn door, you idiot!
What are you doing?
You shouldn't
be going through that.
I wasn't going through anything.
I found it by accident.
Hey, nobody opens
a suitcase by accident.
Put it back!
Do you think I'm stupid?
Reina, don't you dare,
that money
belongs to the German.
Please, just put it back
in the suitcase.
Don't you like to play?
Reina, Reina, please...
just put back that money.
- Reina, give it back.
- Take it.
You're going to give me
the money, aren't you?
They caught us! Hurry!
All right!
- Who is in there? Let me in.
- Give me that money, please.
Reina, please...
We got locked in by accident.
Some kind of accident!
You're sweating, you devil!
I want to show the pictures
of the Cayman lslands...
to all those
jealous old bitches,
who used to give me shit about
being single at my age.
Move! You're in my way,
and stop shaking... move!
What's wrong with you?
You have no idea what it's like
to be coming up with excuses
for the last 35 years
to go to the gynecologist.
Waxings twice a week, with them
breathing down my neck.
Look at where he's
taking me for our honeymoon.
I guess he doesn't
wanna know.
He's a bum and he's here to live
off the hard work of others.
Well, I'm sorry but he's staying
for a few days.
I'm not going to allow that,
I'm going to call the cops.
Oh, you're going
to call the cops?
- What are you talking about?
- Come on!
Get him out of here, I don't
want that bum in my house!
Leave it alone, Pastor!
- I want him out of here!
- Careful with the phone!
Don't be such a grouch!
Just for the record,
I warned you!
Don't complain
to me about it later.
Freaking fag... I'm trying
to run a restaurant here.
Good morning, son,
did you get any sleep?
These will be kind of big
on you,
but this
is all I could find.
Now go get washed,
you're smelling really bad.
Ma'am?
I don't want
to bother you anymore,
but I have to ask you for
a huge favor.
What favor?
- I have to call home.
- Colombia?
Reina probably already called
to say where she is.
We'll have to see, Marlon.
You know those long distance
calls are very expensive.
Please, ma'am,
just that one favor.
Get yourself cleaned up first,
I'll see what I can do.
Hello.
Mom?
- Hello?
- Excuse me, Miss Patricia
- Get out!
- Hello, mom!
Marlon? It's Marlon!
My darling, where are you?
Are you okay?
I got to New York, I'm okay.
Marlon, you get back here
this instant! Where are?
Dad... It's good
to hear your voice.
How could you do this to us,
you are a crook!
You have no idea the pain
you've caused your mother
- and aunt Marlene!
- I'm so sorry, Dad...
and I hope aunt Marlene
will forgive me,
but it was
something I had to do.
What do you mean something
you had to do?
Is that what we taught you?
Get back here and face
what you've done!
Marlon, we've got that
German living in this house
until you get back and
give him the money.
Please come back, please
come back, I'm begging you!
Has Reina called you
there yet, Mom?
Reina? Are you kidding me?
That thief!
Dad, don't call her that, Dad.
What do you want
me to call her then?
You get
your ass back here
All right, come with me
son, tell me what happened.
Come on, let's go.
Then we arrived at a small town
in Texas.
I can't remember the name.
With the money that Reina had,
we were able to catch a bus...
that took 5 days
to bring us here.
And you have no money left?
No.
Well, it's a miracle
you're still alive.
What do you do here when you're
trying to find someone
who's lost?
Well, usually
you start with the hospitals,
the morgue, the police,
but that wouldn't work
in this case.
You need to get yourself settled
and you need to find a job.
Where do I start?
For now,
just start with breakfast
because you're going to need
to get back all your strength.
Good moming!
I just need
to use the restroom.
Go ahead.
Shit!
That's the final straw!
How dare you give him
my clothes! Giovanny!
Stop making such a fuss,
for God's sake.
Have you forgotten
what it's like to come here
and nobody helps you?
No, I haven't forgotten, I know
what you have to do.
You have to work,
like you did, like I did.
- Giovanny!
- Yes, sir!
Take this bum to the wall,
so he'll leam to work freezing
his ass off!
He's going to sleep
in the basement.
What?
He's not sleeping outside!
You hear me?
Go on, get this fag out of here,
or you'll have to answer to me!
What wall
is he talking about?
The only thing I want to do
is find my girlfriend.
Did you come
from here or there?
How could I possibly
remember that?
Everything looks the same here.
Come on.
Okay, man,
we've got to figure this out.
Tell me, more or less,
how far did you walk before you
got to this place right here?
- I didn't walk.
- Okay, how far did you run?
I don't know.
Listen, Marlon,
Patricia said you needed help.
The problem is that things
are different here.
Reina doesn't exist as far
as the Americans are concerned.
So we've got to have
something,
a photograph to put
on a poster for people to see,
a telephone number,
or something, you understand?
I didn't bring
pictures or anything.
But she's really easy
to recognize
because she's got one
brown eye and one green.
People notice those kinds
of things.
We should just ask around.
No, no, no, you don't
understand,
that's not how it works...
this here is not Colombia.
This is New York.
Come with me,
I'm going to show you something.
Take a good look.
This is the monster
you'll have to tame.
You think you can find somebody
in this mess,
when your only clue
is a sign that says "Queen, "
or that she has a green
or blue eye? No, man,
your Reina will turn up if she's
got somebody looking for her,
but it'll take time,
you've got to start the process.
- What process?
- The process...
get your papers, social
security, start paying taxes.
That's the only way you can
become legal in this country.
Or marry an American.
What are you talking about?
Listen Marlon, I know everything
looks bleak right now,
but the day you start sending
money home to your family,
everything changes for you.
And that first remittance,
it's the most gratifying moment
for an immigrant.
No... that's not why I came.
That's not my case.
What does it say there?
Paradise awaits you.
What would that be like...
Here we are.
This is the wall Pastor
was talking about.
What are they doing there?
They're looking for work.
What kind of work?
Whatever there is.
Whatever the Americans
don't want to do.
Bricklaying,
construction, gardening...
The pay is low, but there's
no choice.
You make enough
to eat and sleep.
It's not ideal but it's work
and it's an opportunity.
In a while
you'll find something better,
and you'll see someone else
arrive and take your place.
In this country you've got
to stand in line for everything,
even to be happy.
Put it down.
Excuse me, excuse me.
- Reina.
- What happened?
Wait... are you sure about
going through with this?
Why, you're not?
You can still back out
if you want to.
Excuse me, could you keep
moving this way, please?
Come on,
you're holding up the line!
Don't grab me like that!
You know I hate it.
Ladies and Gentlemen,
this is Aerocol flight # 3833.
Our final destination
is Panama City.
For safety reasons,
we request you to please
fasten your seatbelts and
refrain from smoking
during the whole flight.
This flight will
take 1 hour
You don't
look so nervous now.
Just put your seatbelt on,
would you.
I think we left.
Marlon.
I know these have been very
difficult days for you,
but Pastor finally gave in.
He gave in?
We're giving you a job,
here in the restaurant.
I'll do anything rather than
lifting those sacks.
You can't keep
sleeping here, though.
That was his condition.
But... ma'am.
Where am I supposed to sleep
if I don't know anyone here?
I'm working on that.
But for now,
you'll start working here,
that's the most important thing.
Okay, where do you
want me to start?
Here, brother,
your new office.
Welcome!
Clean the mirrors, the sinks,
take out the garbage.
It's important to clean
after every single customer
that comes in.
I'm going to spend all my time
cleaning shit.
When am I supposed to look
for my girlfriend, Giovanny?
You gotta to stop talking
like that, man.
You have to
focus on working here now.
You think everybody who comes
here gets a job this easily?
Forget that nonsense and take
advantage of this opportunity.
What, is this to hold onto
when you have to push too hard?
What a stupid ass.
That's for
the "handicapped," Marlon.
"Handicapped"?
Enjoy!
Marlon, come on, hurry up,
they're here to pick you up.
Look son... this is Mr. Hernan.
He's very nice, he's always
helping in the community,
and he's found you
a place to sleep for free
until you save
a little money.
Hernan Posada,
at your service.
Pleased to meet you.
Free? Forgive me, Mr. Hernan,
That sounds
too good to be true.
Oh, relax, Marlon, I would trust
my life to Mr. Hernan.
Anyway, what other
choice do you have?
How about we take a walk
and you tell me what happened.
Thank you so much,
Mr. Hernan.
- You're welcome.
- You take care of yourself.
See you tomorrow,
Miss Patricia.
See you tomorrow.
I know
many cases like yours.
If there's any way
I can help you...
any questions you might have,
just let me know.
How do I get rid of the fear?
It's a matter of time.
We immigrants carry fear
and uncertainty inside.
We think there's
always someone coming after us.
People that have been through
downtown, also politicians
Hey, my sweetie pie!
You haven't been here
for so long.
Look at
the present you brought me!
Oh, what a pretty
little pumpkin.
Be nice to the boy,
he's had a rough time.
Make sure
he's well taken care of.
Of course I will.
Look, my love,
don't you worry.
Nothing will happen
to you here.
He's afraid.
Right? Don't take him
away so fast.
Her name is Raquel,
she had to come here
when she abandoned
her family because of alcohol.
She's spent a lot of time
on the streets... she's sick.
Don't let her bother you.
It's taken a lot
of time to rehabilitate her,
but she's a good person.
I don't know what Patricia told
you about me, Mr. Hernan...
but I'm not
like any of these people,
I don't have a drug
or alcohol problem.
I know, son, but there aren't
many places in this city
where you could
stay without paying.
Besides, nobody is going
to bite you here.
What, what, what...
Welcome, travelers.
I hope
you had a good trip.
It's very important that you
pay for your rooms now,
there won't be time
to take care of it tomorrow
because we have to leave
very early in the morning.
It's $30 per person.
- $30 bucks for this dump?
- No, no, no way!
Excuse me, but this was
supposed to be included.
They didn't tell us we needed
to bring more money.
Why would you pay there
for what you will use here?
You're here...
the resort is here.
Did you really think
you could pay there
for what you
have to pay here?
You're gonna have to work
that out with Fabiola
back in Medellin,
we have no money.
Yeah, come on, man,
we already paid for that!
So where are you planning
to sleep tonight?
What do you mean, where are we
supposed to sleep? Here, man!
I have very few beds;
first come, first served.
Okay, I'll pay you, that's for
two, all right?
- Take it, sorry bastard.
- Here, give me my change.
There are three of you,
ma'am.
I'll pay you back
in The States, man, come on.
Stop pushing!
Move, that one
over there's mine.
I got this one, over here,
over here.
This one over here is mine.
If there's not enough beds,
there's always the floor.
* I look up to the sky *
* searching for a little
of my life *
* My stars don't answer me *
* to show the way
to your smile *
* Waves that shade my eyes *
* a league away
from your memories *
* steal pictures of
your face *
* leaving sand in the silence *
* I'm searching for you
lost among dreams *
* The noise of people
around me wraps me in a veil *
* I'm searching for you
flying through the sky *
* the wind has carried you away
like an old handkerchief *
* I do nothing else
but search and search *
* through familiar landscapes *
* in places so strange *
* that I'll never
find you *
Are you sure, Mom?
Were you able
to talk to Mr. Gonzalo?
Marlon, he's not okay
with all of this.
First it's the wife, now
the daughter, he's very upset.
What should I do then? Tell me,
she couldn't have just vanished.
No one knows anything here.
Everyone thinks
she's with you, Marlon.
Why don't you just come back
here to your family
and forget about her?
Is Dad still so mad
he won't even talk to me?
You know him,
what can I do, Marlon?
He's still very hurt,
you did something very bad
- Mom, your blessing-
- God bless you, son,
please, don't stay over there,
come back quickly.
Okay, bye.
- Hi.
- How's it going?
- Fine.
I didn't know you sang...
Well, now you do.
- How did the band sound?
- What band?
You mean
those two little funny guys?
Yup, they're my band.
Yeah, they sounded good.
That's because we're
the best band in Queens.
The only problem is you
made a mistake in the lyrics.
Oh, really? What's that?
You said "l steal pictures
of your face,
crying alone in the silence."
It's "They steal shapes
from your face, "
Ieaving sand in the silence."
It's not a mistake, actually, it
makes it easier to understand.
What? Are you some kind
of music purist or something,
that you get offended if someone
changes the lyrics?
No, I just know that song.
I don't know why but we
always find songs that remind us
of what we're feeling or
experiencing in life,
So that means you're searching.
We're all searching for
something, aren't we?
Or in your case, someone.
How do you know?
There's no secrets
in the restaurant.
I hate these stupid ghosts!
Nice to meet you.
- What's your name?
- Milagros, Milagros Valdez.
I'm Marlon Cruz.
I'm taking the subway,
are you coming?
Yeah, hold on,
I have to get my clothes.
- Yes, Reina, yes.
- So you're horny.
Let me take care of that.
Fuck me...
I'm much more woman
than she is.
What? What's going on?
Get off! Get off!
You dirty bitch!
Fuck her!
Come here.
Rio Suchiate
Guatemala/Mexico Border
Come on,
the kid's next.
- The kid will be fine, move!
- Mom!
Shut that fucking kid up.
Come on,
get over here!
You think I'm gonna get wet for
a dumbass who's so scared.
If you can't cross by yourself
you'll have to stay behind!
This stupid boy is
going to makes us all fall.
Where are you going?
- The boy!
- Just leave him!
I'm gonna get the boy!
- Come here.
- Let go of him.
I'll take him.
If he makes another sound,
I'm cutting the rope, asshole.
On your knees!
Give me your tennis shoes,
asshole!
How could l
give you my tennis shoes?!
How come she hasn't called you?
You're her father.
I know, I know.
Can you speak up?
This call is expensive.
- What happened?
- The same old shit.
That old man
is crazier than a goat!
To top it all, I don't have
a place to sleep tonight.
Come on, back to work.
Hey, Milagros,
how're you doing?
This poor guy doesn't have
anywhere to sleep.
Maybe he can stay with you.
As long as he doesn't snore.
Ehh... no... I'm sorry.
That Giovanny.
- Hey, thanks for nothing, man.
- You're welcome.
Hey, kid, come here.
Mr. Hernan,
how are you?
What's up? What happened
to you last night?
Nothing, it's just
I had to run out of there.
I've already heard, that woman
is incredible! Have a seat.
Giovanny!
I found another place
for you, kid.
- Really? You did?
- It's not great, but...
But, but what?
With what they probably
pay you here,
you can't expect very much.
- Hey, Giovanny.
- How's it going, Mr. Heman?
I found another place for Marlon
to stay at night.
Do you know
where Roger Pena lives?
Roger Pena?
Beautiful, my two favorite
boys sitting down;
would you boys like me
to bring you a drink?
Get back to work, you bums!
How are you doing,
Pastor?
How is it going, my friend.
Man, it's cold.
Yeah... that's the building.
Which one? The cool one?
No, the one next to it.
That place is a rat hole!
It looks abandoned.
It's because It is,
why do you think it's so cheap?
People live there without paying
rent, they're squatters.
In Colombia
I wasn't rich, Giovanny,
but I wasn't this
poor either, brother.
Here, the rich want to buy,
but the poor don't want to sell.
The rich offer too little, and
the poor ask for too much.
Coming, coming.
Welcome, stranger.
Come on in.
How're you doing, Roger?
Hanging in there.
All right, good,
the big bed is mine.
This one right here,
this is yours.
The bathroom is
down the hall to your left
and the kitchen is in there.
You can keep your things here,
under the b-b-b-bed,
because the wardrobe
over here, that's mine too.
And the other bed?
Don't worry about it,
you'll never see him.
He works while we sleep.
Just in case,
his name is Javier,
and the guy who sleeps in your
bed while you're at work
is William, and if you're
here at the same time,
you'll have
to share the b-b-bed.
Are you leaving?
- Yes.
- Bye.
Hey, take this, kid!
Don't lose them, or I'll have to
ch-ch-charge you for a copy.
Speaking of ch-ch-ch-ch...
Charging?
Listen, Roger,
he just got here.
So what?
Do you think you could maybe
give him 'til next week
when he gets paid?
I guarantee you,
he's good for it, man.
I'm not worried, you know why?
Because here, everyone pays
one way-ay-ay or another.
Hey, Giovanny...
I'm gonna have to share
my bed with a stranger.
And look how crazy this guy is.
Relax, nothing
is going to happen to you.
All right, Roger, thanks again
for everything.
See you tomorrow.
Beware, boy, lights out
at 10:00 P.M. sharp.
How long
are you planning to stay?
Truth is, not that long.
I'm looking for my girlfriend,
and when I find her, I'll leave.
- Where is she?
- I don't know.
We got lost from each other,
I'm looking for her.
Here in New York? Right.
Hey, look!
That bag just moved.
Damn right, it did...
that's D-D-D-Demon.
- Demon?
- Yes, like the devil.
Why did you name it that?
Because he's a son
of a b-b-b-bitch.
- Does he bite?
- Of course he bites.
We both do,
when we're f-f-fucked with.
Damn, look at the time,
it's 10:00 already.
Good night, boy.
Hey, Mr. Roger?
What's that noise?
They're b-b-balls.
Balls?
What's going on,
where were you?!
Hurry up, the bus to Reynosa
is almost here!
you'll have
many days to sleep there.
Hurry up, let's go!
Hurry up,
let's go, ma'am.
What's your problem, lady...
That suitcase was
in my spot.
That's what you think.
The spot is mine,
it goes with my seat.
Oh, really? Since when
are the seats numbered?
I don't mind throwing suitcases
around this whole trip.
Excuse me ma'am,
but we were here first.
But your bag was
in my place.
Why don't you go kill yourself,
lndian bitch!
You have to respect me!
Hey settle down!
What the hell
is going on back there?
God almighty...
Come here you two, and you,
and you, and all the tourists.
Why don't you
control your woman.
Mind your own business, asshole.
Damned, I have to treat them
like donkeys!
Let's relax!
Cut it out!
Mind your business!
Move, now!
Why the fuck don't you
stop arguing!
Shut up, why don't you
stand up for me, you asshole!
Come on, baby, now!
Let's go, kid, I have to treat
them like fucking donkeys!
All right,
enjoying your vacation?
The federal police
are tough fuckers...
because I suppose you all have
your papers in order, don't you?
Yes, sir.
And you, you better
keep it down, all right?
Listen, we have nothing to do
with this problem,
- it's that loudmouth.
- Loudmouth?
- That lndian started it!
- That may be, sweetheart,
but there are several ways
of solving problems.
Oh, really,
the way you solved them?
I could stand out here watching
you two fight all day.
You look gorgeous.
But the Federal agents will get
suspicious if they see this bus
sitting here too long,
so we have to get going.
To do that, I'll need a little
cash for some gas, you get me?
- let's go.
- I can't believe this!
It's too bad, we have
nothing left.
They took everything from us.
Everything? They couldn't have
taken... everything.
Hey, cut it out.
Look, we're completely broke,
what do you expect us to do?
No problem...
you can all stay here.
- See you.
- Come on, man,
how are you gonna
leave us here alone
Let's give that old fag
what he wants.
Or are you honey gonna carry us
all across the border?
Why don't you just
kill yourself, too?
Well, I guess it's up to me to
fix this then, huh?
Or you're gonna do it, honey.
Open up!
What is she going to do?
I guess she just paid for your
tickets, lucky bastards.
* Baby that fish *
* I'm not eating it *
* I'm not eating that fish
even if it's *
What's up?
Increasing your repertoire?
Practicing, so I don't
screw up the lyrics.
You finished?
- Yes.
- Okay, wait for me, then,
we'll go together,
where are you going, anyway?
Back to the rat hole.
Excuse me,
how much is this?
I'm closed, why don't you
come back tomorrow? Thank you.
So... do you dance? Or do you
only search?
Do I dance, baby?
I'll light your feet on fire.
Where's the bathroom?
Give me your jacket.
Listen... what kind
of place is this?
Guys ask
to dance, girls accept.
That's the tradition.
Yes... but I just saw them
paying the girls.
Oh, my God,
you've got a dirty mind.
Yes, they pay them to dance.
$2 a song or $40 an hour.
I used
to be a dancer here.
Really, you did?
It was either that
or cleaning toilets.
What would you have done?
Marlon, what are you up to?
In here,
setting up the franchise.
- What is this?
- Customer service.
Does Pastor know about this?
Anyway, come on, I got you
an appointment with a woman,
and she's going
to help us find Reina.
She's the absolute best
at finding lost things,
so come on, let's go.
No, Reina's not a thing,
Miss Patricia.
Oh, come on,
if she can find a wallet,
why wouldn't she be able
to find Reina? Come on.
Leave that, you'll finish
that later, let's go!
- I don't believe in witchcraft.
- Come on.
It seems the cards
weren't shuffled properly.
She's asking ifyou have
anything of hers.
Having something of hers,
it's easier to connect to her.
A picture,
a photo, anything.
Are you sure
you don't have anything?
Otherwise, she can't
connect to her.
Mary, mother of God, Marlon.
She's not lost
and she has the power
of the chameleon in her eyes.
She's not lost
and she's got money,
she's also looking
for someone.
Of course, Miss Patricia,
she's looking for me.
She's finding me,
me, finding me!
It's you that's lost.
In order to find her, you've got
to find yourself first.
- That's what she said.
- Ask her when we'll meet again.
What?
How can you charge $60 if you
haven't told me anything?
There are days she can't
see things clearly, Marlon.
Hey, take it away from her,
take it away!
Calm down, why do you carry that
dirty thing around anyway?
Just be thankful she even
told you that Reina is alive.
But I know she's ok
Ms. Patricia, I know!
How dare you bum
the only thing of hers I have.
She says let her go.
Come on, come on, let's go.
I know she's okay.
Yes, be thankful
she told you that.
What's next? A massage parlor,
I suppose?
Did you know about this?
No, but the customers like it,
don't they?
I think it shows great
initiative of Marlon.
It's a service we've never
offered before.
Service?
This is no "service"...
This is a business inside
my business.
I just think I should
be able to earn some tips.
Maybe... I could even give you
a percentage for rent.
Percentage?
What? Like fifty-fifty?
My God, Pastor, at your age
you're begging for pennies!
- Stop your bullshit!
- Fine!
Let him do whatever
the fuck he wants!
No, not whatever the fuck
he wants, he has my permission.
Oh, he does? Oh, that's
all he needs, that's enough.
- That's right! My permission.
- Fine then, with your permisson!
Nice business, bro.
- They thank
any kind of information.
Marlon Cruz is searching
for a young Colombian woman
named Reina, 18 years old,
height: 1. 67 m, brown hair
distinctive different color
light eyes.
If anyone has any information,
please call us-
I have been searching for you
for the past three months.
I'm so sorry,
I didn't know how to-
- named Reina, 18 years old,
she disappeared six months ago.
If anyone has any information,
please call us at -
Marlon keeps looking for woman
who disappeared 8 months ago.
Her name is Reina,
she's 18 years old.
That's it... m-m-more pain.
Let me feel your pain.
Scream with more pain.
Come on, let's go,
more agressive,
you know, more agressive,
come on, you're an animal!
No, forget it, it's a failure,
a tragedy.
No, give it up;
don't bother, leave it.
So?
See? There we go,
see? It really hurts.
Perfect! Animalistic, just what
I want, just like that!
You're gonna
thank me for this.
I'm telling you,
it's beautiful.
- No, it's not! Let me go!
- Okay, okay, calm down.
At least you had
a hard-on, it would help.
But with that
tiny package, it's pathetic.
- Let me go already!
- Okay, stop whining.
How dare you whip me,
you asshole!
How dare you not p-p-pay?
Are you gonna
let me go or what?
All right, hold your horses,
I'm coming.
You're not very good
at hard work, are you?
Go get ch-ch-changed,
we're leaving.
No way,
I've got things to do.
No, you haven't paid up yet.
What are you
talking about?
You think
I was doing you a favor?
- That's just a d-d-down payment.
- Down payment my ass!
That's enough.
So where are we going?
To see n-n-naked Latinas,
hurry up.
Look at these cows...
Jesus Christ...
but for what that
c- c-catalogue is costing.
Roger, don't put me
in that catalogue.
Stop whining,
your face is always c-c-covered.
- Mr. Roger, how's it going?
- What's up, fag?
I've got some ladies in the back
ready for your happy ending.
Well, the last time
you brought me some
that would make
dogs h-h-h-h-howl.
No worries,
these are hot.
We'll see, we'll see.
No Bro, you stay here.
Well, this goes to all you boys
to the dance floor!
I wanna see you dancing,
because the girls and l
are gonna spank you like rats!
Welcome to "Big Buga!"
Calena!
* Hey you
park your truck *
* Your bike also
if you want to *
* I'll be waiting
for you with my doors open *
* Biscuit you aren't
good enough *
* In case you get naughty
don't you let me down *
* Gimme gimme
sugar cane candy *
What's up?
Hey, sweetheart!
What are you doing here
baby?
I didn't recognize you
when you came in.
What's happening,
tell me everything,
where's the loudmouth?
Calena, right after we got here,
we lost each other.
You got lost? Is that so?
Or did "Miss Loudmouth"
give you the boot?
You wouldn't believe
all that's happened to me.
I've been doing great, I found
a job as soon as I got here.
So anyway, tell me,
how are things with you?
I'm a delivery boy.
What a waste,
you've got to be kidding me.
With your good looks
and being Colombian,
you can do
a lot better than that.
I wasted a lot of time searching
for that girl.
But if it's over, why are you
still looking for her?
Why look out there,
when you can find it here?
And it's all free for you.
Everything you saw up there,
I've been saving for you.
What's wrong,
are you a faggot?
Listen sweetheart, I'm used
to men who respond, so...
That girl
was driving you crazy.
The hell with that.
We'll just have to find
that hothead, won't we?
Hey, Jean Pierre,
put my song on.
At least
there's a lobby here.
Hey, sugar, does your woman ever
give you any room to breathe?
Reynosa,
Mexico/United States Border
Are you planning on fucking
her here in front of everyone?
No... she has a backache
from the bus ride.
She asked me to
give her a massage, that's all.
Calm down, rubbing doesn't make
you pregnant, honey.
You're such a slut!
I need a room for two.
Wait, Reina.
Come here... how do you
plan to pay for that?
You think
I'm stupid, or what?
Why didn't you tell me
we had more money?
Put it away.
- How much is it?
- There's no regular rooms left.
Don't spend our money
on this.
I hate the snores and
farts of all those people.
We're sleeping alone
and that's final.
We'll gonna save that money and
sleep where we're supposed to!
Why, don't you want to sleep
with me alone?
How much is it again?
400 Pesos, and 200 for
the vibrating bed.
But we're not gonna use that,
we're just gonna sleep.
How am l
supposed to know that?
Reina, we shouldn't be spending
that money.
Oh, Marlon.
If you don't know
how to use it...
I'm right here to help you,
my queen.
She is hot, man.
Were you dreaming?
Yeah, it was
the strangest dream.
I dreamt I was shitting fish.
Fish?
They were orange,
like goldfish.
They were swimming around
in the toilet.
Did you flush?
No, that's when I woke up.
What do you
think it means?
That not everything you
have inside you is shit.
Didn't you
want to wait until New York?
I'm sore, rub me.
Tear it.
Hey, turtledoves, be downstairs
in exactly one minute,
or you're screwed, understand?
If you stay here you're going
to be in a mess of trouble.
My clothes?
Here, asshole!
Hurry up!
Oh, no way!
Wipe that expression off your
face, it reeks of poverty.
But look
at the prices, Roger.
Don't be an ass,
pick whatever you want.
Are you serious?
I'm serious,
whatever you want.
Except that, it looks
really tacky.
- How's this?
- Perfect.
Even the color?
Even the color...
do you need pants?
Sure...
these are
a bit expensive though.
Cut that shit out,
they're perfect.
Hold the bag.
Make sure nobody gets close.
How dare you get me into
trouble, you asshole.
B- b-b-be quiet, idiot.
- N-n-n-no w-w-way!
- Don't make fun of me.
Roger, no, this is why these
people always suspect us.
Open the bag,
put this in here.
Here, toss these
out some place.
We started running-
and Roger?
He was running!
He looked so funny!
And after all that we made it
home, and look,
he gave me
new clothes with patches.
- lt looks cool.
- What about these sticks?
Wouldn't it be easier to
use the wide part of the sticks?
- No, like I told you.
- But everything is falling off.
I know... hold on, this is
how they taught me.
Hey, if they'd caught you,
you'd be on a plane
straight to Colombia.
I don't know whether to laugh
or worry about you.
So... would you
really worry about me?
Marlon, look!
- Would you take me to that?
- To what?
You're out so much,
I will add a third shift
for your b-b-b-
Bed!
Like a friend of mine says,
"around pimps and whores,
keep a low profile."
So you're telling me this
because I'm a pimp or a w-whore?
- A whore!
- Exactly... here, put this on.
Yeah, there you go,
the best.
Look at that, you look hot!
You're sure it's okay
to go to a salsa concert?
Relax, it's gonna be fine,
you'll knock that B-B-Brittany
wannabe off her feet.
So what do you think,
open or closed?
Zip it up, totally closed,
yeah, there you go.
Hey, wait a minute.
I'll be back late, Roger.
Careful with the lights.
Reina?
Reina!
Reina! Hey!
Man, you got it bad,
my friend.
You gotta stop this
obsession with her, Marlon.
I'm not obsessed, Miss Patricia,
I saw her, I'm sure it was her.
You're mistaking her
for somebody else.
You end up seeing
what you want to see.
I hate to disappoint you,
but this time it was really her.
Can I get change, please?
That poor girl is
the one paying the consequences.
Everywhere you look, you
see her, you'll end up crazy.
And you'll drive the rest
of us crazy with you.
Hey, Giovanny,
come on, man, I'm not crazy.
Oh, no? All I ever hear from you
is Reina here, Reina there.
Who do you think you are,
some kind of king?
It's the same thing everyday!
I think as long
as you're still seeing one,
you should stop seeing
the other one.
Wh-wh-what was that?
What?
The silence.
Roger, what's going on?
What is it, Roger?
Get up, we've got to get
out of here.
Quick, before the
po-po-police get here.
Turn on the light, Roger.
No, no...
there's no time, come on!
If you don't leave now, you'll
have to deal with the visitors.
Roger!
Roger! wait for me!
Are you coming back here?
Rats will be
the only ones coming back
to collect the scraps!
and you still
owe me this week's rent.
Wait for me!
Roger!
- Good evening, sir.
- Who are you?
I'm a friend of Milagros.
This is no time
to be paying visits.
Could you be so kind as to
tell her I'm here?
I know him,
uncle, don't worry.
- Are you sure?
- Yes.
What do you want?
It's the bicycle's fault,
It brought me here.
What did it want?
This is all shit,
and to top it off,
I've got nowhere to sleep.
So you came here
so I could help you?
But you're the only person-
I'm not the only anything,
Marlon.
The only thing you have in that
head of yours is confusion.
You don't even know
whether you're coming or going.
what you see, asshole!
It's been
very difficult for me too.
The truth is, I'm sick
of fighting with a ghost.
Then get out of here with your
damn ghost and leave me alone!
Why am I such an idiot?
Come in quickly,
before I change my mind.
Are you Milagros' boyfriend?
Everybody,
this is Marlon.
I've told you he'll be staying
here a few days.
- Good morning, Marlon.
- Good morning.
Good moming,
ma'am, how are you?
- Sit down.
- Excuse me.
Hello.
This all looks great...
these arepas look weird.
So... where do you work?
At "Mi Tierra Colombiana."'
Really? You know the rules here,
don't you?
No, but I'll tell him.
It's very simple, if you live
here, you pay your way.
Let him eat breakfast.
He has a job,
he can contribute.
If money's the problem,
then there's no problem,
because there's no money!
I started to eam
some more money, Mom.
- You did?
- Yes.
Tell Aunt Marlene
not to worry.
That I'm going
to pay her back every penny.
I've also sent you an envelope
with some money.
I'm glad, son,
that sounds great! Thank God!
That makes me very happy!
Hey, Mom, how's Mateo?
Is he behaving himself?
Yes, he is doing
very good, Marlon,
but he misses you very much,
we all miss you very much here.
Oh, Mom... would it be possible
to speak with Dad?
It's better to wait a little
until you send more money.
That way he'll see you
will take care of that debt.
Just tell him
that I love him, okay?
Your blessing, mom.
God bless you, my son,
good-bye! Take care!
- You too.
- Bye, honey!
What about your grandmother?
Don't worry, it's okay.
I'm going to get some water,
want some?
All set, Mr. Pastor.
- How did it go?
- $3 in tips.
Biscuit!
I don't believe it, Calena!
Here, Mr. Pastor.
What are you doing here?
Gorgeous!
You just tore my heart to pieces
when I heard the message
you put up for
the hothead on the radio.
Oh, Calena, that doesn't matter
to me anymore.
Right, and I was born yesterday.
Do me a favor, sweetie,
and bring us two shots.
I've got some great news that
will knock you off your feet.
- Two?
- One for you and one for me.
Everything okay, Marlon?
Yes, ma'am.
She's a friend who made the trip
here with us.
Excuse me.
- Here you go.
- Where is yours?
I can't, I'm working.
So, tell me why are you here?
Delicious,
great for my sore legs.
- Your little queen.
- The bathroom, please.
- Where is this?
- It's an address in Atlanta.
Atlanta? Are you sure?
Stop it, do you really think
I would waste my time
to come all the way over here,
if I wasn't absolutely sure
she was there?
And don't you dare tell
her it was me who told you.
- Thank you, Miss Patricia.
- Because remember-
Remember that bimbo
doesn't like me.
Calena, are you
absolutely sure?
Enough... call her,
you've got the number,
and then you'll see
I'm not bullshitting you.
God bless you.
What's going on?
Hello, please leave your
name...
Big kiss and thanks.
It's her, it's her.
What happened?
What's going on?
Why are you packing?
Where are you going?
Talk to me, asshole,
where are you going?
Where are you going?
Talk to me!
You're going to Reina.
Marlon, talk to me,
at least look at me, fucker!
Don't be such a coward,
look me in the eyes.
Marlon, please don't go!
If you leave,
don't ever come back, asshole!
Texas, United States
Wake up, assholes,
we're here.
Let me out!
Let me out of here,
open up!
Let's go
or we'll all pay.
Get down here-
Get off, stupid fucking
"gringo.",
Come on, we've got to get out
of here, come on!
Hurry up, honey,
the gringos are coming.
Bring him down!
Bring him!
He's dead.
Look what
they've done to us, Reina.
What does it matter?
We're here, the worst part
is already over.
We are in
The United States now!
We're here.
Atlanta, Georgia
Yes?
Raquel?
Are you Reina's mother?
Have been all my life,
sweetheart.
Why? Do we know each other?
I'm Marlon, Marlon Cruz.
You're just a baby.
Can I see her?
You want a drink?
Reina! No, ma'am,
thank you.
I just want to see Reina.
Well, I'm going to have one,
because I haven't had
one for a while.
Where's that fucking bottle?
- ls Reina here?
- Here she is.
Look! Sure that you
don't want anything?
No, thank you.
I just came here to talk
to your daughter.
Re- Reina's not here.
Where is she?
Come here
and have a smoke with me.
Please, I've come a long way
and I need to see your daughter.
She never told you about me?
Of course
she told me about you.
She told me you are
a very good boy.
My gosh, very, very good.
Did she tell you
we got lost?
- I don't remember.
- Then what do you remember?
Tell me what she told you.
That old lady
sings incredibly well.
* Black pigeon
black pigeon *
- Tell me!
- All right, don't get so pushy!
You're so desperate, baby.
Calm down,
we'll look for her.
You know what?
Wait for me here.
And this baby?
Beautiful, isn't she?
Baby... maybe you've got
a little money for a blow job?
Raquel, please just take me
to your daughter.
Fine then.
We'll go find your queen...
get out.
Let's go!
And so that
you don't complain,
I'm even taking you
in my Ferrari.
You're going
to drive like that?
Where does Reina work?
She does
a variety of things.
Is it far?
We're almost there.
- Where is it?
- She's just around the corner.
- Show up, "Reinita."'
- Hey watch out, drive carefully.
Queen of hearts...
your prince
is looking for you.
Look, look... there she is.
Reina!
Reina! Hey! Reina!
I though you'd never come.
What happened to your eyes?
This is how they were
always meant to be.
Help me get her inside,
it's gonna start raining.
Whose baby
is that in the picture?
That baby is none
of your business, help me.
Take the keys.
Why didn't you tell me you
wanted to look for your mother?
- How did you find her?
- Looking for her; take the keys!
Come on, Mom, get out.
Why didn't you look for me?
Where was I supposed
to look for you?
I don't know, around the
same places I looked for you.
Everywhere... why did you make
me come with you
- if you were going to leave.
- I didn't leave you,
you went out
and never came back.
Give me the keys,
it's raining!
I got lost! If you had looked
for me, you would've found me,
just like
you found your mother.
Just give me the keys, we'll
talk inside, it's raining.
- Why didn'tyou call home?
- Give her the keys.
- Your father got sick.
- So what? I can still call.
Why didn't you ever tell
me about your mother.
- That baby is mine, isn't she?
- Don't be such a fag!
Do you really think you were man
enough to give me a baby?
- ls she mine? Answer me!
- No, don't be such an asshole!
Can't you see the baby is inside
and I'm getting wet?!
Give me the keys!
You haven't changed a bit,
Marlon, not a bit.
You're wrong; believe it or not
I have changed thanks to you.
I'm not going to try to reproach
something I can't change.
On the contrary,
now I understand that love isn't
why I followed you here.
I doubt there was
ever any love between us.
Nevertheless I want to thank
you for bringing me on this trip
and above all
thank you for abandoning me,
for not looking for me.
Why did you come?
Why did you come here?
- I had to find you, Reina.
- Great, now you found me,
now you can go to fucking hell
for all I care!
You can go kill
yourself if you feel like it!
No, I don't feel like it.
You go ahead and
kill yourself if you want to.