PIRATES
Oh God, Isabel
I can not begin to tell you how good I feel right now
"I love the perfection, I must admit, I'm nervous
Nervous?, We should not be nervous
Is it true that the Caribbean Sea is full of pirates?
Yes, but would not let a pirate in sight or sound yours
You are very sexy
I can not wait to see your body
Already, we're married
You'll see it soon
But there is something
What if he told you, you decide that you do not like?
Then I must sell you a pirate as a sex slave
I think it's worth a few gold coins
You're a fool
- What? "Seriously
You're my wife now and forever, nothing will change that
I love you for all you are
Everything you're not and all that will be
Thanks love
Thank God. Divine Perfection
I've waited for 260 years this magnificent moment
We are close and she has no sign that we have seen
Good job, keep surfing as a soft ball
If Captain
What happens?
Nothing ... my love back to sleep
Where you going honey?
I'll breathe the sea air, and back
"Manuel, you ever seen a night so divine?
In all my years at sea he had never seen such serenity
God has blessed us with peace tonight
Definitely yes
How long before we get to Caribbean waters?
"We'll not later than the morning - So fast?
If we lose the calm breeze, and if it increases, get ...
... Before the sun rises. Still, I'll take safe
No doubt it has always sailed fast and careful
Thanks friend
Go, you should be resting with your beautiful wife
Perhaps it is cold without you
He's right captain. Good night
- How is the sea air? "The only air I want ...
... Is breathing your breath
I love you so
When I have my treasure, I'll give you everything you want
I have no desire
I was a little more endulzarte
You're a fool
I'm a fool for you
It brings together sailors on the bow, and bring me down passengers
And Sarina ... Although I love you so, do not consider
kill anyone this time
What are you doing?
If you let it go I'll do what you want
There is no need for something so violent
Silence
Hello, my name is Captain Victor Stagnetti
I apologize for any inconvenience that we ...
Pirates ... they've caused, we are pirates
Sadly this is our way of being
Usually this would end with people like you beheaded
For the head you eat sharks, but this
... Has to happen if I get what I want
What do you want?
Captain, was at that point
I hate when you interrupt me, right?
Now
I've been looking for a man for a long, long time
My search ends here and now
The man with the name of Manuel Valenzuela, forward pass
How nice pearl necklace
She
I'm Manuel Valenzuela
Manuel I
"Please, let me save, I would have to ...
... Throw the whole boat to meet you
"Captain, please, let me save-No. You are very valuable ...
... For shark meat. That is the fate of your beautiful lady
"You'll be by my side so you're safe," Please, it ...
... My wife is not left to die. I beg you, please ...
... Compassion. "Thank you gentlemen for your time
You can follow his path. Gentlemen, returned to
"La Rosa Del Diablo." And my vicious lady, also
Hellsmith, get ready to sail
- Do let go to save? "Of course not, húndelos!
Captain's Log, August 26, 1763
It has been four long weeks without seeing land
The sailors are impatient and discouraged
I try to motivate and teach them how to fight ...
.. With swords, but soon tire
Somehow, the First Lady, Jules keeps them ...
... The moral high ground. As it does not, I have no idea
Many men do not articulate a lot and she's ...
... Help you improve your oral or fighting attributes. More ...
... Night I hear noises from the cockpit, which can only be ...
... Be produced by his devotion
At least we know that the good Lord be with us ...
... On our trip, but there are many more problems later
Food supplements are quite low and I fear ...
... We have to return to port again. I have wanted ...
... From pirates to face but the truth, I'm worried ...
Chang Woo because you can not make new guns ...
... Shoot very well. Each time the cannon fired smells ...
... A goat's tail. Woo believes that the powder you need more potassium ...
... And less sulfur
The bad news is that we do not have potassium
The same fight with the pirates with swords or hand ...
... To the death if necessary. I feel at ease ...
... Knowing that soon manage to find something. At the call ...
... Action, my crew you want thrown out. We are men ...
... And women in cold blood, we fear hackers. I fear to me ...
Edwards Captain Reynolds. Captain of the "sea horse"
"Edward," Excuse me, is the captain
And he has said clearly not want to be interrupted. Just ...
... When we are under attack, and careful, "Okay, I speak ...
... With the commander-is necessary to complete the log.
"Okay, they apologized. Later continue
I suggest you to report immediately to the bow
Yes
Captain
Oxford was right, you should not bother me. As a captain ...
... Of "sea horse" is my work with all protocols are ...
... Followed exactly. And as captain of the ship I have to ...
... Make sure my orders are followed exactly
As captain it is my responsibility to the rules ...
... Are respected. Edward, for the charade.
What happens?
I'm a bad captain, I can not hunt pirates, or even ...
... I can hunt one. The crew hates me - What do you mean?
You dreaming of this since we were children
I'm a bad commander, we have not seen a boat
pirate in four weeks, four weeks!
Your father was right, I should have stayed on the plantation ...
... Snuff, helping to harvest it
-No. S lost faith in you ...
If true, had never previously been in a boat ...
... Like this. Is it true you've never been in combat ...
... With a man or a pirate. I really do not know is the sea ...
... But you have a dream and that is stronger than any ...
... Wisdom or experience. It is your destiny
What if this is not my destiny? What if this is not my dream?
You can "what" your whole life and die peacefully in a ...
... Warm bed or you can make your life worth and prevent ...
... That the pirates make others suffer as they do
Let's see what our fate has in store for us
- Where are they? "For the bow.
I see nothing.
There's something floating in the water.
I see nothing, check the lights of the dead, Oxford.
There is someone floating in the wood.
Man in the water.
Hampton, takes the boat has the remains. "Yes master, we are already.
Help me carry it inside.
Okay, you're safe.
- Are you okay? "Yes, just a little disoriented.
Take care. Drink this, will help you relax.
My name is Captain Edward Reynolds and you're safe ...
... In my boat, "El Caballo Marino" - Are pirates?
"Pirates, no. Well, I, what ... "We're hunting pirates.
Thank God, I thought I would die.
"You're safe here. "That's what Manuel said.
- Who is Manuel? "My husband.
- Was your ship attacked by pirates? -Si. We just ...
... Married in Spain. We went to the island of Seville.
"He was my family. "Sorry.
"Sorry. "We were attacked by pirates.
Then the pirate captain told my husband that
take out the face and reveal, but Manuel did not.
"And I dived into the water. - Do you remember his name?
"I think I said his name was Victus. "Stagnetti.
- Who is it? "It is a personification of ...
... All that is wrong. "We must find him.
"You may be in the middle of the ocean now. "Like, we ...
... Find it. But first, we need to supplement e. ..
... Information before starting the search. We go to ...
... Sorscabra Island. - Where?
It is a small island along the coast, which protects thieves ...
... Murderers and pirates of the Caribbean.
"I must talk to you about something. - Captain can ...
... Speak in private? "I want to rest secure Isabela ...
... Knowing that you're safe here in my boat.
- Do you think Manuel is alive? "No but if this, what ...
... Find. "Thanks.
- What happened? "You condemn us ...
in this place. Can not we start with a pirate ...
... Less experienced?
If we beat Victor Stagnatti. all the pirates terrorized. Think about it.
"Think what the world would write. - Really?
- What would you say? "The papers say ...
... "Captain Reynolds, save the world of pirates murderers"
- Is it possible? "If it's possible.
- Really? "I would be after ...
... How beautiful you are. "Yes, I look good in these clothes.
-Write your bravery. "Yes, I watch the death of their ...
... Eyes and grabbed his testicles. "And read the love he ...
... Got all creatures. "I love so much sometimes it hurts.
"And women. - What?
"Women. "Yes, women will run to you ...
... For comfort and safety. "I, I have strong arms.
Evil has no chance against these two cannons fire.
What, you're with me my friend?
Yes, now and forever. "Captain Reynolds, hunting pirates"
Faithful crew of "sea horse" I'll take a ...
... Tremendous day. The eye of the danger, a journey which ...
... Some or most would not return. 'll Hunt y. ..
... Kill the most dangerous pirates. Captain ...
... Victor Stagnetti and his ship called "La Rosa Del Diablo"
I have spoken with you about the hazards were found ...
... On this day. But this is an evil like no other.
Woo, Oxford did not blame if you do not want to follow me.
They are my friends now and forever.
Those who want to join me to take a giant step forward.
Remember that all will be well rewarded for my husband ...
... When this is over.
Well done.
"Commander, we sail to the island. "Yes, Captain.
-Crew, get ready! - If Captain!
"Well said, Captain. "Thank you Commander.
- What are we doing? "For now sail.
But when the time comes, do what is necessary.
Crew, at full speed. A Sorscabra Island.
I can feel his power begging. We are close ...
... Sarina, go to the city and is home to Indian ...
... And Report back to me. "As you say.
That is, the brotherhood of thieves, liars ...
... And murderers. Sorscabra Island.
Melvin lead us to the northern end of the island and seek a ...
... Good place to throw the anchor. "If a captain.
Commander, tell the crew that will throw an anchor.
Yes, Captain. Crew, get ready to pull anchor ...
... And land. "We're not ready for this.
I know, not exciting. "We Are we there yet, Captain?
Almost, Woo. We are ready to pull anchor.
Well then I can buy potassium.
Okay, now listen. Jules is looking for
west and south side of the island, I go to the north and east side.
- Where shall I go, Captain? -Woo You look everywhere ...
... Will let you know if we find something. "If a captain.
- I can help? "Yes, go with Woo.
They must remain vigilant. Land on the "Language ...
... Of the Snake "
I'm looking for an Inca Indian living on this island.
Can anyone tell me where you live?
Well ... well. If it's bad for Sarina. The villain, Sarina.
The killer, Sarina.
If you do not know where the Indian, I suggest you get in the ...
... Bottle from which you came. I do not want to harm them.
It is home to India.
So tell me.
So close to death, and still no answer?
I'll tell you, but it will cost.
The Indian lives across the island. I think it's a monk
If what he said is a lie, you have a death ...
... Slow and painful. "Do not expect anything less of you, Sarina.
I have not fear death. I invite every night a. ..
... Take me here, but I always left standing.
I hope that death will find you soon. "Me too.
"Money for the poor. -Si.
May God bless you.
"Look at her pretty dress. "It came by you Love.
Come on. She is good friends. Who gives me ...
... A couple of coins for it?
"Money for the poor. "Wait, I just give ...
Money for the poor.
"Here you go. "May God bless you, Mr.
"Heaven is expensive, if I come. "With a body like that, no ...
... I think you have problems. "Thank you, ladies.
Over here monk.
Look, you're a very handsome boy.
And strong too.
"Beware, the cannons can explode. "You're adorable.
"My name is Edward. What's yours? "I'm Madelin, a pleasure.
"This is Cristina. -Cristina, a pleasure to meet you.
It is also a pleasure to meet you.
- What is a cannibal touched? "Come and show you.
I'm afraid I can not, I'm looking for someone.
We can help you search. We know everyone on the island.
"I'm looking to pirates. "We know many pirates.
- Is not it true that if Madelin? "Of course. But it is not ...
... Good to talk about pirates on the street, going inside.
"I should not. "Come in and tell you all of the pirates
Hello, Marco.
Jules.
Did that come through that door back to my life.
"I'm not here to hurt you. "Then I guess you come a. ..
... Pick up the pieces of my broken heart and enjoy ...
... My suffering. "I do not know why I'm here, my ship came here.
- Captain of the HM are still whores? - Why did you do that?
Excuse me, can I invite you to sit for a drink?
-No. And I thought I saw you ... - Thinking what?
That would invite chaos into my life again.
"This will not work. "My life does not work, since ...
... You left me, nothing works. "For your tragedy.
What stops? Do my eyes stopped when you left me mourn?
Is my stomach stop hurting over the loss of not being touched?
Will my pain ever stop? No. No Jules never stop.
- Why should I stop now? - What can I say?
I'm a whore, a woman of the street and all that follows ...
.. Man is and like it. "It's really just ...
... Is proving a point, idiots.
Putting things into perspective. We had a couple ...
.. Decent nights of sex, do not be dramatic. -Decent
"I was magnificent. "Yes, it was great and magnificent.
- Then why did you leave me? "I made a mistake and I regret it.
If you leave for another man, but I did not hurt.
Hurt, no. I killed him. I walk this world without ...
... Life without love, for your sake. "Okay Mark ...
... I'll leave you alone. "Even if you leave me alone would not find it.
I'm in pain with you here in pain when you leave.
Please let me see your pretty face death.
"Sit down and take a drink. - Can we live now ...
... And only now? -Si.
"We started already. "We'll take that.
Baby baby, lives at night. The past, the dust and the future ...
... Is jarizneo in the wind. Bebe. This night will be memorable.
Father, forgive me, but I have sinned.
What are your sins, son? Why is this man tied up and blindfolded?
"He's not incumbent. "Any man ...
... Suffering in the house of God is my problem. "I'm looking to a ...
... Inca Indians living and working in these walls?
"I can not help. "Let me warn you before you speak.
If you try to lie, I'll let this sword in his skull.
Who you are and what the hell are you doing here?
"Do not call the devil in vain. - Why would hurt a. ..
... Another man? "Because I can.
"Surrender to God and your soul will be saved. "All of you ...
... Coat men are equal. They always want to save souls.
I'll ask one more time. And then he causes so much pain ...
... Your soul will feel in heaven. "I do not fear death or to you.
Well, Sarina tied to the father to the altar. I think it's time for ...
... Confess your sins to Father Victor Stagnetti.
Is Captain Victor Stagnetti? May God help us.
Save Worry about yourself.
"This a little slow tonight. -Cristina, why not look at Edward rum?
"I should not. "A little will not hurt you.
Also, you look tense.
You know, I've been under pressure lately.
"Here you go sweetie. "Thanks.
Damas.
It's good.
"I'll get another. "Okay.
Let's rest that beautiful body.
I'm looking for a pirate.
A pirate name ...
This fabric is so soft, what is it?
India is silk.
So soft.
Not these lips softer than silk.
Toca.
Yes, they are very soft.
Thank you.
There's more where that came delights.
Are kissing with tongue.
Do not worry about them.
"He is of us, bitch. "Ladies, ladies, ladies ...
... Please. There will be no fights, not when Captain Edward ...
... Reynolds is here to save the day. There will be blood.
What was he talking about?
You were saying you wanted to take us to Cristina and my ...
... To the room. - Does that tell you? I do not remember.
Yes, let's talk about this in a more comfortable place.
Do not even think to follow us.
The name of the pirate look is ... is ...
Let's talk about this pirate later.
Yes, let's talk about dreams and fantasies.
- What do you mean? "Everyone has dreams.
The other day I dreamed that my cock was a stick ...
... Spanish giant to hang people.
-No. What is it which always dream to be? "The best game pirates ...
... The world has ever known.
Your wish is our command.
Close your eyes and imagine that the bed is your warship.
These floating on a sea of treasures.
"It's night and these sleeping. "The eyes of a pirated game ...
... Are always open, always awake, vigilant. Willing ...
... To battle instantly. -Details. They always have many details.
Through the darkness, snow, fog. A pirate game ever ...
... Looking for prey. Nothing will stop me and nothing for me.
Pirates attack. It's time to taste the wine pirate.
Do you have wine?
His sword is massive.
"We do not fear their weapons. "Yes, Captain.
Say it. I just hunting pirates in the world.
You're the best hunting pirates in the world.
I just hunting pirates in the world.
That was incredible.
Thank you.
A night to remember.
Good sex, drinking and knowing the pirate ...
... Feared the world. - Who would that be?
The first lady of Captain Victor Stagnetti, Sarina.
- Victor Stagnetti Did you know? "No, I met the first lady.
"I almost cut. - What were you doing here?
No, I was looking for an Inca living in the missions ...
... On the west side of town. - Did he say when he would go?
No. Why do you care?
I'm just curious about pirates.
-Jules, I love you. - What?
I love you.
Okay.
So?
- What can I say? "Nothing.
- Nothing? "Nothing.
"It must be something, Marco. "I say kill ...
.. Love me too. - What happened to "yesterday is dust y. ..
... Tomorrow is a jarizneo "" "The future is here y. ..
... I do not want much.
-Marco. "You know ... go.
"Go with another whore. "Enough.
- Where are you going? "It is clear, try to enjoy ...
... Tonight you and it is clear that not to happen.
-Jules, please do not go. "Do not say a word.
Perhaps I acted on, perhaps I was very dramatic. My mother ...
... Always thought it would be a great actor. "So please ...
... Believe that I will not go, and so will not be alone.
No Jules. Where do you go? I can not lose again.
Where ya no. Jules I can not go through this again.
Why did you leave me stupid bitch?
I feel used.
Ladies, that was exquisite.
"The pleasure was all ours. Here's your coffee-loving.
Thanks dear.
Get out. The longer term.
I must say, I'm a little nervous with you here.
Cristina and Madelin told me that you're a Pirates game.
I always wanted to meet a real pirate hunting.
"I'm just a man, a great man. "You look so strong.
-No pirate can with brute force. "It is not so ...
... I've beaten so many pirates, my wisdom is the sea ..
... Which has guided me so well.
Not only are beautiful, your words are poems.
It is not easy to be so smart. Sometimes people do not understand what ...
... I say. "The captain could not Stagnetti your cunning.
- Have you heard of Captain Victor Stagnetti? "Yeah, right.
"Everybody. He is in town now. -Victor, are there?
Some of his men had just left the room black.
"The black room, where is that? -2 Blocks to the left
- What will you do there? "I was born to do.
"Hunt and kill pirates. "You're so noble. Kiss me.
I must go.
I'll go with you. Together we will fight against Victor.
No, this is something I must do alone.
No, please. I can not stand the smell of here now. Not even ...
... I can take away the stench of the pirates, of my body.
"Please. take me with you. "I must go.
But when I return, I will ensure that those pirates ...
... Dirty, do not return to play.
Edward, I love you.
I have to go.
"No, I need you. -Cristina, help me.
Come on girl, let it go. You must work.
I never want to work here. I found my great love.
Let me go.
I'll be with you soon, love.
Your pain tolerance is incredible.
Why do not you tell me where she lives the Indian? Not hurt.
"I made a promise. "It's a matter of time, I'll find him.
- Why did you doing this? "Because it's so bad ...
... That makes it more enjoyable.
Sarina, wipe the blood from his lips, I hear ...
... Your pain clearly.
My daughter, you're good, God help you.
"It's too late. "Let God be the judge.
I'm glad you mentioned that.
"Let him alone. "In good time ...
... Would not you missed it. -No.
Why did that?
"Excuse me, old friend. "You've gone into the world ...
... Running. And see the evil that caused this man.
I am a descendant of the night. It is your duty to show ...
... I want to see.
Follow me.
Sarina, hides the body of the father. Watch.
"When I was young, wanted to be a magician. "A magician, why?
- Why not a magician? "I like that.
The captain will be pleased with that.
My mother taught me how to make black powder.
Someday I'll be a magician, and perhaps I will see my father again.
How about you?
What will you be?
Isabela, Isabela, where are you?
Where is the blade of Atahualpa?
If you fail, you will drown in the blood of the innocent.
Know that you are not a true descendant will die.
And we all, we will drown in the blood of ...
... The innocent. -Continued.
There you are.
Are you still alive?
-Si. "Well.
And collects the stones set him free.
Alto.
I know you're not a father, but I must confess to someone.
Follow me, daughter.
Tell me your sins.
I have killed many men.
Reza 7 Hail Mary and 10 Our Fathers.
"That's not all. "Proceed.
I had unprotected sex marriage to men and women.
"I participated in many orgies. - Really?
- What? "Continue.
I have helped in the murder of a priest.
I do not want this life.
I want all these deaths stop.
Can you hear me brother?
O Brother?
Sarina, you're doing.
I hear something.
Here our work is done. It was such a beautiful ...
... Ceremony was the father. We will come back.
Sarina communion can participate in next time.
Let's go to this island.
"I have no more money for you. -Edward.
Jules I have ...
"I have something to say. "Me too.
Me first.
Then, I went to cannon balls pink, at first ...
... When she walks in the door and the door does not match ...
-Edward. -Si.
Anyway, by my great intellect and a little ...
... Research, I discovered where now, as ...
... Speak, on this island, where Victor Stagnetti.
Why have this robe?
- What do you say? She's a whore to the bone. "His bun or even ...
... This dry yet and go for another.
- Who are you? "Shut up, lover of earth.
"Mark, why do this? - Is this your new victim?
No, I know him since we were young, my captain.
- What is that? "Tell you what it is.
Captain is a sexual nickname ... means. Sea Witch
"I love you so much. I wish that neither existed. "And when you act like this ...
... I wish you exist. "Shut your mouth.
"She did not hurt more men. - What does that mean?
That means I will not let you hurt other men.
"This is a misunderstanding. "Silence.
-Both die. - What?
Surprise.
Do not worry, do not hurt, but if you do not stop
it hurt to move around, relax and enjoy.
Look what we have captured.
- What should I do with it? "Take off your clothes.
Want to see what's under this dress?
"Let go, you're hurting me. Spanish-spirited.
"Keep fighting them like it. "Let me go.
I let you go about these things.
Is this what I wanted to see?
Yes.
"I kill when I'm free. "When you're free to call me hot
I will not give the pleasure to call you hot.
So, you want to be difficult?
I'll show you what we do with your type.
If I cut will play the part of you who touch me.
"To bitch, I bite my nipples. "I really like.
I liked this.
"I'm married. "Better.
Para.
That feels good.
Do not stop.