Sit.
How do you feel today?
Today is a great day for you, eh?
Your last meeting as a guest
in this place.
Three years is a long, does not it?
Must feel great.
Climber upset sentenced
to 3 years in mental institution.
- It's going well, mate.
- And I appreciate your help.
Walter, my friend, you are able
to inspire a book.
I'm thinking of a complete chapter.
I'm waiting for arrives
spring and has more market share.
It is the story of a man who
climbing accident ...
short rope hanging
his friends to save himself.
Mountaineering accident leaves three dead.
Sole survivor arrested.
The murder conviction
without premeditation.
Sounds attractive.
Technically, I made an agreement
with the prosecutor.
Yes, and technically means that
I plead guilty.
I have only a formality.
These are your appointments for the
next year.
- But the judge said ...
- The judge does not determine the need ...
to continue treatment, I do.
The fact that you think is really
you leave these walls, ...
not mean that we have completed
with our work.
A year of compulsory treatment.
- And then you reevaluate.
- I understand that what I did was wrong.
I know that three people died
for what I did.
- Sorry.
- I believe you.
Otherwise, do not give
probation.
But we are having problems
the question of the decision.
I realize that I could
have taken another decision that day.
See, this is where the sincerity
becomes questionable.
Because I remember your
exact words, Walter and you?
You said "anyone could have
made the same decision I did. "
Either.
I do not think so.
Those are just words, Walter.
Let's see how you doing out there.
One year.
Continue treatment.
Sign and return to your room.
You know what that is, Walter?
Progress.
Progress does not mean
that we're done.
What we seek is complete.
Murder theory
Hey, look down the camera and
the road, man.
No, not until I read Nicole
seriously.
I love you.
Seriously, when was the last time
we passed through a gas station?
- I look forward to urinate.
- I would have got if ...
we did not have to wait
quickie for you by morning.
For the umpteenth time, we fell asleep.
Since you took it to her as the
seriously, do not share even a small detail.
You're a loose, bro.
- He is a gentleman.
- Thanks, baby.
Brent, tell me, do you wonder about
Amber and you all the time?
What do you know?
She shaves,
I, too, is a spectacle ...
Brent, enough.
The bathrooms are on the right.
Brent, my friend, I love
this damn house.
In case you had not noticed.
Son of a bitch.
Hey, Freddy, sexy sister
at 12 o'clock.
I will not engage with the sister
Brent, is disgusting.
Sister, right? I know I
you like or pale or red, ..
but it is not as red or
so pale. You're going to take.
I did not know they came this weekend.
I did not know he had to say when
I come to stay at home.
If you were going to bring some friends,
sorry, the rooms are full.
It is not all misery and desolation.
I am alone, does no wrong.
Walk in things
strange girl.
- What return?
That's Alex.
If it helps, Nicole and I can
sleep on the portal.
A little love outdoors.
Hello, beauty.
Is the wonder drug
you nervous?
Do not play doctor with me. Please
were safe, do not they prescribed.
You know who prescribe anything.
Especially on Tuesdays and
Thursdays.
Dr. B. loves
the earring from my navel.
I bet it is.
The problem is that my friend
could not your size.
- Stop ashamed, guys.
- Tell them you do not need their help.
She would be lucky to be with you.
- I'm Jennifer.
- Hi, Alex.
- Nice to meet you.
- Hey, Freddy.
Go, Dad.
Do not be fooled by the physical,
has a heart of gold.
The girls at school
Freddy Teddy tell.
But the eye is a tornado
between the sheets.
- It's a lie.
- Freddy.
Azar's your specialty, right?
Make the favor and starts.
I will make a bartender
if you show the barbecue now.
The bar is officially open.
What are you looking?
I can not believe Dad
Brent has left all this.
I think Brent's dad has more
toys at home than it can use.
But Amber loves that.
Be nice.
Well?
How long have you
Enli you?
"Enli?
One year.
- Great.
- I think I understand.
All are in pairs, right?
Yes, you're alone and I also.
But I'll leave this clear.
You look like a nice guy,
but ...
I'm not into nice guys.
Never even slept with
a teddy bear as a child.
Well, I'm staying in the room
and you on the couch.
- Nice to meet you.
- Sounds good.
This is crazy.
Do not tell me you have not thrown tipas
of all colors in this boat.
This boat really
gives me joy.
Over here.
Well, be careful.
This is very gangster.
I'm Tony Montana.
Partner, why not have it at home?
By idiots like you.
Will you let me shoot it once?
Tomorrow, right? When we get in
the boat, you can shoot it.
Why have one of these
if you can not send even a message?
Can you?
Come on, we are adults.
The last time we did this
was on that cruise ...
did last year.
- It was a fun trip.
You're a liar, I spent the whole
bugging time that ...
take me to the spring festival.
- Yes, it was.
Below.
But now that I think I recognize that
were the best vacation of my life.
- I can not believe we leave
to graduate. - Oh, do not mention it.
- Will not you graduate?
- No, not really.
Is that when reaching
the end, you realize that ...
not have everything you wanted.
I was not mature enough
to realize what was important.
- Amber ...
- Relax, just kidding.
We no longer walk with jueguitos
long.
"Last summer you think
long?
We had ten hours drinking, was
Error binge. You know.
Let's spend some time
with others or something.
- Before the drinks?
- Yes
It's like a tradition.
I swear, whoever it has been
come to think that "151" with ...
Tabasco sauce was a good drink,
should be killed.
It's a disgusting drink,
that's the point.
- Freddy, "as are the burgers?
- No, I'm cleaning the ...
Well, let marinate meat.
Okay.
Thanks, bro.
- What?
- Do not tell me that you will give the ...
big guy a roll of charity?
What is that? "Protection
half brother?
Alex, I think your mom seems
pleasant, but the fact that ...
by chance your mom is
next to my dad ...
and you come included in the package,
does not make us family.
Okay, because to me your dad
is just the moneybags number 5.
Health brother.
Do you remember the girl he
Freddy spoke last weekend?
- Yes, the dark one of the party.
- Yes
At the end of the night, she gave
Brent a blowjob in the bathroom.
- Poor, Amber.
- In other words, poor Freddy.
I know you're partner
Amber Quarter and all that ...
But Brent is not a paragon of virtue.
She needs to know.
We are staying at his house, right?
"Brother, can you prepare meat
for hamburgers? "
Idiot.
"Could you prepare a hamburger?"
We will prepare, to prepare you.
A little hot sauce
for Adobe.
And a pinch of salt.
I think so you know well.
Enjoying your food?
This is the best burger in the world.
How is yours?
- Have a little.
- If you take whiskey, you're going to drop fire.
I do not drink whiskey after dinner,
that's you.
Hey, what's that?
Oh, my God.
Look for a room.
Come on up there to get away
of others.
- We have not yet provided.
- Then do it.
- I will later.
- Dress handcuffs.
Listen, guys.
As we are all about to graduate
and next year we almost all ...
in different cities, I think
imposing a toast.
It was not my idea.
Jennifer, I think I never
I told you this, ...
but we are all
very glad you came ...
because the girl he left
Mikey before you, ...
- Leave her alone.
- What?
- Here.
- Son of a bitch.
- What was it?
- Say you had arms ...
strangely short.
- Mikey.
- Oh, Mikey.
Thank you for taking the item,
I appreciate that.
I can not believe to be
admit this, but ...
The first time I saw
was shawns Rock.
You used the short white shirt
and pair of jeans with the hole ...
in the right place.
- Quick.
Oh, God.
And all I remember is that I
I was incredibly nervous ...
because he knew he was approaching
to speak, had to do ...
but had no idea what to say.
I guess what I'm saying ...
is that they have been about four years
beautiful y. ..
I want everyone to know that I could not
having shared with better people.
- Health.
Wait a minute.
I know I did not attend school
with you, but can I say something?
- Of course.
- Is this OK?
Thank you.
For my fast friend, ...
who go to bed with a
Templones lot of university.
Come on.
- Is that going to kill you?
- Tastes like piss of old.
Gotcha.
Oh!
- Come on down.
- No.
Slowly.
- You are so beautiful.
- And I'm with you.
I am sitting here.
You have to work a little
before reaching it, baby.
"Kid?
What the hell did you do?
- What the hell happened!
- What happened!
Move it, damn it, move it!
- Nena.
- What the fuck!
Oh, my God.
It must be a joke,
no tone!
Somebody close the window
now.
What happened?
What the hell happened!
I do not know, I was out.
Hello? Hello?
Crap.
- What the hell is this?
- Oh, God, what the hell does that say?
TV
Turn it on.
I love you.
Please
- What gives you the gun?
- Please, please.
Oh, God, Carlos.
- What are you doing?
- Continued, Nicole.
What the hell is that?
Pull the trigger.
- What the hell!
- Turn around, turn around.
She saved you, Carlos.
These were my best friends.
If someone had asked me when
I threw this picture, if the kill ...
I would have said was impossible.
But I did.
Nicole had the same option
with all of you:
Ending the life of another person ...
to save your own.
Now death is certain
for everyone in the house.
There is only one solution: kill their
friends or die with them.
- If they escape they will die.
- Turn it off.
If at 6:00 a. m is one
live alone, is free.
But if one is more alive
at 6. 00, all die.
Bastard!
- Why did not you hear that?
- I was unconscious of drunkenness!
Brent!
- Brent, what are you looking for!
- My dad has a rifle.
- And now that you mention?
- Not now, blanquita of the underworld.
- Fuck you, asshole!
- Hey, look for the rifle.
- You okay?
- Yes
- The rifle went missing.
- Disappeared?
Are pictures of us?
What the hell.
This was two months ago.
Will being followed?
He has been stalking.
The rifle was their first strategy.
They will have to improve.
Now look around you,
Who do you trust more?
In their boyfriends, their girlfriends?
Who do you trust less?
In the narcissist?
In the intruder?
Maybe the guy who put tabasco
in the burger of your friend?
In the next three hours show
how to live.
Away from me is impossible, so
begin to think about ...
how to escape from each other.
Only one back home.
What do we do?
- What about your neighbor?
- Or make a fire?
- We can set fire to something y. ..
- Listen to me, no one is 80 kms
God, how and why simply
not we leave?
Brilliant, the guy probably is
up a tree ...
rifle with my dad for
keep us out.
We will close the doors and put a
trap if you try to enter the house.
Crap.
- Easy.
- No, I will stay ...
to wait until it destroys us crazy.
- Has a gun.
- We.
Carlos, a partner, no!
- It's going to get my gun.
- Hello, is anyone there?
Did anyone hear me?
Hello?
- What do we do?
- Forget what you said bastard.
Just trying to scare us
for us to separate.
Let's go, close the doors
and windows and wait ...
to return the boys.
Well, come on.
Grab a chair.
Carlos, wait!
What are you doing!
Please stop!
Watch the boat!
It is sinking!
- Stop!
- What the fuck do!
- Come!
- Shit! Shit!
Opened!
Shit!
- This will not stop!
- But make noise if you try to enter.
Help me, dammit!
Help!
- Resist, resist.
- Help me!
Resist, my friend.
Resist.
Oh, God.
Do not shoot, do not shoot.
Sorry, partner.
We must leave here.
We have to get out.
We can not leave without them!
- If you are returning.
- Man, that's very strong.
We're screwed.
Alex, this is the end.
We all die.
Why are we so quiet?
Hey, relax.
Please.
Maybe he's right.
Maybe we should go to the truck
and leave.
Baby, we must
them more time, OK?
Amber, get away from the window.
Come here.
Return.
- Where is Carlos?
- Close the door!
- Where is Carlos!
- He's dead.
He's dead, dammit.
I found a kind of trap.
Wait, what's a trap!
What do you mean!
- A sort of bear trap!
- No!
It was not for bears, it was to mankind!
- Let me out.
- Move back, not go out.
This is very bad, man.
This is very bad.
- Where did you put the damn key?
- You had it.
Damn, I should have another copy.
What is all this shit!
Of all the damn places ...
had to choose just one!
- I know that look.
- What look?
Did not tell us everything
happened out there.
Is to see my friend bleed
out there.
So I know when you're cheating.
Not now, Amber.
It's our little game: wonder where
you've been and you invent something.
He is a half truth because it makes
those who know how to lie.
You should have avoided
Part of the girl.
You have the look of when
do not say it all.
I am alone in this house.
There is a fucking murderer out there
and I am alone in this house.
Hey.
Look, I may not be the groom
wonder or anything like that ...
but I will not let anything happen to you.
I wanted to talk alone.
Brent do not trust that gun.
Nena, Brent can be an idiot
arrogant at times, but ...
do not shoot us.
All I know is that left two
people and only one returned.
I do not know, I'm too busy thinking
in how the two of us will come of this.
- It's very bad.
- We are well screwed.
- God, I'm fucked, you're screwed ..
- Partner ...
Freddy!
Erase from your mind.
Come sit here.
We are well screwed.
Freddy, we could die tonight, well
why do not we go to fourth y. ..
we get to work?
Maybe it's our last chance.
Really?
No, but at least I made you think
something else.
Relax.
Want to know what's what
I told them not to others?
Sank my boat.
I think he put the gun because
wants you to use.
As Nicole.
Maybe.
Who cares?
We'll sit in a corner,
away from windows ...
and if that damn patient falls,
I killed him.
Promise you will not let it
nothing bad happens to me.
Of course.
Within a month, we'll be drinking
to pass out in shawns Rock.
How can you be reading?
I try to think of anything else and unless
you want to go out there ...
and find out how to get out of here
this is the best I can do.
Why are they all so calm?
Could they all leave
break my things?
"We sat
waiting to kill us!
- Freddy, you have to calm down.
- Do not even know if it is outside.
Yeah, sure, Barbie, do not you see that we
being manipulated like puppets?
If we stay here, we all die.
We must get to the truck.
- And we have to leave here.
- Yes
Yes, and the guy who sent us the
creepy video ...
sure did not do anything to the truck.
- At least we must try.
We're staying seated
so quietly!
- It's okay to feel afraid.
- Freddy, we're with you.
No, no, I gotta go.
I gotta get outta here.
Yes, as if you were to go.
Sit!
- You're scaring the chicks.
- Hey, listen.
Our best chance
we hold together.
- No, we must leave here.
- Freddy, that's what he wants.
He wants me to go into panic.
You have a panic attack at me.
- No.
- Breathe.
No, I can breathe.
Let me go.
Oh my God!
Are you out there!
- He must have brought.
- This is really screwed.
- You said she was dying.
- Leave me alone.
- What happened at the berth?
- I thought he was dead.
I am not a doctor, dammit.
We have to take him to a hospital
now.
Sure, call an ambulance.
- What is it?
- Do you think it will survive if we leave?
Guys, if we're not
now, die!
- Guys ...
- I assure you that this crazy ...
wants us to go to the truck, is
the first thing that occurred to him.
Brent, If I carry myself,
give me the gun?
- No way.
- Fuck you.
Brent left me.
Did he say anything?
Baby, what happens?
Shit!
Jennifer, what's up!
- Carlos says Brent abandoned him.
- Of course, I thought he was dead.
Shit!
If someone wants to stay until
morning, you can.
Jennifer and I took Charles to
hospital because otherwise die.
And if you do not like it, fuck you.
I'm going.
I'll get the truck.
Stationarity against the portal,
but I will not without the gun.
No, if you give the gun not return ...
and be a pile of corpses.
- Brent is right, we think.
- No time. Good luck.
- Thanks.
Take care.
When she returns, you take the gun
Charles and I, okay?
Well, smartass, we will sit here
expected to turn the keys ...
of the van and all listen
and walks away.
Goodbye sister, farewell gun.
Help me, I will argue for
you by the arms and legs.
- Careful.
- Mikey.
- Do you really believe that's a good idea?
- I do not see you die.
Well, but you will be responsible
they kill us all.
Are not you coming?
Hurry.
Careful.
Brent.
Come on!
Do not fall asleep.
- What will we?
- Do not know.
- You have to start it.
- I'm doing!
- I'm trying!
- I told you!
Fuck it.
Now they're hanging from a rope.
Are escalating at a time
and the next seeing certain death.
The hook was giving because
I could not bear the weight of all.
I was closest to the top.
Shall I get the knife from my belt?
I cut the rope and they fall?
I looked down and all
was so quiet, so perfect.
And then I cut.
One by one their cries faded.
Hers was the last to
left to hear.
And I survived.
I had ten seconds to decide.
You have until 6:00 a. m
Right now they have to
sacrifice someone
Send a person
outside. They have 60 seconds
Crap!
What the hell!
- It gasoline
-50 Seconds
- Leave us alone!
- Give me that damn gun right now!
- Calm down!
- Damn!
Stop fighting!
Okay, I'll shoot for
outside. Everybody ran towards the trees
- Go in different directions
- We will die if we tried that
40 seconds
To hell with this
- Do not even move
- He's dead
We're going to burn, dammit! Everyone!
Anyway kill us!
No, no, it will
If we do this for him, he will not
30 seconds
He has lost too much blood
Look, Michael. Gonna die
- Do not talk about it, damn it!
- Look at her!
-20 Seconds
- Love
15 seconds
To hell with this! No!
Mikey
Run! Run!
We are taught to bury
but primary
Basically, we are all murderers
I tried to tell them, guys
He planned it all
This truck, pistol, all
Do you think we going to let live?
Stop talking as if
knew the fucking guy
- Stop talking like that!
- Are you going to shoot?
- You going to shoot?
- I will not shoot you, you bastard
I will run, if not trigger follow me
Do not leave me
Wait! No!
Okay, grab the gun
and returns. See you there
- Shit!
- What are you doing?
- Come on!
- Dale!
Freddy opens the door!
- Freddy, go!
- Open the door!
Freddy, go!
Come in, come
Please, please
There is no escape
Only the choice of dying with your friends
or survive on your own
Decides
- Charles died?
- Was the only option
- Where is Alex?
- The shooter shot
- And Brent?
- I left
Fuck you!
You are a piece of shit!
See? Did you see?!
- What can we do?
- Do not know
But we must stick together
Why do not we?
We are monitoring all
You know we can do
What will happen at 6
point? Have you considered that?
We should leave now
We have a weapon. No
I will let anything happen to us.
Just try to calm down
Give me that
You know? For as you looked before
I thought you played before me
- What?
- We are alone
And so we die
Outside there's a guy making us
kill each other
Inside ...
.. Our friend Michael has a gun
It is the best man I ever met
And it is exactly why
which I know they both die
It makes no sense what you say
If you have to make a decision "to
choose who you think Michael?
I prefer to Jen before me
Do you really think you will choose?
And would choose Jen over himself
That love will kill us both
Do not say that!
Freddy, you are sitting
beside an open window
He speaks softly
- I thought we had left
- Never leave my crew
Especially after
I found a way out
- What?
- The boat
- Probably also broke
- I checked
All he did was take the keys
but I have an extra copy
- And he must not know
- Well, I'm going to tell Michael ...
No time for group discussion
We must act
Why not?!
Did you see how it is
Michael behaving?
He has the gun and sends
- What if I do not want to go?
- Yes, but if we say on the boat ...
We can not risk
While you have the weapon,
makes all decisions
- I will not leave
- We will not let anyone
Everyone goes. We only need
weapon for the last word
That's all
Jen did not trust me
This means that
Mikey does not trust me
I can not get close enough to the weapon
but they trust you, Freddy
Everyone in this house need your help
You said it yourself. If
we stay, we die
- I can
- Yes you can
I really can not
You want to live?
Amber Where is Freddy?
- It wants to be alone
- Mikey
Remember ... the first year?
"Those guys who made fun of me?
You defended me
And you knew you were
my roommate
I do remember
I just ...
I wanted you to know that I appreciate that
Listen, friend
We will not say goodbye yeah?
I'm so sorry
- That's
- Stand, Amber
That is, give it to me
Give me the gun!
- Now, Freddy!
- Do not give the gun
No, I have the gun. I will go to pot
Brent told me that the boat sank
- What I said is that ...
- Was it a lie?!
- Look, Freddy
- I said no!
- I am so scared
- I know that yes, friend
We're all scared, man
This is not the way
Fuck! Fuck me!
Fuck me!
Movieras told you!
Do you know why am I here?
Because I scholarship
with you in first year
If that had not happened,
parties would have made me!
That's not true! And you know
We're repeating this for
convince you to do this
Detente
What happens when morning comes?
What if you have
choose between us and Jennifer?
- You know that will not happen
- That was not what I said!
I said what if ...
What if that happens?
So, Freddy. So do not
can make decisions
- Now give me the gun
- Please!
As if he knew that
going to shoot us all!
What are you talking about?
Just because you do not sing a Margot
mean you're smart
It is a reality, you're a fucking murderer!
I could have gone. But I am back for you
Now give me the gun
Give me the gun, fat bastard!
How did you feel last week?
- What?
- Come on! You know what I mean
Let How did you feel?
- What are you talking about?
- I bet you do not even know your name
But you had right?
Of course for everyone to know
that are stronger and I am weak
By God! Give me the gun
How do you feel now?
Do you feel weak? Do you feel insecure?
As the bloody fat! Fuck you!
What you gonna do, eh?
- Are you going to kill us all, Freddy?
- No, rude boy, only you!
Freddy, do not shoot
Come on, man. Dale, just go
- Just get out okay?
- God, Freddy!
When dawn will be the only
here with the gun do you hear?
Just me and the gun!
Now go
If you force us to leave, is
as if we shot yourself
- Do not want to die, old
- I know not
Love, okay. Okay
Freddy not shoot us
because Freddy is our friend
Charles also was our friend!
Go away!
- Down
- Out!
You said it yourself
We are alone
What I said is that ...
... both going to die
I want you, Mikey!
I want you
If you want us to leave,
have to come and shoot
Please, please just go away!
Come, look me in the eyes
and pulls the trigger
- Love, not
- OK
You're like a brother to me
And right now you
altered. We all are
That's not the way
So, Freddy
Okay
I told you to give me
the gun, fat bastard
Go forth now, and let you live
But if you do ...
... will come for you
Is there light here?
Find it
Damn!
Over there
Okay, when we leave
run and never look back will you?
You run up to the motorcycle
Let
All right, stay down
Wait till you get closer to exit
Oh God!
- You can do this
- It's the only way, brother
This is about survival
At least give us the
opportunity to say goodbye
- You owe me
- You are my partner
I regret that you
to die like this, but ...
I'm like you, narcissistic moron!
They have 10 seconds
I'm going to pounce
- We will kill
- If you have opportunity,
grab the gun
Sorry, really sorry
Trompe this, bastard!
Jesus!
Are you okay?
- Let
- Amber, we
Let
- It's fucked!
- Do not look
- What can we do?
- It's almost 6
We return to the
corner with the gun. Let
That is not working What about Amber?
What about her? I do not think
to be out of that basement
What if it does? What will we do, shoot?
- What!
- Did you see what he did to Brent?
- I saw it save our lives. Yes ..
- We can rely more on it!
He can not stop bullets OK?
What we do
is returning to the corner
It is our best chance.
Going into a corner
and expect to come to us
You're not listening!
We have to flee
You saw what happened to
Alex when he tried
That guy is out there. Love,
can see what we are doing
- You can not stay here!
- Please, Jen
- If we go, we die
- If we stay here, we die!
... use this
- Michael, down!
- What the hell are you doing?
- Where'd you get that weapon?
- I found
- What do you mean you find her?
Remain calm the two
You were pointing to Michael, bring it down
Low yours
Do not shoot him. It is the only
why I came back
Put your guns down two.
Put your guns down the two!
All pretend that's not true,
but everyone knows that I love
So I'm screwed
taking so many pills
It's not my fault that I love
This is no time for this
I love you and I know I messed up
but is torture
see you with someone else
Put it down
Jennifer, she did not shoot us only ...
Put the gun down and then talk
I know you love me too
- Since when? In first year?
- Jennifer!
Do you think you have
with him is so special?
Not true
If you really loved not
you had secrets from me
What are you talking about,
last summer?
He confessed the next day
We overcame. He does not love you, Amber
- Give me the gun, Amber
- Amber, do not
- Give me the gun
- I guess that is the end then
Amber, put the gun
She is the girl
that boys marry
and I'm the girl who
the boys singen!
God
Oh, God
I had to do it right?
I was going to shoot
- What are you doing?
- I was there!
The basement
Go, Michael
Should not be here.
Should not be here
We still have a chance and she did not
She is the one more chance
Stay behind me
- Shoot
- We have to wait
- Keep approaching you, you bastard
Keep getting close
You gave
God!
Love, we gotta go.
We gotta go, go
Jen, I need your
help. I need your help
No time for this
- Jen, listen
- It's going to kill us
Never happen, you can not touch us
Look ...
- I'd kill for you
- Is the only way
I loved you so much
And could not even realize
Yes I did
I'm so sorry
Stop!
End, sick bastard
It's finished
We did go through
all this to prove something
But I never considered a thing
Were you crazy before
cut that rope
And guess what?
Never ... I seem to you
We'll see
Speech by Dr. Karl Truftin
He has contacted my office
- Leave the message
- Hello, Doctor
I want to talk with you in person
I have a new chapter for his book
Remember when you forced me to say
others would not take the
same choice I made?
He was wrong, and I proved my theory
Do you know what it's called, Doctor?
Close