- Connor, breakfast is ready
- Good morning mum
- Good morning
- Hi dad
Lord, thank you for your continuous provisions
upon this family
Thank you for the hands that you used to create
this food we're about to eat
We'll be always grateful for the things you give us. Amen
- Amen
- So, what are your plans today?
- Not much, just school.
- Are you going to the Bible study  later, right?
- I don't know. I don't think I can.
I've to help out with this after school dance.
- What dance?
- The Senior's Prom.
- I didn't know you were helping to plan the dance?
- I wasn't, but Alex asked me to help, so...
- Alex...
You can tell him you're busy this evening.
You're going to Bible study.
- Dad.....
- No!
- Jim...
- I don't like you to hang out with him.
You know that.
- I have already promised him, so...
- I don't care why. I've said no!
- Why you always do this?
- He is a homosexual.
- He is a Christian. He is just like us.
- No homosexual is a christian or
follower of God for that matter
- Mum...
- I've said no!
He's always trying to get you into the wrong things.
- They are kids, Jim...
- It’s up to us to decide what they are allowed to do.
Alex is struggling and is trying to bring
Connor down with him and
I won't that let happen.!
You are not staying after school today. Be home by 3.30 !
- I'm out of here. Bye mum
- Connor...
- Okay.I'll talk you later. Bye.
- Hi
- How are you?
- I’m good. How are you?
- I'm good. We haven't talked too much lately...
- Yeah, I've been kind of busy...
- Yeah. Me too. I've been planning the dance
and it has been taken up all of my time
- I'm sure.!
I've got those fliers you wanna me to make you...
- Thank you
- Wow!! this is art.!
- Thanks.
- I've gotta go.
- The meeting is about to start. Would you...
maybe you wanna join me?
- Not today Alex. I’ve promised this girl
to go to lunch with her.
- If is about you not being gay, it's okay.
It's a gay-straight alliance...being straight...
- Alex, I'll get it, okay? I'll talk to  you later
- Hey...
- Come on. Do it for me...
Please...
- To all friends, it's already getting started...
- Sorry....
Everyone,this is Connor. He helped us on the fliers...
- Hey Connor, we appreciate your help.
We've heard a lot about you,
nice to finally meet you.
- Yeah, no problem.
- So, we're talking about our experience of coming out.
So, what's new with you Matt?
- Well, I said I've  came out to my dad last week and
he hasn't said more than two words to me
He left this book on my bed and it's called
"Men who struggle with their sexual identity"
You know, he doesn't get that
he is not gonna change who I am.
I am gay and...
I'm not gonna start pretending to like girls again and
do that all thing because...
you know, when I did that
I was feeling I was living a lie.
- So what about you Connor?
This is your first time here.
What's your view on homosexuality?
- I don't know. I was raised christian, you know, baptist.
My dad is a pastor,
so religion, kind has always been a big deal...
- What is it now,Jim?
So, you've found the paper for the school dance, so what?
He's involved in lot of things at school.
It's something most parents would love their kids to be a part of.
- It's the gay-straight alliance that he is putting in on.
He is not planning the seniors prom!
- You know Jim, you need to stop accusing him
of doing something wrong.
- He lied to us.
Since when  isn't that wrong?
- Well, I realize  that and maybe
it's for this exact reason.
You know, acting like this is not gonna bring
the two of you any closer together.
It only pushes him further away from you, every time
It's tearing our family apart.!
- You know why I do this.
You know about Alex.
And I've seen them together, Alex and him,
I've seen how they act and
it's not normal
Do you call this normal?
The fact that he's planning a gay dance?
- Okay, what exactly is normal to you, Jim?
Is it putting on a dress-shirt and a tie and going after church
or putting on a jersey and  some cleats
to go play some sport?
You see, that's your idea of normal Jim,
so everyone else!
- That's what men do, Sarah!
- What men do...
..has to show you...nothing never changes...
- What that is supposed to mean?
- Okay....
Do you remember when Connor was nine years old
and in the baseball team
and season after season you would drag him to sign up again
and he could cry and cry and cry.
But what did you do Jim?
You forced him to play.
So, what are you gonna do now?
What if Connor isn't the child you wanted?
What if he doesn't fit your idea
what the perfect son is?
- According to them in the Bible, you know,
is pretty much considered a sin.
It's the idea that if you're gay, you've been tempted
and by fire for that temptation
is just to fulfill your own greed.
Leviticus 18, 22
and 20,13 says:
”Thou shall not lie with mankind as with womankind.
It is an abomination”
- So what your parents said when you came out...
- He is not an homosexual, Sarah
- What if he is?
- I will not have that in my house or in the church.
He is a child of God.
That is how I've raised him.
- Regardless of who he is or whom he likes,
he is still our child.
You know, you may be able to force him to play baseball,
but you can't  force him to be something he is not!
- So Connor, how have you kept this idea
of accepting Alex even knowing he is gay?
Most Christians with your background
just wouldn't be as tolerant and accepting as
you seem to be with Alex
- Well, since they have been good friends for a while
I don't think anything he says
would change that, right?
I mean, he saw the same person he was before.
- Yeah, right!
- God, look at this place.
The grass's got so long since we had been here
- We've been alright.
- Outside what happened....
You know about what I told you,
you know, that I like you...
- It's fine
- It doesn’t seem fine.
Ever since I've told you, you have been distant with me.
- What else do you think was gonna happen Alex?
Of course it's gonna be different.
- I don't know.
I've always tried to do everything
and I thought was something I should tell you.
- What did you think,that was gonna tear our friendship?
- I know you're unhappy with your life
it is not just about you Alex.
Thank God you don't have to go through […....]now.
Beside you've been were so caught up in this GSA crap
that I rarely get to see you anymore.
I mean, what if you get a boy-friend?
You know, how nice...
It bothers me.
Certainly, it's a distant lately,
you know it just has been an allergy for me...
- What do you mean?
- That I think I'm gay
- What?
- Who else have you told?
- Nobody.
Just you.
- How did you know?
- Because...I like you too.
I've been worried I wont tell you for ever, but...
. Connor, you don't have to explain
- How I'm gonna tell my parents?
My dad will tell me everyday how wrong it is.
- But if this is who you are,
it will be perfect!
Besides, no matter what,
we'll still be best friends.
Wow, let's dance this coming out.
- Alex, come on....
I would love to, you know, but I can't.
- I know, I understand...
- But I've got something for you though...
- Oh, thank you. That’s beautiful..Thank you.
" You and I.
Did you feel my heart beat
next to yours in that scene?
You and I,
just you and I.
And ain't it funny how life turns the tables
in our time and you can't rewind?
All the things that felt so right,
I laid it down on the line,
You and I.
Did you feel my heart beat next to yours..."
- Are you sure you don't wanna anything?
- No, I'm okay, just turning up
-  Why? Don't wanna miss me too much.
- Yeah.
- Are five boxes
- Hey, is not that queer from our school?
Over there .
- Hey you faggot.
- Leave me alone!
- I see you're pretty you little queer
- What do you want?
- Shut the fuck up
- Did you like that?
- Let's go
- What are you gonna do about it?
- Someone is coming in Duke!
- Alex...What the hell man?
- Who are you? His fucking boyfriend?
- And what if I am?
- Come on Duke!
- Queers!!
- Are you alright? What happened?
- Don't know
- Hello?
- What happened?
- Is he alright?
- What's going on?
- So, can you tell me exactly what happened?
- He just came to help me..
- What else?
- Connor, what are you doing in here?
What happened?
- It was nothing. Just some kids wanted to fight.
It was not a big deal..
- Connor, are you alright?
- Connor, you know what did this to you,right?
It's because you were with Alex.
I told you this was gonna happen.
- Dad would you stop?
- No Connor, you listen to me.
You're better than this.
I've raised you better than this.
- No! I like Alex.
- No,you don't.
- Yes, yeah, I do.
- Connor listen to me. You don't like him.
You're confused, you're struggling with yourself.
You just need help.
- Dad, I'm not struggling with this any longer.
That's it, this is who I am.
Who is struggling is with you
trying to understand that.
- This has nothing to do with you.
- You can blame anyone you want,
but this is not Alex's fault.
- Maybe for once you can stop listening
what the Bible says
or what your friends at church are saying
and start listening to your heart
because, maybe, one day
you'll find some answers.
" “Mom and Dad ..."
- Connor...
"Don't worry about your son,
I'll be OK,
I'll take these days one by one"
- I'll owe you that.
- What?
You've been brave within there.
- I think I'll owe you a dance
- Yeah?
At the end of the day all we have is
who we are.
For now
I'll choose this life I live
And for now I'll choose to take my hits
Cuz at the end of the day all we have is
who we are
Subtitles by viandel218