How you doing?
I got it!
Pull up next to the limo.
- Natalie.
- Nice to see you.
Pardon my incredulity,
natalie,
But I'm very surprised
to see you here-
Pleasantly so, of course.
I'm a little surprised
To see myself here,
too, mary alice-
Pleasantly so,
of course.
Were you here
last year?
No. I wasn't
invited last year.
Oh. Curious.
That must have been
an accident.
Oh,
do you know libby?
No, I don't
believe I do.
Libby, this
is natalie standish.
Natalie is reed's-
Oh, is it
all right to, um...
Say that reed
got me pregnant
When I was a bar hop at your country
club, married me to avoid scandal,
Spent the next 10 years
sucking the life out of me,
Got bored with me,
dumped me
And screwed me in court?
Sure. Go ahead.
natalie is reed's ex-wife.
Oh.
Libby percy holt.
Natalie werjachewski
standish.
Well, are you
unescorted tonight?
No, I'm with someone.
A friend. Male.
Well... If the new
fella comes by,
Be sure and point
him out to us.
Oh, I don't think
I'll have to do that.
You'll know him
when you see him.
Oh, great! Aah!
Go on!
Get out of here!
Get off!
feisty little guy.
I don't care for caviar.
I make it a rule
never to eat anything
A fish deposits
in a riverbed. Right?
It's been awfully nice
meeting you...
- Dutch.
- Indeed.
Nice meeting you.
Hi. I missed you.
Hello, natalie.
- Reed standish.
- Dutch dooley.
You look... Great.
I didn't expect
to see you here.
I didn't expect to see you,
either. I thought you were
- Going down to spend time with doyle.
- Something came up.
I have to go to london
in the morning.
How does doyle
feel about that?
I haven't been able
to reach him yet.
You'll be talking to him.
You can tell him.
You haven't told him
you're not coming?
I'm sorry.
Could you excuse us?
This is personal.
Where the hell
did you find him?
Look, you can
call doyle, okay?
I'm tired of doing
your dirty work for you.
I'm being very nice to you.
I gave you a house
to live in,
- With your truck driver.
- He's not a truck driver.
Don't interrupt. You get a
monthly check, a house to live in,
And you get
joint custody of doyle.
You give me a hard time,
you lose it all.
You wouldn't dare
play fair, would you?
I wouldn't dare lose.
Have a nice holiday.
Excuse me.
I know what you were saying
to natalie was personal.
I understand.
I'm involved with her now,
So this is personal, too.
You hurt her, and I'll
hit you so fucking hard,
Your dog will bleed, okay?
Nice meeting you.
I just feel weak
and used.
He took you
out of your life,
Put you in his,
and took off.
I mean,
you don't need him,
His house, his money
or his friends.
Make it on your own.
There's only one thing
he has that I want.
What the heck
would you do with a set
Of tiny little genitals?
- I'm being serious.
- I'm sorry.
He has my son.
- Boy: Hello?
- I'd like to speak to doyle standish, please.
Oh.
Yeah. Hold on.
Doyle.
Do you know
how to knock?
- Your ma's on the phone.
- Do you know how to knock?
The door was open.
It wasn't open.
It was unlocked.
Someone from any sort of
decent background would knock.
And she's not my ma.
I don't have a ma.
You may have a ma.
I have a mother, okay?
Do you want to take
the call, shithead?
I could have you
written up for profanity.
Yeah? I'm terrified.
I will have you
written up.
Working
in the kitchen
Will be good
for you, teddy.
You can have a taste
of what your career
At burger king
will be like.
What makes you think
you're so superior?
I don't have to think.
It's sickening how much
you love yourself.
Yeah.
I guess it would be
To someone
who's enrolled here
Only because his father
is an employee.
At least
I have a father.
- Yes?
- Doyle? Hi, sweetheart.
What do you want?
I'm calling
about thanksgiving.
- What about it?
- I'd like you to come home.
For the umpteenth time,
I'll be with dad.
Dad can't
be with you, honey.
He has to go to europe.
He told me last night.
So if he's made
any plans with you,
Obviously he'll have
to break them.
I really want you
to come home, doyle.
So you can get my approval
of your new boyfriend
To appease your guilt?
Look, you are old enough
to be objective
About me and your father
and to understand
Why we're in
the situation we're in.
Yeah, I know.
I understand.
You couldn't
make it work.
If you could see both sides,
you'd know that that isn't true.
I love you, honey, and-
And I want you home.
I've booked you a flight
on Wednesday,
And I expect you
to be on it.
Forget it!
I'm not coming home
To spend a holiday
with you or the idiot
You're sharing
the house with, okay?
He is not sharing
a house with me,
- And he is hardly
an idiot!
I love you, sweetheart.
A little trouble
on the home front?
- Boys: Aw.
- What a jerk.
You talk
to your son yet?
- Mm-hmm.
- And?
I don't know.
I have a ticket for him.
I know he won't use it.
Do you want to go down
and get him?
He won't
appreciate that.
How about if I go down?
There's no better way for two
guys to get to know each other
Than spend a couple
of days in a car.
Dutch.
He doesn't want
to know you.
Well, from what
I can gather,
All he wants to do
Is sit alone in a room
and hate people.
There's a fair amount
of truth in that.
Let me go down
and get him.
I'm an interested
third party.
I'm a communicator.
I'm a breakthrough
kind of guy.
I've handled some pretty
tough birds in my time.
And when
the smoke cleared-
Almost without exception-
I had a new friend.
Smells good.
I want to do this for you.
It's important.
If we're going to be
together from now on,
I'll have to have a good
relationship with darryl.
Doyle.
What do you want?
My parents
wanted to know
If, since you're
not going home,
You'd want to come over to
our house for thanksgiving.
Don't think I could
handle that much fun.
Is that a no?
That's a no.
Great.
Have a nice weekend
Rotting in your own
pissed-off world.
Peggy, it's me.
I'm at o'hare.
Listen, I'm flying
down to atlanta
To pick up my girlfriend's kid from school.
Yeah, it came up
unexpectedly.
Tell tug and fritz
I'll be incommunicado.
They should take care of anything
that comes up. I'll be back on Monday.
Listen, lady, don't jerk me around, okay?
I have a letter from him
Saying that he's going
to pick me up.
Now, give me his number
in london.
When my father finds out
That you refused
to give me his number,
You're fired.
snatch it back
and hold it
I can't help myself
somebody's
got to help me
'cause I can't
help myself
I'm not doing
too bad, baby
you know, I ain't got
no brand-new bag
a little
he-he-he-he-he-he help.
Yo.
Doyle.
Doyle?
Dad!
Ooh!
Ooh! Aah!
Ow!
Ooh!
Aaah!
Ohh!
Stand up.
What the hell?
I said, stand up!
Hands over
your head!
I don't think
you know who I am.
Ow! Son of a-
Ow!
Give me the gun!
Aah! Uhh...
Uhh...
Uhh!
No, you don't.
Sit.
I'm dutch dooley.
I'm a friend
of your mother's.
I know she called you.
What the hell are you
beating me up for?
Ah, jeez.
I feel the pain in my crotch in my teeth.
Does campus security
know you're here?
Can you say, "I'm sorry
I hit you with a golf club,
Kicked your face,
mashed your testes,
Shot you twice"?
If that's too much,
a simple hello would do.
Answer my question.
You can't say that?
Of course I can say it.
I choose not to.
Now can you?
No.
Well, I have to shoot you.
Now, since we might be
legally related someday,
I'll give you the option
of taking it on the backside.
Won't hurt as bad.
If you shoot me...
I'll have you
arrested.
Well, I'll have to make it
look like an accident, then.
All right, you win.
Clearly. Now leave.
I told your mother I'd take
you home for the holidays.
I have plans.
Stay here? You're gonna
watch the football game,
Make a turkey sandwich,
And hang yourself
in the toilet?
I said I have plans.
Leave it at that.
Now please go.
Waiting for your dad?
I don't have to
tell you anything.
He's not coming.
You don't know my dad,
so shut up.
I know he's in london.
Is that a fact?
We have a very big
problem here.
Yeah. I suppose we do.
I have a problem because
I said I'd pick you up.
And you have a problem
Because the last guy
that punched me
Has a dent
in his forehead...
About the size
of my pinkie ring.
And he dribbles
when he smiles.
Grab your stuff.
Listen one last time.
I'm not going
anywhere with you!
What do you like to do
for fun?
Mmm!
Oh, you like to
wiggle and grunt.
Me, too.
flatfoot sam
bought an automobile
no money down,
was a real good deal
didn't want to work,
just ride around town
the finance company
put his feets on the ground
old flatfoot sam,
you're always in a jam
flatfoot sam
stole a ten-dollar bill
he told the judge
he did it for a thrill
he got 60 days,
suspended fine
he thanked the jury
for being so kind
old flatfoot sam,
you're always in a jam
I like the back roads.
The only thing you see
on the interstate
Is concrete.
You warm enough
back there?
Mmm!
You know,
I owe you an apology.
I lost my temper,
and I shouldn't have.
I was a little crazy.
I wasn't thinking
too clear, so...
I'm not 100% sure
those undershorts
I jammed in your mouth
to shut you up
Were clean or not.
Uhh!
Stop the car.
I don't think
that's a good idea.
This is only a 2-lane.
That's a soft shoulder.
I said, stop the car!
Uhh!
Ohh.
Ohh...
You can't beat a ford
for good brakes.
I'm gonna have you
prosecuted for this.
You mean like
in big people's court
Or some school teen court,
where if I'm found guilty
I got to roll
naked in the snow or...
Make a bed with my teeth?
My father is one of
the most powerful men
In the country.
When he hears
what you did to me,
He'll sue your
working-class ass
Into complete
and total destitution.
How do you know
I'm working class?
From your cheap shoes
To your ridiculous
hairstyle
To your crude vocabulary
To my mother's
taste in men...
You scream it.
Oh. All right.
Is working class bad?
If you want to get into
a political discussion,
I'll shred you.
No. It's not bad.
A solid economy
needs hand workers.
Well, I used to drive
a cement truck.
My father
was a bricklayer.
My mother used to work
in the laundry
At the pontchartrain
hotel in detroit.
You must be very proud.
I am.
I still owe you
that shot in the ass,
If you want
to get it over with.
In case it's gnawing
on your mind.
You know, you might be
the toughest
Little whacker
in the junior high,
But in my world, you're
about as worrisome
As a cloudy day.
You got
anything to say?
Me, I like to talk.
I love to talk.
Live to talk.
You got any
amusing anecdotes?
I'm living through one
right now.
There's
some truth there.
Yeah. This is a trip
We won't
soon forget, huh?
You can count on it.
Ha ha ha ha.
These are the
cumberland mountains.
Beautiful, aren't they?
Heh.
You know what?
The more you babble,
The more
you reveal yourself
As an insecure fool
who's deathly afraid
He's gonna blow
his chance with my mother.
What chance, duncan?
My name's doyle,
And the chance
I'm referring to
Has dollar signs
in front of it.
A chance
at your mom's money.
Bingo.
I may not look like
I could finance
a trip to the zoo,
But the truth is, I make
a pretty good living.
My income's a damn sight
more than your father
Gives your mother
to live on.
Oh, yeah, but my money
doesn't count
In your neighborhood...
Because I worked for it.
Working for your money
doesn't matter
In your part
of the world.
It's whose crotch the doctor
yanked you out of, huh?
You're disgusting.
have you ever seen
the night so long?
stars begin to cry
that means they've
lost the will to live
I'm so lonesome,
I could cry
Fill it up, please.
Unleaded-regular.
We're going to
have some fun now.
Do you like
fireworks?
Is that a "yes,"
a "no," a "maybe"?
Your testicles
descending? What?
Fireworks are illegal
in illinois.
Yes, they are.
But this is tennessee,
So it doesn't matter.
You're going to detonate
this material now?
Not here
in the gas station.
Are you nuts?
Go down the road apiece.
I got m-80s,
I got dragon tongues,
I got, uh...
Oh... Heh heh heh...
I don't even know
what this is.
I got jersey stinkers,
bombay bugles,
And for later,
I got a bag of pretzels,
And...
I got a deck
of racy playing cards.
Huh?
You know what?
You're like a great big
demented child.
Now, that was fun.
Can't beat a good
fireworks show.
Well, I guess
you want to eat.
Waitress: Okay, sugar,
what'll it be?
What won't
make me vomit?
I know you're lying.
Dutch: No,
we're getting along great.
Well, a few problems.
Nah, nothing serious.
till the end of
the world rolls 'round
I'll keep on loving you
as long as the sun
goes up and comes down
till the big blue sky
comes down to the ground
as long as the world
goes around and around
I'll keep on lovin' you
I tried to sail
the sea of life
I rowed my boat alone
your love meant
nothin' to me, dear
my heart
was made of stone
to a harbor filled
with loneliness
my little boat
was moored
and then the day
I first met you
I fell right overboard
till the end of
the world rolls 'round
I'll keep on
lovin' you...
so now I know
the way I felt
was only selfish pride
I thought my heart
was fireproof
but you burned
your way inside
so tell me what
I've got to do
and tell me-
Smoke bother you?
Yes.
You're asking for it
so bad.
Heh heh heh.
I'm not kidding.
You have no idea
how serious I can get
When I want to
let somebody have it.
Hmm. You know,
You might be able
to do some damage
To the small
and exclusive group
Of people
that care about you.
But... I don't think
You could raise a welt
on my fanny...
Because frankly,
I don't care
if you live, die,
Or grow mushrooms
in your crack.
I'll get you so bad.
I don't think so.
You want to put
some money on it?
How much?
$5,000.
I'll bet you got it,
too, huh?
In a little gilded box
under your bed.
We'll keep it modest.
20 bucks.
It's a bet.
Hey! Oh! Aah!
Ow!
Damn it! Ow!
Bastard! You little
son of a bitch!
Uhh!
Go to hell!
I won the bet! Ha ha!
Yah!
Throw one more-
Throw one more,
and I'm leaving you.
Promise?
Guaranteed.
Good riddance!
Here. I'll see you
at the motel...
About 50 miles
down the road.
Uhh!
Wait a minute!
Stop!
I'll die!
Uhh!
Hello.
Hello?
Shit.
You want to
close the door?
I could have frozen
to death, you asshole.
Oh, I don't think
you would've frozen.
Not solid, anyway.
It's not quite cold
enough for that.
Here's something you should
know about me, dale.
I don't screw around.
You piss me off,
I react.
I'm not your dad.
I'm not your grampy.
I'm not your uncle.
I'm a working-class
nobody,
And I don't take crap
from kiddies.
Where's my bag?
Oh, I didn't bother
to bring it in.
I figured you for dead.
Give me the keys.
Lock up
when you're through.
Doyle!
Whoa!
Just-what the hell
are you doing?
Get back here!
Damn it!
God damn...
Uhh!
Doyle.
Doyle!
I never saw a thing!
He came from
out of nowhere!
Doyle!
Doyle.
I think
this makes us even.
You're a lucky man.
Thanks.
Hey, thanks for going
along with my story.
I really appreciate it.
The kid's got
emotional problems.
The last thing he needs
is police trouble.
Take this...
Put it towards any repairs
you might have and your time.
If it's not enough,
call me.
My number's
on the card. Okay?
Thanks. I appreciate it.
If it wasn't
for your daddy,
I'd have busted
every bone in your body!
Show's over. Go home.
Go home.
Listen, you little
son of a bitch,
You could've killed somebody
with a stunt like that.
That poor bastard was on
his way home to see his family,
And because you want to play
some kind of spoiled brat prank,
You put his life
in jeopardy.
Now, what gives you
the right to do that, huh?
I guess I didn't
think about that.
You better start thinking
about a little something else
Besides your own
spoiled ass.
I took on
this idiotic assignment
Because I love your mother.
I got to wonder
how nuts I am.
Man, I've met some scum
in my life,
But you beat all, man.
You are absolutely worthless.
You know what?
This isn't a joke anymore.
This is a full-blown mission.
You're not gonna beat me.
I've had my head split open,
my nose mashed.
I've been kicked and beat
and left for dead.
When I set you down
on your mama's doorstep,
You're going to be
one whipped little puppy.
Don't flatter yourself.
Get your hands down.
I'm not taking
any more of your crap.
You touch me once more,
you'll be sorry.
You want to go? Is that it?
You want me to go?
Hell, I'd love to go.
You want to go?
Yeah.
Okay, fine.
Let's see if your punch
is as big as your mouth.
Only this time,
no sissy kicks, okay?
No geometry,
No kamikaze tricks,
no sucker punches.
Just good all-american
street fighting.
Let me show you
how to do it, all right?
Give me
your little digits.
Here. That's it.
Curl your little digits,
And you wad those up
In little bitty balls
like that.
Watch your little thumbies.
Put your thumbies out here
So you don't break them.
Get loose. That's it.
Bend your little knees.
That's it. Okay?
Let me see you fight
like a man, okay?
Now, you take
the first shot.
Give me your best punch,
all right?
Come on. Come on,
give it to me, pipsqueak.
ba-dah-ow
How'd you sleep...
Ace?
Okay.
Good.
How's your face?
Fine.
No problem.
Partial apology if I did
any permanent damage.
It's gonna take
a lot more than you got
To give me
any permanent damage.
My doctor wants me
To get my cholesterol
under 1,000,
But hot cakes and bacon
on a cold day-
Pretty sexy.
I want you to know
that I could have hurt you
A lot more than I did.
Yeah.
Seriously.
I'm a high brown belt.
Yeah?
Yeah. I've been training
for 3 years.
Your working-class ego
Can't handle a kid of
my position and standing
Beating you up, can it?
My working-class ego
can handle that
And a hell of
a lot more.
Are you admitting that
I could defeat you in a fight?
Why don't you shut up?
I beat you mentally,
Then I beat you
physically.
You know, yesterday
you had nothing to say.
Today you're a parrot.
I'm ready here.
You know, for a split
second last night,
I sort
of respected you...
For how you handled
the cops and the accident.
But today, I see my initial
impression is correct.
You're a clod.
And the cool part is...
I can say that,
And you can't do
anything about it
'cause I can
kick your butt.
Well,
I won't cop to that,
But I will say this-
There's one thing
I can do that you can't.
What?
I can pay
for my breakfast.
Nothing burps
better than bacon.
Your water looked tasty.
You're insane.
Do you have any idea
How dangerous it is
to hitchhike?
You have
a high brown belt.
What are you
worried about?
You're an idiot.
You got a better way
to get home?
We're not without means,
for god's sake.
We are at the moment.
We got 20 bucks.
You ever heard
of a telephone?
Call my mother.
I'll call my grandfather.
Someday you're gonna
get into a situation
Where you can't call
for help.
You'll have to depend
on yourself.
And you'll
let yourself down.
I'm not calling
Because I don't want
your mother to think
We can't make it home
on our own.
Call it male pride.
Old-fashioned,
Pigheaded,
working-class,
Pre-fax machine/
car phone
Masculine pride.
No accountants,
no lawyers,
No mommies, no daddies,
no washington lobbyists,
Just a man...
And his wits.
Yeah. That's helpful
When you're face-down,
dead in a ditch.
That's part of it, too.
But you roll the dice,
you take what you get.
We're not doing
too good here.
Excuse me.
Does that music
have to be so loud?
Thank you.
What'd you pay
for them shoes?
Did you steal them?
I chargedthem.
Hmm.
See, my friend here
Really wants
those shoes.
Well, we're really
moving now, huh?
It's your mother.
Come on, talk to her.
Getting hungry for
your turkey dinner?
Remember-
I'm your dad.
I got a bad heart.
Dale, look at me.
Is that your
most pathetic look?
This is my
"death to you" look.
That's not gonna
get us a ride.
Be pathetic!
Try it!
Pretend that you're not
gonna get $10 million
When you're 21.
You have no plan,
do you?
I got a rough outline.
Actually,
I'm the idiot...
'cause I'm going
along with it.
See? Hands up. Try it.
Come on.
Look up. Look up.
Come on, come on,
come on, come on.
Hurry, hurry!
It's freezing.
All right.
Oh, no.
Oh, my god.
That's it.
Smile, smile.
Smile.
That's it.
Smile with
that face.
Attaboy.
Attaboy!
Oh, help us here,
please.
It's pathetic.
It is really pathetic.
Beg.
help me.
Help me.
I don't have a ride.
We have
to help them.
That's it.
You want a ride,
You got to
look grievous.
See?
My heart.
Hey, kid!
We're going to hammond.
Do you wanna come along?
Get the suitcase.
Let's go.
We got a ride.
Come on.
Not too fast,
but not too slow.
That's it. Wave
at them a little.
That's it.
tryin' to make
a silk purse
from a drunk,
old pig now
just because
of mass hysteria
don't mean
that it's hip
I like to scare
the next-door neighbors
bring the property
values down...
You guys on vacation
or something?
We're going home to
hammond for the holidays.
Both our families
are from there.
Ah. We're
going home, too.
You got a nice kid.
Yeah.
baby, don't you know
that I'm stuck on
the wrong side
of the tracks...
So, what's the word
on you two?
How do you mean?
Well,
are you drifters?
Oh, yeah,
more or less.
Yeah,
I thought so.
How about you?
Brock?
Yeah?
Ha ha. Dutch wants
to know what we do.
Well, I don't want
to be nosy, you know.
I was just making conversation.
It's not important.
Brock: No, please.
It's fine.
No, tell him.
We're call girls.
there was
a little mansion
but it seemed
so damn run-down
baby, you are
out of luck...
I didn't want
to say "prostitute"
In front of the boy.
that I'm stuck on...
I appreciate it.
So, we were down
in new orleans
At the superdome
For the housewares
convention...
We also do
a little dancing.
Naked?
Don't worry about it.
I have a little brother.
Just on top, sweetie.
if the music
makes me money
and it brings me
lots of cash
it'll be
the outlaw country...
Doyle:
So your parents know
And they haven't
disowned you?
Ha ha.
No, not yet.
Don't you think that's
a little amazing?
Hmm... Not really.
I'm honest about it.
And I don't hurt anybody-
not on purpose.
You don't think it
hurts your parents?
Well, eventually,
if you live long enough,
You're bound to hurt
your parents somehow.
Yeah...
It's none
of my business.
So... Do you get along
with your dad?
That guy's
not my dad.
That's my mother's
boyfriend.
I hate saying that.
It's so sick.
He's picking me up
for thanksgiving break,
'cause I go
to this private school
Down south.
I hate his guts.
He's trying to
get to know me
'cause I think
he's planning
On marrying
my mother.
Is there something
wrong with that?
I'm not too crazy
about my mother
To begin with,
And he's
just a slob.
The less I know,
the better.
Yeah, well, he seems to be
going through a lot of shit
To get you home.
It's on purpose.
See, he's got this
ridiculous plan
To drag me around
until I break.
Ha ha ha.
He's got a shock
coming, though.
I don't break.
Hmm.
So, what's wrong
with your mom?
She divorced my dad,
for starters.
Yeah, well, it takes 2
to make a thing go bad.
She didn't
make it work.
You know...
Maybe it's just easier
to blame her.
You know,
maybe you should stop
Knocking your mom
so much
And try to make things
work with her.
I don't think that's
going to happen.
But I really like
talking to you.
Ha ha.
Well, maybe I'll come up
and visit you sometime.
That would
be excellent.
Ha ha ha.
Heh heh.
Brock...
Hey...
You want to wake up
your little friend
So he can stretch
his legs?
Mm.
Hey. Ha ha.
Hey... Wake up.
You want to go
for a walk?
Yeah.
Yeah. I was just
dreaming about that.
Ha ha ha.
Uhh.
What time is it?
7:30.
I'll drive
the next shift.
I'm fine. Could you
do me a favor, though?
Could you go inside
and get directions?
I just want to make sure
I don't get all screwed up.
Sure. We got
enough time to eat?
Yeah, yeah.
You go inside and we'll
take care of this
And we'll meet you
inside.
Let's go, dobie.
Uh...
I'll come in
with brock.
Uh, no,
you go ahead, babe.
I, uh...
I have to get something
from my bag.
I'll meet you
inside, okay?
Okay.
Bye.
Yes.
Yes!
I lifted
the toad's wallet.
Aah!
Oh... Why?
Because it was there.
Well...
I was just beginning
to feel respectable.
Let's not waste a lot
of time eating, okay?
I want to get back in
the car and keep moving.
Yeah.
Yeah, I know why
you want to keep moving.
Let me tell you
something, dwight.
Those 2 gals
are a couple of pros.
I got half a mind to refuse
the rest of the trip.
Do you know what
your mother would say
If she knew what
you were doing?
You refuse the ride,
I'll tell her...
In detail.
You know, you really are
a hypocrite, aren't you?
A couple of hookers...
A couple of hookers
got a set of rockets,
That's okay.
But anyone else in their
station in life is scum.
That's not true.
You and I are riding
in the back seat from now on.
Because what that
missile twister can teach you,
You don't need to learn
till you're in prison.
I'll decide what
I need to know,
And she's not
like that.
She listens.
That's her job.
Shit!
My wallet!
Damn it! Damn it!
Damn it!
I can't believe it.
Believe it.
Your angel with
the dirty wings flew...
Taking my wallet,
my luggage,
My last cigar.
She was so understanding
about my problems.
Stuff your problems!
Stuff your problems.
If you weren't such
a spoiled little worm-
Such a whining
little rodent,
I wouldn't have had
to come down here for you.
You asked for it,
and you got it.
True.
It's not my fault.
True. I know.
It's your mother's fault.
Why is it her fault?
Because
she gave birth to you.
And what about
your mother?
My mother's a saint.
For what,
having puppies?
Oh...
Oh, you want
more, huh?
Yeah, as a matter
of fact, I do.
Come and get it.
Chicken!
Ah!
Oh!
Ow.
God, you're pathetic.
Here's the deal,
dobsy.
I had 200 bucks
in the wallet.
You said
you were broke.
I lied.
You dishonest,
stupid jerk.
We had money
all this time?
We could have
been home.
Probably,
but I had this plan.
Yeah, I know.
No, you don't know!
I know you were
playing around,
Stretching this
whole thing out
So we could get
to know each other.
And then it blew up
in your face.
I blew it,
and I'm sorry.
I'm also out of ideas.
I'm just going to sit here
And hope I get arrested...
So I can get some sleep.
Call your mother.
Have her send somebody
for you.
You can call,
can't you?
I don't want to call.
I'm sitting here,
and that's it.
You talk to your mom,
You tell her
that I said good luck.
Tell her the dutchboy's
calling it quits.
You're dumping my mom?
I'm sparing her of a life
of this kind of misery.
She's going to blame me.
I'll write a letter for you,
nice letter.
Okay? Go on.
I thought
you loved her.
I've talked and talked
and talked to you
Until I could puke
coat hangers.
I'm me, you're you.
There's no reason on earth
Why we should spend
any more time with each other.
Okay. I just think
it's really sick
That you'd cut
my mom loose
Because you can't
get along with me.
Why? You hate her.
Don't fret.
It's okay.
She puts up with your crap,
she can handle mine.
I never said
that I hated her.
No. Gee, I'm sorry.
You're the picture-
is-worth-1,000-words guy.
Yeah. Now, go on.
Go on. Make your call.
Give me some peace.
I don't
hate my mother...
For the record.
Kiss my ass,
for the record!
Act like a rodent
around somebody else.
You've busted my balls.
Congratulations.
Go on.
Did she ever say that
she thinks I hate her?
I got it.
Hello?
Is-is mr. Standish in?
he's sleeping.
Who's this?
Mmm.
Who was it?
Some kid.
Come on.
We can make it home.
We got this far,
didn't we?
Where you going?
Home.
How?
I'm calling your mom.
Enough of this.
Wait a minute.
It would really
mean a lot to me...
To not have to call
my mother for help.
You remember this?
I still owe you one.
You let me call your mom,
I forget about it.
No dice.
This isn't working out.
We're not masters
of the highway.
We were robbed
by home-bound hookers.
Only because you fell
asleep, and I got...
Horny.
You did?
Sort of.
Congratulations.
Slap it.
There you go.
See, I'm not such
a bad guy, huh?
Yeah. Yeah,
you are, but...
I'm still going
to get you home.
everybody knows
you been steppin' on my toes
and I'm gettin'
pretty tired of it
you keep-a
steppin' outta line
and-a messin'
with my mind
if you had any sense,
you'd quit
ever since you were
a little bitty...
Uhh!
We're here.
Where?
I don't know.
There's got to be a-
There's got to be a guard
around here somewhere.
We'll ask him.
Get out of here.
Aah.
Don't come back.
Heh heh heh.
Ohh.
I could sue you
for this.
Ohh...
Dutch: Hey,
the kid doesn't mean it.
I do so.
And you can't hit me
'cause I'm a minor.
Ha ha ha ha.
Ohh!
Aah! Aah!
Hey, hey.
Hey, you okay?
Hey, I told
you guys-
What the hell
is wrong with you?!
What the hell-
we don't want any trouble.
Hey!
Relax, all right?
Why don't you guys
Go inside and we'll
hit the road, all right?
Uhh!
Aah!
Get away from him!
Yeah, yeah.
Uhh!
I said, leave him alone!
Knock it off!
You-
Get your tail
out of here!
You're outnumbered
now, boy.
All right, kid.
Heh heh heh.
Haaaaaah!
Uhh!
Hyah!
Ohh!
Uhh!
Oh!
Whew.
Oh.
Are you okay?
Ooh. We're gonna
get you, kid!
Yeah.
You got me mad now.
You really got me-
Dutch: Doyle,
listen, listen...
I'll make you
eat that gun.
Dutch: All right,
now you guys really did it.
You got him angry.
Pete, let's go. You
don't have to shoot 'em.
Pete... You don't
have to shoot 'em!
You don't have
to shoot 'em, pete.
The kid is crazy.
Don't be crazy, pete.
Tell the voices that
you just killed somebody.
You know, that guy.
You just killed somebody!
Yeah!
Uhh! Ohh,
I just killed somebody!
He just killed
somebody.
Oh. They won't listen.
Don't shoot me.
I gotta do it.
I gotta get rid
of the voices!
Listen, listen,
it's the holiday season.
These guys probably
got families.
I do! I do!
He's single.
Why'd you say that?
Now I gotta kill
your families, too.
Dutch: Oh, no. Calm down,
pete. Look, forget these guys.
We'll find some nice motel
you can burn down.
Yeah. Motel.
Lots of people.
Okay.
You guys are very lucky.
Kid hardly ever backs off
once he gets his neck up.
So long, guys.
Excuse me,
But would you please
get out of here?
This isn't a warming
house, you know.
The boy has a wound
on his head.
We need to use
the restroom.
I'm so sorry, but
from time to time,
These... Road people
wander in.
Excuse me.
I said out.
Can he wash his face?
No!
I'll go outside.
Let him use the bathroom.
Robert, you want
to come over here
And help me?
Excuse us.
Excuse me, sir.
You're on the road?
Yeah. Why?
The boy's your son?
That's right.
We're up from georgia
on our way to chicago.
Lost our car.
We got robbed.
Oh, god.
It's all right.
They'll take good
care of you here.
Who?
This is a center
for displaced families.
Mike's supervisor
is on the board.
So, good luck,
all right?
Don't give up.
Okay.
Have a little faith
in your father.
He's doing
his best, okay?
All right. Bye-bye.
Let's go, hon.
Bye-bye.
And, uh, all our best
for a happy holiday.
Would you like to see
the wine list?
That's mine.
You can have it.
That was nice.
Jeez!
Son of a-
You have to
click it.
Is there a problem?
No, no, I got it.
Thanks.
Ahh, jeez.
Shh!
Woman:
It's all right now.
Doyle.
Switch cots with me.
Mine won't hold me.
How do you know
it'll hold me?
Because I'm 15,000 cheeseburgers
ahead of you in life.
Come on.
Hi.
You from hammond?
Chicago.
I'm from south bend
originally.
Came to hammond
to look for work,
Me and my husband.
He lost his job
in June.
Worked for one of those
auto part companies
That went broke.
We've been here
for about a week.
It's nice.
We was living out of
the back of our car.
That's kind of hard.
What about you?
We got here tonight.
You and your daddy?
Yeah.
Do you have a mother?
But she's not with you,
though, huh?
Where's she at,
chicago?
Yeah.
And I bet you'd like to
be with her right now,
Wouldn't you?
Yes.
Yeah...
I would.
It'll happen.
Hope so.
That's all any of us
in here can do.
What?
Hope.
You better
get some sleep.
Okay.
Hey, doyle.
While you were
brushing your teeth,
I called your mom.
I told her we were
at the holiday inn
So she wouldn't worry.
Is that okay?
Yeah.
You know, 'cause I said
I wouldn't call.
No...
No, that's okay.
Good night.
Did you hear me talking?
No, not really.
Well, I meant it.
I appreciate it.
You still gonna shoot me
in the ass?
Yes.
Good night.
beyond the blue horizon
waits a beautiful day
good-bye to things
that bore me
joy is waiting for me
I see the new horizon
my life has only begun
beyond
the blue horizon...
That's them.
He'll be so happy
to see you.
Hello, natalie.
I'm sorry.
Were you expecting
the mailman?
You take care,
the both of you, now.
Now, you call
the office
First thing
Monday morning.
I'll see what
I can do for you.
Doyle, happy
thanksgiving.
Thanks.
Good luck.
Okay.
Happy thanksgiving.
Hey, buddy!
Surprise.
Huh?
Mom...
I'm sorry.
Could you step outside?
This is a family matter.
Why don't you say
good-bye to your mother?
Why don't you come
to my house?
We've got a lot
to talk about, huh?
I canceled an important
overseas trip
To spend
this holiday with you.
No, you didn't.
I called your house
and a lady answered.
You lied to me.
Don't talk to me
that way.
It's true.
You make up your mind
right now, doyle.
Are you coming with me,
or are you staying here?
Your decision is final.
I'm staying here, dad.
Well... Fine.
I want you out of here
by Monday.
Excuse me.
You wanted natalie
out by when?
Monday.
I'm sorry,
I didn't quite, uh...
I said-
Ehh...
Friday?
Well, she's probably gonna
need a little more time.
Uh... How's 6 months
sound to you?
No problem.
And you'll be more
respectful to natalie?
Absolutely.
And you'll work on being
a nice guy with your son,
Because he still loves you.
He's a great kid.
He doesn't deserve
having his feelings hurt
Or his mind played with,
especially not by his dad.
I like him a lot.
I'm his friend,
But, see, I'm never
gonna be his father.
That's your job.
You better learn to do it.
Yes, sir.
Good.
Pleasure
seeing you again.
Happy holidays.
Thank you-
Thank you.
Heh.
Whoa!
I'm okay.
And here it is.
Oh, wow.
Thank you, dear.
- Isn't he a beauty?
- Looks good.
Uh, dave...
Yeah?
Before we start,
run in the other room
And get my coat,
will you?
I got something in there
for your mother.
Right now?
Yeah.
Can't it wait?
Well, it's something
very special.
Okay.
move over.
yikes!
we've got to
give a little love
have a little hope
make this world
a little better
try a little more,
harder than before
yes, do what we can do
together
oh, whoa, whoa
we can really
make it better, yeah
oh, whoa-oh,
la la la
only if we try
oh, whoa
livin' in this
crazy world
so caught up
in the confusion
nothin' is makin' sense
for me and you
maybe we can find a way
there's got to be
solution
how to make
a brighter day
what do we do?
we've got to
give a little love
have a little hope
make this world
a little better
whoa, whoa
got the worries
on our minds
got the troubles
on our shoulders
sometimes
it seems so much
what we go through
maybe if we
take the time
time to understand
each other
we can learn
to make it right
what do we do?
we've got to
give a little love
have a little hope
make this world
a little better
try a little more,
harder than before
yes, do what we can do
together
whoa oh whoa, whoa-oh
we can really
make it better, yeah
whoa, whoa-oh,
la la la
only if we try
whoa, whoa-oh,
la la la
oh ah oh oh oh
whoa, whoa-oh,
la la la
only if we try
if everybody took
somebody by the hand
come on, take him
by the hand
then maybe everyone
could get to love
and understand
whoa whoa-oh
we can really
make it better, yeah
whoa, whoa-oh,
la la la
only if we try
sing it,
oh, whoa-oh, la la la
we can really
make it better, yeah
oh, whoa-oh
only if we try
we've got to
give a little love
have a little hope
make this world
a little better
make this
a better world
try a little more,
harder than before
yes, do what we can do
together
oh, whoa, whoa-oh
we can really
make it better, yeah
oh, whoa-oh
only if we try
we've got to
give a little love
have a little hope
make this world
a little better
make it
a better world
try a little more,
harder than before
let's do what we can do
together
oh, whoa, whoa-oh
we can really
make it better, yeah
oh, whoa-oh,
la la la
only if we try
we've got to
give a little love
have a little hope
make this
a little better
we can do it together
together
give a little love