Grandfather, Grandmother,
I enter the sacred circle
to give thanks for all the prayers
that have been answered
on my path of learning.
I come with the morning star
as my guide
and the hawk as my protector.
My father, the sachem of our people,
had a vision when I was little.
Like him, I would be a leader
and a warrior one day.
"But you will become
a different kind of leader," he said.
"Your eyes will see
far beyond our horizon."
I did not yet understand
his words of wisdom.
I did not know Mother Earth
was so much bigger than our village -
even bigger than our hunting grounds.
I only began to learn about these things
the day after beautiful Nakooma
and I became husband and wife.
We're going ashore. I've spotted a tribe.
- Form a search party!
- Prepare the launch!
Prepare to land!
Trade.
Dermer, tell the sachem we need five
strong men to carry the furs to our ship.
We have enough men of our own,
surely, sir.
Mr. Dermer, this expedition
is under my command.
Please translate Mr. Harding's request.
Sir.
Squanto!
Move it! Move it along!
You heard the captain!
Prepare to hold cargo!
Come. Come, my friend.
This way.
Down.
Down below. Understand?
Down below.
- Up anchor!
Below. Get them below.
Now! Seize them!
Squanto!
Seize them! Seize the Indians!
Canon, fire!
Mark my words:
treat them as friends, Mr. Dermer,
you'll find an arrow in your back.
Steal from them, Mr. Harding,
and you kill any opportunity
to trade with them in the future.
I'm carrying out orders, Mr. Dermer,
orders that come from Sir George,
who owns this ship and pays our wages.
Excuse me, sir. They still refuse to eat.
They won't eat so long as they're
locked up and treated like animals.
For the last time,
will you let me untie them?
- And then they'll eat?
- Yes!
Well, what will they eat, Mr. Dermer?
They might just start with you!
Me na Epenow.
Me na Squanto.
Mene dalusi Thomas.
Be careful.
- Watch out!
- I'll bloody that savage.
Don't. Come on. Back!
You treat them far too well, Mr. Dermer.
Make way! Make way! Stand aside!
Coming through!
Ah, my ship, my ship!
This is a great day for England,
a great day
for the Plymouth Shipping Company.
Morning, everybody.
What a beautiful morning it is.
Beautiful morning.
Good day, Sir George.
Mr. Hunt, Mr. Harding,
returned alive and well, I see.
We had a very successful voyage,
Sir George.
Well, I expect nothing less
from you gentlemen.
- Lower the chair.
- Well done, Mr. Harding.
- I think you'll find the discomfort worth it.
- I hope so, I hope so, Harding.
Secure the line! All the way!
That's it. Thank you, boys.
Thank you, boys.
Thank you, Dermer. Ah, well...
Now tell me, is this
the full extent of our venture?
Anything gold, silver, jewels,
fine armor, swords?
Prepare to be astonished, Sir George.
Bring them topside.
- What are they?
- The noble savage, Sir George.
They're awful. They're horrible.
Lord, they are wonderful.
Tell me, what would happen
if I approach them?
Oh, have no fear.
My men will protect you.
You know, they seem frightened.
They've never seen a place
like this before.
No. You've never seen
anyone like me before, have you?
I am Sir...
- What is that?
- That's bear fat, Sir George.
How disgusting. Bear fat.
You speak these people's language,
Dermer.
- I do, Sir George.
- Tell them who I am!
I'm the Plymouth Shipping Company.
I own this ship. I own them!
I don't think they'd understand that, sir,
the idea that one man can own another.
Then they'll have to understand it.
This one needs to be disciplined.
Clean him up.
Then we'll put him on display
in front of the great British public.
Now take me back!
Ladies and gentlemen,
for your sporting pleasure,
the next match has never been seen
on English shores.
- Bring them in.
- May I present to you,
by courtesy
of the Plymouth Shipping Company -
of which I am the proprietor -
a wild, wild barbarian
from the New World.
- Oh, my.
- He's horrid.
You see, Dermer, the riffraff adore him.
Yes! Look! He's cut!
Ladies and gentlemen,
Squanto the savage!
I'm making a gold mine here, Harding.
- Gold mine!
- Indeed, Sir George.
No, no! I want him alive!
Go! Get after them!
Don't let them escape, you fools!
Save me, save me!
Get after him! Go after him!
He's getting away!
Round the back, round the back!
They lost the scent.
We're heading back.
You men, check the east dock.
- Harding, did you find him?
- Bring him.
- We've captured one of them, Sir George.
- Not that one, you fool. It's Squanto I want.
I'm afraid he's still at large
for the moment.
This man's injured.
He needs a physician.
You still see them as human beings,
Dermer, that's your problem.
Look, Harding, find him! I don't care
how many men it takes - find Squanto.
Yes, Sir George.
What is that?
Brother Daniel!
What is it, Brother Daniel?
He doesn't look like an Englishman.
You see? You see?
We found him on the beach.
He's not dressed like an Englishman.
Careful, brothers. Back!
This is not a part of God's creation.
He's a kind of devil, I suspect.
Devil...
Brother Paul, this is no evil beast.
Not evil, perhaps,
but a beast nonetheless.
Nonsense. Only so long as
we treat him like a beast.
What are you suggesting?
That he stay in here and eat with us?
I'm suggesting
we do not judge this fellow.
We show him the kindness
we would show any stranger.
And we discover who he is.
Come on, sit! Let us say grace.
- Heavenly Father...
...we thank thee
for these and all thy mercies...
Brothers! Brothers!
Brothers, come quickly!
James! Brother Paul! Daniel!
Outside! He's outside!
Let him be, brothers. Let him be.
We have no hold on him here.
Brother Daniel!
Go, my friend. You are free!
He won't get far.
He's injured. He's weak.
He's the Devil, Brother Paul.
You said so yourself.
Come, brothers.
Come along.
What's he doing?
A miracle.
Blasphemy! That's not a miracle.
Give way! Make way!
There's no trace of the savage
to be found.
I'm tired of hearing "No, no, no, no"!
I want to hear "yes" for a change!
- Do you understand, Mr. Harding?
- Yes.
A naked Indian
with hair down to the ground
and a necklace
made of shells and feathers
disappears into a civilized city
and all the well-paid and well-trained
military men can't find him?
It's not a needle in the haystack -
it's a haystack!
There are some of us who think
he must have drowned in the great storm.
Well, I don't accept your theory.
I don't like it either.
I want my Indian!
I made promises to London.
Sir George, you have the other savage.
He is very popular with the crowds.
I don't want popular! I want sensational!
Squanto was sensational.
He could sing. He could fight!
The public were clamoring
for him to come.
You know... I'm a businessman.
You know that, don't you?
Oh, yes, yes.
I've invested in that Indian.
I want him back.
Continue the search. I don't care
if you have to go as far as Scotland.
- I want my Squanto! Find him!
- Yes, Sir George.
Maushop.
Come. Come.
Come here.
Maushop... that. Is that maushop?
Maushop... horse.
- Horse...
- Yes. Let me show you.
Horse. Come.
You see?
Touch him.
Don't be afraid. Touch him.
Horse. No, no, no.
He won't hurt you.
Don't be afraid. Touch him.
Maushop... horse.
We ride the horse.
Here. Let me show you.
See? I'm holding him gently. Gently.
You see?
Come on. You try.
Hold this.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Kick him. Give him a kick.
Give him a little kick.
A little more. That's it.
- Horse. Horse.
- Horse.
- He's quite good.
Well, he's not as good as we are, but he's...
There you go.
- Horse.
- Horse. Yes, you said it.
Horse.
Horse!
Oh, no. Come back!
You see what you get for your trust,
Brother Daniel?
He's a horse thief!
Brothers! Brothers!
He's coming back!
Brothers! He's coming back!
Horse!
Well done.
You see, Squanto? These are all books.
Book.
- Book.
- Yes.
Horse. Book.
Excellent.
I happen to be a man who has read
far too many books.
My head is full of all kinds of nonsense,
but I love books.
I love everything about them.
Let me show you. This is my favorite.
The Odyssey.
Second favorite.
Lightly. Gently, gently.
Yes.
You see?
Isn't it beautiful?
Nakooma.
Nakooma? This one?
That is your word for "woman"?
"Nakooma."
That is his word for "woman."
Let me show you.
I'm going to teach you my language,
Squanto.
And learn yours if I can.
If I can discover where in this vast world
you've come from,
perhaps I can help you to go home.
- Nakooma.
- Woman.
- Fishing net.
- That's right. Fishing net.
- Brother Timothy.
- Brother Paul? Brother Paul...
What are you wearing on your feet?
Hm?
Oh, uh... footwear.
- Show me this footwear.
- Cheese?
Brother Timothy, I said
show me this footwear!
Squanto made them.
They're extremely comfortable.
Brother Timothy, you did not join
this monastery to be comfortable!
There will be comfort enough
in the life to come.
Yes, Brother Paul.
This is a cloister!
We have secluded ourselves here
to worship,
not to be distracted by visitors!
Hey, Brother Paul!
Brother Daniel!
We are forgetting our purpose here,
Brother Daniel.
There's nothing sinful in this.
Your pagan friend has disrupted
our quiet life.
It's time he left.
- Oh, he can't leave.
- Why not?
- He's still recovering from his injuries.
- Oh, indeed.
Well, I'm not a doctor, Brother Daniel,
but it would appear
that he is fully recovered.
But he's learning from us, Brother Paul,
and we are learning from him.
He's beginning to speak
and observe our ways.
Is it not our duty to bring light
into the darkness?
- Do you see this flower?
- Yes.
It is a pink Mandevilla.
When it blooms,
its petals are like a trumpet.
But it's not blooming
because it is a gift from our brothers
in a monastery in Spain.
You see? You cannot uproot a flower...
and plant it in a place
where it does not belong!
But Squanto has nowhere to go.
He's lost, and from what he's told me,
I believe he's come
from the New World.
Poppycock! I'll never believe it.
There is no New World.
There is only this world.
And this world, Brother Daniel,
is not round. It is flat!
- Oh, Brother...
- Flat!
Whatever you believe,
Squanto came to our country by ship.
Winter is upon us.
No ships will sail before spring.
Will you deny him shelter, Brother Paul?
Come.
Heavenly Father!
Heavenly Father...
we thank thee
for these and all thy mercies.
Amen.
- What is that word?
- Kissuulk.
It is the name of Squanto's god.
Ah. And what exactly
is the function of this... god?
Squanto, tell us about Kissuulk.
He is the Creator.
Tell me, Squanto, this mysterious land
that you come from -
you must miss it after all this time.
Yes, Brother Paul.
I miss my family, my people...
And Nakooma.
Nakooma is the name
of Squanto's bride.
Bride? You are married, Squanto?
Yes, Brother Paul.
Where are the women of your tribe?
We have no women, Squanto.
We have devoted our lives to God.
Your tribe will die with no women.
Squanto, we are not a tribe.
I would never join a tribe
with no women.
We are not a tribe.
I loved Nakooma
when we were children.
I miss her.
I was so fortunate
to be with the brothers,
who taught me their language,
their ways and values.
But as the seasons passed,
I got restless.
Nakooma was visiting me
in my dreams,
and I saw tears in her eyes.
I had to be with my people again soon,
or my heart would die.
For months we've been searching for him.
He must have drowned, Sir George.
It's the only explanation.
That's a convenient explanation.
If he's dead, I want proof.
- If not, keep on looking for him.
- Sir George, look at my men.
The weather's been fierce.
They've been frostbitten!
We've lost two horses!
You lose your position if you fail me,
Harding. You hear me?
Your status, your income,
your reputation, your future.
This is Plymouth! I own Plymouth!
Yes, Sir George.
Who are you?
Sir George, my name is William
Bradford, and this is Dr. Samuel Fuller.
- Puritans.
- In search of religious freedom.
Several of us would like
to book passage on one of your ships.
I have no objection to taking fanatics
like you over the sea,
but I must warn you of one thing,
gentlemen:
I don't deal in shillings, I deal in pounds.
- We have very little, I'm afraid.
- Then you're wasting my valuable time.
- Mr. Dermer.
- Sir.
You're wasting your own time, too,
gentlemen.
The New World is no place
for men of peace.
You won't survive
without military protection.
We have our faith,
and we are resolute in our purpose.
I think you'll need a little more than that,
my friends.
Ah, pork pie!
Why anyone would want to leave
England, I'll never know.
Mr. Dermer, you're a man
of maps and charts.
Look at this map. Now, tell me,
where do you think Squanto would hide?
Well, his tribe lived mostly by the ocean,
so I doubt very much he'd go inland.
Not near any city, certainly.
That would only terrify him.
- Mr. Harding!
You know, you impress me, Dermer.
You seem to understand these people.
You know them.
Well, I do believe, sir,
that if we want to trade with them,
we should at least try to learn
what we can about their culture.
- I can't think of anything more tedious.
- It's practical, Sir George.
And it's good business. Think of
all the opportunities you've missed
by stealing these men from their tribes.
You've made enemies instead of friends.
You can't conduct business with enemies.
But we're stronger than they are.
We can make them do anything
we want them to do.
You watched Squanto fight off
a whole platoon of armed men.
These are not complacent people, sir.
They're warriors.
Bibougest.
Hawk. Beautiful hawk.
My friend, my protector.
He is always with me.
You've learned my language far better
than I've learned yours, Squanto.
For me there was no choice.
Was there, maushop?
- What is it, Squanto?
- The hawk crossed our path.
He warns us.
Who are they, Squanto?
Hold up!
Up there! Follow me! Come on!
Go on, Squanto, hide from them.
Faster!
What's happening, Brother Daniel?
- They've come looking for Squanto.
- Perhaps he belongs with the authorities.
- We mustn't tell them he's here.
- Do not ask me to lie, Brother Daniel.
- I will not lie.
- Then do not speak at all.
You there! You're holding property
that doesn't belong to you.
You, sir, are standing on private ground.
We know he's here, Friar.
Hand him over.
He's owned by
the Plymouth Shipping Company.
The Plymouth Shipping Company
has no business in this sanctuary.
This sanctuary, under Protestant law,
has no business on English soil!
Search the place!
You, search the stables!
Tell me where he is!
This is a place of worship!
- There's nobody here...
- Get out of my way!
- This is a private monastery.
- Spare me your lies!
Please don't. I'm telling you the truth -
there's nothing here.
Follow me! Come on!
Tear the place apart!
- Squanto...
- Brother James.
- It's you that they're after. Stay hidden.
- They are hurting you.
It'll be worse for you if they find you,
my friend. Stay back.
All right! What is the purpose of this?
These are our books, our manuscripts!
I'm out of patience
with that bloody Indian!
- Out of my way, monk.
- I will not.
Out of my way!
This is a place of learning.
Then let me teach you a lesson.
Understand? The sooner you cooperate,
the sooner we stop!
We will cooperate.
Tell me what you want.
You know what we want, Friar.
The beast.
The wild, wild Indian
who lives like a filthy animal!
The savage! Where is he?
Savage? Beast?
Filthy animal?
I swear upon this holy book,
no one like that is here.
Out!
Move out!
You protected me, all of you.
They did this to you.
Your books. Your house.
All this was because of me.
No, Squanto.
It was because there are some people
who bully their way through this world
with cruelty and force.
You have no weapons to stop them.
That is not how we battle our enemies.
Enemies destroy you!
Our books, our windows, yes.
But our spirits are still intact.
You do not hate the men
who did this to you?
No. We do not hate.
Hatred only leads to more hatred.
Brothers...
Thank you.
Humpty Dumpty sat on a wall.
Humpty Dumpty had a great fall.
No, no, no!
Just repeat what he says, will you?
Why doesn't the savage speak?
- I think perhaps it's his dignity, sir.
- Dignity, my foot!
I want an Indian
who can sing, dance, fight...
Like Squanto, the one who got away!
His reputation has been quite special
since his escape from the bear pit, sir.
Has it really?
Tell me, when people talk
about the escape,
am I the object of public ridicule?
Of course not, sir.
Give me that, you thief!
Gold.
In my home, Capoge...
we have gold everywhere.
Did you hear what he said?
How did he learn to speak like that?
- Did you say "gold"?
- Yes, sir.
Heave!
Ah, Mr. Dermer.
- Sir George, welcome aboard.
- Yes, thank you.
The ship is in fine shape, isn't she, sir?
She'll be ready to sail as planned.
Never been very keen on ships.
Anyway, I'm here on business.
My Indian, Epenow,
says there's gold in his country.
Opinion?
It's a vast and wondrous place, sir.
It's perfectly possible.
Do you think if I let him go with you,
you could lure him or persuade him
to show you where the gold is?
Perhaps - in exchange for his freedom.
I could certainly use his help as well
to trade with his tribe again.
I'm reluctant to let him go
without being certain of being able
to replace him by Squanto.
- I thought you'd located Squanto.
- I've located him, but I haven't caught him.
We need to lure him somehow.
What in our culture
could possibly attract Squanto?
Squanto!
Squant... Squanto!
Squanto! Squanto!
Squanto... A ship! A ship!
The market... A ship...
We've been to the market and learned of
a ship that's leaving Plymouth in 15 days.
- What ship?
- It's called the Half Moon.
Plymouth. Plymouth is a dangerous
place for you, Squanto.
All we need to do is get him on board.
Daniel, there may not be another ship
for months. Years!
- What on earth is this?
- It's food, Brother Paul.
Food?
- It's as hard as a rock.
- It's been dried.
You plant it in the ground.
A great big thing like this?
I believe it grows into an enormous tree.
Brothers, we haven't even prayed
this evening, and you...
Food is speaking.
Food from the New World speaks, does it?
Well, Squanto,
I doubt if you'll find many...
English!
Stay back!
English... you have no courage.
Brothers... this is delicious.
It's good.
Have some. Try some now.
It's good. It's really good.
- Really?
- Try it.
It is good.
If such a place of wonder does exist...
your heart must ache to go back to it.
Brother Daniel, you have my permission
to ride to Plymouth.
You must see Squanto safely
to the ship and then return.
Now, you protect these good men
the way you watched over me.
Squanto?
You haven't been fiddling
with this flower, have you?
Well, you look quite a sight
in that sackcloth.
Tell me, does it make you
feel at all like a monk?
I'm still thinking about a woman,
Brother Paul.
Oh. I must tell you something, Squanto.
I confess it's been
a stubborn weakness of mine...
I resist the possibility of other worlds,
other customs, other points of view.
Sometimes I overlook
the goodness in a man
even when it's staring me in the face.
Go in peace. You have my blessing.
Thank you, Brother Paul.
Take this as a gift from my heart.
Mr. Epenow has figured out how
to avoid a whipping, eh, Mr. Harding?
Very liberal of you to give him
his freedom, Sir George.
A business transaction.
This brave that came from the New World
will battle the Ottoman army,
the wildest in the world!
Chief Epenow!
I must warn you though, this
performance is not for the faint of heart.
No, Squanto. No.
You have risked your life for a friend,
Brother Daniel.
Epenow's my friend.
I must do the same.
The fool!
Oh, no! Not yet, Harding.
He will entertain the audience.
Squanto, the savage!
Squanto! Squanto!
Well, now, Squanto, you were
spectacular this afternoon.
The common people loved you.
The gentry loved you.
You were the talk of the town.
There is indeed a ship leaving
for your homeland.
It leaves Plymouth tomorrow at noon.
Your friend Epenow
will be on board that ship.
You, however, will not.
You can't run away from me, Indian.
I own you now.
You will do whatever I tell you to do.
Obey me and you'll be treated fairly.
Disobey me and you'll be punished.
There is a divine order to life.
First there's God,
followed by the angels, then the king...
Then the rest of us
according to our position in the world.
Your position, Indian,
is lower than the animals.
You're not a human being.
You're livestock.
Harding!
Make very sure you keep him
bound and guarded at all times.
- Of course, Sir George.
- Just like my friend here, Epenow.
Take me home, you good-for-nothing.
You there.
The man you're looking for is not here.
- Do you know where he is?
- Locked away.
- He'll die.
- It has nothing to do with me.
Yes, it has.
The man is a human being.
He needs to go home.
He was brought over from the New World
on a ship like this.
I know.
Have a successful voyage, Dermer.
Do good business for me.
- Bring my ship back safely.
- Aye-aye, Sir George.
- Weigh the anchor!
- Aye-aye, sir.
Let go all bunts! Hoist the sails!
On your feet, savage!
- Take him.
- Get up, you animal.
Come on, you, now.
You. What is your business here?
Get out of my way!
After him, you fools!
Capture the savage! Report to Sir George!
- Sir George! Sir George!
- What is it?
- The Indian has escaped!
- What?
Dermer!
Hard to starboard!
He's getting away! After him!
Head round the other side!
Be certain this is the last time
you make a fool of me, savage!
- Brother Daniel!
- There is no time.
You are a true warrior.
Let's go, maushop.
Bless you, bless you. God bless.
After him!
Sir George, the Half Moon!
The Indian, sir!
Out of the way! Move it!
In the name of the king, out of the way!
No, no, no!
Sir George!
My Indian! Stop that ship!
Stop that ship!
Harding! Harding!
- You're fired! You're fired!
- Yes!
Yes, Sir George.
Save me!
Stop that ship!
Brother Daniel!
Thank you!
You won the trust of the English,
Epenow.
The Engli...
The English are greedy.
I promised them gold.
Where is this gold?
I've learned many things
from the English.
One of them was how to lie.
I learned from them, too.
I found friends among them.
Our friends are the people
that we are going home to.
The Nausets and the Patuxets.
I am loyal to my people. And my family.
And my son.
Pequod will be a great sachem one day.
I too am loyal to my people and family.
And my bride, Nakooma.
But new friends do not threaten my loyalty.
Then you are a fool, Squanto.
The white man is not your friend.
He will only betray you.
My father taught me
to let my heart be my guide.
From the brothers, I learned
to keep my spirit, even in pain.
Epenow's words left me concerned.
Land ho!
Epenow!
I was almost home.
My heart was longing for the moment
when I would hold Nakooma
in my arms again
and my family would gather
around the fire to celebrate my return.
But our ship sailed into Nauset Bay,
the place of Epenow's people,
a few days away from my village.
Stow your oars now.
Keep your eyes peeled onshore.
Pequod!
Dada!
Squanto!
I go to rest now.
I leave at dawn for home.
Won't you dance with me?
Dance with me.
How about a kiss, then?
Just a little one. Come on.
Come on!
For God's sakes, man, remember
your manners! You're a guest here.
She's just a bloody savage anyway.
What have you done?
This is not our way!
No, it is not our way!
It is the way of the English!
You welcome them to your village and
now you slaughter them as the enemy?
They came to our land to trade,
then they took us away
and treated us like animals!
You have punished a good man
for other men's cruelty!
I killed them because I am a warrior!
- You have forgotten who you are!
- I have not forgotten!
Go back to your village, Squanto...
and see what the English
have brought to your people.
Then judge me for what I have done.
Nakooma!
I began to understand Epenow's rage.
All of my people were dead,
killed by the sickness
brought by the English.
My heart was bleeding.
Nakooma's tears still haunted me.
The playful laughter of my people
still echoed through the village.
Now I would wear their ashes
and carry their spirits with me.
I had become a sachem without a tribe.
The English would come again -
I knew that.
And I promised the Great Spirit
to be the warrior
my father had seen in his vision.
Dr. Fuller, Mr. Bradford!
Look at this.
We're safe here.
Protected on all sides.
I suggest we bury our dead
before we settle in.
I still feel uneasy about this decision.
This is someone else's home.
God has guided us here.
This will be our home.
- But what if they come back?
- They will be met with resistance.
That is what you pay me for.
Warwick, take one man
and search the surrounding forest.
Captain Fuller!
Man the barricades!
You two, come with me.
Carver, make sure the women
and children are secure.
I want every man of yours
armed and ready.
Mr. Bradford, could you
bring the rosewater, please?
We should try to make contact
with these people first.
We must show them we mean no harm.
I will not allow my men
to be used as target practice.
If we do not show strength now,
then all is lost.
Mr. Standish is right. We've lived
too long under fear and persecution.
I say we fight for what should be ours.
Think of what you're saying, Mr. Carver.
Are we to be the same
as those who persecuted us in England?
- Should we commit murder?
- Bradford, I am preventing murder.
I shall do what is necessary.
I want all men to enforce the barricade!
Squanto!
What has to be done.
What my father would have done.
- Shoot him.
- No, wait.
- Mr. Carver, he's unarmed.
Enough!
Too much blood.
Too much blood on this land.
Too many tears.
It's a trick.
All of my people have died here.
And all of your people will die too.
Put down your weapons!
All of you!
Pequod!
No!
Now kill me! Kill me!
And you'll kill them and they'll kill you.
And more of us will die!
And we will kill each other
until there's nothing left!
Nothing but ashes and bones!
We must end this!
Here! Now!
I'm a doctor. I can help.
I can help! Please, we must take him
inside to stop the bleeding.
If he dies, you all die.
The ball is out.
But his wound is inflamed
and I fear he's growing more feverish.
This.
How is he now?
He's now in the hands of the Creator.
We must wait.
Our Father, who art in heaven,
hallowed be thy name.
Thy kingdom come. Thy will be done
on earth as it is in heaven.
Give us this day our daily bread
and forgive us our trespasses
as we forgive those
who trespass against us;
and lead us not into temptation,
but deliver us from evil,
for thine is kingdom and the power
and the glory forever and ever.
Our Father, who art in heaven,
hallowed be thy name.
Thy kingdom come. Thy will be done
on earth as it is in heaven.
Give us this day our daily...
Dada.
The Creator has given my son Pequod
his life back today.
We will leave this village now.
Thank you, my friend.
And so began a time of harmony
between people whose ways
were so different from one another.
We who knew the land taught
those who had come from far away
how to plant and to hunt.
At harvest we came together
to give thanks.
Brothers and sisters, new friends,
please, let us rise and pray.
Heavenly Father, we thank thee
for this bountiful harvest
and for bringing so many of us together
on this joyous day.
We humbly ask thee for thy blessing.
Amen.
Please, everyone, eat.
My friends!
In the world there are many people...
with all kinds of customs and beliefs...
speaking many languages.
But there is only one moon, one sun...
one Mother Earth.
And there is only one tribe.
Let's live together in peace!