(Boy): Mommy!
(Tires screeching)
Kit, sweetie!
Get down! Get down!
Mommy, who is it?
Get your head down!
Now! Now!
I'm right here, sweetie.
(Tires screeching)
(Horn honking)
(Screaming)
Mommy, I'm scared!
Kit! Get down!
Mommy!
I love you!
It's done, sir.
No survivors.
We'll meet you at the airport.
(Chris): You look like
a tourist, Grandma!
Hurry up!
- This is Chris Cross,
tick-tock!
You can't touch me with this!
We are live!
From Lower Manhattan
to Hoboken in 12!
He'll never
make it. No way.
- $5 will get you $10, he does.
- It's on.
We're doing this
in real time, uncut!
I'm ready.
You ready?
- You know it!
- Here we go!
We better go incognito!
(Laughing)
Whoo-hoo!
Sorry, man! Sorry!
Hey, watch it!
- Hey!
- Whoo!
Yeah!
(Car horns honking)
Whoo-hoo-hoo!
Oh yeah!
- Whoo-hoo-hoo!
Whoo!
Yo, Tommy, can
I get some service!
Maybe a latte?
- Hold on.
- What are you watching?
These... Come here.
These guys, OK?
They're some of our regulars.
- Yeah!
- Whoo-hoo-hoo!
♪ Love is a rhyme... ♪
(All): Oh!
♪ You need that
one perfect line... ♪
- This is nuts!
- No kidding!
♪ I understand you're doing
everything you can ♪
♪ To see a format
or a plan ♪
♪ But you get lost
in your own pretence ♪
♪ And hours seem like days
When inhibitions... ♪
Is this live?
Yeah.
Completely.
It's crazy!
♪ Too much information
And no hesitation ♪
♪ You get it off your chest ♪
♪ Here I am ♪
♪ And there's all this... ♪
(All screaming)
Whoo!
♪ Here I am ♪
♪ And there's always you... ♪
Come on!
Yeah, yeah, I'm coming!
I'm coming!
(Grunting)
Oh!
You OK?
Yeah, yeah!
Go, go, go, go!
♪ You're a victim and a rebel
No matter what you wear... ♪
Whoo! Yeah!
♪ To have your soliloquy
And now you feel... ♪
Ahh!
- That was nice!
- That was beautiful!
♪ And there's always you ♪
(All): Oh!
♪ Here I am ♪
♪ And there's always you ♪
♪ Here I am... ♪
Watch! Watch!
- You got that?
- And we're set!
- Ohh!
- No!
That was tight!
- He lands it!
- Yeah!
- Get out!
- What!
♪ Yeah... ♪
Dude!
(Panting)
Tell me you got that!
Yeah, I got that!
We're coming up
on 9 minutes!
Whoo! Yeah!
Ohh!
I got you, buddy!
Come on!
You can do it!
(Grunting)
Ahh!
- Dude, that was bad-ass!
Get up! Get up! Get up!
(Screaming)
What?
What? What? What?
- It hurts?
- Do you need me to call 911?
No, don't call anyone.
Just go, man.
I'll be OK.
- You've gotta call 911!
- Yeah, that's it. I'm calling.
You good?
How many fingers?
Stop fooling around, man!
Yeah, I'd like to
report an injury.
We gotta go!
We can't sit here!
I gotta get you
to the hospital.
No, ma'am, I was watching
this person on my laptop,
and I saw them fall.
No, no, I gotta call 911!
No, no, no, they didn't
fall on my laptop.
(Screaming on laptop)
You know what?
I know where this place is.
I'm just gonna go.
Ma'am, hold on a second.
(Horns honking)
- I'm gonna talk to her.
- How are you? Are you good?
- Yeah, yeah, I'm fine.
- You had quite a fall, sir.
(Laughing)
You remember your name?
- Out of the way, please.
- What's your name?
- Jordie.
- Do you remember what happened?
- I fell.
- Yeah!
All right.
I need you to not
move your neck.
Renny.
Renny Davidson, right?
That is correct, sir.
I'm Chris Moore.
Yeah...
- Sixth grade.
- Ms. Sheenan's class, right?
Yeah. Yeah!
You remember me?
Yeah, of course I do!
The only boy who didn't laugh
when I said I wanted
to be a paramed!
Yeah, well, look at you now!
Saving my buddy's life here!
How cool is that?
Yeah, making the big bucks.
How does that feel? Good?
What did you want to be again?
A dolphin trainer.
What?
How is that
working out for you?
Well, let me tell you
something about dolphins.
They are very rude!
And cheap.
You know, I shared a cab
with a dolphin once.
Don't tell me. He stiffed you
for his end of the fare?
How did you guess?
They're notorious for that.
OK, friend.
You're under arrest.
For what?
Trespassing, mischief.
Vandalism. And that's
just the first of it.
Come on!
What?
- Tell me if this hurts.
- Come on!
Hey, Renny!
Can I call you?
Hey, Jordie!
Give her my number!
Please! If you
can remember!
Come on, man!
- (Cop): Hey!
- Interesting guy.
Yeah...
Christopher Moore?
Yeah.
This is Detective Clark Ellis,
and I'm Sean Davidson.
You're coming with us.
Where?
You'll see.
(Car horns honking)
Criminal trespass,
fleeing an officer,
resisting arrest.
You're a real hard case, Moore.
You run around on rooftops
like some kind of maniac?
I don't get that.
What's that for?
- Ask him.
- So what is it, Moore?
You get some kind
of rush doing that?
Running around...
Like a maniac?
Yeah. Yeah.
It's called Parkour.
- Par-what?
- Parkour.
It's French for "running
around like a maniac."
Oh yes!
Let's go!
Curb-side service, Moore.
Young lady awaits.
(Laughing)
- Thanks, Dad.
- You're welcome.
(Laughing)
Moore...
Behave yourself.
- Dad?
- Ha-ha!
Well...
I thought they were gonna
throw me in the East River!
I guess I convinced
them not to.
I don't...
I don't know what to say.
"Thanks" would be good.
Thanks.
Dinner would be better.
Do you like Italian?
Sounds good.
It's him.
Feet!
Where you been?
Dad, I met this
really great girl!
We were so worried.
We tried to call.
But your phone wasn't...
My cell phone is dead.
What? What's the matter?
Something wrong?
I can't believe you'd
do something this stupid.
Your last year of Columbia Law.
You get arrested?
What were you thinking?
I was just blowing off
a little steam.
Your father went
to the precinct.
To bail you out.
And they said you were gone.
They couldn't tell us
where you were.
(Crying)
Mom...
I'm so sorry.
No!
No, don't! No,
I'm really mad at you!
Mom, Mom...
Chris, you know how
important school is.
The sacrifices
we've all had to make.
Even with your scholarship.
If you don't get your grades up,
they're not gonna renew it.
And then we are well
and royally screwed.
So I want you to promise me
that you'll buckle down
over the next few weeks.
No going out...
- Dad, I'm 24.
- So what?
So it sounds like
you're grounding me.
You know what I'm saying.
No hanging out,
no distractions.
None of this "parquet" stuff.
- Parkour.
- Whatever
All you gotta do is nail these
midterms, go another semester,
and then you can
write your own ticket.
And you can take care
of your mother and me
in our golden years.
Yeah, right.
So do I have your word?
Yeah.
All right.
Then get to it.
Chris, what was it
you were telling your dad
about that girl you met?
Hmm?
- Ready for field test
9-alpha-niner.
Subject: Gardner,
Bethany Ann.
TIVKOM subscriber number:
K921342-0006.
- Preparing for field test
9-alpha-niner.
Subject: Gardner,
Bethany Ann.
She totally flakes on me.
Yeah, and so now
I'm stuck doing everything.
Uh-huh.
- OK, start her up.
- Yeah, no. I know.
You told me she was unreliable,
but what am I gonna do?
She volunteered.
Initiating.
Target defined.
(Man): Subject is in
position. Green for go.
Repeat: Green for go.
All right, I'll see you
at the meeting. OK, bye.
(Sighing)
Wave form being received
in the household.
Signal strength: 93%.
Initiate the sequence.
And...
Mark.
Initiating.
Initiating indoctrination code.
Sequence beta 3.
Decreasing temporal
dithering to zero.
Initiating indoctrination code.
Sequence beta 3.
(Static)
And... terminate broadcast.
Mom, I have some intuition.
That's what you
said the last time.
(♪ Humming ♪)
(Sirens in distance)
- So by providing a supply-
and-distribution chain
that enhances our
macro-global matrix,
we increase influence, control
and, of course...
Profits.
What about
conflict of interest?
I am so glad you asked
that question, Pete.
You see, under
this new paradigm,
there is no interest.
And ergo, there
can be no conflict.
The situation doesn't even have
to get hot for us to profit.
- What about the
Ben-David situation?
I'm so sorry,
Mr. McDowell.
Could you be
a little more unclear?
I need a little more
context on that one.
- Jalil Ben-David, 33.
Son of Israeli war hero
Ayou Ben-David
and his Palestinian
mistress, Yanakoi Dumi.
Educated at Oxford.
Top of his class.
Now promoting tolerance
in the territories.
"Peace at Last?"
Hmm?
Never seen this
on the cover of World
magazine before, have we?
I don't know, Stef.
This is all seeming
a little bit too
"inside the box" for me.
What's your point?
My sources say
he commands the respect
of both the Israelis
and Palestinians
and is very close
to establishing stability
without providing a solution.
Take him out.
I'm sorry?
You heard me.
I'm assuming you're saying
we should assassinate him.
Worked before
with Kennedy, Sadat...
I see your point. But...
Those things can get messy.
OK, Raatib.
What do you suggest?
What I always do.
Simplification plus automization
equals profitization.
Janet, send her in.
Ladies and gentlemen,
may I please present to you
the esteemed head
of the neurological
research-and-development team,
Dr. Bella Lithia.
This is an executive summary.
I expect few of you
to read it...
And fewer of you
to even understand it.
So let me put it
in simple terms.
As we all know, power,
real power,
is simply the ability
to make people do
what we want them to do.
So far, there has been
3 means to assert power:
Manipulation, coercion...
Or force.
With Flicker Tech,
all this is obsolete.
In other words, gentlemen,
a totally new paradigm.
Our Flicker Tech field trials
have been
successfully completed,
and we are ready
to start operation
6 months ahead of schedule.
Why the delay?
Excuse me?
We have been told it's fully
operational right now.
Is that correct?
Yes. Yes.
Mmm.
So he goes to
Columbia Law, and....
He's from the neighbourhood.
Like, 2 blocks away
his entire life!
My, my, my...
Are you even listening to me?
This whack job in Connecticut,
some soccer mom,
no previous record,
poisons a bunch of parents
at a school meeting!
Nine people dead!
(Phone ringing)
I'm telling you, this world
is turning into pure crap.
Good morning!
You know I'm breaking
every rule in the book
right now by calling you?
Oh yeah?
What book is that?
The Guy's Unwritten
Playbook for Dating.
Rule number one:
Never, ever call a girl
the morning
after the first date.
She will think you're
pathetic, desperate
and a potential stalker.
Funny, that's what the
Girl's Playbook says, too!
So are you?
What?
A stalker!
(Laughing)
Funny!
Funny. Uh, look,
so the point is,
I had a really good time
with you last night.
So I'm calling because I don't
want you to get the wrong idea.
Wait, what?
Well, I told
my parents last night,
I'd really buckle down
and study for midterms
hard over the next few weeks.
So I'm probably really not
gonna have much time to go out.
Go out.
No, I totally get it.
Chris, that's not a big deal.
I mean, whatever.
We just had dinner, right?
No, it's not OK.
It wasn't just a dinner.
So when are your midterms?
Ugh... A week from Friday.
All right.
Until then, you can
always call me.
(Exhaling)
What?
No, it's just that if I call
you, I'm gonna wanna see you.
And if I see you,
we'll say it's gonna
be for 5 minutes,
and it'll end up being
for, like, 5 hours.
- Or you could just use
some self-discipline.
If I had any, we wouldn't
be having this conversation.
I see your point.
All right, so radio silence
until a week from tomorrow.
And then we pick up
where we left off.
OK. All right. Deal.
And, uh, Chris...
Yeah?
Bet you wished you kissed me
when you dropped me
off last night.
Ooh, that is cold!
Ice! You're the Ice Queen!
Bye!
Talk to you later.
Bye.
Calling you the day
after your first date.
Friggin' stalker...
(Laughing)
Why did you lie to them?
Do you have any idea
how much work we have
left to do before...
Before it's perfect?
Perfection doesn't interest me.
Practical results do.
We still need to tackle
a number of
significant problems
before we can attempt an
operation of any magnitude!
Oh really?
Such as?
Override strong
personal feelings
between perspective subject
and target, for one.
Oh, details!
Excuses.
I have spent my entire
adult life in this technology,
and I'm not going to see it
compromised by half measures!
You're right.
We must be responsible, Bella.
We rise together...
We fall together...
But if we fall...
You fall first.
Oh...
(Knocking on door)
- Chris?
- Mmm...
You OK?
(Sighing)
Yeah.
(Exhaling)
Lady with the gun?
Been a while.
Hmm?
Don't make too much of it.
It's just a dream.
No, you know...
Like, sometimes there's a word.
And it's right on
the tip of your tongue,
but you can't think of it.
This lady is...
It's like she's...
Right on the tip of my brain.
It's like I know her.
But how?
(Car horn honking)
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
What did I tell you?
I don't want this
thing in here.
Yeah right, like
I'm gonna leave it outside
in this neighbourhood.
It's dirty!
Dude, just give me a tall
Americano to go, all right?
- What's up?
(Sighing)
♪ At the break of day
You say it, too... ♪
Boo!
Ah!
Didn't you break
your pelvis or something?
I chipped it.
Hurt like hell. No biggie.
Not like the ribs.
But, man, though...
Every time I go over a pothole,
I think I'm gonna black out.
Oh, and thanks for not
popping by to check on me.
Yeah, thanks for telling my
dad I got busted by the cops.
Sort of slipped
past the painkillers.
Yeah, how'd that
work out, anyway?
Well, I'm under house arrest
and I got midterms.
You tell me.
I mean, with the cops.
Oh... Remember that paramed?
Yeah! The one you
was hitting on
while I was dying
on the sidewalk?
Turns out, her
dad's a detective.
Got the charges dropped.
You gotta be the luckiest
guy on the planet.
So then we go to dinner.
Oh, look at you! Player!
All 007 and stuff, eh?
Yeah. Well, turns out,
she's great.
Really?
We talked for, like, 3 hours.
Well, then I'm glad
I had the opportunity
to introduce you guys.
Yeah, me too.
Thanks, buddy.
(Laughing)
What's her name?
Renny.
Oh man...
- What?
- You're in love!
- Shut up!
- Because the way you said it...
"Renny..." I mean, it
sounded like you were in love.
- Well, that's her name.
- No, no, no.
No, no, no!
I'm not saying...
I'm not talking about the name.
I'm saying about
the way you said it.
The way you said "Renny" sounded
like you were in love.
I don't know.
Say it again. Let's see.
Whoa! Whoa! Whoa!
Where are you guys going?
Manhattan. Your dad's
taking me out to dinner.
Ha! On a Wednesday night?
What, it's against the law
for us to go out
on a Wednesday night?
Your dinner's on the stove.
We'll bring you
back some dessert.
OK then!
Have fun!
(Engine starting)
(Chuckling)
What are you doing here?
It was you mom's idea.
She figured you
gotta eat, so...
Why not eat with a friend?
Huh... I can't
believe she did this.
I can go if you
need to study or...
No... No.
Oh no, you don't.
No, did...
Did you make this?
No. Your mom did.
But I helped her
with the salad.
♪ Lots my bags
flying over the ocean ♪
♪ But I'm all right
I got everything I need here ♪
♪ You got your wings on ♪
♪ I got my headband ♪
♪ Turn up the music
Let's paint our faces ♪
♪ When you lift me up
Oh, oh, oh... ♪
Wow...
Yeah...
♪ When you lift me up
Oh, oh, oh ♪
♪ When I am with ♪
♪ You ♪
♪ It don't matter what will
ever come of anything ♪
♪ 'Cause you're here... ♪
You're gonna work hard...
Do awesome on your exams.
And I'll see you Friday.
(Sirens blaring)
(Car engine starting)
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
What do you want?
Ah! Ah!
(Screaming)
No! No!
(Grunting)
What? What? Stop!
Where are you guys
taking me? huh?
What do you want?
Just tell me what you want!
I don't have any money!
I don't have anything!
Christopher Moore. Age 24.
Born October 15, 1986.
No! No! No,
you got the wrong guy!
I was born in July!
July 2!
My ID's in my wallet.
Don't!
You guys are making
a huge mistake!
You're studying
Law at Columbia.
You reside at
20 East 25th Street.
Legal guardians: Frank Edward
and Pam Elizabeth Moore.
Legal guardians?
What do you mean?
What are you talking about?
Who are you people?
Please.
Please, come with me.
I'll explain.
Come. I want you
to see something.
Twenty years ago,
a boy was found scavenging food
from a dumpster in Chinatown.
He was placed in the custody
of Child Services.
It was later determined,
he had suffered a concussion.
He had no memory
of his parents,
where he came from.
Even his name was a mystery.
That child was subsequently
adopted by Frank and Pam Moore.
So you're saying this kid...
Was you.
Yes.
(Scoffing)
No, you know what?
This is ridiculous.
Ten days ago,
when you were arrested,
the police collected
a routine DNA swab.
They entered it into CODIS.
This generated a match
to your biological parents.
I assure you, the results
were checked and rechecked.
They're irrefutable.
Your birth name...
Is Kit Walker.
(Accent):
Kit Walker.
You were born in
Gstaad, Switzerland,
and named after your father...
Who was a very important man.
- Was?
- Yes.
He died 22 years ago.
Cancer.
(Laughing)
OK...
OK! So what you're
saying is, I'm not me.
My parents aren't my parents.
And my real father is dead.
I know this is difficult.
No, no, no, this
is not difficult.
This is insane.
I don't even know
who you people are!
Fair enough.
We represent an agency
known as Bpaa-Thap.
- Ba-what?
In 1664, one of your ancestors,
and a former pirate,
named Barbrouge...
Wait, I'm sorry.
A pirate?
(Laughing)
A former pirate.
Established a small
paramilitary group
whose mandate was
to protect the innocent
against violence
and oppression.
Since then, it has grown into
an international
covert intelligence
and law-enforcement agency,
located in Bengalla.
- Ah! Bengalla?
- Mm-hmm.
A small island nation in
the Indonesian archipelago.
Oh, I know where it is.
My name is Abel Vandermaark.
Director of Field Operations.
Well...
Abel...
I'd really love to hear
about this sometime.
But I got things to do.
Wait! Would you like
to see your real mother?
Diana Walker.
(Exhaling)
You remember her.
She's...
Dead.
Yes.
You were with her in the car
when it was forced off the road.
You recognize this place?
No.
I know who I am.
I'm Chris--
- You are Kit Walker.
Your mother was murdered.
Her assassins are still alive.
Still at-large.
What do you want?
The world needs you...
To assume the mantle
of your forefathers
and take up their
struggle against...
Against what?
Evil.
It's so pervasive...
We don't even see it anymore.
My family...
Has been in the service
of yours for 5 generations.
(Sirens in distance)
If you want to know more
about your real family,
you can reach me at that
number 24 hours a day.
I'll be staying at the Ritz
Central Park until Friday.
I already have a real...
Family.
Do you think it was
wise to let him go
before convincing
him to join us?
He'll call.
He's a Walker.
Mom!
Dad!
(Breathing heavily)
Mom?
Dad?
Dad!
Guys!
(Breathing heavily)
(Coughing)
Oh! Oh God!
(Breathing heavily)
No.
Ah!
(Grunting)
(Car alarm blaring)
Ah!
Walker!
Where are you going to go, huh?
(Laughing)
OK.
Ah!
(Laughing)
It's too bad
I have to kill you!
You are pretty good, my friend!
(Panting)
(Grunting)
(Metal piercing flesh
and groaning)
Jeannot!
(Panting)
Walker!
Tu es Mort!
You hear me?
You're dead!
Dead!
(Clattering)
Show yourself or I'll shoot.
Why'd you kill them?
You psycho!
What are you talking about?
- My parents are dead!
- The Moores?
Two men were waiting
for me when I got home.
They tried to kill me.
(Panting)
Listen to me.
Listen to me!
Now, you think.
If we wanted you dead, then we
could easily have killed you
after we picked you up, right?
RIGHT?
(Panting)
What happened?
I went straight home.
I wanted to hear it from them.
What we talked about earlier?
(Clattering)
Two men...
Were waiting f me.
Parkour traceurs.
Good ones.
(Panting)
French, I think.
Twins?
Yeah.
They might've been.
The Roux brothers.
Singh Assassins.
Top shelf.
Guran, we've been made.
(Groaning)
Send our bodyguard
down for the car.
Meet us outside the lobby.
Yes, he's here with me.
Did you call the police?
No, I lost my phone.
Then it's good you came here.
The police are not equipped
to protect you from the Singhs.
The who?
The Singh Brotherhood.
They're an international
crime syndicate.
(Sighing)
How come I've never
heard of them?
Because they're very
good at what they do.
Time to check out.
Why, you think he'll come here?
They know about you.
There's an excellent chance
they know about us.
I thought you said
there were two of them.
One of them is dead.
It was an accident.
I just...
Made it happen.
(Elevator bell ringing)
It's clear.
One o'clock.
(Kit): That's him.
Which one? I can't
even tell them apart.
Shouldn't be a problem anymore.
Kit took one of them out.
Really?
Where are we going?
That's entirely up to you.
I'm sorry it has
to be like this.
I'm sorry about the Moores.
(Sighing)
But my offer still stands.
You can come with
us to Bengalla--
- Fantasy Island.
I don't think so.
You listen to me!
These people want you dead.
They're relentless.
They'll kill anyone
who stands in the way.
The Moores were just the first.
- This can't be happening.
- It is happening!
What about witness protection?
The Singhs have infiltrated
every intelligence
and law-enforcement agency
on the planet.
It may take them time,
but they will find you.
So what? You're telling me
that my only chance is with you?
It would appear so.
But before you
make your decision,
know this:
Once you chose,
there'll be no going back.
You'll have to walk away
from everyone and everything
you've ever known.
For all intents and purposes,
Chris Moore will simply
cease to exist.
No farewells, no apologies,
no explanations.
Now you're on
the Singhs' radar.
To contact anyone
would be tantamount
to giving them
a death sentence.
- But if I just
disappear, wh--
- I know, they'll be
worried and hurt.
Better that than dead.
How far out are we?
The jets are warming up.
We've got 5 minutes.
I need a decision.
You're just asking me
to give up everything.
My life, my name...
My whole world.
Just like--
Just like that.
Look inside yourself, boy.
You know this was
never your world.
You've always known it.
(Sighing)
OK.
Let's go.
(Man): You've arrived safely
with our young friend.
Kit, this is
Dr. Deepak Baboor,
the director
of Bpaa-Thap.
It's a great honour
to finally meet
the 22nd Phantom.
- It's, um--
- We've prepared
a reception at my lab.
You may meet me and my
sub-directors for tea and cakes,
followed by a most excellent
tour of our facilities.
It won't be necessary.
Mr. Walker has had
a long flight.
There'll be plenty of time later
to meet your people.
- B-b-but we've gone through--
- Whoa, that was kind of harsh!
Trust me.
You'll thank me later.
Baboor's a scientist.
A big believer in technology:
Electronics, surveillance,
intelligence gathering,
cooperation with
local law-enforcement.
So?
So since your father died,
that's where he's directed
most of our operations.
And that's a bad thing?
If it's at the expense
of Field Division, yes.
And that's your thing.
Yes.
Your father's thing.
And your grandfather's thing.
And so on and so on.
There's something
you guys aren't telling me.
Over the last few years,
there've been a number of...
Irregularities.
Security breaches.
It's possible the Brotherhood
was tipped off
to your location.
By someone here.
Keep your eyes open.
Be very careful
about what you say,
especially around
Baboor's people.
What was that he called me?
The Phantom?
It's a title of sorts.
One that must be earned.
End of the road.
Hop out.
Where to?
Wherever they
decide to take you.
Who?
(Girl speaking
foreign language)
(Birds chirping)
What are they saying?
Lukaisa means
"The ghost who walks."
It's a holy name
by which my people have known
your family for generations.
Where are they gonna take me?
Home.
The Phantom has been
the protector of my people
for generations.
Trust them,
As with your father
before you,
they will guide you
to fulfill your destiny.
(Boys speaking
foreign language)
(Birds chirping,
insects buzzing)
(Birds chirping)
Winston Churchill.
Your great-great-grandfather
and he were thick as thieves.
(Chuckling)
The Rat Pack.
- Mm-hmm.
Your father helped
Mr. Sinatra
recover his son
after he was
abducted for ransom.
Is that my dad right there?
- Mm-hmm.
The one in the mask?
The Phantom.
But he's in all these pictures,
going back, what,
at least 100 years?
Oh, much more than that.
1536, to be exact.
- But how could
he possibly be--
- In every case, the man behind
the mask is named Kit Walker.
And so it is passed
from father to son
for 21 generations.
Preserving the
illusion of immortality.
The ghost who walks.
It took over 4 centuries
for the Singh Brotherhood
to discover the truth:
That the only way
to kill the Phantom
was to destroy
the Walker family line.
What's that?
One of Baboor's
recent additions.
Bpaa-Thap's network links with
every major law-enforcement,
mass-media and intelligence
agency in the world.
(Beeping)
Instructions and passwords
are in the drawer.
Lab, medical facilities,
gym, motor pool are below us.
Guran will show you
how to get there.
Meals are served
in the cafeteria,
but if you prefer to eat in,
you just call the kitchen.
Room service.
- Mm-hmm.
Wow! So, wait.
So all this is just--
- Yours.
It's your ancestral home.
(Chuckling)
My ancestral home.
Once you take the oath
of your forefathers
and complete your training,
you will be rewarded
the privilege of wearing this.
You're kidding, right?
I know.
It's a daunting challenge.
We'll do everything we can
to help you assume your
legacy as the 22nd Phantom.
But I didn't agree
to take any sacred oaths
or go through any
training programs.
The only reason I came
here with you people
was to protect my friends.
I see.
I don't know what you expected.
The journals of your
21 predecessors
are collected in the library.
If you're at all interested.
Uh...
I'm sorry.
I told him not to make
any assumptions.
I'm not wearing that.
Ah!
With Flicker, the sky
is the limit, gentlemen.
The sky is the limit.
True, the results
are impressive.
But the subject's behaviour,
so unnatural.
Let's be fair there.
Doug, come on.
This is just a beta, right?
Once Lithia has worked out
and shaken loose all the bugs,
I assure you we will literally
be able to program anyone
we want to do whatever we want.
As crude as it is, even the
beta version has its uses:
Contract killings,
assassinations,
suicide bombings.
Still, it's expensive.
Oh really? And the
old way isn't?
Is that what you're saying?
Case in point: this bloody
Morpheus goes 7 figures
for overhead expenses, contract
services, evidence clean-up.
And all because McDowell had
a little bug up his butt
about Flicker's reliability.
And how reliable
is B.A.U?
One dead operative,
and the target's still alive.
Just let me do my job,
and I promise you:
I will vaporize
this Kit Walker.
It's just a matter of time.
Phantom number 22
will have very,
very short lifespan.
Such p
(All shouting)
And you realize this headache
could've all been avoided
if we had simply
deployed Flicker.
Oh! Peter, what's
that word again?
- Fore.
- Right. Fore!
(Shouting)
Hello.
All right, then.
Gentlemen, why don't
you play through?
I'll catch up.
So you had some
problems in New York.
Oui.
- That's usually
my favourite word, but--
- I will find him.
No.
No, I don't think so,
my friend.
- But Mr. McDowell--
- He's a bloody troglodyte
that still believes
in ghost stories.
No, I'm sorry.
We're cutting
our losses, Jacquot.
I can't see blowing anymore
dough on yesterday's game.
But this bastard
killed my brother!
(Groaning)
I am your brother!
You understand?
Seeking out
of personal vendettas...
(Clicking tongue)
Clean yourself up.
Are you gonna eat
that last shrimp?
No, go ahead.
How'd you know
I liked Chinese food?
I am Guran.
Guran knows all that the
Phantom requires at all times.
Truth is, we surveyed
your place for about a week
and found the containers
in the trash.
Everything I had,
everything I thought I had,
was a lie.
Everything?
Maybe not everything.
Renny Davidson?
I'm sorry.
It's none of my business.
No, you're right.
It's not.
And she wasn't.
Wasn't...
Wasn't a lie.
She was real.
(Chuckling)
Unlike Chris Moore.
I feel like such an idiot.
There's no way
you could've known.
No, but that's just it.
I did know.
At least a part of me did.
I used to have dreams
for years about this lady.
My real mom.
And I had dreams about
places I've never been.
This place.
Did you tell your parents?
Yeah!
About a million times
they had a chance
to tell me the truth,
and they didn't.
Maybe they loved you too much
to see you get hurt.
You're probably right.
But I just wished
that I had a chance to...
To talk to them.
I'm sorry.
They were good people.
I don't know.
It--it just shouldn't
have happened.
No.
But it did.
And somewhere it's happening
to someone else right now.
(Sighing)
How do you stop it?
You can't.
But if I were you,
I'd read your
father's journals.
Thanks for dinner.
(Insects chirping)
(Man): I was born in the year
1516 in the city of Portsmouth
of a seafaring family.
My father was the captain
of a mercantile vessel,
The Mary Elwyn,
upon which I was employed
as a cabin boy
on a voyage to
the South China Sea.
On the 17th day of February,
the year of our Lord 1536,
we were set upon by pirates
of the Singh Brotherhood.
(Swords clanking
and men screaming)
All hands were slaughtered.
Not a single life spared,
except for my own.
In the thick of battle,
I was thrown overboard.
When I awoke, it was broad day
and the weather clear.
I was on the sandy shore
of an island
where I saw another seaman,
still not 30 paces from me.
As I approached,
I saw that he did not stir,
and he was likely dead.
It was only when
I finally beheld his face
that the true horror
was revealed.
I recognized
the terrible countenance
of my own dear father.
I built a funeral pyre
and laid my father's
remains upon it.
I watched as he was
consumed by the flames.
Later I encountered
a native tribe
who initiated me
into their ways.
They would help me
fulfill my destiny.
For it was then that
I swore to devote my life
to the destruction
of piracy,
greed, cruelty
and injustice
in all their forms.
And my sons
and their sons
shall follow me.
(Man on TV):
Despite security concerns,
Israeli peace activist
Jalil Ben-David
will be visiting
the United States.
I know, I know!
A spokesman confirmed
that Ben-David will play a key
role at the Mideast Peace Summit
to be held on the 20th
of September at midnight.
The date is significant
for both Jews and Muslims
as it falls between
the last day of Rosh Hashanah
and the first day of the
Muslim celebration of Ramadan.
(Turns TV off)
You OK?
People don't just fall
off the face of the universe.
Yeah, baby, they do.
Every day.
Whole families?
Stuff happens, huh?
Opportunities come up.
Maybe he got a job offer.
No, he was half a semester
from graduating!
Even if his parents got a job,
he's not just gonna leave.
Maybe he wasn't doing
so good in school.
He might've lost
his scholarship.
No!
Ren, I told you time and again.
It's not police business.
And Jersey's not
in my jurisdiction,
all right?
Yeah, but can't you just
make an exception?
No! He'll call.
Or he'll turn up.
And when he does,
I'm gonna kick
his sorry ass till Monday
for putting you through this.
Call?
Dad, I found his cell phone
on the sidewalk!
Don't you think
that's kind of weird?
(Sighing)
He was walking along,
head in the clouds...
Dreaming about you and...
And then he dropped his phone.
And nobody called
his cell phone.
He never wanted to
figure out where it was.
He's just gone.
(Toaster popping)
You're not gonna
let this go, are you?
All right.
I'll see what I can do.
Really?
Yeah, really.
Oh! Here we go.
Thanks, Dad.
(Sighing)
I changed my mind.
What do you know
about firearms?
(Sighing)
These belonged to your father.
Colt 1911s.
Custom modified to
chamber a .451 magnum
rather than
the standard .45 ACP.
The only downside
is reduced capacity.
Six in the magazine
and one in the chamber.
Which is why the Phantom
always carries 2.
I've always liked
your father's guns.
But we had to upgrade
our arsenal.
I guess I'm a nostalgic.
Wow, that's heavy.
Your turn.
My father died
in August, right?
August 7.
His last journal
entry ends in June.
Well, he was pretty
sick by then.
He must've stopped writing.
No, I don't think so.
I mean, he filled it up
to the last page.
If he just stopped,
you'd think he'd would've
stopped in the middle.
If your father had one flaw,
it was vanity.
Towards the end
it wasn't pretty.
He couldn't even take
care of his basic needs.
He was angry.
There was fear,
rage, humiliation,
self-loathing.
Things he probably
felt ashamed of.
You think he destroyed it.
Wouldn't you?
(Sighing)
Ready?
The Phantom never
shoots to kill.
The bulls eyes
mark target areas
to disarm or incapacitate.
Now, assuming your adversary
is wearing a ballistic vest,
the shaded portion at
centre mass is also nonlethal.
Knees and elbows bent.
Relaxed.
Weight slightly forward,
Two hands on the grip.
Eyes level
with the target and...
Safety off.
(Gun clicks)
Relax, weight forward.
Can I just shoot?
I don't know.
Can you?
(Sighing)
Again, but this time
don't shut your eyes!
I didn't shut my eyes.
Yes, you did.
Again.
Don't worry about it.
It's just gonna take time.
This isn't working.
- The gun's fine.
I just inspect--
- No, no.
Not the gun.
This whole stance thing,
you know?
Let me deal with this
- One good way--
- No, just--
Please.
No more talking.
Think you can do that again?
(Gun clicking)
Did I break it?
No, that just means
it's out of ammunition.
So?
Get some more.
(Exhaling)
They're strong in you...
The drums of your fathers.
Take it down another 3 degrees.
(Heavy breathing)
- (Female voice):
Temperature is now minus-5°F.
All right, he's had enough.
Let's warm him up.
What the hell did you
guys do when I wasn't here?
In what year did the
the Phantom strike
in the following
countries or cities?
Cairo.
I don't know.
- Corsica.
- 1960.
- Madagascar.
- I don't know!
(Man): Come on! Go!
Move it!
Across the stream!
The Singh Brotherhood:
Describe its current
infrastructure.
The Brotherhood is an
international crime syndicate
engaging in
drug distribution,
money laundering and extortion.
Kidnapping and prostitution.
I'm sorry. I'm a little
distracted here.
Focus. They're catching up.
Trail! Trail the trail!
- I still got
a 100-yard lead.
Sure you do.
Come on!
(Grunting)
Release the dogs.
Come on! Let's go!
Let's go!
Legitimate operations.
Mostly arms trading.
Private and
paramilitary security.
Uh, what's your timeframe
to add the night vision?
Soon. Within the week.
Their main corporate front
is Singh Tactical Research.
You're toast.
Their main sphere
of influence is...
(Barking)
...Southeast Asia, the Middle
East and the Mediterranean.
You forgot Eastern Europe.
Well, sorry, Vandy, but it's
a little tough to multitask
when there's dogs
chasing after you.
The point
of this exercise:
You need to maintain clear
tactical thinking under stress.
And don't call me Vandy.
They got him!
They go him!
Go! Go!
(Grunting)
How's your
head functioning, Kit?
Still a little
tough to focus.
- I don't want him
over-reliant on technology.
It's not wrong to rely on
something that's reliable.
- It needs to be tested.
- That's what we're doing.
(Beeping)
(Barking)
Come here.
Come here, boy.
Damn it!
Ah, good boy!
(Laughing)
Good boy.
Come here!
This is a waste of time.
Get him back to Bengalla.
You live it!
Food! You hungry?
The things we do for love, huh?
Aw, would you put a sock in it?
So, what else has
Renny got you up to?
Running numbers?
Bad checks?
Bet you do her laundry, too.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
If you had kids,
you'd understand.
(Chuckling)
- Uh-huh.
Besides, we got probable cause.
Citizen called in
a burglary in progress.
That citizen was you.
All right.
Look around down here.
I'll take the upstairs.
All right.
Clark, you got anything?
Clark!
Idiot.
- Think you're right.
- Jesus!
It's not a barn, Clark!
You just about gave me
a "thrombo"!
You should cut down
on the donuts.
What you got?
Not even dust bunnies.
I want the number
of their cleaning lady.
(Chuckling)
I bet if we powdered,
we wouldn't find one print.
Something went down
here all right.
There's new glass
in this window.
Ah, yeah.
Fresh putty.
Give me a hand here.
Yeah, sure.
Yeah, I got it.
(Clearing throat)
Wait a minute.
What have we here?
Oh, yeah.
Nice catch.
All right, now.
What do we got here?
Bingo.
Homo sapiens.
So, climbed up...
Then he ran across...
Jumped over the side.
I'll talk to
the local precinct,
see if anything happened here
in the last couple of nights.
OK, Kit, just
don't move an inch.
You know, Vandy knows
you've been slipping treats
to his dog pack.
So, why would that upset him?
Well, because it's cheating.
Now, hold still.
Uh, what? Cheating?
No, I call that
advanced situational prep.
Sorry I'm late, but I got
strangled in red tape.
Does it work?
(Kit):
Yeah, no problems.
Jase here is a genius!
Yeah, why your father
appointed me as director,
I will never know.
Maybe he thought you were
the best man for the job.
That's silly.
There are many others
who could've been
better suited.
Mr. Vandermaark,
for instance.
Hey, so what's up
with this ring?
Ah, the good mark,
my most prized possession.
Vandermaark has one
like it, yeah?
It's given by
the Phantom to friends
he's placed under
his personal protection.
Oh. So do I get one?
Come!
I have a surprise for you
that will make you
very happy... I think.
So do I get a ring?
I started working on it
for your father
before he passed away.
He didn't like
the old suit either?
(Laughing)
Are you kidding?
He loathed the old suit.
He felt it was too,
uh, theatrical.
Ballistic vest and Cal helmet,
reinforced with contoured
carbon-Armour plates
and wired for cellular
and radio communication.
What is this?
- Ah, a layered micro-weave
of Kevlar, Twaron
and Heracron fibres
skinned in a titanium-ceramic
alloy neuro-symbiotic mesh,
resistant to heat
and small-arms fire.
Wait, neuro what?
You know, kind of like
modern bio-electronic
prosthetics.
In English.
OK.
When you tense, say in
anticipation of being struck,
well, your brain sends
signals to your muscles
and they, you know,
they contract.
- Well, the neuro-symbiotic
mesh works in much the same way.
Its density is determined
by the signals from your brain
and will protect you
from bladed weapons,
falls and impacts.
Oh wow!
That is so cool!
Yes, and what is even more cool
is that, like an
insect's exoskeleton,
the mesh effectively amplifies
your innate speed and strength
by a factor of 2.5 times
your normal output!
Can I try it?
(Sighing)
Are you comfortable?
Yeah, feels nice.
(Groaning)
Dr. Kim,
are we ready?
Yeah.
Set.
We're hot.
If you please,
punch the dummy
with all of your might.
Go ahead.
(Chuckling)
No, no, no, no!
Not like that.
Not with a closed fist.
You'll break every
bone in your hand.
Excellent.
OK, on the count of 3.
One, two, three!
(Electricity buzzing)
Oh my! Look,
you've broken its neck.
- Baboor, Baboor.
- Yes.
2,618.
What?
You've just struck that object
with a force of over
2,600 pounds per square inch!
(Applause)
(Kim): Yeah, yeah!
Is that good?
It's excellent!
A homeless guy called it in
almost a month ago.
Found in the area
you guys are talking about.
Injury's consistent
with a fall.
ID?
John Doe.
Guy was stripped
to his skivvies.
No wallet, nothing.
Ran DNA, prints.
No hits.
There you go.
It ain't him.
You sure this is the guy
from the warehouse?
That's him.
Ran him through AFIS and CODIS.
No hits.
What about Interpol?
(Sighing)
Hello, Jeannot Roux.
This guy's one hard ass.
What's that?
"Vio
a- - This guy's one hard ass.
You know, that one right there.
Aggravated rape.
The one right below:
"conduit obscene."
Lewd conduct.
French sure is
the language of love.
No arrests after 2004.
Hmm! Maybe he rehabbed.
(All chuckling)
Guys like this
don't go straight.
They get proficient.
Any K.A.'s?
Whoa, look at that!
There's 2 of them.
Man, this one's worse.
Meutre. That's "murder," right?
Yeah.
I saw that on
the other guy's sheet.
2 counts.
4 counts, one conviction.
Manslaughter.
Nothing after 2004.
These guys aren't
just proficient, huh?
They're professionals.
(Beeping)
(Sighing)
(Man on TV): You'll notice
to the left of the Senator
Mr. Grant Rogers.
He's been a friend
for many years,
a lawyer as well
as an advisor.
Mr. Rogers is figuring
prominently in the news today,
having received an acquittal
for Dr. Raymond Oliver.
Having a winning lawyer
at his side is...
And terminate broadcast.
(Panting)
Indoctrination of
subject, Clark Ellis.
Completed successfully.
Senator Sinclair seems
to have a lot of support
from the local community.
And this November's election
looks to be shaping up
as an easy win
for the Senator.
As the incumbent Senator,
he doesn't seem to have...
To talk.
You're right.
I'm glad you came down.
Your attitude lately
makes me doubt the sincerity
of your commitment.
What?
It's been 2 months
and you've failed to demonstrate
the maturity and devotion
to duty necessary
to step into
the Phantom's shoes.
I have done everything
you've asked!
And as far as I know,
I've been kicking ass.
Physically, yes.
But mentally...
This whole process is designed
to be transformative.
In order to become the Phantom,
you must let go
of your old life.
I can't!
The detective who broke this
case is my friend's father.
According to this article,
they've initiated
a major investigation.
They think I've been murdered.
Good!
It'll take you off the radar.
And put him on it, dead centre!
He's a police officer.
He can take care
of the situation.
That's not good enough.
I need to tell him I'm OK.
Out of the question.
If he doesn't call off
this investigation,
the Singhs will kill him.
You know that!
I will not permit you to risk
everything we are doing here.
There is too much at stake.