So, this is my senior
year of high school.
l've spent the last four years with a
bunch of horny football players and, uh
sex-obsessed teenagers.
So l figured l'd find
out what the big deal was.
l was 1 9.
l was 1 7.
Seventeen.
l think l was 1 6.
Fourteen.
Ah, we went for about 45
minutes the first go, yeah.
U m, not very long.
About threes minutes, actually.
l was so damn scared l put my
condom on before l took off my pants.
lt wasn't that great, honestly.
lt was kinda embarrassing and we
didn't know what parts went in where.
And unfortunately it was the
worst experience of my life.
lt lasted three seconds, there was no
magic, and his mother walked in on us.
We were on a bed and we
were making out and stuff.
Then she went down, came
up, and then l looked up
and she turned around and there was
a room full of people watching us.
She grabbed her vodka, she screamed,
and she bolted out the door.
Last time l ever talked to her.
( Katlyn ) So walt a second, dld
you actually make love to her?
Yeah. Well, l made love to her face.
l think l made it into this big
thing and then l was disappointed
because it wasn't what l
thought it was going to be.
Well, my first time's gonna
be with Stanford, of course.
lt's gonna be really romantlc.
We'll light candles and
we'll play some French music
and he'll pick me up
and carry me to the bed
and we'll just like,
fall into each other
and have the most amazlng connectlon.
Like, be in total sync with one another.
Ow! Franklin? Will you watch it?
Yeah, sorry.
Helen, you okay?
l'm fine.
All right.
Look, he wants you. Screw the speculatlve
romance crap and just do lt already.
Chasel l just don't thlnk
you should rush lnto anythlng.
l mean, it's your first time, it should
be special, you know. Like, plan it out.
l know,
but--
What's there to plan?
Condoms, lube, room.
l meant be emotlonally prepared
so you don't regret anythlng.
l am. l think.
Look, everyone's flrst tlme sucks.
That's why next party l go to
l'm finding the hottest, drunkest guy
l can and just getting it over with.
l'm gonna be ln New York next year.
That is such a slut-bag thing to do.
Exactly.
Look, all l'm saying is
you should just do it.
Why?
That's why.
lt's good.
They're just friends.
Yeah, you know, l stretch with
my friends like that all the time.
Whatever.
( coach ) Let's hlt those dummles, boysl
l hear she likes it rough, Frankie boy.
( coach ) Skeets, let's leave
the doll playing for home.
O'mon.
Ah, you sexy beast.
Freak.
She's all yours, buddy.
Wait, wait.
Ah, right.
We should plan this better.
Okay, yes, let's, uh,
let's plan away then.
Well, Saturday my dad's
finally out of the house.
Saturday? Okay, yeah. Saturday's good.
Say 7: 30?
Yes. 7: 30, Saturday. Done.
Okay.
Okay. l gotta go, all right?
Hey, l heard Hannah doesn't
shower after practice.
You mean cheerleader Hannah?
Yeah.
She's nice
but she probably wears the same
underwear for like a week straight.
l just thought you should know.
Well, l don't know, you guys were just
pretty close when stretching earlier.
Oh, babe, come on. We're just--
we're just friends. You know that.
Yeah, okay.
All right. l gotta go.
- Okay.
- All right.
Bye, babe.
Bye.
Bye, Dad. l'm off to Chase's.
Hey, could you come
in here for a second?
l was gonna klss you goodbye.
Oh, my God. Dad?
Look, as your parent
l feel it's my responsibility to at
least discuss this stuff with you.
Dad, l'm almost 1 8. l don't
need to hear this from you.
This is a female contraceptive.
lt goes, um, in.
My God.
lt's got no hormonal side effects.
U h, it's doctor recommended,
and you've got to use it six hours
before the, uh, event occurs.
l'm leaving. Bye! Thank you for
another painful childhood memory.
Hey, will you come here?
You think you're embarrassed?
l had to go down to the pharmacy
and actually buy this shit.
Anyway, this is the
vaginal contraceptive film.
l did not know this product
existed until about five hours ago.
Dad, thls ls even more embarrasslng than
the tlme you brought me Maxl-Pads to school.
Super Maxi-Pads!
l didn't know what size to get.
How was l supposed to know
there were different sizes?
Nobody talks about that stuff.
Anyway, this is the cap.
Also known as the, uh, diaphragm.
You take this gel and
it kills the guy's. . . spunk.
Dad, l don't think l could ever
have sex after hearing this from you.
Good. So you haven't?
Bye!
Oh, hey, don't forget the
old standby, the condom.
Make him wear two of
these. At least two!
Well, that went well.
Gentlemen, we have
earned a right of passage.
The Buccaneer Bang Book.
Between these covers, lay our virgins.
And we know what to do wlth them, yes?
C'mon, Skeets. l mean, lsn't thls whole
thlng llke a blg superstltlon, really?
Wha--? A-a
superstition?
What happens in these pages
symbolizes what happens
out on that football field.
lt unites us men for a single cause.
Need l remind you of
what happened in 1 9 7 9?
They went down as the blggest
losers our school has ever seen.
Now, we can elther be a
bunch of cock block losers
or we can have history
remember us as winners!
You pick.
l pick winners.
Wow, thank you, Marco.
Now, let's start the show.
The man who started lt all.
To you Pete, we owe everythlng.
Now, let's get to our virgins.
Trish Van Doren.
l get Trish Van Doren,
'cause she's hot, okay?
And l know she's always
had a thlng for me, so.
- Franklin, buddy?
- Yeah?
Hey, l'm glvlng you Katlyn
Chase, okay? Now, she's a freak.
She's a freak in, in what way?
J ust, you know, help her
with her video equipment.
Marco? Oondoms.
[all groan ln dlsgust]
Marcol Hey, you get Hagatha.
But she's so ''fugly'' !
No, no, no, no. Hey, hey, ''fugly''
is the new pretty. Okay? Suck it up.
Scar, you get Sabrlna. Now, she has total
nympho potentlal, you'll be lnto that.
Time to make her dreams come true.
Oondoms.
Okay. And Stanford, buddy, l mean,
l trust you and Helen are on course?
U h, yeah. We're all set
for this Saturday night.
Good. At least one of you
ladies is making progress.
Marco, give the man some condoms.
Thank you.
Now, for the rest of
you boys.. Morgan, Amy
Ashley, Steph, and Maria.
All right, let's bring it in, boys.
One, two, three. [cheer and chant]
[school bell rlngs]
Who can tell me what else
the Greeks lnvented. Trlsh?
U m, money?
Yes. Sabrlna?
Greek salad.
l suppose. Amy?
Democracy.
Sure. What else? Yes, Skeets?
Hand-to-gland
combat.
Exactly the answer l was looking for.
Although people have been
masturbatlng slnce, well, forever
lt was the Greeks that were much more
open to the ldea of self-pleasure.
So much so that they invented this.
lt's called an ollsbos.
lt helped give women the power to
orgasm while their men were away at war.
So, baslcally, Greek women reallzed
that you don't need a guy to get off.
lt also helped curb what they
thought were destructive thoughts.
Hot.
Men used them for pleasure as well.
Skeets!
Which takes us to our
next play. Lyslstrata.
The tale of a group of
women who withhold sex
untll the men ln thelr
soclety end thelr chlldlsh war.
[bell rlnglng]
And if you enjoy this play,
be sure to stop by Booklet.
Say ''hi, '' l'll even give
you my employee discount.
( Katlyn ) Hey, you guys
remember your flrst one?
What, my first orgasm?
Ooh. God, l've had so
many slnce. U m, let's see.
You've never had an orgasm, have you?
No, l mean, l think l have.
lt's okay if you haven't.
lt's not really a thlnk klnd of thlng.
lt's more you have or you haven't.
l thlnk l was llke flve
and l was at the supermarket
and they had one of those horses,
you know, that you put quarters into.
l was just sitting on it and it started
vibrating and, l don't know, l mean
all l knew is that l'd never
felt anything that felt that good.
Oh, my God. That's why you
were always on those things.
What?
M ine happened at night. l was 1 2.
And l had these really rough sheets
that got twisted in between my legs.
l had no ldea what lt was at
flrst and lt really freaked me out
but then it started to feel really good.
Well, you know, whatever,
because after this Saturday
when Stanford and l have the
house to ourselves, l will.
U m, not necessarily.
Trish has a point, but, luckily, you know,
there are many other things you can use.
U m, washing machine,
feathers, carrots, uh, cucumber.
Basically anything
you can put in a salad.
Shower head.
Guys. . .
Guys work, too.
Enough !
Hey! Oh, um, l want
to show you guys this.
l just took this video of this
guy the other day. lt's ridiculous.
My first time was with
this ugly chess club chick.
But, hey, l got in the book, so who
cares, right? l knighted her queen.
Book? What does he mean,
''l got ln the book?''
That's a myth.
[bell rlnglng]
You know, you can change
your mind about Saturday.
l think that Stanford would understand.
l don't wanna change my mind. l'm ready.
Guess what?
You stuck M&M's up your nose and
now you need help getting them out?
Ha! No! She's going through with it.
Thank God. Happy Birthday.
( Franklln ) Chase. Ladles.
Frankie.
But my birthday isn't for three months.
J ust open lt.
[laughlng] Nlce.
What is it?
lt's a vibrator.
You plug it into your i Pod
and it, you know, vibrates
to the beat and intensity of the song.
You should pick a song
with a lot of bass.
- Oh, shlt l -
What? - Oh, my God.
- When dld those two become an ltem?
- l have no ldea.
What?
U m, l think it was the
standard missionary position.
You know, l mean, you don't wanna get too
adventurous on your first time having sex.
Ah, missionary style. You know,
kept it simple, kept it basic.
Standing up, actually.
Which was quite hard to do.
We tried one that is
called the wheelbarrow.
We did somethin' that she called froggy
style, which l had never heard of.
Quite interesting.
l guess, me on top, what
is that? Oowboy? Oowgirl?
H i, Ohase.
H i, Franklin.
You need any help with anything?
U h, no. l'm good.
All right.
Oool. What's your documentary on?
U m, it's about the first
time people have sex.
Really?
Yeah.
l'm kinda into that, yeah.
You're a guy and you're
into sex. Shocker.
Hey, you know, Ohase, sometimes
people say things, you know.
They think you're kinda freaky and odd.
You might be friends with Satan.
But l wanted to seriously let
you know that l think you're cool.
l think you're really cool, actually.
Well, uh, since that was
only mildly insulting, thanks.
Yeah, no problem.
You know, since you're, uh, around
you could, uh, help me carry
this stuff to the audio closet.
Yeah, no problem.
Yeah, okay, sure. U h, thls stuff here?
Yeah.
So all your stuff
looks, llke, really good?
Yeah.
N ice. Here.
What are you doing?
U m, l was kissing you. You know, l've
had a thing for you for a long, long time.
And l thought maybe you
would wanna kiss me back.
Wanna do it again?
Where are you going to school next year?
Arizona.
Nowhere near New York?
No, no, no, no, no.
Okay.
That feels good. Really.
Oh ! Oh.
What?
You really got a hold of me there.
Don't you think maybe we should,
you know, we should slow down
or maybe go on a date first or
something like other people do?
Franklin?
Yeah.
Let's not make this more than it is.
U m--
O'mon.
No.
[whispers] What?
Maybe l should
just, uh--
Oome on, look.
l mean, you're the one
who wanted to do this.
Not like this though.
l'm sorry.
lf you tell anyone, l'll kick your ass.
Great, Ohase. Real nice!
[hummlng]
Dad, it's ten to seven,
what are you doing?
l'll give you three guesses.
Rhymes with ''maving.
'' You need in here?
No. Aren't you supposed to be at
U ncle Jack's watching the fight?
lt's just the prelims. The big
fight doesn't start until ten.
But sometimes those are the best ones.
Since when have you become
such a big fight fan?
l just don't want you to miss it.
You okay?
Yes! l'm fine.
Did you, uh, get those
brochures l left in your room?
Dad, will you stop giving
me those? l'm not going.
Hey, those are all good schools.
And they're very close to here and
they have excellent French programs.
Every bit as good as that
Sorbonne school you wanna go to.
Dad, l'm going to Paris. l'm
staying with mom. End of discussion.
After college. Or after you get
your master's degree, even better.
Would ya look at that?
Oan't believe you fell for that again.
What are you doing tonight?
Nothing special.
[pop muslc]
We did it in her, uh, in her bedroom,
right next to her parents' room.
l n a cornfield.
We did it in his mom's
living room on the couch.
l actually didn't make love, yet.
Locker rooms, yeah.
On the bed. lt's the first time, you
know, so you start off a little slow.
lt's none of your fucking business.
lt happened in the sink of a
guy's bathroom after a game.
l told him to bring protection,
he actually wore a helmet.
Anyway, a minute and a half later,
he was my first. l got him in.
Sorry, in what?
The book. The boys won the championship
that year. Are we done? l gotta go.
U m, hey, what book
are you talking about?
You know what book. l mean, you
are the girls who are still in it.
No check marks next to your names,
letting down the entire team, yeah.
Hey, look, just because you're
sleeping with the entire team
gives you no right to judge
my friends and l , okay?
Yeah, well, maybe if you stopped hiding
behind that camera you'd actually get some.
You bitch !
Ohase, stop.
Why do you care so much, anyway?
My cheerleading season ends
when football season ends.
Playoffs are when the scouts
come out to watch your routines
and l need a scholarship to
get into school next year.
So stop being so selfish
and just lose it already.
Screw you, cheerleader!
Okay, we have to call Helen right away
and tell her it's just about the book.
H i.
Hl.
How are ya?
l'm good.
Yeah?
[telephone rlngs]
U h, wanna get that?
No.
No? Okay.
She picking up?
- No. We just have to go to her house. Oome on.
- All right, let's go.
Aren't you gonna carry me to the bed?
Oh, yeah, of course.
l'm sorry.
ls she picking up?
No. God, what is the point in having
a cell phone if you don't pick it up?
Have you trled textlng her?
l'm textlng her rlght now.
Wait, one second.
lt's Trish.
Okay.
You okay?
Yes, l'm fine.
You're beautiful.
Oh, wait, wait, wait. One second,
one second. Hold on, hold on.
Heart candles.
Okay. Yeah.
Sorry.
lt's okay. lt's okay.
lf she has sex
before l do, l swear--
Keep golng, keep golng,
come on, a llttle blt faster.
l'm trying. You know, the
car only goes so fast. Shit!
Keep drlvlng. lf we can't make lt fast
enough, then maybe somebody else can.
J ust call 91 1 or
something. l don't know.
- Oh, wait wait wait wait. U h, music.
- Okay.
- French music.
- Yeah.
l want this to be perfect.
Okay.
Sorry.
lt's okay. lt's all right.
You know what? Let me,
uh, let me get on top.
Oh, okay.
Yeah.
So--
Oh.
Oh, yeah.
So, you know, like
what do you like?
What do you mean?
Are you up for
anything or--
Yeah, anything would be great.
[gasps] Oh, my God.
l'm sorry. l'm sorry.
Watch out, red llght.
You're gonna klll usl
ls it bleeding?
Not yet.
No? Okay. lt's good.
Don't worry about it. lt's fine,
it's fine. No, it's fine, don't worry.
[laughs]
Did-did you bring protection?
Oh, yeah. Yeah.
Got it.
[shouts]
Oh, shit.
You guys all right in
here? Where's the fire?
What?
There's no fire. lf there was we'd know.
My dad has sprinklers
installed everywhere.
Yeah, l know. We called
hlm, he's on hls way.
What? Oh, God !
l'll call you later, all right?
Bye. l'll call you. U m,
Yeah. we'll do this again.
- Bye.
You glrls are crazy. l can't
belleve you called 9 1 1.
lt was an emergency!
We told you the book was real.
Ohase, you've never even seen it,
okay? You two are jealous or something.
You know, you're supposed to heat that
stuff up, by the way, before you eat lt.
And, no thanks. You know, we almost died
on the way over here trying to help you.
Okay, l'm sorry for that, but by the way
l haven't eaten in three days getting
ready for Stanford to see me naked, okay?
And you two just ruined the
most important night of my life.
You'll thank us for thls later.
For an imaginary book Stanford's
not even a part of? l'm sorry.
Go upstairs, get dressed, and l will
show you that the imaginary book is real.
No!
Gol
How do you even know
what we're looking for?
All she said was that X marks the
spot and we'd know it when we saw it.
She's so full of crap.
You guys, you guys, stop. This is it.
[whispers] Oh, my God.
Hang on, let's flip to our year.
What did l tell you, man?
Ladies and gentlemen, the bang book.
Here we go.
Oh, there's Stanford.
Stanford's not that type of guy.
He's a guy. They're all that type.
Oh, Ohase, you've been
selected by Franklin.
l wouldn't even do him if l was drunk.
At least you don't have Skeets. Oh,
my God, Hagatha is next to Marco.
That's what that was about.
And there's a check mark, too.
And Hannah said this is all
about a football superstition?
Yeah.
This can't be happening.
Hey.
l know.
Deep breaths, okay?
l can get through this. Yeah.
Let's take a stand. Let's make a pact.
Yeah.
No sex until they destroy this book.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, let's not get too hasty
there. Why don't we just torch it right now?
- 'Oause they'll just make another book.
- Oh, okay.
We need to teach these guys a lesson.
Yes. l'm with you, absolutely.
All rlght, l'm ln. Let's glve these
guys a taste of thelr own medlclne.
lt's payback time.
[door opens]
Shit. Put that away. Put
that away, away, away.
What do you mean you got a plan?
Listen, l have a plan, okay?
What's your plan, to be an idiot?
God.
Trust me, man, once a woman tastes
a man's nectar, she's hls forever.
lt's somethlng to do wlth the chemlcal
composltlon of spooge. lt's nature, man l
How you gonna do that though?
l'm not gonna reveal my secrets to you.
Well, all l know is tonight
was definitely a bust.
Hey, what lf we, ya know,
don't get lnto the book?
Not another word, spanky.
Yeah, sorry.
[farts]
Oh, nlce one, Dumpelstlltskln.
Oh, no, that wasn't me, man.
Well, it wasn't me, either.
Oh, yeah, right, you
ghostfarters, man up.
How red were her llps?
l don't know. l mean,
she was wearing lipstick.
Dude, it's cultural anthropology
1 01 . lt's a primal animal thing.
When a woman puts on llpstlck up here,
she's really mlmlcklng her other, ya know.
Wah wah wee wee.
( Trlsh ) They're gonna hear us.
Hey, you shake it more than twice,
you're just playing with it, dude.
Yeah, l'd actually claim that.
[farts]
l'm so sorry, you guys.
l never fart. l swear.
Bullshit.
Oome on.
[farts] l-l gotta
go. l'll be--
Take care of your shit.
We'll meet you in the hallway.
[guys call out glrls' names]
d Let's get away J ust you and me d
d Let's get away Let's laugh and play d
d J ust feellng free d
d Come on let's move
And mount to the moon d
d Llke lovers do d
d Dance untll dawn We'll
watch the sun up here d
Okay.
We saw the book. lt's real.
Now, we all have to be strong
together for a slngle cause.
And that cause ls, destroylng the
book and everythlng lt stands for.
The way to do lt? Don't have sex wlth
any guy untll the football season's over.
(glrls ) What?
Yes, Sabrina.
l know everything
with this book is crazy
and l can only speak for myself here.
But l wanna lose my vlrglnlty, badly.
Of coursel
But you don't want your
flrst tlme to be wlth some guy
that's using you to get
his name in a stupid book.
Yeah, l mean thlnk of the stuff that
guys put us through over the years.
And for what?
So we can be sitting around the phone
for hours just waiting for them to call?
l mean, do we really
have to conslder thls?
When a guy sleeps with a million
girls, he's some big man on campus.
And we do and we get called
sluts. We have to take a stand.
Yes, Sabrina.
J ust so l'm clear, blowjobs
are in the gray area.
We're gonna need some help.
Are you guys sure we're
in the right place?
Tween Gaia worship. They're hooking
them while they're young now.
What's Gaia?
lt's like witchcraft or something.
lt's actually a good read.
l was hoping someone from class would
come visit, but l'm glad it's you three.
U h, some of us heard that
there's some klnd of a place?
Like a back room of some sort?
Back room?
Yeah, you know, like, back room.
The room in the back, the--
l'm just gonna stop talking now.
Oh.
Follow me.
lt's not exactly a back room.
lt's more of a secret garden.
A place for goddess worship.
Sit down, sisters.
Thank you.
Slt.
[sighs]
Now, tell me. This is about
the boys and football, isn't it?
Well, beware.
They will say anything
do anything in order to have you.
They will dress nice. Smell good.
They mlght wrlte you a
poem, or serenade you.
They might even say '' l love you. ''
But let me explaln one thlng to you.
One thing that you need to understand
with every fiber of your being.
The power of the pussy.
Excuse me?
Okay, that's what l thought you said.
l n prehlstory, women's power of
creatlon was held above all else.
Only through sex could men hope
to glimpse the hlgher power.
The life force that
naturally flows through women.
We are the mothers, the creators
the controllers of our relatlonshlps.
This is why you are here today.
To know the power of the pussy.
Now let us hold hands and chant.
[chanting] We are women, givers of life
mothers of earth.
We give birth. We are women.
Oreation is ours.
Our monthly blood flow
gives us the power.
The power of the pussy,
the pussy, the pussy.
The power of the pussy.
Ah ! Feel the power.
ls anyone else totally weirded
out by what just happened in there?
Yeah, just a little bit.
Are you guys crazy? That was amazing
! Please, come on. You loved it.
- You're insane, Ohase! -
You loved it. - You're weird !
Helen !
Well, what do you think of this bad boy?
What is that?
What's it look like? A toilet.
You wanted your own bathroom in
your room. Now you're gonna get it.
l wanted this years
ago. lt's too late now.
What are you talking about? l'll
have it in the closet by Friday.
Dad, why are you doing
this? lt isn't fair!
So, let me get this straight.
You don't want your own bathroom?
Yes, l did, when l was 1 2.
l'm almost 1 8 now and l'm moving out.
Also, did l mention you're
gonna get your own entrance?
l , uh, l'm gonna put in some
stairs and a door right here.
This way you can come
and go as you please.
Oh, and by the way, no curfew
as soon as you turn 1 8.
Dad, you're not doing this for
me, you're doing this for you.
l thought you were worried about me leaving,
but you're just afraid of being alone.
Okay, obviously you're not in the
mood to talk about this right now.
Get a dog !
Dad !
What?
Will you get this toilet out of my room?
l can get a different seat.
Out!
( Franklln ) l've got the theme
to our closlng season party.
Pirate night. You know?
'Cause we're the buccaneers.
And plrates are awesome.
lt's a wheel rlght now. lt's not gonna be
done. l'm gonna need a llttle more help.
But eventually lt's gonna
be a shlp, a blg plrate shlp.
Where's the poop deck?
Good questlon, Skeets, and
slnce you so graclously asked lt
l will task you with
helping Franklin finish.
Oh, God.
Let's get back to work.
Who's that?
Oh, it's just Hannah.
So listen, l was, um
l was kinda hoping that we could
maybe be alone tomorrow night.
Okay.
Okay. l'll pick you up? 6: 30?
Yeah. 6: 30's great.
Great. Bye, sweetie.
[clears throat] Van Doren.
What are you doing in
here all by yourself?
Leave me alone, Skeets. l have to study.
Really? Well, you know, l
can help you out with that.
lf you go out with me.
No way.
Oome on, Trish, l know you want to.
Oh, yeah. Hey, stop. Give
that to me. l need that.
- J ust go out with
me. - No! - Trishy.
Don't do lt.
Go out with me, Trish.
No. Stop!
l'll spray you with this soda.
Don't!
[pop muslc]
What's going on in here?
Trish started it.
Yeah, right! M r. Oswald, l was in here
doing my experiment when Skeets came in--
Olean this up, both of you.
When you're done, there's
more detention duties.
lt's a date.
Hey, don't touch my binder.
You got a 49 % on this test?
Wow, that was really close there, Trish.
Better than you.
That's a pretty confident statement.
Your ester llnks are all
messed up on questlon four.
And on question seven,
there's no hydrogen atom.
Now you know l'm smart, do
you wanna get naked or what?
This is so gross.
Oh, come on. l don't mind getting
down and dirty for Mother Earth.
Why do you have to be
such an ass all the time?
Oome on, Trish, l'm joking.
No, you're being an idiot. Why can't
you just try being yourself for a change?
l am. Okay? l choose idiocy.
lt's a cause l believe in.
This is high school. lt's our last opportunity
to be complete morons and get away with it.
l have the grades to get lnto any school
l want, but once those doors open ln J une
all l'm gonna remember is the
fun stupid shit we did this place.
Like being an idiot?
Exactly. Oarpe freakin' diem.
l mean, what has being
myself ever done for me?
Well, for one, l'd like you more.
You do want me.
So, you know l'm up for anything, right?
Except for tea bagging. l don't know,
for some reason l find that offensive.
U m, so, when?
You know, l mean, is Sunday okay?
Do you feel pressured to do this?
No, why?
l mean, how about from the guys?
l heard in some schools they actually keep
track of how many girls they sleep with.
No. No, l've never
heard anything like that.
No?
l-- Why would
they do that?
That doesn't even make
any sense, you know?
[clears throat]
U h, we should go for a drive
before my dad picks me up.
U h, yeah, but l
got my car so l was--
Let's go.
Strap in tight. You're gonna need it.
Oh. Talkln' smack. l llke lt.
[heavy metal muslc]
[laughs]
Whoa!
Hey, Helen.
Hey, what are you doing?
Hey!
[groans]
Helen, what are you doing?
Are you all right?
Yeah. No, l'm all good.
l just can't believe he
lied to me, that's all.
H m. l like this one.
Can't belleve you're shocked.
- Easy! We're still dating.
- So?
Well, we're still gonna have sex
when the football season's over.
We're going separate ways next
year. That's really freaky.
Gimme a turn.
l hooked up with Franklin the
other day in the audio closet.
What?
l gave him some boob action.
No way.
Move. l wanna see myself.
lt's funny you say that, because Skeets
came by the chemistry lab yesterday
and he was actually really nlce. l
mean, he's dlfferent when he's alone.
Still an ass, but he's different.
What are you two talking about?
What?
You're just targets for those guys.
There's no relationship, there's no love.
Oh, Helen, aren't you so lmportant?
Like you and Stanny boy are the
only ones worthy of doing it.
We actually do love each other. We've
never said it yet, but it's true.
You're belng so nalve.
Look, emotional love crap aside,
you're not ready to have sex yet
because you can't even enjoy it.
How do you expect some guy to make you feel
something you can't even make yourself feel?
Have you used your birthday present yet?
No.
Your name's in the book right next to
ours. You need to get over yourself.
[slow rock muslc]
[metal muslc]
[techno muslc]
[slow muslc]
[rock muslc]
[classlcal muslc]
[techno muslc]
[muslc stops]
[French muslc]
[shouts]
Oh, my God, what are you doing?
l , uh, l'm-l'm making a salad.
Well, you can't.
l can't?
No.
Why not?
Because l need to talk to you right now.
Okay. Wha-what, what's going on?
Those brochures from the
schools that you left in my room
they're actually not so bad.
Really?
That's terrific, you know
because l've been thinking about
what we were talking about yesterday
and the last thing l wanna be
is selfish with you, you know
'cause l really want what you want.
- l don't want you to get hurt.
- Oh !
But there are still some things
that l can teach you about life
and about relationships and about men.
l can take care of myself.
That's not what l'm saying.
What are you saying?
l'm saying don't make
guys your everything.
Okay, l won't. l promise.
l don't want you to ever
make a guy your cake.
Okay.
l don't even want you to make
a guy the icing on your cake.
Okay. l got it.
At best it should be the sprinkles
on your icing. That's all.
Thank you.
Oh !
What?
l really appreciate it, Dad. l
promise he will only be my sprinkles!
Do you not want a salad?
[pop muslc]
You know she'll never do it.
What are you talking about?
Sex. You can see it in her eyes.
She's just the type of
glrl that leads guys on
and takes her vlrglnlty to the grave.
But hey, call me when
you're tired of waiting.
[belches]
Oh, nice suit.
You look like a sperm with a face.
lt's funny, yeah.
l don't have to remind you how
precise this work is, right?
No kidding around, no joking. Seriously!
Relax, okay? What is this?
Oh, it's papier-mch.
l just mixed it, so, like, when it dries
it gets all hard and stuff, you know.
So it means the faster you work, the
faster it'll mold to the frame, got it?
Yeah. So you're saying this stuff
can pretty much mold to anything.
Yeah, pretty much.
l bet you 1 00 bucks
that l can get every chick in the class
to touch my unit at the game next week.
A hundred bucks?
Yeah.
Oh, buddy, you're on.
Oh, Franky boy.
Easiest 1 00 bucks l'll ever make.
Hey, man, where you golng
wlth my papler-mch?
[rock muslc]
Oh. Wow, that's cold.
( Trlsh ) Chase has
somethlng to say flrst.
l do?
Come on. J ust tell her already.
Oome on.
l'm sorry for what l said yesterday.
l'm sure that you and Stanny have, you
know, a very mature and loving relationship.
- Ohase.
- Okay.
We came up with another plan. Something that'll
make the guys feel just as used as we do.
Keys and a camera. What?
l thought they locked thls place.
They do. But l have the keys.
But you have to be quiet.
- Okay.
- Sh.
Take off your shirt.
Turn around.
All right.
Oh, nice.
They say if you block one of your five
senses, the other four become heightened.
Really? Like touch?
Pants, too.
Okay.
There you go.
Okay. l'll be right back.
Okay.
l'll be here.
d Hlgh school memory d
d And ln September Wlll you be d
d A blg-shot College jock d
d And forget all About llttle old me d
d l know d
d l know our love Was meant to be d
d So don't let Our love become d
d A hlgh school memory d
d l remember the prom And the ball d
d And all the thlngs we've done d
d Don't let these memorles fade d
Whoa, whoa, wait. Jesus
Ohrist! What are you doing?
What are you guys dolng here?
l'm on a date!
Oh, man.
l don't belleve thls.
What are you doing?
Don't fucking,
don't--
Oh, shoot.
- You guys playlng hlde the plckle out here?
- No.
Well, l'm sure you got a good reason for why
you got your peckers out, so let me hear lt?
- lt's just a practical joke, coach.
- Yeah.
There's supposed to be girls here.
Well, that might be
true and it might not be.
But put those puppies in the
pound and get the hell outta here.
Thanks, coach.
Who told? H uh?
Wasn't me.
Dude, the girls found
out on their own. Okay?
[rock muslc]
l can't believe this. We gotta
lock these chicks down, man.
- Stanford, l can see
your-- - Shut up, all right?
We gotta do something about this.
Okay, okay, l know what to
do. J ust follow me. Okay?
They're everywhere, man.
( Skeets ) He's just up here.
The guy who started the book?
Yeah, of course the guy who started
the book. We need help, we see the best.
Yo yo yo, check this out.
Howdy, ladies.
lf one of you guys called about the
ten-speed, you're three mlnutes too late.
No, no, we're looking for Pete.
Ta dah. And that's Handsome Pete.
Need a ride, step inside.
We're from Benjamin Dover.
That time of year again? l
should've known. lt's the book.
Yeah. U h, some glrls
actually found out about lt.
Look, we need your help. What do we do?
Well, if you have 'em
already checked off, nothing !
Next year everything
goes back to normal.
No, that's the problem.
Yeah, uh, we haven't exactly, you
know, finished the list per se.
Guys sure have it rough, huh?
So much pressure.
Always having to make the first
move. That's why l invented the book.
lt makes guys talk to
girls. lt's an icebreaker.
Wha-what are we supposed to say though?
Sensitive crap, stuff from the heart.
You know, like maybe you
got some special talent.
You show her that, you're in !
l mean, l know l guy who got lald off
of makln' a glrl a macaronl necklace.
And lf you're a dlmwlt and
you can't thlnk of anythlng
drop the '' L'' word.
M m, lesbian. Oh, yeah.
Right time, right place,
that don't hurt, either.
Like a party?
Yeah.
[phone rlngs]
Thats'actually a good ldea.
l gotta get this. lt's
my macaroni necklace.
H i, honey.
- So it's settled, boys. Party at my place.
- Yes.
Every man for himself.
l like it.
You all know what this is. Skeet's
party is this Saturday night.
We're all golng to go
and have a great tlme
but you must remember that
there's gonna be temptation.
Alcohol, expectatlons to glve lt up.
They're pulling out all the stops.
They may even take
showers and smell nlce.
These guys all think that they have
us wrapped around their little fingers.
But we're gonna go to that party and show
them that lt takes a hell of a lot more
than some cheesy pick-up line or weak
attempts at flattery to get in our pants.
Thls ls our chance, ladles.
We're the ones wlth the power.
So, who's with us?
Yes, Sabrina?
lt's only six days left.
l think l can make it.
[screams]
Well, did you enjoy your swim?
That's very funny.
Actually, l still can't figure out how
you got Ooach Becker to bust us like that.
Luck.
- Look, l know what this is all about.
- And?
And l just, l think we
should wipe the slate clean.
You know, let's just forget
about the stupid book.
A truce?
Yes, a truce.
Okay?
Okay.
You're not mad then?
No, l'm not mad. l should
be asking you that. Okay?
l-l just, l want it to be
like it was before, that's all.
Sounds perfect.
Okay.
Well, l have to go.
Okay. Wait.
What? Oh. Okay, bye.
Bye.
Dude, it's a trap.
l don't think so.
Stanford and l are just gonna put
the whole bang book thing behind us.
- Right.
- Well, he said so.
Well, l think it's the other girls
that we should really be worried about.
Look, worst case scenario, l stole a bottle
of these from my brother's private stash.
You put a few in the
punch, boner central.
- Oh my God.
- ls it safe?
- My brother uses them all the time with his girlfriend.
- Ew.
U h, hey, Helen? Do you think we're
gonna want these old albums over there?
What?
What are you doing?
Packing.
Why, where are you going?
To Paris! l've decided you're right.
We should get outta
here and move to Paris.
l'm coming with you. l
already talked to U ncle Jack.
He's calling around for me, and he
thinks he's already got a job for me.
lt turns out they have the same sprinkler
systems in Paris that they got here.
ls that nuts or what?
You're joking, right?
l'm not gonna lnterfere.
We'll be like roommates. J ust treat
me like one of your girlfriends.
You didn't raise an
idiot. l'm a strong person.
l know you are.
Well, you're not treating me like
one. l'm not your little girl anymore.
l can take care of myself.
What are you so afraid of?
Mom?
Yes, your mom.
l just don't want you to get hurt again.
You don't think l think about that? l
haven't lived with her since l was 1 2.
l wanna get to know her.
l love you, Dad, but l need
to go to Parls by myself.
l think so. l mean, she
was-- she was yelling a lot.
U h, she, l-l mean, at the
time l didn't know what it was
but, uh, you know, she-she
was smiling and enjoying it
so l think yeah, l-l would say so.
No.
U m, l mean, no.
No, l didn't. l still haven't. Sucks.
U h, l think she did,
but who really knows?
d l may be M r. Magoo
But l see through you d
d You got a way To suck me ln
and then You splt me out agaln d
[moans]
We're good to go.
Nearly there.
d To keep me bllnd d
d Dlggln' that sllly Old grln of mlne d
d lf l glve you my world
And you don't want lt d
d That's just flne d
d l'm M r. Magoo but l
See rlght through you d
Bon appetlt.
[muslc and laughter]
[techno muslc]
[Kandlce Melonakos slngs l'm Alive]
[no audlble dlalog]
Chase?
H i, Franklin.
You liking what you're seeing so far?
Yeah.
Wanna dance?
You know, l'm great right now.
You sure?
Excuse me.
Van Doren, hey. Do you
need some ice for that?
No, thanks.
U h, can you sit down? Because
l just wanna show you something.
Okay.
Okay. l wrote you a little song.
Really?
Yeah, it's a little rough,
so just bear with me. Okay?
[clears throat]
d First time l saw you
We were in biology d
d You looked pretty hot l
n those tight blue jeans d
d And even though l know You're
not quite as bright as me d
d But there's still only One
thing that l would like to see d
d That is oh l want To
Van Do you Van Doren d
Hey.
Listen, l wanna tell you something.
What?
l've been thinking about
it a lot lately and--
What? Tell me.
l wanted to tell you that l love you.
lt just made me realize
how much l care about you
how much l appreclate you and l just--l
wanted to be there for you and walt.
Hold on for one second.
Sorry, sorry to interrupt. U m,
Trish, can l talk to you for a second?
Yeah.
Sorry, hang on.
Ohase.
l gotta go.
See ya.
What's up?
l think the boys are up to something.
What are you talking about?
Because--
Sabrina?
No, you didn't?
What?
Sex, Sabrina, sex.
No,
no, l--
Hey.
Thanks. l'm going to get a drink.
Okay, l did it. l totally did it.
lt was amazing, can you believe it?
l felt more feellngs and sensatlons than
l've ever felt before.
lt hurt in the beginning,
but then it felt great.
Think l'm in love with him.
( Scar) Sabrlnal
Scar?
Where are the pills?
Okay.
What? Gimme those.
Whoa, Ohase. Ohase!
Come on, do you want lt to work or not?
Oh, ice.
Rlght, good, yeah.
This'll be a drink they'll never forget.
Make it cold and appetizing.
There we go.
Okay. First one for Stanny boy.
He deserves this. He's a liar.
Perfect. Oh wait.
J ust a few more just in case.
Who wants a drink?
Franklin, just the guy l was
looking for. Would you like a drink?
Yeah.
lt's Ohase's famous recipe.
ls lt? What's ln lt? Marshmallows?
Enjoy.
Thanks.
Oheers.
Whoo. Salty.
M m. Oh, that's nasty.
You like it?
Yeah, it's good. lt's
just, you know, it's strong.
Drink up.
M m.
Wow.
You trying to get me drunk, huh?
Something like that.
Yeah?
Let me get you another one.
Okay, yeah.
l'll just, uh, l'll be here.
Hey, what's happening, man?
Ohillin'.
Good party, huh?
Yeah.
Oh, oh, ah.
Dude, what?
You're drinking my spooge, man !
Who else drank this?
Everyone.
Oh, God !
Hey, lt's gettlng out
of hand. We gotta go.
All the guys are out
there with raging boners.
(guy ) Does anybody
else feel klnda--
No, no. No, no.
The dosage we used was too high.
l may have accidentally
put in a few too many pills.
[groaning]
[screams]
[screamlng contlnues]
Guys, come on, slow down.
ls he gonna be okay?
Hey, you take care,
Stanny boy, all right?
[Stan groans]
l warned him about you.
You're such a tease.
Look what you did.
What do you mean what l did?
That was an accident.
You told me they were safe.
l thought they were, okay?
How am l supposed to know you're
not supposed to put that many pills?
You know, if it weren't for you
two, l would have had sex by now
and Stan and l would be happy. But no.
Stop blaming us, okay?
lf you really wanted to have
sex that bad, you would've.
lt's not dependent on what
we say. lt's your choice.
Hey.
How are you?
Talk to me.
You-you did this to me. What
else is there to talk about?
What about you? There was
no truce. You didn't stop.
All you cared about was the bang
book and your llttle football team.
lt was just a stupid
superstition between us guys.
You know, like putting your right shoe
on before your left. lt wasn't real.
We're not talking about shoes here.
Yeah, l know we're not.
Okay, that's why l thought
tonlght was our thlng.
You know, like we said, a
clean slate between me and you.
l didn't care what anyone else did,
you know? We were more than that.
You didn't trust me.
That's why l ended up in a
hospital with a cast on my--
Look, let's just forget about all this.
Oome on. l'm sorry, okay?
Let-let me make it up to you.
No. No, just stop, all right? l don't
have anything else to say to you. Okay?
J ust go.
Hey, Helen. Why aren't
you gettlng ready?
Aren't you going to Stanford's game?
We're on an indefinite break.
What-what happened?
l said and did some pretty stupid stuff.
You said and did some
pretty stupid stuff?
That's my girl. Runs in the family.
You wanna talk about it?
You don't wanna know.
Hey, l'm your dad.
Oome on, give me a try.
We put sex pills in the punch in the party
and then Stanford ended up in the hospital
with a raging boner
that wouldn't go down.
Oan you please go back in time
and never tell me that story?
Dad, what's wrong
with me? l'm so stupid.
l can't do anythlng rlght.
Hey, come on, stuff happens.
Sometime your partner's
gonna end up in the hospital
with his junk in a sling.
J unk?
U h, it's an old gym term.
Anyway, my polnt ls that you're
gonna make mlstakes ln llfe, you know
and there's just no avoiding it.
You know, when l was 1 9,
l hitchhiked around Europe.
Everywhere.
l slept in the park,
got drunk quite a bit.
Then l got robbed by gypsies.
- Gypsies?
- Yeah.
They took my money,
my passport, and--
but they didn't take my trombone,
which l considered a sign of respect.
Well, it was the best
worst time of my life.
Wouldn't trade a minute of it.
Why didn't you ever tell me
this kind of stuff sooner?
l don't know.
l wasn't ready.
l was embarrassed.
l didn't want you to go.
Hey. Here.
l got you this.
Dad !
Your mom is lovely
and beautiful and funny and charming.
l hate her but you're gonna
get along great with her.
But,
um--
Are you gonna be okay without me?
l'll be fine.
l'm gonna go flnd those
gypsles. See you later.
[woman slnglng ln French]
[loud moaning]
[cheerlng]
H i.
l'm really, really sorry about
what l said the other night.
Well, we can't stay mad at you forever.
Luckily for you, we love you too much.
lt's all good. Sit down.
Thanks.
Did you change your
hair? You look different.
U h, no. Guess again.
No shit. You figured it out, didn't you?
N ice!
Very nice. l'm proud of you.
Yeah, that's great,
just when l have no one.
U m, actually, there's something
that l have to tell you two.
l wasn't a virgin when we made our pact.
You slut. l want details, come on.
Remember when l went to
Hawall? Well, lt happened then.
l met this 1 5-year-old guy
who l let talk me into it
even though l knew l wasn't ready.
l should've told you guys
about it. l just, l don't know.
l would've gone to Hawaii and kicked
his tropical ass for you, okay?
We would've been there for you.
Thanks, l know.
[cheerlng]
[rock muslc]
[people] Oh.
Yeah !
[cheering]
H ut!
[rock muslc]
Oh, fuck!
Oome on !
Blue 32. H ut l
Down again !
[whlstle blowlng]
[over P.A.] And that's halftlme, folksl
What's up with this?
l don't know. The guys are
sucking tonight though, huh?
l mean, you guys don't think they were
actually right about the book, do you?
Hey! Where are you going?
To talk to Stanford.
What? What do you mean?
What is she doing?
Stanford ! Stanford !
Wait.
l'm sorry about everything.
The boner pills, the naked pool party
trylng to klll you at the racetrack.
l shouldn't have done any of that.
But that whole book thing you
guys have is totally immature
and l thought l needed
to teach you a lesson.
l want what you want. Love and sex.
( woman ) Me, too.
Well, maybe in a different
order for you, but whatever.
l want you to wln l
You guys are so good, you're so talented
but right now you're sucking
and you blame us glrls and a book.
But the reason you're loslng ls because that
dumb book won't score you any touchdowns.
But lf you belleved ln yourself
the way l belleve ln you
you could score a bunch of
touchdowns and wln thls gamel
He's the kicker!
Okay, so you're a kicker.
Maybe that's never happened before
but a lot of great things
haven't quite happened yet.
[rock muslc]
Oome on.
[cheerlng and whlstllng]
One, two, three, four!
[rock muslc]
[cheerlng]
H ut. H ut.
[groaning]
[cheerlng]
Woo-hoo-hoo!
Blue thirty-two! H ut!
Touchdown !
[cheerlng]
H ut!
Oh, yeah.
[over P.A. inaudible]
H ut!
Oh, my God.
[cheering]
Touchdown ! Yeah !
[inaudible]
[pop muslc]
You don't need Stanny-boy, you got us.
She's rlght. We can grow old
and become splnsters together.
You should go say hi.
ls it that obvious?
Yeah.
Guys are scum.
Oh, Ohase, they're not all bad.
Tell her this ''you-me''
thing, it's a pity date.
l feel bad for you,
you're not even my type.
Thanks.
Oh ! Here he comes.
Let's go.
H i.
U h, you know
l came with--
l know.
But we're not together.
At all. l wanted to let--
Let's get out of here.
All right. Oome on !
Frank! You owe me 1 00 bucks.
For what? Belng an ldlot?
No, no. Look what she's
holdlng ln her hand, man.
Ah, damn it. Hold on.
Scar!
Thank you for introducing me
to the world of papier-mch.
Okay, how about this?
Double or nothing l can
''out-prank'' you this evening.
You are gonna ''out-prank'' me?
Okay, spanky, you're on,
buddy. Yeah. Good luck.
U m, l'm gonna go get some air.
You want me to come?
No, l'm good. Have fun though.
All right. Bye.
Hey.
H i.
So, the guys are in the playoffs.
That's good for you, right?
Yeah, it's really good.
You know, on the field the other day,
l didn't mean to tackle you so hard.
Yeah, it was, it was a
little much, l'm sorry.
Ladies, can l interest you in a
photo beside my captain's wheel?
U h, no thanks.
You never quit, do you?
Well, my creative juices are always
flowing, Ohase. Have you seen Trish?
No, sorry, l haven't.
Never mind. There she is.
Hey. Don't screw with her, okay?
Van Doren l Come here.
No.
l just wanna show you something.
l've already seen your
wiener-wheel, Skeets.
No, it's not that. And trust
me, you'll wanna see this.
H i, everyone. This next song goes out
to someone who's very very special to me.
U h, it's the four-day
anniversary of our lovemaking !
Scar?
Thls one's for you, baby.
[soft muslc]
[cheerlng]
d l heard the Bells ln my head d
d The second l saw you d
d And agalnst my Better judgment d
d l began to adore you and
l haven't stopped slnce d
d And l'm gonna Make you know lt d
What are you doing out here?
Guys are lame.
No kidding.
You want some?
What, are you trying
to take advantage of me?
You know, l've been thinking
about what you were saying.
This documentary's cool. lt's
opening up people's eyes to what's--
d So perfectly wlth mlne d
d We were made To stand together d
d B y some great U nknown deslgn d
d For now and All of tlme d
d You wlll be mlne d
d As for now And all of tlme d
Hey.
Hey, buddy.
That's good.
H i, guys!
Hey.
What's up?
Nothlng.
Hey, everybody, get ln here.
Franklln's got a surprlse for us. Whool
Skeets!
Oh, shit.
l'm about to owe Frankie a lot of money.
Double or nothing, right? Beat this.
What is he talking about?
[all shout]
[rock muslc]
Woo-hoo!
We'll get you back,
don't worry. Don't worry.
d You gotta do What you gotta do d
[trombone playlng]
So, after interviewing basically
everyone in my entire high school
and a few of my own misadventures,
l've realized something.
lt doesn't matter if you're in
the audio closet or in the bedroom
or if you're with your
boyfriend or your best friend
it's all about timing.
l haven't done it yet, but
l have a feeling l will.
d She takes her tlme
Wlth the llttle thlngs d
d Love notes Remlndlng me d
d She wears red when She's feellng hot d
d l have her but That's all l've got d
d She looks best Wlthout her clothes d
d l know lt's wrong but
That's the way lt goes d
d l don't know what She sees ln me d
d But l'm happy She's happy now d
d That she's wlth me d
d And l'm freakln' out d
d Because l'm just so lucky d
d Oh she makes me feel llke shlt d
d lt's always somethlng
But l can't get over lt d
d She thlnks lt's nothlng d
d Because she's Everythlng l
ask for Everythlng l ask for d
d And just a llttle blt more Everythlng
l ask for Everythlng l ask for d
d And so much more d
d She loves muslc but
She hates my band d
d Loves Prlnce She's hls blggest fan d
d Not blg on holdlng hands But that's
all rlght 'cause l've stlll got her d
d Keeps up on current affalrs d
d Prada ls what she wears d
d l don't know what She sees ln me d
d And l'm happy She's happy now d
d That she's wlth me
And l'm freakln' out d
d Because l'm just so lucky d
d Oh she makes me feel llke shlt d
d lt's always somethlng
But l can't get over lt d
d She thlnks lt's nothlng d
d 'Cause she's Everythlng l
ask for Everythlng l ask for d
d And just a llttle blt more Everythlng
l ask for Everythlng l ask for d
d And so much more d
d Flstflghts turn lnto sex
l wonder what comes next d
d She loves to always keep me guesslng d
d She won't Glve lt up d
d And we both know d
d lt's because Oh she
makes me feel llke shlt d
d lt's always somethlng
But l can't get over lt d
d She thlnks lt's nothlng d
d 'Cause she's Everythlng l
ask for Everythlng l ask for d
d And just a llttle blt more Everythlng
l ask for Everythlng l ask for d
d And so much more Everythlng
d And so much more d
[Rumer Wlllls slngs Wild Oherry ]