[Church bell tolling]
[Clock ticking]
It's time.
[People screaming]
Ah.
Let's get out of here.
[People shouting]
Oh, my God.
It's over.
Hey,
I don't hear anything.
Where are the sirens?
[Electronic beeping]
Collect
Sean Michaels.
[Demon roaring]
No!
[Screams]
[Demon shrieks]
[Haunting piano music]
# #
[wind chimes ringing]
Sean?
[Papers rustling]
Where are you?
You left me hanging here.
[Sobbing]
Oh, my baby.
Helen?
You were
sleepwalking again.
Why didn't you wake me up
when we got here?
I wanted to let you rest.
But you said.
The kids
have been a big help.
We've got most everything
packed already.
I'm gonna
go check on the kids.
Pete, you want to...
you want to take a break?
I just want to get...
just get it over with.
Are we separating
Grandpa's stuff from Sean's?
That would be nice.
Can I get you
something to drink?
Not right now, Mom.
Thanks, though.
You can, um,
you can stay at home tonight
if you don't want
to drive back to campus.
That's all right.
Why don't we just get rid
of all this...
shit.
[Footsteps]
That's how
I want to remember him,
you know, before he moved
into this house, and...
Katie, I think
that you should know that the...
the coroner
and the police agreed
that it was self-inflicted,
but I...
What'd you expect?
I mean, he was supposed to be
fixing this house up.
And there's black paint
everywhere,
and the mirrors are broken,
and the furniture is...
But there has to be
a better explanation.
He was not suicidal.
Can we just change
the subject?
Sorry.
You haven't talked
to your friends
in a really long time.
When's the last time
you talked to Jeanette?
She tried to relate by talking
to me about her dead cat.
You could try meeting
new kids at school.
How about that?
You know,
you could go to a club.
You could do drama club.
Join the theater.
You know,
Sean loved the theater.
[Tense music]
# #
[sparks crackling]
Fuck, Sean.
Pete?
[Water running]
[Coughs]
[Knock at door]
Are you okay?
Uh, yeah.
I'm... I'm fine.
Just... just a little sick
to my stomach.
Uh, Mom?
Can I talk to you
about something?
Let's talk when you
come out of the bathroom.
Never mind.
We don't have to sell
the house.
I mean, we've always
managed before.
It would've fixed up
real nice,
just the way
Sean wanted it.
[School bell rings]
Tomorrow and tomorrow
and tomorrow,
creeps in this petty pace
from day to day
to the last syllable
of recorded time.
And all our yesterdays
have lighted fools their way
to dusty death.
Out, out, brief candle.
Life is but
a walking shadow.
You know
he's going to get lead.
I wouldn't mind
starring with him.
It is a tale
told by an idiot,
full of sound and fury,
signifying nothing.
Scene.
[Applause]
Whoo!
Kathryn?
[Girls giggling]
Kathryn Michaels?
My name is Kate Michaels,
and I will be doing
a piece that I wrote.
Is that all right?
Proceed.
Dear God,
I heard that you can see
into people's hearts,
and I wonder
what you find,
because everybody I know
wears the same face.
They carve their thoughts
into bite-size pieces
and hack their emotions
down to a manageable size
till their words are dulled
to travel down their tongues.
I would ask you to shatter
their grotesque masks
and let me see
what's within.
But I fear finding nothing,
that my thoughts
would choke them,
and my feelings
crush them,
and my words
slice their tongues.
So you remain quiet,
and I'll pretend
that they' re hiding.
You remain quiet,
and I'll pretend
that you' re there.
Scene.
Awesome.
Ooh, thank you so much.
Okay, bye.
[Clears throat]
Bless us, O Lord,
for these Thy gifts
which we are about to receive
from your bounty
through Christ our Lord,
amen.
Amen.
So who was on the phone?
That was Miss Bliss.
Who?
Miss Bliss,
my theater teacher.
She said that
all the other girls
were more experienced.
[Clears throat]
I'll get them.
But she's giving me
the leading role.
Really?
Yeah.
That's fantastic.
What for?
[Scoffs]
The winter play, Dad.
Well,
I want to hear more,
but I have something
that we need to talk about.
I found something disturbing
at Sean's grave today.
What?
[Crows cawing]
A dead raven nailed to the
ground next to his headstone.
And there was this...
this woman.
What was she doing?
I don't know.
Exactly.
Mom's in denial
about Sean's suicide.
Sean was a mess
before he died,
completely paranoid
and delusional.
He wired pipe bombs
in his closet.
Why?
I think to protect
his notebooks.
Have you seen them?
[Tree branches creaking]
[Dog howling]
I don't know.
This is really...
This is just...
This house is...
I don't know either.
Look at this.
What is this?
Bankruptcy,
wedding ads,
mattress sale,
wholesale factory outlet,
tampon ads, used cars.
Planned betrayal?
" Cover the reflections,
any reflections. "
" He comes for us.
10:28.
10:28."
What?
" Black paint...
Worked. "
You' re going to stay?
Do I need to stop
at the store?
No, there's things
in the freezer.
Okay.
Drive careful.
I love ya.
Let's go.
[Clocks ticking]
[Peaceful piano music]
# #
[faint screaming]
[Alarms ringing]
[Screams]
[Ringing continues]
[Haunting moaning]
[Film hissing]
[Water running]
[Projector clicking]
[Glass shatters]
[Faint screaming]
[Gasps]
[Knife clatters]
[Screams]
[Shushes]
I heard somebody
moving around.
Oh, sorry.
What are you doing up?
Are you all right?
[Sighs]
I was sleepwalking again.
If you resist me,
you may find
the church against you.
They could hang you!
Sorry?
Your line.
"They could hang you
for your infidelity. "
I just thought that...
You' re supposed
to resist him.
Did you listen
to his last line?
I just was hoping that...
actually, I'm...
I got...
Maybe you should read
the script.
I can't watch.
She only got the part because,
you know, her brother...
[grunts]
[Screams]
They don't know
what they' re talking about.
You didn't get that part
because of your brother.
Thanks.
I just thought
you should know.
Why do you think
I got the part?
Probably...
because she left it
up to me.
Stop messing around.
You don't believe me?
No, I'm not gullible.
Well...
I'm not a liar.
[Suspenseful music]
# #
[haunting music]
I'm so sorry.
Don't be.
Where do you think she is?
I don't know.
Want to use my phone?
Yeah.
[Phone rings]
Shit.
Hello?
[Sighs]
Kathryn?
[Theatrical music
plays over speakers]
[Objects clattering]
Hello?
[Yells]
Mom?
[Screams]
[Groaning]
[Gasps]
[Screams]
[Demon roaring]
[Percussive music]
# #
[yells]
[People screaming]
Father?
Yes?
I didn't know who else
to talk to about this.
Denial is a natural form
of coping.
The church believes
that Satan meddles
through the acts of men,
not through monsters.
It's a waking nightmare.
I actually saw a demon
when that child took his life.
Helen.
God will shepherd you
through this.
Thank you.
[Door clicks shut]
To mourn
this tragic loss.
Whenever the Lord calls
one of his flock up to him,
it's good to take a moment
to reflect on the happy memories
you had together.
Close your eyes.
No one has to speak,
but now is the time to share
your memories about Todd.
It could be about his laugh,
his smile,
his baby blues.
[Teeth gnashing]
What are you doing?
[Hisses]
[Dramatic orchestral music]
# #
[panting]
[Footsteps fading]
Sean's notebooks?
The other side...
[church bells ringing]
Helen Michaels
saw him collect your boy.
How unfortunate.
Obituaries.
[Phone rings]
[Line trilling]
Hello?
Oh, I'm... I'm sorry
I missed dinner, honey.
I'll be home
pretty soon, okay?
I just wanted
to tell you that
it was a good idea,
getting involved at school,
I mean.
Tell her
I booked my flight.
Dad got
his business tickets.
Oh, good, okay.
Um, can we talk
about this when I get home?
Yeah.
I love you.
You too.
I'll be home soon.
Well, have a good...
have a good night.
Bye.
Sorry I have to miss
your opening night.
It's not that.
" Cover the mirrors.
Not enough. "
[Screams]
"10:28."
[Glass shattering]
" Reflections.
Any reflections. "
" Black paint. "
"Worked.
Cover everything.
The Collector
comes for us. "
" Must protect. "
Must protect...
Must protect who?
Oh, my God.
[Demon howling]
He was covering the reflections
to keep him out.
Oh, shit.
[Paint buckets sloshing]
[Tires squeal]
[Grunts]
Cover the mirrors.
Oh.
Black paint.
[Groaning]
[Gasps]
[Sobbing]
[Sobbing and laughing]
[Whimpering]
[Buttons beeping]
[Demon hissing]
Pacific Daylight Time
will be 10:28 and 30 seconds.
Beep!
[Groans]
[Demon howling]
[Gasping]
Helen, what is...
Get out of my way!
What the hell
is going on here?
[Yelps]
Mom!
[Glass shatters]
[Screams]
Call 911.
Call 911!
I got him.
I stopped him
from coming in.
[Sighs]
Charlie?
Hey, I'm here.
Peter came down
to see you,
left you some flowers.
How are you feeling?
Where's Kathryn?
She's at play rehearsal.
We have been so worried.
At play rehearsal?
Yeah, we have been
so worried about you.
No, Charlie, we got
to get her out of there.
- No, no, no.
- No. Mrs. Bliss.
You've got to lie down.
Mrs. Bliss,
she's a part of it.
No, no.
You have got to lie down.
No.
Look, we have
got to talk about
what you think you saw
in the mirror.
What I saw
in the mirror?
Yes.
You didn't see it?
See what?
You didn't see him?
It was...
See who?
The Collector.
- What?
- Charlie.
Look, I'll go get Kate
if you just lie back.
No, no.
Let me go.
Helen, what?
We got to go.
Helen!
Helen?
We' re over here.
Drive faster,
drive faster, drive faster.
Helen, get a grip,
will you, please?
We' re here, all right?
[Scoffs]
What?
Oh, for Christ's sake.
Don't; you'll pull out
your stitches!
Oh, no!
[Panting]
[Inhales]
Confess!
This is madness!
Won't any of you
listen to me?
You leave us no choice.
Perfect.
Marvelous.
[Screams]
No!
Can we get some help?
Let me go!
[Laughs]
No, no, no!
You' re...
[yelps]
Charlie! Charlie!
Charlie?
Charlie!
Are you okay?
Mom?
What are you doing here?
You' re okay.
Yeah, it's just
the dry run.
The show opens
tomorrow night.
I am so sorry.
She just hasn't been
herself recently.
I'll keep you both
in my prayers.
Katie?
[Objects clattering]
[Knocks at door]
Ow, fuck.
Katie?
You've got
a lot of stuff in there.
I got to take it down.
Come on.
Open the door.
Katie?
Damn it, Katie.
Come on, let me.
Let me in.
You got to let me in.
Katie?
[Gasps]
Oh, God, Charlie.
[Shushes]
[Broken glass jingling]
[Sighs]
Silverware?
I'll get it.
Kathryn.
You' re not allowed
to be in that play.
What?
You' re not allowed
to be in the show.
It opens in 24 hours.
What are they supposed to do
without me?
It doesn't matter.
Yes, it does.
It's one thing
for you to ruin my day,
but you can't screw up
the entire show for everyone.
I'm trying to protect you.
From what?
Can we please just
finish our meal in peace?
I have to be at the airport
in an hour.
How can you let her
do this to me?
Tell her she's being
unreasonable.
Tell her she's wrong.
Kathryn.
Dad, do you really think
that my theater teacher
would try to hurt me?
It doesn't matter
what I think.
It's just
a high school play.
This is not
just about the play.
Goddamn, tell her.
Watch your language.
Tell her
she's completely crazy.
Do you know
what time it is?
Lt's 7:36, Charlie.
It's 7:36.
10:28.
He's coming at 10:28.
We don't have time!
We don't have time.
You haven't touched
your dinner.
The Three Musketeers
ends with a hanging.
Othello strangles Desdemona.
Judas Iscariot
hangs himself
at the end
of Jesus Christ Superstar.
What do you
want me to say?
It's terrible
living like this.
I'm late.
No, no, Charlie.
Charlie, don't go.
Please, please, please,
please, don't go.
If I nail this,
we can move out of here.
Okay?
Can you hold on
until I get back?
Yes.
I love it
when you laugh.
It's beautiful.
I love you.
Oh, Christ.
"And do not fear those
"who can kill the body
but cannot kill the soul;
rather, fear him who can destroy
both soul and body in Hell. "
10:28.
[Echoing] 10:28.
He's coming at 10:28.
We don't have time!
We don't have time.
God damn it, Charlie,
do something.
Mrs. Bliss,
she's a part of it.
I'll keep you both
in my prayers.
[Horn honks]
Go!
Light's green!
Yeah?
What time does the show end
tomorrow night?
Around 10:30.
Oh, my God.
Kathryn.
Please, just let me
prove this to you
when it comes tonight.
Mom, I'm really...
I don't...
Please, Kathryn.
If nothing happens,
will you drop this?
Come on, hurry.
[Hinges creaking]
I'm going
to go get a jacket.
Wait.
[All chanting]
Dehenia Ni'enen!
[Screaming]
[Coins clicking]
[Alarm ringing]
He's coming.
[All chanting]
Dehenia Ni'enen!
[Demon howling]
In exchange
for our lovers,
destroy our enemies.
Kill Charlie Michaels.
[Panting]
[Sighs]
[Demon shrieks]
Dad!
[Skull crunching]
[Choking]
[Groans]
[Demon shrieks]
I still can't let you perform
tomorrow night.
Why are you
doing this to me?
Because I love you.
That does not
make it okay.
Katie, if anything happens
to you...
Nothing's going to happen
to me, Mom, okay?
Everything will be okay,
if you just let it.
But they' re still
after us.
Who? Who gives a fuck
about our family?
Why are you so adamant
about this?
Do you know something?
Have you listened
to yourself?
Do you think with
the entire audience watching,
she would still kill me?
She wouldn't have to.
Mom, there's nothing there,
and there never was.
[Screams]
Holy fuck!
[Knocking at door]
Hey.
Is everything okay
with your mom?
[Sighs]
Lt's just
one of those days.
Well, listen, we...
there's a cast party
going on.
I want you to come.
It'd do you good.
- Um...
- Please?
Yeah?
Do I have time
to change?
Absolutely.
Okay.
Can I come in or...
I'm really sorry
about the house.
Okay.
Oh, God.
Mom?
You got to listen to me,
Pete.
You have to, okay?
Nobody else will.
Just calm down.
10:28.
The Collector
comes at 10:28.
Sean figured it all out,
wrote it all down
in his notebooks.
It was all shorthand,
though.
People were killed.
Some were murdered...
I mean, hung like Sean.
I don't have it all
figured out.
But Sean had a girlfriend.
Angela.
Pete.
Sean had a girlfriend
he hid from us.
What's wrong with you?
How come
you' re not saying anything?
You don't want
to know the rest.
What?
Don't.
You knew?
Just don't.
Why didn't you
say anything to us?
Why didn't you tell us?
Because
I didn't say anything,
I protected
this whole fucking family.
I held
this family together.
You don't understand, Mom.
Then help me
to understand.
Angela
was part of this cult,
and your favorite
blew them all up.
He killed them,
and then he killed himself
because he couldn't live
with the guilt.
I can take you there.
I can show you
where it happened.
No, come on!
This way!
What the hell?
[Hard rock music]
# #
[laughter]
Ooh.
[Yelps and laughs]
[Flames crackling]
# #
# Of what it means
to be alive #
# Suddenly doesn't mean
that much #
Relax, just go with it.
# We came to
fuck up everything #
[man continues singing
indistinctly]
# Wishing #
# It won't bring me back #
# #
[faint roaring]
No.
[Screams]
[Yelps]
[Groans]
Dehenia Ni'enen.
This was their house.
He was madly in love
with her.
He was in
a whole nother reality.
She was always depressed
and miserable,
and she got involved with
this demonic cult following...
West Memphis Three...
and she brought them
to this fucking house.
[Timbers creaking,
glass shattering]
What if he
didn't cause the fire?
What if Sean
He made
a shitload of these
in some abandoned factory
outside of the cemetery.
What if we find
the explosives?
What if we go to the factory
and find the explosives?
Just stop, just...
I know this is hard.
I know it's easier to believe
in some heroic fantasy
than to face this.
No!
If that's where
you' re going to be,
you're going
to be there alone.
Kate's play opens tonight.
You should come.
I'll save you a seat.
I'm sorry.
Sorry.
[Haunting music]
# #
[gasps]
[Winces]
[Dramatic music]
# #
[footsteps crunching]
[Faint conversation]
You look nervous.
Don't worry.
You' re going to do great
out there.
Let me help you.
[Gasps]
Angela.
I'm waiting for Sean.
You' re waiting for Sean?
When the Collector comes.
What happened
to the explosives?
How can I find them?
Just answer me!
I tried to set it right,
told him everything.
We tried to destroy
the following,
but the detonators failed.
Please,
you have to help me.
Can I still light the fuse?
It's too short.
I'm so sorry.
Tell me
how to get to them.
[Footsteps]
[Groans]
If you resist me,
you may find
the church against you.
[Shrieks]
[Engine revs]
Come on!
[Coins jingling]
[Swords clashing]
[Cell phone buzzes]
Yeah?
Peter!
No, Pete, shut up.
Listen to me.
I can't be two places at once,
and I...
I went to the factory again.
They' re going to kill Kate.
You have to get her
out of there.
Did you find the trunk?
No, but there's
not a lot of time left.
They' re gonna...
they' re gonna hang Kate.
Peter, no!
No, God.
[Groans]
[Long beep]
Holy Mary,
mother of God,
pray for us sinners
now and at the hour
of our death, amen.
[Cheers and applause]
[Gears clanking]
Thank you, thank you.
We will have
a brief intermission
before the last act.
So please enjoy refreshments
in the lobby.
Thank you.
[Door scrapes open]
[Women moaning and gasping]
[Whines]
[People speaking indistinctly]
[Sighs]
[Whispering]
Dehenia Ni'enen.
[Straps zipping]
Need any help?
What the fuck happened
last night?
What do you mean?
I don't even remember
leaving my house.
We never left the house.
Stop fucking around.
We went up to your bedroom,
undressed.
I don't believe you.
I'm not a liar.
You' re not a liar?
Does God ever answer
your prayers?
No.
What if he did?
And all he asked for
in exchange
was to murder your lovers?
[Screams]
Mom was right.
Peter?
Run.
Run!
You gonna protect her
with that?
At least your brother died
with some dignity.
[Grunts]
[Wood clatters]
[Discordant piano strike]
[Groans]
[All chanting]
Dehenia Ni'enen.
Dehenia Ni'enen!
[Grunts]
All: Dehenia Ni'enen!
Dehenia Ni'enen!
[People screaming]
[Dramatic operatic music]
# #
[demon shrieking]
Dehenia Ni'enen!
[Screaming fades]
In exchange
for our lovers,
destroy our enemies.
Collect
Kathryn Michaels.
De profundis,
et verbum caro factum es.
[Gasping]
Oh, fuck.
[Growling]
[Gasps]
[Panting]
Set him free.
I know the price.
[Yelps]
[Echoing screaming]
[Gasps]
[Demon shrieking]
[Screams]
[Lantern shatters]
[Screaming]
[Screams]
[Glass shatters]
[Screaming]
[Groans]
[Screams]
[Yells]
[Gears whirring]
[Demon growls]
[Grunts]
[Screams]
[Punch thuds]
[Screaming]
[Flames crackling]
Amen.
[Fuses hissing]
Hey, Bliss,
you better start praying.
[Laughs]
[Laughter echoing]
[Roaring noises]
[Faint screaming]
[Metal clatters]
[Gasps]
[Sobbing]
No.
[Thunder crashes]
[Man screaming]
[Screaming]
I didn't get the part
because of my brother.
Kate.
Oh, God.
She left it up to you.
Ah, come on,
you don't believe that, do you?
You' re not
that gullible.
I just thought
you should know.
[Groans]
[Choking]
[Rope strains]
[Audience screams]
[Audience clamoring]
[Church bells tolling]
[Haunting operatic music]
# #
[indistinct whispering]