## [Classical]
[Horse Whinnies, Collapses]
[Thunder Rumbling]
[Animal Howling]
[People Laughing]
[Tapping On Microphone]
[Man] As you go forth
on your journey and lead us
into the next century,
I know that you're
going out into this world...
and will give 110%.
[Kids Chattering]
You are the best...
and you are the brightest.
- We could be looking at future
leaders of this country.
- [All Chuckle]
Writers, senators,
and scientists...
humanitarians and
heads of industry.
[Man Narrating]
A lot of years have passed
since that graduation.
And coming out of continuation
school, I had no clue what we
were gonna do with our lives.
But I knew for sure that
none of us were gonna become
senators or scientists.
Just ain't gonna happen.
Sparky was a wild one, man.
Beauty of Sparky was you never
knew where he was comin' from.
[Gargling]
Who took a dump in my mouth?
Sparky would rip off
a line of "fuck yous" better
than anybody I ever heard.
I'm gonna castrate you and fuck
your mother in the fucking ass
with your own fucking dick!
[Girl]Yeah. I'm glad
I left your sorry ass...
Fuck you! Fuck you!
[Narrator] Shit. Lardo?
He was everything you could
have asked for in a friend.
He was funny, he was charming,
had a way with words.
Dude, shit happens.
[Narrator]
Did pretty good
with the chicks...
and always seemed to make light
of a serious situation.
[Water Bubbling]
[Radio: Ronald Reagan]
My fellow Americans, I'm
pleased to tell you today...
that I've signed legislation
that will outlaw Russia
forever.
- Whoa.
- We begin bombing
in five minutes.
[Screams]
[Narrator]
Together, we were one.
I mean, we had it all.
## [Mexican, Traditional]
At least I thought we did.
## [Continues]
## [Singing In Spanish]
[Lip-synching]
[Narrator]
And every summer,
we'd get a visit from Iris.
[Knocking]
[Woman]
Iris!
[Door Opens]
[Groans]
- Anne wants to know when
are you coming to the Hut.
- [Groans]
There's coffee in the kitchen.
[Groans]
[Narrator]
And then there was Anne.
[German Accent]
Johnny boy, why is the door
closed with a girl inside?
Give me five minutes, Mom.
I'm having sex!
Johnny, stop that now!
Bad boy!
What will the neighbors think...
girl in your room
and the door closed?
They'll think I'm gettin' laid!
[Narrator]
Like we always said, a little
bit of booty never hurt nobody.
Growing up as a kid
on the beach was a blast.
I mean,
everybody knew everybody.
The surf was always good,
and every night was a party.
[Man] J. D! What's up, man?
Hey, Skinner!
What's happening, dude?
Somebody's parents were
always gone for the weekend,
and if that didn't happen,
we'd take it to
the Shelburn house.
## [Band: Punk Rock]
[Boy]
# Ow #
# Well, I want a war between
the rich and the poor #
# I want a fight and know
what I'm fighting for #
[Narrator]
But what went down
over the next 24 hours...
is something
I will never forget.
## [Punk Rock]
[Man]
# Amoeba #
# We are scientists
in our lab looking
through the microscope #
# Those little glass slides
They never lie
How can this small mind cope #
# I've never seen anything
like this before #
# This amoeba's got a mind
of its own #
# But don't turn your back
you stupid science world #
# This is reaching
for the telephone #
# Amoeba #
## [Guitar Solo]
# A one-celled creature
A one-celled thing #
# It hardly knows
its alive #
# You're better off dead
if you only knew #
# That your life's
taking a dive #
# I've never seen anything
like it before #
# This amoeba's got
a mind of its own #
# But don't turn your back
you stupid science world #
# This is reaching
for the telephone #
# Amoeba #
# Amoeba, amoeba
amoeba, amoeba #
# Amoeba #
# Amoeba, amoeba
amoeba, amoeba #
# Amoeba #
# Amoeba, amoeba
amoeba, amoeba #
# Amoeba #
# Amoeba, amoeba
amoeba, amoeba ##
[Narrator]
So check this out. Every kid has
someone they look up to, right?
Whether it's a baseball player,
a rock star,
or drives a race car-
a hero.
Well, it just so happened
that my hero, he lived
right down the street.
And this guy had the ability
to make you feel...
like you were walkin' on water.
[Machine Grinding]
[Machine Shuts Down]
What's up?
Hey.
20, 25, 45, 50 bucks.
One more payment
and it's mine.
[Knocking]
Hi!
Hello!
Good morning.
Hi, hello!
Sorry it's so early,
but, um, this may be
a little bit embarrassing,
but...
[Whispers]
we're lost.
Would you happen to know where
1117 Shelburn Lane might be?
- I do.
- [Woman] Oh, great.
Oh, good.
That's wonderful.
Excuse me.
Oh, thanks.
Yeah, okay.
Yuppies.
You know what?
Day after graduation,
summer's callin'.
I'm gonna give you your board.
Just pay me when you
got the cash.
Here's your board.
This is, um... You know,
it's your board.
I mean, I made it for you.
So you take care of the board,
and she'll take care of you.
Now go on.
Make me proud.
Hey, Mooney. Wanna come?
I gotta work.
[Seagulls Squawking]
## [Punk Rock]
[Girl]
# In the chamber of hellos
Hello, hello, hello, hello #
# In the chamber of hellos #
# In the chamber of hellos
Hello, hello, hello, hello #
# In the chamber of #
# In the chamber of ##
Huh?
[Tapping Sticks]
Two, "Q," "A," "N."
Five, seven, four.
Hey, J.D.
How's it goin'?
Hey, Del.
Surfin', huh?
Yeah, I was.
"Q," "A," "N."
Hey, I found this seaweed
with these shells.
It's sparklin', see?
Oh, yeah?
- And this.
- [Seashells Rattling]
Sea glass.
"Q," "A," "N."
I'm not really in the mood
for a nature study right now.
"Q," "A," "N."
Five, seven, four.
Five, seven...
Oh, shit.
Fuck!
[Whispers]
Nice.
[Screams]
Wake up, Ventura!
Whoo! Ha-ha!
## [Punk Rock]
[Tires Screeching]
Watch your fucking
driving, asshole!
- You stupid blind fucker!
- [Tires Screech]
What the fuck, man?
What's up, man?
What are you gonna do, huh?
Come on.
Get the fuck back in your car
and drive back to your stupid
valley and stay outta my city!
Fucking Ventura surfers!
Yeah, you say that, and then
you drive off, you pussy!
Fuckin' souther!
What's up, J. D?
Que pasa, J. D?
I lost my board, man.
Maybe someone took it.
Took it?
No one takes surfboards
around here, amigo.
[Female Reporter]
In a move that could seriously
hurt his reelection prospects-
[J.D.]
Hey, Harry.
Hey, J.D.
Where's your board?
Gone.
I don't know.
Maybe someone stole it.
Stole your board?
Uh-huh.
Motherfucker.
Beer?
I don't spend every day
workin' my ass off at the D.M.V.
so you can buy beer, old man.
- I didn't buy it.
J.D. gave me one.
- What?
- J.D., did you give him beer?
- No.
- Where's your board?
- [Groans]
[Farts]
- Rise and shine, ladies!
- [Gasps]
- Come on. Get up.
- Why are you doing this to me?
Come on. Get up.
You know, in some countries,
this is considered torture.
[Exhales]
Listen up.
J.D. lost his board.
So?
Well, so, you guys
should go help him find it.
- He lost the Mooney?
- Yeah, the Mooney.
[Laughs]
That shit didn't happen.
It happened.
Seriously, you guys
should go help him find it.
He should help me
find the bong.
- Oh, God.
- Where is it?
[J.D.] Dude, why?
[Lardo]
I don't know.
I mean,
how does something
like this happen?
Dude, I have no idea.
Mooney's gonna kill me.
It's just kind of incredible
that your board would
just be gone.
I know.
Hey, what's goin' on, guys?
Sparks.
Punk.
Hey, bro.
Where's your board, man?
Dude, my board
got pilfered.
Dude, don't flip out,
all right?
I can't fucking believe
this shit. I'm gonna fucking
kill all of 'em!
I mean, they just come and they
just take our fucking boards
like it's nothing?
These are our boards,
our property! Fuck them!
Fuck off-
All right, I'm here.
Where's the fire?
Thank you.
Okay, um, can you fold these,
please, and then put them
outside when you're done?
Only because I need you
in my life.
Love you.
So, how's things?
Oh, you know.
Same old together one day,
broken up the next,
back together again.
On again, off again.
Sex one day,
no sex the next.
It's nice to know
we have the same problems.
...theirfucking beating heart
outta their chest
and show it to 'em.
Yeah, l- Uh, Anne?
[Bat Pounding Pole]
I'm not fucking around!
Yeah?
That boy's not good
for business.
They just fucked with Sparky,
and Sparky's gonna fuck 'em up.
That's just Sparky.
He breaks it, he buys it.
All day!
Pretend this little fuckin'
totem pole's their fucking face!
[Panting]
Whoa.
[Anne]
Hey, J.D.
Hey.
- Um, where's your board?
- It's gone.
Hey, J.D.
Hey, Iris.
- How's your mom?
- She's in Vegas
with her new boyfriend.
- Did you look up
and down the beach?
- Of course! Aw, please.
- Come on.
- Well, wait. Maybe the
tide took it out, dude.
- How many times a year
do I go out?
- A lot.
- And how many times
have I lost my board?
- A lot.
And how many times
have I swum in to get it?
As many times as you lost it.
Right. And how many times
was it right there
waiting for me?
Yeah.
Every time.
Exactly, dude.
Every time,
except this fucking time.
Oh! Whoa, whoa, whoa!
Did anyone hear about Reagan
bombing Russia?
What?
Reagan's bombing Russia. I heard
it on the radio this morning.
Shh. You're that stoned
that Reagan is talking to you
personally through a radio?
No, no.
I'm not that stoned.
I'm... that stoned.
[Both Laughing]
Dude, me too.
Let's get more stoned.
What am I gonna do, man?
Fuck.
This is a symbol
for all that's sacred
to our way of life.
So, what?
Is something sacred
to your way of life?
Wake up.
A surfboard is the most
sacred thing to our way of life.
It's- It's your girlfriend,
your car and your dick,
all in one.
Guys, he's, like,
a Mexican Jesus.
So, uh, Jesus,
what do we do?
We do what we do whenever
we don't know what to do.
Oh, no! It's alive!
[Laughs]
Party at the Shelburn house
again, Anne?
Come on. We gotta
meet some new people.
Withering away over here.
Oh, God, Iris, please. Shut up.
Have some fun. Lighten up.
I want to have fun.
I really do.
Okay, then have fun.
[Groans]
Okay, who's gonna be there?
Well, who do you think?
J.D., Lardo,
the Yard guys,
Mike Moke,
um, James, Bernard-
[Grunts]
What?
What is your problem?
I just... Well, look.
I wanna meet some guys who are
into the same things I'm into.
Um, Iris, boyfriends
aren't into poetry,
painting and art.
Just have some fun,
for me, please? Please?
Yeah, for you. It's easy
for you to say. You've got
sunshine boy out there.
Yeah, that's not
that easy.
Know what?
First chance I get,
I'm getting outta here.
I'm going to New York
and I'm gonna be an artist.
You know, I don't care about
being rich or famous, dude.
I just wanna work
and keep my edge.
Your edge?
Yeah. My edge.
And when I do get a boyfriend,
he'll be into poetry,
painting and art. You watch.
Um, news flash, Iris.
Hmm?
Boyfriends who are
into all that already have
boyfriends of their own.
Crap.
I got an idea.
Oh, really? What?
Let's flash Sparky.
Okay.
You ready?
Yeah.
One, two, three.
What the hell
is wrong with you?
[Shouting, Laughing]
All right, J.D.,
tell me the story
in excruciating detail.
All right, so,
I was out on my board,
and then, like, all
of a sudden out of nowhere,
this, like, perfect wave
just comes at me.
So I paddle into it, right?
And I get up, and I lay down,
like, this sweet bottom turn,
and then, like,
I was right there, yeah.
I'm right there, and the wave
just starts throwing
its lip over me,
just, like, throwing it
over me like that.
It was, like, the most
beautiful feeling of my life.
And what happened
after that, man?
Uh...
Come on, man.
You had to see something, bro.
Yeah, uh, I'm lookin'
around, and...
And I see Del.
Yeah, man.
The first person I saw
on the beach was Del.
Del. Hey, Del.
Oh. Hey, guys.
What's up?
Hey.
Hey, hey.
Everything okay?
Yeah. Del, uh, listen.
Do you remember
seeing me this morning?
Sure. It was about 8:57,
close to 9:00.
I tell time by the sun,
and I usually get it right
within a minute or two.
All right, well, look,
my surfboard got stolen.
Did you see anything?
Yeah.
Did you see... anything?
What do you mean,
the souther?
He was drivin' a Datsun 280Z.
It was orange.
Do you remember
anything else?
Dudes, you can't get
the right answers in life unless
you ask the right questions.
Whoa.
[Lardo]
"2QAM574."
Uh...
[Sparky]
So, what is
the right question?
[J.D.]
I don't know.
Really, J.D., if I could find
the guy who did this to you,
I would kill him!
No. You know what?
I wouldn't just kill him.
[Laughs]
I'd beat his ass first,
and then I would kill him.
No. You know what?
I'd kick his ass and kill him,
but first, I'd steal his board
so he knew what it felt like.
Shut up, stupid.
Why would he steal J.D.'s
board if he already had one?
What?
If he had a board
to steal, I mean.
I'd steal that one.
Wait. What?
Which one would you...
steal?
I'd steal 'em both, dude.
Yeah.
I'm a badass.
Okay, so how are we
gonna find this guy?
Oh, she said something
about that souther
in the Datsun, yeah?
Yeah, right.
The orange 280Z, huh?
Yeah.
- You stupid blind fucker!
- [Tires Screech]
[Screams]
Oh, fuck.
Here we go again.
What-
What, Sparky?
What's wrong?
What? I saw a guy
driving an orange 280Z,
but I didn't think
that anyone would
fuckin' steal a board,
so I didn't even get
a good look at him!
Dude, relax!
What?
Fuck you. I'm not gonna relax.
[J.D.]You're just
remembering this now?
I'm gonna fuckin' kill this guy
after I kill you.
Hey, hey, hey, hey!
Who, the souther?
Yeah, man.
He was driving around
in this sleazy,
fuckin'
"pick up some pussy"
Valley boy car...
with the board hanging
out the back, dude.
Green and yellow,
right?
Yeah?
Yeah? Well, how do you know
he was a souther?
Dude, he had a fuckin'
typical Ken doll haircut.
Total valley boy
faggy-ass shit,
and... the fucker
had pants.
Like slacks.
Pants?
[Both]
Uh-oh.
Hey, guys,
uh, look who it is.
[Lardo]
It's red bikini girl.
[J.D.] Red bikini girl.
[Lardo]
Coming straight for you.
Check it out.
Mm-hmm.
What I wouldn't do to nib
on one of those nips.
Dude, what I wouldn't
do to suck on both
of those nipples.
[Together]
A little bit of booty
never hurt nobody.
Your mom home,
Sparky?
Maybe we should go in
and say hi.
Yeah, I don't know.
- Is she okay?
- Yeah.
Shit.
What?
I'm supposed to meet this kid
today, and I'm selling him
my skateboard.
You're selling
your skateboard?
Yeah, they're gonna
shut off our electric
if we don't pay the bill.
- Seriously, bro?
- How much?
Sixteen dollars.
Don't sweat it, dude.
Uh, we have to figure out this...
uh, what is it-
2QAN...
Later.
Later?
Yeah, later.
First we're gonna
get 16 bucks.
You ready?
Check this dude out.
Mr. C., how ya doin'?
Hey.
So, uh, anyway,
Mr. Candidas.
Candianedas.
Uh, okay, so-
So I see this bitchin'
wave coming in, right?
I've already heard
this stupid story from
your stepfather, the drunk.
Oh, yeah?
He was in here already?
Oh, that's great. Typical.
Hey!
Hey. So, uh, yeah,
I was trying to tell ya
a story, all right? So listen.
So I drop in on this wave,
and I'm, like, totally stoked,
and then it was,
like, I'm doin' a cutback
and I lay it down with my hand.
And I'm, like,
skimmin' it with my hand,
and the lip starts folding over.
It's, like,
coming over me like this.
And I'm like, "Whoa!"
And then I'm like, "Whoa!"
And this giant liquid cavern
of liquid water
from another planet-
[Lardo]
Dude, I've been looking
for these all day.
Look what I found.
All right.
Yeah, we'll have these.
Beef.
Uh, you got any dough?
Uh, no. Do you?
Yeah, um,
we're gonna have to
come back for those later.
Yeah, later. Okay.
Catch ya.
[Lardo Laughs]
Let's get outta here.
[Chuckles]
Feels kinda good, huh?
What?
Helpin' out Sparky's mom.
She's a nice lady.
Can you keep a secret?
Dude, yeah.
What-What's up?
Alice is not really his mom.
What?
Yeah. She's his grandma.
He just calls her that.
Where's his mom?
She bailed, man.
Whoa.
There ya go, son.
Sixteen dollars.
There you go.
Thank you, sir.
This is a nice couch.
Got it at Sears.
Now if the wife asks,
I didn't give you any money.
Sure, okay.
Harry, Peggy works
at the D.M.V., right?
Mm-hmm.
What?
All right. Bye, Marge.
Okay.
We got... 2QUAN574,
1979 Datsun,
registered
to a 17-year-old kid
named Brian Kramer,
212 South Valley Road,
Valley Village.
Here ya go.
Brian Kramer.
You don't know how much
we appreciate this.
Well, do me a favor.
Don't kill him.
Oh, and next time you sell Harry
some stolen beer, get somethin'
better than this shit, please.
Fuckin' southers.
Oooh, stand by
with the beer.
[Laughs]
[Coughing]
If you barf,
I am not cleaning that up.
That what dogs are for,
tardo.
Hey, boys.
[Both]
Red bikini girl.
Little bit of booty
never hurt nobody.
[Chuckles]
[Woman]
Do you think
she's had a boob job?
[Anne]
Hey, Mom?
Yeah, honey.
Can we, like, have a bottle
of something, please?
Oh, go ahead.
Take the half bottle
of vodka from the bar.
But no drinking and driving.
Okay. Thanks, Mom.
You rock hard.
Yeah, well, I used to.
Anne.
Yeah.
- I found it.
- You found your board?
[J.D.] Yeah.
Hi, J.D.
- Oh, hey, Brenda.
- What's this about your board?
We know where it is. I just
gotta go get it. Can we go back
to my house? I need to change.
[Anne]
Yeah, yeah, sure.
Need a hand, J. D?
- [Laughs]
- Anne, your mom's, like,
totally hitting on me again.
Mom, come on!
We talked about this.
Okay, we're going. Geez.
- Wow.
- [Anne] Bye. I love you.
I love you too.
Have fun.
[Iris] Bye.
[J.D.]
How come you're
never like that...
Oh, there you are,
Johnny boy.
I heard what happened.
Oh, honey.
Mom!
Ja. Herb, the milkman, told me.
Oh, Johnny.
Come on, Mom.
Oh, don't worry.
We'll get it back for you,
my poor baby.
We're onto it, Ma,
really.
Oh, Johnny.
I give you some stew
to take with you.
La Lumbie.
Come on, sweetheart, huh?
Did you miss me?
I need ya now.
I do.
Come on now.
Come on.
Here you go, honey.
Jesus, Mom. I'm communing
with my automobile here.
Oh, Johnny, please.
Just try it.
All right, all right.
Mm-hmm.
Uh-huh.
Ja. Is good.
Uh, now can I go?
Oh. Ja.
Here, Anne. Hold this.
I gotta focus.
Okay, baby.
Come on. Come on.
Come to Papa.
Mmm.
[Engine Revs, Dies]
That's it. Come on.
Come on, baby. Come on.
[Engine Starts]
Whoo! Atta girl!
Good luck, Johnny.
# Oh, Gidget goes to hell #
Whoo.
[Laughs]
So get this.
I totally saw this guy
today, man.
He's drivin'
down the road...
in this bright-ass orange
"look at me" 280Z.
The typical souther.
I mean, it seemed like his hair
was personally styled
by Vidal Sassoon.
And, uh, he was wearing pants.
[Anne] What?
[Lardo]
Pants.
# Gidget goes to hell #
# She's the center of attention
as she runs into the wave #
# Paddles way outside, yeah
waiting for the big one ##
[Knocking]
[Boy]
Come on. I gotta pee.
[Exhales]
[J.D.]
Everybody!
We got a situation here,
so listen up.
These fucking southers,
they come to
our beautiful beach...
and they desecrate it,
and I'm sick of it!
It's over, and they're
going to pay now.
- [All Cheering]
- So fucking frightening.
Totally.
It turns me on.
What?
Whatever.
God, you're so weird.
All right, now here's the deal.
An elite team of us,
a band of brothers,
are gonna go tonight,
in La Lumbie...
and we're gonna find
this guy and we're gonna
bring my board back!
[All Cheering]
We're going.
No. Anne, no.
I'm not going.
Yes. Shut up, Iris.
We're going. Shut up.
No-Anne... Shit.
[Belches]
My fellow Venturians,
the time has come.
- Lardo.
- Fuck it.
- [Engine Starts]
- [All Cheering]
What, Mooney's?
[Engine Stops]
What are we doing here?
There's somethin'
I need to do.
So, Mike, I know I should
have been more careful.
I'm gonna get the board back
and I'm gonna get you
that last payment too.
We got an address,
we know where this guy is.
So, you know, don't worry.
It'll be easy.
These kids.
They're gonna run off
to the Valley and probably
get into a bunch of trouble.
Let's go get us
a surfboard.
Mooney's comin' with us.
Now we can take on the
whole fuckin' Valley, dude.
Let's do this.
[Engine Starts]
## [Surf Rock]
## [Man Singing, Indistinct]
Why do you call your car
La Lumbie anyway?
Well, it used to be La Bamba,
but the "L's,"
they took over.
Well, it was Bomber,
then La Bamba.
Now it's La Lumbie.
Yeah. Because
le lan lalk lin lels.
I'm sorry?
Le lan lalk lin lels.
You can talk in "L's"?
Wow. I really gotta
get away from here.
[Laughs]
## [Continues]
We're goin' to war,
and we need war music.
We need a fuckin'
battle hymn.
Yeah.
- [Anne] Check the tapes.
- [Sparky] To the tapes.
To the tapes.
- Germs.
- Uh, Ramones.
- Bob Marley.
- I got the Thompson Twins.
[Mooney]
No. No Thompson Twins.
Pick a tape.
Tape?
Fear.
[Lardo]
Hell, yeah.
- Right on.
- [Anne] Whoo.
Now that is road-trip music.
- [Man On Tape]
One, two, three, four!
- Mooney rocks.
Turn it up.
## [Volume Increases]
# There's so many of us
There's so many of us
There's so many #
# There's so many of us
There's so many of us
Let's have a war #
# So they can go die
# We could all use the money
Let's have a war #
# We need the space
# Yeah, clean out this place #
# It already started
in the city #
# Suburbia #
# Will be just as easy #
# There's so many of us
There's so many of us
There's so many #
# There's so many of us
There's so many of us #
There's so many of us
There's so many #
# There's so many of us
There's so many of us
There's so many ##
The valley
of the shadow of death
in all its wretched glory.
Millions of southers,
wearing pants.
I hate pants.
I hate pants too!
One of 'em named
Brian Kramer.
Yeah.
Somewhere down
in that cesspool of humanity
is J.D.'s surfboard.
Watch for Van Nuys
and turn right.
I'm from here,
remember?
[Man On Tape]
# This place is comin'
like a ghost town #
We need gas.
# Bands won't play no more #
# Too much fighting
on the dance floor #
Hey, Sparky.
What's up?
I challenge you
to a sponge war.
All right, you bastard,
show me what you got.
God, I can't wait to
get outta here next month.
I know.
Parsons's gonna be so cool.
You'll be in New York,
and meanwhile,
I'll be at UC Santa Cruz.
Oh, but you'll like it,
Annie. You'll love it.
You'll meet some guy,
an intellectual who surfs.
You'll fall in love,
get married, have babies,
grow old, fade out.
You make it sound
so boring.
Are you kidding?
I wish I could do that.
I'm... I'm too psychotic.
You got nothin'. Huh?
Come on.
Ah, but you'll be
in New York. Your life
is gonna be so awesome.
I mean, I hope so. I just can't
wait to visit all the places
I've read about.
You know, like C.B.G.B.'s.
I wonder who's
playing there now.
Oh, Max's Kansas City
where Lou Reed and the Velvet
Underground played with Nico.
Grace Church, where
Allen Ginsberg and Jim Carroll
read their poetry.
Someday I just really hope
I meet Laurie Anderson.
Um, who's that?
You know. She has that song,
"Oh, Superman."
I don't know it.
[Both Shouting]
Yeah.
Whoa, whoa.
Hey, whoa.
Whoa, what?
## [Mexican, Traditional
Playing Over Speakers]
- [Lardo]
Yes. Yes, it is.
- Oh. Oh, yeah.
[J.D. Laughs, Grunts]
Whoo.
Oh, gasoline.
Oh! Oh!
[Laughs]
Hey!
[Laughing]
- Here we go.
- Why are they doing that?
Uh, they lost a bet
to Lardo's cousin,
so now every time
they hear that song,
this ensues.
Just like that!
[Moaning]
That's the dumbest
fuckin' thing
I've ever seen.
[Sparky]
Fuckin' jerkin' La Lumbie!
[Laughs]
Yeah, all right!
Hey. Hey, Mike.
Yeah.
You all right?
[Man On Tape]
# This town is comin'
like a ghost town #
There it is.
This is the part where
they cut to outside the car...
and we see, like, this
jerky point-of-view thing.
And there's this guy
dragging his foot.
He's creepin' up on the car,
and we don't know it,
but he's got a steel hook
for a hand.
Whee!
Shut up.
- [Iris] Just save it.
- All right, seriously.
What's the plan here?
- Torch the place.
- Sparky. Down.
What if we sneak
around the house
and look in the windows?
You're such a perv.
That ain't a perv thing.
This is James Bond
shit here.
[Laughs]
No, no, no.
We get a brick,
cover it in a towel,
douse it in gasoline,
set in on fire and chuck it
through the window.
That's a bit extreme,
Sparky.
One more.
- One more what, Mike?
- One more beer.
Yeah.
All right.
So assuming our information's
correct, my surfboard's
in that house,
in his car,
or he hid it someplace.
Oh, my God.
Just do something... anything.
How 'bout that?
[Lardo Laughs]
Knock on the door.
Totally.
[Deep Breath]
Uh... Hi, sir.
My name's J.D.
Uh, these are my friends,
and, well, it seems...
We're here 'cause
there's a problem with...
Do you have a son?
You see, my board
was stolen today, and...
Well, we think that
maybe Brian...
That-That's his name, right?
That Brian kind of...
Well, that he was the one
who stole it, and-
We got a license plate
from an eyewitness.
And we're pretty sure
that he's the one
who stole my board.
But maybe we got it wrong.
[Whispering]
It's okay.
[Dialing Phone]
Hello.
[Sparky]
Dude, you got it!
Yeah. It was right there
in his room.
That was, like, too easy, man.
We should just get
outta here, bro.
No. We're not goin'
anywhere yet.
There's one thing I hate
worse than a liar.
And that's a thief.
I need to apologize.
My son's done a bad thing here,
and I can understand
you all being upset.
- What's your name?
- Mike Mooney.
Well, Mike Mooney, I suppose
you have an idea of how
you'd like to handle this.
I think we'd like
to handle it ourselves.
My son stole a surfboard.
He didn't kill anyone.
It's understood.
All right.
What's up with you?
Nothing.
Come on, Iris.
I know you
better than that.
What's goin' on?
What?
Don't "what" me.
What's goin' on?
There's nothing
going on, Anne.
Iris. Speak to me.
I know the guy. Okay?
I know him.
You what?
- You got it back.
Right on.
- [Anne] That's awesome!
[Mooney]
That was too easy.
Yeah. Now what the fuck
do we do?
Why don't we just,
you know, go home?
What? What?
No, no, no, no, no.
Fuck that, J. D!
We came all the way
out to this Valley.
We gotta do something
to this fucking guy!
Come on!
[Anne]
Come on, J.D.
You got your surfboard back.
There's still time to go
back to the Shelburn house.
Imagine the look
on everyone's face when
you come back with the board.
No! Shh! No.
Getting the board back
is only half the journey.
Totally.
[Opens Tailgate]
You know what you
gotta do, right?
I mean, you gotta
find this guy.
And scare the living
shit out of him.
[Lardo Laughs]
[Sighs]
Okay, great.
Um, so what
do we do now?
[J.D.]
I don't know.
I'll know it when I see him.
That's it?
We're just gonna wait here
until he comes back?
You don't get it, do you?
I can't walk away from this.
I gotta- I gotta either
wait here till he comes,
or I gotta go
find the guy.
That's it.
That could take forever.
Do you know how fucking huge
this city is?
He's at Buffalo Records
in Tarzana. He works there.
[Sighs]
At least that's-that's where
he worked when we were dating.
[Laughs]
You dated this guy?
Iris.
He wears pants.
- Idiot. You have pants on.
- That's completely different.
He gave me records, okay?
It lasted for, like,
10 minutes.
And then I dumped him,
and he got all freaky.
I didn't know he would do
something like this, J.D.
I'm sorry.
Okay? I'm- I'm really sorry.
## [Woman Singing Pop]
Studies have shown
that acts of revenge...
actually trigger a response
in the brain's pleasure zones...
like, um, when you eat
or you have sex.
[Iris]
Really?
Yeah.
And where did you get
this tidbit of information?
Uh...
Maybe it was in the American
Journal of I Don't know What
the Fuck I'm Talking About.
Ho-ho.
[Anne Laughs]
[Fake Laugh]
So, how shall we
do this?
Just take it nice
and smooth.
All right.
I can be smooth.
Okay. I will be with you
in one second.
That's it!
That's it right there!
That would
be nice.
[Tires Screech]
- [Sparky]
That's him! That is him!
- [Lardo] Go for the door!
Hey, guys, be careful.
We're comin'
through the door!
[Sparky]
Fuck you!
You're gonna
fucking die!
Open the door, asshole!
Go fuck yourself,
motherfucker!
I'm gonna fucking kill you!
I'm gonna fuck you up, bro!
Fuck you!
I got it!
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
Sparky, put the fucking
rock down!
[All Shouting]
He'll call the cops.
[Mooney]
Fellas... Bros,
guess who's calling the cops.
[All Shouting]
[Sparky]
I'm gonna kill you!
- [Anne]
Get in the fucking car!
- I'm gonna kill you!
- I'm gonna fucking...
- [Others Shouting]
- [Mooney] Let's go.
Go, go, go!
- Sparky, get in the car!
Cocksucker! I'm glad
I dumped your sorry ass!
- Once you fuck with me,
I don't stop!
- Fucking asshole!
Fuck you!
You better sleep
with one eye open!
[Out Of Breath]
Sorry, guys.
Oh, it's amazing
what someone will do
to get the latest hit.
It looks like
the only hit they wanted
was on you, Brian.
It's...
[Exhales]
How did we do?
Uh, not so smooth.
What do we do now?
Beer!
[Iris] Beer!
[Laughs]
## [Muzak]
Pierpont Vodka, huh?
Yep.
- That's imported, right?
- Sure.
I hear them crazy Russkies
make this shit out of potatoes.
Yeah. I'm gonna need
to see some ID.
[Chuckling]
Yeah.
Just kidding.
Thanks a lot.
There you go.
Can you change four bucks?
Need some help?
I got it.
Have a good day.
Happy New Year, chief.
Come on, baby.
How's it goin'?
Hey. Kenny.
So, uh... Yeah, I see
this bitchin' wave
comin' in.
And it's, like, pitchin' over.
I'm, like, scratchin'
for the outside, like-
I'm goin' like this.
[Panting]
And it's, like, pitchin',
and then it slams me
on the ground, man!
And I'm, like, whoa!
Getting worked, dude.
And then... Do you surf?
No.
[Clears Throat]
Hey, man, I do this thing
with my hair.
It's killer, bro.
Ready?
[Shrieking]
[Shrieks]
[Exhales]
So you're
from Ventura then?
[Laughing] Yeah.
Yeah, I can tell.
- These are 69 cents here?
- [Pops Lips] Yep.
In Ventura,
they're 49 cents.
Hmm. Then you should go
buy one in Ventura.
Man, what kind of lifestyle
do you live?
- That's insulting.
[Laughs]
- [Lardo Burps]
Have a beer with Fear, boys.
[Largo]
Yeah.
## [Loud Rock]
[People Laughing, Shouting]
## [Continues]
Yes!
## [Man Singing, Indistinct]
You guys aren't
gonna believe this.
- Mooney went with the guys
to find J.D.'s board.
- Wasn't he in 'Nam?
No, but he saw
Apocalypse Now,
like, nine times.
Hey, everybody!
Listen up!
Those guys make it
back with the board,
we're lettin' 'em on the deck.
[People Cheering]
Bitchin'.
Whoo! Thanks, Santa!
Yeow! Ha-ha!
[Engine Stops]
I don't get it.
This guy dated you,
and you dumped him.
Why'd he steal my board?
I didn't do nothin' to him.
[Iris]
I have-
[Laughs]
I have no idea, J.D.
I told you.
He's just a freak.
[Burps]
So, this is the most
exciting stakeout
I've ever been on.
[Anne]
It's like a surf contest
with no swell,
and everyone's just sitting
there waiting for something
to happen.
Not the West Coast
Invitationals.
You goin' to that,
Mike?
No. I'm out.
[Largo]
What? Why? You killed it
last month at Pismo.
Killed it.
Dude, I finished 34th.
Comes a time to move on.
I surf for the fun of it
and shape for the love of it.
[Anne, Laughs]
So, I was just thinking.
[Sparky Snoring]
You know, in a couple months,
summer's gonna be over.
[Lardo]
So what?
That always happens.
So? We're all out
of high school now.
Some of us are gonna
go to college and...
get jobs,
start doing adult stuff.
Yeah, and shit
that we hate.
Look, all I'm saying is,
you know,
things are gonna be...
different now.
Man!
[Clears Throat]
I hate this shit.
Start talkin' about
the future,
gettin' all high
and serious.
[Scoffs]
Shit. I don't know
what I'm gonna do
in an hour.
Yeah, and that's
really fucked.
What are you saying, Anne?
A lot of people,
they stay in Ventura,
keep partying, surfing.
People like who... Harry,
you know, who gets kids
to steal beer for him?
Great fuckin' role models, J.D.
You think we should
buy into this shit-
that we should start workin'
and wearin' pants?
Is that it, huh?
Buying insurance.
Or get a vacuum cleaner
and shit?
Yeah?
You really think that this
is all there is to life?
[Exhales]
Maybe.
If I thought that,
I would so fucking
kill myself.
[Mooney]
You don't have to,
you know?
You don't have to buy
a vacuum cleaner.
What choice do you have,
Mooney?
We need more beer.
[Lardo]
I'll go.
Me too.
[Iris]
Yeah.
Are you okay?
Will you help me,
Lardo?
Those guys are acting
like such guys tonight.
Yeah.
[Laughs]
This pot's having,
like, no effect.
Um, you just gotta give it
some time to kick in,
you know?
Careful, dude.
[Sighs]
I'm thinkin'
about Iris.
Anne's goin' to college.
Probably meet some guy.
Iris is movin'
to New York.
How do you guys
do that anyways?
Do what?
Get chicks and all, man.
Easy. Just put
your hand here...
inside their leg.
And then you just
slide it up.
Slide it up.
It works every time,
man.
Yeah. Feels pretty good.
Not your own leg, man.
The chick's.
Oh.
Well, Lardo says
apple wine works
pretty good too.
It's like... It's just
like driving a car.
What would you do
if you were gonna go
on a long road trip...
with... La Lumbie?
Mmm, get in,
start 'er up...
and take off.
Go.
[Laughs]
God, no. Listen.
You gotta... You gotta
sweet-talk her a little.
Give 'er a little loving,
a little nurturing.
You baby her a little.
You check her, um-
You check her fluids-
make sure there's
enough lubrication.
You kick the tires...
make sure your rubber
is good.
When you feel confident
and ready,
you slide
in the driver's seat.
You tickle the starter
and you turn her over.
Then you... You slip it
into drive...
and you gently...
start to push her forward.
And then
you're on your way.
But that's when you
have to... you have
to listen to her,
really start
to pay attention.
And as she starts to warm up,
her temperature starts to rise,
that's when you know,
you know, you can...
you can pump her
a little harder.
You know?
And she'll let you know.
When she's ready, she'll-
she'll start to hum.
And when she starts to hum,
you go pedal to the metal,
as hard as you can
for as long as you can.
That's... That's
when it's good.
That's when it gets,
you know-
That's, like,
you're a machine...
on the open back road
somewhere in America...
with nothing but, like,
forest or cornfields
on either side of you,
with stars and sky and-
And no traffic lights.
There's no coppers.
There's no worries.
That's as-That's
as good as it gets.
That's...
That's being a man.
That's heaven on earth
is what that is.
What does all that
have to do with
gettin' women?
[Exhales]
That-
You don't have
to worry about it
for a long time,
um, Sparky.
## [Reggae, Indistinct]
All right.
Where's the turn?
It's coming, l-I think.
It's either coming,
or we passed it.
What?
Turn here.
Turn here!
Okay, okay!
[Lardo]
Take the back streets,
all right?
Okay. Valley View.
Valley Lane.
Valley Drive.
Great.
They're all the same
stupid name.
Damn. We're gonna miss it.
[Anne]
Miss what?
The fight.
Lardo, you are so busted.
You wanna see the fight.
Yeah. I kind of do.
Okay. Where are we?
Lost. Totally,
completely lost.
I'm leally, leally lost.
Loh, ly Lod!
Li'm lost lin lels!
[Shrieks]
[Laughing]
Not funny, Lardo!
What have you
done to her?
[Crying]
[Engine Sputters, Dies]
All right, what
just happened?
Well, I think
we're out of gas.
You just filled it up.
I only put one dollar in.
- [Groans]
- [Laughing]
Doomed.
We're all doomed.
[Whimpers]
Whoa.
- Whoa, what?
- You hear that?
I don't hear shit.
That's just it.
You can't hear
the ocean.
That's weird.
You can't hear it.
You can't smell it.
Yeah.
[Vehicle Approaching]
Whoa. Shit.
You proud of yourself,
Brian?
What got into your head?
Stealing... I know I didn't
teach you that.
What's he doing?
You think this
reflects well on us?
Shh. I can't hear him.
You're damn right
it doesn't.
[Snoring]
Okay, boys.
Shit.
You can come out.
Sparky. Psst!
[Snoring Continues]
You got somethin'
to say?
Why'd you do it?
Do you even surf?
Then why steal a surfboard?
It was stupid.
Just forget it.
Too late for that, Brian.
Just tell him.
My girlfriend...
Iris.
She broke up with me
for some, uh, surfer.
So you were just pissed
at some random surfer,
and so you decided
to steal my board?
What's the fuckin'
logic in that, huh?
You got your board back.
This is over.
That's not for you
to say.
Now, the way I see it is this.
You have two options.
One, you can
call the cops.
[Scoffs]
Or two, you can dole out
a whipping for yourself.
What's it gonna be?
I'll take option number two.
Dad, these guys are
gonna fuckin' kill me.
Brian, don't embarrass
yourself any further.
You get three swings.
That's all. Fair?
Fair.
I got him!
[Grunts]
That's one.
Fuck, Sparky.
- Piece of cake.
- Come on. He's drunk. He
doesn't know what he's doin'.
I said three swings.
That counts.
- You got two left.
- Wait a minute.
He said one of you guys
gets three swings.
He already took one,
so he's gotta take
the other two.
I mean, that's the rule. Right?
Three swings, one guy.
That's what he said.
Fine.
Did you hear that,
Sparky? Huh?
Yeah. Yeah.
Two swings.
Just get me close.
I can't miss him.
Get in there.
All right, fairy boy.
What the fuck?
Aw, fuck!
That's two.
That should count
as two and three.
Keep quiet. Take your licks.
He hasn't even hit you.
Get up, Sparky.
You gotta get up.
- You got one more.
He's laughin' at us, man.
- All right.
One more. One more, Sparky.
Come on! Come on!
Don't laugh at me!
- Dude.
- [Laughing]
- What you laughin' at?
- This is your last chance.
Then I'm takin'
my boy inside,
and that's it.
Come on, Sparky.
Get up, man. Get up.
You gotta get up.
Get up, Sparky!
Get up! Come on!
[J.D.'s Voice, Distorted]
Come on, Sparky!
Get up!
[Thinking]
I got it. I got it.
[Distorted Laughing]
[Distorted]
Come on, Sparky!
Get up! Get up!
[J.D.]
Whoa!
- All right!
- Oh, shit!
[Laughing]
Sparky, man!
Sparky, you did it, man.
You did it.
You nailed him, man!
You got him! You got him!
[Snoring]
Sparky?
Holy shit.
He's asleep.
[Laughing]
All right then.
You fellas
satisfied?
Now I want you
to make up.
Shake hands.
I, um-
I'm sorry, man.
It's cool.
No real harm done.
You okay?
[Muffled]
Yeah.
[Deep Breath]
Come on, Brian.
Let's get you inside,
put an ice pack
on that jaw.
Excuse me.
I never got your name.
Sam. Sam Kramer.
I just wanna say it was, uh...
It was real nice meeting you.
I just... I wanted
to say that to you.
I was gone a lot
when he was growin' up.
Didn't do a very good job,
I'm afraid.
Most of the time, you do
the best you can do and...
hope the rest just...
falls in line.
And... sometimes it does.
[Pats Shoulder]
Don't forget Sparky there.
Wiener man. What'd you do,
go down to Ventura
and get more wieners?
[Laughing]
Hey, bro.
Kenny, dude,
I ran out of gas
about a mile down the road.
Yeah, I was just wonderin',
can I borrow a gas can?
Oh, man. Well, uh,
this isn't Ventura.
You know, we sell gas cans.
We don't just lend them out.
I'll be happy to sell you one,
and I'll sell you some gas too.
- Oh. yeah.
How much are they?
- Three dollars.
Three dollars?
Yep.
Yeah, I got three bucks.
I think I got three bucks
somewhere in here.
One. I got one.
[Coins Jingling]
Hold on.
Okay.
Dude, 2.20- Oh.
Three bucks.
And 15 cents.
Yeah.
So I guess you have
enough to get, uh,
15 cents' worth of gas,
wiener man.
Hey, bro, look,
can you just-
Give me a break, man.
Let me borrow the gas can.
I'll bring it right back, dude.
Look, man, we sell 'em.
Okay? We don't rent 'em.
[Pushes Money]
[Mooney]
Dude, where are
your friends?
Lost in the valley
of the shadow of death.
This whole day has been, like,
one endless bummer, dude.
It's all about-
Hey, bros.
How's it goin'?
Do you, like, have
a gas can I can borrow?
My car ran out of gas,
and, well,
this dude won't let me
borrow a can.
Uh, you ran out
of gas, huh?
Yeah. It's just, like,
a mile up that way.
We got some beers left over
if you help us out.
Yeah, sure, man.
Sure.
Bitchin' can, dude.
Thanks.
Hop in.
Man, I just wanted
to fuckin' kick
that guy's ass.
You know, just-
just kick his ass.
One punch.
Just one fuckin' punch.
You got one punch.
Well, yeah, but...
I mean, I should've
fuckin' pounded him.
I should've kicked
his fuckin' teeth in, man.
You know what?
I'm gonna go back
in there.
You wanna come?
He said three swings,
Sparky.
Oh, who gives a shit
what that old fucker said?
I'll kick his ass too.
Fuck, Sparky!
I'm sick of it, man.
You talk all this bullshit.
"I'm gonna do this,
I'm gonna do that."
And you just get drunk
and you don't do nothing.
You don't do shit.
So shut up, all right!
You okay?
I just
wanna go home.
Thanks, bros. Hopefully,
it'll fill up and we'll
be able to get outta here.
Hey. Hey, what are
your names?
Esmeralda.
Guinevere.
Esmeralda
and Guinevere, huh?
- Hey, where you from?
- Africa.
- South Africa.
- Johannesburg.
Can't you tell
they're just fuckin' with us?
Oh. Is that true?
You just fuckin' with us?
- Hey, listen, guys.
Thanks so...
- I don't think so.
- [Anne] Get the fuck
away from me!
- Fuckin' asshole!
Let go! Lardo!
Get off me!
Hey!
What the fuck?
Go, Anne! Go! Go!
Aw, fuck!
[Groaning]
You like that?
- Hey, asshole!
- [Groans]
Motherfucker!
[Gasping]
- Later, bitch.
- [Groans]
- # I don't give a damn
'bout my reputation #
- Get in the car! Fire it up!
Pieces of shit!
Get in your fucking
piece-of-shit van,
or I will fucking
smash your brains out!
Come on!
Come on, Anne!
Let's go!
# And that's what I'm
gonna do #
# And I don't give a damn
'bout my bad reputation #
What about our beer?
[Tires Screeching]
# Oh, no, no, no, no, no #
# Not me #
Aw, shit!
They're gonna follow us.
No, they're not.
# Oh, no, no, no, no, no #
[Laughing]
Fuckers.
# Not me ##
[Vehicle Approaching]
Whoa. They're here.
## [Soft Rock]
[Man]
# Nobody ever knew
they would #
# Nobody ever thought
they could #
# Livin' out the life
that they lead #
# Well, what's right, wrong
Sailin' along #
# Livin' by the ocean
and a-singin' a song #
# Mama always said
What's wrong with you, boy #
# You better get your mug
right back to school #
## [Continues, Indistinct]
# And in the surf
you will find #
# A little piece of mind
anytime #
# Livin' out the life
that you lead #
# My mother is the ocean
and it lets me see #
# Really nothin' else
can make me free #
## [Continues, Indistinct]
All right.
Thanks for comin', Mike.
Yeah.
I'll get you
that money too.
Just give it
when you get it.
So?
[Engine Stops]
Gotta grab my skateboard
out of the back.
Hey, Sparky. Hey.
Thanks, dude.
No, really.
I mean-
[Sighs]
That shit I said before,
it's just- I don't know.
[Chuckles]
Weird fuckin' night, huh?
Yeah.
I just-
If I gotta have someone
at my back,
I'm just glad
it's you, dude.
Yeah?
Yeah.
We're gonna be talkin'
about this for years.
We will, won't we?
I'm gonna catch
some z's, man.
Yeah.
You goin' surfin' later?
What else?
You know, I actually
enjoyed myself today, man.
Me too.
Later, Sparky.
Uh!
I gotta find my tape.
Uh, I got it.
Cool.
I gotta go to work.
So, I guess
I'll see you.
[Door Shuts]
[Iris]
Of course.
Hey, uh, you know,
whatever happened back there...
Oh, he just... He just
roughed me up a little.
The fucker, he tore
my shirt.
You're okay, and I'm okay.
So we're good, right?
You-You're okay?
You know what?
[Exhales]
Whatever doesn't kill you
makes you stronger, right?
Whoa.
[Laughs]
Dude, I didn't
make that up.
It's still good though.
Yeah?
Yeah.
Later?
Sure.
Hey, I'm really sorry
that prick stole
your board, dude.
- It's not your fault.
- [Scoffs] I know that.
[Laughs]
Later, gator.
Nice work.
Hey. Later, darlin'.
Tell your mom
I love her stew.
I love her daughter.
You're such a liar.
What? I'm so totally
committed to you.
Yeah, you're committed
to something, but...
it ain't me, babe.
What's that
supposed to mean?
When you figure it out,
call me.
Hey, Lardo.
What do you think
it all means, man?
What?
The whole thing, dude.
I mean-
This guy gets dumped,
he steals my board.
He doesn't even
know me.
And Del just happens
to be there, and it's,
like, we get this name.
And because of that,
we go to the Valley?
Yeah, yeah. No, no.
We're building over
in Ventura.
Oh, it's wonderful.
Four stories.
[Lardo]
Brian Kramer, bro.
He turned out to be
not such a bad guy,
just some dude
who got dumped by Iris.
Bro, she took his heart,
and she just, like,
ripped it up into pieces.
She's fuckin' vicious,
that girl.
Well, we got your board back.
[Brakes Squeal]
Shit!
Oh, shit!
[Groans]
[Sighs]
It looks okay, dude.
Mmm.
- It doesn't look too bad.
- Whoa!
Hey, man!
Whoa! No!
[Board Clattering]
[J.D. Narrating]
At that moment, it hit me.
It wasn't about a surfboard.
It was about the journey-
with my friends.
Lardo and I are still
the best of friends.
He has a beautiful daughter now
and always makes the best
of every day-
in typical Lardo fashion,
of course.
Sparky lived every day
like there was no tomorrow.
He rode his last wave in
at the age of 25.
He was truly
one of a kind, man,
and I'll always remember
the crazy shit we used
to do together.
Nobody did it like Sparky.
Miss you, bro.
Iris went to New York
and became an artist,
just like she said
she would.
She's not rich and famous yet,
but she still keeps her edge...
and visits Ventura
whenever she can.
Anne found a great guy
willing to commit to her.
She's married,
has a beautiful boy.
And I still remain great friends
with her and her family.
My hero... Mike Mooney.
He's a family man now.
Still the legend on Pierpont
and hand-shaping surfboards
in the same garage...
for the love of it.
## [Rhythmic Tapping]
Hey.
[J.D. Narrating]
There's been a whole lot
of change in Ventura.
But then again, lots of things
have stayed the same.
Like Del.
## [Rhythmic Clapping]
And as for me,
I got a beautiful wife,
four great kids,
play music with my friends,
and still surfing...
in Ventura.
[Woman]
# Love is so strange #
# When you don't know #
# How can you tell #
# Where you're goin' to #
# You can't be sure #
# Of any situation #
# Somethin' could change #
# And then you won't know #
# Whoo #
# Where do we go from here #
# It seems so all too near #
# Just as far on beyond
as I can see #
# I still don't know what this
all means to me, no #
# I have nowhere to go #
# I don't know what to do #
# And I don't even know
the time of day #
# I guess it doesn't matter
anyway 'cause #
# Love is so strange #
# Destination unknown #
# When you don't know #
# Your destination #
# Somethin' could change #
# It's unknown #
# And then you won't know #
# Destination unknown #
# Life is so strange #
# When you don't know #
# Your destination #
# Somethin' could change #
# It's unknown #
# Then you won't know #
# Destination unknown #
# Whoo ##
## [New Song: Punk]
[Man]
# Well, this isn't
the right thing to do #
# So let's go #
## [Continues]
# Young girls
know what they're after #
# And young girls
don't kiss me good-bye #
# Rockets shoot off
into space #
# And buildings rise
through the sky #
# Bang, bang
Well, I got mine #
Reach for the sky ##
Subtitles by LeapinLar