Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
An Invisible Sign
Then the king ...
Once upon a time there was a kingdom ...
dad told me when my birthday is ke10.
I love my father's story ...
A future where all people will live forever!
Eventually everything becomes strange, crowded population of the kingdom began.
Subtitle By: GingErwan
Removing  royal mandate to reduce the Population ...
decree of the King.
All my people, please select a family to die.
A mass executions bring back much-needed space.
I Apologize for the inconvenience, but it is a necessity.
Each family was murdered.
Except for one family.
Your honor, we are unable to decide.
We loved each other so that we all die together.
No! They can not die! They guard the bakery!
They make the best cinnamon bread in the kingdom!
And if we each own pieces?
With the discount will be combined as one person less to stay here.
Interesting.
Continue
But her daughter refused.
Dad, I love my legs.
Do not be selfish! Like one of us dies?
- You can save my arm!
- After my right ear!
There is no problem about losing one of my fingers.
I walked with my nose!
I guarantee the foot, wrong!
LEG x 2.1 = LOVE Well, I have another.
Okay, I'll do it.
Once in a sense they qualify ...
The family is not getting better, and the business got worse. So ...
family began selling their bread cinnamon ...
by mail to the neighboring kingdom.
Since there is no need to look at them, it was a success!
They obtain a lot of money.
And the farmer said to his daughter ...
"See what you can accomplish when we unite?"
End
This is the last birthday party.
There are two things I love in this world more than any ...
that is running and Mathematics.
My father was a mathematician, so math is love love my dad.
What's this? What are you reading?
- Pre-calculus?
- Yes
We both feel safe in numbers.
In my family, 1 and 1 equal to 3.
- I hope when I grow up ...
- Life is beautiful.
My father was a track star in college ...
and I dreamed of the day I actually ...
will run faster than him.
But the last good day my dad has ...
no one wins.
What?
That's when I started knocking on wood.
hit each number, each number and give me security.
Without them I would be alone.
They knew the body repair ...
but to fix his head?
My father looked much ...
but I knew he was there, somewhere.
And I'm determined to bring him back ...
then make a deal with the universe.
I'll give it all you like ...
and the universe will come back to me my father.
I gave up dessert ...
I gave up going to the movies ...
I gave up my friends ...
I gave up flipping through the atlas ...
I give up runs.
The more I liked one thing, more is needed to destroy it.
The only thing I did not give figures.
If I can jump rope 43 times without a mistake ...
or if I can catch the ball 27 times in a row ...
The number of fallen leaves that I have to say ...
is equal to the number of letters in the name of my father ...
then maybe I'll be back.
Never stop counting ...
I never stopped hoping.
Rate
insurance ...
Trusted ...
Perfect.
Then, suddenly, my mother decided that three is too many.
Is my drive?
You have no friends, no job.
It's time to go.
But I like it here!
You lie, Mona.
And the worst part is that you do not realize it.
I should care.
You do not.
On the third night, my math book and I agree.
We can help you with the first month's rent.
I save a little, and his father have a disability pension.
He will never find an apartment with a private well as us.
FOR RENT
Suddenly I knew what it was like eternity.
Very long.
Mother!
Mona Gray?
"There we go! I finally got to the point.
- Here is Miss. Gelband.
I am the head of his elementary school.
- Yes.
I just found her mother in front of the bakery.
Our math teacher, Miss Swordstrum ...
fled to Paraguay to be revolutionary.
Then his mother told me ...
You live in the city ...
who are unemployed but have a college degree ...
- Math. It's you! "Me?
Our new math teacher!
I remember playing when you were a child ...
while other children were playing dodgeball ...
You sit in the swing to make the division.
You work for the mayor, Mona Gray!
Why say I have a degree in Mathematics I left college?
Need to turn to pay the rent.
Why? It was you who threw me out.
- You may want to teach.
- I hate it.
The Committee welcomed to come to accept it!
I like to think of ourselves as being above average.
A teacher for every subject.
I think that makes you our Pass the Math!
We will want to brighten the decor.
Something optimistic and fun.
You make a mistake. I am not a teacher. I do not ...
There is an old saying: "There is no teacher to become a teacher."
I studied mathematics in space with Mr. Jones.
1 ... 2 ... 3 ...
7-8
13 ... 21 ...
Who can tell me what is the next number in this sequence?
- Ms. Gray? 34%
- Yeah right.
I've never seen him without wax number around his neck.
Number varies according to mood.
High when he was in a good mood ...
lower when he feels depressed.
I wondered whether he had a father figure that I needed.
To the world, only the number ...
but for us ...
signs are visible.
Mr. Jones quit teaching and opened a hardware store.
And I was the only one who understands why.
He tried to increase their numbers.
We did not talk more ...
And then I can count on you?
Hi!
First class?
I Miss Gray.
- Really.
Can I call you "mom"?
Series Second, look at the numbers on the board.
Child
Take a look!
Figures are cool.
I liked the second.
I love the ninth.
I like 5.
- You are the third series? yes
What's your name?
- Elmer Gravlaki.
Okay. Thank you.
Please sit down
Let's go!
make jokes.
How to say ...
Your name and favorite number?
He hit me!
-What is your name?
- Danny O'Mazzi.
Danny can not throw things in the minds of others.
Go to the corner and stood facing the wall.
"Cool." It's not fair!
Why he'll stay in the corner facing the wall?
Not a good thing. This is a punishment.
I Williams Rita ...
and I want you to know that Ellen always pee ...
when it becomes nervous.
He has a change of clothes in a room nurse.
So go get changed, Ellen.
Mlle. Gray?
I'm Lisa Venus, and my favorite number is 1 billion.
What?
- What to say our name ...
- And our favorite numbers.
- Yeah, if the league!
And you are ...
- Ann DiGanno.
Lisa, why not choose a number between ...
- And 9?
- Nine ... I mean, 2. No, seven!
Seven?
Seven, of course.
Okay. I have several other volunteers?
Also! Also!
Also! Call me!
My name is Levan Beeze, and my favorite number is 1.
Okay, Levan, Lisa and you come here for the next ...
and shape of their body.
What is the total Lisa Levan more?
- Eight!
-That 's right.
Lice from her hair to give the answer.
I do not have lice in her hair!
Ann is in a bad mood because her parents would divorce.
- My mother was a lawyer of his mother.
- They will not be divorced!
Is a separate courts.
Levan, the confidentiality of attorney-client confidential.
Very nice. Who wants to be 8?
I?
- Okay, Danny.
Who wants to be o. .. plus?
- Also! Also!
"Call me.
This is the first equation of human!
What do we do now?
What about us ...
- You think?
What if ...
Our numbers ...
with nature?
One of you will bring ...
number ...
every Friday!
As a show of numbers.
And let's call ...
"Figures and Materials."
- Can I be first? Is that OK? "
Lisa ... Venus ...
bring very good.
I'm glad you became a new math teacher.
-Dad?
Father, today is my first ...
Mona ... Mona ... read the book ...
a physician and professor at Harvard.
It is called "Shape of Health."
Come here. I'll show you. Come here.
According to the book ...
injured Olympic athletes use them. They have done studies.
The problem is out of the opening round!
Mona is a book that can be relied upon.
Want to join?
Come on. Can you feel, right?
You sit here ... sitting here ...
"Take a deep breath."
and let it all go through the hole.
And let it all hang out. Leave out, let it out ...
Resume. Inspire ...
and exhale.
"What happened?
It is called "Shape of Health."
I'll call Dr. Wallace.
This solution also does not work.
And you're not helping!
I have a doctor at Harvard Medical School!
Experience with caramel extrapolation.
Making a mess, but ... love of children.
Never fill it.
This sorbet is yours?
ora.
This is a funny name, huh? "Sorbet".
If you say several times is ... "Sorbet" ...
Sorbet ...
Sorbet?
Not so funny, but it is a weird name ... "Sorbet."
So is the new math teacher? Mlle. Gray?
I'm Ben.
Ben Smith. I teach science.
This idea is one of the greenhouse?
Greenhouse! Half the room talking softly with their glass houses ...
the other half, no ...
and we will compare ...
their growth rates. Why? What happened?
Rita's mother found him crying in the bathroom ferns ...
saying things like "You're a disgrace to his family" ...
and "What you see, you bastard ... you nuts?"
What is the reaction of plants?
Do not be cute!
Let's discuss this in my office, Mr. Smith?
We have to discuss it in your living room.
Even more, Ms.. Gray.
Mlle. Gray, 7 clouds fall.
Mlle. Gray!
- Hey! Be careful, sucker! Sorry.
- Does she wear?
- Looks like garbage.
- Lisa Venus ...
- Yes.
... What's in your head?
- An IV
- Understand? What is my initials.
No, no.
There are his initials.
Almost was.
- You are retarded.
- Ann!
I am ready Numbers and Materials.
Rate
Me too.
Materials and ...?
Remember!
Every Friday we bring the number of Nature.
Or things that look like numbers.
Mlle. Gray, never remember anything!
How could a teacher?
Danny, now for the angle!
Good for you,,
- Lisa ...
Numbers and Materials!
Please.
Subtitle By: GingErwan
This is my zero. This is the Nature.
This is not Nature. It's plastic!
Plastic is derived from nature.
It is created by humans, and humans derived from Nature.
Zero times anything is zero.
127 minus zero equal to 127.
10 billion less than zero ...
equal to 10 billion.
What?
Certainly.
Good.
- What has this big?
- Ann!
Mr. Wilson: Hi ya Id consider selling directly to you! this skirt on the way & have been posted so you should contact you soon! I'll look for the slip transmission to see if I could see when it will be sent & returned to you. Best greetings LOLITA J
Who wants to come next week?
Also! Also!
Fireflies are not flies or bees. Do beetles.
And is on every continent except Antarctica.
And why do they glow?
Good question. Especially to find a partner.
The man gave the signal and waited.
Expect that women ...
respond.
- Lisa?
- Ms. Gray!
You wait for someone?
My aunt. He's always late.
Want to touch me I. V?
Just do it.
Press.
Where'd you get that?
- With my mother.
He has a very serious cancer and wearing a red wig.
Guess what her cancer.
- Of the lungs?
- No.
- Colon?
- Boca?
- No.
- Throat?
- Breast
- No.
- Heart?
- Pancreas?
- No.
Blood ...
- Brain?
- No.
BONE
SKIN
- No.
What else is there?
Eye cancer.
- Never heard it.
- It's pretty new.
My mother is one of the first. Will die in less than a year.
Is there anything I can do?
I like pirates. Hate DiGanno Ann.
Are you sick?
"What do you mean?"
Lisa!
Hurry!
If you want to do something for me ...
so do not be sick. Not ever.
Lisa!
He does not need a cardiologist, Eva, you need a psychiatrist.
"What's the problem?"
- Mom, what is it?
- No, everything is fine. Come on.
Come on.
No matter how many times I asked ...
the answer is always the same ...
- None.
Lisa wearing a crown as the truth.
She makes jewelry with plastic.
And I only have the word "nothing."
-Dad?
Happy Birthday, Mona Gray!
Happy birthday.
Just live. "
Let's go for coffee for a change. As a family.
''We are a family.''
Like other families.
Hi Table for three, please. Thank you.
I can not sit here. This is ... air flow.
No, that's gross. Gross.
Come to the fund.
No, no ... not! Whether under the AC.
- Here's good?
It's nice!
Thank you. It's great.
Now ...
let's have some fun.
This is Mona's birthday!
Go to the hardware store and buy 2.5 kg of fertilizer.
No, not now. We celebrate.
I have a surprise. Who came on his birthday.
Therapy with a magnet.
- Magnet?
- Keep your voice down.
I do not want to go back to the FDA.
- Why?
- Why? Because ...
- Since they confiscate! "Thank you.
May reclassify Health Form to get rid of it.
Mona, do not disturb your father.
Mlle. Gray?
Hi.
Are you a parent? Hi I am ...
Ben Smith. His daughter and I worked together.
- I am a science teacher. "Hi,
- I am the mother of Mona. Very pleased.
- Mr. Gray, I imagine.
Sit with us, please.
Agree?
Forgive me now.
The Moby Lane here is fantastic, and toast ...
You ... FDA?
ora.
"Well?"
- You are here?
- The short version:
I moved here when my fiance ...
got a job as a librarian at the hospital.
Then he ran off with a nurse. That's funny. They stole my car.
Sorry.
This is a tragedy. Sorry.
That's all right. I made a mistake.
All my calculations are wrong.
They must be tired of hearing this, but you ...
very similar.
Really? Everyone says that ...
- Mouth ... No doubt.
How you ever been to Science?
I have always had an interest in ...
know why things are like them.
My father also influenced me, but ...
"I want to be a scientist!"
I think I'll buy what you ask.
Mona, do not!
"We do not ..."
- Can I help you, Miss Gray. Just wait.
- A 2.5 kg bag.
- But this ...
- Should I go with you?
- Mona, please sit down.
It's your birthday! It was his birthday.
Congratulations!
Mr. Jones.
I came to show the new catalog Panida tool.
I have everything I need.
This is my card. Go find me.
I hope your day fun!
He says one thing about that number for the first time ...
when she was 9 years old.
Hi, Mr. Jones! Glad you better. Nine times better than yesterday.
Yesterday you 2.
It is remarkable that a child's record.
You're a great observer.
Notification?
I woke up and thought ...
"If Mr. Jones to use even numbers, my dad would laugh today."
"If he uses an odd number, the new drug will work."
"He must know the number that helps."
But if he knew, he said.
It was just a neighbor who was looking the other way.
So I decided to throw 60 eggs at his car on Halloween.
Hi, Mr. Jones.
- Hi, Mona. "Well?"
why do you use this number in the neck?
I think you know.
Know.
Know what?
I also wear an invisible sign.
I say ... "Fuck you, hypocrite!"
I'll take the ax.
Is $ 28.
See what we can achieve when we unite?
See what we can ...
You are the 3? You are the 4?
You are the 5? You're 6?
You are the 7? You're an 8?
Are you a 9?
1, 2, 3 ... 6, 7, 8 ...
Why do it?
At home, the ax. At school he was 7.
A little wrapping paper and some stickers ...
and turned my nightmare into Numbers and Materials.
- Levan, what happened?
- It's scabies.
Scabies?
Who said that?
Ann? What about you?
My tongue was swollen!
My tongue!
My God! His tongue?
Danny, what's wrong with you?
Malaria!
Emergency calls 911.
- I want to report the epidemic.
"Where are you?"
- Something like chicken pox.
- You know, you can ...
"Miss."
You can make a week of malaria ...
if you make a good tuberculosis today. How do you think?
- What are the symptoms?
- Tired, coughing. Coughing a little.
"Miss."
- With strength.
I'll send an ambulance.
More power! Perfect.
- And cramps.
"Miss."
- Curve as if gas. Is that OK? "
So: "There we go, I finally got to the point.
Rocks!
Very nice, Elmer. It was as if he has too much gas.
"What happened?
We are representing life.
- Lady?
- Help children understand ...
symptoms of the disease.
You. .. is ...
fired!
I did not say two words ...
and then reject me?
Wake up, Lisa. You are not sick.
I suffer from cancer.
my mother's wig is made of human hair.
They have some that are not, but you can tell.
Come on.
Wait. Still more must be done a little cancer.
Mlle. Gray?
What is it?
It's a ... 7.
- It's not a 7! This ax!
- It's a 7.
- Love Guru!
- Enough, Ann!
Ann was angry because his father had a girlfriend ...
and my mother, a lawyer his mother ...
have pictures to prove it.
- It does not exist! Yes!
Levan, just gossip. Do you have to sit in the corner!
Very good
does anyone know what this is?
Bird beak.
- It's like the mouth ...
- It's ass bird!
Danny!
As for the singing!
Let's pretend it was a mouthful.
And the mouth is always hungry.
And 179 ...
less than 255.
Mouth always wanted to eat the higher number.
Mouth larger because come 5556.
Right.
This is called "greater than" and "less than".
Who wants to come here and make your own?
I'm dying of diphtheria!
Get out of my room now!
Not again, Ellen!
"Faking sick is very difficult."
"The disease is less false than true disease."
Car accident?
- Do not know if I can compare ...
- Yes, I can.
I had a car accident once. I survived.
War
Old age?
Old age is nothing more than war.
Disease is the biggest of all!
Murder
Mine is the largest.
No,
They say psychopathic serial killer.
Sad, but true.
Cancer?
Fight! Fight!
Stop, you two! Stop!
Or I call your parents!
His mother would not know.
Silent ...
- Ann!
Better you should control the classroom, Miss Gray.
Remember to create a "greater than" and "less than"!
Lisa ...
no one is bigger than anyone else!
This is not true.
You're the best teacher in the school.
You know, my father was sick.
Lisa, do not be late to class?
I went, Miss Gelband.
Mlle. Gray ...
Lisa seems happy in his class!
Must create a great atmosphere!
Although I do not understand why, at lunch yesterday ...
he took a cigarette, bologna ...
margarine and a packet of sweetener!
Have you heard that?
Looks like a theme lunch.
A lunch with the theme of "cancer."
- Yeah right.
Thank God.
he has someone as well-balanced ...
like you in her life.
Thank God.
Well .. see you tonight!
- Tonight?
- Open School Night.
Ace 20h sharp!
- Why not move?
- Why do not you move away?
We're here. We must speak with all teachers in Ann.
We'll leave the math to the end. Ann says that she is a bit strange.
Hi!
You must be a math teacher.
I am the aunt Lisa.
Lisa is one of my students are smart.
I always hated math, but Lisa is a strange child.
Well, should not be easy for him ...
Now?
And for me?
I crossed the state to care for her e. ..
and did not get a "thank you" from anyone.
He had to get my license to work as a broker.
Maybe go back to school. Now I can not do anything about it.
- Maybe when her mother is better ...
- Increase?
What spacecraft are you falling?
Forgive me now.
I sing seductive lure you here?
No, I ...
If anyone asks, this is a scientific demonstration.
Environment.
- I also avoid the elderly ...
Me too.
"Well?"
agree on something?
It is a smile?
- No.
- Yes
This is very pretty when she smiles.
I must go.
No, do not go.
We are making progress. The last time he saw me, you fired me.
You fired me.
Do not worry. If there are people who would be fired here, is you.
May saw that Ellen made with pork yesterday.
That's ... gave me nightmares!
You put ... Lisa to represent the cancer!
"Yes, I know.
She knew that her mother had cancer?
Sei. That's why she chose.
- He will die! Of course.
That's why she chose.
Wait. Want to try?
Try it.
- I do not bubble.
- Who is not? Bubbles are ...
circle ... This math. 360 St. Think about this.
Everyone loves bubbles.
When I first saw you is ...
teaching, and children in front.
They are ...
representing numbers.
I like that.
That's why I ...
That's when I realized there was something special about you.
You know,
I need ...
must go.
- You did it!
- Good evening, Mr. Smith.
Good night, Miss Gray.
Once ... a woman from Texas ...
write all the numbers from 1 to 1 billion.
He spent several years ...
and lots of paper.
He uses recycled paper?
I do not know.
If you're using, is a good story. If not used, it is bad history.
Should I ask for your aunt to prepare lunch for you better.
Can not live up to basic chips and chocolate.
Yes, I can. That's what pirates eat.
Why do pirates prefer?
My father took me into a pirate ship when I was little.
Can I stay with you after my mother died?
- I have a small apartment.
- I'm not too good.
You can not.
because it would be unfair to other students.
I mean, I could help him with math lesson e. ..
would not be fair.
Makes sense.
- They are very angry.
- You are a brilliant teacher.
'Back Avoiding me, Miss Gray?
ora.
I thought I had dropped something. Window.
Like what? A quadratic equation?
Type a decimal point.
I see a decimal point. He flew in that direction.
- Decimal point can not fly.
- What are they doing?
They were leaning.
You are a strange woman I have ever encountered.
"So what?"
Then ...
Come on.
I help you find ...
decimal point is tilted.
Going to the movies.
I do not like the movie.
Okay. He did not invite you.
Okay, you can go to the cinema with me if you want.
I do not ... go to the movies.
What folly! It's like saying you do not hear the music.
- I hate music.
- What is this lie? The third?
I have to go to the hardware store to buy nails.
Lying 4.
I hate thrillers!
This is a 5!
- This is 5.
- The first is the music.
Is 5. You lie a lot.
Everything about you is funny. Come to the movies with me!
You can pay for popcorn.
Or you hate popcorn, but not really?
I need a nail.
I sat in the middle of the media.
42.
Come on guys!
Hi.
- Where are you?
- I forgot to buy popcorn.
It is enough for two people. Here.
But I like butter.
They are soaked in butter.
Sit down, lady!
-Sit!
Subtitle By: GingErwan
That person is an expert in bank robbery.
He was caught red-handed.
Then police found the murderer who left the victims in the vault ...
and fill the inside of them for money. So ...
now the police had ... help the bank robber.
They are filled with money from that place?
I can not answer.
But this is an interesting question.
It's my mother, Miss Gray.
Sorry.
- No need ...
- You'd better stop talking, ma'am.
- Why do not you sit somewhere else?
- Go, you!
Defended my honor?
What?
Mona!
How do you know where I live?
I followed you.
But you're quick.
Very fast.
I used to ...
- Run!
Why are you running ... movie?
I admit that artist.
- Who did this? Paulo
This is a 7 ... a little lonely.
Who did the volcano?
Ellen.
I like that.
I like this,
- Pot ...
- Bouquet of numbers.
And this ...
This is Lisa. "One of the six lashes."
They're real!
I think so.
I like you.
I do not like anyone else ...
so long ago.
How long did you do?
13 months
What month?
December
until July.
Why? "
Is 212 days.
Unless that leap year.
Did you know?
I have to go to the bathroom.
I asked: "Are you okay?"
What happened?
I just -
not in the mood.
- Your previous.
- Not.
- What are you doing in the bathroom?
- Go away, please.
Wild.
classes
I Miss Gray and I'm weird.
Who wants to come here to represent a snot?
Ms. Gray is not strange.
Yes! And so do you!
- Ann ...
- You are late!
And it was my turn to do Numbers and Materials.
Now it's your turn again?
I'm not lying!
See? A number of perfect.
Awesome.
Where'd you get that?
"I see it."
42 plus 5 equal to 48.
Nothing! It's 47!
You do not!
I know who it is.
This is mine and I!
You can go, Lisa.
Fine, but do not let it get away.
Why do not we go to the hardware store together ...
to give back the number on Mr. Jones?
He will be very happy that might give you a gift.
A gift? Do not want to reward an idiot!
And could not stop me going to the park to play.
Give me.
- Yes
This.
Weird.
I ....
I would shop with your hardware.
Then you can take me to visit my mother.
Hi Encouraged to experiment with sulfuric acid tomorrow?
Let's kick ass.
Mr Smith!
And also
Want to go to the hardware store with me and Miss Gray?
I can not. I Science Club meeting after school.
I need to look for ... I said I would.
And I always do what I say and say what I do.
I play clean. Not everyone plays. But thank you for the invitation.
Will lose the fun!
Mr. Jones.
If he is not here, why leave the door open?
Maybe it was captured by pirates.
This way.
- "And he fell on the bench, he laughed ..."
- Mother! Nan!
This is my math teacher.
Miss ... Gray ...
It is the unseen teacher?
Mlle. Gray?
This ... is Miss Gray.
Lisa, like potatoes?
- I love.
- Then come with me!
I like your hair.
Cancer is not contagious.
Lisa asked me to bring him here today.
He does not like my brother.
But as you.
I also like that.
His father made a pirate just like him? He said ...
No Lisa has never met his father.
I think ...
- You can ...
take care of Lisa and again?
Of course.
Mr. Jones.
Mother!
Mother! Daddy! Did you see Mr. Jones?
Mother saw Mr Jones?
He disappeared. And I do not think the car keys.
Who is missing? Mr. Jones?
No, Mona. His father. Her father disappeared.
What? Where did he go?
I do not know. I do not know where he is!
And I found it behind the washing machine.
He's hiding. I do not know how long ago did not take.
This will never happen if I still live here.
Stop! You can not help you.
And I do not know where he is.
-Dad?
- It's your father?
I tried to take him down, but did not appear.
-Dad?
The energy trapped ...
in this round and should be released.
Let's go home. Subtitle by Mandala Putra Bima
Should I call someone?
No, it's okay.
Mr. Wilson: Hi ya Id consider selling directly to you! this skirt on the way & have been posted so you should contact you soon! I'll look for the slip transmission to see if I could see when it will be sent & returned to you. Best greetings LOLITA J
Why did you stop taking the drug?
Because it is toxic. And it will poison my body.
No, it will help you.
Here is the end.
I have to dig here.
If I did not open it ...
_____I ... Is.
Please.
Go home.
- Not that I want to improve?
- It's everything I want.
I took my number and Materials. I knew it was not Friday, but special.
This is my father prosthesis.
- It seems the number one, right?
- Can I play?
Pretty cool, huh?
There seems to be the first. Apparently arm.
Apparently the number one!
Why is her father's arm fall?
Did not fall. He was hit in the war.
Is reduction, Miss Gray?
Ms. Gray? Ms. Gray?
- Ms. Gray! What?
Deductions do now? Hey, that's my dad!
Elmer!
- Return the arm his father Danny!
- I'm back here!
Elmer!
Hey! Elmer!
Danny!
- Elmer, come back!
return;
Mlle. Gray ...
can not control the class.
Will be terminated.
Silent ...
Nobody cares about you, Lisa.
kemariin hands lo.
-No!
Mlle. Gray, look!
I'll share ...
less ...
- And you multiply.
- Lisa!
As for the singing!
Ann, you have to learn to be good!
Oh GOD.
Agree?
Sorry.
Oh GOD.
- Lisa! Lisa!
Lisa!
- Lisa!
Let me go!
- Stop!
Stop!
My mother died!
He died!
Why can not I also have cancer?
Sorry.
- I'm sick of seeing ...
Lisa show off!
- Ann!
- I will split it into several parts.
Ann ...
- My God! ... Drop the ax.
- I will cut them.
- Go, nothing.
I will cut them to bits.
It will not bite anyone.
- I'm full of it! ____Please ...
And I'm sick of you.
Give me the ax!
There are a few moments ...
when you look around ...
and expect the cost to help you.
Then you realize that you are responsible.
You're an adult.
You're grown only there.
And not very good.
Life is too ...
far more difficult than mathematics.
-Dad?
Mlle. Gray ...
- It took nine points.
- I took 27.
Nine times three equal to 27.
"You're right!
- What are you doing?
What are you doing?
I imitate you at lunch.
Bank makes the same sound that your table.
Why did you do that?
Why? "
I do this ...
when ... I feel ...
alone.
So that's why I'm doing. I want to be like you.
Do not do that. Do not be like me.
But I own ...
-Own.
You do not just take an ax to school ...
but also lied by saying he has a college degree.
Shame on you ...
You are a great math teacher, Miss Gray ...
but forbidden to set foot in my school anymore.
Mr. Jones.
Hello?
What are you doing?
What are you doing? Get out of here!
- You do not die?
- Why do I die?
"What happened? I do not know why.
I think their numbers throughout the city. His shop is open.
- Your car is missing.
- Get out of my room!
- Who is the girl?
- Mona Gray!
Mona Gray, would you please leave?
- Do I have to call the police?
- No.
But keep your number!
How do you know how you feel or who you are without them?
Andrea, I'm back.
Sorry.
Why not have more than their numbers?
What do you get?
This is because I love math!
You taught me that the number is everything! I saw their numbers and not ...
bar graph to compare them with their moods.
He made the table?
Want to sit?
I left the store opened, I sold the car ...
all because of 42.
Who cares about anything when you use 42?
I saw you that day.
A beautiful day. The best I ever had.
What about 42?
I realized that if I do not need ...
number ...
I could be anything.
I do not understand why you are interested.
You're the meanest girl I ever knew.
Threw eggs at my car every Halloween.
- I know it's me? Of course.
What I do not know is ...
why you do it.
Because you ignored me.
And do not know my father.
What?
You never ask about it!
- I said yes.
- He asked, nothing.
One day you ...
playing in the park ...
and I ask:
"What happened to your father?" He seems to wilt. "
I asked! Of course I asked!
You're right there with their green wellies ...
threw stones at the tree.
I asked about his father, and you say to me:
"Shut up, Mr. Jones."
I should have asked again.
Sorry.
Maybe that day you ... not good.
I think I have never been better.
What is the problem with your father?
She thought she was dying.
Do you think he will die?
Did you miss work?
Want to know how I hurt my leg?
You did not ask.
Sorry. I think about ...
create another form of health in the backyard.
But this time, with a larger radius.
The latter is very small. I'm thinking about making a ...
with greater range.
What do you think?
I guess I can not stay with you.
My beautiful daughter. It's okay if you want to wait in the car.
He does not understand.
But I finally understood.
I received this by mail.
HI, MR. MISS SMITH. GRAY
I found through long-winded.
I do not know what to do.
Lisa insisted that I ... come and see it.
How is he?
Quiet than that.
Sorry.
You're right.
I lied.
Just so you know ...
next time, whether there will be other times ...
when I say I went to the bathroom ...
do not leave.
I'm not going to monitor your bathroom, Miss Gray.
Mona! Forgot to say one thing.
I lied.
I will monitor your bathroom.
No need to monitor the bathroom.
Not?
I lied, but it's for your kindness.
Agree?
- I just wanted ...
Thank you for coming back.
Mlle. Gray? Alisha Beeze, mother of Levan.
I am a lawyer and I think it is a major cause ...
toward family and school DiGanno Ann.
You can request a large indemnity.
I only want one thing.
And to say that in exchange for their jobs back ...
You give up this process, will graduate Pedagogy ...
and promise never to bring tools to the classroom.
Pen?
All this is very unfair.
I could not leave when he is around.
I'm not sensitive.
I'm not going to do it.
I'm not just ready.
I know it's horrible ...
but I do not want it.
I want
The history of my father around.
Love does not mean having to sacrifice part of himself.
the whole is greater than the sum of its parts.
What do you see?
- Any takers?
- Also! Also!
- Ms. Gray?
- Okay. I would choose ...
Isabelle ... David ...
and Kevin!
There were 122 frogs in the lake ...
and 57 in other countries.
frog How many total?
Not the history of mathematics is good.
179.
Good.
- Do you know better?
- I should think. I know!
Put 3 in the story. And pirates.
FINISHED
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org