EMPTY (2011)
Do you know how to drive?
- Yes, we have plenty of time.
Not enough fuel.
How far can we last?
- Not the whole trip.
Oh my God, oh, no, no.
- It's okay, no worries.
No alsjblieft, so we lost. What
if the wrong direction?
They do not live without us away, Piper.
I do not know if this is the good way.
We're going to run, no time to lose.
Shit, is that a car?
EMPTY
ONE WEEK EARLIER
Forward.
- As an exercise commander.
An exercise
-Commander? It seemed not even on.
My father was a fucking soldier.
- Really?
These drillers will give you really down,
if you had something out.
Oh yeah, I forgot your military background.
Yeah, interesting.
- If we wanted to see it for you.
We would be living here year round, so fish.
So in the wild, make a campfire.
- I see the fun in that.
I feel like a real guy here, you know?
Not bound in an office,
gazing at my computer.
Scour the Web as a bloody zombie.
Same office, which ensures that we
can pay the rent?
This here is as it should be
before one makes a mess.
Honey, I love to town ... No, I love it.
Perhaps you are even a few days to hang out.
Oh yeah, nice balls into the woods here
for five days is definitely not enough?
Thanks for this beautiful view, very sexy.
Hey.
It's better here than stay there, where everyone
fights for a piece of junk.
You know, I do not care if
they all make to the ground.
Okay.
What the hell was that about?
- Very strange.
A hippie.
- Not all in a row.
Fighting for a piece of junk?
Yes, and they all get the fuck.
- Probably stoned.
Not too close.
Chicken.
Tastes good.
Look at you, it's a campfire.
What do you think?
- Think?
You're beautiful.
Thank you.
How would you feel if I were
to ask you to marry?
Um, you ask me that?
I mean, I have no ring or
anything, I'm just saying ...
I see us the rest of our lives together.
What do you think about going to marry me?
Surely you can at least
show a little interest?
I do not say I did not do?
- With that expression on your face?
What should I do? I was only just thinking.
What do you think, how
would your father react?
- No, not at all.
Or how our parents met for
the first time would meet?
And how terrible it all will not.
Stop it.
I'm sorry that I have started. It
was stupid, I was somewhat excited.
Whatever.
Are you awake?
- Yes, what is it?
I'm sorry.
- Do not worry about it.
Are you sure?
- Yes, definitely.
MAXIMUM SPEED 40 KM / H
Won!
Can you get something for me: some
with cherries and pineapple vruchtencakeje?
Yes.
- Thank you.
5 NEW CALLING YOU MISSED. YOU HAVE
5 NEW VOICE MAIL MESSAGES.
What is it?
No gasoline here. I think
they're not even open.
Have you tried the door?
NO FUEL DUE TO FUEL CRISIS
Something strange going on here.
Yes, I have voice mails from my father.
Everyone wonders if all is well with me.
Tell me that this is a joke.
- What? What is it?
That sign on the door says
closed due to gas crisis.
What?
- Look there!
FUEL CRISIS AFFECTING ALL AMERICA
Have you seen cars on the way here?
No, no, not me.
I'm going to call my brother,
I know it either.
I'll call you back, then I know what to do.
Are you serious?
I love you, man, you see.
Yes Mom, listen, I gotta go ..
I have to find out.
Okay, I'll call you. I gotta
go I love you, Doeg.
My mom says that in California,
no gas. Nothing, though one week.
Stores have already closed because
nobody could work.
My brother says that Boston is a madhouse.
Are you okay with him?
- Yes, he sounded good, but ...
It's pathetic, because I think he
has more fun too.
I see no way.
- How far is Cambridge?
About 600 km.
- So far it is not.
That's it.
How far do you think we
can go with this tank?
Turn off the ignition.
It's official. We can in no way home.
There is still everything is possible.
The President has assured us
that gasoline is ahead next week.
The army will operate military food
drops and care where needed.
Meanwhile, New York on fire in
Chicago doin 'too bad ...
That does not yet ...
We need to really figure out
how it managed to come.
... It will take some time before petrol
again will be available to the public.
It took a while before I could get
People just do not get
the news they need.
But it's why I highly appreciate
that you came here
to try to transfer the
news to the people.
No trouble hearing.
- I think this ...
I just need a little
convincing ends have
they inform me that we
can save gas ...
Listen, I need to stop. I
have to change clothes.
Here, now?
I wear these clothes for five
days. I feel dirty.
I need to purify thoughts.
Hey, why do not we go to
my father. The summer cottage.
Connecticut?
- Yes, it is not far from here.
I'm sure we catch up with the fuel we have.
There must be a better place where we can go.
Where?
- No idea, Kishidi motel?
We'll go near me. Wait a few days.
You know, see what happens, we know nothing.
Why not go to that house? He's
not himself, he's in England.
Listen, I do not want help from your
father, I get there damn it acidic.
Do not be ridiculous. Piper,
we can find some.
40, $ 50 per night, stay
there one week. No problem.
That could be longer. This
can not continue, Piper.
Probably some political game. Hold the oil
tap as close to us.
We keep it as full and then back to normal.
What are you talking about?
Who is stopping us?
The Middle East.
- Who? Which country?
That sucks Pakistan or Afghanistan,
or any pokke
-standard whatsoever.
You do not know what you're talking about. Okay,
you watch any news unless it's sports news.
You read the paper disagree.
- I just heard on CNN ...
Please. Find a motel
- Fine, whatever.
Why something like this, as we
just go to the cottage?
So retarded.
- Come on baby, let's just watch.
Go on, now.
Jesus.
Hello, you had a few minutes ago called?
Yes, that was me, hello.
- How did you here?
Driven.
- Really?
Yes, we camped last week and
now back to civilization.
Or what's left of it.
- I don 't.
Just a warning. Fuel Shortage, thus
no cleaning crew, etc.
We get discount or something?
'm Afraid not, I must now
work longer than usual.
Of course, we meant nothing.
Whatever.
Can I have your credit card,
driver's license see, please?
Where is the nearest supermarket?
Excuse me?
We want some food, we are starving.
You said you have been camping
for a few days?
6 days.
So you do not know what's going on?
Oh yes. Fuel Crisis and many
other deficiencies, we know.
Tell us where the nearest supermarket and
book us in and ...
Most shops are closed ...
and many robberies now.
It is very dangerous here.
So there is no more food to get?
I have enough food stored
and other stuff prior to the
hell breaks out here ...
-Excuse my language, ... one week ago.
I knew a lot of people, some
homeless people and guests can use.
Okay, so ...
I can deliver what you need.
No risk of going into stores, they
can see you as criminals.
Are we criminals?
- Good idea, do not you think?
Or waste gas to get anywhere.
It is so extraordinary.
- That's it.
I offer it because I
who are trying to get away.
- God, that's terrible.
Sorry, only even try to penetrate
what we stand for.
There are even reports of rape had been.
A taser. If someone tries something fun
I leave them a scare.
Give me enough time to tie
them, until the police arrive.
Okay, thank you made us a guide how to ...
Rape?
Can you give us the keys, please?
And how much would you pay?
Okay, That's $ 200.
- What? $ 200?
Cash. Our kredietpasautomaat does not work.
Fantastic.
- Pay him normal.
This would not cost more than $ 50?
- That was so, yes.
Pay it simply, Dell.
- Okay.
Thank you.
Can we order food or something?
I made a list.
There is everything available,
cost per piece.
Ipods and portable DVD players?
- Also available for rent at night.
Beautiful collection of films, games or
activities for your enjoyment.
We watch TV a lot, usually.
I'm sorry, our rooms
are not equipped with TVs. Many of our
guests come to escape them properly.
Well, the portable DVD player.
Honey, it's very expensive, do not you think?
There is a risk involved for
these things get so small I
have to take charge ...
A little?
Okay, fine.
We call you when we need some.
Sure, I'm here.
- Thank you.
Of course, I want my guests feel at home.
My name is Guy and I are 24
-7 there, well, since the crisis began then.
Call but if you need anything,
no matter what. I'm here.
You do not need to worry about.
What did you think of the janitor?
- You mean the receptionist.
I even unnecessary.
I wonder if he ever picked up
anything decent in his life.
He's a little eccentric.
That list looked quite cool, so
we want something from?
I do not know.
It says: $ 3 for a bottle of
water. $ 10 for a sandwich.
Come on, there must be a
shop here in the neighborhood.
Just use the list.
Honey, I do not see why
we should spend money unnecessarily.
We do not waste money.
Come on, let's just stay here. Feel
safe, for now ... yes?
Okay, we'll stay here and order
some of the list.
Moreover, we have enough food in the
camp that we can eat.
Nice.
But tomorrow I'm looking to see if I
can buy some at normal cost.
I'm not off by that bum on the counter.
He is no bum.
More like a pedophile.
NEW RESULTS FUEL CRISIS
Yes, wait.
SPREAD PANIC AND VIOLENCE RECORDED IN NYC
Where's the lady?
- Under the docuhe.
Got everything?
Sure, magazines, or 2 weeks old.
That's all, better than nothing, right?
- Yes.
And I have snacks for you or your wife.
Oh, we're not married, she's my girlfriend.
Sure, nice, I suppose.
And what is it, $ 35, right?
I also ask $ 5 for delivery.
It is therefore $ 40
- Delivery?
You say anything about delivery.
Hi.
Hello.
$ 35 here, okay?
- $ 40 including delivery.
Listen friend, I do not understand what
you're trying to get here.
But your prices are slightly exaggerated.
If you can get this stuff anywhere else,
I love you not to hear.
We are glad that we get from you. Pay him.
Listen, I understand it a
little difficult now.
So, I pay a little extra
now, more than usual.
But come on man, you are exaggerating a bit.
I show you the price, you'd
have to buy anything though.
You've called me.
- Yes, and to be honest
I felt like I had been taken but it
will be, we wanted to have this.
But now you ask me, delivery,
out of the blue?
It's not that, it's my standard delivery fee.
There is sometimes a manager or
someone I can achieve?
Let me know what you're doing.
- Dell, be nice.
We are talking here.
- Well, I'm about.
If you do not like what this is,
we do not have to do this.
Well, mate, actually ...
Please, we are satisfied with what you give.
He's a little upside down when
he should spend money.
It's a bit of a hectic period for everyone.
Listen, let me handle this, okay?
You're pretty rude.
- You know, you trade it and see, okay.
Not very, as I said,
what everyone is stressed.
What we owe you?
- It comes to $ 45.
Okay, let me just pay.
- Jesus, unbelievable.
I'm sorry for the turmoil.
- No problem.
Enjoy your meal.
What is your problem?
- My problem? Are you kidding?
Angry and your enemy up with
no reason for it?
He tried to take advantage of us.
I tried him to stop.
What exactly are making an extra few bucks?
Piper, you can not let you be snowed under.
Forget that stupid. He continues with excuses
to then ask for money.
You exaggerate!
- You ...
Do not make a point.
A showdown with the concierge
is just ridiculous.
Really? So you think it's a dirty showdown?
Yes, he works 24 hours a day
for a few dollars more
people a pleasure to do.
- You're so naive, you know?
Yes, and are such a smart guy.
It's all relative, compared to you.
I am the great explorer.
- It'll do. Childish.
I was trying to protect you, damn it?
I'm a short walk away from this bullshit.
- Dell!
Bullshit, damn.
Yes Dad ... Everything is fine.
Yes, Dell arranged for the best
hotel, best room ...
and the service is really great.
What is it?
- Nothing.
Sorry Dad. Can I call you back?
Yes, yes, I have to go now.
Everything is fine ... Okay,
I love you. Doeg.
Your Father?
- Yes.
Tell me what happened?
- I do not want crazy.
Okay, tell me, for I am your
stack mesjokke if you say something.
I went to some blocks ...
I then heard some controversy.
- And?
I do not know exactly, but it seemed
A raid or something.
- I'll call the police.
Okay, how is it that 112 is not working?
I do not think the police or
whatever is nearby to help.
Think, no gasoline, how do you
think they come here?
Nonsense, of course that petrol.
Already a police on the street, anywhere?
Well, not me.
Okay, what do we do? Guy calls?
Guy? From the desk?
Yes.
- Are you serious is it?
Well, we have to do what?
Listen, be honest ... it did not look
so bad. More panic on my part
I went out just what my roof, that's all.
I want only what is on my ease, Dell.
Are you okay?
- Yes.
Yes.
I swear.
Damn what?
Hey, Damn, what are you doing?
- What is it, what happens?
Get out, motherfucker!
An asshole who wanted to steal our gas.
What? Stolen anything?
No, it is him lubricated.
We have to go here.
- Now?
I would not stay here. Not funny anymore.
Where?
- The summer house.
What I wanted to go much earlier.
No, listen. I'll stay here a minute longer
if someone steals gasoline from us
He has nothing stolen. I scared him
off. What does that make?
I want to leave, I'm not safe here anymore.
I have spent $ 200 on.
- What do I care about the money now, Dell.
I'm not risking our lives because we
have been given $ 200
There must be something else we
can go, but the summerhouse.
I'm sorry that you are not my father.
- I never said.
I'm just saying I do not want
to be dependent on him.
Fine. You're right. We pack our things.
Meet the big bucks.
- Nice place.
Can your father is no castle afford?
- It's a holiday.
So many states it's also not.
- As if I had suggested otherwise.
You just get used to it. Like my father.
It is but the rugged exterior.
- A rugged exterior, you call him?
He's not as bad as he arises.
- You're right. A great guy.
As if we have dinner with him and
he no question about my life.
I wish it would happen more often.
I'm going to take a shower
before we go to bed.
Where is it?
- Step on the right.
Dell, honey. Wake up.
No power.
What time is it?
No power. Should have happened last night.
Maybe a blown fuse.
Only in this room?
- No, the toilet and the hall also.
Cunt.
Damn!
- Sorry, I did not know.
Back on?
- No.
Now?
Cunt!
Do you think this area is
called the failure affected?
It's not the fuse, unless the
case concerns the whole stop.
God!
- Maybe a cable or something.
Who will fix?
- Nobody.
So, what do we do?
- What about your house warming?
No idea, electricity?
- Shit.
Nondedju!
- Wait a minute.
No, it's now the day Expl ...
We use the fireplace, then
we can just continue.
It goes from bad to worse.
- No, not that bad though.
Look, all these cans of food, pasta ...
How will heat the pasta? The
oven does not agree.
We have camping bunch more. The campfire.
And the news? You surely are you aware
we completely shut off from
the civilized world.
Dell, stop it!
- Look, it's all fucking heavy!
I will not sit and pretend everything
is fine, because it is not.
Lets face it, the situation is just cunt,
until we ourselves going fucked up!
Honey, calm now ... No, I
do not settle down. No.
When they said that?
- Yes, I know, I know t.
My God.
Watch out. Okay bro, I love you.
Dad, I gotta go. The battery is almost
empty and I 'm not charging.
Yes, do not forget. I'll call you
back in a few hours, okay?
I love you, I gotta go, bye.
And how's your brother?
He was watching the news on
when the power went out.
And it was announced that the crisis is to
Could take three months, we have power again.
Three months?
- Yes, he told me.
And your father, what did he say?
And they ride bikes everywhere. Use only
cars when absolutely necessary.
And he said he wanted me, so
us, to come to England.
He wants us to come to England?
I'm sorry, baby, but your father seems to
me some of the clasp tapped.
Do not be.
Not surprising that he thinks
he's Napoleon or something.
But he is confident stroke.
- You're mean.
Sorry, did you forget what he said
to me, right in my face?
But first I had an expensive
university education and then
had to get a degree before I
could even deal with you.
I know that my father sometimes
can be a jerk but
does not mean he does not
have to worry about us.
I try not, you're forcing me to.
You say you he wants "we"
have to come to England?
And you know yourself that it's hogwash.
- Whatever.
I'll get some wood for the fireplace.
- Why? It's not cold.
Would you sit in a dark
house? I have a flashlight.
Your childish behavior.
- Because it is wood?
It does not matter to me whether
we have a fire, okay?
I'll do it myself.
- Fine.
Would that be enough?
I must have fallen asleep.
- Yes, the fireplace a good
start to get going.
Nothing, just nonsense.
Sounds strange but ... it feels almost good.
- What do you mean?
With everything going on.
We make it. Maybe we are better off this way.
It is the great similarity,
it does not matter
whether you're a rich or a poor
devil stinker, it does not matter.
You're not fat cats. That makes
me not care at all.
I know, but because I ...
- Hey, just you and me.
Exactly, and that is why I stay.
Do you?
I know one of the past but
that was a little one.
Leeggerooft may be?
We can go to that house and
take everything we can meenenem.
A good idea, why did we not previously?
Do you?
- Yes k've got a good feeling.
I try to remember. It is
quite a long time ago.
An accident or something?
Probably out of gas?
- Unusual. Just push it?
Honey, I'm afraid.
- Do not worry, it come good.
I'm with you.
No, stay here. Be right back.
Wait, man. That's my car.
Are you out of gas?
- Just before a bridge too shitty.
Sucks.
- Yes, it's all bollocks.
I want to go to my mother, she
is sick and who does not kutverpleegster.
In any case ...
could you help me to him from off the road.
You want me ...?
- Put it in neutral and I push.
I'm now pushing. Send him but to the side.
Good.
- Sorry about your car.
So is the way life is, right?
I gotta go.
- Sure.
Ok, thanks, man.
- Good luck.
You too.
- Thanks.
What was there?
- No more petrol ..
What will he do now?
- No idea.
Can we offer to no lift or something?
Piper, we know nothing of that host.
- I know, but you helped him anyway?
He has not done anything, right?
It just does not feel good to a
stranger in our car to have.
We can not ask where to go?
- Piper, I really do not.
Fine, whatever.
Hey, buddy?
- Yes.
Do you need a lift or something?
- Man, that would be great.
Okay, step.
- Thank you.
Many thanks.
Where did you go on our way?
Man, if you would bring me a
few miles, it would be nice.
Sure I can go further from there.
Thanks, I really appreciate that.
No problem. Sorry for your car. You
have nothing left there anyway?
Nah, it's so good.
Turn it right.
- Here?
Yes, this rotation.
In the middle of the bush.
Okay, turn here but.
Stop right there.
- Here? Are you sure?
Step out of the car. Get
off this fucking car.
Get out! Okay, calm down!
I help only! Shut up, shut up, that car!
Well I'm low.
Get out!
Do not make me mad!
Do not touch my arm! Stop!
Piper, the car!
No, no!
- I sucked his blood on me.
Cunt. I never got stabbed?
- Do you remember?
You have to go and him help.
- Damn, that you kidding?
This guy tried to abduct. Why?
We helped him alone. I do not understand!
- This is ridiculous.
Cunt.
- Do not you stop?
You should be thanking me, hugging me.
You can 't let it not die, right?
The only reason he was in the car
for him to give a kutlift!
- I'm trying to grasp what was happening.
If this shit happened in the Middle Ages
you would not call the police.
There was no security.
- Don 't like you're retarded!
You know what? You can pot,
Piper, really the pot!
Do not talk to me!
- Call me not backward!
After all I've done just for you?
You're terrible.
I'm terrible? Do you think I had a choice?
Choice for what?
Did you think we could get away
without me him stabbed him?
I can not, I can not ...
- Oh, you fucking now?
Okay, damn it, great!
What happened, happened.
- Easy for you to say.
You wanted to bring that bastard and I
need to clean up your mess?
It's not fair.
Indeed, it is not.
Thank you.
Are you mad at me?
- I am disappointed.
What?
- In so many things.
What things?
- The situation, everything.
Once in the car?
- I could go to hell, you
said, you were so angry.
Given the circumstances, you had better
neglect can catch me.
You really frightened now.
- I just want to understand, help me.
Why did you have quarreled about
today? Of course I'm grateful.
You risked your life for me. I ...
But? I ... I do not know, it scares me ...
What made you afraid? I've stabbed someone?
You can not sit there as if you did not care.
It scares me!
- Pure nonsense!
What nonsense?
From the first day I was trying
to prove myself to you!
That has nothing to do with it.
- Has everything to do with it!
I'm the bastard never wanted the car.
I know I made a mistake.
Yes, I know it that your mistake.
But I have sure pay!
You think so much smarter than me.
You make a point about everywhere
salvaged and how naive I am or not.
- You are, is that my fault?
You know, I can not.
Have you slept here all night?
-Yes.
Where you going?
To the lake, there is a
section where you can fish.
You're you're surely aware that the
more likely it is frozen?
They call it ice fishing, Dell.
It's not so much frozen!
Let me help you.
I did not know you can eat frozen fish.
- You can not pretend nothing has happened.
I do not.
Someone down and stabbing him there
to die, is this normal?
We have done nothing wrong,
it was an accident.
An accident? You put one down by accident.
He was the one who threatened with
a knife. He tried to abduct.
Why did you do then stabbed twice?
I wanted to make sure that he
would do us no pain.
I had to stop him.
Why not give me the feeling that
this is all my fault?
I do not.
I'm not here to ridicule because you
invited him to ride more.
Why do you blame me that I protect?
- I know you do not.
I just wish this never happened.
Are you glad that it happened?
I would do anything for you to take it back.
I can not believe we eat frozen fish.
Why not? They do it enough in Alaska.
Have you left the door open? No,
I do not think so.
Stop, both!
- Run, run!
Quick! Go!
Inside!
- Okay, okay.
Does not!
- Okay, okay!
Come on, this is our house!
- Do you have weapons?
What, you just rob us? Keep your Kanis!
Take those bags, they have nothing we want!
Hey, you lucky. Some people shoot
at you for fun.
Yeah, thanks for that. You're welcome.
They brought all the food
we had. You bastards!
They will come back.
They're not coming back, because there's
nothing more to be gained.
But they can come back.
- Listen, I can not look far ahead, okay?
Okay.
Listen, I gotta go because the
battery is running out.
I'll call you in a few hours
back, okay? I love you.
What's going on?
- I was talking to my dad.
And?
He said he would help us get out of here.
I know, but we need help. We
can not stay here, Dell.
We have no choice, Piper.
My father said people knew
who have their own boat, who
could dock in the harbor.
Really?
- It was worth a try.
With this gas crisis ...
I have my serious doubts that
even ships might go somewhere.
If it does not work, then
we have lost nothing.
Come on, Dell. I can not stand
that macho bullshit talk to you.
Call it what you want.
This is quite different to take
money from my father
This is survival, Dell.
I know we can.
- Somebody just broke into our house!
We can at night not even sleep,
come on, do not ...
We have to leave.
- What if he fails?
I have no choice. But if he
can help us we go, Dell.
We would not even be talking about,
because it is simply impossible.
Hey but if he gets us out, will you join me?
Yes.
Yes, I will go.
Hi Dad.
Okay.
I'll call you in a few hours back, okay.
I love you, adios.
What did he say?
- Nothing new. He works there still.
Listen, go get some sleep, okay?
You'll feel much better tomorrow.
Thank you.
What is it?
- Good morning, honey.
Where did you get all that food come from?
- Oh, found in a box in the basement.
You have certainly overlooked. How many
left? We need to ration.
I phoned my dad this morning. And?
It's him successful. We go out
of here, baby. To England.
A ship stops at the nearest
port and picks us up.
We should note at 16.00 hours.
Can not. There is no fuel, no oil,
or peanut butter sometimes you doin?
There is fuel, not only in the States.
Europe is now rationed, but my
dad says not so fast runs.
- Unbelievable.
Yes, you're right. I'm happy. Let's go eat.
By the way, my phone is dead.
- Really?
Yes, but we still have yours.
- Mine is dead too.
What? I thought the more power
you have yours than mine?
What should we do if something happens
the way to the port?
You know the way to this?
I wrote down the route. But I have
not taken into account without a phone.
God, this is so annoying, I do not even hear.
Yes.
Why did not you tell me about your phone say?
Not thought about.
Moreover, sitting somewhere in verweggistan
If you already can get in touch with someone.
What do you think they do?
I really wish you had told me.
You have the route?
- Yes, we still have plenty of time.
We do not have enough gasoline.
How far can we go in the tank?
- Hopefully the whole way.
We have 30
-40 minutes to arrive there.
Do not worry, we will get there.
I think we need another 32 km.
Oh my God.
We can walk the last km, we have time.
It is light that makes me scared.
As if there is constant
curse hanging over us.
Not so dramatic.
Okay, we need to Halcon Road is
still 16 km to the port.
We will get there, you watch.
- Can not you a little harder?
No, I keep the speed constant.
You use more gas if you give more gas.
A little more gas, so more gas?
So easy. That means I do
not do much to accelerate.
If I do do I use more gasoline.
Shit. Nothing wrong.
- No, please, please.
It cost us more than two
hours to reach the port.
We have two hours when we need it.
What if we get lost, run the wrong direction?
We're not going away without us, Piper.
I do not know.
- Come on run, we have no time to lose.
Shit.
All these things carry?
- Just in geaval that.
You think we will not make it.
I never said that, I just take them along.
Come on, we gotta go.
We were already at the exit should be.
Perhaps the distance from incorrectly chat.
We can not go back now,
that's no longer an option.
Just go, okay.
I can not stand.
Shit, is that a car?
Would they have gas?
- No idea.
Hey, manage it?
I do not think they have
seen us. Even up close.
How do we know they are trustworthy?
- You do not know, it seems fine.
I think I did more horror.
You do not think I am about to pee.
- Come on, we gotta go.
Walk forward and arouse attention.
Okay.
Hello, we are but two, we do no harm!
Not come closer, okay?
Who is there with you, I see it not?
- My friend, he is okay.
Just camping gear!
We have nothing, we can not help you ..
We just need to Bridgeport Harbor,
a few km away.
Okay, okay, come on. We take you along.
Quick!
Hi, Louise is the name.
- Piper, and this is my friend, Dell.
How are you?
Thank you, thank you very much.
So you go to the port?
- Yes.
If he can get us out of
here, will you join me?
Yes.
Yes, I go with.
It's Halcon Road direction, you know?
It almost feels good.
- What do you mean?
So many strange things happen. Realizes that
to me that we can do.
Yes I know where it is, about 15
-20 minutes away ...
If we wish, we can
live here year round.
Hunting, fishing and a campfire.
Where you going?
No matter where we go.
Oh, you do not tell us though.
There are currently many robberies and
threats here. Quite dangerous here.
It is what krapjes.
- Does not matter.
You people are not your run
and certainly not as it now stands.
Hi, thank you.
Stop here.
- Here?
Honey, come on, hurry up.
Fuck you!
Go on, honey.
Do not you put
someone down accidentally.
Come on, we gotta go.
If this happened in the Middle
Ages or some such ...
you can not polite to call,
or the security alert.
Listen honey, I would not count.
What?
You lucky man. There are people
shooting you down for fun.
Why tell me this now?
Have you seen somewhere the police?
- Not me!
What happened to him? I want it just a ride.
It's all right. Dell get into the car,
we have an amazing talk about.
I can not.
- What are you doing, doing?
Come on baby, stay with me.
- I can not believe you do this.
I can not.
- We will find food and shelter.
I feel like fucking a real man here.
We can not stay here all
day while you are arguing.
Come with me.
I can not.
How would you feel if you
were to ask to marry?
Can we go?
You and I together.
- Exactly.
And I want it that way.
If he can help us, then go right?
- Okay, but do not have too much hope.
Yes, let's go.
Come on, this is our house.
- Do you have weapons?
No.
Dell! Do not!
Correction: Onnie  2011 ~
~ Home Translations