Oh, Nick, I...
I didn't know who else to call.
You were so good
with him the last time.
It's okay. Now, where's
Mike? He's in his room.
He's locked the door-- I'm
afraid he's gonna hurt himself.
I can't believe
the cops accused him
of raping somebody? He
wasn't making any sense.
He just kept saying that
he didn't want to go to jail. Mike?
It's Nick Morelli.
Your mom called me.
She's worried about you.
Mike?
How long has it been since
you've heard anything?
I don't know,
maybe five minutes.
Nick?
Mike, slow down.
Just slow down.
That could be
an ambulance, Mike.
Now, just tell me what's going
on. I didn't rape anybody, Nick.
Okay, now,
why would the police think
that you raped anybody?
Just tell me.
Mike? I was walking home from Desi's,
and they came flying up,
then they threw me
against the car, and
they said that the guy had
a red hoodie just like mine,
and they kept asking me why I
did it, and he went for his cuffs, and then
I just ran. O-Okay, nothing that's happened
can't be fixed,
but we got to deal with
the situation right here, Mike;
the police are coming.
They're not gonna believe me.
Mike, they will listen to you.
I am here, I will protect you,
I'll take care of it--
don't worry about it.
Mike, put that gun away. What
are you doing?! Put the gun down!
May, now, go in the bathroom, and
lock yourself... Put that gun...
Go now, May!
Mike, you got to give me that
gun. Mike, give me that gun.
I can't go back to jail.
Give it to me. The police are
I didn't do any... gonna be here soon,
and as soon as they get here, you're not
gonna look good with
a gun-- now, give me the damn gun!
Police! Open the door! Give it...
Give me the gun!
Gun! Gun!
All right,
all right, all right!
On the ground!
This is my client!
We are not resisting arrest!
Here's the gun! Face down
on the ground now! Face down!
All right, in my suit pocket,
there's a business card.
I'm an attorney!
Hold on, hold on.
I know him; let him up.
Nick, you got to help me, okay?
He invokes his
Fifth Amendment rights.
Hey, Morelli, what do you
call a defense lawyer
holding a gun?
What?
Justifiable homicide.
Hilarious.
It won't be, next time.
Sync and corrected by
www.addic7ed.com
The Defenders - Season 1, episode 12
"Nevada v. Wayne"
Now, you've known Mike since
he was 12? Oh, yeah, yeah.
Played shortstop on a Little League
team that Pete and I sponsored.
Then five years later, the mother called
me and he got busted for possession.
Wow. And where's his dad?
He ran. He was gone
before I met the boy.
Here he is.
How you doing?
What happened?
Nothing. I'm fine.
You didn't answer me.
We're well past
capacity in here.
Things happen.
Yeah, well, not
to this kid.
If I see
one more scratch on him,
I'm gonna depose every one
of you guys wearing a badge.
Are you all right?
I'm fine.
Guy sucker-punched me.
All right, this is Lisa,
my associate.
She's gonna run us
through the facts of the case.
All right,
the police report says
that the victim was asleep
in her apartment
and woke up when the attack
started at 10:17 p.m.
She called to report the rape
after the attacker had left
at 11:14 p.m. I was home till
after 10:00-- my mom can prove that.
We were watching TV, and I told
her I was gonna go out for a while.
She told me to make sure that I
double-locked the door, and I left.
Well, that helps.
Well, it's a start, but a mother
sticking up for her son--
that's not the strongest alibi.
What did you do after you left? I
was at Desi's the rest of the night.
Desi. And when did you get
there, and when did you leave?
10:30. Left after midnight.
I was walking home when
the cops jacked me up.
We're gonna need Desi's
full name and number.
Is my mom here yet?
Your mom?
Yeah, she's here.
You'll be able to see her.
Now, let's finish up.
She'll come in.
Nick?
Yeah?
Everything's gonna
be okay, right?
Yeah, Mike, it's
gonna be fine.
Hey, May.
I don't want you to freak out,
but, uh, he's
banged up a little bit.
Oh, my God, what happened?
Well, an inmate
attacked him.
But I already put
the guards on notice.
If anything else happens, he
goes right to protective custody.
Oh, my God.
Now, Mike said he was at home
with you until
after 10:00
last night watching TV?
Yes. He was.
We were watching TV,
and then he went out.
Do you remember
what you said to him?
Well, I always tell him to
double-lock the doors when he goes out.
Okay, May,
go see your son.
Being a juror is
an honorable and rewarding job,
but the rewards jury duty offers
are balanced by
important responsibilities.
Hey.
Is this taken?
There's something off
about that judge.
Oh, yes, there is.
Hello.
Shoot!
Pull the chute, honey--
you just got shot down.
No, I...
just got a smile;
you missed it.
And it is your job
to report juror misconduct...
Hm! If anyone knows
about misconduct...
What?
Tell me!
Last year the cops found him
passed out in a sex club.
Head-to-toe rubber suit.
Had to breathe out of this
little snorkelly thingy.
Swore it was a
"weight-loss outfit."
I don't remember
hearing that in the news.
It wasn't. You hear things
when you're a defense attorney.
Oh.
♪ ♪
Somebody drank my juice!
It's behind the milk.
It's gone!
Oh. Thank you.
Hmm.
What do you got?
Desi Williams, 21.
Mike's known him since
they were both 16.
Met him in drug court-- went
through the program together.
All right, all right,
well, they were juveniles,
so we can keep that out;
any other trouble?
A bust at 18
for possession.
Oh, please say pot.
Pot, pot, pot, pot?
Heroin.
I heard "pot."
Well, Desi's totally cleaned
up his act since then, though.
He's working for
the past few years,
going to N.A. meetings
regularly. All right, well,
when are you gonna talk to him?
Because we need to lock in
that alibi. Well, he hasn't
called in to work and
his landlord hasn't seen him,
but she promised to contact us
the second she does.
All right, what
about the victim?
Um, a Lona McKerin, 21,
full-time student at USLV,
no arrests, no history of substance
abuse or emotional problems.
I tracked down Detective Smith.
I had to promise
the dispatcher tickets
to Thunder
From Down Under.
Before you go, I need
you to sign these.
Sign.
Initial.
Oh, wait,
that's for Pete.
That's for Pete.
Give me that.
He's using a corporate
card to buy his suits?
I don't know.
I don't know anything.
Zoey... Zoey!
I don't know.
Zoey!
Ladies and gentlemen,
you've all been sworn.
This case involves a charge of
attempted parental kidnapping.
The defendant, Alexei Nemerov,
has been accused
by his former wife,
Kelli Lazine,
of abducting their son.
Now, has anyone here
had anything to do
with the defendant
or any of the lawyers
involved in this case?
Judge, I'll see ya.
Anyone other than Mr. Kaczmarek?
Down.
Um, I-I'd like to be
excused from this jury.
On what grounds?
Well, I don't have a car,
so to get here this morning
I had to take three busses.
Sorry, that's not
grounds for dismissal.
Um, if you want to carpool,
I have a convertible...
Sorry. Sorry.
Mr. Anderson, it
says on your questionnaire
that you're recently divorced.
Do you think that will
affect your ability
to be impartial in this case?
No.
So the divorce
was amicable?
I wish she were dead.
State strikes
for cause.
You are free to go, sir.
The defense strikes for cause.
You are excused, sir.
The State strikes for cause.
Free to go.
Strikes
for cause. You are excused.
State strikes
for cause.
Free to leave.
Strikes for cause.
Free to go.
You are dismissed.
You are excused.
Free to go.
Dismissed.
Excused.
Does the State or the defense
have any more peremptory
challenges for this jury?
No, Your Honor.
Cole, psst, psst.
We have a jury.
Thank you all very much.
Please see the jury clerk.
And trial starts tomorrow.
Excuse me. Coming through.
Cole... Cole... No, I can't talk to you.
Are you insane?
I...
You just put a defense
attorney on your jury!
Look, despite how
I feel about you
personally, Kaczmarek,
I know you love the
law as much as I do.
Okay? Which is why I'm
hoping you'll overcome
all your baser
instincts and convict.
And when you do, a little piece
of you is gonna die inside.
9:00 sharp. Don't be late.
My, you got such tiny feet
for a man with a big mouth.
It's my day off, Morelli.
Hank, listen,
I need to talk to you
about my client, Mike Wayne.
Less than an hour
after the victim
reported the assault,
your guys picked him up
because they think he did it?
He matched the description
and he was in the area.
Well... My guys asked
him a couple of questions,
and he turns into the Flash.
Innocent people
don't run from the cops.
They do if you bounce them off a cruiser.
And who bounced him off a cruiser?
Your guys did. Yeah,
they did. No, they didn't.
No, they didn't!
Yeah, they did.
No...
Okay, okay.
Did you even look into
any other possibilities?
Sex offenders in the area,
guys on parole?
Did you check
DNA or prints?
No useable prints, no DNA.
Latex residue, however.
He wore a condom.
Look, the kid's only other
charge is some grass as a minor.
Now all of a sudden he's a master rapist
that knows enough to hide his own DNA?
Come on, Hank, it
doesn't make sense.
This doesn't fit.
You know what fits?
A couple of hours
after we pulled your client
from his house,
the victim put a big red circle
around his picture in a lineup.
"That's the man
that raped me, Officer."
I wish I had another story for
you, Nick, but I don't.
Now, it's my day off.
I'll see you guys in court.
Bye.
Aw, come on,
what is this all about?
I have no idea.
Is this the
right address?
The one the landlord
texted me.
You look nice today.
Thanks.
Where'd you get
that outfit?
Pete got it for me.
Pete?!
Yeah. Did he put it on
a corporate credit card?
I heard it was on sale.
Hey, Nick. Detective, how are you?
Good. Heard you almost got shot.
Oh, yeah, good
times, good times.
Oh, I bet, yeah.
What are you doing here?
I'm here to
see a witness
about a case.
What's his name?
Uh, Desi Williams.
You didn't bust
him, Tom, did you?
We didn't just bust him.
Oh...
How long has
he been gone?
Less than 24.
Cause of death?
Judging by the bindle
in his pocket,
the needle in his arm, I'm going
with heroin overdose. Oh, man...
I heard "pot."
Positive victim I.D.,
a dead alibi witness--
we're screwed.
If we were on a mountaintop
with a telescope,
we couldn't see the
light from screwed.
No. Desi doesn't get high anymore.
It was someone else--
they make mistakes, right?
They make mistakes.
Mike, well... I got
the crime scene photos.
It's Desi.
Hey...
they have the time of death--
right around the time
you two were together.
Now, tell me,
will the prosecution have
evidence saying that
you were doing drugs that night?
No. Just eating some pizza
and playing some video games.
Are you sure?
It's okay-- I just need to know.
I can't get blindsided in court.
Hey, I'm clean.
I'll take a test
if you want.
Okay.
Hey. You look like a
truck just hit you.
So do you.
Yeah, well, my best alibi for
the sexual assault just O.D.'d.
They just put me
on a jury!
Okay, on the scale of things,
not as bad, I'll admit it.
I'm glad you didn't
lose your perspective.
Is that a new suit?!
This is a perfectly
valid tax exemption. Pete,
this... is
a business credit card.
You cannot write off suits.
It's not a suit;
it's a work uniform.
Pete, you know how
they brought Al Capone down?
It wasn't the G-men;
it was the IRS.
I know; I saw the movie. Didn't
you learn anything from it?
Yeah, don't lie to Robert De Niro
if he's holding a baseball bat.
Come on, Pete,
you can't do this!
Everybody does it. Okay,
okay, I didn't just hear that.
I didn't hear anything you said
about committing tax evasion.
So when the IRS comes
and drags your ass to jail,
I'm gonna act
shocked and confused.
After your divorce
from Mr. Nemerov,
who was awarded primary
custody of your son, Sasha?
Alexei was too busy
whoring around
to be a proper parent.
Objection, non-responsive.
Sustained.
Objection, Your Honor.
Non-responsive.
Sustained. The
witness will limit herself
to answering the questions.
I have custody.
He had visitation.
And on the day
in question,
where did Mr.
Nemerov tell you
he was taking Sasha?
A movie.
And when Alexei didn't bring
him back by Sasha's bedtime,
I called the police.
That seems extreme.
How did you know your ex-husband
had abducted him?
Objection, leading.
Objection.
Mr. Cole is leading the witness.
Sustained. Shh, you're
gonna get me in trouble.
And once he was apprehended,
where had Mr. Nemerov
actually taken Sasha?
To the airport...
about to board
a flight to Russia.
If they had gotten
on that plane,
I never would have seen
Sasha again. Objection!
You were gonna hide him
in some backwater hovel
just to punish me,
you bastard!
Hate her.
Mr. Nemerov,
you quit your sales job
at Petersen's Used Carland
two days
before you were apprehended at
the airport, is that correct?
It was time for a change.
So it wasn't because you had
no intentions of ever
returning from Russia?
No, no, no.
You stated earlier
that Miss Lazine
gave you permission
to take your son to Russia.
Yes. Uh, to attend
the birthday of my grandmother.
Her 90th.
Talk directly to the jury;
that's a defense lawyer trick.
This guy is good.
I just wanted my son
to see his great-grandmother
before she died.
She said
it would make her life...
complete.
Hm.
I was asleep.
Um...
I'd had a pretty long day,
so I fell asleep early.
And then I...
I felt a pressure on my chest.
At first I thought
I was dreaming, b...
He was tying my arms.
You woke up, and the attacker
was on top of you?
I fought so hard.
I really did.
People say you, um...
you float out of your body,
but I didn't.
I didn't at all.
I wanted to so badly...
But I...
We can take a break.
No.
Please, I want to do this.
It was, um...
it was dark, but I could
tell that he had a...
he had sort of a baby face,
'cause he, uh...
no scruff, you know?
I could...
I could feel him rub
against me when he was...
...as he was raping me.
Do you see the man
who sexually assaulted you
in this courtroom today?
Yes.
Him. He raped me.
No, I didn't.
Order.
I didn't. She's wrong.
I didn't... Mike, stop.
Control your client, Counselor.
Stop it. Stop. Your Honor,
we're terribly sorry.
The State rests.
Mr. Morelli.
The defense has no questions
for the witness at this time,
Your Honor.
We finally got
the police video
of Lona McKerin
picking Mike
out of the photo lineup.
Great.
Let's see it.
Okay, if you see the man
who attacked you,
just circle his picture
with the red pen.
I have the one
from before.
This one.
You sure?
Yeah.
Okay.
She said, "I have
the one from before."
Yeah, so?
What before?
I wish you weren't here
today, Miss McKerin.
I wish I didn't have
to ask you these questions.
But a terrible crime
has been alleged.
Miss McKerin,
I'm gonna show you
the police video
of your identification
of my client,
and then
I'm gonna ask you
a few questions.
Are you gonna be okay with that?
Okay.
Thank you.
Okay...
if you see the man
who assaulted you,
just circle his picture
with the pen.
Take your time.
It's okay.
Can I take a break?
Yeah, sure you can.
I'm just really tired.
It's fine.
No problem.
Do you remember
asking for a break?
Yes. I-I had been
up for so long.
Absolutely, absolutely,
I understand.
But you resumed a half hour
later, is that correct?
Yes.
Okay.
Okay, if you see the
man who attacked you,
just circle his picture
with the red pen.
I have the one
from before.
This one.
You sure?
Yeah.
Okay.
Miss McKerin, is this the...
lineup that you circled?
Yes.
Were you aware that
this was not the original lineup
you were shown?
What?
You were shown
two different photo lineups
that night, and
the only person
that appeared in both...
was my client.
You had no idea
that there were two, did you?
No.
You were unable
to identify my client
in the first one.
Is that correct?
Yes.
But you could see him
in the second one.
Yes.
Is it possible...
that that's because
you remembered him from
the first photo lineup
and not the attack?
No.
No, it has to be him.
Wh... When I pointed him out,
they told me not to be afraid
because he was in jail already.
Now, I-I know this is
very tough for you,
but I need you to take a moment
right now and just think.
In light of
these new facts,
can you say,
for certain,
that it was my client
who sexually assaulted
you that night?
Objection, asked and answered.
Overruled.
You may answer the question.
I'm not sure.
Miss McKerin...
you need to be sure.
I don't...
I don't know.
No further questions,
Your Honor.
Okay, Mary. We are all clear
that you do not belive Kelli.
Now, without using the term
"micro-expression"
or anything else you might have
learned while watching
48 Hours Mystery, can
you please tell us why?
She seems like a bitch.
Aw, come on!
She thinks so, too.
I didn't say
it like that!
Okay. Kelli...
was a terrible wife.
She was judgmental,
she was withholding,
she was snippy, and...
Alexei, all the cheating aside,
seems great.
He's-he's funny,
he's personable,
he's good-looking.
Both of them love Sasha
with all their hearts.
Do you both agree with that?
Right, Mary?
Yes.
Talia?
Yeah.
Great. None of that
has anything to do
with our verdict.
Here we go.
"If the mother of a child
"has primary physical custody,
"the father of
the child shall not
"willfully conceal
or remove the child
from the physical custody
of the mother."
That is all we are
allowed to consider.
Now, did Alexei willfully
conceal or remove
Sasha from Kelli?
Hands for guilty.
Come on, Mary.
Yes.
Talia.
Come on.
All right,
all right.
Guess we'll pick up tomorrow.
All right, I'm out of here.
Please,
we've been here forever.
Gladys, careful
with that diabetic cat.
No more candy
for her, okay?
Can we just make
up a verdict, please?
See you guys tomorrow. Talia.
Just one sec.
I'm not disputing
that the...
cuisine is four-star...
but come on, don't you have
a life you got to get back to?
I have to go.
Hey, Talia, you
forgot your purse.
How are those busses running?
Fine.
Hey.
Sorry I'm late.
Are you all right?
Yeah.
Sorry, I'm... I'm just
not used to all of this.
Well, it's a good thing.
Find anything?
Not much.
She was a full-time student
at USLV, huh?
Yeah. Why?
Where's her books?
Wait, look at this.
She works at Fabio's.
A lot.
How does a full-time student
work a double shift
six days a week?
♪ ♪
Hey, Nick.
Hey.
What, um...
what is this?
I can't see with
your fingers in the way.
It is a bill from
our corporate card
with charges for
room service
and spa treatments at the
Beverly Hills Hotel.
That was from a year ago!
Don't change the subject.
I was at a legal seminar
in Los Angeles-- what, are
you going through the files
trying to find
something on Nicky?
You went with Jess.
She's my wife!
Vacations with your wife--
it's not a valid
business deduction.
Uh, ring-ring, hello?
Oh, Mr. Tax Computer.
How are you?
Who you looking for?
Nick Morelli?
Yeah. Stings, doesn't it?
Ow!
I'm gonna sting your ass.
Ha-ha-ha!
Lisa.
Pete.
Hey, what's going on?
Well, Lona was
a student at USLV,
but she dropped out...
after accusing another student
of sexually assaulting her.
How come we
don't know about this?
No charges were filed.
School handled
it internally,
and during the hearing,
it came out that
both of the students
were under
the influence of alcohol,
and the school
dismissed the charges,
then she dropped out. Do we have
the name of the guy she accused?
Well, we can't
use this in court.
Well, what do you mean?
The allegation
goes to
the accused's credibility.
Look, I know this is
your first rape case, Lisa...
That has nothing
to do with it, okay?
This is about
attacking the victim.
The jury needs to know
if the victim lied
about a past
sexual assault.
Yeah, well,
she's not lying now,
'cause they did
a rape kit on her.
And our guy didn't do it.
Yeah, and Lona
already admitted on the stand
that she wasn't sure
Mike was the guy
who attacked her.
So we already have
our reasonable doubt.
Okay, Lisa...
let's play this out.
What now?
We drop our defense
and just...
hope the jury
goes along with us?
Well, what
do you want?
We're just supposed to go ahead
and destroy
this girl's reputation?
You think I want to do this?
Huh?
Is that what you think?
I have no choice, Lisa.
You were a student at USLV,
is that correct?
Yes.
And you just dropped out?
Objection,
relevance.
Withdrawn.
Miss McKerin, have you
ever made a claim
for a sexual assault before?
Objection,
the question introduces
inadmissible
prejudicial evidence.
It goes to credibility,
Your Honor.
I'll allow, but you are
on a tightrope, Counselor.
Have you?
Yes.
In college.
Was there an investigation
into that claim?
Yes, there was.
And what was the outcome
of that investigation?
The administrative board ruled
that the charges were false.
They said that
I was lying.
I wasn't.
Thank you.
The court will take
a ten-minute recess.
Hey.
How you doing?
I'm okay.
You want to go over anything
before you testify?
No.
She's gonna be
all right.
You know, Michael could
afford to move out...
but he stayed
'cause he knew I...
I couldn't stand to be
in the house alone.
He's good to me.
Mm.
And you're good to him.
You know, if
you want an ear,
if there's something you want
to talk about, I'm here for you.
I don't know what to do.
I'm all he has.
Hey, just do what your
heart tells you to do.
He's my son.
She's their daughter.
I had a couple
glasses of wine,
and I fell asleep while
we were watching TV.
What time?
I don't know.
When I woke up, it was
around 9:00. Where was Mike?
I didn't see him.
You didn't see him,
or...?
He wasn't home.
I looked.
Okay...
All right.
We got a problem.
Desi's gone; my mother has to
testify-- she's my only alibi.
Mike, I-I can't put
your mother on the stand
if I know she's
gonna commit perjury.
What are you gonna do?
I'm gonna let the defense rest.
The victim's testimony
is suspect.
Is that enough to win?
Well, it helps
that there's no physical evidence,
but there's no way to know for sure.
Put me on the stand.
What are you gonna say, Mike?
I mean, your alibi is based
on your mother's lie
that she saw you leave.
But the jury doesn't know that.
What?
Well, the truth doesn't matter.
You're a defense lawyer--
your job is to win.
So you got to put me
on that stand
so I can convince the jury
that I'm innocent...
...just like I did with you.
If you don't, it's
ineffective counsel.
I get a new trial anyway.
Guard?
Just do your job.
I'm not going to jail
for this slut.
Nick! Hey! Hey!
Nick! Nick, come on!
Guard! Guard!
Come on.
I looked that kid
dead through the eye,
and I can't believe I
didn't see through his act.
Well, you've known him
since he was 12--
you wanted to believe. Aw,
I'm smarter than that, Pete.
Okay, well, what now, Nick?
'Cause if you put him
on the stand and he's lying,
you're committing a felony.
You got to withdraw
from the case.
Yeah. No, we're in the
middle of the trial.
No way in hell the
judge lets me out.
I can't believe it.
I made that victim...
doubt herself.
I practically called her a liar.
There is another option.
Mike wants to testify,
you let him testify
on the narrative.
Step back and let him
tell his own story.
And if Nick doesn't
question Mike on direct
and he doesn't
object during cross,
the ADA will know
something's up.
Let him sink himself.
Why don't we save time?
Put "I'm a
lying rapist"
on a sign around his neck.
No, Nick,
let him do it himself.
Get out of the way.
That's what you got to do.
No.
We're defense
attorneys--
we defend.
That's what I got to do.
Is the defense ready
to call its first witness?
Yes, Your Honor.
Well, Counselor?
Just do your job.
Mr. Wayne, can you tell the court
what happened the night
of this alleged offense?
I ate some dinner with my mom,
and after dinner, we
both watched some TV
until a little after 10:00.
I told her I was
going out for a while,
I gave her a kiss good-bye,
and I-I left.
Is there anything else
you'd like to tell the court?
Well, after I left the house,
I walked to my
friend Desi's apartment.
Got there around 10:30,
and I sat on his couch
and played some video games.
I left right
after midnight,
and I was accosted by
some police officers.
I have no more, Your Honor.
Thank you.
Your witness.
Mr. Wayne, you said
you sat on Desi's couch
and played video games
that night.
Is that correct?
Yes.
Where was the couch?
In his living room.
And where was the television?
Across from the couch.
So... you couldn't have been
at the victim's house
sexually assaulting her,
because you were at Desi's
playing video games?
Yes.
Mr. Wayne, this is a photo taken
at Desi Williams' apartment
after his death.
Mr. Wayne...
can you explain
how you play video games
on a television
that isn't there?
Mm.
Zoey.
It's go time.
Oh!
Sorry.
Wait. This
isn't my purse.
Huh.
Petersen's Used Carland.
I hope you're aware
that jury tampering
is a serious allegation,
Mr. Kaczmarek?
I am, Your Honor,
but during voir dire,
she made a point about
how she had to take the bus
because she didn't have a car.
Was I the only one
paying attention?
And you're sure
that the key ring was from
the defendant's
previous place of employment?
Petersen's Used Carland--
a name that bad
is hard to forget.
Were you aware
of any contact between
the defendant and this woman? No, sir.
Get the juror.
Thank you, Mr. Kaczmarek.
You noticed she had
a new purse, huh?
I notice everything.
I'll be expecting a gift
for making your case, Cole.
Shoulder bag
or tote?
I can still hear you.
Sorry.
Has the jury
reached a verdict?
Yes, we have,
Your Honor.
On the crime of sexual assault,
the jury find the defendant
Michael Wayne, guilty.
♪ ♪
Thank you.
Court is adjourned
until tomorrow,
when we begin the penalty phase.
You son of a bitch.
You set me up.
You did it all yourself,
my friend.
I'm gonna get a new trial, 'cause
you didn't do your job, Nick.
Good luck with that.
♪ ♪
I'll have what he's having.
What are you doing here?
That hot juror that
was a hold-out... Yeah?
Defendant gave her a car
to hang the jury.
Ten minutes after replacing
her, 12-zip, guilty.
What kind of car?
A used Tercel.
Geez!
God, I wouldn't sell my soul
for less than a four-door.
Thanks, Steve.
Pete...
you ever wonder...
what we'd be doing
if we weren't lawyers?
Well, a hundred years ago,
my ancestors were
digging up potatoes
with their bare hands.
Even our worst day
is better than that.
Here's to our
worst days.
And the better ones
ahead. Sir, yes, sir.
Leave the bottle.
Here. Let me get it.
Whoa-ho, easy.
You know who got
Al Capone, don't you?
Yeah, it was the, uh... G-men.
Right?
Sync and corrected by
www.addic7ed.com