(HORN HONKING)
MAN ON RADIO:
On the Maryland Giant,
I'm the Fryman in the morning,
and it's time for sports!
The Orioles continue to shoot
skyward like a Saturn V.
Having locked up the
pennant over a week ago,
last night in Municipal Stadium
in front of over 19,000.
(SIREN WAILS)
Excuse me, sir. Can I
speak with one of your passengers?
Sure. Go ahead.
Go in back.
I'll go back there now.
Thanks.
Robert Kearns?
Dr. Kearns?
Yes?
Sir, your family's very
concerned about you.
Why don't you
come with us?
The Vice President asked
me to come to Washington.
Yes, sir,
we understand.
You should
come with us.
I suppose I could.
Hmm.
I'll take that
for you.
Be careful.
That's for my kids.
Don't you worry, sir.
We'll take good care of it.
(CHURCH CHOIR SINGING)
PETE: Scott, you and Louise want to
come to our place for dinner tonight?
SCOTT: Well, what
about the Pistons game?
No, I gave my tickets to my kids.
Prices where they are,
you gotta be kidding.
Hiya, Bob.
Hey.
- How's the teaching going?
(MEN CHATTERING)
Oh, good.
How many Kearns kids
are there now? 13?
I can divine it.
- Oh, you can divine it.
What Scott here divines is that
the Knicks have two guys out
with ankle injuries,
right, Bob?
Mmm. You talking
about basketball?
(CHUCKLES) Kearns,
you probably mean that.
I do.
(CHUCKLES)
(ORGAN PLAYING)
REVEREND: As I look out over
this sea of familiar faces,
I see men from
G.M., A.M.C.,
Ford, Chrysler,
Jeep and Dodge
all under one roof,
as it should be.
And it brings to
mind the apostles.
What was it that brought these
very different men together as one?
(KIDS CHATTERING)
Father Rooney was good
today, huh? He was funny.
He was great.
He really was.
Can I pinch you?
No, dipshit.
- Mom, make him stop calling me...
What did you just say?
Dipstick. It's an
automotive term, Mom.
Well, say that one more time and
I will have your chassis waxed.
Okay? That's an
automotive term, too.
Look at this.
I turn this thing off, 10
seconds later, I can't see.
PHYLLIS:
I can't see, either.
So you turn it back on,
and now the
windshield's clean,
(WIPERS SCREECHING)
but the wipers are dragging.
You hear that, that screeching?
- Mmm-hmm.
(CHUCKLING) Yeah, I hear it, I hear it.
TIM: Yeah, it's annoying.
All right, so it's raining
and I turn it back off.
But now I can
barely see.
I can't... I can't see anything, sweetie.
- I can't, either.
Sweetie, turn them on.
- Right now, I can't see a thing.
If I don't turn this thing on
right now, we'll hit somebody.
Turn it on, honey. Please.
(ALL EXCLAIMING)
Look at this!
(HORN HONKING)
PHYLLIS: Okay, that's
not funny at all.
BOB: Whoa. All right.
All right. All right.
Ten thousand engineers
in Detroit,
you'd think they'd know
how to design an automobile.
What are you doing?
Oh, I was thinking
about how eyes work.
We blink about every four, six seconds,
and there's this lachrymal fluid and...
Really?
Interesting.
And what are you
thinking about?
(SIGHS)
I'm thinking we should
make another kid.
Gotcha.
(CHUCKLES) - Yeah.
Oh, that's good.
You're funny.
(CHUCKLING)
I'm gonna be
right back.
Huh? Huh?
- Yeah.
Spell "giant."
KATHY: G-I...
PATRICK: G-I-A-N-T. It's so easy.
Is your name Kathy? Is it
your test? I don't think so.
It's Kathy's test.
Kathy, what's the next one?
Puppy.
Puppy or science? Puppy's
too easy. Do science.
Hi, poop.
- Okay. S-C-I-E-N-C-E.
Six minutes, you guys.
Come on, let's really hustle.
KATHY: S-C-I-E-N-C-E.
PATRICK: When is
Calvin's sleepover?
Friday. I have to call his mom.
KATHY: Can I go...
TIM: "Police described the
badly decomposed body..."
I don't think so today,
sweetie. I don't know.
"...as one of the most gruesome crimes..."
PATRICK: What time?
What is that?
- My current event.
I thought we agreed we weren't
doing murders for a while.
KATHY: Mom, what
about after school?
Honey, good morning.
- Hey.
You tired?
- No, I'm fine.
What time did
you come to bed?
I don't really know.
Are you substituting today?
(WAILING) Yeah, fourth
grade. Eat something.
BOB: No, no. I'll get something
at school. That seems like a lot.
No, they called.
It's at Pat's school,
and so I can pick
them up after anyway.
Well, who's gonna watch him?
- And I'm gonna take him to the...
Don't worry about it.
Eat something, honey.
Okay. Hey.
Bye, kids.
All right?
TIM: See you, Dad.
DENNIS: Bye, Dad.
PATRICK: Bye, Dad.
- Don't use your wipers today.
Bob, what?
Yeah, I needed
the motor.
Honey, what
if it rains?
No, no. It's
not gonna rain.
(THUNDER RUMBLING)
BOB: Good morning, everybody.
I want to welcome you all
to the first day of the quarter
for Applied Electrical Engineering.
My name is Dr. Robert Kearns
and I'd like to start by
talking to you about ethics.
I can't think of a job or a career
where the understanding of ethics
is more important
than engineering.
Who designed the artificial
aortic heart valve?
An engineer did that.
And who designed the gas
chambers at Auschwitz?
An engineer did that, too.
One man was responsible for helping
save tens of thousands of lives,
another man
helped kill millions.
Now, I don't know what any of you
are gonna end up doing in your lives,
but I can guarantee you
that there will come a day
where you have
a decision to make,
and it won't be as easy as deciding
between a heart valve and a gas chamber.
Everything we do
in this classroom
ultimately comes back to
that notion. All right?
(STUDENTS MURMUR IN AGREEMENT)
Grades count, too.
(ALL LAUGHING)
Hi, Jerry.
- Dr. Kearns.
I'm gonna make a donut run.
Are you interested?
Mmm, you can't do
it mechanically.
Can't do what?
That's the pause between wipes.
That was my mistake.
Can't do it mechanically. You might
be able to do it electronically.
Oh, probably.
You want a donut?
No, thanks.
Okay.
BOB: Dennis, stop it.
Timmy! Cut it out. Get over here.
Okay, Dennis,
problem again?
To make it pause
between sweeps.
BOB: Good.
And solution?
Well, I guess we could change the speed.
- Yeah.
Yeah, except it would be the wrong
approach and it wouldn't work.
What do I
always say?
"Who farted?"
Besides that.
Uh, look for
the unobvious.
Yeah. So you do listen.
All right. Well, we're just looking
for a measured,
consistent pause.
Like your eye, right there.
See that?
The way it blinks
away a tear?
And we could try
a bimetallic timer
that responds
to heat changes.
But then, of course, what
do we do on a cold day?
Put the ball down.
Sit down here.
I want you to
put this together.
I want you to solder this, all right?
Dennis, help him out. Get over here.
Here we go. Here we go.
We got Team Kearns here!
Yeah, this is hot, this is hot.
So, careful, all right?
That's got a transistor and a
capacitor, and resistors in there.
That's as simple as I can get it.
That's when you get real beauty.
When less is more.
Will it work?
It works up here
perfectly.
We got resistors, each one
rated at a different tolerance.
And each one should work in a wiper
motor. Where are the meter cords?
Uh, just over there.
Of course, there's a thousand
different combinations.
Our job is to find
the one that works.
And there is one
that'll work in theory.
You know, Marconi spent seven
years trying to perfect the radio.
(BALL BOUNCING)
Timmy, stop with
the ball, please!
Well, what do you
know about that?
KIDS: One, two,
three, now!
Wow!
- One, two...
PHYLLIS: Honey, it's so great.
It really works.
MAUREEN:
Two, three, now!
PATRICK: That's it,
it's going.
(IMITATES FRANKENSTEIN)
It's alive!
It moves!
It pauses!
(SQUEALING) It's alive!
Alive! Alive! Alive!
What do you think?
Let's go out and
celebrate in real style.
Really?
- Yeah.
KATHY: I'm gonna
buy a diamond ring.
Thank you, Peggy.
PATRICK: You're only six.
You got a little ways to go, sweetie.
- I got the burger, right?
DENNIS: Can I have
some more Pepsi?
Uh, me, too, please.
Sure, if your parents
say it's okay.
All right this time.
PATRICK: Did you get a pickle?
You know why I wanted so many kids?
Because I had six in my
family and you loved my family?
(CHUCKLES) True.
I missed that growing up.
(CHUCKLING)
I think you're all caught up.
BOB: Hey. Hey. Listen up!
- Look at him. Look.
There's 20 million cars built
in this country every year,
and every one of them
is gonna need our wiper.
Wow!
- Huh?
And guess who's gonna
manufacture those.
KIDS: Who, Dad?
Us.
We are?
Yeah, we are.
In fact, here you go.
I want to toast to the
Kearns Corporation right here
(KIDS CHEERING)
and its board
of directors.
GIL: Lou Galin's two weeks
late on that glass shipment.
PAUL: What do you
want me to do?
GIL: Well, why don't you give
him a call? He's your buddy.
PAUL: Did you pay him?
GIL: Yeah. Half.
I'll call him.
Well, that's the
damnedest thing.
Yeah.
Get this, it's also possible to build
a timing control into the wiper column
so that you could adjust
the time between movements.
Well, why?
Well, because it obviously rains
at different intensity levels.
GIL: Yeah.
- Right.
That's part of
the whole idea.
What do you want
to do with it?
GIL: Well, Bob wants
to manufacture it.
So from our end, we just put
up the dough for the patents,
research and development, all
of which goes through Kearns,
and we also seed the
money for manufacturing.
And I could be ready
to go very soon.
Yeah, it's a pretty
simple deal. The fact is,
if we can nail a quarter of cars
in America at, what, 50 bucks a pop?
Think about it.
Just curious, do you have any
manufacturing experience, Mr. Kearns?
Inventing, with all due respect,
is one thing, but building is...
Well, Bob's background's in
engineering, so I don't see how...
Gil, Gil, let Bob talk,
for Christ's sake.
Right, right. Bob?
- Yeah, um...
Well, no actual
experience, no, not yet.
But, uh... Look, I know I'm
not your ordinary businessman.
I don't have
an MBA, but...
No apologies, Bob.
You're doing great.
We'll hold his hand
the whole time.
It's not gonna be a problem.
Yeah, it's a bet.
But so was the kidney
machine that keeps Dad alive.
Barely alive.
What are you gonna call it?
The Kearns Blinking
Eye Wiper.
(CLEARING THROAT) Yeah. Well,
I'm not sure about the name.
You look sensational, hon.
Thanks.
You're a little
nervous, huh?
Aren't you?
No.
(CHUCKLES)
Welcome, ma'am.
- Thanks.
Welcome, sir.
Sir? Here you go.
Funny, we've never been
inside here before.
Oh, yeah. I never
thought about it.
Well, start thinking
about it.
I want to be able to take
you to more places like this.
(CHUCKLES) Okay.
No, really. This is a big
deal. Start of a new life.
You gonna quit teaching?
You think I should?
I think you should take
it a step at a time.
Oh, so you're saying
it's not gonna last.
No! I'm saying I'll
love you either way.
Which is French for
"be prepared to fail."
Robert!
- No.
I just want to do
something important.
You will.
Will you love me
more if I do?
No. I'll love you
more if you're rich.
I married a gold digger.
What do you know about that?
PHYLLIS: Oh, I just...
They're driving me crazy.
They don't want to go to
the rec center anymore,
and at least when school starts,
that takes care of four of them.
(CHUCKLES) And then we've just
got the two little ones at home,
but we have fun.
Well, ours are up at Harbor Springs.
They just love it up there.
Oh, I bet!
But you don't go with them?
Well, that's the problem.
It's just hard to find time to get away.
Right, Bob? They think it's
like summer camp up there.
I don't even think they
notice we're not there.
Mmm.
(CHUCKLES)
Do you see Robert's eye?
Yeah, is that bothering you?
No.
- Do you know the story of Robert's eye?
BOB: Oh, Phyll, Phyll, forget it.
- The story of our wedding night?
It's such a funny
story, honey!
So, it's our
wedding night,
(CHUCKLES) and I'm getting
ready in the bathroom
and putting on my
little negligee.
Okay, okay, okay!
And Robert's in the next room,
opening a bottle of champagne.
Well, I'd never
opened one before.
Figures. Bob had never opened a bottle
of champagne before his wedding night.
So I had it down between my
legs, and I look down and, pow!
Cork goes off
right in my eye,
and I fall back on the sheets.
I was bleeding.
I come out and
start screaming.
Screaming bloody murder, Phyllis.
- I don't know what's happened.
But it all
turned out okay
and he made it
up to me later.
Hey, hey!
JOE: Good evening, everyone.
My name is Joe Warwick,
and I'm the guy who leaned
on you to come out tonight.
And I'm glad I did.
I want you to give yourselves
a big hand, because tonight,
we raised $11,000 for
the Children's Hospital.
Now, let's do some more dancing to
the sound of the Telegraph Five!
Hey, let's dance.
- No.
It's okay, it's okay, come on.
- No, Phyllis. Phyllis.
Come on.
(BAND PLAYING UPBEAT MUSIC)
(SCREAMS)
Hey. Say, Bob.
Phyllis, you look lovely.
Would you mind if Gil and I dragged
Bob outside for some business chat?
Where we can hear
ourselves think.
Go on.
(MAN SINGING)
PAUL: We've got some real
interesting news for you.
Paul, when are they gonna
fix that seventeenth green?
I'm tired of playing
on that temporary green.
I'm on it, I'm on it. I took it to
the board. It'll get taken care of.
Bob, you don't play
golf, do you?
Uh, no, no.
So, Bob, we got some really
good feedback on the feelers
we put out for
the Blinking Eye.
Yeah, it turns out the concept
isn't as unique as we first thought.
The Big Three have assigned
their windshield wiper teams
to come up with an
intermittent wiper.
That's what they call it.
The Intermittent Wiper.
I'll be damned.
No, it's fine. More than anything,
now we know there's a demand for it.
Until now, your wiper
seemed like a clever gadget.
But they want it. And more importantly,
they haven't cracked it yet.
Mercury's been working on one for over
a year and they still haven't beaten it.
So we want to set up
a demonstration.
Now, Ford is very interested
in seeing what we have.
Ford?
You didn't mention
anything about...
Are you ready?
Wow, Ford. Wow.
I don't know.
I mean, it needs some more work.
More consistency.
I can assure you we won't
sell it if we don't show it.
Yeah, but should we be showing them ours if
they're already working on their own version?
Well, that's
up to you.
But maybe it's a good reason
to show it sooner than later.
I don't know, Gil.
Kearns, I'd hate to see
you if you got bad news.
We're not gonna let
anybody take it apart,
especially after the money
we've put into the patents.
We'll just give them a peek.
Cat stays in the bag.
(INAUDIBLE)
Now, Paul's real
excited about this.
In fact, I haven't seen him
quite like that in a long time.
Well, I got
a lot to do.
No, I know, know.
By the way, this is yours.
Mine?
For now. No more
aquariums, Bob.
Just throw the unit in
here and take it to Ford.
Sal!
Sal here'll help
you put it in.
Just tell us what you want,
Mr. Kearns.
Okay.
He'll be here.
We're very busy
here, Mr. Previck.
FRANK: This is him, yeah?
GIL: Yeah.
Hiya, Bob.
- Hey, Gil.
Frank Sertin, Vice President
of Research and Development,
meet Bob Kearns,
the inventor of the
Intermittent Windshield Wiper.
(CHUCKLES) Oh, we'll see.
We'll see.
It's a real pleasure.
- Good. Thank you.
All right, Bob, let's
see what you got.
All right.
- And, Bob!
We want you to do it
with the engine running.
We've found that the heat can play havoc
with some of the systems we've tried.
Right now?
Right now.
(CLEARS THROAT)
(ENGINE STARTING)
FRANK: Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Where... Where's he going?
GIL: Bob's real
big on security.
FRANK: Okay.
Okay, Bob!
Come on, let her rip!
What's going on?
- I don't know.
Okay.
Bob?
I don't know.
(GRUNTING)
Okay.
GIL: Bob!
- Yeah?
Oh, here! It's a fuse.
It's the fuse.
- It's a fuse!
Yeah, we're good.
GIL: It'll do that all day,
engine running or not.
Well, that is...
That's good.
We call this
"variable speed."
Variable speed.
"Variable dwell."
That is very
impressive.
Gil, how about giving us a
little look under the hood, huh?
Sorry, Frank,
we can't do that.
He's not doing that
manually, is he?
(CHUCKLES)
Bob? Bob!
Uh, would you get
out of the car?
They think you might be
manipulating the controls.
Well, I am.
That is very
good, Bob.
(CHUCKLING)
That is very, very good.
I think we should get
you a copy of our specs.
But I can tell you this, though.
At a minimum, at a minimum,
it's gonna have to run a
million and a half cycles
under real-time
conditions.
And operate...
Uh, excuse me.
What's the maximum
temperature under the hood?
ENGINEER: It's, uh...
- Two hundred and seventy degrees.
Mmm-hmm.
(CHUCKLING) If it operates in
the field like it did here...
Where'd you get
your degree?
Uh, Case Western.
I'm gonna look
under the hood.
Sorry, we'd rather not.
It's nothing against Ford, sir.
I've admired the company my whole life.
No problem.
But I'll get to work right away,
just as soon as I get the specs.
Okay, good, good.
Listen, I know that we are
gonna be in touch with you.
Yes, sir.
- Very good. Gil.
Frank.
Dr. Kearns?
Case Western.
That's a...
That's a good school.
Get out of the car.
You did a hell
of a job, pal.
(CHUCKLING)
Hell of a job.
Thank you.
I'll see you.
(WATER RIPPLING)
BOB: Well, there's
a difference between
a good idea and
a good product.
I've had a lot
of good ideas.
Just nothing that's quite
clicked, you know?
It makes you wonder what it
is makes a man successful.
Brains?
Talent?
Of course, there's a lot of unsuccessful
talents running around out there.
Maybe this is the one.
Maybe this'll get you where
you want to be, you know?
Yeah.
But I don't know. I look at you
and I look at us and I just think
you're a success.
Don't you feel that way?
Maybe it's some
other thing.
Like luck, timing.
Some intangible
thing like that.
It haunts me a little.
I'm gonna get some more tea.
Do you want anything?
No, I'm good.
- No? Okay.
DENNIS: I explained it to
her, and then she just, like...
Patrick, come on
with that paper!
PATRICK:
I'm good, I got it!
(ALL CHATTERING)
Okay, it's Tuesday,
"Cold, clear and sunny.
"Wednesday,
clear and warmer."
Hey, hey, hey.
PATRICK: Hey, give it back!
Let him have it.
Okay, "Thursday, clear.
"Friday, partly cloudy and
colder, and a clearing on Sunday."
BOB: Well, we
need some rain.
Maybe instead of grace, we
should say a prayer, Dad.
DENNIS: Didn't we just say grace already?
- Yeah.
No, no, that's okay.
That's okay. Let's do that. Come on.
Let's do a little prayer here, huh?
When you say a prayer, you're
supposed to fold your hands.
Dear God, thank you for all the
sunshine you've been sending.
We know in your
infinite wisdom,
you managed to create the elasticity
of rain water different than tap.
If you could see it
in your good graces
to, you know,
send us some rain
so that we can test the Blinking
Eye in real-life conditions,
we'd appreciate it.
Amen.
ALL: Amen.
Do you think he heard you,
Daddy?
My luck,
he's a G.M. man.
(THUNDER CLAPPING)
KIDS: Go, go, go!
Careful! Dennis, in the
back! Maureen, be careful!
(ALL EXCLAIMING)
(ALL WHOOPING)
BOB: And it's working, too.
Watch that, watch that.
(ALL CHEERING)
I can adjust the speed, too.
I can adjust it.
Look at that.
DENNIS: Yeah.
Perfect.
PATRICK: That was awesome.
Hey, hey, hey! Hey, you see
that car across the street?
Oh, yeah.
Look at the driver.
He's staring right at us.
He thinks I'm turning
the wiper on and off here.
PHYLLIS: You think he can tell?
Look at this. No, no!
Look here.
Look at that, mister. No hands! He's
wondering what the heck's going on!
How's he doing that?
TIM: No hands.
PATRICK: Hi.
How the heck are
they doing that?
(KIDS LAUGHING)
We got ourselves a winner here,
I'd say.
RECEPTIONIST: Ford Motor Company.
How can I help you?
What's the deal?
MAN: Well, he's got it,
and it really seems to work.
And you've gone
through it completely?
As close as we could
from a distance.
(CHUCKLING) He hasn't
actually let us do any surgery.
Why not?
He's nervous about
people getting too close.
Mack, he is a particular kinda guy.
Well, whatever.
We gotta get this puppy moving.
The marketing department's all over me.
They think they can sell the shit out of it.
What's he want?
To build it.
He wants to manufacture it?
Himself?
Apparently, that's
his dream, yeah.
(SIGHING) Okay, well,
we'll deal with that later.
Right now we need
to get him on board.
Okay.
(DOOR OPENS)
FRANK: Come on in,
guys. Bob, Dick Gordon.
There you go.
BOB: Nice to see you again.
Gil, nice to
see you again.
You, too, Macklin.
This is
Dr. Bob Kearns.
Bob Kearns, winner of the
wiper competition. Congrats.
Bob, I've been going over the reports on your
Intermittent. It looks like you cracked it.
Have you worked up
a unit price yet?
No. Not yet.
I'm hoping to...
Good. And you do want
to manufacture it?
BOB: Yes, sir.
I want to come through for Ford.
And we like that. So let's
get a unit price, then.
Frank, have you sent a
working unit to Washington?
No, Mack, we haven't.
Bob's... He's not comfortable with that.
Really?
Now, Bob, you do understand
this is a safety device.
And before we can install any
safety device on any of our cars,
we have to submit it to
Washington for approval.
And that means we're gonna
need a working unit from you.
I understand that. And I understand
I'll need your cars for my wipers.
(CHUCKLING)
But I thought that,
uh, if we had a...
We like to work closely
with our people, Bob.
That's...
That's the deal.
Nothing else would make sense.
I'm sure Gil will tell you that
we have a very close relationship
with Previck Automotive.
Bob knows that.
That's why we came here first.
He's right, though,
Bob. It does need to be approved.
TYLER: We're interested in offering the
Intermittent as an option on at least
one model next year. From there, our
plan is to expand it to the entire line.
Now, that means we're working
under a serious deadline.
So we're gonna need a unit
from you as fast as possible.
Okay. Yeah,
I can do that.
Great.
Let's get started on
the legal right away.
Right, gentlemen?
- Absolutely.
Thank you.
Thank you so much.
I'll get my demo and
research over to Mr. Sertin.
Excellent. This is what it's all
about, Bob. Corporate "can do."
FRANK: How about that?
Now, remember. There's a right way
and a wrong way to do this, okay?
Whatever you do, don't let
them think that it's perfect.
TIM: But what if it is?
Hey, listen to
your father now.
Here, you wanna take him?
No, I'm serious about this.
Be very careful
what you say, okay?
The moment they think they got a
sucker in the line, you're dead.
Here he comes.
Just everybody take it easy.
Let him come to us a little bit, okay?
We'll be fine.
Let me do the talking.
DENNIS: What's
new about that?
Hey! No back talk.
Come here.
Michael?
- Hi.
How are you? Bob Kearns.
- Nice to meet you, Bob.
(KIDS CHATTERING)
PHYLLIS: How big is it?
Thirty thousand
square feet.
Structurally, this is as sound as
any building you'll find in Detroit.
The loading ramps are more than
ample for any job you may have.
Sure looks like it
needs a lot of work.
We're concerned about the price.
Is it the best you can do?
Well, we can probably work out an eight
cents per foot improvement, Mrs. Kearns.
What do you think, guys?
- How much is it?
AGENT: Fifty cents
a square foot.
No.
No, we were figuring
on a lot less than that.
I think the owners
might come down a bit.
Well, we'll have to think about it.
BOB: (ECHOING) Hey!
You hear that echo?
This place is solid!
It's perfect, Michael.
Absolutely perfect! I love it.
(BOTH CHUCKLING)
SALESMAN: It's such
a simple idea.
I'm amazed no one's cracked it before.
Where did you do your research?
My basement.
So, these S.D. 25s
are fixed costs?
Yes, we can do a discount
after 400,000 units.
I assume you'll put the Ford contracts up
against costs. They're backing it, right?
Oh, yeah. We're down the road on
all that. My biggest concern is
that you'll be able
to provide us with
the necessary transistors
and circuits that we need.
Mr. Kearns, Motorola is the biggest
electronics manufacturer in the world.
I think if we can supply the
Pentagon, we can supply you.
The who?
- The...
(CHUCKLING)
That's a good one.
Hiya, Bob.
- Hi.
The gentleman at Motorola put me in
touch with their finance department.
Yeah. Yeah. Bob?
No, I'm serious about this.
We should talk about cash flows...
Want me to take your order?
- Yes.
Actually, do you mind
giving us a second?
Sure.
- Thanks, hon.
Sorry, I'm starving.
They want out, Bob.
Who wants out?
- Ford.
What?
They're just not
interested anymore.
Wait, wait, what... What do
you mean? Well... What happened?
I'm not sure.
Well, who did
you talk to?
Tyler. Yeah.
- Macklin?
What did he
say exactly?
Like I said,
they want out.
Out?
They're not ready yet, and they're
not gonna make a move until they are.
They gave me a line like, you know,
"It's not the Ford style."
Out, or ready, Gil?
Which one is it?
Hang on a second.
I'm in this, too.
(SIGHING)
They have the unit.
We'll get it back.
- When?
I don't know.
I closed on the
operating loan.
Well, don't forget,
I thought you should slow down on that.
They're loading
in transistors.
We're gonna figure this out.
All we gotta do is take it to another...
Bullshit.
Listen. Chrysler,
A.M.C., G. M...
My kids. It's my kids.
Ford was our best bet.
We both know that. But we're not done.
Okay, but they... They strung us along,
and they looked at my work.
I know.
We had a deal.
I think they might be
negotiating here, Gil.
No. They're not.
You sure? Because I haven't...
- Yeah.
It's dead there, Bob.
My God.
(WORKERS CHATTERING)
WORKER: All the boxes are going in
the cage until you know where they go!
Professor Kearns.
Find what you want?
Yes, Louis, thanks.
"State Highway System:
History and Facts."
This for one of
your classes?
No, I'm just doing some work for the
state, analyzing pavement erosion.
Nothing too exciting.
Yeah, but they're paying
you to come up with stuff.
Sounds pretty good to me. You know,
I'm sort of a amateur idea man myself.
A few of us even have
an inventors' club.
Maybe I can call you sometime,
ask you some questions.
Absolutely.
(GROANS)
Hey, you guys are late.
Take it around the back entrance.
MAN 1: Have your invitations
out and ready, please.
Hey, folks,
welcome to Ford.
Got your invitation, sir?
MAN 2: Yeah. Right here.
WOMAN: There are
tons of options.
Excuse me, sir.
Please don't touch the car.
(CLEARS THROAT)
WOMAN: It comes with Select Air
air conditioning in all the models,
and many options
are available.
What about the tires?
Oh, beautiful
Magnum 500 wheels...
(INAUDIBLE)
(UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYING)
CHORUS: (SINGING)
Go, go, go, go!
M.C: (SINGING)
Come on and fly with me
CHORUS: Go, go, go, go!
And take a drive with me
And try a Ford with me
Don't stop! Don't stop!
Go, go, go, go!
CHORUS: Go, go, go, go!
M.C: Our Fords
are bright tonight
CHORUS: Go, go, go, go!
They're outta sight tonight
They're really right tonight
Don't stop! Don't stop!
Go, go, go, go, go!
Ladies and gentlemen,
members of the Ford family.
Introducing the new, the
redesigned, the finest
Ford Mustang in the history
of the Ford Motor Company.
With more options
than ever before.
Stereo, rear window defroster
and the brand-new electronic Intermittent
Windshield Wiper. Let's give it a hand!
Ladies and gentlemen, have you seen
anything that's sexier than that?
And I'm talking about the car
now, not the Mustang girls,
who, by the way, know these
automobiles inside out.
Don't hesitate to ask them any
questions you have, and remember,
in the main auditorium we have
all of next year's exciting buys!
(CHATTERING)
Excuse me, sir.
Could I see your invitation?
Uh, I'm with,
uh, Mr. Tyler.
Why don't we talk
about it outside?
No, I'm with Mr...
Mr. Tyler!
Sir, please.
Right this way.
Mr. Tyler!
Right this way, sir.
Sir, outside.
Thank you.
Okay. Easy.
Step outside.
- Easy!
Their story is that they
went with another design,
one they had in the
works before ours.
Yeah, and that's...
- Or yours.
...just what it is.
It's a story.
It's a goddamn lie.
GIL: Come on.
No, no, I took apart
one of their motors, Gil.
You know what I found inside?
Transistors, capacitors, variable resistors.
Now, that is my design!
What about the patents?
Aren't they worth anything?
Legally, they're
Previck's patents.
What is that
supposed to mean?
Nothing. It's
a technical term.
Barney's putting together
another letter. It's tougher.
You can take a look at
it once it's drafted.
Another letter?
A letter? Gil, they
stole this from us!
Whoa! Let's be careful
with our language.
Let's not use words
like "steal."
Who the hell is this guy?
Huh?
Bob...
Who the hell are you?
What's your angle?
Bob! We gotta be really
strategic about this. Methodical.
And whatever you say
reflects on all of us.
So we're gonna fight it, but
we're gonna do it the right way.
How long is it gonna
take to get an answer?
First, this is Ford.
It won't be quick.
Second, patents.
Christ, they're a minefield.
Not to mention, the patent
courts are totally jammed.
It's gonna take
some time.
Well, whatever it takes.
The point is, this is all gonna be okay.
Good. And in the meantime, let's
go a little softer on the language.
So, a lot of these formulas work
in opposition with one another.
So that a capacitive
reactance,
uh, varies inversely
with the product
of both...
Uh, frequency?
Yeah. Did I
call on you?
Sorry.
Frequency, yes.
And capacitance. Make a note of it.
I'm gonna take
a quick break.
WOMAN ON PHONE: Mr. Previck would
appreciate your patience in this matter.
Yes, well, I'd appreciate it if Mr.
Previck could return my phone call.
(DOORBELL RINGS)
(BARKING)
Who is it?
BOB: It's Mr. Kearns.
Come in, Mr. Kearns.
Oh, hi, Wade.
- Hi.
Wade, did you
ask who it was?
He did, Jean. Hi.
Hi. Bob!
What's going on?
Uh, is Gil here?
It's not really a great time
right now. You should have called.
Jean, hon, do you mind
getting me a refill?
Sure, hon.
GIL: Thanks, hon.
I'll just be a second.
JEAN: Okay.
I'm sorry. I...
- Hang on a second.
I thought we were gonna stay
in communication here, so...
Don't you think it's a little outta
line, you coming over like this?
Okay, well, you haven't
returned my calls in six days.
I'm not sure
I like your tone.
I'm through waiting. I'm not
gonna sit around and do nothing.
You're not
doing nothing.
You called the lawyer,
you pulled Taylor out of a mock trial.
You're on everybody.
You even called my father,
for crying out loud. He's sick!
Tell me one thing.
Are you backing out of this?
What I'm doing is
looking at our options
like any sensible
person would.
Of course they're stonewalling us.
What do you expect?
So then we take
them to court!
Is that right?
This is Detroit, Bob.
I did $17 million in business last year.
You want to guess what
I'm gonna do next year
if I start taking my
customers to court?
This is not about money. This is
about right and wrong, and you know it.
For Christ's sake,
you're my friend!
That's right. I am.
Did you ask to be
involved in this deal?
You need some
perspective.
You need to take a hard look at reality
and realize what we're up against.
It's not your
only good idea.
You've been coming up with stuff
like this since you were 14.
Now, I need to get back to my
dinner, so we'll continue this later.
I'll go it alone.
No. Leave it
alone. Bob?
It's not over yet.
BOB: I'm not gonna
back off of this.
We don't have the money to
bring in lawyers right now,
so we're gonna have to do the
legwork ourselves, and then...
Are you talking about
suing Gil Previck?
No. No, we're gonna go
after the Ford Motor Company.
They're the ones that screwed us.
- What?
Gil just let me down.
Robert, slow down.
We're...
No, no, we're gonna have
to dig up everything
that's ever been
written about me. Okay?
Character stuff,
everything.
This is my number one priority, Phyllis.
Whatever it's gonna take.
Josh, I'm gonna need at
least 10 new wiper motors.
And some of the
earlier versions, too.
JOSH: Sure, Professor.
Not a problem.
BOB: Good. And
circuit boards.
Yeah, they just trash
the test models anyway.
All right, um, where
are we gonna do this?
I'll meet you at the first
lab on the second floor.
Okay.
BOB: Where's the
itemization file?
PHYLLIS: All the files
are in here, hon.
You should see a doctor.
Oh, I'm fine.
Let's keep going.
Previck Automotive
Legal Affairs.
Something to bring their attention
that various automotive manufacturers
are considering using
electronic intermittent wiper...
I don't have it yet.
Considering using electronic
intermittent wiper control...
Do you want to list who?
- Yes.
And that these are in direct
violation of patents jointly held
by both Previck and
Kearns Corporation.
As the inventor of the
Intermittent Wiper, I ask, no...
I demand that they take
immediate legal action.
"Demand" is too strong.
They're our friends.
What difference
does it make?
They're not gonna
read it anyway.
Then why are
we doing this?
Because it makes
me feel better.
Does it?
What is this file?
What is this?
Kathy won it in the swim meet.
She wanted you to see it.
DOCTOR: This is a bad
case of psoriasis.
Now, Phyllis, I want you to take
care of yourself. Use the medication.
Here's the sample.
- Thanks.
And I'm going to write
you a prescription.
How long do I
take that for?
Well, just a month.
I don't know what's going on with you,
Phyllis, but this is all stress-related.
You understand me? You have to
take the stress level way down.
I'll be fine.
Hello, Jean.
- Phyllis.
How are the kids?
- Good.
Phyllis.
Why is Bob
doing this?
He can't stand
being called a liar.
Well, nobody's
saying that he is.
They might as well be.
Oh, for God's sake, Phyllis,
it's Ford. He can't win.
Take care, Jean.
Oh! God!
(CHUCKLING) Yeah.
Med school gives them to us.
We use them
for crash tests.
You should see it when we
drop them down elevator shafts.
It's very instructive.
I'll try that sometime.
Did you get the boards?
What the hell is this?
I know, it's just motors.
I couldn't get any circuit boards.
Why not?
They didn't have any extras. Didn't
have any complete units. I don't know.
These are nothing.
Hey, man, this is
the best I could do.
This doesn't
help me, Josh!
I'm sorry.
(SIGHING)
What does that mean?
Wait a minute.
Did somebody
talk to you?
Did you have a
conversation about me?
What?
Are you working
with them?
Huh? You even know
who they are?
Man, I gotta go.
They're the...
They're the ones who don't
give a shit about you!
MAN: Hey! Hey!
Come on!
What the hell are you doing?
Hey! Hey!
(GLASS SHATTERING)
(SNIFFLES)
(MAN CHATTERING ON RADIO)
(SIREN WAILS)
Look at this lady.
She had five babies at the same time.
(PHONE RINGING)
That's quintuplets,
that's what they're called.
Hello.
MAN: Is this
Mrs. Robert Kearns?
Yes.
Mrs. Kearns, this is Trooper Dale with
the Maryland State Police Department.
Yes.
We've located your husband, ma'am.
Is he okay?
Well, he was found on a bus
outside of Brunswick.
A bus? Where is he?
May I speak to him, please?
Uh, no, ma'am,
he's not here.
He's being transported
to a hospital facility in Rockville.
What happened?
Sorry, I don't know exactly, but you'll
hear from the hospital when he arrives.
Will you be at
this number?
Yes, we'll be here.
Thank you so much.
Thank you, Mrs. Kearns.
Thank you.
- Bye.