Warning!
At ease.
Listen, up people.
Due to operational commitments,
Our Deployment date is been moved up.
We will be on standby to deploy in Iraq,
in 96 hours.
Enjoy your thanks giving,
Ladies.
- Kill
- Wow!
Enjoy the 96 marine.
Good morning, sir.
Yes, go USA! Ending her brother!
Hooray!
Come on,in.
I love you. Bye.
- Did you said Bakersfield?
- Yes.
That's from I'm too.
So this seat is vacant?
No, but I like my books ?up
and things.
What would you do if some old lady
comes sits next to you
talk your head off
Showing you ugly little pictures
of her kids?
fallen a sleep on you,
See? you're Smiling. All right.
- Mike.
- Cristina.
Cal State, this is hard.
Congrats on it.
Thanks. Are you a marine?
- How do you know?
- your haircut.
A type of neighborhood was in the marines.
Really?
He was hurt bad
by a bomb in Iraq.
But you're not get going?
Good.
What the hell!
Jake, look at you,
- The new car with wheels 24.
- Look at that haircut you have.
Come on, Jake.
Welcome back to Bako, brother.
I got a new tattoo.
Ok. This is hard. Dino did that?
Dino? What ...
Do you think Dino could do this?
This is art. This is fucking
Michelangelo, Mike.
All right.
Check this out.
- "you suck?
- No, "i beat your ass."
That's marine's sign there.
That's your tribe now, right?
We need to wearing colors.
Man, did I'll never believe
what girl I met on the bus.
- What? Really? Right now?
- Yes.
- On the way home?
- Baffling.
Damn. I had to leave work.
Jorge, who's up, bro?
No, I already told him ....
I will not ... All right.
Yes. No. Only i just drive off  my friend.
I had to pick him up.
And i one to go there,
one to tell myself.
All right. No, Trace the ...
Wait, are ...
Let me call you back, please.
Thank you.
- I'm sorry about this bull shit.
- It's all right.
I'll see you later, right?
We have big fucking plans, Mikey.
Good to have you back.
I miss you, man.
Oh man like what.
- All right.
Hello?
Family?
I'm home.
Mom?
- Boogerbean!
- Heiniehead!
- What are you doing?
- Okay.
I missed you.
Where are you?
All right.
About this talk.
You're ready for a dunk?
Come on.
Yes.
... said rate. Nothing ...
You like it when I talk to you?
Dad!
What is my baby?
I knew you were coming home today.
- You came back much?
-so you just leave by ourself?
Oh I had a my meeting Today
and  sister was not here.
Sister wasn't here? Sure.
Mike.
mom.
Look at you.
I'm so glad you're home.
- You seem weaker.
- Yes.
oh yes that's because of whole lot of  exercises
and bad food.
- Get you right.
- Yes. I knew you're too good.
- It was hard?
-Oh yes.
So how's my brother?
he on his third strike?
Last time I heard of him,
lived with some people in Oildale.
I only can pray for him.
You're working hard, ha mama?
You know what I was thinking?
I want to take you and
Trisa out for thanks giving.
Dale already got a turkey.
This is cool. you wanna do it.
Yes, we have a real Family dinner
You can invite Jake if you want.
thinking of a devil ...
All right. be carefull, okay?
you promise And no drugs,all right?
mama, i am a marine, do drugs.
Come on now.
- Glad you're home.
- Yes.
Move your ass in the car, soldier!
What are you doing?
You better not expect given you over it, Mike.
I got some wild birds aligned
for you, dog. Get the hell. What the hell!
Get the hell out of here.
That's stupid.
Shut the fuck up.
Where did that? Tijuana?
Mike, have you wearing that hat.
- it's the head of a warrior.
No, whats the hat doin,
who hasn't got any head
- Unless you wear the sailor cap.
- Yes.
Yes, it's a birth control hair style,
Mike.
you're not gotta a get laid in rock in a look.
I am gotta do my best for you,
but that's saying something.
You clearly have forgot.
- I am the pimp of all parties.
- Obviously, I forgot.
- Obviously ...
- I tought you everything you know.
Matter In fact ...
Let's see your phone, man.
- Why?
- Come on, so i can call
A girl, Cristina,
i was telling you about.
Only she is felt out
she felt hope
Give me the fucking phone.
ok, obviously she's a filthy, Mike.
- I hate you.
- What we need, just six?
Mike!
Cristina?
Yes, yes. It's Mike.
So far so good, you know.
it's a family stuff.
I want to stay
with my friend Jake.
- How much on it?
- I know him.
Fortunately, not.
- Can I see your identity card?
My ID?
I got it right.
- Yes, its a tattooed albino...
- What the hell?
- Hair gel everywhere.
- that's me.
- No, you look like ...
- No, not me.
- There are ...
- Yes, it is my id. i am 23.
- Yes.
- Okay.
no, keep the change
I do not care about.
Cristina?
How come i don't know who Cristina?
- Oh yes, the word? all six?
- Yes, all six of them.
Yes, she over 13.
Go to college.
She's a college girl.
she got 4 days to do as a college
Think you can do that?
- I'll deal with this girl.
- its always like that, Mike.
Do not you worry, I have plans for you.
We plan A, plan B and C.
- I backup from backup.
- Asshole.
What the hell did you say?
- You heard me, asshole.
- Mongrel bastard ...
- Asshole.
- Come on.
- You bastard!
- Keep your boy. Let's go.
- Climb-in car.
- On and rad!
- Nice haircut.
- Yes, all right.
I can not believe you left
us like that, Mike.
I thought you'll be pulling out some
Rambo style Marine,or ninja shit
but you know, you busted the diplomat fucked.
What's so funny man?
Don't they teach you that shit
in military school?
Death grips and, martial arts
and all that shit?
but you wanted this be out this crap
it was some high school's.
Yes. It would be fun.
We have to rise above
this shit, Jake.
Come on,you know me.
"Usually i am a fighter.
But tonight, your boys been
like a lover?.
hey come on, we got them party, right?
Man, that's how you want
to do private.
Damn.
lets do this.
Allow me to reintroduce myself.
What's up?
Take a look at him!
Doors URELIT, door URELIT.
So you're all we here doing same old shit?
- Got yourself low little party goin on?
- What?
You have put the biggest party
Do not even look up.
The girls there, right Mikey?
The rough tough bitches? Yes.
Yes, your mom's like a captain of ship
All right, lets go, lets go.
You grab the special sauce?
hey straight out of box liqueur.
I want baby. That's good.
- Yes.
- What , Look at you.
- It's me, man.
- Darcy, what you got for me, smoke?
- i got this for you.
Hey,Mickey, why're you leaving come on.
Me,i love you all ,
but I get on this shit.
- Come on, Mike.
- i got a reputation to defend.
- Follow the fuckin leader.
Let's go.
You don't see that shit on news.
no more
Look it IED. Improvised Explosive
Devices.
Listen to the Pentagon over here.
Military codes and shit.
It's a real talk right there.
Glad you ain't you goin, Mickey,
because if you were gone ...
So what have you done?
You were in a kind of Basic training
, or ...
All kinds of shit. Basic training,
combat infantry school, everything.
Yes? So you got to shoot a few times
Yes. Shit, we have one gun, man ...
Fucking M16 A2, right?
Yeah, man, I read about that shit.
- Dude's awesome.
- Shut the fuck up, Goldie, let him talk.
pass the blood.
oh I forgot.
They piss test you, right?
Yes, you got busted or what?
they said you go to Iraq?
Shut the fuck up.
That's him right there, That's Mike,
That one with the bad hair.
- Shit.
- Come on. These are Tammy and Courney.
- I am Tammy!
- This is Tammy and. ..
I'm sorry baby what's your name again,
Hi. I'm Amber.
- Hi, Amber.
- Amber.
Okay, ladies,
i would like you to meet the fellows.
I will not got to list every bodies namesl.
There are too many.
Let's see how it matches up.
this is good.
That's all I want to hear.
Love has gone shit?
Where did it go?
- Mike, look ...
- Come on.
- Come on!
- Mike get in to room Open the door.
Mike, I hope your little marine infantry
ready for review.
Down!
What the hell is wrong with you?
-Turn hot, soldier.
- Marine.
- Oh Marine.
- You have some nice friends.
- What the hell?
- Are you making vdo of us?
What's going on?
Ladies, ladies.
we're bachelor number two.
- Come on, baby.
- What are you doing, man?
- Which one do you want?
- Look, man, give me your keys.
That's not for me.
Give me the keys and you can have it all.
- It's all yours, man.
- More money. I need more money.
Now I will paying you to shut the fuck up.
Do me a favor and calm down,
Where the hell is Mike?
- Hi.
- What's up?
So What happened to "boys night up "?
I was around boys
for the last seven months, that is ...
Tequila?
I had to take at least one,
but a tea.
I like your apran. Looks nice.
You can come to sit down, if you want.
Are you sure? i mean, never been troubles?
- I do not care.
- Cristina.
Can i get you refill?
You think you will be happier
If you order something else?
She never be happy.
How about you? You are happy, sir.?
I'm lot a happier to closing you
to get to quiting off.
Go, go, go.
I never been any where. have you?
Tijuana. Lake Havasu.
In Reno, twice, to see my dad
playing blackjack.
Nothing serious.
I saw Clint Eastwood
buying cheese at once.
- What kind of cheese?
- I do not know.
- Smell like Cedar.
- So are good at sniffing?
kind of everything.
Smells, feelings.
- You know what I like?
- What?
Shooting gun.
-I do not like that.
- But,  you have never tried that.
Mean its crazy. guess you like this power.
Not a good or bad things.
just power.
What else?
sleeping like a the dead bear. knocked out.
Sex, of course.
And  honest.
Can I see you tomorrow?
Yes. just for a minutes.
84 hours.
What's up, paps?
No, i am good.
Marine don't smoke?
Where are we going?
I need your help me out some for a minutes.
They are awake all night fo pit is,
so I should be ...
Huh?
Do you know some crank's gang
named Dawn.
Do not you worry,
its only weighs about 80 pounds.
Unbelievable.
What will you do with that?
Tough Love.
Muscle like a big Dino last time.
Who is it?
This is Mike. looking for my brother.
Its your hot little sexy,
why don't you invite him in for
a little hospitality?
Where you going, man?
Where the hell are you going?
Cut it! Cut it, Mike!
Next time.
How long you stay?
Not long enough.
Yes.
So What's Jakey doing now a days?
Same old.
Doing land escaping for a salvadorian.
Really?
Yes. Why, would you hear?
Isn't it.
What's your female situation ?
I met this girl
on a bus way out here.
Yes, yes.
Ain't like a bus
for a little love.
Come on man, i am jocking.
What is her name?
Cristina.
Yes, well live it up my man.
Its all gone so fast, Mike. all of it.
- Thanks,babe.
- You're well come honey.
Maria likes to have ass pinch
When she's getin from behing.
I give you the information free of charge.
Yes, thanks.
You know,  Bush adores you to join the army.
Yes, help the war effort.
Shit makes you proud to be
American.
What do your point, Eddie?
My point is there's a war,
going on genius.
You're in the marines,infantry
That means that you're going.
- So, i'll go.
- oh Just like that.
Just like that.
Why do you think I'll be listed?
Shit, I do not know why didn't you enlist?
You know what don't come and tell me.
Shit just break my heart, regardless
what stupid reason you might add in mine.
Look, I signed up because I wanted
to test myself, okay? That's all.
Besides, what else should I suppose
to do around here without college?
mean don't workout too good,
if you're not did?
Do not you worry about me.
I'm all right.
Danny will retire soon.
Probably gonna pay him out.
Danny will be retire since i was 10.
I am not you, ok?
I don't think like you.
I don't act like you. Period.
you kind of look like me,
lucky bastard.
Your mother and I have did pretty,
good things in this department at least.
Shit, your brother, too.
Yes, Aaron was the best then.
Now however, looks like hell.
And do not tell your mother
that you saw him, okay?
Just don't.
She asks too many fucking questions.
All right.
All right, grab the edge carefully.
Take care, is more oil on it.
hey you're not suppose to be here, Eddie.
You give me a private moment
with my son, man?
Yes.
So what you got planning?
Darcy have a little party.
A bunch of barrel
around here kid?that it?
You ain't going to seeing nothing but swinging
dicks, on a partner.
Need to take this Cristina camping
on your last weekend of freedom.
Camping? i don't like camping?
who laugh if you want.
always work for me.
So, where are you headed?
Paris Embassy .
Presidential of detail work?
We hope to ship an assault in San Diego,
you know, to float up to Korea,
or something like that.
Korea.
Yes. Ship Boxer.
I was thinking and to force the recon
after deployment too.
Yes. Eyes and ears, sure, but i don't see that.
Maybe guess you look college in way out there.
Come back as an officer.
Well  you got some good tiddy bars
and Pusan anyway.
They will let you off
that ship, send me a postcard.
All right, "Semper Fi."
You bet.
Can you go to visit my neighbor?
the marine that i told you about?
My Mom told him that and you
are marine
Sure.
Papa this is Mr.Mike
Your paps looked at me
the whole time.
Yes.
It's not a raciast thing.
It's a Latino thing.
You have to prove your self
for a family.
Did not you tell him that i am black, right?
No.
- Guess you want a hint?
- Yes.
Well, this is the second worst birthday
ever
All right, Christmas will be the first.
- So ...
- December 26.
Oh that sucks.
if you like all the send is left over
Like going at dark with reflector shoes
yogurt makers?
Happy birthday,to you.
Yeah, that's not good at all.
Well ...ok. Philosophy of life.
In one sentence or less.
- Pay attention.
- that it?
What?
To everything.
I really like your brain.
Nobody's ever told me
that ain't likes my brain.
Mike. Hey man, what the hell?
Do you abandon your crew like that?
that Shit is not done.
Shaky, my fault. What's New?
Seriously , some Indian tribes
will cut off an ear for that shit.
Or even worse, man.
Come on man, my bad man.
I was taking care of business.
I walked with Cristina.
- I did the right thing to do.
- Yes, yes, yes.
Bus stop girl.
that's right
- Are you're mad at me? Come on, man.
- A little.
I'm going up to store i buy you a beer.
I am still needed
of an identity document in Tijuana.
This is a stupid man.
Do you put the bottom of a fight somewhere,
But you can't buy a beer.
ain't that right shorty?
You mind your own business little girl.
Look at you, man. all googly eyes
and pussy workin shit.
And you called your self a warrior,
mother fucker
We were friends for a long time.
So go ahead man, come on out the closet.
Shut the hell, man.
i am not in closet.
It's good old days, man.
Feel the same way, don't you?
- Yeah, man.
Your thanks for the great nation
of ours and we pray for our military,
God, for men and women
overseas, especially those in Iraq.
know you'll protect them. ..
And thank you all,
for bringing Mike home.
And pray that you move his heart
to be one closer step  with yours.
- Amen.
No, it's my pleasure, sweetie.
Thank you so much for coming.
Bye, Bye.
And i am having little go away party
for Mike,
Sunday after church. Okay?
- All right, bye.
- Come on.
Come on,lets go in house, Trish.
We got cleaning up to do, come on.
Come on, Jacob. Let's do it.
Take you back in those days.
Let your show as I used to do.
Let's beat the ball.
In fact, you know what?
You start from there. i got it.
Free kicks, you start.
- It's the curse day gratitude, man.
- Sorry, sorry.
I like that you have one tonight,baby.
Because Mike is back.
"I want to be like Mike."
Come on, what, what?
What, what, come on.
Shit? Well.
Horrible.
- Because so gonna be. All night!
- All right, fine.
Damn little move and marine.
move marine? ok, even so?
- Yes.
Want to talk about it?
How is your little  landscaping buisness
going ?
Business, Mike?
- Yes, what about it?
- Good.
- Okay?
- Yes.
It's as good as this?
Get off me, man. Let me, come on.
Why play hard and all this shit?
Damn, man. What's happening?
- Fuck you, Mike. Fuck.
- What?
Why you doing this shit?
all time.
- Doing what?
- You know what I'm talking about, Mike.
Why do you play
stupid, man?
Play just only playing a
game of basketball .
Fuck you, Mike.
- So, its just like that?
- Yes, like that.
You don't live here
any more.
So why you gotta come back
and act like a hero all time?
Man, that's bull shit.
judgeing, Mike. Fuck you.
- Thank you for doing this.
- No problem.
jlio , you ask calling Junior, right?
- Yes.
-you know his rank?
Devil dog I was wondering
when you show up, brother.
Check you out, man.
- Hi, Cristina.
- Hi.
- Long time,?
- Yes.
Fucking devil dog, brother!
you want a beer?
Cristina, could you open up the blinds?
Its feeling like in a cave here.
I do not know why.
Shit makes me lazy.
Understand what I mean?
Do you like my shirt?
This is funny brother
Yes, yes, it's funny.
Yes. Army doggy and Landsthul
means to whole world.
But they let us wear them there,
They said that lower the morale
and shit, you know?
Anything that gets you laughing
in to the hospital, right bro?
Come here, brother.
I miss my brothers, man.
Yes.
Come on, marine.
You know we don't do that.
Let's get a beer, man.
And ING, man, you did not trust
those fuckers , brother.
ING? What's that?
Iraqi National Guard.
They are worthlessless, man.
Always watch your back
when these ship birds around.
Yes, but Mike is not going to Iraq.
- What 's your call?
- 0311. riffle.
Shit man, and me too bro.
You're going, man.
Riffle man? Hell, yeah, you're going.
- Where do you get...?
- my leg blowing off?
Yes.
Ramadi.
Rough fucking, Ramadi.
If You find anything minor,with there
you bring back, all right?
i am going, brother.
No doubt.
Man, old lady wants to know
if we can trim grass, man.
I have to admit, its looking
pretty fucking ghetto here.
- You want a beer?
- No, I'm fine.
Pour gas on the asphalt, right?
And fire it up and then dig a hole
while the road is still soft.
Then they bury the bomb and cover up back
with the taar
and detonate when you pass over it, man.
This is a mess.
And we were at Fallujah too.
remember that shit?
It was real fighting, man.
RPG and mortars, IED's,
snipers fires and other shit.
A little of this, little bit of that.
Trying to way your ass down.
punk ass haji's to struggle.
I took my share.
Damn, I did.
I got them, man.
Oh God, I swear this creed.
My riffle,my self that's my country.
We are the masters of the enemy.
We are saviors of my life.
Get me in the shade, man.
Need to rest the hell, man.
I want to play Grand Theft Auto.
You're lucky, man. You're lucky.
- It was so intense.
- Yes.
What a day.
I think you mad
if you have to go over there.
What is happening, Mike?
Only less dizzy.
Have you eaten anything today?
- Want to go eat something?
- Yes.
She's saying that his grandmother is worried
because she doesn't do nothing.
It is possible for him to go back
and get another job with marines?
Not sure. That, with his disability.
I do not know.
- So you leaving on Sunday?
- Yes, sir.
Cristina has going to college.
That's what she really wants to do.
Yes. Yes, sir.
You think this is cool
If you buy you a truck?
Why you just take it.
I mean, why do you ask?
So that's no, right?
whatever.
Read this book to me.
This is a little kid's book
You're too old for that.
I like when you do voices.
Look, I am late. Tomorrow, i promise.
All voices, i promise.
I'll talk to you when I get back.
- Mom, can i borrow your car?
- keys are in my hand bag.
Sit down for a minute.
- So how is Eddie?
- Eddie is Eddie.
At least finally taking an interest, right?
He came to see you.
- Because he wanted something.
- What he want?
- You ever take for camping?
- Yes, I did.
Actually talking sleeping on the ground in the tent.
I hated it. He told you that?
No. Nothing.
You know, he hasn't always been like this, Mike.
Eddie and me.
And good times too you need
to do that
Is never all bad.
I never had to worry about you did i
solid as a rock.
Come here. Let me squeeze you.
- Solid. got like a grown up man feel to you know.
- Sure i do.
- All right, go, go.
- have a good time.
- All right.
- You look great.
- Thank you.
- What do you do on this weekend?
- I hanging out with you.
- I like that.
- Me too.
You know what?
There was going to give you this
untill later, but I brought you something.
No big deal.
There are two diaries. One's for me.
While i am away ,you write
what is happens to you.
I'll write what happens to me
and when I get back, we'll switch.
Thank you.
- You want to go for couple of minutes?
- Yes.
- Let's do it
- yeah.
Somebody ever like got to meet
this is Cristina.
- Miguelito.
- Hi.
My man, Shawn, who get drunk there.
- Darcy, it's target.
- Crazy Goldie, Cristina.
- Hi, nice to meet you.
Are you sure you can handle that talk ?
It's tough.
Yes, I can handle this.
- What the hell with everybody?
- Mushrooms,
you want some.
- No, I'm good. Thanks.
- All right.
Jake escaped from the chain, tonight.
He ate whole quarter alone.
Mike, you're my dog,man.
Always have been my dog, you know?
Listen tomorrow we have fun, ok?
Its going to be me him.
Just you and me, brother. just ...
Mike!
Come and get your girl.
Mike! Mike!
Mike! Mike! its done, man.
You're allright?
Yes.
And you?
I can not believe
that I exit it what happen
I'm sorry.
Why say that?
Some eggs are great, man.
You out?
Eggs! Eggs! Eggs!
Do not give them on foot, not so ...
No, wait.
I got to go home.
You're right.
Plan B backup.
Turn off the lights, man.
Stops up ... do not laugh.
Are you ok?,I feel?
I am sorry about
tonight.
Do not you worry,
about happen.
Hey, let's go camping.
Kinda cold to go camping.
we'll never get out from our sleeping bags.
Good luck with that.
Yes, thanks, good night!
... Its not going to stop ...
Jake,  you're home.
You're wrong.
This is your mom's house,
get your ass out off car.
You got a light all over my face ..mike.
Come on,shake  man what you want to do?
It's late.
I don't live here any more,mike,
take me to my apartment.
Apartment?
Since when have your Apartment?
where you been living?
Can you just drive around for a while
please?
Mike, pull over to mini mart,
pull over right here ,pull in ...
Jake!
What the hell?
Jake, you can't fly,
just a little remind
you watch me doing.
You done a lot dumb shit to your life,
but this beats of them all.
Damn, man ...
If you fall down, i'll keepig your truck.
Fuck you
you're out of your minds, man.
how's the view?
I thought it would be like
the emrald's City.
Well how's it look like?
Fuckin 'Bakersfield.
Feels totally sober all of a sudden.
Hey,Jake?
I'm going to Iraq, man ...
you hear me?
Yeah I heard you
Go to Kuwait on Tuesday
then ... to Iraq.
You know, I can't wish
you hadn't told me that Mike.
And I can't wish you  let me
come? to fuck up here,MIKE.
Why did you let me get up here, Mike?
you let me climb this mother fucker?
This is ridiculous.
- What you want me to do?
- Come up here and get me marine.
- How long?
-  A year at least.
Told anybody else?
- Yes.
- Maybe easiest that way.
You scared?
Crazy thing is this I'm not real
whats up.
Nothing is real.
Life is just a big fucking video game.
Do you think about Cristina?
I think the moment on a bus
I am got a hit that shit.
- I will be gentle.
- Beat your ass.
I really like that girl,man.
"Mike, I'm afraid ..."
You're a dumb fuck.
Yes, dumb fuck too.
Mike, where's my car?
You didn't do something stupid, did you?
I left Darcy's at store
All right,  I am got to need you
to drive me to work.
We take Dale's truck.
Mom!
- up Mike please, .
I am  lucky now.
This gate is never locked.
Enhanced security around here, huh?
It might look like a shit,
but I just got a new TV.
Demn Jake ...
Shit is nasty like
Seen all Cops one times.
I guess this suppose to be the sleeping bag
you let me use at camp.
Why don't you just go to your to your hotel
room like a normal person
Instead of going camping?
what do you got to do , you got to shot a rabbits
for a dinner Do the shit in woods?
Take this money, take it Mike,
take the money get yourself a hotel room.
Don't ask stupid questions.
I ask those questions.
you worried about
I forgot.
What do you do for money ?
Selling cocaine?
You really think that i deal with low
price bull shit,mike?
It does not matter to you.
game the same .
Whatever you doing ,
where do you think it will take you?
I know where the marine core taking you
don't you?.
What do you think shacky Jake
mold on
since the day he dies? Fuck that !
Choose your weapon, private.
Jake, man, just like four tickets to
Pelican Bay.
Well its better than dieing on you feet
than to live on your knees.
No blue west?
and a lolly world name tag.
Let's go shooting
i will show you how to do this shit.
You Iraqi mother fuckers
Take that shit!
Crazy shit jake.
You ain't comming back
to Bako when she leave, right?
What the hell are you talking about
Of course i.
I wouldn't fucking come back.
- Oh mother fucker.
- Jake!
hey, back the fuck up!
Hey ok
you remember me?
You son of a bitch!
What the fuck is wrong
- Fuck you!
Get in the car man
Fuckin peace of shit
You got the wrong neck!
Get in the car
- Let's go!
Fuck you!
That mother fucker wants nothing
He was nothing but on the ground ,
i will pissing himself man.
We Just like Goodfellas
what's up "
Damn!man.
See, you don't even be in marine core
To be a hard core mother fucker.
That was the stupid shit
that you have ever done.
What the fuck you talking about, Mike?
- Pull over,pull the car over!
-I am  not pulling over!
- Pull the fucking car over!
- i am not pulling over, Mike!
We're having fun, Jesus,
Sit back and relax,
watch the fucking good show?
I am not going down with you,
fuck that pull the car over.
What do you think i am got to get pitched
i gonna fucking rat
you know?
Man calm the fuck down,
you don't even been here.
Take me to my car.
Jake,
How is that feel mike ?
People point gun at you
and you don't even know why?
Better get use to it.
You even told me
that you going.
You just went ahead.
we'll pull gun together?
But no, you had to break up the union.
Fucking right.
Go run after your bitch.
Fuck you!
fuck you, Mike.
Hi.
I can hear you pi , Mike.
Marine don't pi , they piss.
Sailors pi and girls.
You know that camp Pendleton
is only couple of inches away from my college?
You can, visit me
on week ends?
- Sounds good.
I do not want to talk about
the future right now.
We can talk about later, later.
It's really a nice hotel.
- I'll be right back.
- Okay.
Thanks.
I should call my parents, right?
Am i, should not right?
Whatever.
Let me see how you do it.
I like this setup.
Pressure ...
We don't have to do this.
Are you sure?
I'm sorry, i am just ...
I want to mean something.
And I want to mean something too.
How come you never tell me
about your ex girlfriends?
- You want to talk about that right now?
- Yes.
I do not want to know about
your old boy friends.
I am trying to get to know you
It was love at first sight?
How long you been together?
How long did it last?
Nothing really it was.
kids stuff ...
I was never been in love before.
How did you really know?
How do I know that I was never
in love before?
Yes.
I mean, way I feel about you,
I never felt that way before.
- I feel like crazy ...
- Like physico?
Like i want to eat the world ...
What?!?
I feel everything so good to you ...
Can we stay here forever
hiding?
Mike
Are you ok
Go to sleep.
Good morning
Hungry?
Sleeping.
Let's have breakfast.
together.
What do you want to eat?
Little cereal you know.
Little cereal in a big bowl.
Can be arranged.
What's the matter, honey?
Whats wrong?
You lied.
I already told you i will really gone
i wouldn't be here right now.
It was just been a nice bus.
ride that's it
That I would want to be.
- You don't mean that.
- i do.
And what you want me to do?
Can not say that you can not go?
- I order, I have to go.
- No.
And what to do just runaway?
And what if they find us,
And they follow me around forever.
This is been a best time in my life.
For real.
That's enough for you now
That's not enough Mike.
I mean are you tired of being told
you have to say few words
I pack my shit and go.
Damn.
Hi, Mike
Want a hot dog, burgers do not know.
No, thanks. My mom is really upset, right?
She's upset. she's really upset.
Jake came by,
told us that you shipping out to Iraq.
- Trish.
- You missed the whole party, dude.
Come on, you know I'm sorry.
Trisha, you helping me to go to your father
please?
Mom.
Why Mike?
I do not understand why didn't you tell us?
I can't lose both my sons.
Why do you've to go?
Why it can't be somebody else,mike?
Why does it have to be my son
Its just the way it is.
Why does it have to be you?
Because I signed up.
Okay?
So I got to be man up,
go over there and do my job.
it got to be somebody, right?
And you tell the truth , i much rather be
over there facing that shit
than the be here
wasting way like everybody else.
Do'nt you telling me that.
Mom.
Those who go over there,
they come back alive
They survive.
I love you very much.
And I am got al pray for you every day.
And i don't want you to worry about
us, ok
Because we got to be strong like you.
And i want you to think about
how proud you've made us.
And i want you to  think about comming home
When your job is done.
Because i can see it now
i can see you comming home.
Telling us stories like you do.
It will be just like you
never even be left.
That's how it got to be.
It will be exactly like that, mom.
You're coming home for christmas ,
is that allright?
Not this year.
I will send you something.
Hey, Dale.
Take care of my Mom.
Its not an easy job.
Seriously.
Good.
Subtitle by Arif chandio
The End