[slow guitar music]
¶ ¶
THAT LOOKS
LIKE A SINGLE PLATOON.
THERE'S NO PICKETS POSTED.
NO PICKETS--
I DON'T LIKE IT.
MAYBE WE JUST
CAUGHT THEM NAPPING, SIR.
EASY PICKINGS FOR A CHANGE.
THE SUN WILL BE UP SOON.
WHICH IS WHY WE SHOULDN'T TAKE
TOO LONG DOING IT OVER, CAPTAIN.
THERE'S NEAR TWO TON OF GOLD
BAR IN THEM THERE CRATES.
THAT'LL KEEP OLD JEFF DAVIS
GOING FOR A YEAR, MAYBE MORE.
IT'S TIME TO GO GET THEM, SIR.
THERE'S ALWAYS TIME
TO GO.
WE'RE ALWAYS ON THE MOVE.
YOU EVER NOTICE THAT, SERGEANT?
NEVER TIME
TO JUST BE WHERE YOU ARE,
TAKE IN THE SCENERY,
ENJOY THE SHOW.
THERE IS A WAR ON, SIR.
YEAH, THERE'S ALWAYS A WAR ON
ONE WAY OR ANOTHER.
YOU PROBABLY HAVEN'T NOTICED
THAT EITHER, HAVE YOU?
JUST OUT OF CURIOSITY,
WHAT'D YOU DO
BEFORE THE WAR, SERGEANT?
I REALLY DON'T REMEMBER, SIR.
OH, FIGURED YOU'D SAY THAT.
JUST THOUGHT I'D CHECK.
[horse snorts, neighs]
[grunts]
NOT INCONVENIENCING YOU,
ARE WE, CORPORAL?
NO, SIR.
JUST ADMIRING THAT MOON.
[sniffs]
IT'S BIG ENOUGH TO REACH OUT
AND TOUCH, ISN'T IT, SIR?
YOU'RE NEW HERE,
AREN'T YOU?
JOINED THE REGIMENT
AT VICKSBURG, SIR.
HMM.
GENTLEMEN, MARK YOUR TARGETS
AND WATCH YOUR ASSES.
S DO THIS.
YA!
[horses neighing]
[gunshot]
[screams]
[gunfire]
IT'S A TRAP!
HEY!
[horses neighing]
WHAT IS THIS?
THIS SUCKS.
WE WAITED TOO LONG.
YEAH, SORRY ABOUT THAT,
OLD FRIEND.
WE'LL GET THEM NEXT TIME.
[horse neighs]
JEAN, STOP THIS CRAP ALREADY.
WAIT.
[sighs]
ALL RIGHT,
WHAT'D I DO WRONG THIS TIME?
(Jean)
THERE WERE SEVERAL PROBLEMS WITH
YOUR ATTACK STRATEGY.
YOU'RE NOT FOOLING
ANYONE, FRANK.
WHAT?
WHO SAID THAT?
I DID.
[clears throat]
WHAT--
YOU'RE NOT FOOLING
ANYONE, FRANK...
LEAST OF ALL YOURSELF.
JEAN, WHAT IS--
[exhales deeply]
JEAN, WHAT
THE HELL JUST HAPPENED?
(Jean)
THE ENEMY FORCES
KNEW YOU WERE COMING.
I KNOW.
HOW?
(Jean)
EVIDENCE POINTS TO A CONFEDERATE
SPY IN YOUR TROOPS.
I UNDERSTAND
THE CORPORAL WAS A SPY.
WHAT I DON'T UNDERSTAND
IS HOW HE WAS ABLE TO CALL ME
BY MY REAL NAME
AND VIOLATE
THE RULES OF THE PROGRAM.
(Jean)
IT'S UNCLEAR, SIR,
BUT I SUSPECT IT'S SOME KIND
OF PROGRAMMING ANOMALY.
I'LL TRY TO ISOLATE
THE PROBLEM.
IS THERE ANYTHING I CAN DO?
JUST GIVE ME MY MESSAGES.
(Jean)
YOU HAVE TWO.
DR. MEYER WOULD LIKE TO SPEAK
WITH YOU,
AND MR. BRAUN WANTED TO KNOW
IF YOU'D HAD A CHANCE TO CATCH
THE RESULTS OF THE GAME.
AND THE RESULTS ARE?
(Jean)
NEW YORK, 27, WASHINGTON, 10.
OH.
WE'VE ALSO BEEN EXPERIENCING
SOME INTERFERENCE
WITH OUR MESSAGE PACKETS.
THE COMM ARRAY AGAIN, RIGHT?
AFRAID SO.
I SUGGEST A REMOTE REALIGNMENT
OF THE TRANSCEIVER ASSEMBLY.
WELL, THANKS FOR THE PERFECTLY
OBVIOUS, JEAN.
(Jean)
ANYTIME, COMMANDER.
[sighs]
(Jean)
I'M SORRY, COMMANDER,
BUT TODAY IS WEDNESDAY.
ON WEDNESDAYS OUR SPONSOR
IS NU-TREC.
RIGHT.
YOU'RE UP EARLY.
AREN'T YOU ON NIGHT SHIFT
THIS WEEK?
COULDN'T SLEEP.
WELL, SINCE YOU'RE UP,
OUR O2 PRODUCTION
AND CO2 ABSORPTION RATES
ARE BOTH DOWN 5%.
YOU'RE IN A GOOD MOOD.
A LOT GONE WRONG
WITH THIS HEAT.
I THINK
THAT WE'RE GONNA BE OKAY.
DO I MISS EARTH?
SURE.
YEAH...
SOMETIMES.
THE GOOD PARTS--
I MISS THE GOOD PARTS.
YOU COULD SAY PLANTS
ARE BETTER ADAPTED
TO SPACE TRAVEL THAN WE ARE.
THEY DON'T NEED SOIL OR ANY
OF THE NUTRIENTS IT PROVIDES.
THEY DON'T CARE IF THEIR LIGHT
COMES FROM THE SUN
OR AN L.E.D. LAMP.
THEY DON'T GET LONELY.
I'LL SEE WHAT'S GOING ON
WITH THE O2.
THE COMM ARRAY'S
OUR BIG WORRY RIGHT NOW,
BUT I'M ALSO FOND OF BREATHING.
DON'T WORRY.
I'LL LOOK INTO IT.
HEY, I LEFT SOME GREENS
OVER THERE.
DO YOU MIND TAKING THEM
TO THE GUYS?
FINE.
[scoffs]
RIKA, WHAT THE HELL?
WHAT?
THEY'RE NOT MINE.
SOMEONE MUST'VE LOST THEM.
SOMEONE, HUH?
[Jah Wobble's Desolation]
¶ ¶
¶ DESOLATION ¶
¶ SEEMS TO BE THE STATE
OF THE NATION ¶
¶ DESOLATION ¶
¶ EVERYONE IN ISOLATION ¶
¶ IS THE WAY IT SEEMS TO BE ¶
¶ TO ME ¶
¶ SPIRITUAL VALLEY ¶
¶ DESOLATION ¶
HEY, COMMANDER.
HEY, HOW'S IT GOING?
ALICE, KENJI.
WE'RE ALMOST FINISHED REALIGNING
THE CONTAINMENT FIELD
OF THE FUSION GENERATOR.
GREAT.
YOU MIGHT WANT TO REVIEW
THE MISSION RULES
ABOUT PICKING UP
AFTER YOURSELVES.
SOMEONE LEFT THIS
IN THE GREENHOUSE LAST NIGHT.
YES, SIR.
ALL YOUR FAULT.
I THINK WE'RE PRETTY LUCKY.
NOTHING LIKE
A TEN-YEAR ADVENTURE
TO ADD A LITTLE ROMANCE,
RIGHT?
ESPECIALLY WITH GO/NO GO
JUST A FEW DAYS AWAY.
I MEAN, IT'S ALL
COME DOWN TO THIS.
ALL THE PLANNING,
ALL THE TRAINING.
ONE LAST CHANCE
TO TAKE THE PLUNGE
OR PULL THE PLUG.
ONE LAST CHANCE
TO MIX OUR METAPHORS.
HEY.
[upbeat quirky music]
¶ ¶
THAT SMELLS GOOD.
COMMANDER.
FRESH FROM RIKA'S GARDEN.
I--I'LL MAKE THE SALAD.
WELL, THAT LOOKS GOOD.
THINK IT NEEDS
A LITTLE SOMETHING?
IT'S A LITTLE SALTY.
MMM.
IT'S A BIT SALTY, YES.
LIKE I TELL YOU--
YES, THE COMMANDER--
A DIRECT ORDER.
YOU KNOW WHAT? NO, NO, NO.
IT NEEDS SALT.
YOU KNOW, GET THIS.
WOULD YOU LIKE A LITTLE SALT
ON YOURS?
HOW ABOUT THAT, HUH?
ENOUGH, ENOUGH, ENOUGH!
ENOUGH WITH THE SALT!
I DON'T KNOW WHY--
YOU'RE NOT THE HEAD CHEF HERE!
WHEN I--WHEN I WAS A KID,
THERE WAS THESE--
WELL, THESE ROCKS
THAT WE USED TO DIVE OFF OF.
ONCE, WE DARED EACH OTHER
TO DO IT AT NIGHT.
YOU COULDN'T EVEN SEE
THE WATER.
YOU JUST HAD TO KEEP TELLING
YOURSELF THAT IT WAS THERE.
LEAP OF FAITH.
YEAH.
FAITH THAT WHAT WE HOPE IS OUT
IS OUT THERE
AND THAT IT CAN TURN THINGS
AROUND FOR ALL OF US.
WHY AM I GOING?
[laughs]
YOU'RE ASKING ME THIS NOW?
I'M--I'M NOT HERE
TO GIVE THE OLD PARTY LINE
TO THE BOOBS BACK HOME.
SORRY.
THAT WOULD BE YOUR PROBLEM.
I HAVE PROBLEMS
OF MY OWN.
DR. J.
EL JEFE!
¿COMO ESTAN LOS NIÑOS?
LISTO PARA HACER
UN GRANDE BOOM!
[scrambled speech]
LISTO PARA HACER UN GRAN--
SO AS WE PREPARE TO SLINGSHOT
AROUND THE...
AS WE PREPARE TO SLINGSHOT
AROUND THE IRIDESCENT PLANET
OF NEPTUNE,
SLINGING--SLINGSHOTTING
AROUND THE...
SURE. I MEAN, SURE,
I'M NERVOUS.
[laughs]
I GET NERVOUS EVERY TIME WE MAKE
A COURSE ADJUSTMENT.
[laughs]
YEAH. AND NOW, WITH GO/NO GO,
I MEAN,
I GUESS WE'RE ALL
A LITTLE FREAKED OUT.
AS PHAETON APPROACHES
OUR FINAL GO/NO GO POINT,
WHERE A SLINGSHOT
AROUND NEPTUNE CAN SEND US HOME
OR LAUNCH US INTO DEEP SPACE
AND THE NEXT PHASE OF OUR
FIVE-YEAR JOURNEY TO ERIDANI,
THE AIR OF TENSION ABOARD
IS PALPABLE.
AND HERE'S THE MAN
WHO WILL ULTIMATELY DECIDE
WHETHER SHIP AND CREW
ARE FIT TO CONTINUE
THIS EXTRAORDINARY MISSION
TO A DISTANT STAR.
IT'S BEEN A TEAM EFFORT SO FAR,
BUT NOW GO/NO GO
RESTS SQUARELY
ON HIS SHOULDERS.
FRANK...
UH, COMMANDER.
WELL, WE COULD REALLY USE SOME
MORE INTERVIEW FOOTAGE OF YOU.
YOU KNOW, THE LAST ONE DIDN'T
GO QUITE LIKE WE HAD--
ROGER,
IS IT TRUE YOU GET 10%
OF EVERY DOWNLOAD
AND WEB STREAM BACK ON EARTH?
THAT ACCUSATION
IS A DIRECT INSULT TO MY AGENT,
WHO WOULD NEVER ACCEPT
LESS THAN 20, FRANK.
WELL, I HOPE HE ALSO GOT YOU
A CUT OF SPONSORS LIKE NU-TREC--
THE FINEST NAME
IN UNCOMFORTABLE, ILL-FITTING,
POLYESTER GARMENTS
IN THE GALAXY.
IT IT'S SCRATCHY,
IT MUST BE NU-TREC.
OH, VERY NICE.
I'LL MAKE A NOTE TO DEAL
WITH PASSIVE AGGRESSION
AT OUR NEXT SESSION.
I SEE EVERYTHING THAT HAPPENS
ON THIS SHIP.
THIS WHOLE CONFESSIONAL
WAS DESIGNED BY ME.
IT WAS DESIGNED
TO BE UNCOMFORTABLE.
IT WAS DESIGNED TO MAKE PEOPLE
FEEL UNCOMFORTABLE
IN THE HOPE
THAT THEY WOULD BE MORE REAL.
OKAY, LET HIM GO, BILLIE.
JUST HEAD UP TO THE CORE.
HE'S THE WORST INTERVIEW.
IT'S OKAY.
JUST LET HIM GO, BILLIE.
WE HAVE ENOUGH.
(Jean)
PREVIOUSLY ON PHAETON TV...
SIX MONTHS AGO,
THE RESEARCH VESSEL PHAETON
WAS LAUNCHED
ON AN EXTRAORDINARY MISSION
TO THE DISTANT STAR
EPSILON ERIDANI
IN THE SEARCH FOR INTELLIGENT
LIFE IN ANOTHER SOLAR SYSTEM.
BUT ONLY A FEW MONTHS
INTO THE JOURNEY,
SCIENTISTS HAVE MADE
A SHOCKING DISCOVERY--
THAT EARTH WILL BECOME
UNINHABITABLE WITHIN A CENTURY.
NOW THIS MISSION OF EXPLORATION
HAS BECOME A MISSION
OF SALVATION.
WITH THE HOPES OF BILLIONS
RIDING ON THEIR SHOULDERS,
12 BRAVE ASTRONAUTS NOW APPROACH
THE MOST CRITICAL DECISION
OF THEIR LIVES--
GO OR NO GO,
LEAVE THE SOLAR SYSTEM
AND JOURNEY FOR TEN YEARS
OR TURN AROUND AND COME HOME.
THE STAKES ARE ENORMOUS.
THE DRAMA INTENSE.
AND YOU'RE ALONG
FOR EVERY STEP OF THE WAY.
EDGE OF NEVER, PHAETON TV,
ONLY ON FOX.
ONCE WE PASSED NO/NO GO,
THAT'S WHEN WE ENGAGED THE
ORION DRIVE FOR THE FIRST TIME.
UH, IT'S THE FIRST LARGE-SCALE
APPLICATION OF THIS TECHNOLOGY,
WITHOUT WHICH PHAETON
WOULD NEVER BE CAPABLE
OF THE NEAR-LIGHT SPEEDS
THAT WILL LET US REACH
ANOTHER STAR SYSTEM
IN A MATTER OF YEARS
INSTEAD OF LIFETIMES.
I GREW UP
IN A FAMILY OF LIARS.
AND I HATE NOTHING WORSE
THAN BEING LIED TO.
THE PHYSICS BEHIND IT ARE
ACTUALLY QUITE REVOLUTIONARY.
THAT'S GREAT, JULES.
EXACTLY WHAT I NEEDED.
THANK YOU.
OH, LOOK WHO OWES ME MONEY.
A BLOCKED FIELD GOAL AND
A BAD PASS INTERFERENCE CALL.
THAT'S WHAT YOU CALL
DUMB LUCK.
UH, NO.
THAT'S WHAT I CALL TOUGH D,
A GOOD REFEREE, AND 5 Gs
YOU OWE ME, BRUDDAH-BRUDDAH.
I'LL MAKE IT BACK
IN BASEBALL SEASON
IF WE'RE STILL OUT HERE.
OH, UH, WELL, SHE WAS UP
ALL NIGHT,
CHECKING THE ACCELERATION GRIDS
FOR EROSION.
CUT HER SOME SLACK.
SAID SHE DESERVED TO GET WET.
SURFING. YEAH.
IT'S HER NEW THING.
NOT ENOUGH LIGHT THERE,
SHE'S NOT.
WAKE HER UP.
[beeps]
SUE.
I DON'T NECESSARILY
FEEL COMFORTABLE
TALKING ABOUT MY FEELINGS.
I KNOW MY PLACE,
AND I UNDERSTAND
THAT I AM JUST ONE PIECE
OF A GREATER THING,
BUT I AM A REALLY
IMPORTANT PIECE.
DOC?
MEYER?
YOU HOME?
JEAN, CAN YOU LOCATE
THE DOCTOR?
(Jean)
DR. MEYER IS IN AIRLOCK C.
OKAY, JEAN, TELL ME
I'M WRONG ABOUT THIS.
(Jean)
I'M SORRY, DOCTOR,
BUT I ESTIMATE A 6.3% DECREASE
IN DOPAMINE ACTIVITY
IN THE BASAL GANGLIA,
ALONG WITH AN INCREASE
IN TRANSITION METALS
IN THE SUBSTANTIA NIGRA.
IS THERE ANYTHING ELSE
I CAN HELP YOU WITH?
NO, JEAN.
THAT'S ALL.
[beep]
ALL DOCTORS REALLY WORK
UNDER PRESSURE,
EH, BECAUSE AS A DOCTOR,
YOU HAVE TO RESPOND
TO EMERGENCIES ALL THE TIME,
AND WE'RE TRAINED
TO DO SO.
HEY, DOC.
YOU WANTED TO SEE ME?
YES.
UM, THERE'S SOMETHING
I NEED TO TELL YOU.
THIS CAN'T BE GOOD.
[scoffs]
AFRAID NOT.
[sighs]
ALL RIGHT, TELL ME.
A MEMBER OF THE CREW IS ILL.
HOW ILL?
BAD ENOUGH TO SEND US HOME.
WHO?
ME.
[camera whirring]
[rock music]
[singing in foreign language]
¶ ¶
SIS, I HOPE YOU KNOW HOW PROUD
WE ALL ARE OF YOU,
BOLDLY GOING WHERE NO GIRL
FROM THE LOWER NINTH WARD
HAS GONE BEFORE.
LITTLE HENRY HERE WILL BE IN HIS
TEENS BY THE TIME YOU GET BACK,
SO HE'LL THANK HIS BIG,
BRAVE AUNT IN PERSON.
[Henry crying]
I BETTER GET GOING
BEFORE I START BAWLING TOO.
BYE, SIS. LOVE YOU.
[beep]
DO YOU AND KENJI EVER TALK
ABOUT HAVING KIDS?
YEAH.
AND?
AND, I MEAN,
YOU KNOW--
YOU KNOW THE RULES.
WE COULDN'T BE ON THE MISSION
IF WE HAD KIDS,
SO WE DECIDED THAT THE MISSION
WAS MORE IMPORTANT.
ALICE, BABY, COME ON.
WE'RE ON A SHIP.
WE'RE GONNA BE HERE
FOR 9 1/2 YEARS.
I'M SURE THAT IF YOU WANTED
TO GET PREGNANT,
YOU COULD DO
WHATEVER YOU WANTED.
WHO WOULD WANT TO RAISE A CHILD
IN A METAL TUBE?
I MEAN, HAVE THIS BE
THE ONLY WORLD THEY KNOW?
[beep]
[sighs]
[beeps]
EIGHT WEEKS?
I'M SORRY?
OH, YOU'RE JUST STARTING
TO SHOW,
SO I'M GUESSING.
EIGHT WEEKS?
UH, YES. EIGHT.
OH, YOU WON'T FEEL
ANYTHING YET, HON.
BUT THEY WILL BE ABLE
TO SHOW YOU THE HEARTBEAT,
AND THAT'S WHEN
IT REALLY HITS YOU.
TRUST ME.
WOW.
IS THIS YOUR FIRST?
YES.
WOW.
[door opens]
MRS. THIBADEAU,
IT'S GOOD TO SEE YOU AGAIN.
DR. FALLON,
YOU WANTED TO SEE ME?
BILLIE, GOOD.
COME IN. SIT DOWN.
I, UH, FINISHED A ROUGH CUT
OF YESTERDAY'S SHOOT,
AND I THINK
YOU SHOULD SEE THIS.
AS PHAETON APPROACHES
OUR FINAL GO/NO GO POINT
WHERE A SLINGSHOT AROUND NEPTUNE
CAN SEND US HOME...
OH, GOD.
OR LAUNCH US INTO DEEP SPACE
AND THE NEXT PHASE OF OUR
FIVE-YEAR JOURNEY TO ERIDANI,
THE AIR OF TENSION ABOARD
IS PALPABLE.
THAT'S TERRIBLE.
BILLIE, YOU'RE A NATURAL.
AND IT'S NOT JUST ME
THAT THINKS SO.
FIVE BILLION VIEWERS
CAN'T BE WRONG.
WHAT?
FIVE BILLION.
[chuckles]
THAT'S THE BEST RATINGS
WE'VE HAD
SINCE THE LAUNCH,
AND IT'S WAY BETTER THAN
ANYTHING I GOT WHEN I WAS HOST.
WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
I'VE BEEN TALKING
TO THE CONSORTIUM,
AND WE'RE ALL IN AGREEMENT.
I'M STILL GONNA PRODUCE
THE SHOW,
BUT FROM NOW ON, YOU'RE GONNA BE
THE VOICE OF PHAETON.
YOU'VE GOT
TO BE KIDDING, RIGHT?
YOU'VE GOT SOMETHING
THAT JUST CAN'T BE BOUGHT.
PEOPLE RELATE TO YOU.
I DON'T THINK
THIS IS A GOOD IDEA.
LOOK AT IT LIKE THIS--
YOU'RE DOING ME A FAVOR.
I'M A SHRINK. I WAS NEVER
ANY GOOD AT ANY OF THIS.
AS THE REALITIES
OF THIS MISSION SINK IN,
I'M GONNA BE GETTING A LOT
MORE PATIENTS THROUGH MY DOOR.
DR. FALLON,
I DON'T KNOW WHAT TO SAY.
WELL, SAY YES.
[sighs]
YES.
[laughing]
SAY YES.
(Jean)
EXCUSE ME, DR. FALLON.
MANNY AND VAL
WOULD LIKE TO SPEAK WITH YOU.
OH, THIS'LL BE FUN.
CONGRATULATIONS, BILLIE.
I'M REALLY PROUD OF YOU.
(Jean)
IT'S TWO DAYS AND COUNTING
UNTIL THE PHAETON
REACHES NEPTUNE,
AND IT'S THE DECISION
WE'VE ALL BEEN WAITING FOR--
GO OR NO GO.
AND WHILE LIFE IS SWEET
FOR KENJI AND ALICE,
THINGS ARE STILL SALTY
FOR VAL AND MANNY.
ARE THERE JUST TOO MANY COOKS
IN THIS KITCHEN?
PHAETON TV, THE EDGE OF NEVER.
WEDNESDAYS AT 10:00
ONLY ON FOX.
I DON'T WANT ANY MORE FOOTAGE
OF US ARGUING
ENDING UP ON THE SHOW.
LOOK, I AM CONSTANTLY GETTING
NOTES FROM OUR NETWORK PARTNERS
ASKING FOR MORE CONFLICT
IN THE SERIES.
YOU'RE CONSTANTLY MAKING US
INTO BITCHY KINGS.
QUEENS.
BITCHY QUEENS.
GUYS, MAYBE THINGS
WOULD BE DIFFERENT
IF THE PUBLIC KNEW
WHAT WE KNOW,
BUT THAT'S NOT THE CASE.
I DIDN'T SIGN UP FOR THIS.
I DIDN'T SIGN UP
TO BE AN INTERSTELLAR
PUNCH LINE, ALL RIGHT?
WELL...
[sighs]
LOOK, THINGS ARE MUCH WORSE
THAN THE PUBLIC KNOWS BACK HOME.
DRY LAND IS BECOMING
AN INCREASINGLY
EXPENSIVE COMMODITY.
THE SECURITY COUNCIL
IS CONSIDERING RELOCATION VISAS
FOR ANYONE WANTING TO MOVE
FROM THE COASTAL REGIONS INLAND.
IT IS THAT BAD?
IT WILL BE.
GETTING ON ONE
OF THESE VISA LISTS
IS GONNA BE
INCREDIBLY IMPORTANT.
[laughs]
I DON'T KNOW
WHY YOU'RE LAUGHING.
I-I HAVE FAMILY IN LONDON,
AND YOU HAVE FAMILY
IN--IN FLORIDA, RIGHT?
WHAT ARE YOU SAYING?
IF I DON'T COOPERATE, THEN
MY FAMILY DOESN'T GET A VISA?
THE CONSORTIUM
IS A VERY POWERFUL COMPANY.
THEY'RE GONNA BE WILLING TO HELP
PEOPLE WHO HELP THEM
TO MAKE MONEY.
NOW, I-I KNOW YOU GUYS
ARE TRYING TO PAINT ME
AS THE VILLAIN HERE,
BUT REALLY,
I'M JUST TRYING TO HELP YOU.
WE'LL DO IT.
YOUR FAMILY WILL NEED HELP.
I DO LOVE YOU, YOU KNOW.
YOU SHOULD.
(Jean)
ATTENTION, ALL CREW.
PLEASE REPORT IMMEDIATELY
TO THE BRIEFING ROOM.
SO ANY QUESTIONS?
YEAH, I HAVE QUESTIONS.
HOW LONG HAVE YOU KNOWN
ABOUT THIS,
AND WHY ARE THE REST OF US
JUST HEARING ABOUT IT NOW?
THAT'S REALLY NOT THE ISSUE.
WITH ALL DUE RESPECT, SIR,
THE HELL IT ISN'T.
WOULD YOU GET THAT THING
OUT OF MY FACE?
I'M JUST DOING MY JOB.
DID SOMEONE GIVE YOU
A JOB TO DO?
LET'S JUST TRY AND ABSORB
ALL OF THE INFORMATION
BEFORE WE MAKE ACCUSATIONS,
SHALL WE?
I'M SORRY, ROGER, BUT IT'S
A QUESTION, NOT AN ACCUSATION.
AND HERE'S YOUR ANSWER.
DOCTOR CAME TO ME YESTERDAY
WITH HIS PRELIMINARY DIAGNOSIS.
I ASKED HIM TO TAKE
SOME MORE TIME TO CONFIRM IT.
HE DID,
AND NOW YOU'RE BEING BRIEFED.
PARKINSON'S?
IS IT FATAL?
NO.
BUT IT CAN LEAD TO SOME
PRETTY SERIOUS COMPLICATIONS.
NOW, SO FAR,
I'VE ONLY EXPERIENCED
A FEW SYMPTOMS
AND ONLY INTERMITTENTLY--
SOME HAND TREMORS,
UH, CRAMPED HANDWRITING.
WHAT COMES NEXT?
DO YOU START DROOLING?
WELL, THE SYMPTOMS
AND THEIR RATE
OF PROGRESSION VARIES
BY INDIVIDUAL.
BUT COMMONLY,
WE SEE PROBLEMS WITH BALANCE,
UH, MOBILITY,
LATER WITH SPEECH
AND SWALLOWING,
UH, FATIGUE.
BILLIE, I AM NOT KIDDING.
I WILL ANNIHILATE YOU.
I'M JUST DOING MY JOB.
JUST TURN IT OFF!
[overlapping shouting]
OKAY, CALM DOWN, SUE.
PUT IT AWAY!
LET'S TURN IT OFF, BILLIE.
LET'S JUST ALL TRY
AND STAY FOCUSED.
SHALL I CONTINUE?
PLEASE.
UH, PROBLEMS
WITH SHORT-TERM MEMORY LOSS
AND DEMENTIA,
INCLUDING HALLUCINATIONS
AND PARANOIA,
ARE POSSIBLE
LATE-TERM DEVELOPMENTS.
ALL RIGHT, THIS CAN BE TREATED
WITH MEDICATION, RIGHT?
SO THE ONLY
RELEVANT QUESTION HERE IS,
"DO WE HAVE THE MEDICATIONS?"
YES...
WELL, TO VARYING DEGREES.
AND, YES,
BUT ONLY IN LIMITED SUPPLIES.
WE DIDN'T PLAN
FOR SOMETHING LIKE THIS.
OKAY.
WELL, WE WERE COMING UP
ON THE GO/NO GO
DECISION POINT ANYWAY.
ALL THIS MEANS
IS THAT WE'RE FACING IT
A LITTLE SOONER
THAN WE ANTICIPATED.
I SAY GO.
DEMENTIA,
HALLUCINATIONS, PARANOIA--
ARE WE ALL GETTING A VOTE?
[overlapping shouting]
KIDS!
NO ONE'S VOTING.
THIS ISN'T A DEMOCRACY.
I'LL MAKE THE FINAL DECISION
AFTER HEARING THE DOCTOR'S
PERSONAL AND MEDICAL ASSESSMENT.
NOR IS ANYONE ELSE GONNA BE
BRIEFING MISSION CONTROL
OR THE CONSORTIUM
ABOUT THIS SITUATION.
YOU GOT THAT, ROGER?
AND BY THE WAY,
THIS ISN'T THE ONLY SAFETY ISSUE
WE'RE FACING RIGHT NOW.
JEAN'S GOT A LIST
AS LONG AS MY ARM,
ANY ONE OF WHICH
CAN SCREW UP THIS MISSION.
SO IF YOU WANT TO BE PRODUCTIVE,
START DEALING WITH THEM.
I'M JUST PLAYING A ROLE.
WE ALL PLAY ROLES ALL THE TIME.
WE BECOME MORE...
DEEPLY ENTRENCHED IN THEM
IN MOMENTS OF CRISIS.
I THINK, FROM AN AUDIENCE
PERSPECTIVE, IT'S VERY EXCITING.
I THINK IT'S AS REAL
AS IT COULD POSSIBLY BE,
AND...
IT MAKES VERY GOOD TELEVISION.
IT'S ALWAYS
SO DAMN RESTFUL HERE.
MM, NOT ALWAYS.
OH, THERE ARE STORMS
SOMETIMES.
THE LAST ONE ALMOST TOOK OUT
THE SUPPORTS UNDER THIS BALCONY.
I'M IN THE MOOD
FOR A STORM RIGHT ABOUT NOW.
THAT COULD BE ARRANGED.
TALK TO ME.
YOU JUST GONNA USE
THIS MEYER THING
AS AN EXCUSE
TO DUMP THE WHOLE MISSION?
EXCUSE?
I'M NOT SAYING
THAT WE'VE NOT HAD
AN IMPRESSIVE ARRAY OF SETBACKS,
BUT IT ALMOST SEEMS
AS THOUGH YOU'VE BEEN LOOKING
FOR A REASON TO ABORT.
IF WE'RE GONNA GO FORWARD
WITH THIS THING,
WE'VE GOT TO BE REALISTIC
ABOUT THE PROBLEMS WE'RE FACING.
I MEAN, COME ON.
MEYER HAS GOT PARKINSON'S.
YEAH, I WAS AT THE BRIEFING.
WHAT'S GOING ON...
REALLY?
IT'S NOT THE--
THE FACTS OF WHAT THEY TOLD US,
SO MUCH...
IT'S THE TIMING.
I MEAN,
ENVIRONMENTAL DISASTER, OKAY?
HOW LONG HAVE WE BEEN WAITING
FOR THAT SHOE TO DROP?
BUT FOR IT TO GO
SO WRONG SO FAST,
IT'S A LOT TO SWALLOW.
AND THE CLOSER
WE GET TO GO/NO GO,
THE TOUGHER IT GETS.
YOU'RE IMPLYING
THAT THEY'RE LYING TO US.
THIS IS A $200-BILLION PROJECT.
YEAH.
THEY'RE NOT GONNA START
PLAYING GAMES.
MAYBE IT'S SOME KIND OF TEST.
[chuckles]
OF WHAT?
OF ME.
I'VE BEEN GETTING THIS FEELING
FOR A WHILE NOW
THAT MISSION CONTROL
DOESN'T EXACTLY HAVE
THE GREATEST FAITH
IN THEIR COMMANDER.
COME ON.
IT'S NOT SAID OUT LOUD
ON AN OPEN CHANNEL.
BUT READING BETWEEN THE LINES,
I'M NOT SO SURE THEY WOULDN'T
RATHER SEE SOMEONE ELSE
IN COMMAND UP HERE.
HEY...
LOOK ME IN THE EYE AND TELL ME
THAT YOU BELIEVE THAT.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT I BELIEVE.
MAYBE YOU'RE RIGHT.
MAYBE I'M OVER-THINKING THIS.
YEAH.
BUT I--
I'VE GOT THIS FEELING
IN MY GUT.
IT JUST DOESN'T ADD UP.
I KNOW THERE'S SOMETHING
THEY'RE NOT TELLING US.
I--I KNOW THAT--
OH.
I'M SORRY.
DO--DO GO ON.
YOU SHOULD COME
TO MY PLACE SOME TIME.
YOU'D LIKE IT--
OPEN AIR, INTERESTING PEOPLE.
YEAH, YOU KNOW WHAT, FRANK?
I'M BORED.
COME AND PLAY WITH ME.
[mellow music]
¶ ¶
[breathing heavily]
[ringing]
YOU GOT TO BE KIDDING ME.
WHO'S CALLING YOU HERE?
I DIDN'T PROGRAM IT.
[breathing heavily]
[ringing continues]
ARE YOU GONNA ANSWER IT?
HELLO?
(man on phone)
I'M VERY DISAPPOINTED
IN YOU, RIKA.
WHAT?
WHO IS THIS?
YOU'RE BEHAVING VERY BADLY.
YOU KNOW THAT.
WHO IS IT?
I DON'T KNOW.
I CA--
I DON'T UNDERSTAND.
I SAID,
"YOU'RE BEHAVING VERY BADLY."
BOTH OF YOU.
WHAT THE HELL?
CAPTAIN.
WHAT'S HE DOING HERE?
WAIT A MINUTE.
HE'S FROM MY MODULE.
YOU BROUGHT HIM OVER HERE?
I DON'T EVEN KNOW
HOW TO DO THAT.
NO ONE BROUGHT ME
OVER HERE, FRANK.
I AM HERE,
AND I TOLD YOU BEFORE...
YOU'RE NOT FOOLING ANYONE.
[gasps]
[scream]
UGH!
[breathing heavily]
[gasps, breathing heavily]
HEY, BABY, BABY,
IT'S OKAY.
SHH, IT'S OKAY.
DON'T WORRY.
HEY, COME ON, LIE DOWN.
SHH.
IT'S OKAY.
I CAN'T IMAGINE THE SCENARIO
IN WHICH MY WIFE
WOULDN'T BE HERE WITH ME.
AND YES, IT GIVES ME
SOME COMFORT.
[sniffs]
ARE WE GOING, FRANK?
WHAT?
SORRY.
I HAVEN'T MADE A DECISION.
YOU'LL BE THE FIRST, OKAY?
REALLY?
YEAH.
PROMISE?
OKAY.
IT'S JUST THE THING IS, FRANK,
IF SOMETHING
WERE TO HAPPEN TO YOU--
[mumbling]
HIT BY A BUS--
[chuckling]
IF SOMETHING
WERE TO HAPPEN TO YOU,
I'M THE ONE
THAT HAS TO PICK UP THE BAG,
AND I REALLY SHOULD KNOW
WHERE THE BAG IS.
JIMMY.
I JUST TOLD YOU
I HAVEN'T DECIDED YET.
I'LL LET YOU KNOW, OKAY?
OKAY, ALL RIGHT.
YEAH.
I'LL GO, THEN.
I SHALL BE TENDING
TO THE CHILDREN,
IF YOU CHANGE YOUR MIND.
HURRAH.
HERE'S A RARE MOMENT
OF TRUTHFULNESS.
I...
RESPECT THE MAN GREATLY.
I WISH HE RESPECTED ME
AS MUCH...
AS I DO HIM.
BIOLOGICAL PROTECTION
IN THE ROOT ZONE.
I MEAN, I THINK I CAN FIX IT
BY INTRODUCING
SOME PROTECTIVE MICROBES
INTO THE SOLUTION.
GOOD.
LAST THING WE NEED IS A THREAT
TO OUR FRESH FOOD AND OXYGEN.
WELL, EXACTLY.
UM, I MEAN, LET ME SHOW YOU
SOME OF THESE TEST SLIDES
I'VE BEEN WORKING ON.
WHAT EXACTLY HAPPENED
LAST NIGHT?
I HAVE NO IDEA.
I DIDN'T THINK ANY OF US COULD
GET INTO SOMEONE ELSE'S MODULE
WITHOUT AN INVITATION
AND AN ACCESS CODE.
AND I GATHER YOU DIDN'T EXTEND
MY INVITATION
TO YOUR LITTLE FRIEND.
SO HE COULD EXECUTE US
IN THE SACK?
I'M NOT THAT KINKY.
YOU HAVE YOUR MOMENTS.
YOU KNOW,
IT'S EXACTLY THE KIND OF STUNT
ROGER WOULD PULL IF HE KNEW
I WAS CHEATING ON HIM.
NO ONE'S CHEATING
ON ANYONE HERE.
THIS IS ALL
JUST SOME HARMLESS FANTASY.
REALLY?
THEN YOU WOULDN'T MIND
IF I TOLD MY HUSBAND,
WOULD YOU?
OKAY, FINE.
HE'S NOT A SOFTWARE EXPERT
EITHER; HE'S JUST A THERAPIST.
DOESN'T HAVE THE SKILLS
TO PULL OFF SOMETHING LIKE THIS.
WELL, THEN SOMEONE ELSE
IS SCREWING WITH US.
RIGHT.
(Jean)
TONIGHT ON PHAETON TV,
THE EDGE OF NEVER...
IT'S ALL COME DOWN TO THIS.
IT'S TIME
FOR THE COMMANDER'S DECISION.
THE WHOLE REASON FOR GOING ON
IS THAT WE BELIEVE
THAT WE CAN BE SUCCESSFUL.
AND IF I BELIEVE THAT
WE CAN BE SUCCESSFUL,
WE WILL GO ON.
(Jean)
THE PHAETON CREW GRAPPLES
WITH THE CHOICE
THAT WILL CHANGE THEIR LIVES
FOREVER AND OURS TOO.
GO/NO GO.
TO GO OR NO GO.
GO.
(Jean)
IT'S THE ONLY SHOW
YOU CAN'T MISS.
ABSOLUTELY, THERE IS A RISK THAT
WE WILL GO BACK.
(Jean)
PHAETON TV PRESENTED
COMMERCIAL-FREE, ONLY ON FOX.
[beeping]
BEGIN RECORDING.
DEAR SHAWN,
WELL, A LOT'S HAPPENED
SINCE MY LAST LETTER.
WE'VE, UH--
WE'VE HAD SOME BAD NEWS.
THE SHIP'S DOCTOR IS ILL,
AND IT COULD THREATEN
THE MISSION.
YEAH, WE ALL WORKED SO HARD
FOR THIS.
WE, UH, COMPETED SO HARD
TO BE A PART OF IT,
YOU'D THINK THAT'D BE THE ONLY
THING ON OUR MINDS RIGHT NOW.
BUT, UH...
WELL, SIX MONTHS
IN A METAL TUBE
CAN MAKE YOU LOSE TRACK
OF YOUR PRIORITIES.
Y-YOU START TO FOCUS
ON OTHER THINGS...
THINGS THAT JUST
MAKE YOU CRAZIER.
[beep]
TWEETY BURGER--WHAT A TREAT.
MUCH MORE MEAT THAN YOU CAN...
[microwave beeps]
EAT!
COME ON, DR. J, WHY ARE YOU
EATING THAT CRAP AGAIN?
I MADE A NICE CARBONARA.
ONCE BITTEN, MANNY,
ONCE BITTEN.
WELL, LET ME--
LET ME DO SOMETHING TO IT.
LET ME PUT, LIKE,
A LITTLE SALT IN THERE.
YOU WANT A LITTLE SALT,
JUST LIKE A TOUCH?
JUST A LITTLE BIT?
THIS GUY PADDLES
INTO THE LINEUP.
WAVES LIKE I'M HIS BUD.
HE DROPS IN ON ME.
NEXT THING I KNOW--
DROPS IN ON YOU?
WHAT IS THAT?
IT MEANS HE CUT ME OFF
ON A WAVE.
OKAY.
NEXT THING I KNOW,
I'M STUCK IN WATER WHILE
I GET DRILLED INTO THE REEF.
BY THE TIME
I MANAGED TO RIP OFF MY HEADSET,
IT FELT LIKE
I REALLY BOUGHT IT.
YOU SHOULD RESET THE PARAMETERS
TO NO GENERATE AND--
TO NO GENERATE--
YOU THINK
I DIDN'T THINK OF THAT?
I PROGRAMMED IT
FOR A MELLOW BREAK, OKAY?
MELLOW, PEACEFUL.
SOMEONE HACKED MY MODULE.
YOU'RE LOOKING AT ME?
YOU'RE THE COMPUTER GENIUS.
I DIDN'T TOUCH YOUR MODULE.
REALLY?
YOU DIDN'T THINK THAT MAYBE
PROGRAMMING A LITTLE DANGER
MIGHT MAKE FOR A BETTER SHOW
NOW THAT YOU'RE THE NEW HOST?
[scoffs]
WHAT, YOU THINK...
I'D USE YOUR PERSONAL MODULE
JUST TO GET RATINGS?
I WOULDN'T PUT IT PAST YOU.
OH.
SUE.
WHAT?
LOOK, I'M SORRY,
BUT I KNOW A COMPUTER HACK
WHEN I SEE ONE.
AND THAT FREAK
WAS HACK A MILE AWAY.
THAT DOESN'T MEAN BILLIE
HAD ANYTHING TO DO WITH IT.
OH, GOD, ALICE, JUST SHUT UP!
YOU ALWAYS BUTT INTO THINGS THAT
HAVE NOTHING TO DO WITH YOU.
KENJI, CAN YOU DO SOMETHING
ABOUT YOUR WIFE?
DON'T BRING ME INTO THIS.
SHE'S DOING IT AGAIN.
NO, I THINK A CATFIGHT
IS GONNA HAPPEN.
OH, NO.
BABE.
SORRY ABOUT THAT.
THANK YOU.
[laughter]
I DIDN'T WANT TO EAT THIS.
HERE, HERE, HAVE MINE.
SEE YOU AT BREAKFAST.
YEAH, I WILL.
SO, SUE, ARE YOU
COMPLETELY PSYCHOTIC
OR ONLY WHEN IT COMES
TO OTHER WOMEN?
I DON'T REALLY LIKE WOMEN
THAT MUCH.
[laughing]
SO, UM--
NEITHER DO I.
THAT'S WHY WE GET ALONG
SO WELL.
[footsteps]
HEY.
WHERE HAVE YOU BEEN? I'VE
BEEN LOOKING ALL OVER FOR YOU.
I'M OKAY.
ARE YOU SURE?
YEAH, I'M SURE.
I JUST NEEDED TO LEAVE
BEFORE I KNOCKED HER OUT.
SHE'S GOT ONE MORE TIME
TO TALK TO ME LIKE THAT.
HEY, OKAY, OKAY, OKAY, STOP.
OKAY, STOP. OKAY, STOP.
N-NO, NO, NO.
BREATHE, BREATHE.
BREATHE.
YOU WERE THERE.
STOP.
[exhales]
IS THERE ANYTHING I CAN DO?
YEAH. ME, THE CORE,
TONIGHT.
[playful growl and bite]
[slap]
[laughs]
OW.
YOU THINK, UH, PIKE'S
REALLY GONNA TURN US AROUND?
IF THERE'S ANY DOUBT,
I'M WILLING TO TAKE ODDS.
THE SKIPPER
KNOWS WHAT HE'S DOING.
AND IF HE THINKS THIS PROBLEM
IS TOO BIG, WHAT DO YOU WANT?
OH, GOD.
YOU PEOPLE
SEEM TO BE FORGETTING
THAT THERE'S A SOMEWHAT
BIGGER PROBLEM BACK AT HOME.
SO IF WE HAVE TO LIVE
WITH A LITTLE RISK,
I'D SAY THAT CAME WITH
THE TERRITORY, WOULDN'T YOU?
YEAH, MAYBE THERE'S BIGGER
PROBLEMS BACK HOME.
ALL RIGHT, BRAUN,
WHAT--WHAT IS THAT?
I WORK MISSION CONTROL.
THEY'RE NOT ABOVE LYING
TO THE CREW,
YOU KNOW, FOR OUR OWN SAFETY.
DOES IT MEAN THE COMPANY MAN'S
GETTING A TOUCH PARANOID?
MAKE FUN OF ME IF YOU WANT,
BUT IT'S MAKING ME NERVOUS.
YEAH, WELL, BRAUN,
IF YOU'RE NERVOUS,
GO TO THE COMMANDER
AND GET A REASSURING CUDDLE.
YOU'VE EXPERIENCED THIS?
YOU KNOW WHAT, JIMMY?
IT'S VERY EASY
TO PLAY ARMCHAIR GENERAL.
ARMCHAIR WHAT?
HE DIDN'T MEAN THAT.
YOU HEARD ME.
TELL HIM YOU DIDN'T MEAN THAT.
SHUT UP, JULES.
I MEANT IT.
[laughing]
[slow jazz music]
¶ ¶
JEAN, IDENTIFY THE HUMAN FIGURE
IN MY LANDSCAPE.
(Jean)
I'M SORRY, DR. MEYER, BUT THERE
IS NO OTHER HUMAN FIGURE.
[chuckles]
THAT'S RIDICULOUS.
I'M LOOKING--
NEVER MIND.
MY MISTAKE.
MUST BE SEEING THINGS.
[footsteps]
[breathing heavily]
[beeps]
THAT'S THE AURELIAN DRIVE,
RIGHT?
YEAH, ALMOST.
IT'S ORION.
IT'S NAMED AFTER
THE FIRST DESIGN FOR A SPACESHIP
WITH NUCLEAR-PULSE PROPULSION
ALMOST A CENTURY AGO.
A CENTURY?
THAT'S 100 YEARS.
MM-HMM, THAT'S RIGHT.
YOU KNOW, SOMETIMES IT TAKES
A LONG TIME FOR AN IDEA
TO BECOME A REALITY.
DON'T YOU WISH
YOU WERE GOING?
I'M A SCIENTIST,
NOT AN ASTRONAUT.
BUT YOU DESIGNED IT, DAD.
WELL, THAT, UM...
THAT PRIVATE CONSORTIUM
I TOLD YOU ABOUT,
UM, THEY'RE, UH,
THEY'RE ALREADY, UH,
THEY'RE--THEY'RE RECRUITING
A TOPNOTCH, UM...TEAM.
JEAN, FREEZE PROGRAM.
(Jean)
IS THERE A PROBLEM,
DR. BRAUN?
YEAH. YEAH.
THIS ISN'T MY SON.
HE'S GENERIC.
HE COULD BE ANYBODY'S SON.
(Jean)
THE PROGRAM EXTRAPOLATES
AS BEST IT CAN
BASED ON THE DATA AVAILABLE,
PUBLIC RECORDS.
YEAH, LOOK, JUST--JUST FORGET
ALL THAT CRAP, ALL RIGHT, JEAN?
ACCESS ME.
(Jean)
YOU, DR. BRAUN?
YES, USE MY, UM,
MY PSYCH RECORDS,
MY EVALUATIONS,
MY FAMILY HISTORIES,
AND ALL OTHER DATA AVAILABLE
TO BUILD A MORE REALISTIC
VERSION OF THIS--
THIS CHARACTER, AND THEN TAP
INTO THE NEURAL INTERFACE
USING REAL-TIME BIOFEEDBACK
OF MY COGNITIVE RESPONSE
TO SHAPE THE CHARACTER.
HELP ME.
HELP ME FIND OUT WHAT
HE'D REALLY BE LIKE, JEAN.
(Jean)
EXTRAPOLATION COMPLETE.
SHAWN?
[beeping]
SON?
ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
WHY DO YOU COME HOME
EVERY NIGHT NOW
WHEN YOU NEVER USED TO
BEFORE?
WHAT?
WHY DO YOU COME HOME
EVERY NIGHT NOW
WHEN YOU NEVER USED TO
BEFORE I DIED?
(Jean)
READY TO REPLAY PIKE SIMULATION
USING REDUCED SPEED
AT END OF RECORDING.
[rewinding]
WHAT?
YOU'RE NOT FOOLING
ANYONE, FRANK.
[sniffs]
LEAST OF ALL, YOURSELF.
JEAN, WHAT IS--
[gunshots]
[gasps]
[gasping]
[exhales]
[beeping]
[takes deep breath]
JEAN, WHAT TIME IS IT?
(Jean)
18:31, SHIP TIME.
THAT'S GOOD.
(Jean)
IT IS, SIR?
IT'S TRUE.
IT'S REALLY TRUE.
¶ WHEN JOHNNY COMES MARCHING
HOME AGAIN ¶
¶ HURRAH, HURRAH ¶
¶ WE'LL GIVE HIM A HEARTY
WELCOME HOME ¶
¶ HURRAH, HURRAH ¶
¶ THE MEN WILL CHEER
AND THE BOYS WILL SHOUT ¶
¶ THE LADIES ¶
¶ WILL ALL COME OUT ¶
¶ AND WE'LL ALL FEEL GREAT ¶
[click]
¶ WHEN JOHNNY
COMES MARCHING ¶
¶ HOME ¶
[imitates gunshot]
THERE ARE MORE EFFECTIVE
TREATMENTS ON EARTH,
BUT WE'RE HERE,
AND RIKA THINKS WE CAN EXTRACT
ENOUGH LEVODOPA
FROM THE PLANTS ON BOARD
TO PROVIDE--
GREAT.
EVERYONE'S HERE.
BEEN HERE
FOR 15 MINUTES, FRANK.
DIDN'T YOU CALL THIS MEETING?
YES, YES.
UH, I WAS JUST TRYING TO, UH--
YOU OKAY?
I'M FINE.
YOU ARE? GREAT.
YEAH, I'M FINE.
YOU LOOK GOOD.
THANK YOU.
OKAY, UH,
YEAH, YOU ALL LOOK GOOD.
SO, UH...
ON THE--ON THE GO/NO GO, UM...
I MADE THE DECISION.
IT'S GO.
WE'RE GOING ON.
WE'RE NOT TURNING BACK.
SO I WANT A FULL SYSTEMS CHECK.
WAIT, JUST LIKE THAT?
YOU'RE REALLY
NOT GONNA GIVE US A SAY.
[scoffs]
WHA--
[sighs]
UH...
LOOK, UM...
I KNOW IT'S BEEN--IT'S BEEN--
IT'S BEEN A TOUGH FEW MONTHS,
AND--AND, UH,
A LOT OF THAT'S ON ME.
YOU KNOW, I--
I'VE BEEN HARD
ON--ON ALL OF YOU,
WHEN THE TRUTH IS YOU--YOU'VE
JUST BEEN DOING YOUR JOBS.
YOU KNOW, IN FACT...
WE'VE ALL JUST BEEN DOING
OUR JOBS,
YOU KNOW, FOCUSING SO HARD
ON THE TASKS IN FRONT OF US
THAT--THAT
WE COULDN'T SEE CLEARLY.
BUT NOW...
UH, NOW IT'S ALL THERE,
RIGHT IN FRONT OF US,
YOU KNOW,
LIKE--LIKE IT ALWAYS WAS.
WHAT'S IN FRONT OF US?
WELL, EVERYTHING.
I MEAN, I-IT'S ALL
ABOUT TO CHANGE--
EVERYTHING WE KNOW,
EVERYTHING WE BELIEVE.
BUT YOU'RE RIGHT.
YOU'RE ABSOLUTELY RIGHT...
ABSOLUTELY RIGHT.
I'LL MAKE THIS A VOTE.
YEAH, RIGHT NOW...
A GO/NO GO VOTE
FROM EVERYONE.
WE'LL START WITH THE DOC.
YOU'RE THE MAN WITH THE PROBLEM.
WHAT DO YOU THINK?
HUH?
UH...
A FEW DAYS AGO,
I WOULD HAVE SAID NO, NO WAY,
BUT...
[chuckles]
TODAY I--I HAD THIS EXPERIENCE.
IN YOUR VIRT MODULE,
RIGHT?
YES.
[chuckles]
WELL, KIND OF A GLITCH,
ACTUALLY.
THERE'S A LOT
OF THAT GOING AROUND.
WELL, WHATEVER IT WAS,
IT--IT SUDDENLY FORCED ME
TO LET GO
OF EVERYTHING, YOU KNOW?
I FELT.
ALIVE.
YES.
EXACTLY.
ALIVE.
AND?
WELL, I KNOW THIS MUCH--
I WANT TO SEE ERIDANI.
GREAT.
SO DOC'S MADE HIS DECISION.
SUE.
THOUGHT YOU'D NEVER ASK.
GO.
ALICE?
MANNY, VAL?
COME ON, GUYS.
HOOK ME UP
WITH A DOUBLE PLAY, HUH?
I-I SAY GO.
GOOD TO GO, COMMANDER.
YEAH.
UH, KENJI, WHAT DO YOU SAY?
GO.
WHAT?
YEAH.
[laughing]
OKAY, ROGER,
ROGER, IT'S YOUR TURN.
THIS IS A SHAM.
WE DON'T LIVE IN A DEMOCRACY.
YOU'VE ALREADY MADE
YOUR MIND UP, FRANK.
IT'S A VOTE.
GO OR NO GO.
IT'S WHAT WE'RE HERE TO DO.
EXACTLY.
RIKA?
GO.
GREAT.
BILLIE?
UM, GO.
YEAH.
JULES, MY MAN.
WELL, I DIDN'T DESIGN IT
TO STAY.
[laughter]
THAT A BOY.
AND FINALLY, DR. J.
LET'S HEAR IT
FROM PHAETON'S
SECOND-IN-COMMAND,
THE MAN WHO'LL BE LEFT
HOLDING THE BAG
AFTER THE BUS.
HUH?
WHAT DO YOU SAY, JIMMY?
SERIOUSLY?
YOU READY
FOR AN ADVENTURE, OR...
YOU WANT TO JUST
ROLL ON HOME?
[chuckles]
THAT'S MOBY DICK.
YEAH, YEAH, GO.
HEY, THAT'S IT, THEN!
OKAY, FULL SYSTEMS CHECK
AT 0900.
LET'S DO THIS, PEOPLE.
WHOO!
LET'S DO THIS.
[laughter]
WHAT'D YOU EXPECT?
COME ON.
ERIDANI, HERE WE COME.
[laughter]
YES.
[indistinct chatter]
SO WHAT'S GOTTEN INTO YOU?
YOU KNOW, I'M NOT SURE
I CAN PUT THIS INTO WORDS, RIKA.
[chuckles]
IN FACT, I KNOW
I CAN'T PUT IT INTO WORDS,
BUT JUST TRUST ME.
IT'S, UH...
IT'S EXTRAORDINARY.
(Billie)
WE ARE ABOUT TO LAUNCH OURSELVES
INTO DEEP SPACE
FOR THE FIRST TIME.
AND I AM HERE WITH OUR RESIDENT
NUCLEAR PHYSICIST,
JIMMY JOHNSON.
CAN YOU SIMPLIFY IT
FOR OUR VIEWERS, JIMMY?
UH, YEAH, SURE, BILLIE.
UM...
[sighs]
BASICALLY WE GONNA BLOW US UP
A BUNCH OF BIG-ASS BOMBS
OFF THE ASS END
OF THIS HERE SHIP.
THEM BIG-ASS BOMBS
GONNA VAPORIZE
SOME BIG-ASS ALLOY PLATES.
AND THE TRANSLATION
OF ALL THAT--
BIG-ASS MASS ENERGY
MAKE US GO REAL FAST,
REAL FAST.
YIPPEE KI-AY--
ALL RIGHT, JIMMY.
THANKS, JIMMY.
[laughing]
[Chemical Brothers'
Alive Alone]
¶ ¶
¶ NO WAY OF KNOWING ¶
¶ IF SHE'S EVER COMING BACK ¶
¶ IF I CARE OR NOT ¶
¶ NO WAY OF KNOWING ¶
¶ IF SHE'S RIGHT
OR IF SHE'S WRONG ¶
PRE-RUN SYSTEMS CHECKS
COMPLETE.
READY FOR SLINGSHOT.
OKAY, PEOPLE, REPORT.
MEYER, RIKA?
YEAH, ALL SET HERE.
RIKA?
YEP.
[laughs]
ALICE, KENJI?
WE'RE READY.
WISH WE HAD A FRONT-ROW SEAT.
GOOD TO GO.
GOT TO PEE, BUT...
ALL RIGHT.
BILLIE?
YEAH, READY, READY.
MANNY, VAL?
[exaggerated Russian accent]
FEARLESS GAY DUO
ARE READY
TO FACE UNKNOWN, COMMANDER.
ENOUGH FOR NOW.
THEY'RE SHOOTING THIS, YEAH?
OH, WELL, GOOD.
BIG HELLO
TO ALL OUR INTERVIEW FANS.
BE SURE TO BUY
THE FULLY ARTICULATED
MANNY AND VAL ACTION FIGURES
WITH YOUR NEXT PURCHASE
OF TWEETY BURGER MEGA MEAL.
YEAH, UH, COMMANDER,
WE'RE AT THAT POINT
OF, UH, NO RETURN,
SO I GUESS--
I GUESS WE'RE READY TO GO.
SO IT SEEMS.
ROGER?
OH, I'M READY TO RECORD
SOME GREAT FOOTAGE, FRANK.
I'M SURE YOU'RE NOT
GONNA DISAPPOINT ME.
OH, IT'S
MY TOP PRIORITY, ROG.
SUE?
UH, YEAH,
I'M GOOD HERE, SKIPPER.
NAVIGATION ONLINE.
CORE INTERFACE ONLINE.
STAND BY.
YOU HEAR BACK
FROM MISSION CONTROL
ABOUT MEYER AND OUR GO-ABOUT?
NO.
OF COURSE,
I DIDN'T SEND THE MESSAGE
UNTIL ABOUT TEN MINUTES AGO,
WHICH THEY WON'T GET
FOR ANOTHER 90 MINUTES.
SO WE'RE LOOKING
AT PROBABLY ANOTHER TWO HOURS
FOR A RESPONSE.
WELL, I GUESS THEY'LL JUST HAVE
TO GRIN AND BEAR IT.
WELL, I GUESS SO.
THIS IS THE FLIGHT DECK.
INITIATING D-SPIN.
¶ ¶
DISTANCE NOW
AT 100,000 KLICKS.
SPEED INCREASING
TO 30 KLICKS A SECOND.
NAV, HOW'S OUR AIM?
WE'RE THREE MILLIARD SECONDS
OFF THE "B" PLANE.
RCS THRUSTERS AUTO-FIRING
TO COMPENSATE.
BACK IN THE PIPE,
FIVE BY FIVE,
READY FOR SLINGSHOT.
INITIATING.
¶ ¶
¶ I'M ALIVE ¶
¶ I'M ALONE ¶
¶ AND I'VE NEVER WANTED TO BE ¶
¶ EITHER OF THOSE ¶
WE ARE NOT GONNA WANT
FOR RATINGS THIS WEEK.
[chuckles]
IT'S AMAZING.
JUST A-AMAZING STUFF I'M
GETTING HERE, GUYS, AMAZING.
I'M HAPPY FOR YOU, ROG,
BUT WE'RE A LITTLE BUSY
RIGHT NOW.
NAV, STATUS?
PERFECT BURN.
SLINGSHOT COMPLETE.
¶ AND SHE SHINES ¶
¶ AND SHE SHINES FOR ME ¶
¶ ¶
[beeping]
[sighs]
JIMMY, YOUR SHOW.
I HOPE NO ONE
HAD A BIG LUNCH,
BECAUSE THE RIDE
IS ABOUT TO GET...
BUMPY.
DEPLOYING FIRST CHARGE.
¶ ¶
ON COURSE, SPEED--
19.2 MILLION METERS PER SECOND.
ROUGHLY 1/15 FLIGHT SPEED.
ONE DOWN, 182 TO GO.
READY FOR ANOTHER?
HIT ME.
¶ ¶
WHOO-HOO!
[laughing]
WHOA.
[mellow guitar music]
¶ ¶
AS I OBSERVED
IN CHAPTER FIVE...
LONG-DURATION SPACE MISSIONS
PRESENT
A PSYCHOLOGICAL CHALLENGE
FOR MAINTAINING
CREW MOTIVATION,
MORALE,
AND INDIVIDUAL WELL-BEING.
UP TO NOW, EMPIRICAL KNOWLEDGE
OF RELEVANT
PSYCHOLOGICAL ISSUES
HAS BEEN BASED ON MISSIONS
OF ONLY UP TO TWO YEARS.
HOWEVER, THE EXTENDED DURATION
OF THE ERIDANI MISSION
PRESENTS UNIQUE ISSUES,
AS WELL
AS PROMISING OPPORTUNITIES
FOR FURTHER STUDY.
THE RE-PURPOSING
OF VIRTUAL-REALITY TECHNOLOGY
ORIGINALLY DESIGNED TO MAINTAIN
MISSION-CRITICAL SKILLS
AS A RECREATIONAL TOOL
IS ONE NEW FEATURE
THAT IS ALREADY SHOWING
GREAT PROMISE AS A--AS A MEANS
OF AMELIORATING CREW TENSION
AND ENHANCING MORALE.
OF COURSE, AS WITH ANY NEW...
THERAPEUTIC TECHNOLOGY,
THERE ARE VARIABLES
AND--AND UNKNOWNS...
AMONG THEM, CONFLICTS BETWEEN
THE CLIENT'S EXPECTATIONS
AND THE--THE STILL UNKNOWN
LIMITS OF THE TECHNOLOGY,
AS WELL AS PROBLEMS
WHICH CAN'T BE ANTICIPATED...
DUE TO THE UNIQUE FUSION
THE TECHNOLOGY ENABLES
BETWEEN INTELLIGENT
COMPUTER SYSTEMS...
AND THEIR BIOLOGICAL MODELS...
THE HUMAN MIND.
[rock music]
[singing in foreign language]
¶ ¶
[cheers and applause]
WHOO!
NIKKI, WE JUST GOT A FIX
ON LAZERUS' POSITION.
HE'S IN SHANGHAI.
SKIP THE ENCORE.
PREP THE CHOPPER.
[foreign word], TOKYO!
WHOO!
[cheers and applause continue]
GREAT SHOW, NIKKI.
THIS OUR ONLY SHOT?
YEAH, BOTH INTERPOL AND MI6
BELIEVE HE'S CHANGED
HIS APPEARANCE AGAIN.
ALL THE PLASTIC SURGERY
IN THE WORLD
WON'T SAVE HIS ASS THIS TIME.
HELL-RAISERS?
YEAH!
LET'S ROCK AND ROLL.
[cheering]
[gunshot]
LAZERUS.
HE SHOT RICO!
AAH!
YOU'RE NOT LAZERUS.
NO, I'M NOT.
UGH!
JEAN--JEAN,
THAT REALLY HURT.
CAN YOU TAKE THE PHYSICAL IMPACT
DOWN THREE SETTINGS?
I DON'T THINK JEAN'S
GONNA HELP YOU TODAY, BILLIE.
JEAN?
JEAN, WHAT IS THIS?
JEAN!
[breathing heavily]
JEAN.
PROGRAM OFF.
[gasps]
[groans]
JEAN...
FREEZE PROGRAM, JEAN.
IT'S YOUR FANTASY, BILLIE.
WHY NOT ENJOY IT?
[gasping]
[crying]
I THINK WE SHOULD TAKE
THE ENTIRE PROGRAM OFF-LINE,
ALL THE VIRT MODULES,
UNTIL I CAN FIX THE PROBLEM.
I MEAN, WHAT IF SOMEBODY
GETS TRAPPED
IN AN EVEN WORSE SITUATION
AND STRUGGLES TO GET OUT OF IT
LIKE I DID?
THERE COULD BE SYNAPTIC DAMAGE
FOR ALL I KNOW.
I THINK YOU'RE RIGHT,
BUT I'M WONDERING
IF YOU'RE TREATING THIS ONE
A LITTLE BIT INTELLECTUALLY.
YOUR COMPUTER GLITCH
THAT NEEDS TO BE SOLVED,
RATHER THAN SOMETHING
VERY TRAUMATIC
THAT HAPPENED
TO YOU PERSONALLY.
WELL, NOTHING HAPPENED
TO ME, REALLY.
I MEAN, PHYSICALLY,
IN REALITY, NOTHING HAPPENED.
[scoffs]
IF YOU THINK ABOUT IT,
IT'S NO DIFFERENT
THAN A BAD DREAM,
AND DREAMS AREN'T REAL,
RIGHT?
WELL, THE EVENTS
THEY PORTRAY MAY NOT BE,
BUT THE FEELINGS DREAMS EVOKE
AND THE MEMORIES
THEY LEAVE BEHIND,
THEY CAN BE AS REAL
AS ANYTHING IN OUR LIVES.
BUT I'M--I'M CURIOUS WHY YOU
CHOSE TO DESCRIBE IT AS A DREAM.
I'M SORRY.
UH, WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
WELL, SOME PEOPLE
BELIEVE THAT DREAMS
ARE THE MIND'S WAY
OF EXPLORING THINGS
THAT WOULD ORDINARILY
BE SUPPRESSED IN WAKING HOURS.
YOU'RE TALKING
ABOUT FANTASIES.
I DON'T HAVE A RAPE FANTASY,
IF THAT'S
WHAT YOU'RE GETTING AT.
NO, I'M NOT GETTING
AT ANYTHING, BILLIE.
I'M JUST SHOWING YOU
YOUR CHOICE OF WORDS.
BY DESCRIBING IT AS A DREAM,
YOU'RE IMPLYING IT'S SOMETHING
THAT YOU DREAMT UP,
AS IF, IN SOME WAY, YOU BLAME
YOURSELF FOR WHAT HAPPENED
OR EVEN FEEL YOU DESERVED IT.
IT'S A COMPUTER GLITCH,
AND THAT'S ALL IT IS.
[door opens]
THE VIRT MODULES
WERE YOUR BABY, ROGER.
YOU FOUGHT TO INCLUDE THEM
IN THE MISSION.
NOW YOU WANT THEM SHUT DOWN?
WELL, ACTUALLY,
IT'S THE LAST THING I WANT,
BUT THE SAFETY OF THE CREW
HAS TO BE PARAMOUNT.
"IN PSYCHOLOGICAL TERMS,
THE PHAETON MISSION
"WILL AMOUNT
TO FORCED CONFINEMENT
FOR 12 PEOPLE FOR TEN YEARS."
THAT'S VERY CLEVER, FRANK.
"WITHOUT THE ABILITY
"TO ESCAPE THE CONFINES
OF THEIR METAL TUBE PERIODICALLY
"TO EXPERIENCE
OTHER ENVIRONMENTS
"AND INTERACT
WITH OTHER PEOPLE,
"EVEN IF THEY'RE ONLY
COMPUTER-GENERATED,
THE PRESSURES OF THE MISSION--"
YEAH, YOU DON'T HAVE
TO READ THE WHOLE THING.
"DIVISIONS WILL FORM
AMONG THE CREW.
"BARELY ACKNOWLEDGED
ANIMOSITIES AND JEALOUSIES
"WILL CROP UP.
PARANOID AND EVEN DELUSIONAL
BEHAVIOR IS POSSIBLE."
I KNOW WHAT I WROTE, FRANK.
[scoffs]
YOU'RE PLAYING WITH FIRE.
IN EVERY SENSE BUT THE PHYSICAL,
BILLIE WAS RAPED.
SHE'S GONNA FEEL THE EMOTIONAL,
PSYCHOLOGICAL EFFECTS OF THAT
FOR THE REST OF HER LIFE.
HOW IS SHE?
SHE'S IN SHOCK.
RIGHT.
SHE'S HANGING ON
TO THE VIRTUAL NATURE
OF THE EXPERIENCE
AS A WAY OF SAYING
IT WASN'T REAL,
THEREFORE NOTHING HAPPENED,
AND SHE DOESN'T NEED TREATMENT.
WHAT DO YOU THINK?
WAS IT REAL?
WHAT ARE YOU ASKING ME,
FRANK?
I'M ASKING IF YOU KNOW
FANTASY FROM REALITY, ROGER.
I THINK I DO.
DO YOU KNOW WHAT'S REAL, FRANK?
I'LL TELL YOU WHAT I THINK.
I THINK THIS MISSION
HAS CHANGED.
I THINK OUR EYES
ARE ABOUT TO BE OPENED
AND THAT--THAT--
THAT WE ARE ON THE VERGE
OF A PROFOUND AWAKENING
THAT--THAT YOU AND I
CANNOT EVEN IMAGINE.
AND I THINK THE VIRT MODULES
ARE CRUCIAL TO THAT AWAKENING.
I WON'T SHUT THEM DOWN.
IN MY PROFESSIONAL OPINION,
YOUR BEHAVIOR OF LATE
HAS BEEN ERRATIC AT BEST.
ARE YOU SAYING THAT
TO MISSION CONTROL?
I KNOW THE VALUE OF LOYALTY
IN ANY ISOLATED CREW, FRANK,
AND I LIVE ON THE SHIP TOO.
WHAT'S REALLY GOING ON?
I ONCE WAS LOST,
BUT NOW I'M FOUND.
WAS BLIND, BUT NOW I SEE.
LOOK, AT THE VERY LEAST,
THE CREW DESERVE
TO KNOW THE FACTS.
THEY'RE OUR FRIENDS
AS WELL AS OUR COLLEAGUES.
DON'T LEAD THEM
INTO TREACHEROUS WATERS
UNAWARE, FRANK.
YOU KNOW, ROGER,
YOU'RE RIGHT THERE.
THEY DO DESERVE
TO KNOW THE TRUTH.
THE TRUTH
SHALL SET THEM FREE.
WHOO!
A SEXUAL ASSAULT?
COULD YOU BE MORE SPECIFIC?
ASSAULT AGAINST WHO?
WELL, THERE'S
A PRIVACY ISSUE HERE.
I'M NOT AT LIBERTY TO DESCRIBE
THE ATTACK IN DETAIL
OR WHO EXPERIENCED IT.
BUT IN MY OPINION,
THERE IS A SERIOUS DEFECT
IN THE VIRT SOFTWARE,
AND I'M STRONGLY RECOMMENDING
THAT WE REFRAIN
FROM USING THE VIRT MODULES.
UH, FOR HOW LONG?
UNTIL WE KNOW THE PROBLEM'S
BEEN IDENTIFIED AND REPAIRED.
CAN'T WE JUST UPLOAD
NEW SOFTWARE?
NOT AT THIS RANGE AND SPEED.
WE'RE LUCKY TO GET
SIMPLE ENGINEERING PACKETS,
LET ALONE
COMPLEX SOFTWARE UPLOADS.
I DON'T THINK
THERE'S ANYTHING TO FEAR
FROM THE VIRT MODULES.
ARE WE TALKING
ABOUT A PERMANENT SHUTDOWN?
POSSIBLY.
WELL...
WE'VE ALL EXPERIENCED
COMPUTER GLITCHES BEFORE,
AND JUST TO PLAY
DEVIL'S ADVOCATE HERE,
ISN'T IT POSSIBLE
THAT WE'RE OVERREACTING?
YOU HEARD HIM SAY
"SEXUAL ASSAULT," RIGHT?
[sighs]
YES.
WHAT DOES THAT MEAN EXACTLY?
I MEAN, THERE'S A BIG
DIFFERENCE BETWEEN SOMEBODY
GETTING A PINCH ON THE ASS
AND BEING GANG-RAPED.
SOMEONE WAS VIOLATED
BY A COMPUTER PROGRAM.
DOESN'T MATTER
WHAT IT MEANS EXACTLY.
UM, FOR ONCE, I HAVE TO AGREE
WITH JIMMY HERE.
AND I DON'T MEAN TO SOUND
INSENSITIVE OR ANYTHING,
BUT, UH, THESE PROGRAMS
ARE THE ONLY CHANCE
THAT ANY OF US HAVE
FOR PRIVACY HERE ON THE SHIP.
AND IF ALL WE'RE TALKING ABOUT
IS SOME C.G. CHARACTER
COPPING A FEEL,
I DON'T THINK IT'S A--
WAIT, I'M SORRY.
WHAT KIND OF LOGIC IS THAT?
ONE OF THESE CHARACTERS
SHOT ME, JULES.
SORRY, IS MURDER
A GRAY AREA FOR YOU TOO?
PEOPLE GET SHOT IN THEIR ACTION
PROGRAMS ALL THE TIME.
IT WASN'T
IN AN ACTION PROGRAM.
I WAS RELAXING
IN MY BEACH HOUSE.
I WAS SUPPOSED TO BE ALONE.
AN INTRUDER CAME IN
AND SHOT ME IN MY BED
WHEN I WAS ALONE.
SO YOU WERE SHOT,
AND SOMEONE ELSE WAS ASSAULTED.
IT'S A SIMULATION.
LOOK, JUST GO BACK IN,
CREATE A COUPLE MACHINE GUNS,
TAKE YOUR REVENGE.
YOU'LL FEEL BETTER,
BELIEVE ME.
LOOK, I'M SORRY.
I JUST DON'T SEE
WHAT THE BIG DEAL IS.
NONE OF IT'S REAL.
IT'S ALL IN YOUR HEAD.
BRILLIANT, BRILLIANT.
YOU AND I ARE GONNA
REVISIT THIS.
WELL, WE'RE STILL WAITING
TO HEAR FROM YOU, SKIPPER.
GONNA SHUT DOWN
THE MODULES OR NOT?
NO, I'M NOT.
KNOCK, KNOCK.
WHAT?
CAN I COME IN?
YEAH.
I'M SORRY.
THEY'RE IDIOTS.
I KNEW THAT.
HOW OLD ARE YOU?
[scoffs]
I'M 24.
I WAS 24
WHEN I JOINED THE MARINES.
AND I WAS ON, UH...
I WAS ON
THIS TRAINING MISSION,
AND TWO GUYS
FROM MY OWN UNIT...
THEY, UM...
YOU KNOW, THESE GUYS--
I MEAN, I--I ATE WITH THEM.
I RACKED WITH THEM.
I--IT--
AND THAT WAS THE WORST PART,
YOU KNOW?
JUST THE REALIZATION
THAT NONE OF THAT MATTERED,
THAT I DIDN'T EVEN
REALLY EXIST TO THEM.
[scoffs]
THAT'S THE THING, YOU KNOW.
LIKE, THESE GUYS--
THEY DON'T GET IT, YOU KNOW.
THEY DON'T GET THAT--
THAT EVEN WHEN SOMETHING
LIKE THIS HAPPENS
IN THE REAL WORLD,
YOUR MIND IS WHERE IT HAPPENS,
MORE THAN YOUR BODY.
I MEAN, WHEN THAT'S GOING ON,
YOU'RE NOT EVEN IN YOUR BODY.
THEY'VE ALREADY TAKEN THAT
FROM YOU.
THE ONLY THING
THAT I CAN TELL YOU RIGHT NOW
IS YOU'RE GONNA BE OKAY.
DON'T LISTEN TO THOSE ASSES
TELLING YOU THAT IT'S NOT REAL
OR IT'S ALL IN YOUR HEAD,
AND SO IT DOESN'T MATTER.
JUST FEEL IT.
YOU PLAY THE FLUTE?
YEAH.
YOU ANY GOOD?
I'M OKAY.
YEAH, YOU ARE.
SO WHAT WAS THAT CONVERSATION
YOU HAD WITH FRANK YESTERDAY?
THERE'S BEEN QUITE
A LOT GOING ON WITH HIM.
MM-HMM.
YOU'VE NOTICED IT TOO?
WELL, YEAH.
[laughs]
BUT QUICKLY,
THE LAST FEW DAYS,
ONE MINUTE,
DEPRESSED,
ANGRY AT THE--AT THE CREW.
THAT'S NOT LIKE HIM, REALLY.
HE'S VERY LEVEL.
THE NEXT MINUTE, HE'S UP.
HE'S COMPLETELY HIGH AS A KITE.
JUST NOW WE SAW HIM.
HE'S...
[sighs]
WELL, MAYBE HE'S HAPPY.
I DON'T KNOW.
MAYBE HE'S HAPPY.
I-I HOPE HE'S HAPPY.
SOMETHING
MIGHT'VE CHEERED HIM UP.
[sighs]
I DON'T KNOW,
BUT SOMETHING IS NOT...
QUITE RIGHT,
AND I'M NOT SURE
WHAT TO DO ABOUT IT.
(Jean)
EXCUSE ME, COMMANDER.
COMMANDER?
YES?
THERE'S A CALL FROM JULES
ON THE FLIGHT DECK.
[beeping]
WE GOT A PROBLEM HERE, BOSS.
UH, WE RETRACTED THE COMM ARRAY
SO WE COULD
THOSE AIR-BRAKING TESTS,
AND NOW IT WON'T DEPLOY AGAIN.
IT COULD BE A SERVO FAILURE.
IT COULD BE
A BLOWN POWER SUPPLY,
BUT I'VE DONE
ALL I CAN FROM HERE.
SOMEBODY'S GONNA HAVE TO TAKE
A WALK, CHECK IT OUT.
TELL RIKA, VAL, AND MANNY
TO GRAB THEIR PRESSURE SUITS
AND MEET IN THE AIRLOCK.
JULES, YOU'RE IN CHARGE
OF MONITORING THE E.V.A.
ROGER.
[beeping]
[sighs]
JULIA CHILD SAYS THAT THE KEY
TO MAKING GREAT SOUFFLE
IS BEATING OF EGG WHITES
TO FORM AIR BUBBLES THAT EXPAND
WITH HEAT FROM OVEN, YES?
OH, RIGHT,
YEAH, I LIKE JULIA.
SHE CAME
TO OUR SEND-OFF, RIGHT?
SHE'S THE ONE
THAT BROUGHT ALL THE--
NO, NO, THAT'S
JULIA CHILDRESS.
IT'S PROBABLY
A FRIED CIRCUIT BOARD.
I DESIGN THESE THINGS
TO WITHSTAND A SUB-ZERO VACUUM
AND EVERY STRESS
KNOWN TO MAN,
AND THEN
SOME SUIT COMES ALONG,
CHECKS A BOX, AND FARMS IT
OUT TO THE LOWEST BIDDER.
YOU THINK
IF THERE'S ONE THING
THEY WOULDN'T CUT
CORNERS ON, HUH?
YEAH, NO COMM ARRAY,
NO DATA UPLOADS, NO SHOW,
NOT THAT I MIND.
HEY.
ATLAS, DO YOU WANT A HAND
WITH THAT?
I CAN MANAGE.
[laughs]
SURE YOU CAN.
LIFT IT.
AH, IT'S HEAVY.
CAN I ASK YOU
A PERSONAL QUESTION?
MM-HMM.
ARE YOU GOING NUTS?
PROBABLY,
BUT WOULD I KNOW IT IF I WERE?
UH, PROBABLY NOT.
NO.
FIRST CLUE YOU'D HAVE
WOULD BE US RUSHING AT YOU
WITH, UH,
ROPES AND A SYRINGE.
UNTIL THEN, I GUESS YOU'LL ALL
JUST HAVE TO TRUST ME.
DAMN IT.
THIS THING WON'T RELEASE.
[grunts]
WELL--
CAN YOU GET ME A PAIR
OF PLIERS FROM THE LOCKER?
[breathing heavily]
YOU'RE NOT SERIOUS.
NO, CONCERNED.
AS A MEMBER OF THE CREW--
I'M FINE.
NOW GET ME THE PLIERS, PLEASE.
THERE WE GO.
[breathing heavily]
[grunting]
[beeping]
ONE OF THESE IS A BACKUP,
AND ONE OF THEM IS THE ONE
THAT'S SUPPOSED TO--
LET'S CHECK.
WE HAVE ONE, TWO...
[door closes, locks]
THIS--DID YOU--
HEY.
VERY FUNNY.
WHO'S THE JOKER?
SO DO YOU, UH, WANT--
OPEN THE DOOR IF YOU WANT IT.
ALL RIGHT,
SERIOUSLY, COMMANDER.
SORRY.
SO OPEN THE DOOR.
[laughter]
OH, COMMANDER, COMMANDER.
I CAN'T HEAR YOU.
(Jean)
ATTENTION, AIRLOCK C
OUTER DOOR HAS UNSEALED
AND WILL OPEN IN 20 SECONDS.
NO, NO, NO, NO.
HE HASN'T GOT HIS HELMET ON.
JEAN, RESEAL THE OUTER DOOR.
(Jean)
UNABLE TO COMPLY.
OUTER DOOR IS NOT RESPONDING
TO COMPUTER COMMANDS.
FLIGHT DECK, WE HAVE A PROBLEM
IN AIRLOCK C.
OKAY, WE'RE ON IT. SOMETHING'S
TRIPPED THE OUTER-HATCH RELEASE.
JIMMY, JIMMY.
I'M AHEAD OF YOU.
IT'S COMING, IT'S COMING.
IT'S GONNA TAKE A SECOND.
PIKE'S GONNA GET SUCKED
OUT THERE.
DON'T SHOUT!
OPEN THE DOOR, JEAN!
(Jean)
THE OUTER DOOR
IS NOW OPENING.
OVERRIDE COMMAND, JEAN.
[hissing, alarm blaring]
[screaming]
LET'S GO, LET'S GO!
RIKA, LISTEN TO ME.
DO SOMETHING!
I CUT THE POWER BUS.
THE OUTER DOOR
IS NOT OPENING ANYMORE,
BUT I CAN'T SHUT IT.
[screaming]
(Jean)
IN 60 SECONDS,
EXPOSURE TO VACUUM WILL RESULT
IN COMMANDER PIKE'S DEATH.
PROJECTING REMAINING TIME.
HELP!
MANNY, HELP!
[screaming]
[indistinct shouting]
[alarm continues blaring]
COME ON, COME ON!
HURRY UP!
I'M TRYING, I'M TRYING!
COME ON!
HELMETS ON, GLOVES!
COME ON, GLOVES, HELMETS NOW!
CAN'T WE OVERRIDE
THE SYSTEM INSIDE HERE?
HE'S DOING THAT RIGHT NOW!
GET THE DOOR OPEN!
I'M TRYING TO OPEN IT!
HURRY!
COME ON!
VAL, COME ON!
GO, GO, GO, GO, GO, GO!
COME ON, GET IT OPEN!
GO!
WE'RE IN!
[grunting]
GUYS, I NEED YOU TO DO
SOMETHING MANUAL IN THERE.
JEAN, IS COMMANDER PIKE
STILL ON THE SHIP?
(Jean)
20 SECONDS.
COME ON, COME ON,
COME ON, COME ON.
[grunting]
FIX IT!
DOOR CLOSING.
[coughing]
(Jean)
STANDARD ATMOSPHERIC PRESSURE
IS BEING RESTORED.
FRANK.
FRANK!
VAL, WHERE ARE YOU?
[flat-lining]
AH, SO HE'S...
GONE.
AND I AM...
IN COMMAND OF THE MISSION.
OH, HAPPY DAY.
[crying]
SO IT'S SATURDAY.
OR SUNDAY.
I DON'T KNOW WHICH.
TIME'S DIFFERENT NOW.
EVERYTHING'S DIFFERENT NOW.
EVERYTHING MOVES FASTER
OR SLOWER.
I DON'T KNOW WHICH.
BUT IT'S SATURDAY SOMEWHERE,
RIGHT?
[laughs]
THIS MAKES NO SENSE
WHATSOEVER,
AND IT MAKES UTTER,
UTTER SENSE.
[exhales]
I'M SORRY.
IT'S NOT REAL.
I'M JUST...
PLAYING A ROLE.
I EVEN HAD IT WRITTEN DOWN,
WHAT I WAS GONNA SAY.
IF, IN SOME WAY,
BY CONTROLLING MY EMOTIONS,
I COULD CONTROL
THE CREW'S EMOTIONS,
I COULD CONTROL YOUR EMOTIONS.
I MEAN, HOW ARE WE SUPPOSED
TO TRUST JEAN?
I MEAN, JEAN KNOWS EVERYTHING.
JEAN DOES EVERYTHING, AND THEN
THE OUTER DOOR JUST OPENS.
OH.
[sobbing]
AND THEN WE'RE SUPPOSED
TO COMPLETE OUR MISSION.
WE CAN'T COMPLETE
OUR MISSION WITH--
[breathing heavily]
OH.
WHAT ARE WE SUPPOSED TO DO?
WE HAVE TEN YEARS.
NO CAPTAIN.
[screaming]
GOD, DON'T YOU TOUCH--
TOUCH ME!
SHH! SHH! SHH!
ARE YOU HAPPY NOW, ROGER?
WILL THIS BOOST OUR RATINGS?
DEAR SHAWN,
I DON'T KNOW
WHY I'M STILL WRITING TO YOU.
IT'S NOT AS IF I'M--
I'M PRETENDING
THAT YOU'LL EVER READ
THESE LETTERS.
BUT, UM, I HAVE TO TELL SOMEONE
ABOUT THIS,
AND RIGHT NOW THERE JUST, UH,
ISN'T ANYONE ELSE.
THERE WAS NO QUESTION
ABOUT TURNING BACK.
HAVING PASSED GO/NO GO,
WE'RE COMMITTED TO THE MISSION.
THERE WAS A BRIEF ARGUMENT
ABOUT THE INVESTIGATION
INTO THE COMMANDER'S DEATH.
WHEN WE, UH, PULLED APART
THE, UH, AIR-LOCK MECHANISM,
WE FOUND A SHORT INSIDE ONE
OF THE HYDRAULIC RELAYS--
A 20-CENT FUSE
THAT MUST'VE OVERLOADED.
NOW, RIKA FELT
THAT WE SHOULD CONTINUE TO STUDY
OTHER POSSIBLE CAUSES,
BUT DR. JOHNSON...
[chuckles]
DR. JOHNSON,
WHO WAS SECOND-IN-COMMAND,
DECLARED IT AN ACCIDENT.
SAID WE HAD NO CHOICE
BUT TO MOVE ON,
TRY AND PUT IT BEHIND US.
WELL, AFTER THAT, WE ALL JUST
TRIED TO GET BACK TO NORMAL.
BUT WHAT'S NORMAL?
YOU GOT TO ASK YOURSELF
WHEN YOU'RE HUNDREDS OF MILLIONS
OF MILES FROM EARTH,
AND YOU'VE JUST LOST
THE ONE MAN
WHO WAS ABLE TO HOLD
YOU ALL TOGETHER,
AND YOU KNOW SOMETHING
THAT NOBODY ELSE KNOWS.
I KNOW EVERY INCH OF THIS SHIP,
EVERY SYSTEM, EVERY SUBSYSTEM.
AND I ALSO KNOW THIS...
THERE IS NO WAY THAT
THAT OUTER AIR-LOCK DOOR
COULD'VE OPENED ON ITS OWN,
NO MATTER HOW MANY RELAYS
WERE SHORTED OUT.
IT'S IMPOSSIBLE.
SOMEONE HAD TO DO
SOMETHING DELIBERATE
THAT CAUSED
THAT DOOR TO OPEN...
WHICH MEANS THAT SOMEONE
ON THIS SHIP IS A KILLER.
AND BECAUSE I DON'T KNOW
WHO THAT IS...
I CAN'T TRUST ANYONE.
[sighs]
[beeping]
I LOVE YOU.
[crying]
JEAN.
(Jean)
YES, RIKA.
WHOSE HEADSET IS THAT?
(Jean)
IT'S COMMANDER PIKE'S.
WHAT'S IT DOING HERE,
IN MY QUARTERS?
(Jean)
I DON'T KNOW.
[rock music]
¶ ¶
WHAT DO I DO NOW?
YOU MEAN,
WHAT DO WE DO?
JUST WHAT JIMMY SAID.
GET SOME GUNS.
FIND THAT SCUMBAG.
WE KILL HIM.
¶ ¶
I NEED TO SEE
THE DOCTOR NOW.
DO YOU HAVE AN APPOINTMENT?
NO.
[shouting]
WE NEED TO TALK.
[mellow rock music]
¶ ¶
[beep]
NURSE?
A LOT OF WOUNDED HERE.
TELL YOUR DOCTORS TO GIVE THEM
THEIR BEST CARE.
JEAN, WHEN DID FRANK--
COMMANDER PIKE
CREATE THIS CHARACTER?
(Jean)
I HAVE NO RECORD OF WHEN
THIS CHARACTER WAS CREATED
OR BY WHOM.
CAN YOU TAKE CARE OF MY MEN?
I CAN TRY.
THANK YOU, MA'AM.
FRANK.
IT'S OKAY, RIKA.
NONE OF IT'S REAL.
WHAT?
FOLLOW ME THROUGH THE MIRROR
AND DOWN A RABBIT HOLE,
BECAUSE THE ONLY WAY OUT FOR ANY
OF US NOW IS TO KEEP GOING.
TRUST ME.
IT HAS TO BE THIS WAY.
YAH.
[rock music]
FRANK!
¶ ¶
DO YOU THINK
IF I PLAY A VIDEO GAME
AND I KILL SOMEONE
IN THAT VIDEO GAME,
SHOULD I THEN BE TRIED
FOR MURDER?
I DON'T THINK IT'S REAL.
UH, IT'S A GAME.
www.tvsubtitles.net