23.976
captioning made possible by
warner bros.
night,
here comes the night
another night
to dream about you
ba ba ba ba ba
dd night,
each lovely night dd
dd the only time
i'm not without you dd
dd once more,
i feel your kisses dd
i know what bliss is dd
dd comes dawn,
my darling, you're gone dd
dd but you come back
into my arms each night dd
dd once more,
i feel your kisses dd
i know what bliss is dd
dd comes dawn, my darling,
you're gone dd
dd but you come back into my arm
s each night dd
[horns honking]
marie:
when you are alone eternally,
you live for the comfort
of the senses--
food, sex.
i'd become very selective,
and it was getting harder
for me to find food,
even living in the city.
my choosiness about food
cost me my lover,
and without him,
there is no sex.
for six nights,
i have found nothing to eat.
but then came good news.
i was sad.
i was starved.
it was time
to treat myself,
and i thought,
"what about italian?"
don't worry
about the car.
leave the keys in case
we have to move it.
hey, lenny.
how you doing, huh?
all right.
what took you?
i had to dress right.
i had to shave.
he wants you
in on this.
hey, ton, what's
this all about, huh?
watch this.
aah!
[crunch]
i love that.
place is bugged.
we do business
downstairs.
come on.
see? we come so far down,
we're in china.
sal, how you doing?
i was honored
by your call...
a little surprised.
i didn't think--
have a seat.
so, uh, sal,
what's happening here, huh?
what's this?
it's a...it's a toaster.
it's a toaster oven.
whoa, hey.
it's a nice one.
a lot of buttons.
hit this button...
pops open.
you could put
anything in here--
slice of pizza,
pastry.
you pop it in.
comes out,
the crust is crisp.
[slams oven door]
microwave don't do that.
you ever tried cooking
calzone in a microwave?
it comes out
like a limp dick.
[laughter]
yeah.
korean.
they're getting a big chunk
of the electronics action.
do you know why?
because they fucking steal.
any fucking idea
that ain't nailed down.
you think
some korean asshole
came up
with the toaster oven?
well, here they are,
knocking them out.
where'd it come from?
what, sal?
the toaster?
honestly, i don't know.
you was with leguto.
when leguto fell
off the face of the earth,
you became mine.
then you got this idea
because i just took over,
maybe i'm confused,
maybe i'm letting things
slip through the cracks.
no, sal,
i would never think--
where did it come from?
sal, tell me
what the answer is.
what should i say?
it came from a warehouse.
it came off a truck
from the airport!
a truck you hit
tuesday!
where's my end,
gilly?
i had to take inventory,
make sure you got
a complete cross section
of the merchandise.
i thought this was
just a sit-down.
yeah, but somebody
ain't getting up.
i got a message
for your warehouse guys.
please, god.
sallie, no.
the message is...
don't fuck with me!
sal!
we got eyes on us!
maybe somebody saw
this guy come in here.
what are you saying?
you telling me something?
get rid of him
discreet.
you want discreet?
you fucking shoot him.
ray!
do it!
please, sal, no.
you don't understand.
it's a terrible mistake.
i want to live.
i'll do anything
for you.
please!
please help me!
please, sal.
you don't understand.
gilly,
that's fucking disgusting.
no, please!
don't do it to me!
you don't
understand!
don't do it to me.
don't!
you don't
understand!
fucking die.
next time i tell you
to pull the trigger,
you fucking pull the trigger!
sal, come on, relax.
joe's one of us.
yeah.
ha ha!
this shit's starting
to get to me.
ha ha ha!
yeah.
he does what
he's got to do.
he loves it.
he's fucking sick.
you can't talk like that.
this is war.
we're soldiers.
we kill to protect
what's ours.
here. take this.
it's clean.
i'm good at stealing.
i'm not a shooter.
if you're not a shooter,
you're shot.
bang!
you just can't sit around
and watch anymore.
sal will tell you
to whack somebody,
and you got no choice.
come on.
fucking cops!
hey!
jesus, joey!
aah! ow!
hey, back off!
you think we're
fucking entertainment?
fucking asshole!
oh, shit.
you think we're
fucking mtv?
get out of here!
back off!
yay!
come on!
what's wrong
with him?
whoa!
fuck, joey!
you don't do that!
what the fuck
am i supposed to do?
you don't do
those things!
take it easy, man!
go home and get
your head straight.
go ahead.
i'm sorry, tony.
oh!
jeez, i'm sorry.
i ruined you.
let me help you.
give me your bag.
put your hand
up here.
i'm really, uh...
i'm sorry
about that.
i didn't
see you there.
marie:
he looked promising.
can i give you
a ride somewhere?
maybe i could buy you
a drink--coffee, hot tea.
you could do
with some warming up.
marie:
he felt promising.
but his eyes were...
sad, so very sad.
my first rule--
never play with the food.
are you sure?
[engine starts]
[tires screech]
[honks horn]
do not touch the car.
do not touch
the fucking car!
marie:
this guy was perfect.
gee, i'm sorry.
don't hurt me, o.k.?
i--i just
got scared.
i could have got
run over.
thank god you've got
good reflexes.
you can really move
for someone so...
big.
look, we're getting soaked.
i'll give you a lift.
where you going?
gee, tony, this is
just so great of you.
i know it's a little
out of your way.
across the fucking
river.
all sinatra?
hey, don't start
on sinatra.
there's this park--
got a great view of the city.
you want to see
a great view, tony?
sinatra: dd that old black
magic has me in its spell dd
dd that old black magic
that you weave so well dd
dd icy fingers
up and down my spine dd
dd same old witchcraft dd
dd when your eyes
meet mine dd
dd the same old tingle
that i feel inside dd
dd and then that elevator
starts its ride dd
very nice.
dd down and down i go dd
hey.
dd round and round dd
hey, yourself.
i can tell
you're excited.
yes.
dd i should stay away,
but what can i do? dd
dd i hear your name,
and i'm aflame dd
not shy, are you?
dd aflame with such
a burning desire dd
dd that only your kiss dd
dd can put out the fire dd
come on, baby.
let's get in the back.
give tony a little room
to get into some motion.
come on.
dd i have waited for,
the mate dd
aah!
what are you,
some kind of a freak?
grrr!
aah!
dd round and round i go dd
dd in a spin dd
dd lovin' the spin
that i'm in dd
dd under that
old black magic dd
dd called love dd
marie:
my second rule--
always finish the food.
that means eliminating
the feed marks
and a central nervous system
disconnect.
[siren]
oh, that's o.k.
this one has everyone
a little spooked.
standard shotgun hit,
right?
nah. this guy's lost
a lot of blood.
yeah, well, he had
his head blown off.
this guy's really lost
a lot of blood.
it's not here.
decent amount of splatter,
but hardly what you'd expect.
blood should have settled
in his ankles,
turning them purple.
i'd say this guy's
about five quarts low.
what in hell
are you doing out here?
i was with tony
last night.
i heard he got hit.
any of these cops could be
in the mob's pocket.
the damn press is here!
he was a friend.
a friend?
he stood up for me.
without tony, i'd be in
a lot of trouble.
you're not
in trouble, gennaro.
you're gone.
it's over.
what?
i'm putting you
into protection.
morales!
you're kidding me.
mm-mm. you've been
under too long.
look, sinclair--
no. no.
save it, gennaro,
because i'm not listening
to you this time.
you are a danger
to this investigation
and to yourself.
i'm in
total control.
oh? coming here?
that cowboy stunt
last night with the van?
this asshole
was too damn close.
that's bullshit!
i was doing my job!
just get him
out of here!
you cannot
pull me out now.
it's absolutely
the wrong fucking time.
macelli will ask me
to make a hit.
i'm going to tape it
and nail the fucker.
i've lived with them
for three years--
eating, drinking,
stealing.
you've been sitting
behind a desk.
you come here and say,
"that's it. it's over."
it's all i fucking got.
all right. we got
your testimony, your tapes.
you'll get us
macelli, huh?
come on.
miss sinclair!
hi, guys.
this was the first time
my food made the front page.
hey.
thank you.
that fucking pig.
i knew he wasn't right.
sallie,
our problem is--
the problem is,
find joey gennaro.
put two behind
his fucking ear.
don't say that in front
of your attorney.
sinclair will come down
on you with the rico act
and freeze
your assets.
you're afraid
you won't get paid?
that's the least
of my worries.
i'm saying
make arrangements.
yeah. yeah. yeah.
what if i go
right here?
make arrangements,
that's what i'm saying!
make arrangements!
you putz.
who's this?
little girl got lost.
i figured
i'd take her home.
i got my ass
on the grill,
and you can't get
your mind off pussy.
jacko, ain't that the prick
from the papers?
[camera clicking]
yeah.
punch his fucking
lights out.
[tires screech]
ha ha ha!
you dress like a pimp
and talk like a goon.
what makes you news?
excuse me?
she's from out of town.
must be from mars
to talk like that.
nobody calls me pimp.
nobody calls me goon.
since i'm 16,
what people call me
is sallie the shark,
and i pick my teeth
with girls like you.
sal.
you're the dumbest
bitch i ever met,
but you got balls.
want a ride?
you got one.
i should have walked away,
but he annoyed me.
thanks, carmine.
you're wonderful.
maybe i got to
apologize.
my world's going to shit
at the speed of light.
puts me in a mood.
call me sal.
what do i call you?
marie.
oui,marie...
let's make up over
a little late supper.
i'd love a little
late supper,
but it looks like
we're not exactly
alone.
tell me about it.
my guys, the feds,
reporters.
probably some bastards
want to put lead in my head.
lenny, lose them.
the hideaway.
losing them, sal.
ok, stay on your toes.
take me about an hour.
right, sal.
where's the bag?
right here.
oh.
hey, come on.
all right.
come on.
[music plays]
sinatra:
dd i've got you dd
dd under my skin dd
what do you think?
dd i've got you dd
it's you.
i could do without
the bars on the windows,
but what are you
going to do?
the city--it's
a fucking zoo, right?
dd i've got you
under my skin dd
i was going to
eat this
with a colleague
from squirrel hill.
boy, is he
going to be pissed.
prepare yourself
for a little bit of heaven.
[gasps]
none for me, thanks.
hey,mangia, mangia.
you're a good-looking broad,
but a little
meat on the bones
never goes out of style.
mussels and garlic
from munafo's,
for christ's sake.
come on.
i--i do not eat fish.
you're a vegetarian?
ha ha!
well, this is mussels.
they're vegetables...
more or less.
ha ha ha!
uh!
i've got to...
hey, the bathroom
is over there.
this was a mistake.
uh!
oh...
eh...
baby...
anything i can do?
come on, baby.
relax, hmm?
you want to lay down?
uh...
garlic...
garlic
is hard for me.
you ain't italian,
that's for sure.
heh heh!
this light...
my eyes
are sensitive.
sensitive.
is everything
on you sensitive?
[breathing heavily]
hey!
don't play
mary virgin with me.
i look in your eyes.
you've been down
some dark alleys.
yeah. heh heh.
come on, bitch!
take a ride, huh?
mmm.
mmm. mmm.
oh, yeah, baby.
oh, yeah, come on.
yeah. oh, yeah.
oh, yeah. give it.
oh, yeah, give it.
grrr!
aah!
ah!
sal!
oh, god!
[gagging]
i know i'm a freak
to you guys--
half a crook,
half a cop.
my wife
thought that, too.
she left you,
didn't she?
you'd leave me, too,
if you could.
shh!
[suspenseful music
plays]
aah!
[knock on door]
shh!
uh! ah!
pizza man.
[ring]
yeah.
...myself.
i stand at attention!
name, dan quayle.
rank--
o.k. thanks.
[click]
look, when
things cool down,
you can start
all over.
this shit
won't cool down.
these guys will want
my head forever.
who died?
macelli.
he took a hit
on the north side.
shit.
you made him
look so bad,
his people took him out.
it's justice.
no,
this is impossible.
you still got plenty
of cases against his crew.
big cases.
shit!
excuse me.
i had you nailed,
you son of a bitch.
where's the blood?
pardon?
the carotid artery
was cut, right?
there should be blood
from wall to wall.
well, what
do you think?
my thinking is
the less i say,
the safer my pension.
you found something
under his nails, right?
hair? flesh?
traces of makeup?
perp was a female.
hmm.
what?
his temperature
should be dropping.
yeah?
it's going up.
poor sallie.
he wasn't
such a bad guy.
who was she, lenny?
who was she?
your mother!
come on. let's go.
come on!
you're dead.
you're already dead!
you're
a fucking whore!
break it up!
jesus!
sorry you lost
a client, bergman.
there's plenty
more scum.
compared to you,
my clients are
paragons of honor!
get off me.
get off of me!
[spits]
tape it over
to the west wall.
man:
watch your back!
[sirens]
watch your back,
please.
coming through here.
let us through.
shit!
[rustling]
grrr!
aah!
[tires squealing]
uh!
[panting]
grrr!
[door slams shut]
[breathing heavily]
[barking]
hey!
that's my dog.
oh.
[barking]
thanks.
aah!
ah! ah!
[glass breaks]
you are under arrest.
stay away from me
or i'll kill you!
god...
just when i thought
i understood some shit.
[grrr]
this him?
the big guy himself?
yup. he don't look
so big now, though.
just another hefty bag
enchilada, like the rest.
o.k. you can
take him up.
see ya.
[door opens]
[belch]
pardon you.
no, that wasn't me.
it was--
it was him.
it's just gas,
fella.
come on. 1...
2...3.
some nights there's
so much belching in here,
it's like being
in a ball park.
i'll see you later.
[click click]
uh!
what the hell
hospital is this?
this isn't a hospital.
ugh!
yeeaah!
yaah!
grrr! yaaah!
ugh!
well, stop him!
youstop him.
uh! uh!
oh!
i want a line out.
i want my lawyer!
hey, look.
why don't you
just lie down--
yaah!
come on, folks.
step aside, please.
step aside.
coming through.
all the way back.
right there.
that's good.
ladies and gentlemen...
you cannot rush
an autopsy.
as soon asweknow,
you'llknow.
macelli?
macelli's alive!
oh.
[bell rings]
damn it!
[crash]
oh!
aah!
[tires squealing]
[horn honks]
that's my car.
man:
petrelli with you?
[siren]
will you get this car
out of the way?
fuck!
move it!
what's the rush?
macelli's car smashed into
a gas station in shadyside.
what was the meat wagon
doing up there?
macelli was driving.
oh!
uh!
aah!
ugh!
stop!
i said...
ooh!
stop the fucking car!
aah!
ah!
how the hell
do i get to shadyside?
manny...
[glass breaking]
turn off
the fucking lights!
[muttering]
...find something
that appeals, god damn it.
son of a bitch!
i'm fucking dying here.
sallie, maybe you
ought to sit down.
no, no. i'm
not sitting down.
i ain't lying down.
last time i laid down,
a fucker tells me i'm dead!
some prick stuck
a thermometer in my kidney.
it must have healed.
it's ok, sal.
it's ok.
let me get you
that drink.
hey...you smell.
oh, i'm sorry.
i'm sorry.
you smell good.
sallie!
we got to talk.
everybody thinks
you're dead--
the cops, the press.
that's right.
it's a fucking plot.
yeah!
somebody tried
to whack me--
the gambinos,
the feds.
they laid me out
in the morgue.
they tried to
saw me in half.
you got to call
a press conference!
you got to sue
those cocksuckers.
[sniffing]
huh...
sallie?
[sniffing]
i was warming this
for you.
sallie!
sallie, what
the hell happened?
crazy bitch.
she fucking bit me.
we got to get you
a doctor.
mmm!
no, i'm fine.
i just got
this appetite.
mmm.
i'll call a couple
of the boys.
grrr!
[horn honks]
you are
in deep shit, lady,
really deep shit.
you're the one that
blew tony silva's head off
and took macelli out.
i'd appreciate it
if you would drive.
who do you work for?
self-employed.
you do this for fun?
for sport?
you do this
for the blood?
you're a cop.
where's your cop radio?
this isn't
my cop car.
i wish you hadn't
jumped on it.
sorry.
macelli's not dead,
is he?
why are you
after him?
to kill him?
why didn't you make
sure he was dead
the first time
you killed him?
[distorted voice]
i fucked up, o.k.?
don't tell me
it never happened to you.
what in hell are you?
i'll find out
where macelli is.
jesus, joe!
macelli's here?
he's alive?
should i
cuff him?
cuff her, for christ's sakes,
but be careful.
she's fast,
and she's strong.
she's the one
who got macelli.
she's a goddamn freak.
she chomped macelli
in the neck
and drained his blood.
she blew tony's head off
to make sure he stayed dead.
look, guys, i'm aware
of how this sounds.
flinton,
be careful. get out!
where'd you find her?
at the church
outside macelli's.
she can climb--
joe, shut up and
listen to yourself.
you got such a hard-on
for macelli,
you figure
whoever iced him
had to be some blood-
sucking superbitch.
i know this whole thing
is crazy.
how did macelli
drive the car?
as far as
i'm concerned,
the medical examiner's
a moron,
and macelli is one
dead son of a bitch.
what happened
to your car?
she, uh...
she jumped on it.
ha ha! god.
put him
in the car, dave.
oh, man.
you'll help me now?
yeah, yeah.
she's got him
eating out of her claw.
you stay put,
or the cuffs go on.
i mean it.
calling me a killer?
the whole time,
he'sdriving
like a maniac!
i mean,
look at this car!
this is unit 5-3.
i need a home address
in shadyside
for a mr. emmanuel bergman.
he's an attorney.
this guy is a cop?
well,
he's been suffering
from job-related
stress lately.
it's about
7 blocks up.
thanks.
sir, could you let me
powder my nose?
oh, yeah. sure!
absolutely.
go ahead.
i am dracula.
oh...
it's really
good to see you.
i don't know
what happened
to the driver
and my luggage
and...
well...
and with all this,
i...
i thought i was
in the wrong place.
i bid you welcome.
[wolves baying]
listen to them.
children of the night.
what music they make!
i swear on my mother,
he was dead,
and this ain't
no improvement.
dracula: a spider
spinning his web
for the unwary fly.
blood is the light,
mr. renfield.
[sniffing]
gennaro.
what about
gennaro, sal?
he's here.
what do you mean,
sal?
they probably
stashed that prick
in an underground
bunker somewhere.
dracula:
you'll like it.
renfield:
aren't you drinking?
dracula:
i never drink...
wine.
hey, sal,
wait a minute.
no, sallie!
don't, sallie!
no, sallie, don't!
the boys will
check it out!
jesus christ!
everything all right?
stevie, uh...
gennaro split.
fuck!
i don't need this.
mmm.
sal! sal!
sal! oh, my god!
don't, sal!
don't kill him here!
boys, boys, help!
help!
sal, listen to me.
you're losing it.
don't murder a cop
on my lawn! sal!
forgive me, sal.
you've got to get
ahold of yourself.
come on.
come inside.
please.
can you believe
this cocksucker?
show up here, huh?
where's the gun?
oh, he's got cuffs!
let's cuff him.
you see, sal?
now that you're inside,
you're in
an excellent situation.
no blood.
even if the cops came
with a search warrant
to talk to macelli,
i'd tell them to get
a ouija board
because he's dead.
there's nothing in
the fucking constitution
clearer than freedom from
unreasonable searches,
and this isn't unreasonable,
it's demented.
the government can't
pronounce a man dead
then invade his home
looking for him.
you really
whacked me,
but there ain't
no blood.
what a guy, manny.
hey, sallie!
manny, i...
i need you.
sal, come on!
you always do for me.
do for me, manny.
it's o.k.
it'll be o.k.
[distorted voice]
do this!
aah!
aah...
woman in movie: the walls
around are bare,
echoing to our laughter,
as though the dead
were there.
man: ha ha!
nice little sentiment!
but there's more,
even nicer.
quaff a cup to
the dead already.
ah-choo!
oh, never mind
the rest, dear!
that son of a bitch
is heavy!
dracula:
to die, be really dead...
that must
be glorious.
woman:
why, count dracula!
there are far
worse things...
awaiting man...
than death.
manny?
aah!
out light!
you killed him.
nah!
ha!
resting.
he's dead.
they said i was dead.
i ask you--am i dead?
[gasps]
i got this tingle.
there's something
you can do for me.
aah!
this shirt is disgusting.
this fat bastard.
come on!
what's he got,
lead in his ass?
1...2...
3!
ugh!
please! help me!
god! god, please help me!
my manny!
manny, manny, manny!
lenny!
lenny, look!
please help me!
please! help me! help me!
help me!
oh, here's sal!
sal!
come on!
hurry the fuck up.
oh, god, somebody help me!
why don't you help me?
help me!
stop! please stop!
oh!
please stop the car!
help me!
he killed my manny.
he ate my manny!
he wha--he--he...
he killed my manny!
he ate manny!
radio: steve, what's
happening? you find joe?
for christ's sake,
will you talk to me?
come on!
ugh!
i'm going to grind you
down to blood...
and screams.
hey, joey, we're going to
take this nice and slow...
so why don't you
take your shoes off,
get comfortable?
whoa! hey, come on!
no, stop!
hey, come on!
sal, this is going to get
all over my coat.
[crack]
i want him alive!
hey! hey!
stop, for christ's sake!
son of a bitch.
would you please
help me in the car?
he shot my fucking foot!
oh, shit!
if you had just
left him to me,
i would have stopped him
before he fed.
now he's 100 times
more dangerous.
who did macelli eat?
some guy named manny.
an innocent person dead
because you screwed up!
manny bergman?
he wasn't innocent.
he's a lawyer.
maybe he's not dead.
maybe i have to
finish him, too.
or what?
he becomes like macelli
or becomes like you?
macelli's
nothing like me.
he's a cold-blooded
killer.
and what are you?
yeah.
[horn honks]
[horns honk]
hey!
jesus christ!
heh heh heh heh!
what the hell you doing?
we're on his ass!
it's over for now.
you two want a room?
yes.
no!
you know what
macelli was.
i know what
he's become.
if we stick together,
we can find him.
i could find him
right now.
just help me get out
of these cuffs.
try that little
key there.
macelli's
got to get inside.
we should do the same.
you look beat.
you look a little
drained yourself.
i'm fine.
you lost a lot of blood.
are you sure
you don't need more?
don't worry.
you're not my type.
aah!
what is this shit?
what the fuck?
gee, mr. macelli.
i never seen you here
so early.
is there something wrong?
mr. macelli, you want
i should, uh, call somebody?
this is good.
leave me alone.
shut the door.
but you're
in the freezer--
get out!
hit the fucking lights!
yeah, ok.
yeah, in my cold storage!
he's got a rump roast
for a pillow!
thank you.
we have a deal?
we'll be staying
till sundown--7:17 p.m.
she insists
it was macelli
and that joe gennaro
was loaded
into the back
of macelli's limo.
then find them--
macelli and gennaro--
and you better hope
gennaro's still alive.
oh, fellas. try not to
lose your car this time.
yes, ma'am.
dr. kivowitz says
you'll be fine, manny.
you just need
a transfusion.
mr. bergman, we know
macelli did this.
he also tried
to assault your wife.
can i count on you
to press charges?
bergman?
you're ok.
you're going to be fine.
you've been in there
a long time.
you having trouble with
that deep-down clean?
i thought you'd be
asleep by now.
dream on.
i'm trusting you to see
i don't get any sun.
can i trust you?
it's kind of
a one-way street,
this trust thing.
you can trust me.
right.
my eyes are sensitive.
i know you're good, joe.
a good man.
i see that.
i feel that.
yeah, well, see this,
and feel this--
get the fuck
away from me.
i won't hurt you.
just get over there
on the bed.
chicken shit.
sleep tight.
hiya, bill.
g'day, haynes.
you better win
at southampton tomorrow.
park these in
a lucky spot
for a few hours.
[beeping]
[alarm sounds]
[alarm stops]
aah!
my god!
fuck!
aah!
[bed creaks]
we have to go.
i can't.
now's the time
to get macelli.
he's sleeping.
he will sleep
if he's not disturbed,
but his senses
are razor-sharp.
he can wake like that
and move like this.
aah!
you need me, joe.
you really do.
i can't do this.
what happens when
you get excited?
pretty much
as usual, joe.
yeah, but
maybe you bite.
right now, i need this
more than blood.
[unzips zipper]
face it...
you trust me.
at least, partially.
still a little
worried here.
how can we
stop this worry?
think i can have
your name now?
marie.
where is everybody?
close the door!
lenny, what's
the fucking emergency?
what happened to you?
someone shot me
in the foot.
why?
what's going on,
lenny?
he had me call you,
said it was
something important.
frank, ray,
listen to the guy.
look at the guy!
tell me if it's not time
to pass the torch.
you got
macelli in there?
i'm just saying,
look at the man.
hiya, boys!
sa--sallie.
how you feeling, boss?
oh, i feel
fucking fantastic!
[fly buzzing]
i can hear an angel fart.
i heard you, lenny.
sal.
come over here.
come here. come on.
yeah.
[laughs]
lenny...
i loved you...
like a brother.
you son of a bitch.
aah! stop!
no! aah!
grrr!
[distorted voice]
don't you fucking move!
put lenny in the trunk
and get me
some clean clothes.
yeah.
you must help me
find macelli,
and when we find him,
we kill him.
understand?
let's go.
[engine starts]
voila.
hey, guys,
want to party?
open the trunk.
we're in the middle
of the street.
open the trunk.
think
what you're doing.
open the fucking trunk.
jesus.
lenny.
huh?
yeah.
come on, lenny.
easy. come on.
[laughs]
hey, easy, lenny, easy.
i'm not going to
hurt you.
you're family now.
can you help me?
grrr!
[laughs]
come on, lenny.
[music plays]
dd get off dd
dd let a woman be a woman dd
dd and a man be a man dd
dd get off dd
dd if you want to, baby,
here i am dd
dd here i am dd
dd i got the jazz dd
dd from a friend of yours
named vanessa dd
yeah! yeah! yeah!
hey! hey! hey!
dd a fantasy that
got her all wet dd
dd some in the bottom,
little box rhythm dd
you look good enough to eat.
dd after you say
i can... dd
awoo!
whoa! can i help
you gents?
sallie?
i heard you was...
so listen, sallie,
i hope you like
remy martin,
'cause horse just
sent us over 50 cases
from a truck
they jacked on 95.
take a dozen...
two dozen!
would you tell tommy
to get over here?
yeah.
you got it.
dd he was thinkin' of sayin'
we could continue outside dd
dd let me throw your body
against the parking meter dd
dd i want your dress down dd
dd i got to see your
peter paul's almond joy dd
dd let me show you, baby,
i'm a talented boy dd
dd grab a partner dd
dd grab a partner... dd
frankie,
is sal o.k.?
oh, yeah.
he's a fucking peach.
come on.
yeah.
[laughing]
boys...
you don't know how big
this is going to be,
but it's going to be
fucking amazing.
you're going to be
made men.
but when you're made by me,
nobody can touch you.
so fuck the gambinos.
they think there's a war,
but it's over.
and fuck the colombians
and the jamaicans, too.
the macelli family...
we're going to take
this town.
grrr!
aah!
aah! aah!
frankie...
welcome to the family.
aah!
he's not here.
those guys swell up
like roosters
when he's around.
i brought vinnie.
boys...
i want you to meet
frank and ray.
but, uh...
we know frank and ray.
you don't know them...
like this.
grrr!
he's not in bloomfield.
let's try the melody
lounge downtown.
ok. let's go.
let's go.
dd sexitivity dd
dd what you really need dd
dd get some sexitivity dd
dd satisfy your need dd
dd sexitivity dd
dd makin' all of you good dd
dd get some sexitivity dd
dd makin' you by the book dd
dd everybody, say yeah dd
dd whoa-oh-oh dd
he's here.
he's upstairs.
dd well, let me
hear you say dd
dd yeah dd
excuse me, honey.
hey, come on, man.
hey, shut up.
shut up.
freeze!
on the floor now!
they're
on something.
where's macelli?
anywhere
i want to be.
aah!
oh, shit.
closed.
hey. hey! hey!
closed!
where's macelli, gus?
you...
the scumball cop.
i don't know
where sal is.
you leave your address,
and i'll make sure
he looks you up.
i ain't even breaking a law
if i break your head.
i'll swing on you.
i'm a girl.
some girl.
[laughing]
uh!
whoa!
[distorted voice]
i'm going to eat your face
like a chicken.
grrr!
[muffled yelling]
[click]
aah!
[growling and yelling]
[crack]
[yelling]
grrr!
you broke
my fucking teeth!
[crack]
[yelling]
don't!
shoot her, joe!
shoot her!
will you
fucking shoot her, joe?
she's ok.
she's a fucking monster!
she's one of them!
she's with me.
yeah? joe...
joe, you all right?
yeah.
where's macelli?
he's here somewhere.
he took the other guys
out of here.
we got to get out here.
call backup. tell them
what we're up against.
i'll try, man.
i will try.
we got the muscle.
we got the hunger.
we'll crack this town
like a lobster.
let's call it a night.
[click]
ha ha ha ha ha!
yeah.
hey...
little girl...
i got a question
for you.
you gave me something,
and i like it.
why did you
give me this thing
and then
try to shoot me?
well, sallie...
i'm pretty fucked up
about men.
uh!
you know,
i might actually
miss you.
[gunshots]
uh!
i'm ok.
get him.
heh heh heh heh yeah!
get him!
[speaking italian]
ah ha ha!
[honking]
jesus!
grrr!
no!
fuck!
hey, man!
i'm sorry!
where the fuck
did you learn to drive?
come on.
heh heh heh heh heh!
yeah.
hey, you fuck!
you think
you can kill me?
ah ha ha!
what you killed here
is my fucking suit!
i am the power!
you fucking cockroach!
i...
am the light!
am...
macelli!
marie.
no!
where are you going?
to watch a sunrise.
you don't want to die.
i died
a long time ago.
joe! don't make me
hurt you.
i love you.
come on.
[siren]
i take lives.
yeah, well...
if you
were perfect...
you wouldn't
still be single.
he made me feel...
alive.
and i thought...
[rings bell]
why not?
dd goin' out
to all the sexy girls dd
dd oh dd
dd summertime dd
dd oh, oh, yeah dd
dd doo doo doo doo doo doo
bah bah bah bah dd
dd uh-huh dd
dd whoo! dd
dd go, go, go, go dd
dd oh dd
dd oh, listen to me, girl dd
dd this is an open invitatio
n to a party dd
dd and you're the only one
i'm gonna invite dd
dd 'cause i've been
sittin' here dd
dd watchin' you moving
your sexy body dd
dd and there's no way
you're goin' home tonight dd
dd your legs and your hips,
your lips dd
dd your eyes
could tell a story dd
dd you got it goin' on
from head to toe dd
dd and on the subject dd
dd i ain't speakin'
with much authority dd
dd so here's a simple thought
i'd like you to know dd
dd i wanna make,
i wanna make love dd
dd i wanna make sweet love d
d
dd i wanna make love to you
dd
dd a-you dd
dd oh, yeah dd
dd i wanna make,
i wanna make love dd
dd i wanna make sweet love d
d
dd i wanna make love to you
dd
dd a-you-ooh-ooh dd
dd uh! dd
dd let me begin by tellin' you
what i have to offer dd
dd i'm a creative lover
like you never have known dd
dd so once i get
a girl going dd
dd you know, there's just
no way to stop her dd
dd she'll need my lovin'
like a doggie needs a bone d
d
dd givin' it to her
like this dd
dd and you know that i'm
givin' it to her like that d
d
dd i'm makin' her tell me dd
dd evan, you're the best
i ever had dd
dd and when i'm done dd
dd she won't know
whether she's comin' or goin' dd
dd don't you think
it's time? dd
dd now, baby, baby,
let me know dd
dd i wanna make,
i wanna make love dd
dd i wanna make sweet love d
d
dd i wanna make love to you
dd
dd whoo! dd
dd over and over
and over again dd
dd i wanna make,
i wanna make love dd
dd i wanna make sweet love d
d
dd i wanna make love to you
dd
dd a-you dd
dd yeah! dd
dd go, go, go, go dd
dd that's right dd
dd go! dd
dd go, go, go, go dd
dd a little bit to the right dd
dd so i can hear you say dd
dd a little bit to the left
dd
dd you know that i'm
makin' you say dd
dd i'm thinkin'
you want some more dd
dd 'cause now i hear you say dd
dd you're down on your knees,
and you're begging me please dd
dd and it's better
than all of your fantasies d
d
dd i wanna make,
i wanna make love dd
dd i wanna make sweet love d
d
dd i wanna make love to you
dd
dd a-you dd
dd over and over and dd
dd i wanna make,
i wanna make love dd
dd i wanna make sweet love d
d
dd i wanna make love to you
dd
dd i'll say it over and over
and over again dd
dd whoo! dd
dd i wanna make dd
dd love to you,
love to you dd
dd i wanna make love to you
dd
dd over and over
and over and over dd
dd and over and over
dd and over
and over again dd
dd go, go, go, go dd
dd oh! come on! dd
dd i said i wanna make,
i wanna make love dd
dd i wanna make dd
dd i wanna make love to you
dd
dd yes, i do dd
dd i wanna make,
i wanna make dd
dd i wanna make love, yeah d
d
dd i wanna make dd
dd i wanna make love to you
dd
dd i'll say it over
and over again dd
dd yeah, yeah-ah dd
dd go, go, go, go dd
dd ooh, ooh, ooh-ooh dd
captioning made possible by
warner bros.
captioning performed by
the national captioning
institute, inc.
576x368 23.976 1.52.52 wersja
>> Napisy pobrane z http://napisy.org <<
>>>>>>>> nowa wizja napisw <<<<<<<<