Subtitles ripped by tiger6ex
(c) BitShock.org TEAM
Let's do it.
Look, those are the guys
that robbed me.
Kill those fucking bastards.
Please forgive me for not paying you on time.
What are friends for.
Give me a hug...
God be with you!
-Thanks
Yes, lndio?
Bury him.
No! No!
-No!
-Take it easy, take it easy.
Calm down boy.
Don't do anything foolish that can
bring you trouble with the law, ok?
This marchandise is for Chicago, right?
-Yes, sir.
Finish loading.
Please leave us.
Yes Chilango.
How easy.
-Not that easy
but will be fun.
-We'll have to kill a bunch of people.
-Sir... this motherfucker was
getting high with the ladies.
Did you like it?
-Yes.
-Did you take anything with you?
-No.
-What the hell is this?
-l'm so sorry...
l didn't mean to...
-No, Chilango, wait.
No, Chilango...
Please, people.
...the management.
Please help me.
Care for a lap dance, Darling?
Count me in.
-Watch out, motherfucker.
-Motherfucker my ass.
-Oh, really?
-Want some?
-l don't smoke, thank you.
Look, Jefe.
But l have a little present for you...
Kill everybody.
As you say.
What a hit.
but they have to be hitmen.
Cheers brother.
What happened to you now?
l got in a fight with Raúl Baeza's friend.
-The guy who lost his parents.
Let me see...
l was distracted.
Welcome gentlemen.
Come in, please.
...dark skin, tall ones, short ones.
Raúl, come with me.
-Anything else sir?
-Stay put, just in case.
Don't act stupid with me.
-Who is it?
Come in.
How much?
El Chilango will be
contacting you tomorrow.
Very good...
Do you like it?
-Yes of course. ls it all for me?
Gentlemen
l have good news for you...
the boss sent you a
retirement fund
-Motherfucker.
-He's a fucking cheater.
Oh damn.
Of course, man
And l think it's that asshole Mon.
We're already paying him a
lot of money.
Fucking bastard.
You farted again, didn't you.
-No, man, it's the same one
from before. lt was hiding bro.
Let's go, let's go.
l have the money.
Let go off me, asshole
-Let go off her, asshole, let go off her...
Darling, come here...
Come here, don't be afraid.
She's yours. Talk to her.
-l'm fine.
-Good?
Well, l was with one of the DEA agent
the day before yesterday.
Then this lndian shows up
and leaves a bunch of money.
Thanks guys.
No, man...
Be careful man. Make sure you
don't get robbed by some guys.
Don't worry, they'll be in for a surprise.
Take this to the Asesino.
Take care.
Hi Baby.
Here.
You're not charging me with anything?
Fucking bitch.
Where do you think
you're going, bitch?
Rot in hell.
Throw her in front of the
''Conejo Loco.''
Bring me some Tacos. l'm hungry.
l want 3 Pork Tacos.
-That's all?
- No, no, no. Make that two.
l'm on a diet.
-What's up, bro?
l was on my way home
when l found Diana dead.
The stripper, on the street.
Where? ln the street?
Yes, in front of the ''Conejo Loco.''
l already killed that bitch.
l don't give a shit.
Are you blind or something?
-Sorry. sorry, sorry...
-You hit me!
-Excuse me
Don't you know how to drive?
-What happened here?
- You stay out of this, man
Asshole...
Take it easy.
Listen Bishop.
You're here for you own protection...
As soon things chill out,
you can go. Ok?
Come on, be a good boy.
Come on...
Come in
Commander...
-Bring me Bishop
-Yes, boss
He'll be here soon.
Hi, Darling
Answer me...
Where were you?
Get out of here!
Asshole!
Let's toast.
Why Chilango?...
He lost a hundred thousand.
l don't trust that guy.
Sir, this is Bishop.
The Police Chief...
-You'll have a bad time
What happened with Chilango?
He had some business to attend.
Here's Bishop.
Or you'll end up the same
way as your parents.
Get in there!
-That guy is very tough.
-Yeah.
And his wife fucks like an angel.
Fucking lndian!
Hey Raul. Chilango and l
have a business plan for you.
We'll talk about tomorrow, ok?
Come on in guys, come on in ...
lndio, take care of the wagers.
Stay out of this.
come on Tin-Tin.
Relax.
What's the matter with you?
... supports us?
...makes me lose a lot of money.
on my side...
Let me know if he gives you trouble.
Excuse me, sir?
Would you like to buy a chewing gum?
Get out of here, girl!
!Shit!
But we'll need some help,
these guys are very powerful.
l don't give a shit.
lt's that simple.
Once Juarez is mine,
l could raise the prices as l wish...
2:30pm, at the bank downtown.
at the border...
They just called.
The deposit will be made soon.
Bishop escaped.
Jefe, find the General.
l have a job for him...
You'll pay for this.
l should kill you now, bitch...
but no...
Let's do it.
Look...
Kill those fucking bastards.
There they go those motherfuckers.
Take this, motherfucker!
Motherfuckers!
Give me the bazooka.
Let them go.
We'll come across with them again.
Let's go.
Do you want some advice about women?
They're all the same shit.
Oh women... it could be your girlfriend...
your wife...
...fat, skinny, chubby, tall...
They're all the same shit...
Never get married.
That fucker is here.
Long time...
How are you, Raul?
Where's your friends?
They're on there way. l spoke with them,
they just left the airport.
You bring the merchandise?
Yes
Here's Carlos.
You farted again, didn't you?
Serve us the usual, Darling.
Please take a seat, Carlitos.
You don't know how much fucking
money you blow in this place.
l'm going to the bathroom.
Hey...
Remember... more than three shakes
becomes a jerk-off.
lt's hot like hell, bro.
We're just hanging out, chief.
lD.?
ls this helpful?
Fucking shit...
Stubborn like a motherfucker.
Of course.
Fucking bastard...
What are you looking at bitch?
Your pretty fucking face.
Pick it up...
.. You stain my shoes, fucker.
troublemakers.... l'm going to check you.
l already gave you your tip,
you fucking dog.
You're both together on this, aren't you?
lsn't that right motherfuckers?
You ldiot!
l'll be the man!...
No, no, no. l don't want details.
Take him to the ranch.
Send Raul's head
to Bishop under my name.
Yes, sir.
Good.
We buried him to his neck and
drove the truck over him.
That boss, and his crazy ideas.
And Raul?
They already decapitated him.
l sent them his head
to send a clear message
Dont't worry, Chilango. l'll give
that order to all. l'll take care it.
Remember everyone...
l'll see you at 2:00 pm.
at the ''Centro Histórico.''
Let's go guys, all to your cars.
Oh, shit!
Scram kid!
He even left it dirtier.
Take care.
Well look at that.
Go that way.
Chilango, your delivery is here.
Bishop's little present. Bring it over.
Ok
Fucking bastard!
Bishop? Come out, Bishop.
Hi, pretty girl.
Subtitles ripped by tiger6ex
(c) BitShock.org TEAM