DJ [ON RADIO]: Welcome back, folks.
This is Gotham Talk Radio.
Give us a call at 555-7630.
Tonight, I promise, we're not going to
talk about President Luthor's impeachment.
Instead, I wanna switch gears...
... to Gotham's new fleet
of automated surveillance blimps...
... which took flight earlier this week.
Are these unmanned eyes in the sky
a black eye on people's privacy?
[HISSES]
That's what civil liberty groups
are saying. What about you?
Before we get to your calls,
here's headline news. Vicki?
VICKl: A.J., blimps aren't the only sights
we've been seeing these last few nights.
A rash of meteor showers has lit up
the skies from coast to coast this week...
... following the destruction of a giant
kryptonite asteroid by our own dark knight.
Today, NASA officials, who have been
monitoring the situation...
... say we've seen the last
of these shooting stars...
... since most of the kryptonite debris
has moved beyond Earth's orbit.
Meanwhile, there's been no comment
from Batman...
... who seems to have gone back
into seclusion.
This morning in the nation's capital...
... Superman completed his deposition
for the impeachment hearings.
He hoped the removal
of President Luthor...
... would usher in a new era
of peace and tranquility.
[ELECTRICITY BUZZING]
DJ: From what we gather, something
has come down near Gotham harbor.
Let's take some more callers.
MAN 1:
It was unbelievable.
It lit up my bedroom
like the middle of the day.
WOMAN 1:
There was this big boom...
... and then the whole apartment
just started shaking.
I was so scared.
MAN 2: Huge fireball.
My neighbor said it fell in the bay.
WOMAN 2:
Had to be a meteor, right?
I mean, what else could it have been?
[GRUNTING]
[BEEPING]
Hey, check it out.
Well, hello, beautiful.
You getting a little fresh air?
[SPEAKING IN KRYPTONIAN]
Whoa, whoa. Slow down, honey.
What is that, Swedish?
Hey, Gus, I think she likes you.
Come on, sweetheart. Let old Gus give you
a private lesson in foreign relations.
[BONE SNAPS]
[GUS SCREAMS]
Hey, lady. Gus may be a jerk,
but you shouldn't have...
[YELLS]
Lady, I didn't have nothing
to do with them. Here, take it.
It's all I got. I swear.
[PANTING]
GUS:
Hey, man, you okay?
[GROANS THEN GASPS]
Tell me what happened.
[YELPS]
[HORN HONKING]
Lady, are you all right?
[SIRENS APPROACHING]
[GUNS COCK]
[GRUNTING]
Bring her down.
[GUNSHOTS]
[CROWD WHISPERING INDISTINCTLY]
Enough.
[BOTH GRUNTING]
[YELLING]
[CROWD SCREAMING]
[SOBBING]
[SPEAKING IN KRYPTONIAN]
I don't know who you are,
but you've had enough fun for one night.
[GROANS]
[MACHINES BEEPING]
Her DNA is definitely not human.
Enhance.
Extremely high concentrations
of neural stem cells.
[GRUNTS]
[SPEAKS IN KRYPTONIAN]
[BOTH SPEAKING IN KRYPTONIAN]
Her name is Kara Zor-EI, from Krypton.
She's my cousin.
Your cousin just torched $50,000
worth of custom hardware.
- Send me the bill.
- On a reporter's salary, right.
SUPERMAN: "This vessel contains
my daughter, Kara Zor-EI...
...from the now dead planet Krypton.
Treat her as you would your own child.
She will prove a treasure for your world."
Treasure. You're sure of the translation?
It says treasure. Not terror, not trouble.
Always the cynic.
You can't help yourself, can you?
You know those tests I was running?
Her cellular structure
is a shade more dense than yours.
She metabolizes sunlight
more efficiently.
It could be her youth.
It could be something else.
Bottom line,
she might be more powerful than you.
It makes me wonder.
So does her sudden appearance.
I find it just a little too...
[BANGING]
[SPEAKING IN KRYPTONIAN]
BATMAN: Speak English.
KARA: It's attacking.
What's attacking?
That.
Krypto. No.
[KRYPTO BARKING]
Bad dog.
Kara's a friend. Leave her alone.
I'm sorry, l...
I've tried to get him to like me,
but he just barks and growls, he hates me.
Go up to your quarters.
But I didn't do anything wrong.
We'll talk later.
[KRYPTO GROWLS]
Krypto's just feeling a little overprotective.
Aren't you, boy?
I don't know. I've always considered him
a good judge of character.
Look, she's been through a lot.
Not to mention learning
an entire language in less than a week.
- Why don't you cut her some slack?
- We don't know anything about her.
She claims to have no memory of anything
prior to splashing down in Gotham Bay.
I'm not saying there aren't loose ends.
Having no control over her powers
is more than a loose end.
She's dangerous.
Which is why she's in quarantine
until she can gain control.
She may be the only blood relative
I have left.
I'm willing to give her the benefit
of the doubt, at least for the time being.
You don't have a problem with that,
do you?
No problem at all.
But I can't speak for the dog.
[GROWLING]
[BIRDS SHRIEKING]
[CREATURE ROARING]
[CHIRPING]
Spying on me now?
You don't like me, do you?
Huh. It's you that has the problem.
Why can't you leave me alone? You'll
never understand what it's like to be me.
Then explain it to me until I do.
Does any of this help
fill in your memory lapses?
KARA: Some. I know that's my Uncle Jor-El
and my Aunt Lara.
Because Superman, Kal-EI, told you.
No. Because I remember.
Uncle Jor-El was like my father.
They both believed
the planet was doomed...
... which is why my father
also built a ship.
He told me the navigation system
was locked onto Earth...
... and that he and my mother
would soon follow.
I was just about out when...
[RUMBLING]
I saw them die, right before my eyes.
And then there was that light,
that awful, blistering light.
Then, all I remember is darkness.
The rest you told me.
How the asteroid carried me
across the galaxy...
...until it broke and I landed here.
Do you remember your mother's name?
You know I don't.
Why don't you trust me?
Kal-El has enemies who would go
to great lengths to destroy him.
You think I would hurt my own cousin?
Perhaps not intentionally.
KARA: I sensed your presence earlier
because I thought I heard your heartbeat.
I was wrong.
You have no heart.
GRANNY: My Treasure, you are one
of the finest warriors on Apokolips.
But do you really think you have what
it takes to be captain of the honor guard...
...to the almighty Darkseid?
Bring them forth
so they can taste my blade.
Furies.
[GRUNTS]
[ALL GRUNTING]
This one was no match for us.
Let the dogs clean up the mess.
DARKSEID:
You disappoint me, Granny Goodness.
You led me to believe Treasure could
replace Big Barda as captain of my guard.
She showed such promise.
There has been
an interesting development on Earth.
Bring me the girl
who fell out of the sky.
The one they call Kara.
And this time don't fail me.
Or it will be you, dear Granny,
whom the Furies carve up next.
[SHRIEKING AND WAILING]
[HORNS HONKING]
[BIRDS CHIRPING]
KARA: I'm so glad to be out of quarantine,
I can't tell you.
Don't get me wrong,
I like the Fortress of Solitude.
But you have to admit,
it is a little boring.
Metropolis is much more my style.
This is the life I want, Kal. Uh...
I mean, Clark.
You've got plenty of time to decide.
I wanna know everything there is to know
about being an Earth girl.
Where do we start?
I have a pretty good idea. Come on.
Whoa!
KARA:
Ready?
Ta-da!
Well?
Uh, no way.
Perfect. I'll take it.
[CRUNCH]
Oops. Heh-heh-heh.
Oh, my gosh. That was so much fun.
I'm going to love being an Earth girl.
You've certainly got
the shopping part down.
Are you hungry? I'm starving.
- They're not really made out of...?
- No.
That's so good.
Well, that's it.
Shopping, junk food...
I'd say you're a bona fide Earth girl.
It's so beautiful here.
Not like that other city
where Grumpy Ass lives.
Grumpy Ass isn't so bad
once you get to know him.
What's his problem anyway?
He just wants you
to take things a little slower.
Adapting to a new culture,
any culture, can be difficult.
Is that why you wear those eyeglasses,
as a way of adapting...
...even though you can see better
than anyone?
It's a way for those of us who are heroes
to have lives without the cape.
It's important to keep
our identities a secret.
That's why Mr. Friendly never takes off
his lead-lined cowl.
You noticed the lead. I didn't know
your x-ray vision had kicked in.
You didn't ask.
Oh, my.
This is how they see you.
Bigger than life.
You're their champion.
These powers.
- Do you ever regret having them?
- No.
Not even a little?
Can I tell you something?
You can tell me anything.
They terrify me.
I mean, the responsibility.
I don't wanna be anybody's champion.
- No offense.
- None taken.
- What is it?
- Stay close.
- Guess it was... Unh!
- Kal.
[GRUNTING AND GASPING]
Help me. Someone, anyone.
Kara.
[GRUNTING]
WOMAN: We were told you would try
to stop us, but we're taking the girl.
She's not going anywhere.
[WOMEN YELLING]
WONDER WOMAN:
It may not seem like it now...
...but this is for your own good.
You.
I'm sorry, but it has to be this way.
BATMAN:
She's right.
I don't understand.
Look around.
What if this had been the middle of the day?
The park crowded with people, children.
She needs more specialized training.
I'm taking her with me.
And what if I say no?
There's another reason she can't stay.
I'll explain later.
For now, I'm asking you to trust me.
Kal, you're not gonna let her
take me away, are you?
I'll work at controlling my powers.
I promise.
Kal.
[METAL CLANKING]
[GROANS]
[KNOCKS]
AMAZON:
Lyla, hurry.
Kara is going up against Artemis.
LYLA:
Be right there.
Ready when you are, Artemis.
Ready.
Go.
[BOTH GRUNTING]
What's the point of this?
Kara could level the entire island.
Having power and knowing how to use it
aren't the same thing.
You of all people should know that.
She's getting on my nerves.
I heard that too.
Now, little one, prepare... Unh!
Don't touch her.
Kal, it's a training exercise.
She wasn't going to hurt me.
Is there a problem?
You asked me to keep an open mind?
Well, I've kept an open mind.
But Kara belongs in Metropolis with me.
We agreed this was in her best interest.
Wait a minute, don't I have a say?
- No.
I'm sorry, of course you do.
But you've been hidden away
on Paradise Island for two months now.
You don't know
what the rest of the world has to offer.
Who else is suited to decide
what's right for you?
How about me?
You let them bring me here...
...and now because you have a problem
with it, you want me to return?
I'm tired of being jerked around,
treated like a child.
From now on,
I'll decide what's best for me.
Come on, Lyla.
Let's go before someone tries
sending me to bed without dinner.
Don't ever do that again.
You looked like you were ready
to snap Artemis' neck.
Harbinger's visions show Kara in danger.
How do you expect me to react
with a sword to her throat?
I expect you to be rational.
- Bruce.
- No.
Ever since this girl came into our lives,
you've let your guard down.
Even exposed your secret identity
despite common sense.
Unlike you, Bruce,
I don't look for the bad in everyone.
You may think I'm naive...
...but my every instinct tells me
this girl is my cousin.
She's done nothing to show me otherwise
and she'll be safe with me.
Clark, the visions are getting worse.
KARA: I know Kal is only trying
to protect me, but he's making me crazy.
And everyone pretending to know
what's best for me. Agh!
I thought I knew what I wanted,
but now...
...I feel more lost than ever.
Kara, when I first came here,
I was confused too.
Able to see into the past, the future...
...yet not having a clue
what to do with my own life.
A harbinger for everyone but myself.
Diana took me in without hesitation.
If you need someone to turn to,
you can trust her.
You've all made me feel so welcome.
Especially you, Lyla.
I feel like you're the only friend
I have right now.
- Kara.
- What is it?
Nothing. I'm just glad we're friends.
Hey, how about a swim?
I could use a little cooling off.
Maybe we should get back.
Kal will be worried about you.
Come on, one little swim.
You're not afraid of the water, are you?
SUPERMAN: Are you telling me
these visions are about to become a reality?
- Lyla believes so.
- But she hasn't given us a lot to go on.
Which is why it's just as well
we keep Kara in the dark.
So we just keep waiting?
This is the safest place for her, Clark.
I've had my army standing by.
I can call them up anytime.
[BOOM IN THE DISTANCE]
Now might be good.
Doomsday.
[ROARS]
Protect Kara, I'll handle this.
Wait, the tube.
It isn't closing.
SUPERMAN:
Darkseid. He's replicated the monster.
Then we draw a line in the sand
and hold them here.
WONDER WOMAN:
Batman.
[DOOMSDAYS ROARING]
Well?
Did you come here to sightsee or fight?
Amazons, attack.
[AMAZONS YELLING]
[ALL YELLING AND GRUNTING]
There's no blood.
Something's not right.
Wait a minute.
SUPERMAN:
Diana, pull your army back.
- What?
- Do it.
Amazons, fall back.
This ends now.
[GROANS]
SUPERMAN:
I had no choice.
They weren't truly alive.
No blood, no minds.
You did what you had to do.
Where's Batman?
BATMAN:
The Doomsday attack was a diversion.
A second tube opened here.
There were four, maybe five.
She didn't go down without a fight.
Kara.
Lyla.
She died trying to protect Kara.
I swear that her death will be avenged.
I'm going to Apokolips.
That's exactly what Darkseid wants.
Then I won't disappoint him.
You mean we won't disappoint him.
KARA:
Let me go, you witch. Let me...
[SMACK]
[KARA GRUNTS]
GRANNY:
Shut up.
See?
Granny has your room all ready.
Don't worry, baby girl,
you won't be alone for long.
Enjoy the accommodations.
[INSECT CHITTERS]
[KARA YELPS]
DARKSEID:
You may feel powerless now...
...but soon you will watch the fear
in men's eyes.
As captain of my Furies your fame
will spread throughout the universe.
You will see the fiercest warriors
flee your presence.
Armies brought to their knees.
Entire nations crumble
at the mere mention of your name.
You will know power
you would've never known on Earth.
Never again will you be lost.
From now on you will be at my side.
Forever mine, forever Darkseid's.
BOY:
Over here, come on. Over here, I'm open.
When I said drop in anytime,
this isn't quite what I pictured.
Hello, Barda.
Diana. You didn't leave, like,
an invisible plane in the driveway, right?
We need to talk.
Can I get dressed first?
BATMAN:
You were captain of Darkseid's honor guard.
I defected.
Was it easy? No.
But for the first time, I'm free.
And this...
This nice, quiet, boring little life...
...it's all mine.
We need your help, Barda.
Darkseid has kidnapped my cousin, Kara.
Then she is lost to you.
I'm sorry.
SUPERMAN:
Barda, you can't just...
Listen to me, it's too late.
Darkseid will control her mind.
Mold her into a killing machine.
Exploit her weaknesses.
Just like he did me.
Barda.
We know you were made
to do terrible things.
No one blames you.
Now he's got Kara, my cousin.
We're going to Apokolips.
We need your help to get there.
You have no idea what you're up against.
All we ask
is to borrow your Mother Box...
...so we can generate a boom tube
to get there.
BARDA: It sounds as if you think
you're coming back.
We'll get back.
BARDA: There are no exits
from that inferno, Superman.
The entire planet is a deathtrap.
It was a mistake to come.
If Barda refuses to help, how are we...?
BARDA:
I'll help you get to Apokolips.
On one condition.
I'm going with you.
- Barda.
- No way.
I know Darkseid's fortress
like the back of my hand.
You need me, so get over it.
I'm over it. What about you two?
No place like home.
Smells like death.
You think Darkseid knows we're here?
He knows.
[GRUNTS]
[BOTH GRUNTING]
[ALARM BLARING]
[GRUNTING AND GROANING]
Well, I guess that warmed us up.
We've gone over the layout of
Darkseid's fortress. We all know our jobs.
[METAL CLICKS]
Stay sharp.
Good luck.
I guess we'll take the low road.
After you.
[BEEPING]
This might not be the right time, but
you've always been an inspiration to me.
- Barda.
- Seriously, Diana.
When someone brings hope
to another person, it's a gift.
And growing up in this hellhole...
Where you grew up, Barda,
is where you will die.
[LAUGHING]
Well, well, the gang's all here.
You should never have come back, Barda.
Although, personally,
I look forward to watching you die.
I'd tell you to go to hell, Gillotina...
...but given the situation,
that'd be redundant.
They'll go for position,
try to separate us.
Let them try.
Furies, destroy them.
[BEEPING]
- Damn.
- Bring the intruder's head to Darkseid.
[ROARING]
Glory to the one
who takes the life of the Kryptonian.
Hail Darkseid.
[ALL GRUNTING]
- They're very good.
- They should be, I trained them.
[BATMAN GRUNTS]
Great.
Okay, boys, chew on this.
[RAPID BEEPING]
[SCREAMS]
[GRUNTING]
[GROANING]
[BEEPING]
Bingo.
Hellspores.
Enough power here to blow a hole
straight to the planet's core.
[ROARING]
Darkseid.
Kill them.
[GROANS]
- Thanks.
- Don't mention it.
Diana.
Nice try.
Let's see you smile now.
GRANNY:
Surrender, Amazon.
- Barda.
- Surrender now, or the bitch dies.
No, Diana, let them kill me.
Never surrender.
[GRANNY CHUCKLES]
Imagine how pleased Darkseid will be.
Why settle for some girl
who fell to Earth...
...when I can deliver to him
the champion of the Amazons.
[LAUGHING]
Darkseid.
Kara leaves with me.
She's free to leave,
if that is what she desires.
Kara?
Hello, Kal.
- Kara.
- I'm fine, Kal, really.
I don't know what he's done to you,
but the nightmare's over.
You're safe now.
You're right, she is safe now.
Let's go home.
That's the problem, cousin.
I'm not sure where home is.
You're just confused.
I'll be back. You and I have unfinished...
You didn't listen to what Darkseid said.
- Kara.
- You never listen to anyone.
[BOTH GRUNT]
[SUPERMAN GROANING]
He said I was free to go, if I wanted to.
And I don't want to.
Good. Now kill him.
I won't fight you.
Good. Makes my job that much easier.
[BEAST WHIMPERING]
What's wrong with the beast?
SENTRY:
Must be something he ate.
Take off your armor.
Now.
Let me kill her, Granny.
[BARDA GRUNTS]
No, it's me you want. Let her go.
I like to have my cake and eat it too.
Make her bleed.
[ALL GRUNTING]
[GASPS]
You were saying, Granny?
Go ahead. Kill me.
- That's what you're programmed to do.
- Barda.
What's the matter, Barda?
You know you want to.
[SUPERMAN GRUNTING]
All these years of pretending to be human
have made you soft.
Kara, he's controlling you. Fight it.
Do not hesitate. Kill him.
As you wish, Lord Darkseid.
[KARA GRUNTING]
With your death, cousin,
my life begins here on Apokolips.
Not if I can help it.
[SUPERMAN YELLS]
Darkseid said
you wouldn't be up to the challenge.
That your feelings, your beliefs,
would cloud your judgment.
He's right, you know.
Earth does need a new hero.
Not his version.
You think killing me will set you free?
He's just using you.
Liar. He cares about me.
No, Kara, I care about you.
But you won't listen.
His control over you is total.
I see that now,
which is why I have to do this.
BATMAN:
It's over, Darkseid.
Even you must realize the folly
of being a king without a kingdom.
I doubt the battle between the Kryptonians
will bring about such destruction.
I'm not talking about them.
Your armory, the hellspores,
they've been activated.
DARKSEID:
Impossible. The arming code is encrypted.
I broke the code
and reprogrammed them.
You're bluffing.
Omega lambda 7- X-L-9.
That sound like a bluff to you?
One hellspore can turn an entire planet
into a fire pit.
What will happen to Apokolips
when 500 go off simultaneously?
You dare? You dare?
[GRUNTING]
I could destroy you with a single blast
of my omega beams.
You could.
But that wouldn't stop the hellspores,
would it?
You will disarm them.
Here's the deal.
Release the girl and give your word
you'll leave her alone.
Forswear Kara Zor-EI.
Say it.
Well played.
Had the Kryptonian or the Amazon
taken that gamble, they would have lost.
They do not have the strength
of character...
...to destroy an entire planet
to achieve success.
But you, a human?
You kill your own kind to win battles.
An admirable quality.
Take the girl.
I will make no move against her.
[GRUNTING]
SUPERMAN:
I'll hold you to that.
WONDER WOMAN:
We'll all hold you to it.
[GRANNY GRUNTING]
Mercy, Barda? Disappointing.
Disarm the hellspores.
Leave Apokolips.
[GROANS]
Hey.
KARA:
Am I dreaming?
What happened?
I don't remember anything after...
Lyla.
You're safe now.
It's nothing. Just a scratch.
I remember dreaming,
a horrible nightmare.
All I wanted to do was get home.
I did terrible things.
Darkseid lives for manipulation.
He has hypnotists,
scientists and sadists...
...whose only functions
are to break your spirit.
Darkseid is evil.
But did he influence me?
Or just bring out a darkness
that is already there?
You're here with me.
And you're okay. Nothing else matters.
You said to me once
you didn't wanna be anybody's champion.
When you're strong,
there's somewhere I want to take you.
Where you can be safe.
Where you can fit in.
Where you can just be yourself.
You're sure it's a good idea?
It feels right.
- Can't let it rest, can you?
- Knock it off, you two.
Lyla.
I'm going to miss you more
than you can even imagine.
You were my first friend
and you accepted me without question.
Maybe because as Harbinger
you saw something in me that's worthwhile.
Now, all I have to do is find that thing.
I'll try not to disappoint you.
Diana, I can't thank you enough.
You will always have a home here.
Alura.
You once asked
if I could remember my mother's name.
It was Alura.
Kal, I'm ready now.
- Thank you.
- You still owe me a computer.
Might take a while. Reporter's salary.
Always has to have the last word.
[GRUNTS]
Welcome to Smallville.
KARA:
This is where you grew up?
It's not so bad.
No, I didn't mean...
It's just so different
compared to Krypton.
Even Metropolis.
[CHICKS CHEEPING]
I think I'm going to like it here.
It can be a little quiet.
Kal, I've been chased,
shot at, kidnapped...
...beaten up,
had my mind controlled and I broke a nail.
I'm ready for a little quiet.
If I know my mother, she'll have some
of her famous apple pie waiting.
You okay?
Little nervous, I guess.
It's just, you have this life.
You can be Clark, or Kal-EI,
or Superman.
Even a son.
Who am I going to be?
I can't answer that, Kara, only you can.
Whatever you decide,
I'll be there for you.
I promise.
Now, come on.
Let's go meet the folks.
[SUPERMAN GRUNTS]
[KARA GRUNTING]
I gave my word
I would not come for the girl.
Your death, however,
is long overdue, Superman.
[SCREAMS]
Kal. Unh!
Kara, no!
Stupid girl.
You murdering...
[YELLS]
Time to die, Man of Steel.
Darkseid.
[BOTH GRUNTING]
There's more where that came from.
Fearless. Untapped power.
It would have been a glorious life for you,
captain of my honor guard.
Instead, my omega beams
will reduce you to ashes.
Take your best shot.
[DARKSEID YELLS]
Impressive.
Under my guidance, you could have become
the most powerful being in the universe.
Your life here
will be nothing in comparison.
But it'll be my life.
We will meet again, Kryptonian.
You didn't think
you could just walk away, did you?
Don't ever come here again,
or you won't be going back.
[SCREAMING]
[GROANS]
That should give him something
to think about back on Apokolips.
Apokolips? I'm not so sure.
While you were busy...
...I took the liberty of reconfiguring
the boom tube's coordinates.
Something Darkseid taught me...
...that I'm guessing
he's probably regretting about now.
I don't think he'll be a problem again.
Not until someone
thaws him out anyway.
Kal, there was a moment there
when I thought you were dead.
And I realized, ever since I arrived...
...I've been running away from who I am
and what I'm meant to be.
I've made a decision, Kal.
I know what I want to do.
[TRUCK APPROACHING]
SUPERMAN:
Uh-oh.
Mom, Dad, this is Kara.
My cousin? Your niece?
Mr. Kent, Mrs. Kent.
It's so nice to finally meet you.
I've heard so much about you both.
Don't worry,
I can build you a new one.
I can help. I'm great with a hammer.
I can pound.
I'm a good pounder.
[CHICKEN CLUCKS]
I know how busy you all are...
...but it's only appropriate
that you should be the first to hear.
You, who would put your lives
on the line for a perfect stranger.
We're all alike, for each of us,
in our own way...
...had to struggle to become who we are.
But what better role
for anyone to aspire to, than hero?
So allow me to reintroduce my cousin,
Kara Zor-EI.
Or as the world
will come to know her, Supergirl.
To be honest, I'm not sure
I've earned the right to wear this uniform.
But I will.
[AMAZONS CHEERING]
SUPERMAN:
Hey.
[KARA GIGGLES]
[ENGLISH - US - SDH]