- Common marker.
- How about me, James?
- You're doing great.
- Thanks, James. Thanks.
- Mark.
- Well, I've...
All right, serious Lex.
Serious Lex. Here we go.
All right.
I'm twitching.
Right there.
This time a little better.
Go ahead, Kristin.
- Whoa!
- A little smaller. Here we go.
- Sorry. Okay.
- Here we go, here we go, and...
Manage to prove it.
The other sheriff may have looked
the other way.
I'm sorry.
It was good up to there, wasn't it?
I just wanna say
that I'm really sorry, and...
This really sucks.
Hold on, let me do this again. Sorry.
I came here...
Fuck yourself.
I came here to tell you I talked to...
Don't laugh. Keep going. We're good.
I came here to tell you
I talked to Walden.
I'm not laughing.
I came here to tell you I talked to...
Just can't get it.
Tom's killing me.
All right, here we go.
You're killing me.
Put your arm around me,
you son of a...
I came here to tell you
I talked to Walden.
He won't budge.
You wouldn't be keeping secrets
from me...?
Is that really me? That's never
happened before. I'm so sorry.
Excuse me just for a second.
Hey, I love you.
It's our music.
That's very embarrassing.
Perfect timing, dude.
Sure, son, we're an alien race,
but this alien...
That's not right. Flawed.
It's okay, I can pull it together.
I'm falling over.
That depends...
If I make a mess or not.
Shit! We didn't have to cut.
- Yeah! You know what?
- Not that.
You know what, you...? Get out of here,
you punk! Get out of here!
I just... This is good.
Really.
It's Alison Sanders.
Yeah, Alison Sanders.
- Whoa!
- Cool!
- All right.
- Let's do it again.
He may go to Smallville...
...High.
Hi.
- Jonathan.
- Tom. Good to meet you.
Nice to meet you.
That really cute guy that works
at the phone company.
You mean, the Hungarian guy
with the toy scooter.
Oh, shit.
And I'm tired of watching
every little nick and...
- Cranny.
- Nook and cranny.
Don't fuss.
Damn it!
- Are you all right, sweetie?
- Yeah.
Let me get some of that.
And cut.
What the hell are you guys
laughing at over there?
- You have hair in your face.
- I always do.
- There's nothing I can do about it.
- We could...
They're just pieces. You put them
all together in the editing room.
Yeah.
Father! Hello, Daddy.
- B mark.
- How would you like to consider a...?
Do you believe in ghosts?
No.
- Damn!
- Cut. Print.
You're weird.
Dr. Walden, you're confused.
I won't let anyone stop me.
Cut.
And cut.
I can't look at him. I can't...
Antagonized... Oh, damn it.
I seem to recall a young man
who defied his father.
I remember a certain young man who...
This has to be a certain temperature.
Now I have to be serious. Here we go.
And set.
Holy chocolate starfish...
...Batman.
Mark.
- Does it hurt?
- Not now.
Shit.
Sorry, dude. I had to do it once.
Maybe some of us wanna celebrate
the day you came into our lives.
I never thought of it that way.
Make a wish.
It's hot.
- One second.
- Okay.
I'm sorry.
- Cut.
- Did you hear the...?
- I'm sorry.
- And cut.
Cut.