It's not a threat. I just can't do
my work under these circ...
You knew the drill
when you signed on.
This is the third planet where
I can't find decent clientele.
Sorry to cut into your retirement fund.
Would it kill you not to spread for a spell?
You are unreal.
I don't know why
I haven't left already.
Well, no one's forcing you to stay.
I'm a big girl, just tell me.
None of it means a damn thing.
This is just an object.
It doesn't mean what you think.
- You know that's not to be touched.
- Stop yelling at her.
River, I'm sure you
want nothing to do with that.
Put it down.
What were you thinking?
Where'd you get that?
- Don't yell at her.
- Just let me... Thank you.
Fully loaded, safety off.
This here is a recipe for unpleasantness.
Does she understand that?
She understands.
She doesn't comprehend.
I'm glad we've made that distinction.
No touching guns.
Okay?
No touching.
- River.
- It's getting very, very crowded!
I thought she was on the mend.
Her medications are erratic.
There's not one her system
can't eventually break down...
If I want a lot of medical jargon,
I'll talk to a doctor.
You are talking to a doctor.
Yeah. Okay. My point is...
...it could have been you she shot,
the doctor...
...as you just made note of.
And who, exactly, could fix you?
Not nobody.
We're deep in space,
corner of no and where.
You take extra care with her...
...because we're very much alone
out here.