(thunder crashing)
(whirring, zapping)
[Woman]:
George, what are you doing?
[George]: The crazy neighbor next door
is up to something.
Come on, Zeus.
Let's go check it out.
(thunder crashing)
I'm telling you, buddy, ever since
we moved into our new home...
some weird things
have been happening.
(whines)
You know I have issues about going out
in thunder storms, right Georgie?
Oh, I know.
Let's go back inside...
'cause "The Real House Puppies
of Beverly Hills" is about to start.
Come on, buddy. You're not afraid
of a little thunder storm, are you?
Me? Afraid?
Come on, us Bannister men
got to stick together.
Okay.
(thunder crashes)
(groans)
You owe me a big steak
for this, George.
All right, back me up, buddy.
Back me up.
Back you up?
Who's gonna back me up?
- (thunder crashes)
- (Zeus screams)
(whining)
Can't we just come back
when the storm's over?
- Please?
- It's okay, buddy. It's okay.
I got a bad feeling about this.
Seems like there's someone
in there, buddy.
That's great.
Let's go. Come on.
(thunder crashes)
- Thunder! Aaah!
- Zeus, come on.
Zeus!
Zeus! Zeus!
(squeaking)
Bats!
(barking)
- Oh! Ah!
- [Zeus]: George, watch out!
- Cover your head.
- I hate this, I hate this, I hate this!
Ah!
I can't look.
[Woman]:
George, is that you?
Zeus, Zeus, I can't see.
I can't get this off my head.
Man:
Who's making all that noise
[Woman #2]:
Sounds like the new neighbor.
[Woman #3]:
Bruno, what are you doing?
[Bruno]:
I want to see what's going on.
Georgie, look out
for the tombstones.
Ow, ooh, my brain.
I'm coming, George.
- (growling)
- Georgie, look out.
- No!
- Medusa.
You tell that idiot
to stay out of our yard.
Oh yeah?
Well, I'm a former K9
and I smell probable cause.
(exhales)
I'm sorry, Georgie.
I heard the thunder and it scared me.
Oh, well, that could have
gone better.
Um, you might want to turn around.
[Woman]:
Ahem!
(yawns)
- [Man]: I don't believe this.
- [Woman]: Unbelievable.
Oh, hey, honey.
Did you get a haircut?
- Oh, George.
- Moron.
(thunder crashes)
¶ I was having a party
on Halloween ¶
¶ When some ghostly things
came to visit me ¶
¶ With chains and fangs
and bandaged heads ¶
¶ I couldn't tell
if they were live or dead ¶
¶ Boo, said the ghost,
aah, went the vampire ¶
¶ Awoo, said the werewolf
on the full moon rising ¶
¶ Zombies were moaning,
ghouls were groaning ¶
¶ No one's ever gonna
believe this story ¶
¶ Then when I saw
what happened next ¶
¶ I must say
I was quite perplexed ¶
¶ As I was sure
they would all eat me ¶
¶ But instead they came in
to join the party ¶
¶ Boo, said the ghost,
aah, went the vampire ¶
¶ Awoo, said the werewolf
on the full moon rising ¶
¶ Zombies were moaning,
ghouls were groaning ¶
¶ No one's ever gonna
believe this story ¶
¶ Boo, said the ghost,
aah, went the vampire ¶
¶ Awoo, said the werewolf
on the full moon rising ¶
¶ Zombies were moaning,
ghouls were groaning... ¶
[Woman]: George,
we've only lived here two months.
Do you know how hard I have worked
to try to get everyone to like us?
Looks like someone's in
the dog house now, Georgie.
Belinda, has it ever occurred to you
that maybe I'm trying
to protect this family?
You know, it's not like we moved out
of state. We moved three blocks.
I'll do better next time, George,
I promise.
It's just I was scared by the thunder
storm and the lightning.
I don't know what came over me.
It's all right, buddy.
It was probably just an accident.
Besides, something
did happen at that house.
- Did you actually see anything?
- Yeah, I did.
You know, a little bit.
I don't think a little bit
is gonna hold up in court.
- Eat your cereal.
- But what about that strange noise?
Oh, and that creepy light
coming from the attic.
George, you've got to tell her.
You've got to tell her.
Mom, my stinger fell off again.
Kara honey, I've already
sewn it on three times.
What kind of a bee
doesn't have a stinger?
A dead one.
Honey, just leave it here
and I'll sew it on again later, okay?
Ricky Jameson said he's lucky
no one called the cops.
Smooth move there, Pops.
Oh, be nice to your father.
You know what? Tell Ricky Jameson
to mind his own business.
- Ow! Ben!
- Sorry.
What have I told you about playing
with this in the house?
Hey, Dad, check it out.
I made some modifications.
- Oh yeah? Pretty cool.
- You see that?
- Here, let me show you.
- Ooh, what's that?
Zeus.
Hey, come here.
Come here, you. Come here.
Stop torturing the dog.
Cut it out.
Okay, look look look.
Take that thing upstairs.
You get dressed for school.
Take off your wings.
And then come back down
and have your breakfast, okay?
You know, I'm not even hungry either.
I'm just gonna get up and go to work.
(groans)
Jeez.
Be careful, George, or they're gonna
put a cone on you.
You are not going anywhere
with that leg.
Sit down.
Just call the office
and tell them that you need
the week off.
Sweet. It'll be you and me,
Georgie, all day long.
We can play fetch.
You can rub my belly.
Give me extra doggie treats.
Just try not to make a mess around
the house while you're here, okay?
Because Friday is our Halloween
housewarming party
and it's our last chance to make
a good impression on the neighbors.
- Okay.
- All right.
And stay out of trouble, you.
Yeah, you hear that?
- Honey.
- Yeah?
I was talking to you.
- Oh, okay.
- Busted.
- Bakaw.
- Stewey.
- What?
- Put the egg down.
- I'm hungry. It's an egg.
- Stop it.
Leave it alone.
We're gonna get in trouble, okay?
We've got to make a good impression.
Let's go.
Here she comes.
All right, let's see.
We've got Ted Stein
and Stewey McMan.
Aren't you just precious people?
Two counts of breaking and entering,
two counts of attempted theft,
two counts of animal endangerment.
I don't even want to ask
what that's about.
One count of vandalism
of public property.
- Quite the resume.
- Thank you.
Hey, what's wrong with you?
Um, Miss...
is it Miss or Mrs.?
Miss is just fine.
Miss Cloverfield.
I just want you to know
that Stewey and I
are very very happy to be here.
Thank you very much
for giving us this chance.
And, uh, we plan on becoming very
productive members of society.
We thank you so much
for this opportunity.
And might I add you look
very beautiful today?
Well, let's get one thing
perfectly clear, twinkle toes.
I don't like you.
I didn't like you
before I came in this room.
I didn't even like you
before you were born.
I'm not even sure
I like your mother.
So what we're gonna do,
we're gonna start all over again.
This is gonna be a fresh start
for the both of you.
You will complete
the work release program.
Every single step.
And if I'm lucky I will make upstanding
citizens out of the two of you.
Otherwise it's back to prison
for both of you.
And I don't mean
just a year this time
because this is my world, baby.
And in my world characters
pay for their crimes.
Do you have that?
Now got that out of the way.
Have I got the perfect assignment
for the two of you.
(squishes)
(dogs barking)
Thanks, Ted.
Look what you got us into.
Jackpot.
Barbeque, my favorite flavor.
Thank you, my friend.
Know what goes with this?
- A can of cola.
- One cola coming right up.
Oh, do I got him trained.
Okay, here we go.
Just a little tug here.
Pull it and bingo.
Thanks, buddy.
What do you think?
"Chappy" marathon?
No wife, no kids, no work.
Sounds good to me.
There we go, share the love.
This is the life, baby.
One for you.
- Absolutely.
- One for me.
Love it.
Mmm, keep 'em coming. Let's go.
- Let's have a contest.
- Oh, I'm on. Let's go. Down.
Here we go.
Best day ever.
Eh, how much TV can I watch?
- How many chips can I eat?
- What is it, Georgie?
How about some fresh air?
(engine starting)
This is so much fun.
I want to try.
That is the coolest thing
I have ever seen.
What?
I am hurrying.
Uh, G-George, no no no.
Not Mr. Weagle.
No no, don't... whoops.
- What the...?
- What the heck?
- Oh!
- Oh! (laughs)
- (growls)
- Hey, honey.
Bannister!
Sorry, my bad.
Why don't we go inside?
(grunting)
[Cat]:
He shouldn't cry over spilled milk.
What's happening
to this neighborhood?
I told you
we should have moved.
- Hey, G-man.
- Look what the cat dragged in.
Ah, what's up, Max?
Well, nice work last night,
waking up the whole neighborhood.
Maybe the whole town.
Way to impress
your new neighbors, duh.
Don't you work for a living?
Oh come on, G-man.
You know I make websites at home.
What a nerd.
Which reminds me,
if the missus needs to hit me up
for a website,
you just give me a jingle.
Give her a discount.
- Okay, yeah.
- We'll be sure to let her know.
So...
did you get a look at what
was going on up in there?
No, why?
Come on.
Guy's been living there nine months,
no one knows anything about him.
Nothing.
No one knows anything?
Is he living there alone?
Yes he is.
With that creepy dog of his.
Creepy?
More like psychotic.
If you ask me,
I think he's a mad scientist.
The postman tells me
he gets these
mysterious packages,
some of them
marked hazardous.
You see, George?
You see?
I told you I had
a bad feeling about him.
I mean, who knows what kind of weird
experiments he's performing up there?
You know, with...
eight-legged pigs
or flying gerbils.
Flying gerbils?
It's not too late to move again,
is it, George?
Ugh.
He could be up there
right now.
Right now?
- (car approaching)
- What?
One. Two, three, four,
five, six.
Look, Mother.
It's that creepy neighbor.
- Honey.
- What?
Look.
Come on. Come on.
What?
Who's that?
It's him.
(barks, growls)
It's her.
What is that?
I don't know.
I'm telling you, Georgie.
This guy is bad news.
Those aren't dog biscuits.
Well, uh, listen, I...
I've got to go.
There's a special one-hour
"Judge Jimmy".
I can't miss it.
Good luck.
And he wonders
why he's still single.
I'm telling you, Zeus,
I don't know what's going on,
but something's afoot.
I think so too, Georgie.
I think so too.
Rusty, what's up, dog?
Hey, kid, want to play?
Look out, ladies.
Oscar is on the prowl.
Hey, that's mine.
Get back here.
Finders keepers.
I know I put that bone
in here somewhere.
I'll get it.
(panting)
I'm gonna...
I gotcha!
(muffled)
I got it! I got it!
[Ted]:
Sanitation? Yoga?
You've got to be kidding me.
We should have just stayed in prison.
Over here.
I've got a fresh one for you.
I swear those dogs
are watching me.
- (whining)
- It's all in your head, Stewey.
It's not in my head, Ted.
I don't like dogs.
I can swear they're watching me with
those brown little beady eyes right now.
Of course we're watching you.
You're an idiot.
- Get out of here.
- Why don't you make me, tubby?
- Shoo.
- This is our park.
I can't stand those dogs, Ted.
The feeling's mutual, pal.
Stewey, I was reading
my book and it says
that we are stuck in what is called
a self-destructive cycle.
Listen, Ted, I can't go straight.
You understand me?
I've tried to go straight before.
I can't do it.
Relax, Stewey.
- Nobody's going straight, okay?
- All right.
We just have to find a way
to break the cycle.
Push back a couple years
of bad karma.
And then... foom...
we're on easy street.
Easy street.
They got Chinese food on easy street?
They got burritos on easy street?
- Probably.
- Well, you'd better make sure.
'Cause I'm sick of this, Ted.
I've been out a half hour,
you got me cleaning stuff,
you got me picking up dog poop,
you got me picking up garbage.
I can't do it no more.
You got me sweating up a storm.
Look at this, I'm sweating.
- You understand me?
- Ew.
- You got a little... you got...
- What?
- (stammers)
- Did I get it?
- Yeah, you got it.
- Where you going?
I'm talking to you.
I can't go clean.
I can't do it.
What's that smell?
(sniffs)
Ted! Come back here, Ted.
Ha, and they call me fat.
Aren't we a little too old
to be carving pumpkins?
Ben, this is a Bannister
family tradition.
I did it with my dad,
he did it with his,
and now I'm doing it with you.
What about me, George?
Don't I get a pumpkin?
Can't we do something fun?
Let's break out the Ouija board.
Absolutely not. It's not good
to mess around with that stuff.
Not with All Hallows Eve
just around the corner.
There's no such thing as ghosts,
right, Mommy?
- Of course not, sweetheart.
- Sure there are.
No, honey, there's no such thing
as ghosts.
Don't worry, Kara.
He's just pulling your paw.
(laughs)
Aren't you, George?
Okay.
Zeus, the lights please.
Oh boy.
Here we go.
- George.
- What?
What are you doing?
I think it's time Ben and Kara
knew about the story
- of the hook man of Halloween.
- The what?
I don't think that's a good idea.
- It was a cold and quiet night.
- George.
Much like the one tonight.
Your mother and I
were going out on a date.
Don't listen to him, honey.
We ran out of gas and broke down
just outside of town.
But it was right next
to the railroad tracks.
Choo choo.
And as your mother and I
sat quietly in the car
we heard a noise.
It was a thump and a thump.
(stomps)
And we thought it would get
further and further away.
And did it?
No.
It got closer and closer
with a thump and a thump.
(stomps)
Then I heard a noise.
It was metal on metal.
(whines)
And as I looked
outside the window,
- I saw...
- What?
- I saw a hook!
- (screams)
(shouting)
- George!
- What?
You have just scared her to death.
She's gonna have nightmares now.
Belinda, it's a Halloween story.
- George.
- Good going, Dad.
Ben, come on.
You love Halloween stories.
This whole family
has got to get in the mood.
(sighs)
Zeus, it wasn't that bad, was it?
I'm sleeping in your bed
tonight, George.
(wolf howling)
[George]: All right, buddy.
Let's make it quick.
It's cold out here.
Oh, George, look.
Something's going on next door.
[George]:
What's going on?
Who would have thought of getting
a delivery in the middle of the night?
Okay, so the mail guys
got new uniforms?
(burbling sound)
Maybe it's new equipment
for his experiments.
I don't know.
That's not normal.
Okay, Georgie, we have to
tell somebody.
Yeah, let's go tell Belinda.
Let's go.
Belinda, I'm telling you,
they had this van that pulled up
and these guys in robes came out
with this equipment.
And they were taking it out of the van
and bringing it to the creepy house.
Honey, it sounds like they were just
getting a delivery of some kind, okay?
I'm gonna go to sleep, okay?
You know Weird Max?
He said that the mailman told him
that this guy
is some kind of scientist.
- George.
- Yeah?
[Belinda]:
So what if he is a scientist?
[George]: Yeah, like a crazy,
spooky Copernicus scientist.
George, I can see...
that you have completely
overreacted to the situation.
You have already completely
terrified your daughter.
Do you really want to make it worse?
Yeah, I think our daughter
should be terrified.
It'll thicken the Bannister skin.
There is some crazy stuff
going on over there, Belinda.
I'm telling you, it happened.
Okay. Okay okay.
Honey, it happened.
I believe you, okay?
Now unlike you I have to get up
and go to work in the morning.
So I'm gonna go to sleep, okay?
(claps)
(thunder crashes)
(electronic humming,
zapping)
(cat screeches)
[George]:
Honey, listen to this.
Two high-voltage electron generators
were stolen...
from the Seaman Neck power plant
late last night.
- Hmm.
- You know what I'm thinking?
Maybe that's what those guys
were carrying up to the house.
I knew he was no good.
Two high-voltage
electron generators.
- You know what that means?
- George.
- They have enough power to...
- Enough power to do what, Daddy?
Didn't you ever see "Frankenstein"?
Enough power
to get one of those
ultra powerful hairdryers
like your mama wants.
Sweetheart, you just eat your breakfast
and don't listen to your father
because sometimes
he says crazy things.
I'm telling you,
this guy is up to no good, Georgie.
We got to be on high alert here.
Oh!
- Can I come in?
- Sure. Over there.
Something wrong with the doorbell?
- Hi.
- Hi, Monique.
I hope I'm not intruding.
[Belinda]:
Oh no, not at all.
Can I get you some cereal?
I know.
How about some pants?
[Monique]: No thanks.
No. I'm not gonna stay.
I just wanted to find out
if any of your had seen Rufus.
Something happened to Rufus?
- Is that a cat?
- Yes.
A very beloved cat.
He's been missing since last night.
Last night?
Huh.
Kent said he saw him playing
with you-know-who's dog after supper.
But he didn't answer the door.
I don't think he's a people person.
Wait, the neighbor's dog?
Uh-oh.
Anyway, if you wouldn't mind,
I'd appreciate it if you'd
show these to anyone
who might know where my poor
defenseless little pookie-poo is.
Sure thing, Monique.
Thanks.
- Bye, George.
- Bye, Monique.
Oh, goodness.
Well, that poor thing.
She just really loves
this little cat.
Sure hope she finds him.
Yeah well, probably dead
and buried in someone's yard.
What was that?
I just said that the coffee
is very good
and that Rufus is probably running
around someone's back yard.
Oh. Well, good.
You can just keep your eye out
for him while you're recuperating.
Oh, honey.
Watch it.
That's the bad leg.
- And promise me...
- Yeah?
no more snooping around
the neighbor's yard.
[George]:
Okay, let's see what we've got.
Wow, these toys are a lot fancier
than when I was a kid.
You're telling me.
My toys just squeak.
Okay, Eli Cole,
show me what you're up to.
[Zeus]: So what do you see,
Georgie? Anything?
All right, we got a bogie
in the southeast perimeter.
Man,
look at the security system
this psycho has.
(beeps)
Uh, what is that in the ground?
Looks like his dog likes to dig,
I'll tell you that.
[Zeus]: Yeah, those would be some
pretty big bones there, George.
All right, let's check out inside,
see what we got.
What is that?
That doesn't look like a recipe
for candied apples.
I want a turn, Georgie.
Let me look.
[George]:
What the heck?
"Countdown to zero hour"?
That doesn't sound good.
Where the heck did he go?
Whoa, how you doing?
(laughs)
Hi, how are you?
I. Uh... sorry.
I'm bird watching.
Little hobby of mine.
Nut job.
You think he bought it?
Well, if something's gonna
go down in two days,
we're gonna have
to get inside, Zeus.
Uh, George, you mean you actually
want to go inside the house?
Now remember, Mommy,
I want to go to every house
in the neighborhood this year.
Don't shortchange me
and my candy, all right?
Nice outfits.
Love the color.
Ted, how come we can't go
trick or treating?
You really want to risk our freedom
for a little bit of candy?
It depends.
What type of candy they got?
Remember when I told you about being
stuck in a self-destructive cycle?
Ted, you're starting to scare me
with this self-help stuff.
Do you really think it's our destiny
to be stuck here
picking up trash and dog poop
for the rest of our lives?
No.
So we've got to break
the cycle.
I got plans. Big plans.
You've got plans, right?
You still want to open up
your little butcher shop
- right there on the beach, right?
- Yeah.
Okay, so we finish Miss Cloverfield's
stupid little program,
we're on the first flight to Daytona
and we'll hook it up
with Tony Rowe.
No more picking up dog poop.
No more picking up
dog poop.
How you gonna do that?
I don't know.
I'll think of something.
Ah!
- Hey, what's up, buddy?
- I want some. Me me me.
No no no no.
You can't have this.
This, my friend,
is a store-bought pumpkin pie...
that we are gonna give to our
wonderful neighbor Mr. Cole.
[Zeus]: Oh, I see
where you're going with this.
Place it into the preheated oven...
for approximately five minutes.
Watch out, Julia Childs.
And we have ourselves a home-baked
pumpkin pie.
Sneaky. I love it.
- Hi.
- Hey, whatcha doing, Daddy?
Oh, I just made a little
pumpkin pie for Mr. Cole.
You just want to go
inside his house.
Uh, well, you know what, son?
There's nothing wrong
with being a little neighborly.
Fine, then we're coming with you.
I don't think that's a good idea.
(crow cawing)
- Honey.
- What?
- Take a look.
- What?!
Mmm.
Look at that.
Come on, George,
you watch the cop shows.
We got a pie,
not a warrant.
Hey.
[Zeus]: I don't see any sign
of Cujo anywhere.
Godspeed, G-man.
Now or never, Zeus.
Why don't we just friend him
on Facebook?
Look, Daddy.
He fixed the scarecrow you broke.
[George]:
Oh yeah, what do you know.
- (squishes)
- Ugh, that's disgusting.
- [Kara]: Ew.
- [George]: Ugh. Ick.
- [Ben]: Gross.
- Don't worry about it now, Ben.
You sure we shouldn't
wait for backup?
- Age before beauty, Daddy.
- Huh?
Oh yeah.
Yeah, normally.
But on a situation like this, honey,
you know, where Daddy's
hand are full...
maybe...
Cowards.
(gongs ringing)
Aw, shucks. No one's home.
Let's get going, guys.
(door creaks)
Guess he wants us
to come in.
(whines) Fine.
Everyone follow me.
Mr. Cole.
George Bannister from next door.
George, I think we should
get out of here.
Hello? Mr. Cole?
This is gonna be good.
(laughs)
Uh, we baked you a nice
fresh pumpkin pie.
A little friendly thing.
Wait for me.
[George]:
Here, buddy.
[Zeus]: I don't believe it.
They got nuts. I love nuts.
Look, Daddy.
He's got fish.
Oh yeah.
(laughs)
(fish laughing)
Look at that. Sometimes they like
when you play with 'em.
- [Fish]: Look, finger food.
- Ow!
Dad, are you okay?
Yeah, I'm fine, Ben.
Boy.
I can't take you anywhere.
- What is it, Daddy?
- Rufus' collar.
Rufus?
You mean Monique's missing cat?
Dad, look.
Over there.
- Who's that?
- Here.
Hey, Mr. Cole.
George Bannister.
These are my kids
Ben and Kara.
Was wondering if you'd like...
Oh, how you doing?!
(screams)
What, you've never seen
a skeleton before?
- (growling)
- (whines)
You're the new neighbors.
Yes. Yeah, I'm George Bannister.
And these are my...
my kids.
This is my son...
Kara, my daughter
and Ben my son.
And of course Zeus.
You know, like the Greek god.
I'm Medusa,
like the goddess of death.
Oh, that's nice.
Eli Cole.
What are you doing in my house?
Trying to find out what you're up to.
Oh well,
we were just out walking Zeus
and we thought we would
come over and bring you
a nicely fresh pumpkin pie
I baked for you.
I hate pumpkin pie.
Oh.
Medusa, why don't you take Zeus
and the children and show them around
while I entertain Mr. Bannister?
Come.
Here, honey.
If we're not back in 10 minutes,
call Search and Rescue.
Watch out for trap doors.
This way, Blondie.
Ladies first.
Come on, kids.
(crows cawing)
Can I get you anything?
A Bloody Mary?
Uh, no. Water's fine.
Thank you.
You know, I was just noticing
your fish tank here.
I was wondering what kind
of fish you have in here.
- Piranha.
- Oh hey, piranha.
Here's your water.
Oh.
- Yeah, I'm sorry about that.
- Sit.
Oh yeah, sure.
(sighs)
You're not thirsty?
Oh no.
No, I actually had a big lunch.
- Drink it.
- Okay.
(sighs loudly)
Quite a glass of water
you've got there.
Cashews?
Cashews.
Uh, no thank you.
I don't like furry cashews.
Who are you calling furry?
[Cole]: That's just Shelley.
She's harmless.
So, Mr. Bannister.
You're the one who destroyed
my display in the yard?
Yes. Yes I am.
Terribly sorry, sir.
It was an accident
and I'd be glad to pay you back,
Dr. Cole is it?
Professor.
And that won't be necessary.
Oh, okay, Professor.
Nice.
Professor of?
Paranormal research.
Oh, paranormal research.
Oh!
Very sorry, sir, about that.
I didn't mean to alarm you.
- Sometimes I don't...
- Oh.
This is quite a house you got here.
You know, the workmanship
is just...
you don't see
this woodwork anymore.
The problem with these homes
is the attics.
Very drafty. Maybe we can
jump up there and take a look?
- No.
- All righty.
- (knocks)
(knocking)
The house is settling.
So anything you want
to tell me about Rufus,
the missing cat
from across the street?
What are you supposed to be,
some kind of cop?
"Some kind of cop".
No, I'm a retired K9 police dog.
A police dog that's afraid
of thunder storms?
You've got to be kidding me.
Hey, I wasn't afraid.
That's not what I saw.
Yeah? What about the strange noises
coming from your house at night?
Want to say anything about those?
I'm not gonna say another word
until my lawyer gets here.
That's fine.
But just so you know,
I'll be watching you.
No, I'll be watching you.
Find anything?
I think I found a doll.
I noticed you've had some kind
of a power drain or something.
I noticed a green light upstairs.
Are you running any kind
of heavy machinery.
You're bugging me
with all these questions.
It's an old house.
The wiring needs to be redone.
Hmm.
It's interesting because I also heard
some loud noises late at night.
I find that Halloween
is a particularly interesting time
for me to indulge my talents.
I do most of the leg work.
Talents, right.
And Halloween is about what,
two days away?
Ew.
I have an idea.
We're having a bit
of a get-together tomorrow night,
Halloween party for the neighbors.
Why don't you stop on by
and, you know, bring the wife?
Unfortunately I'll be working
at the school lab all night long.
- Ah, bummer.
- In fact,
if you don't mind, I've really
got to be getting back to work.
Yeah, okay. Well, I'm sure
you have plenty to do.
Thank you for the water.
That was delicious.
It was a pleasure
meeting you, Professor.
Happy Halloween.
Oh, yes siree.
Okay, kids, Zeus, let's go.
Come on.
Okay, take it easy.
I believe they're starting to suspect.
Two days, Medusa.
Just two more days.
(Medusa laughs)
[Mr. Weagle]: Would anybody happen to know
what this meeting is about?
[Mrs. Weagle]:
Maybe he and the kids saw something...
when they broke in next door.
[Mr. Weagle]: I'll bet you 10 bucks
this is a waste of time.
[Mrs. Weagle]:
Oh, honey, behave.
George:
Good afternoon, guys.
Some of you are probably wondering
why I even called this little meeting.
We're supposed to be having
dinner in the city.
- Sushi.
- Yeah, what's going on, Bannister?
Well, some of you might recall
that earlier in the week
my friend Zeus and I have heard
some mysterious noises
coming from this house.
Not to mention a strange light
coming from the attic.
Was that before or after
you started crying like a little girl
and woke up the whole block?
(laughing)
Laugh as you will,
but let me tell you something:
This house belongs to the one
and only Professor Eli Cole.
And his partner in crime Medusa.
Yes, I knew he was a scientist.
I knew it.
Except, Max, there's a problem.
I happen to call every college
within a 50-mile radius
and no one has heard of Eli Cole.
- Ahem. Uh, George.
- Yeah?
Maybe you should
just get to the point.
Tell them about the electron
generators, George.
Please, Belinda, exhibit A.
This you probably recognize
as a high-voltage
electron generator
stolen from the Seaman Neck
power plant late last night.
Not one hour later,
Professor Eli Cole
received a mysterious
late night delivery
with the same size
and description as this.
And the delivery guys
were wearing creepy robes.
- You should have seen it.
- Can you believe...
Exhibit B... Rufus.
- Honey.
- Yeah?
Rufus. Sorry.
The cat Rufus missing
ever since the same generator
had been stolen.
I already told Monique I saw him
playing with Cole's dog.
- Uh-huh.
- Oh, you did?
You told Monique you saw him
with Cole's dog?
Show them the collar, George.
Well, then if that's the case,
then how is this in the house?
(gasps)
Rufus' collar.
[George]:
That's right, Max. Rufus' collar.
And also take a look at exhibit C.
Honey.
What is this?
Honey, that's exhibit C, okay?
Just pass it.
No thanks.
What, did you blow
your nose in this?
That, my friend, was taken
off the shoe of my son Ben...
after he tromped
in the yard of one Eli Cole.
No, it's true, people.
I was there.
And this is important why?
This shows that there's evidence that
there's paranormal activity happening.
- (laughing)
- Please stop laughing.
Oh, this is evidence.
Evidence that you're losing your mind.
- Oh!
- (all groaning)
Oh, that's disgusting.
That's evidence C.
Does anybody have a Handi Wipe
or a wet nap?
- (gasps)
- Thank you.
He got slimed.
That's awesome.
Also, might I add,
that this gentleman has a chart
counting out the days
to something called zero hour.
Do I know what it is?
No I don't.
But I'll tell you what,
I'm not gonna put my family at risk
and I don't think you should either.
And just what do you propose
we do about it?
I propose we go over there and see
where the proof is, all right?
Who's with me?
That's it, I'm out of here.
Come on, we need the Weagles.
- Good night, Bannister.
- Oh, Bruno.
We're out of here.
- Good night, Bannister.
- Oh, Edelsteins, please.
- Keep it. Yeah.
- Thanks.
- Kent, Marilyn.
- It's okay.
So you really found
this stuff in his yard?
Max, I'm telling you,
this guy is up to no good.
All I need is the evidence.
Well, let me know
when you find it.
I wouldn't go near that place
if you paid me.
(groans)
Bye.
Can you believe that?
Are you pleased
with yourself, George?
Do you see what you've done?
Belinda, I feel very strongly
about this stuff, okay?
(sighs)
Oh, George.
Where are you going?
We live here.
George, let 'em go.
You and me can stop this guy.
I need some time to think.
Let's go to the park.
(dogs barking)
(panting)
- Give me that.
- What are you doing?
Give me this.
I can't control myself.
- Give me the stick.
- Do you want to go back to jail?
- Give me the stick!
- Will these two just give it a rest?
I can't believe it.
I mean not even Max seemed to care.
He's scared, George.
They probably all are.
Well, I just thought getting out
would clear my mind,
but I can't stop thinking about it.
Someone's got to help us
get into that house.
[Zeus]:
No, it can't be.
Hey, Zeus, look at that.
Aren't those the two guys that broke
into our house and stole Bella?
Oy vey.
What are they doing?
(arguing)
Yeah, I think it is.
You know what? You're right.
Let me at 'em, George.
(barking)
You hear that?
You hear that dog barking?
It's a dog barking.
No no, that's a familiar
bark right there.
No, it's every dog barking.
We're in a dog park.
What a coincidence.
What are the odds?
- Do you know what this is?
- It's a really bad idea?
No, this is a sign, buddy.
We're finally gonna find out
what's inside that house.
Look, I am all in favor
of bringing this guy down,
but there has got to be another way.
Look, just let me do all the talking.
My lips are sealed.
Hey, will you pull yourself
together, okay?
We're gonna be late
for our next appointment.
- Do we have to go?
- Yes we have to go.
(arguing)
[Ted]:
Stop. Let go.
- Excuse me, guys.
- It's him. It's them.
- (barks)
- That's the guy who put us in jail.
And if it was up to me,
you'd still be there.
Relax relax relax.
I was just out
walking my dog Zeus here...
and I noticed that you were
picking up some dog poop.
Yes sir, Mr. Bannister.
That's part of our probation.
We are trying to become more
productive members of society.
So we're not doing anything wrong.
Oh well, fantastic.
That goes right in line
with what I have to say.
You know, kind of crazy,
but I have a little bit
of a proposition for you.
You got a moment to hear it out?
Don't do it.
Uh, do you mind if I confer
with my associate for one second?
Sure. Yeah.
- (stomach growling)
- You hear my stomach?
I'm anxious.
My stomach is never wrong.
[Ted]: Okay, listen.
Them being here, us being here...
- I think this is destiny.
- No, it's trouble.
No, okay, we're the unstoppable
force, right?
No, we're movable objects.
What happens when two forces,
opposing forces, collide?
You call your insurance company.
No, they reverse direction.
I got that good canine hearing
thing, George, you know?
And I'm telling you
these guys are trouble.
This is our chance
to change everything.
No more bad luck.
No more probation.
No more picking up dog poop.
- You sure?
- Yes.
Mr. Bannister, we'd like to hear
what you have to say,
but we're late
for our next appointment.
Okay, well, tell you what.
Zeus and I have nothing to do.
Why don't we go with you
on the next appointment?
What kind of an appointment is it?
- (rings)
- (woman chanting)
[George]:
Why are we here again?
[Ted]:
Court order.
And there's a lot of hot chicks here.
Psst.
(scoffs)
She don't like me
'cause my "chy" is clogged.
Stupid, how many time I got to tell you?
It's not "chy," it's chi.
(farts)
Oh, someone please
crack open a window.
(rings)
And coming to your hands and knees.
Inhale and thread your right arm...
through your left.
[Stewey]:
What kind of position is this?
- Mr. Bannister.
- Yeah?
What is it you want
to talk to us about?
I want you guys to break into
my neighbor's house.
- What?
- Shh!
I told you this was a bad idea.
Sorry.
Look, it's really important.
This guy is up to something bad.
I don't know what it is.
I've got to find out.
Ted, I don't like it.
I don't like it, Ted.
Oh well, they're not interested.
Time to go.
You guys are gonna be heroes.
You're not doing anything wrong.
You're not stealing anything.
You're gonna break in,
find the evidence that I need
to put him away and that's it.
Ted, I always wanted to be a hero.
You know that.
(gong rings)
And coming to fire log pose.
[Ted]:
I don't know about this, Mr. Bannister.
We're already on probation.
- It's a huge risk for us.
- I'll pay you guys.
Wait a minute.
You're actually gonna pay these guys?
- How much?
- Hey.
Hey, let the man make an offer.
I don't know.
How much do you want?
- How about some candy?
- Stewey, really?
It's Halloween.
I got no candy.
Okay, fine, candy.
Now wait a minute.
What about me?
(gong rings)
Coming into
downward facing dog.
Finally my kind of pose.
I just want to make sure
you guys are in or not.
How about some
peanut butter cups?
Deal.
Get you a whole case.
- What?
- I know how to negotiate.
- When?
- Tonight.
This is the address.
- I'm gonna get out of here.
- (stomach gurgles)
I got a little stomach issue
going on. Come on, Zeus.
All right, people. Move it.
Canine coming through.
Right leg forward into pigeon.
Ted, I can't get out of this.
Namaste.
[Zeus]:
And a very Namaste to you too.
(rings)
- Oh, there you are, George.
- Oh boy. Hi.
You are just in time to help me with all
these decorations for the party tonight.
- I got a little situation going on.
- You what?
Yeah, some business stuff
I've got to take care of.
But I'll do that in a day or so.
Okay. All right.
All right, Zeusy.
Zeusy, you want to help me?
- Good boy. Good boy.
- Always happy to help.
Go ahead.
Go help George with whatever.
This is the place, Ted.
Look at that house, Stewey.
Forget the house, Ted.
Look at the decorations.
I'll bet they have good candy
there for Halloween.
Popcorn balls and peanut brittle
and candied apples
and chocolate momos.
When I go trick or treating
that's exactly where I'm going.
We're not going
trick or treating, Stewey.
- (dog barking)
- Ted, you hear that?
Bannister didn't say nothing
about no dog, Ted.
Don't worry about the dog.
I'll handle the dog.
That's what you said
the last two times, Ted.
Stewey, I swiped a couple of sleeping
pills from Miss Cloverfield's purse.
Okay? A couple of pills,
little juicy sausage,
- night night doggie.
- You got sausage?
- Can I have some?
- No, Stewey.
We got movement.
That's him.
Ted, look at that.
Ooh!
Hallelujah.
A load like that, Stewey,
we could retire.
Ted Ted Ted Ted. You said you
weren't gonna take nothing, Ted.
That's not nothing, Stewey.
That's a trunk full of solid gold.
Our luck, it's changing.
It's going good now.
- Come on, Stewey, look at that.
- Ted, I can't go back to jail.
I told you that before.
I told that lady in the office before.
- I'm not going back to jail.
- Stewey, we're not going back to jail.
We're not going back to jail.
We get caught... if we get caught,
which we're not gonna get caught...
we pin it on Bannister.
He hired us.
It's all on him. Hmm?
Ted, I've told you before,
you always know how
to make me feel better.
Don't touch me, Stewey.
Ted, can I just
trick or treat real quick?
No trick or treating.
Let's get out of here.
We'll come back at dark.
- What's wrong with you?
- You're not fun, Ted.
That's what the problem is.
(thunder rumbles)
(music playing)
(laughs)
Oh, good and bad.
I got you.
- Oh, I love your costumes.
- Thanks.
Wow, did you make that yourself?
Yes, I actually did.
I sure did.
Oh hey, kids kids.
No running in the house.
They're excited.
Oh, come on in.
Come on in. Welcome.
- What a wonderful job you've done.
- Oh, well, thank you.
Here, there's punch here
on the table and cupcakes.
We've got games in the other room
and pizza in the kitchen.
Just make yourselves at home.
George.
George, the Weagles are here.
Okay, honey.
Tell the Weagles I'll be right there.
Or not.
All right, here we go.
All set up.
This is looking good, buddy.
Zeus, where are you?
Zeus, what's the matter, buddy?
I told you, I'm afraid of thunder.
Oh, come on.
It's the thunder, isn't it?
And the lightning?
Don't worry about it.
A little thunder storm.
It'll be over in a second.
It's easy for you to say.
Peanut Butter, this is Jelly.
What's your 20?
[Stewey]:
20? Peanut butter?
Peanut... is this Ted?
Put Ted on.
Give me this.
Ted, where are you?
Jelly, this is Peanut Butter.
We're moving into position, over.
I smell intruders.
- Ted, the dog.
- Shh.
- The dog, Ted.
- Shut up.
- What's that, Ted?
- The sausage.
Give me some, I'm hungry.
Give me that.
- It's got sleeping pills inside.
- That's all right.
- I'll eat a little bite.
- (barking)
- Stewey, stop it.
- (barks)
Here you go.
Three, two...
- (thumps)
- Huh?
You go in there first.
I'm scared of the dog.
(Medusa snoring)
Sleeping.
Close it. Close it.
Close it. Close it, Stewey.
All right, Stewey,
give me the clippers.
No.
I'm cutting this this time.
- Give me the clippers, Stewey.
- No.
Don't you remember all those houses
over on the north end?
Those high-end alarm systems?
I remember we almost got caught.
Let me do this.
I worked for an electrician
for three months. Watch this.
- Move out of the way.
- Careful. Pick the right one.
Pick the right one.
(crackling)
- Ted!
- Let go of it, Stewey. Let go of it.
- Ted! Ted!
- Stop.
- Ted Ted Ted!
- You okay?
¶ Twinkle twinkle little star ¶
¶ How I wonder... ¶
Stewey. Stewey.
You okay?
Huh?
You all right?
- Your heart okay?
- Yeah.
- Okay.
- What just happened?
Okay, let's go.
What was that?
- Are you guys all right?
- (knocking on door)
- George, someone's coming.
- Uh, come in.
Hey. -
- Mom's looking for you.
Okay, yeah.
Zeus and I are getting
just the final touches
on our costumes.
We'll be right out.
We definitely weren't spying
on the neighbor's house.
[Ted]:
Jelly, this is peanut Butter, over.
Ahem.
- What was that?
- What was what?
Whatever. It's just Mom
wants you to talk to the guests.
Okay, I'll be out in a second.
I'll be mingling like crazy.
- Okay.
(exhales)
Oh, Zeus.
That was a close one, buddy.
Not sure I can be by your side
on this one, Georgie.
All right, I'm gonna go
mingle with the guests.
You stay here, okay?
You gonna be all right?
Right, and I'll keep my eye
on Ted and Stewey over there.
Awesome.
Man the fort.
- (thunder rumbles)
- Okay, wait for me, Georgie.
All right, I learned this in Europe.
What, the slow part of Europe?
Give me this.
Let me show you how we do it
in Harlem. Watch this.
Stewey, no.
Don't, it's got...
- (shouts)
- (glass shatters)
Okay.
- Ted, I did it.
- Okay okay.
Stop.
Give me the flashlight.
I didn't bring no flashlight.
You forgot the flashlight?
You didn't tell me to bring
no flashlight, Ted.
It's a nighttime job, Stewey.
How are we supposed to see
what we're doing?
- Turn on the lights.
- There's no power.
There's got to be a candle
in here somewhere. I'll find it.
You'd better find it.
Ah.
Good.
See?
I'm happy I shoplifted that lighter.
Ted, this place looks like
a haunted mansion.
(thunder rumbles)
Stewey, there's no such thing
as ghosts.
(squeaks)
Ted, look!
Stewey, no funny business, okay?
Remember what we're here for.
What are we looking for?
I thought we were trick or treating.
How about a trunk of gold?
Okay? Or anything else
out of the ordinary.
- Like what Mr. Bannister said.
- Okay.
Ted!
- What?
- Nothing.
What's wrong with you?
It's all in your head.
Knock it off.
- Are you sure?
- Yes, I'm sure.
Jelly, this is Peanut Butter.
Come in.
- We swim 50 laps every morning.
- Oh.
20 more after dinner.
I bet you can't doggie paddle
though, can you?
- Well, people like to swim,
- [Ted]: Jelly, this is Peanut Butter.
- Honey, what is that?
- Excuse me for a second please.
Yeah yeah, Peanut Butter,
this is Jelly. Go.
Okay, we're inside.
Okay, what you're looking for
is probably in the attic.
Okay, we got it.
Over and out.
- George. George.
- Yeah, honey?
Is everything okay?
Is anything ever just okay
with this family?
- Yeah, great.
- Is that a walkie-talkie?
Yeah, uh-huh.
- Honey, who are you talking to?
- Nobody, honey.
It's just a toy.
You know, a little pirate radio.
- (chuckles)
- Oh, really, George?
- Ted, let me hold the radio.
- It's not a toy, Stewey.
- We bought it at a toy store, Ted.
- Who cares?
- Let me hold it, Ted.
- Who cares who holds the radio?
- Stop it, Stewey!
- (static)
- Oops.
- That's great.
Get...
Let's just do what
we're supposed to do, okay?
Follow me.
(squeaks)
Ted, Ted, Ted, hold on.
[Ted]:
Quit being such a baby.
I'm scared, not a baby.
Ted, I hate spiders
more than I hate dogs.
Hey, what did we
ever do to you?
Ted, wait for me.
- Stop it, stop it.
- Ted, I'm scared.
Nothing to be scared of.
Ted. I think this house
is haunted, Ted.
- Ted!
- What?
- It's haunted I'm telling you.
- You're haunted, Stewey.
You're haunting me.
Now be quiet. Let's get this done.
- George.
- Yeah.
Honey, you're acting
very strange.
Even for you.
What is going on?
Nothing, Belinda.
Everything's great.
I mean, come on,
this is a strange holiday.
You're out of punch here, G-man.
Oh, hey, sorry, Max.
I'm gonna go grab that.
Listen, you stay with the guests.
You look delightful.
Little Bo something.
And, you know, have a good night.
- Come on, Zeus.
- Coming.
Honey.
Georgie, you see anything?
What's going on?
[George]:
Man, I don't see anything out there.
No sign.
Peanut Butter, come in.
I'm not seeing anything.
Where are you guys?
Peanut Butter, this is Jelly.
Where are you?
What's going on?
(thunder crashes)
Ah.
- (gasps)
- Stop messing around with that junk.
- Let's find the gold.
- I looked for it already.
I think the ghost stole it.
How many times do I have to tell you?
There's no such thing as ghosts.
(screaming)
- It won't open. It won't open.
- Stewey.
- It won't open.
- Try the other door.
Hey, get out of the way!
Come on, Ted.
Ted.
- Stewey!
- Ted, I'm stuck.
- Stewey.
- Push. Ted, push.
I'm pushing.
- (growling)
- Ted, the dog.
- (barks)
- Pull back, Ted. Pull back.
- I'm pulling. I'm pulling.
- (barking)
Pull! Pull!
- (farts)
- (screams)
What was that?
- (thunder crashes)
- (whines)
What's the matter, buddy?
Oh, the storm huh?
The storm bothering you?
Itll be over soon.
George, promise me you won't say
a word to the other pets.
Something must have
happened to you.
It was my first day on the job.
My partner and I chased a burglar
into this building during a storm.
When I heard the thunder I thought
it was the burglar shooting at us.
I was so scared I ran to hide.
My partner trusted me.
He needed me and what did I do?
I let the bad guy get away.
Do you know
what us Bannisters do?
- We count.
- Count?
That's right, buddy.
We count the seconds after we see
the lightning until the thunder.
And the longer the seconds take
the further the storm.
I hope so.
You got nothing to worry about.
(thunder crashes)
[Ted]: We'll tear this place apart
until we find that gold.
Ted, Ted, Ted.
I'm coming with you, Ted.
You go that way
I'm gonna go this way.
Stewey, Stewey, Stewey.
It's...
a bookshelf?
Where is this attic?
This is ridiculous.
Come on, keep looking.
Come on, Stewey.
I'm tired, Ted.
Ted! Ted!
Ted!
Look, Ted.
Stewey.
Great job, Stewey.
This has got to be it.
It's a secret door.
How do you...?
Ted, in the movies you usually
have like a key in the book thing.
Here we go, move the books.
It's got to be here.
Maybe there's a secret lever
or something, Ted.
Ted, look.
Colorado skiing. Fun times.
I don't like Colorado anymore.
Stewey, come on.
Ted, you always said I was
an unstoppable force.
Move out of the way.
I'm going through this door.
All right, Stewey. Get it.
Go get it. Get it, Stewey, get it.
- (grunts)
- Look at that, Stewey.
- It's open, Ted.
- Yeah, let me look.
- Ted, I'm scared.
- Don't be scared.
Here we go.
(Stewey farts)
I have a little bit of gas, Ted.
Ted.
(farts)
(wind blowing)
Ted, wait for me.
Ted, I thought you said
you shut the lights off.
I did.
Then how come
there's lights still on?
I don't know, Stewey.
I'm not a doctor.
Ted, look.
It looks like my eyeball.
Look at this place, Ted.
Ted, I don't know.
I think Bannister was right.
This place is like one
big haunted movie.
Stewey, there it is.
Isn't that the most beautiful thing
you've ever seen in your entire life?
- I could cry.
- Don't cry, Ted.
I could cry.
This is it.
Stewey, this is everything
we've ever dreamed of.
Everything I've ever wanted,
it's just...
- It's...
- It's candy!
Ah, Ted, it's candy.
Look!
No, this can't be happening.
It's happening, Ted.
¶ Come to Uncle Stewey. ¶
- (laughs)
- (sinister laugh)
(screaming)
Stewey.
Stewey, don't close it!
Stewey!
(screaming)
Hey, Stewey!
Stewey, open the door.
- Stewey, it closed.
- I want to go home.
I want to go home.
Mommy!
Mommy! I want to go home.
I want to go home.
Ted! Ah!
There's spiders.
[Shelley]:
Peek-a-boo.
(screams)
- (clangs)
- (screams)
(screams)
- (laughs)
- (screams)
- (organ playing)
- (water bubbling)
- (screams)
Ted!
Ted! Ted!
- Ted.
- No, Stewey.
Stewey, don't let it close.
Great, Stewey.
Now we're both stuck in here.
[George]:
Oh boy.
George, I hear a car.
I think he's coming.
Got to go, Zeus.
Got to go.
Better stop him before
he gets in his house.
10-4.
I'll just be here waiting for you.
- George George, there you are.
- Huh? What?
I thought you were
getting the punch?
What punch?
What are you talking about punch?
- The punch.
- Oh, the punch. I'm getting it, yeah.
What do you think I'm doing?
Hey, listen, Ben.
Look, you and Kara got to
distract Mr. Cole, all right?
- What?
- You can't... what? What what?
You can't... don't say what.
On the walkie-talkie.
I'm running this operation.
Don't let him in the house!
Heads up!
I've got an idea.
Follow me.
No, kids. Kids. Where are you going?
Wings. Wings. Wings. Wings.
Um, would anyone
like to bob for apples?
What strange neighbors.
- Maybe the storm is over.
- (thunder rumbles)
(whines)
Oh, you can do it, Zeusy.
Come on, baby, just count.
Just like Georgie said.
One Mississippi.
Two Mississippi.
Three Mississippi.
(thunder crashes)
(whines)
Whoops.
(chuckles)
Excuse me.
I'd like to go home now.
Oh, excuse me.
- Now we're talking.
- Mom's not gonna like this.
Hey, kids, what are you doing out
here in the thunder storm?
(laughs nervously)
Hey, Medusa.
- (barks)
- Hey.
[George]:
Nice doggie.
Nice doggie didn't come
to work today.
Watch this.
Go right. Go right.
- Whoa.
- Now left. Now left.
- (whimpering)
- (Medusa barking)
I'll get you.
Get back here.
You in the pirate costume,
I'm talking to you.
Get back here.
(toy car humming)
All right, I want to try.
Here we go.
Yeah.
Whoa, look at him go.
Hey, girl, fetch.
(barks)
Is that a toy for me?
Oh boy. Oh boy.
He is so scared.
Look at him go.
Whoa. That's it.
I'm calling the cops.
I've got to get back to the telescope,
see what's going on.
[Ben]:
Dad's gonna be in trouble.
What is going on out here?
Benjamin and Kara Bannister,
you will listen
to your mother right now...
or you will both be grounded
until Christmas.
Dad asked us
to distract Mr. Cole.
What?
Why would he do that?
Look, both of you
inside right now.
Get back inside.
Go, Ben.
(sighs)
Oh, George.
You have got to be kidding me.
(playing)
Ted. Stewey.
Don't see that every day.
Ted.
- Stewe... ooh!
- George!
Belinda, what are you doing here?
What am I doing here?
What are you doing here?
- I'm... I'm... I'm actually...
- George.
- I'm helping Mr. Cole.
- George, we have to go.
Mr. Cole is right outside in the front.
He could come in at any minute.
- What?!
- Yes.
George, is that organ
playing itself?
Yes it is. I told you there's
weird stuff going on here.
- I was right all along, Belinda.
- Maybe you were right.
- Yes, I was right.
- What do we do?
Listen, I've got to take care
of some stuff, all right?
Take care of what stuff?
George. George.
George!
George. George. No, George.
Outside. Outside this minute.
Better stay close, honey.
I really think we should go.
(sinister laughing)
George. George.
The doors are opening and closing.
Belinda, that's what doors do.
Guys?
Wait wait wait,
is someone else here?
- Guys?
- [Ted]: George, back here.
Who is that?
George. George.
Wait for me.
Wait for me, George.
(music playing)
Guess what, everybody.
I found Rufus.
Hello?
Rufus? Uh-oh.
Ted. Ted.
[Ted]:
I'm behind the bookcase.
- George, what is going on?
- Huh?
Nothing.
There's a hidden door, Belinda.
- [Ted]: Who are you taking to?
- My wife.
- Who are you talking to?
- Ted and Stewey.
The two guys
that broke into our house?
Yeah, I hired them
to break into this house.
George, have you completely
lost your mind?
I just have to figure out how
to move this stupid bookcase.
The thing opens up.
I don't know where.
- George, have you tried pushing it?
- Huh?
Well, not yet.
- But I was gonna do that.
- Uh-huh.
Yeah, if you weren't in here
arguing with me the whole time.
Oh, George.
I'm looking for the door that...
- George.
- Yeah?
- It's right behind you.
- Yeah, thought so.
All right, thank you.
Step back.
Zeus, where did everybody go?
Pinch my tuchus
and call me Sally.
You're alive.
Of course I'm alive.
What did you think?
Well, we all thought
you were a goner.
No, I finished playing
with Medusa
and I decided to go
for a stroll in the woods.
It was such a nice day.
And I walked and walked
until I didn't know
where I was anymore.
Aren't cats supposed to have
a keen sense of direction?
If you tell anyone
I'll kill you.
So if you're alive,
that means...
oh boy.
Zeus, what is it?
There comes a time
in every dog's life
when you've got to grab the situation
with your paws and take control...
storm or no storm.
George and Belinda
are inside that house
and I am not about to let
anything happen to them.
It's time to face my fears
and save Halloween.
[Monique]:
Where are you going?
Where do you think
you're going, Blondie?
Look, get out of my way.
I need to get inside the house...
and save my owner.
He thinks you did something to Rufus.
Rufus? Please.
I couldn't hurt him.
- He's my sweetheart.
- Say what?
I've been head over heels for that hunk
since the day we moved in.
Oh, TMI.
Look, just let me in
and I promise I'll explain
everything to you later.
- Fine.
- Thank you.
- Good luck, Blondie.
- Stop calling me that.
(playing)
Have no fear,
Zeus is here.
Hello? George?
Belinda?
Where are you guys?
Don't be scared.
It's just a storm.
- (thunder crashes)
- Here we go.
One Mississippi.
Two Mississippi.
Talk about some bad gas.
Yowch.
Hey, guys.
Can you hear me?
Rufus is alive.
Jeepers creepers.
This house really is haunted.
(barks)
What are you looking at,
Sir Rustalot?
(whirrs)
Wait a minute. What, does this ghost
run on electricity?
Hey. Hello.
Yo, anybody in there?
Hey, hello.
Hmm.
(powers down)
Ha, not so spirited now,
are you, tough guy?
- An off switch.
- (music stops)
Hmm, this looks fun.
(playing)
Never had one lesson.
Huh, that dog wasn't half bad.
Hello?
Where are you guys?
I can do it.
Come on, one Mississippi.
Two Mississippi.
It's all in your head.
(sinister laughing)
Okay, that's not in my head.
Guys, where are you?
(barking)
Is that Zeusy?
Zeus. Zeusy!
- [George]: Zeus, in the attic.
- (barking)
Hang on George.
Zeus is coming to the rescue.
All right, come on.
There's got to be some kind
of hidden door behind
this shelf somewhere.
Push. Push. Push.
Push. Push.
Come on, Zeusy.
Now to find a way
to keep it from closing.
Got it.
Here I come.
- [George]: Oh, good dog.
- [Belinda]: Zeus.
Georgie, I did it.
I conquered my fear of thunder.
[Ted]:
Now we can finally get out of here.
Not so fast.
There's something you need to see.
What is it, Zeusy?
Ugh. Oh brother.
(laughing)
Dude, that is one
scorching sunburn.
(barks)
[Stewey]:
The mutt's trying to tell us something.
[Belinda]:
What is it, Zeusy?
All right, you ready for this?
Check this out.
What is that we're looking at?
[Zeus]: Huh? That's the house.
Look at that, every room.
He's been staging everything
the whole time.
Don't you understand?
Between the monitor and the board,
don't you understand, guys?
Whenever somebody uses parentheses
and shapes we're not familiar with,
it means they're up to something.
"Countdown to zero hour".
You know what this means, Belinda?
Yes, George.
Haunted house.
You know, Belinda,
I don't even know why I ask.
- George.
- Yeah?
- Turn it around.
- What's that?
Turn it around.
"Haunted house plans"?
How do you explain the generators?
None of this was real.
I don't understand that.
(siren blares)
[Man]: This is the police.
We have the house surrounded.
- Come out with your hands up.
- Uh-oh, coppers.
- That sounds pretty real to me.
- Real real real.
- I'm not going back to jail, Ted.
- I'm not going back to jail.
- They're gonna go back.
- You!
We're not going to jail.
We didn't do anything, right?
- You and your wife Little Miss Bo Peep.
- We work for you.
I got no time for this stuff.
I can't go to jail.
I'm a minor.
[Mr. Weagle]:
There's an exit for you.
Why am I not surprised?
You're a nightmare, Bannister.
- You broke in the house.
- You belong behind bars.
Daddy.
Hey, honey.
Listen, you dad might be going
to the slammer for a little bit.
Just make sure you're good
to your court appointed guardian.
I'll look after them for you, G-man.
Yeah, not in 1000 years.
- [George]: Officers, arrest this man.
- Cole: On what charge?
Monique, Rufus' collar,
we found it in the house.
Georgie, about that, um...
Mr. Cole brought him back
this afternoon.
He'd found him lost in the woods
behind his house.
He's fine. See?
Weagles, you were
at my meeting, right?
The electron generators
that were stolen that night,
how do you explain it?
Come on, Bannister.
That meeting was bogus.
And I want my easel back.
They found those generators
last night.
Yeah yeah yeah,
couple of low lives were out
looking for copper wire or something.
That's all it was.
George, we should probably
quit while we're ahead here.
Okay, how about this?
I happen to call around to all
the colleges in the area.
No one has ever heard
of Professor Eli Cole.
Oh yeah. How do you like
them apples, Professor?
- You called?
- Sure did.
And you called
and you asked for Eli Cole?
You got that right.
Well, Eli is my nickname.
My real name is Cornelius.
I'm Professor Cornelius
of the drama department.
- Seriously, George?
- Well, he's good.
Mr. Cole, would you like
to press charges?
Officer, I think this is a big
misunderstanding.
Yeah, a big big big
Yeah, yes.
Now look, I feel partially
responsible for this,
my work and my preoccupation.
I realize I could have
done a better job
at introducing myself to you
rather than, you know, bugging you.
Oh.
I do this every year,
this haunted house
for my nieces and nephews
and their friends.
I enjoy them enjoying
my little special effects.
You know that...
that truck that came?
- That delivery?
- [George]: Yeah.
- Well, those are just props.
- Props?
Didn't you notice that the guys,
these messengers,
they had theatrical
costumes on.
- Yeah, I just thought they were...
- (sighs)
On second thought,
they were kind of strange uniforms.
Professor Cole, on behalf of
the entire Bannister family,
I want to apologize for everything
that has happened here tonight.
Right, George?
- What about the...
- Right, George?
- Yes yes.
- Apology accepted.
That's great.
Can we get these off, please?
Thank you.
- Thank you so much.
- Thank you.
- Hey, what's that?
- Hey, that's mine.
How's that get there?
Officer, a ghost!
- Hey, get 'em!
- Hey!
I'll see you in nine to 12 months,
goofballs.
- Send me a postcard.
- I had nothing to do with that.
Hmm.
[Belinda]: Well, listen listen.
We'll all get together.
Everybody will come over
for swimming.
- We have our own pool.
- I'm busy.
- Monique.
- Great job, Colombo.
Be seeing you
when you get back, genius.
Kent. Marilyn.
Hey, where you going?
Give me a call tomorrow.
[Kent]:
If the phone doesn't ring, it's me.
(door slams)
Come on, George.
Let's go home.
And I'll make you some of your
favorite pumpkin cookies.
- With the chocolate in it?
- Mm-hmm.
- Arr.
- Oh, George.
(giggles)
And you too, Zeusy.
I'm gonna make you
something very special
because you saved Halloween.
You did it.
All in a day's work.
- [George]: Let's go, guys.
- [Belinda]: Come on.
¶ Creepy little thingies ¶
¶ Crawling on my skin ¶
¶ I just can't keep
from scratching ¶
¶ Someone let them in ¶
¶ Creepy little crawlies ¶
¶ With tiny little feet ¶
¶ Get them off my body
so I can get some sleep... ¶
(children laughing, chatting)
Aw, this is the life.
Well, if this isn't
the cutest bunch...
of ghosts and goblins
you've ever seen.
Hey, who wants to go
trick or treating?
- [Kids]: Yeah!
- (doorbell rings)
Oh, somebody's at the door.
Trick or treaters.
Yay!
Trick or treat!
Oh, hi.
I have got Grandma's homemade
pretzels for you guys.
Well, thanks,
but can I have some more?
- That's all I got.
- Are you sure?
- Those look yummy.
- Good.
- Thanks.
- You're welcome.
Bye-bye, have fun.
Happy Halloween.
- Hey, guys.
- [George]: Hey, Mom.
Well, hello.
Happy Halloween.
Hi, Grandma.
Come on, we're just about
to go trick or treating.
- You too, Zeus.
- I'm gonna go get my costume on.
Hey, guys. So how's everything
with the new house?
- Not good. Not good.
- George.
He had a little problem
with the man who lives next door.
So, you know.
Maybe he's single.
Oh, he's definitely single.
Bannister.
Zeus Bannister.
What's up, Doc?
(high voice)
I'm here to audition for the black swan.
You like to eat wampum?
I'll take a kibble
shaken, not stirred.
Elementary, my dear Watson.
You ain't nothing
but a hound dog, baby.
I can't "ear" you.
- That looks perfect.
- Thanks, Dad.
Guys, check me out.
Speaking of perfect,
look at this guy.
I'm licensed to trick or treat.
What do you think?
Can we please go
trick or treating now?
- Yes, honey.
- [Grandma]: No, no, no, no.
No, wait until I take a picture
of my little munchkins first.
Who are you calling munchkin?
I'm a certified K9.
Hey, Belinda, come out of the kitchen.
Just putting some treats in the oven.
You go right ahead.
- Yeah, maybe we should do it later.
- Okay, I'll get a picture of her later.
All right, everybody, come on.
Come on, come on. Ready?
- (doorbell rings)
- Oh, somebody's at the door.
Trick or treaters.
Oh, hold on. Let me get the door.
Trick or treat.
A little too old to go
trick or treating, aren't you?
No.
- (high voice) I mean, no.
- Uh, yeah.
Uh-huh, I'm gonna say
that you are.
- No no no no no.
- I'm gonna call the police.
- Don't call the police.
- Get away from here!
Don't call the police.
Does she look familiar to you?
That's the fourth house in a row.
- I told you you're too old.
- Give me some eggs.
We egged the last house.
- Give me the toilet paper then.
- All right, fine.
Here you go. Ah!
Ted. Ted, wait up.
Come here. Aah!
Okay, guys.
Let's all group together
and take this picture
before you go out.
All right now, on the count of three
I want everybody
in their witchiest of voices
to say "Happy Halloween".
Happy Halloween.
Okay, that's a good voice,
but wait till I say three.
All right, ready?
One, two, three.
[All]:
Happy Halloween.
Oh, that's great.
What are you guy waiting for?
Come on, let's go.
- All right, let's go.
- Let's go trick or treating.
[Grandma]: Come on, everybody.
Yay. Oh my goodness.
Yo, Roscoe.
Want to hear a joke, buddy?
Oh brother.
- Oh come on. Knock knock.
- Who's there?
- Phillip.
- Phillip who?
Phillip my bag with candy.
- (laughing)
- See?
- I knew you'd like it.
- That's funny.
Come on,
let's go trick or treating.
¶ I'm not scared
of going out tonight ¶
¶ No, I don't care about
goblins taking flight ¶
¶ I don't know what makes them
full of fright ¶
¶ Just pull the plug
and everything's all right ¶
¶ Night turns into daylight ¶
¶ With sunshine burning bright ¶
¶ No, I'm not scared
of going out tonight ¶
¶ I said, boo hoo hoo ¶
¶ Bats are flying,
boo hoo hoo ¶
¶ Ghosts are coming,
¶ Kids are running,
boo hoo hoo ¶
¶ Everybody, boo hoo hoo ¶
¶ Everybody,
boo hoo hoo ¶
¶ Everybody, boo hoo hoo ¶
¶ Everybody,
boo hoo hoo ¶
¶ Night turns into daylight ¶
¶ With sunshine burning bright ¶
¶ No, I'm not scared
of going out tonight ¶
(howling)
¶ Yeah... ¶
Come on, let me hear it now.
Come on.
Whoo!
Go.
¶ I said, boo hoo hoo ¶
¶ Bats are flying,
boo hoo hoo ¶
¶ Ghosts are coming,
¶ Kids are running,
boo hoo hoo ¶
¶ Everybody, boo hoo hoo ¶
¶ Everybody,
boo hoo hoo ¶
¶ Everybody, boo hoo hoo ¶
¶ Everybody,
boo hoo hoo ¶
¶ Night turns into daylight ¶
¶ With sunshine burning bright ¶
¶ No, I'm not scared
of going out tonight ¶
- ¶ I'm going out tonight ¶
- ¶ No, I'm not scared ¶
¶ Going out tonight ¶
- ¶ I'm going out tonight ¶
- ¶ No, I'm not scared ¶
¶ Going out tonight ¶
- ¶ I'm going out tonight ¶
- ¶ No, I'm not scared ¶
¶ Going out tonight ¶
- ¶ I'm going out tonight ¶
- ¶ No, I'm not scared ¶
¶ Going out tonight ¶
- ¶ I'm going out tonight ¶
- ¶ No, I'm not scared ¶
- ¶ Going out tonight ¶
- ¶ I'm going out tonight ¶
- ¶ No, I'm not scared ¶
- ¶ Going out tonight ¶
- ¶ I'm going out tonight ¶
- ¶ No, I'm not scared ¶
- ¶ Going out tonight ¶
- ¶ I'm going out tonight ¶
- ¶ No, I'm not scared ¶
- ¶ Going out tonight ¶
- ¶ I'm going out tonight ¶
- ¶ No, I'm not scared ¶
- ¶ Going out tonight ¶
- ¶ I'm going out tonight ¶
- ¶ No, I'm not scared ¶
- ¶ Going out tonight ¶
- ¶ I'm going out tonight ¶
- ¶ No, I'm not scared ¶
- ¶ Going out tonight ¶
- ¶ I'm going out tonight ¶
- ¶ No, I'm not scared ¶
- ¶ Going out tonight ¶
- ¶ No, I'm not scared. ¶
(howling)