There's juice in the blender.
Jared's gonna say he hates it,
but he has to drink it.
- Juice is not negotiable.
- I understand.
Oh, and I need you to stop
at the farmer's market
to pick up some vegetables.
There's a list on the counter.
The farmer's market.
Why can't we just shop at the
supermarket like everybody else?
Leland, please. Do you want your
children to be like everybody else
and have chemicals and
pesticides and God knows what,
or do you want them to be better
than everybody else?
Better.
Damn!
- What is in there?
- Lighting equipment.
- Well, how much did that cost?
- Oh, don't worry, Leland.
I will pay you back.
That's not the point.
What I meant was that it's...
We-We can't afford lighting equipment!
Move.
If I had a digital camera I wouldn't need
so much lighting equipment.
We cannot afford a new camera!
Karen, I do not want to have another fight!
I would love to have another fight,
because I am sick and tired of this one.
Don't forget about the farmer's market,
and don't pretend...
to forget about the farmer's market.
I will call you later.
And I love you too.
Hi. I'm leaving right now.
Is Sandy there yet?
Tell Jerry I'm bringing my lighting kit.
We'll need about an hour to set up.
MONK Season 2 Epi. 14
Mr. Monk and the Captain's Wife
Hey, Monk.!
Captain.
- Happy garbage day!
- Thank you.
What are you doing here?
Oh, I was just in the neighborhood.
I was going to the farmer's market
to buy alfalfa sprouts.
I figured I'd drop that off.
That's your check for the Rutherford case.
Late.
- Who's late?
- Garbage truck.
It's 8:22. They've never been this late.
No, it's 8:15.
Is that the watch that Trudy gave you?
So, you're never gonna know what time
it is for the rest of your life? - Maybe.
You know, Trudy's been gone
for seven years. I...
I think maybe it's time
you think about letting go.
- Letting go?
- Yeah.
You should think about your future.
What future?
- Your future.
- I don't have one.
Yes, you do.
And I think that you should...
you should start thinking about
building a life.
You should, uh, get on with it.
Just let it go.
At least buy a new watch.
- Just think about it.
- I'm afraid to.
Here! Here they come.
Hold on. Where's...
- Where's Tully?
- On vacation.
He never said anything to me
about a vacation.
Why would he tell you?
We have a relationship.
He's been collecting
my garbage for years.
Mister, relax, okay?
We know what we're doing.
You know, we taught Tully
the garbage game, okay?
Okay. Yeah, but wait, wait,
wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
You... You have to start from this end.
Tully always starts from this end.
Didn't Tully mention me?
Believe me, I would have remembered.
What's in here?
Water.
You're throwing away water?
Don't ask.
Okay, now... now this one.
Dude, what difference does it make, man?
I mean, it's all going to the same place.
Actually, no.
When you get to the dump, uh,
my bags go in Sector Nine.
Sector Nine?
Tully puts my garbage in Sector Nine,
so... so it's separate.
Right. Sector... Sector Nine.
- You got it, Sector Nine.
- Have a good day.
Hey, God bless you and your work.
Captain, I've been trying to call you.
What's going on?
This morning...
This morning... - For God's sake,
Randy, just say it!
It's Karen.
I'm Leland Stottlemeyer.
My wife, Karen, was just brought in.
Captain, I'm Dr. Maulding.
I was on duty when she was admitted.
Um, would you like to come with me?
I have an office upstairs...
No, no. Now. Tell me now.
She has some internal hemorrhaging
and a non-displaced fracture of the skull.
Bottom line. What's the bottom line?
Her vital signs are strong.
They seem to be holding.
If the swelling goes down, we're going
to operate first thing in the morning.
Wh-Who's gonna do that?
- Dr. Schecter and Dr. Foster.
- They're good.
I'm an R. N. I interned
here seven years ago.
She's right.
They're the best we have.
Okay. Could I see her?
In a few minutes. Um, Captain.
We're good at our job.
Let us do it.
Okay. Okay.
- Right, right. I'll call you back.
- What do you got?
Okay, this is what we know...
Sniper on Highway 9.
So far it looks completely random
a thrill killing.
He took out the tow truck driver,
- and the truck spun into the...
- Into Karen!
Who was it?
We don't have him... yet.
- I want everybody.
- You've got them, sir.
Everybody is volunteering.
There's gonna be a task force.
I talked to the commissioner.
- He said whatever you need.
- All right, good.
Monk.
You... - I know.
If I lose her... - I know.
We... Karen... - I know.
- Since... Since we were kids.
- I know.
I know.
Is there anything I can do?
You know what you can do.
The victim's name was Fernandez.
Frank Fernandez, 34, unmarried.
He lives in Oakland.
Witnesses?
We're still knocking on doors. Not yet.
He shot from over there?
Yes.
Any idea where he parked?
We haven't found any tracks.
He could have parked anywhere.
There's a million little side roads
around here. We're still looking.
But why there in the open?
The surrounding area is heavily wooded.
There'd have been more cover.
I don't know.
It's a good question.
Ooh! Hey, you lost?
No. I'm just thinking.
I'm not talking to you.
Don't, Sharona! Don't...
Don't touch the dog, okay?
Just please don't pat the dog.
- Don't touch the dog.
- Well, why?
Okay, if you touch the dog, Sharona,
I'm...
I have to let you go.
You always say you're gonna let me go,
but you never do it.
Don't listen to him.
He doesn't like anybody.
- Come on. Whose doggy are you?
- We recovered the shell.
It's a thirty-aught-six from
a Winchester bolt action.
It's not a sniper's rifle.
He's a hunter.
Look at this.
He crawled through this hole.
Shirt got caught.
He fired from over there
behind the mound.
How did he know the hole was here?
Maybe he cased the area?
Or he lives nearby.
She's gonna want to keep it.
We can't have a dog!
You don't live together.
Oh, yeah. Yeah.
You want to see something really weird?
No.
Okay.
He wasn't wearing any shoes.
What?
- Watch your step.
- Bare feet?
Why would a sniper... go barefoot?
Especially at 6:00 in the morning.
It's been freezing.
Maybe he was an American Indian?
An American Indian sniper?
Maybe it was an uprising...
against technology.
That doesn't make a lot of sense.
Hardly any, really.
- Oh, "Native American."
- That doesn't help.
Lieutenant Disher...
Really? - Uh-huh.
You're gonna wanna to see this.
Yahhh!
This can't be a coincidence.
What are you talking about?
Frank Fernandez, the truck driver.
They've looked everywhere.
They can't find them.
Can't find what?
His shoes.
He was barefoot too.
Hey.
Hey yourself.
- I brought you some coffee.
- Thanks.
How's Mrs. S.?
She's still unconscious.
- Have you seen her yet?
- Yeah, I've seen her.
I'll feel a whole lot better when
she can see me.
How are the boys doing?
They're scared to death.
They're with my mother,
which is scary enough.
What do you got?
It's coming together.
What does that mean?
The killer and the victim were
both barefoot.
I mean, Monk isn't sure what it means,
but he knows it's important.
What, do you have a suspect?
Do you have a name?
Not yet. The task force has a theory.
They're checking it out.
What?
I'm not supposed to tell you.
They warned me.
You know the local transport
union's on strike. - Yeah?
Harry Bolston, the union boss,
he's made a few threats.
It's getting ugly.
Okay.
The tow truck belonged to a union shop.
The driver was a scab.
It was a union thing?
It's just a theory, sir.
- They're not sure yet.
- Son of a bitch.
- Where are you going?
- Never you mind, son.
Okay, I'll go with you.
No deal, no work!
- No deal, no work!
- Who's on the front gate?
Little Tommy and his crew.
Tell him to take pictures of all
the drivers, so we know who they are.
And don't hide the cameras.
I want them to know that we know.
Yes, sir, Mr. Bolston.
If you want, they can do more than
just take pictures.
No. - You're the boss.
No deal, no work!
Okay. Okay, bye.
That was Disher.
They're on their way.
Why are we even here?
- I want to protect the captain.
- From who?
From himself.
Adrian? No!
You call him "Adrian"?
It seemed to fit.
He's nervous,
and he's always cleaning himself.
- You should be flattered.
- I should be, but I'm not.
Scabs go home!
Scabs!
All right.
Scabs.!
Union! Union!
Scabs go home!
Union!
- What are you doing?
- Well, I'm a union girl.
- Since when?
- Since I started working for you.
Scabs go home!
I should start my own shop.
Do it. I'll join you.
You're not allowed.
You're management.
Oh, yeah? Good.
Get rid of the dog.
Will you stop worrying about this?
I got the vet's number off the collar.
They gave me the owner's name,
and I'm gonna drop him off later, okay?
Okay.
I'm gonna miss you.
Gonna miss you, honey.
No work, no deal!
- Where is Harry Bolston?
- Captain, please be careful.
Bolston's already sued
the department twice.
I'm just gonna talk to the man, Randy.
That's all.
Captain, I think you're making
a mistake. - Not now, Monk.
I-I don't think the union is involved.
Look, you've been
reading about this strike.
The negotiations are going their way.
Every editorial is behind them.
Why would they do something stupid now?
- It doesn't make any sense.
- It makes sense to me.
Also, the shooter wasn't wearing shoes.
Can you imagine any of these guys
running around barefoot?
- Well, maybe he wasn't thinking straight.
- Maybe you're not.
Look, Monk, you don't know
what I'm thinking.
I think I do.
The place you're in now,
that's where I live.
Look, I'm just gonna go talk
to the guy, all right?
- There's no...
- That's all. Stay here.
Hey, Bolston.
I'm Captain Stottlemeyer,
San Francisco Police Department.
This is a legal strike, Captain.
We've got every right to be here.
I don't care about your strike.
There was a shooting
on Highway 9 this morning.
- A driver was killed.
- Yeah, I heard about that.
I already talked to the cops.
I'm gonna tell you the same thing
I told them...
I had nothing to do with that.
It's what we call serendipity.
"Serendipity."
You've got five seconds to wipe
that smile off your face.
Did you say this?
"We're gonna bring this company down
using any means necessary"?
- Did you say that?
- No. I was misquoted.
- You know how that goes.
- This is incitement, you son of a bitch.
You might as well have pulled
the trigger yourself.
Now look, Captain. I can't control
every member of my union,
just like you can't control every stupid,
loudmouth cop in your department, can you?
You're Frank Wicks, aren't you?
I brought you in for assault
during the last strike, didn't I?
- You got a good memory.
- You're damn right I do.
- Do you own a hunting rifle, Wicks?
- I don't have a gun.
- I don't need one.
- Right.
- Where were you at 6:00 this morning?
- He was with me.
We were here, okay?
All morning, setting up.
Captain! The hospital just called.
Karen's awake.
This isn't over.
I got 10 lawyers.
Call one of'em!
We've stopped the hemorrhaging
and all the internal bleeding.
About an hour ago she
started fasciculating.
Oh, my Lord!
No, no, no. That's a good thing.
It means she's... she's stable.
She's not out of the woods yet.
We still don't know
how serious the head injury is.
The next six hours will tell the story.
Can we see her?
Maybe tomorrow after the surgery.
I think her husband
could use some help.
Hey.
I hate hospitals.
The doctor says she's stable.
Thank God.
She woke up for a couple minutes. I...
She could barely breathe.
That's how much pain she's in.
She asked how the kids were.
I said the kids were fine.
She passed out again.
If I lose her...
What if I lose her?
You're not. You're not.
You're not gonna lose her.
"Not gonna lose her."
I remember I said that to you one time.
I'm sorry.
Peanut bar.
I hate these.
Do you want it?
- Why'd you buy it?
- I didn't buy it.
I felt like hitting something.
Adrian, I'm gonna spank you.
Come on.
- Are you talking to me or the dog?
- Both.
Ooh! - Oh, I'll-I'll-I'll-I'll...
I'll stay here.
That's a good idea. Come on.
Come on. Come on.
Samson! There you are!
Oh! Where you been, huh?
Where's you been? Mmm.
Where's my squirrel?
Usually when he runs away he brings
me back a dead squirrel.
You must be disappointed.
Your taste is getting better.
She's a lot cuter than a dead squirrel.
Thanks.
I'm Evan Coker.
Uh, Sharona Fleming.
Sharona, I...
I don't know how to thank you.
I... I've been going out of my mind.
I don't know how he got away.
I must have left the gate open.
Well, he's really a great dog.
I had to leave him at my sister's,
'cause if I brought him home,
my son would have fallen in love with him.
He gets very attached to pets, you know?
I think it's because his father's
not around. I...
I'm divorced.
- Okay.
- All right.
- I like your car.
- Thank you.
I just got it.
It's kind of an impulse thing.
Well, impulses can be fun.
Excuse me.
What are you doing?
Hi.
I was, uh, just fixing your sundial.
- Yeah, leave it alone. It's fine.
- Ahhh.
It's five hours off.
No, it's not.
My son checked it last week.
Oh! Well, he did it wrong.
- Well, he's an astronomer.
- Oh.
Maybe his watch was broken?
Who are you?
Just a concerned citizen, ma'am.
Just a Good Samaritan just passing by.
- You're demented!
- Well, that's a matter of opinion.
Oh. There you go.
It's all done, and you'll thank me later.
Get out of my yard, you creep!
Do you know him?
Yeah, he's my boss.
I don't know how he got out.
I must have left the gate open.
- So what does he do?
- He's a detective.
We're working with the police now
on that sniper case.
Oh, yeah, I heard about that.
They think it's a union thing, right?
No, no. My...
- My boss doesn't think so.
- Oh, he doesn't?
No.
And believe it or not, he's never wrong.
Hi, Karen.
Hi! - Hi.
- Hello.
- Are those lilacs?
I love lilacs. Thank you.
- Will you put 'em here?
- Sure.
- How do you feel?
- Like I was hit by a truck.
Ah, get it? - Oh. I do.
Shhh. He's been sleeping there all night.
What are you doing?
Just making them even.
- Even?
- You'll sleep better if they're even.
What are you talking about?
Hey! Did Max draw this?
Yeah. The boys were here all morning.
You know, they're
the best medicine in the world.
You know, if... if there's anything
we can do, we...
Well, as a matter of fact are
you busy tomorrow?
Because we need someone to
take the boys out to lunch.
Yeah. Sharona, I promised my mother
that I'd give her a break.
But I've got to work, so...
You know, I'd love to,
but Benjy has a dentist appointment.
Hey! But Adrian can take 'em!
- Uhh...
- They would love that!
Would you mind, Adrian?
You mean, take the children
to a restaurant?
- Uh-huh.
- You mean, a public restaurant?
- Umm...
- They would love it.
Sure. Great idea.
Boy, I can't wait.
Monk, I'm wide awake.
Wide awake.
Get over here.!
He's hurt bad.! Hurry up.!
Right. Okay, good work. Captain?
- What?
- You were right.
Second shooting at the truck depot?
Thirty-aught-six from
a Winchester... the same gun.
So they're both union related.
Don't try to tell me any different.
- What about the barefoot angle?
- What about it?
Well, Monk seems to think
the union isn't... - Look.!
It's not his wife being fed
through a tube, is it?
No, sir.
You know, I've been reading about this,
uh... this sniper.
That's, uh, really terrifying.
The police think it's union related.
And what-what, you don't agree?
I think the second shooting was
a diversion to throw us all off the trail.
Hmm. Well, it's still a tough case.
How do you feel?
I'm torn.
Half of me is worried about Karen,
and 40% is worried about
Captain Stottlemeyer,
and five percent...
is relieved...
that somebody finally understands
what I've been going through.
You know that's not 100%?
I know. I always keep...
part of me empty
for-for emergencies.
What... So-So, what, you-you offered
to take the two boys to lunch?
I didn't exactly offer.
I just felt it was, uh...
it was something that
I-I-I had to, uh... Sorry.
I can't concentrate.
What is that noise?
Oh. Oh, that's, uh,
the white noise machine.
We've always had it here.
No, this one's different.
Well, yeah. I mean,
the-the other one broke.
Uh, it's just a new... newer model.
But it's the same.
No, it's not.
No. The old one went,
"shuuu."
And this one goes, "shiii,"
not "shuuu," "shiii."
It's like a half an octave higher. I'm...
I'm sure all your patients
are complaining.
No, No, actually, you're the only one.
Well, they're being polite.
Is that better?
No.
All right, Adrian, would you like me
to try to get the old machine fixed?
- Oh, that would be great.
- Uh-huh.
Thank you.
I'll wait here.
I didn't mean now, Adrian.
I'll try to have it for next week.
- Captain.
- What's that?
That savings and loan robbery
in Delmare last Monday.
Clerk was shot and killed
during the get away.
- The clerk was 22 years old.
- I got it, Rick.
Captain?
Captain.
What? - We've got other cases, sir,
and they're starting to pile up.
No! Randy, you have other cases.
In this room, there are no other cases.!
Understood?
What the hell is this?
What is he doing here?
Harry Bolston to see Agent Grooms.
Yeah. He'll be right with you.
Good. You got a room around here
where I can make a call in private?
Right out here, first door to your right.
- Agent Grooms called him in.
- He... Without my okay?
According to Grooms,
he's been cooperating.
Yeah, I'll bet he's been cooperating.
Sir, don't.
Randy. This is my house.
Randy, the man is in my house.
- Where'd Bolston go?
- Conference room.
Just spend the money.
Yeah, that's what the strike fund is for.
Later.
Captain Stottlemeyer.
Captain Stottlemeyer is not here.
It's just us, Harry.
Just a couple of guys.
I heard about your wife.
I'm sorry, I really am.
- What's her name?
- Her name is Karen.
Well, I'll look into it.
And if it was one of my crew,
I'll take care of it.
It was one of your crew, Harry.
Probably handpicked.
- Everything okay, boss?
- Yeah.
Why don't you call in some more goons,
make it a fair fight?
Now, listen, Captain. I can't do business
with you hounding me like this.
So what's it gonna take to
get you off of my back?
It's gonna take a heck of lot more
than your girlfriend here.
Stay down!
Oh, boy!
- What did you do?
- He didn't do anything.
My friend tripped...
on his own shoelaces.
It wasn't me.
Ever been here before, Mr. Monk?
No.
No, I don't... go out much.
Oh, we come here all the time.
Well, I can see why.
It's so... loud...
and... loud.
- Is this really what the '50s were like?
- Exactly.
It's like a time machine.
Max, stay in the lines, okay?
Max, you have to stay inside the lines.
I don't want to.
Please. It's-It's a rule.
Rules are fun, huh?
Finish that later, okay?
Hey, cats and kittens, what's shaking?
I'm Cindy-Lou.
I'll be your waitress.
Who's ready to roll?
I'll have an Astro Burger and a Coke.
Me, too. - Yeah.
How about you, Pops?
Uhhh.
Uh, nothing.
I'm fine. I'm good.
I just ate, uh,
nine hours ago.
All right. I'll be back in two shakes.
Say something crazy.
Hey Max, he's not crazy, okay?
He's... troubled.
Thank you, Jared.
I saw your mom today.
She-She's really doing great.
The doctors say she's gonna be
coming home soon.
I pray for her every night.
Yeah, me too.
Check please.
- Isn't this fun?
- Yes, it is.
But what are you gonna do?
What is it with you and this sundial?
I remembered something when
I was with Stottlemeyer's kids.
- How'd that go?
- Fine, fine. Kids love me.
Oh, my God, he's back!
I told you before!
This is private property!
We'll just be one second, ma'am.
Thank you very much.
Call the captain.
I solved the case.
Go!
- Who... What... She did it?
- No. I wish she did.
- You solved it with the sundial?
- The sundial is the key.
Okay, we've got our warrant.
We're going into the union
headquarters building here.
- I need a block at these two
intersections. - It's already done, sir.
All right, now, the main offices are
on floors two and three.
- Are they armed?
- We're not sure. Assume yes.
We're going in heavy.
Two entry teams... here and here.
Nobody's knocking.
We pick and ram.
- Who's takin' point on Team One?
- That would be me.
I go in first.
Harry Bolston is mine.
- Any questions?
- Okay, it's showtime!
- Disher.
- Suit up! Vests and helmets!
Okay. Captain, that was Monk.
He said he solved the case.
- He what?
- He says it's not a union thing.
Is he sure?
He's Monk.
It's your call, Captain.
Stand down!
Hey, Monk!
What do you got?
You got a name? Okay.
- Take it easy.
- Don't worry.
I'm not gonna hurt anybody.
I promised Karen.
What do you got?
Evan Coker.
This was his car.
This was the car that was being towed
when the driver was shot on Monday.
Yeah, remember that dog I found?
It belonged to Evan Coker.
Coker, yeah.
Yeah, it was being repossessed.
I mean, we checked him out.
He was clean.
I mean, I don't even think
he was worried about losing it.
- Didn't he just buy a new T-Bird?
- He didn't care about the car.
He cared about something in the car.
What, money?
A handgun in the glove compartment.
Look at the owner's manual.
That's gun oil, isn't it?
It sure is.
He kept a handgun in here.
- A gun he had to get back.
- Why?
I... I don't know. Obviously, it...
it connected him to something.
Something worth killing for.
Here's what happened.
On Monday morning, the sound of the
tow truck must have woken him up.
His car was being repossessed.
He knew that if the car ever
got to the impound lot,
they'd find his gun.
Somehow he had to stop that truck.
He had less than a minute to
come up with a plan.
He didn't have time to get dressed
or put his shoes on,
which explains the footprints.
The truck had to go all the way back
through town to reach the highway.
He knew that if he ran,
he could head it off.
That's how the dog got loose...
and how the sundial next door
got turned around.
He cut through the backyards,
across the edge of the park,
climbed through the chain-link fence,
and waited for the tow truck.
Then... - Yeah, I know
what happened after that.
Right after the crash,
he retrieved the gun.
There was a gravel road, and
he didn't want to walk home barefoot.
So before he left,
he stole the dead driver's shoes.
And somehow he managed to get out of
there without anyone noticing him.
Don't move her!
Don't move her! - Get some help!
Well, what about the second
shooting at the truck depot?
Strictly for our benefit.
He wanted us to keep thinking
it was a union thing.
What do you think?
- It's good enough for me.
- Okay, Captain.
Wait a second.
Wait a second!
Captain, wait. We've got to...
We've got to call the task force.
We need a search warrant.
We got this guy.
We've got him.
Let's do it right.
Hey!
What are you doing here?
I was just in the neighborhood.
Hi.!
He missed you.
Actually, we both did.
What happened to your feet?
Oh, a windsurfing accident.
Mm. - You wanna come in?
Well, actually I'm not alone.
I have a few friends with me.
Great. The more the merrier.
- What's going on?
- It's a warrant.
My friends wanna look around.
Look for what?
A rifle, a handgun,
maybe a pair of shoes...
taken off a dead truck driver.
Do you know who I am?
I'm Leland Stottlemeyer.
I read about you, uh...
How's your wife?
My wife is gonna be fine.
The doctors saved her life.
You should call them and thank them,
because they saved yours too.
You might wanna let the lieutenant
hold that for you.
Why? Are you afraid I'll use it?
I would.
I understand now, Monk.
You can't let it go, can you?
No.
Don't ever lose that watch.
I won't.
- Anything?
- Not yet.
Is that it?
Can I start cleaning
my place up now, please?
No.
Step inside. I'd like to ask you
some more questions.
Thank you.
Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
It's garbage day!
Hey! Stop!
Stop the truck!
What are you doing?
Hold it.!
Hold it there.!
Oh, my God, Mo', it's him, man.
- How'd he find us?
- Leave that garbage!
- Let's just go, man. Let's just go.
- Don't... Wait up!
- You've got the gun.!
- Go! Go! Let's get out of here!
Wait! Don't go!
Don't go! Wait!
- That guy is demented.
- No, no, no, wait!
It's going!
Stop.! Stop.!
There's evidence in there.!
Stop. There's evidence in there!
Wait up!
Turn off the compactor!
Did Adrian Monk just jump into
a garbage truck?
Yeah.
- You okay?
- Mm-hmm.
Brown Merrills, ten and a half.
You get these off the driver you shot?
What else you got in the bag?
Beretta, a nine-millimeter.
The savings and loan job in Delmare.
Do me a favor!
Resist! Go ahead, please!
Captain, don't.! Captain.
Don't do this.
You'll lose your badge.
It's not worth it.
You're right. He's not.
He's not worth it.
Arrest him.
Don't hurt him.
Mr. Coker, you're under arrest
for three counts of felony murder.
Get him out of here!
Read him his rights.
Hi!
- Mommy!
- Boys! Oh, my little sweeties.
Hi. Oh, I missed you so much.
I love you fellas.
Smile.
Oh, my... Where did you get that?
- I bought it.
- A digital camera!
Oh, Leland!
But we can't afford it, and the other
camera was not even insured.
- It's only money.
- "Only money"?
Yeah. - Who got hit on the head,
me or you?
That would be me.
Oh! Mmm!
Ew!
- I love you.
- I love you too.
Mmm.