How long will you be?
Oh, I don't know.
Uh, not very long.
Carol?
Yes. Are you Michael?
Yes.
Nice to meet you.
Am I late?
Not at all.
Brian was right. You are lovely.
Thank you.
Uh, our dinner reservations
aren't until 9:00.
Would you like a drink?
Sure.
You didn't have to drive.
I'd have been happy to pick you up.
Sometimes I have to work late.
Anyway, I prefer to drive myself.
In case you need a quick getaway?
Blind dates can be a bit grim sometimes.
Ever since Brian joined the firm,
He's been trying to marry me off.
Are you divorced?
Uh, widower.
I'm sorry.
No, that's all right.
What kind of work do you do?
I work with a publishing company.
I'm one of many editors.
It's no big deal.
I read manuscripts and
take work home at night.
I've known Connie for years.
After my divorce,
She took me on as something of a project.
She thinks I work too hard.
I hope you don't mind my asking,
But why did you accept a blind date?
I don't know.
Connie was seeing Brian,
And the three of us
Had been out to dinner
a couple of times.
He seemed like a nice guy.
Connie said the senior partner
in Brian's law firm
Was coming to Los Angeles,
And that you were some heavy-duty lawyer
And a really nice guy.
I said I was busy.
She said, what did I have to lose?
The worst thing that could happen is
I'd have a nice meal.
Your friend's right.
Dinner will be good.
Mr. Tarlow?
Message for you, sir.
Thank you.
Excuse me.
Oh.
I have to go upstairs
and make a phone call.
Anything serious?
No. Just an anxious client.
Would you like to come up?
I won't be very long.
I know it sounds fishy.
If you prefer to stay down here,
I'll  just be a little while.
No. It's all right.
I'll come.
Thank you.
Wow, this is beautiful.
It is, isn't it?
Have a look around.
I'll just be a minute.
Yeah, hi, It's Tarlow.
Is he there?
Are you sure?
I got a message to call him.
Tell him I returned his call, OK?
Thank you.
Leo.
I just got a message to call you.
Hello, Michael.
I thought you were in New Orleans.
Yeah, but...
I decided to come home a day early.
I wish you would have let me know.
I'd have called you.
There's no need for that now, is there?
You going to invite us in?
Uh, yeah. Sure. Excuse me.
Wootton, this is Michael Tarlow,
My lawyer.
Michael, Jack Wootton.
How do you do?
Sit down.
Can I get you something to drink?
No, thank you.
I take it you've been busy.
Yeah.
What brings you to Los Angeles?
I'm closing the gallway deal.
I should have papers on your desk soon.
You didn't have to come here.
You could have called.
When you do things face to face,
It's a lot clearer.
I agree.
You seem edgy, Michael.
That's not like you.
I'm fine.
What can I do for you?
I have a problem.
I need your advice.
that's what you pay me for.
that's right.
That's what I pay you for.
There's a man who works for me.
He's close to me. I trusted him.
So what's the problem?
He got himself into some
financial trouble.
He made some investments.
He leveraged himself up to his eyeballs.
The investments didn't work out.
He got himself in serious debt.
He didn't come to me and
tell me his problem.
He didn't come to the man
who trusted him
And ask for help.
What he did was, he just took my money,
Took a lot of it.
He was very clever,
so it was very hard to find out about.
I need your advice, Michael.
What should I do with this man?
Leo...
What do you think?
What would you do?
Now, you don't understand, Leo.
I understand.
I can explain it.
Good.
I would like you to.
It's not what you think. I would never-
Please, Michael.
Have enough respect for me not to lie.
I...
I was desperate, Leo.
I took some funds from
the con-amalgate account...
To cover a loan. I--
I was going to pay you back.
I swear!
I'm so disappointed in you, Michael.
For god's sake, you got to believe me.
You know I'd pay you back.
Michael, don't be afraid.
You're acting like you think
I'll harm you.
Michael...
Even though we were close,
Even though you betrayed me,
And I trusted you,
I would never harm you.
Here's what You're going to do.
You're going to go back to New York.
Someone else will close
the gallway deal.
I will never do business with you again.
You'll pay me back what
you owe with interest.
If you have to sell your nice apartment
With the David Hockneys,
Then You'll do that.
You will pay me back.
I will never speak to you again.
You're right, Michael.
It's better to talk these things
over face to face.
It's clearer that way.
Good bye, Michael.
don't get up.
Oh, Michael?
I lied.
Yeah?
Caulfield here.
What?
How soon can you be here?
Five minutes is too long.
Right.
He's in a conference.
Good morning.
Won't you come in?
Martin, James,
Detective sergeant Benti.
Nice meeting you.
This is James Dahlbeck.
Like Caulfield, He's a deputy D. A.
We were discussing his trial tomorrow.
that's why my door was closed.
I believe It's called a conference.
Remember those latents we found
On the bathroom glass in Tarlow's suite?
Yes. They never checked out.
Not in California.
But detective sergeant Benti's been hard at work.
I'm impressed.
Go ahead, detective sergeant.
Make me look good.
We ran those prints
through the federal computer.
They belong to carol Hunnicut,
Arrested for disorderly conduct in 1981,
Some kind of antinuke bullshit.
She works for a publishing company.
She's been absent since Tarlow died.
This is riveting.
He'll get your attention.
I checked through our logs.
Two days after Tarlow died, we got a call.
Constance billings said her friend
was Missing.
We told her to file
a Missing persons report.
She changed her mind,
said maybe her friend left for a while.
She never gave us the friend's full name,
Just carol.
Still with us?
I'm holding my own.
I got Constance's address
and went to see her
Early this morning.
Before they've had their coffee,
They rattle easier.
She didn't want to see me from nothing.
She said she didn't know anything.
She had total amnesia.
She was scared shitless.
I said we'd protect her and her friend.
We couldn't if she didn't help.
She cracked like a raw egg.
Then she comes out with it.
The reason why
Hunnicut's fingerprints
were on the glass
Is because she was there
when Tarlow got hit.
She saw it.
She was there.
It gets better.
It gets a lot better.
Guess who Was there with the button man?
You're kidding?
Leo fucking Watts.
In person.
In living color.
The woman Was in the other room.
She saw everything.
Everything.
Nobody knew about her.
Where is she?
She understand ably freaked and took off.
She called her friend,
told her what happened,
And that she was still alive.
She's hiding in a cabin in east Jesus.
There is a god.
Unbelievable.
I've chartered a plane.
It'll fly to a small strip.
A helicopter will fly us where she is.
I'll pick her up.
Nobody knows anything about her.
Leo's in for a surprise.
Meantime, get your warrant.
What if she won't talk?
She'll talk.
You know this for a fact?
I'll promise her protection.
I'll offer her relocation.
She has to talk.
Shouldn't you find out
if she'll cooperate?
There's no phone.
She might just take off.
Where is this place?
In Canada.
I can't authorize this
Without checking with the director
of branch and area operations.
I have to follow procedure.
This is Leo Watts.
We've got him for murder one.
You understand what that means?
I do. I still have to check.
What's the matter with you?
Nothing.
Why are you doing this again?
Doing what?
Last year we had him.
You put me in your bureaucratic blender,
And we lost him.
You had uncorroborated statements
From an informant doing hard time
Who'd sell his own mother.
In fact, he did try that,
Except his mother had been dead
for 10 years.
You want to make the announcement?
Television cameras are an aphrodisiac to you.
You could be on the news.
Does that satisfy you?
Our job is to convict criminals,
Not to have them acquitted.
I'll conduct business in a proper way,
Whether it pleases you or not.
I don't like the implications
of what You're saying.
Let's go.
We're going.
We're going now.
Not without my authorization.
Why does he have to fly so low?
We're not low.
The ground's high.
See?
Now we're high.
I hate these things.
Sorry, sir.
A little turbulence in the thermals
On the mountain's windward side.
I don't want to know about thermals.
You have to admit,
the scenery's spectacular.
If I want scenery, I'll  get a postcard.
How much longer?
We'll be there in five minutes.
that's too long.
What does she look like?
I don't care.
I don't like the company she keeps.
You realize when we go down,
Nobody will find us except
some fucking moose.
You think top gun up there can tell
If somebody's following us?
Like what, a condor?
There it is.
Keep the motor running, OK?
It's warm.
Miss Hunnicut?
I'm detective sergeant Dominick Benti,
Los Angeles police department.
With me is deputy district
attorney Robert Caulfield.
We know You're in there.
We'll wait all day if we have to.
Real cold out here.
Hope we don't have to.
Can I see some identification, please?
What do you want?
I think you know.
I don't know what You're talking about.
You were witness to a murder.
We'd like you to testify.
I never saw anything.
How did you find me?
Constance billings told us.
She said you saw a lot.
I have nothing to say.
You wouldn't happen to have a drink,
would you?
You' re on duty.
I only drink when I'm on duty.
How do I know who you are?
You saw our i. d.
It could be fake. I wouldn't know.
If we were going to do you some harm,
We'd have done it already.
There's coffee on the stove.
Do you have any beer?
No.
Nice place.
Thanks.
Jesus! She really doesn't have beer.
We'd really like you to come back
and testify.
I'm not going anywhere with you.
I didn't see anything.
I don't know anything.
I'm not testifying.
aren't you pleasant.
I really have nothing to say to you.
Please leave.
You don't realize your situation.
I know exactly the situation I'm in.
I don't think you do.
We can protect you.
They'll find you here.
There's no reason for anyone
to come after me.
I'm not testifying.
I have a subpoena.
Let me see it.
I can get one.
I think you should leave.
Lady, You're kidding yourself.
You think those guys would come here,
You, who could put Leo Watts
in the gas chamber,
And you tell them You're not testifying,
And they' d say, that's a relief.
Thanks.
Have a nice day.
Then they'd turn around and go home?
They'd never find me.
We did.
I'll take my chances.
Do you have the keys to that car?
On the table.
I don't suppose There's a back door,
is there?
No.
How about a window?
Yes. It's in the bathroom.
You get to that window, all right?
Keep low. Wait for me there.
Go! Go!
Now!
What have you done to me?
Nobody knew where I was.
Sorry. I didn't know
they were following us.
aren't you supposed to?
isn't that your job?
How could you let somebody follow you?
Where's the closest telephone?
8 miles down this road.
The trains slowing down.
How far to the station?
About a half mile.
Let's go.
Excuse me.
Where's the closest big town?
I beg your pardon.
A big city with an airport.
Where's the nearest one?
East, about 1 00 miles.
Which way is this train heading?
West, of course.
Vancouver's as big as you get.
This train goes to Vancouver.
How long does that take?
You arrive Vancouver 1 0: 40 a. m.
You're kidding?
No, You're not kidding.
I'd like a private compartment.
Sorry. All we got left is coach seats.
I have to have a private compartment.
Then wait until tomorrow.
I'll see if we got space on that train.
I have to be on that train.
I'd like to help you out.
There's nothing I can do.
I have to lie down.
She has to lie down.
If I go into labor, I have to lie down.
The baby' s not due
for another two weeks--
I have to lie down.
It's OK.
I couldn't help overhearing.
My wife and i, we have a compartment.
You kids need it more than we do.
We couldn't do that.
Please. I insist.
I remember how it was with our mark.
Is this your first?
Yes. that's very kind. Thank you.
I'll pay for both tickets.
I insist.
Is there a phone on the train?
Afraid not.
$ 1 95, please.
that's car 564, drawing room A.
It's toward the end of the train.
Thank you.
Get on the train.
don't wait for me.
Get in the room, lock the door.
don't let anybody in.
They probably haven't seen you.
All right. Here.
Go. Go.
I'm really very grateful.
that's quite all right.
Take care of the little lady.
Yes?
There's been some mistake.
This is my compartment.
If There's a mistake, It's yours.
This is our compartment.
You're sure?
Yes, of course I'm sure.
Could you please excuse us?
The conductor said this was mine.
He couldn't have said that.
This is our compartment.
Could I see your ticket, please?
Can I see yours?
My wife has our tickets.
Well, maybe your wife is
in the proper car.
This is my son. This is not your wife.
This is our compartment.
I would like you to leave.
This guy's lying.
I'm sorry for the inconvenience, really.
I'm always getting myself
into these kinds of things.
One time, I, uh, I lost my car.
I parked it in a parking lot
And forgot where I parked it.
I just--
You know what that's like.
No, I don't. Would you please get out?
Yes, of course. I'm sorry.
Is this car 564?
No.
Well, there you are.
See? I've done it again.
I'm supposed to be in car 564.
Maybe you should go to car 564.
Would you know where that is?
No, I wouldn't.
He's lying, mom. He's a train robber.
Why would I want a train?
Do you have a gun?
I guess I'll see the conductor.
He'd know where car 564 is,
wouldn't you think?
I'd expect so. Try doing that.
I'll do that.
I'll go find him
And ask him where car 564 really is.
Good idea.
Well, uh, sorry for the inconvenience.
You folks have a nice trip.
You, too.
It's me, Caulfield.
How you doing?
I've been better.
Yeah, me, too.
So, are we expecting company?
There's two of them.
It won't take them long
to find this compartment.
I'm getting off at the next stop.
that's impossible.
You watch me.
We'd be sitting ducks out there.
Who said anything about we?
You're going out there alone?
We're in the middle of
a goddamn wilderness.
Look out the window, for Christ's sakes.
You're going out there on foot?
A breeze.
I can protect you better here.
Protect me?
You're the one who put me in danger.
I'm not stupid, Mr. Caulfield.
I won't survive stuck on this train
until tomorrow.
Let me tell you something.
A police officer died
Trying to help get you back
to Los Angeles.
I'm going to get you back there.
I can't tell you what a comfort that is.
I don't think I like you.
The weekend in Paris is off?.
You got a big mouth.
Use it on the witness stand.
I don't think you hear very well.
I'm not testifying at this trial.
You still don't get it.
These guys are grownups
with automatic weapons.
If they see you, they'll kill you.
We got two things going for us--
One, they've seen me, but maybe not you.
They might not recognize you.
And... we got one thing going for us.
But I've got you to protect me.
Who is it?
The conductor, sir.
Uh, yes?
I'm sorry to disturb you.
A gentleman has lost his briefcase.
Yeah.
Well, we think the porter
may have left it
In one of these compartments by mistake.
We're checking the whole car.
It's not in here.
You're welcome to take a look
if you'd like.
Thank you.
Hmm. I guess It's not in here.
I guess not.
I'm sure It's in this car someplace.
Maybe not.
We'll keep looking.
I'm sorry to have bothered you, sir.
He'll be back, won't he?
Yeah.
How do we stop him?
We don't.
Want me to set out some hors doeuvres?
I want you to do exactly
what I tell you to do.
Excuse me.
I wasn't looking where I was going.
that's quite all right, sir.
Operator, I want to make a collect call
to James Dahlbeck.
My name is Caulfield. C-a-u-l-f-i-e-l-d.
Caulfield, where the hell are you?
I'm on a train.
You're on a what?
We were followed. Sergeant Benti's dead.
It seems strange.
Larner doesn't want to send me here,
Then we're followed.
You're way off base.
Think so?
Two times in one year
he tries to stop me.
that's stretching coincidence, isn't it?
What can I say?
don't say anything. Just listen.
At least two guys are following us.
One has an automatic weapon.
Maybe they both do.
The helicopter was destroyed,
the pilot is dead.
The Perps are on the train.
They don't know what the girl looks like.
They sure as hell know what I look like.
Where the hell's this train?
We're heading west towards Vancouver.
We'll be there at 1 0:00 a.m.
We can't hold out. They'll find her.
Where's the next stop?
Uh, a town called Monashee.
We'll be in there about midnight.
Do what you can to keep the girl
hidden until then.
I'll have you met at the next station.
don't say anything to Larner about this.
I won't. Hey, uh... You hang in there.
Yeah, sure.
He's gone.
We're changing cars.
This one is getting too popular.
We get into the next station
around midnight.
There'll be some people there to meet us.
Then we can get off this damn train.
Thank god.
These guys can't just go blasting
Everybody in sight.
They' re professionals.
They start a war on a train
in the boondocks,
They got a good chance of being caught.
They have to find you, do it cleanly,
Without drawing attention to themselves.
If they don't know where you are,
You're OK.
It's going to be OK, really.
I'm telling you,
It's going to be all right.
I'm not going to Los Angeles with you.
I'm telling you right now, I'm not going.
You hungry?
Oh, I don't know.
I'll  get you something.
I'm not hungry.
Lock this door.
don't let the porter or the conductor--
I said I'm not hungry.
You need something to eat.
OK, you stay, and I'll go.
What?
Every time you leave
And every time you come back,
you put me in danger.
They know what you look like.
They don't know me. I'll go myself.
Suppose they do know what you look like?
Maybe they've seen you.
Maybe your photograph was faxed
When they checked you out.
W ant to risk that?
You don't want to bring me food.
Lock the door behind me.
May I get you something to drink, sir?
Yeah, a beer, please.
What kind?
Oh, I don't know. You choose.
Yes, sir.
Oh!
I'm terribly sorry!
It's all right. It's OK.
Does it hurt?
It's just my foot.
I'll grow another in a week.
I'm so clumsy. I'm sorry.
It's not you, It's the train.
It's very bumpy, that's all.
No, It's me.
I'm always doing things like that.
Oh, I'm sorry again.
It's OK. It's OK. It's the same foot.
Gee!
Can I buy you something to drink?
No, that's not necessary.
I'd like to.
I'm fine, really.
I insist. I am clumsy, but I have money.
I'm not that liberated yet.
I'll  have the same, please,
and this is for both of them.
Here, let me--
No, no, It's done. Was it so difficult?
I feel like Phil Donahue.
My name, Skathryn Weller.
I'm Robert Caulfield.
How are you?
Good.
You don't look like somebody
who takes the train.
What does somebody who takes
the train look like?
Patient.
Yeah, It's the first time I've done this.
No, that's fine.
Thank you, ma'am.
How about you? Do you do this often?
No, not often. I, uh...
I was trying to water-ski on lake Louise.
I wasn't good at it. I tend to fall down.
I noticed.
I'm also terrified of flying, so...
Really? I don't mind that at all.
I'm in no rush.
The one thing I have is time.
You also said you had money.
Oh, i, uh... i had a good divorce lawyer.
Am I interrupting you?
No, I'm sorry, really. I, uh...
Well, Here's to, uh...
Community property.
Come to think of it, I earned it.
Are you--
Are you traveling alone?
Yes.
Oh.
How long were you married?
Six years.
Mm-hmm.
One day over bran muffins--
He loved bran muffins--
He said he had to find himself,
just like that.
I'm standing there with
a pot of brewed decaf--
He only drank brewed decaf--
And he said he had to find himself.
I asked if he wanted
to finish breakfast first.
Ha ha!
Before I knew it,
He'd taken his air popcorn maker--
No cholesterol, you see--
And his lifecycle and moved
into this nice duplex
With a 23-year-old waitress
from one of his restaurants.
Not bad for somebody who's lost.
He won't run out of waitresses.
You'll have to excuse me.
I'm sorry, I've been talking too much.
I tend to do it--
No, It's not you.
I understand.
I wish I could explain, but--
By the way,
I think your restaurant guy is nuts.
I don't think this will work.
I'll back up. It's shorter this way.
I appreciate that.
These things weren't designed
For people my size.
No one loves a fat man but his grocer.
Did you find your briefcase yet, sir?
No, not yet.
aren't your seats
at the head of the train?
that's right. I get mixed up.
Well, it can be confusing, sir.
Thank you.
What the--
Shh! Shh!
Please. I'm not going to hurt you.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
You're supposed to say something.
Like what?
Something reassuring.
It's going to work out.
Thanks. That made a world of difference.
We'll be in the station soon.
You'll be safe when we get there.
I hope they've gotten
to your cabin by now
And taken care of Benti.
He shouldn't be left alone like that.
I'm sorry about your friend.
He wasn't my friend.
I just met him.
The jerk.
Two years away from retirement.
I'm sorry.
Are you?
There are two guys on this train.
One killed a police officer and a pilot.
I couldn't see in the helicopter.
I couldn't identify them,
You couldn't identify them,
Except...
They' re the guys.
They work for Leo Watts.
There's nothing I can do.
All I can charge him with
is riding on a train.
They're going to walk.
There'll be a funeral for Benti.
Flag-draped coffin,
Everybody in dress blues,
His picture on the precinct wall,
People saying how terrible it was.
Another funeral for the pilot,
Not as spiffy as Benti's.
No flags, nothing like that.
There'll be two wives serving
a lot of food,
Two groups of children trying
to be very brave.
Those two guys died
Trying to help get you back
to Los Angeles,
And the two guys who killed them
Are going to walk,
Unless you testify against the man
who sent them up here.
Two years from retirement.
What a jerk.
Keep the lights out.
Jesus, they didn't exactly
bring out the national guard.
I guess they didn't want to
attract too much attention.
You stay here, OK?
don't do anything,
but just stay out of sight.
When we're ready,
when I think It's secure,
I'll come and get you.
Oh, and, uh...
I know, I know, lock it.
You Caulfield?
Yeah.
I'm sergeant Nigro, rcmp.
This is detective Loughlin.
They sent two of you, huh?
It's a pretty remote area.
Backup's on the way.
So, you guys are mounties?
Yes, uh, we don't really
use horses anymore.
that's mostly for the tourists.
Besides, horses don't
have air conditioning.
I don't think we should
stand around out here
Any longer than is necessary.
Where's the woman?
She's on the train. I've got her hidden.
A couple guys on the train
have been following us.
They're armed.
I think I've got them on a possible 314.
Let's get the woman into safe custody.
Your 3 1 4s can't get anywhere.
We'll send units to meet
the train at the next stop.
We'll nail them.
I think You're right.
Why don't you get the woman
And we can get out of here?
Right. I know You'll think
this is dumb of me,
But I haven't been feeling good lately.
My stomach, you know.
So I got to run over to the toilet
For a second.
Are you serious?
I don't have any choice.
You know what It's like.
I'll  be right back.
Mr. Caulfield, you all right?
Caulfield?
Shithead.
A 3 1 4 is indecent exposure.
You're no cop.
Who sent you?
Fuck you.
You're a dead man, do you know that?
You all right, sir?
Yeah. That was close.
I was taking a walk.
I didn't realize the train was leaving.
You could have been hurt.
That was stupid of me.
I'll never do that again.
I certainly hope not.
Listen...
Never mind.
Mr. Caulfield,
I have a business proposition
That might interest you.
Would you care for a drink?
What will you have? It's my treat.
Coffee, please.
Seven and seven for me,
And scotch for my associate.
I figured him for something
with an umbrella in it.
He won't lose his composure.
He's very good at what he does.
So am i.
But I do it for a living. He enjoys it.
People should have fun at work.
It makes the day go by quicker.
As I said,
I have a business proposition for you.
Tell me,
How much does a deputy district attorney
Make in a year?
Enough. Oh, I doubt that.
Are you thinking of becoming a lawyer?
I was thinking we might
negotiate an arrangement
That would be mutually satisfactory.
He says he thinks we can make a deal.
Ha ha ha.
Does he speak?
Yeah. Sometimes very convincingly.
I'm going to enjoy this.
Thank you. Keep the change.
Thank you, sir.
The people I work for
are very determined.
They want the woman.
You have her,
And the question is simply,
How much do you want?
What woman?
Well, you know we're going to find her.
It's just a matter of time.
What I'm proposing here
Is that you recognize the inevitable.
I don't know what woman
You're talking about.
First you lost your briefcase,
And now you've lost some woman.
You ought to be more careful.
The people I work for
have a large investment in this matter,
And they are very determined.
They sound like interesting people.
Very interesting.
You have a good dental plan?
What I'm talking about
Is probably 1 0 times
what you earn in a year,
Including whatever you
steal on your expense account.
I don't steal.
I like an honest man.
So do I.
10 times.
You could never make that much
if you worked another 30 years.
Possibly you won't survive that long.
that's true.
All you have to do is point her out
And look the other way.
Now, that's not much effort
For more money than you ever dreamed of.
And no risk to you at all.
You go through the motions
of guarding her.
We'll take care of the rest.
This offer doesn't stay
on the table too long.
There are a few things to know
before making your decision.
Jack, show him what you have.
Do you know what this is?
I have a feeling You're going to tell me.
Somethings happened to the
communications gear on this Trai
There's no way for anyone to radio ahead.
that's a shame, isn't it?
The other interesting item
Is that when this train
reaches its destination,
Some people will be waiting for you.
Quite a few of them.
They're not like us.
Now, we have no desire
for needless violence.
We're professionals, like you.
T o have an ugly incident occur on this train
With no method of escape
isn't in our self-interest, either.
However, the men waiting for you,
that's a different matter.
They simply won't let you and that woman
Get off this train and walk away.
It's that simple.
I've been doing some checking on you.
You have an interesting resume.
T op of your law school class.
A decorated marine.
And you have a reputation
for being a very good prosecutor.
You also have a reputation
for having a big mouth.
It seems you pissed off too many people.
You're never going to be the district attorney.
It's a shame, isn't it?
I suppose There's two reasons
Why someone would remain
a deputy district attorney.
You're either rich or afraid to
go out on your own.
There's a third reason.
I don't like people like you,
And I really don't like people
like your boss.
I enjoy putting you away. I really do.
If I wanted to make money,
I'd have to defend you.
That wouldn't be any fun.
I'd always feel like showering.
I enjoy sitting in a courtroom,
Watching the judge pass sentence,
As your shirt collar
starts to get a little tight.
I'll love sitting there watching Leo Watts.
I like my courtroom side.
Pay's not so good, but the air's a lot better.
I'm offering you enough money
to make your whole life different.
don't tell me that
You're above temptation.
I'm very tempted at your offer, yes.
There's just one small problem.
What's that?
I don't know who this woman is
you keep talking about.
I'll really enjoy this.
Give it a rest.
There are no more stops
between here and Vancouver.
Neither of you can get off the train.
You don't have a lot of choice.
Think about it.
I will.
Do you really think
you can get her off this train?
Get who?
Well, uh...
Thank you for the coffee.
Uh-huh.
I've really enjoyed this little chat.
I really have.
I must go now.
We'll talk again.
Yeah, well... I'm in the book.
It's me.
Jesus Christ, what happened?
Your friend Leo Watts has
a buddy in the d.a.'s office.
His name is Dahlbeck.
Those two guys he sent here,
they weren't cops.
I thought you were dead.
Well, I'm not.
When I get to L. A., Dahlbeck is mine.
If you get there.
We'll get there. I'll take care of it.
Are you telling me not to worry
While you work everything out?
This is my life we're dealing with.
I thought you were dead
And I was on my own.
You prance in here with your fancy I. D.
And tell me not to worry?
You're really a jerk.
My friend Leo Watts?
Do you know what really happened?
I mean, do you know anything about me?
I know You're Michael Tarlow's
girlfriend.
It must be really nice
Not to let knowledge get in your way.
I never met Michael Tarlow in my life
Before that night.
I was fixed up on a blind date
By a well-meaning friend.
I saw a man get murdered.
I don't know if he was good man or he was bad man.
I saw someone take his life
As casually as you'd buy a stick of gum.
It's not like it is on television.
It Was horrible.
It's not a part of my life.
It's something you read about,
Except that it never happens to you.
Ohh...
I don't know how I got home that night.
The most difficult part was acting normal
When I paid the babysitter.
Yes. I have a son.
He's 10 years old.
But I thought you would have known th at,
Since you know everything about me.
I just went into his room that night
and watched him sleeping.
Thought maybe the sight of
that kind of innocence
Would make the world seem less horrible.
It didn't.
It was all over the 1 1 :00 news
Who Michael Tarlow was,
That he was a lawyer
For this... famous gangster
named Leo Watts.
They had a photograph of Leo Watts on television.
That was the man in the hotel room.
All I could think of was to run.
I took my son to his father' s house.
I told his father to go away right then.
Not to tell anybody where he was going,
Not even me.
I knew I had to get
as far away from my son as I could.
I went to my brother's cabin.
It's so remote I thought
I'd be safe there.
I figured no one could find me.
So don't you ever judge me.
don't you dare.
I'm scared stiff.
I don't want to die.
I'd gladly die for my son, however.
This is not just about me.
I would like to do the right thing.
I really would. I just--
I'm just so scared.
This is not just about me.
So Here's the program.
You're going to tell me what's going on,
And you'll tell me your ideas
if you have any.
I need to know.
I'm sorry.
They still don't know where you are.
I don't think they'll move tonight
Because they don't have to.
We have to do something
Before this train makes the last stop, though.
We can't get off the train.
There isn't anybody I can call for help.
They've got somebody else on the train
Besides the two guys.
I think I know who it is--
a big, fat guy.
I, uh...
I don't know exactly
what I'm going to do.
I just know that I've--
I have to make my move
before they make theirs.
Why don't you try to get some sleep now?
You're going to need it.
I can't sleep.
don't worry. I'll  be up.
You should wash that.
Thank you.
Ooh. Oh...
It's OK.
Nothing's happened.
OK? We're not dead yet?
No... we're not dead yet.
Well, that's good.
I'm leaving you alone for a little while.
Where are you going?
T o the dining car.
There they can't get by me
Without my seeing them first.
If they come after me,
at least you won't be right next to me.
You'll be all right.
Would you like some coffee?
That would be nice.
Freeze, mister.
You're not robbing this train.
Jesus Christ.
That thing's not for real, is it?
Course not. I'm a kid.
You could get hurt pointing that.
You could go to j ail for robbing people.
I'm not a robber.
I don't believe you.
Now, uh...
Listen, I got to go.
I didn't say you could move.
Well, I got to go.
I'll be watching you.
what's your name?
Nick.
Do you always go around
pretending You're a cop?
Sometimes I'm the bad guy.
I understand. It pays better, right?
But now You're a cop.
Can you keep a secret?
Of course.
Suppose I told you I was really a cop.
No way.
Suppose I could prove it to you.
Suppose I asked you for your help.
Would you give it to me,
Without telling anybody,
not saying anything to anyone?
Prove it.
Is that real?
Yes, it is.
No shit.
This doesn't say You're a cop.
I can read.
doesn't it say deputy?
Are you on a case?
Big one.
Where's your gun?
I don't have it.
If You're a real cop,
how come you don't?
That's the problem.
The bad guys took it.
Are you kidding me?
No. I need your help.
You do?
I need to borrow your gun.
But it's not real.
Well, we won't tell
anybody about that, OK?
Raise your right hand.
Put your left hand on the gun.
I'm going to deputize you.
According to California state laws
And international laws of criminal justice,
I hereby deputize you as special assistant...
Uh, subject to all the laws of, uh...
Secrecy and jurisprudence, so help me god. Say I do.
I do. What does it mean?
It means, um...
If you say anything about this,
Your ass is grass.
OK.
OK, deputy.
Go see your mother now. Just act normal.
Yes, sir.
Good morning, sir.
Would you like some breakfast?
Uh, no, thanks. Just some coffee,
please. Black.
And a cup of coffee to go.
Certainly, sir.
Well. Good morning.
Good morning.
Mind if I join you?
I'm just having coffee.
I'm not having breakfast.
Um... oh, of course.
Please. Sit down.
Thank you.
Sleep well?
Not much.
Me, too.
It's so difficult to sleep on a train.
God, It's beautiful, isn't it?
Yes, yes.
Good morning, ma'am.
Would you care for some breakfast?
Um, just some tea, please.
And some toast.
What kind of bread?
Any kind. Wheat?
You, um, getting coffee for someone?
No. I thought I'd have a cup here
And take a cup back to the compartment.
I have reading to do before we get in.
What kind of work do you do?
Mmm. Sales.
What do you sell?
Construction, um... Supplies.
Heavy equipment.
Oh, I see.
You don't look like the salesman type.
What type is that?
Well, somebody who looks comfortable
With a name tag on their pocket.
Hello, my name is...
Yes. I don't have to do that.
Your toast is coming.
Thanks.
Where are you from?
Uh, Los Angeles.
Oh, I go there quite often.
In fact, I'm going to be there
next week.
I stay at the, um, the belair.
that's a very nice place.
Would you like to see me?
What did you say? I'm sorry.
Nothing. It's not important.
No, what did you say?
I feel like an idiot.
I asked if you'd like to see me again.
How's she doing?
Your wife.
I gave him my compartment.
He had coach seats.
His wife looked ready to have the baby.
She's doing fine, thank you.
that's very kind of you.
I hope you and your wife
were not uncomfortable.
Hell, no. We played cards all night.
I cheat. So does she. But I cheat better.
that's why she's buying breakfast.
Well, I got to be going.
Hope everything turns out right.
Thank you. You don't understand.
I do understand.
Please.
You don't have to apologize.
No, please. I just--
I can't explain. Please.
Come with me.
What?
Come with me now.
I don't want to.
I'm not asking, I'm telling.
You're in danger.
What's going on here?
What is it?
Ow!
Where are you taking me? Who are you?
Those two guys think You're someone else.
Let go of me!
Get in your compartment and lock it.
My compartment's back the other way.
You can't go that way.
Tell me what's going on.
I don't have time.
What's the problem here?
This man-- no problem.
Looks like There's one to me.
I don't give a shit.
No way to talk.
Come with me. The name's Keller.
Railroad security.
Step away from the lady
and come with me.
You're a railroad cop?
Two men on this train are trying
to kill someone.
They' re after a woman.
I know who you mean.
I've been watching you all.
Where is she?
She's safe. I believe they think
she's the woman.
How can I help?
Where's your compartment?
One car behind us.
Let's go there.
Keep her in there.
They won't think to look there.
I can call ahead for help.
Communications aren't out?
Mine's a portable.
Have your people contact
The Los Angeles district
attorney's office.
Have them ask for chief deputy district
attorney martin Larner.
No one else. that's important.
I want them to tell Larner that
Dahlbeck is dirty.
Do it right away.
Listen. It's not just your grocer
who loves you.
It's Caulfield.
What took you so long?
We're going to change compartments, OK?
What happened?
Things are looking up.
I'm going to put you in a railroad
cop's compartment.
If nothing else, it'll give us
a little time.
Jesus Christ.
Oh!
They took her.
Who?
There was a woman in here.
They thought she was you.
Oh, dear god.
Oh!
Get out of the way!
Wait!
Get on the roof!.
I can't!
You don't have any choice.
don't think. Just do it.
When you get on the roof, lie flat!
You're doing fine!
End of the line, asshole.
Wiggle your ear. Wiggle your toes.
Come on. I want to do you.
Toy gun.
Ha ha ha ha!
Let's go!
I can't move! I'm afraid!
Yeah, so am i. Let's go. Come on.
I can't.
Come on.
Aah!
Oh!
I don't want you. Just her.
You understand.
It's strictly business.
You should have taken the money.
You know what i like about you?
You're tall.
Oh!
Larner.
This is Caulfield.
Where have you been?
No time to explain. Listen.
Our friend Dahlbeck works for Leo Watts.
We wound up on a train.
The trains stopped.
I'm calling you from a farmhouse.
I'm about 100 miles from Vancouver.
The woman is safe.
I've contacted the Canadian authorities.
They'll be here any minute.
Get in touch with them.
Meet us at the border.
I'm on my way.
And then the man told
Mr. Tarlow not to be afraid.
I remember he said,
Michael, You're acting
As though you think I'll harm you.
And, uh, then he told Mr. Tarlow
That he was to go back to New York
And pay back all the money he owed.
Then he started to walk toward the door,
And he stopped and turned around
and said,
Michael, I lied.
Then the other man that was with him
Turned around and pulled out a gun...
And shot Mr. Tarlow.
Did Mr. Tarlow call anybody
in the room by name?
Yes, he called the man Leo.
Did you get a clear look at Leo?
Yes.
Could you identify him?
Is he here now?
Yes.
Could you point to him?
It's that man sitting right there.
Let the record state that the witness
Has pointed to Mr. Leo Watts.
Thank you, Miss Hunnicut.