The Keeper.
For the record.
You say no warrant to have?
I said I have not
have decided.
How is it done?
The informant is in their.
Do not worry
she will introduce us.
They'll all be.
Obviously not what you do.
You can pot.
Well we talk as friends?
That sounds normal. What?
You call that normal?
Hands up and go against
the wall.
Against the fucking wall.
Everything is safe.
Do you see?
That must have been a few million.
Wait Roland.
K361. Shots fired.
It is 4. The code is 4.
I bring our thoughts together.
We need support.
This is 2 million.
Nobody is claiming this.
You're joking, right?
The informant must have slipped away.
She tells it to anyone yet.
Only we are here and
these streamers.
I still thought I could?
Quiet, Roland.
I fucking something up.
I thought, man.
Roland Jesus, it had
could have been much easier.
We had the money to deal
without anyone surrounded.
Well, do your knees, huh? Everyone
may fall to a heart attack.
I retire and
I move to Utah.
But not you, Ro.
You have just become a hero.
I come back for you later.
This is D63H, there is an agent injured I
have an ambulance immediately.
D63H, what location?
Normandy 107 South-West corner.
Understood!
The ambulance is on its way.
Jesus I think my partner dies.
What time the ambulance arrives?
I need him here now.
It is the day I do, huh?
Sure that you not
the hospital wants. Yeah I'm okay.
It is time to arrest them.
I can not believe he is dead.
What dick you?
He had a pulse, Trevor.
They bring him to the hospital.
What?
The doctors say that 't look bad
sees, but he is still alive.
I saw him breathe his last
breather
He died.
Miracles. Let
We pray that this is one.
I leave you bring to the office
and there you put a statement.
Then take a
few days Fri
What have we here?
Gunshot wound to the chest.
All is ready. The team has come.
Here we come.
His pupils do not respond,
sir.
Give him 10cc.
Put on 75. Vrijf the discs. Free.
10CC and we begin.
I need a pen here?
Oh, Jesus.
It is difficult for him
like that.
He stable for now.
There is brain activity.
But unfortunately we can not say:
when he comes out of the coma.
Is he your uncle?
We worked together.
Give me his status? We can
not with certainty.
We know if he was not within 48 hours
added. Then we ...
testing on him brain damage.
Let me know if something changes?
On the desk is my number.
Roland, I must admit.
You're a tough rascal.
Shit.
That is bad luck.
You're lucky if you
have come far.
Damn ...
you were still
so faithful.
I get you now forever, Roland.
Who wants to really live nou
as a kind of vegetable?
Get the clothes.
Asshole.
You always have the last word.
Hey, pick up. It is Regina.
I listen because I have to come later
to the therapist this afternoon.
What is that good.
We can
arrange another time.
I can only one thing at a time, huh?
I do not know why I
refurbishment this stuff again?
Roland your injuries
killed the most people.
The fact is that you can still walk
is in itself a miracle.
When it is time
we throw them away.
If it is fast.
You have your incredible things
do it.
You are an inspiration to everyone
S.W.A.T that the team wants to hear.
Well, you know what?
I just want
the exercises.
They do.
Are you ready for a walk?
The fresh air will do me good.
I like to hear that.
I am proud of you, Roland.
Like many others.
Texas is not one
bit far away?
Not really, it's a great
State, Ms.
I have trained some.
I have good friends.
What the Chief is his name?
Conner. Standard guest. Good friend.
How are you?
It goes well with me.
it is nice to hear.
This is my dad, Conner Wells.
I stop with that shit man.
Is it so hard, Dad?
They seem fine.
Mason? Hello, dear.
Come here sweetie.
I find it exciting.
No, everything is good.
Well done, Mason. Sit down?
- Thank you, sir.
Cheers.
I would like champagne like here?
Mason?
Hello darling.
You're drunk.
Yeah, and?
What ...?
Where are they ...
It is time to go.
We are only
What about you?
We have only slightly
to celebrate.
Why four you
not with me?
Why are you angry?
I'm sorry sweetie.
Come with me?
Come we get the car and go.
It is too busy with
this lift to go.
Watch the step.
But first I'll go after you.
Here comes the Durak.
Let your ass
of here.
Stay away from the car.
Honey? Oh, shit.
Let me here.
- No ...
have you not had enough?
Of course not.
Go your way guys.
You want a shot?
Okay, I want to go.
Go to the car.
Mason, go back in the car
it is too dangerous.
Neeeeee.
Mason?
Get out of here. Shut up.
- Neeeee.
Go, go, go.
Mason, Mason? No!
Stop the car?
Stop ...
I am not available
leave a message.
Police Pensions Medical Missions
You know that they study
have run against, Trevor?
I thought so on
would be?
That you the next morning
could begin again.
That's what you get from:
20 years loyal service.
Are you:
A good deed does not remain unpunished?
This is special for me thanks.
The medical board wants to improve your recovery.
They want to retire.
You know what I'm going to do?
- Oh, boys.
Hello?
Role ...
I am so glad to hear your voice.
You know you're talking to?
I know.
How does the city enjoyed?
Not bad for an old man.
They treat you well?
Not bad I'm out in the corps.
and I'm under surveillance,
everything else is good, I.
Thank the Lord for this.
I have a problem, Roland.
And I think you're the only
you who can help me?
What can I do for you, brother?
They have tried something
by Nikita
Is she okay?
She is in order.
Well ... But ...
I think it would look better to you
to talk in private.
If you want to get tomorrow
after you?
That is fantastic.
I will arrange everything.
My people will be informed.
See you tomorrow.
A plane is ready for you.
Is good brother.
Hello sir.
How are you, Sir?
I'm Detective Simon. It
I am happy to meet you.
Welcome to the city. Thank you
We still have a point ...
all baggage check
private flights and ...
that is the drug problem
in this continent.
Your name came up.
I understood that you
ex cop.
The fact is that your Security Training
've had ...
here at the police force 10 years
ago.
The good old days.
I understood that you are
retired.
I see that you also firearms
have taken.
I was a cop for 25 years in L.A,
I'll be a friend.
A simple thing. I understand.
I have no support
called.
Joker.
You know how we are agents.
We never go anywhere
without weapons.
Yes I see the matter.
I hope that no
problem is ...
if you remember why
you're here.
I love watching you.
Yes, sir.
I always nice to find someone
behind my back.
That we have ever seen.
Have a good day. Thank you Sir.
Roland Sallinger?
Everything good?
I Chauffeur for Mr. Wells.
Nice to meet you.
Mr. Wells offers his apologies ..
that he was not available ...
to get to personally.
He left his complex to
waiting for you.
If you have children, future wife,
ex-wife, ...
children you know of anything?
Yes who has a nou
radio to ...
you kind of musical talent?
Do you like it?
It's a Mexican National Anthem.
Very popular.
Great.
Hello darling miss us?
Why you do that?
I love girls who swallow.
But that does not spit.
Teach your boyfriend swallow.
Why not tell you where
your brother is his army?
Hey, is that my cousin?
I do not know where they are?
- You do not?
I accept you do not NO,
okay?
That's my cousin.
Elena?
No.
You do not protect
baby, okay?
I kill you ...
Hey, that's my cousin, man.
Stop, leave him alone?
Got a problem?
They owe me money.
What is your problem?
Here you have it, asshole.
Bastards, I cut you open.
Rule one ...
If someone pulls a knife to me,
kill him.
I also have a rule.
I do not kill children.
What should I follow?
No children murder.
Jo ... come?
You will die, bitches.
You really want to murder me,
either?
You die.
Listen to me?
I told you already ..
I do not like children to
to murder.
Try me out.
Let's go.
You do not know who
you arguing?
This is not over, punk.
Huh?
You forget your knife, friend.
Thank you sir.
Henrica, wait?
Pay attention to your sister.
I had problems with
employees of Mr. Cross.
Everything okay with you?
- Yes.
That great man helped me.
His office is right here.
Good Afternoon my friend.
- Hello.
How about that.
Roland, it's too long ago.
Please, are you okay?
My apologies for the security.
What security?
Let's talk.
This way.
- Yes, sir.
Sit Roland.
Thank you
Make yourself comfortable.
It is good to see you, partner.
Likewise.
See that thing there?
You still running
in that piece of junk?
- Yes.
Why is that?
I brought him back
is long past time.
Well, I know how that feels.
Let me tell you, Roland.
A year in Texas ...
and you look at Texas.
That is very nice, thanks.
I'm glad you do
like.
My father came from Texas, I can
This remind me a bit.
Tell me:
what's going on?
Someone has tried,
Nikita to abduct.
Have you any idea who?
Not really.
Any idea why?
There is a change in our
Family Tree.
My father is already deceased.
His oil and land threatening me
lose.
Why do not you call the police?
- I mean ...
In this part of Texas ...
will be on your estimated value.
A man here has everything
under control, I am sure.
Ok. What do you want me to do?
I want ...
you personally for Nikita
care.
I am not a babysitter but ...
I want her bodyguard are you?
Do you buddy?
I feel you
something told me ...
which is very important.
Someone in my organization
perhaps an enemy?
That changes the dynamic case
Roland, you're the only one who
I can trust.
Okay, what can I do?
Nikita, is out.
She is constantly locked
in here ...
and I can not
forever shut.
Listen?
You need security cameras
not work.
You have no direct security
for your windows.
I do not know much about your staff.
If you want me security
Enter line, ...
then you listen to ...
what I say.
Deal?
I will protect you for Nikita.
I make sure that
nothing happens.
Thank you.
I knew I could count on you.
Of course sir.
We will settle you.
Can you take me for?
Honey there is someone here for you.
- Who is that?
You remember, Roland yet?
Damn.
How are you?
Fine, it could not be better with me.
We find a place where he can stay,
Indeed, we are practically family.
He is an expert in several things.
- What do you think?
If I say yes then that means,
I left that house is?
Yes Ms that you can
Want a coffee for me?
Course, comes immediately.
- Do you want a massage?
Nikita, he is not your slave, treatment
him the respect he deserved.
I respect him, Dad.
It is just that Voorhees ...
did everything I asked.
- I understand.
Voorhees was a bodyguard who
we are lost in an ambush.
I get it. We were
always very close with him.
Mason.
Hello darling.
Our Dad has a new
beveiliger hired. Oh yeah?
Roland met Mason.
He found his answer in boxing
and correspondingly what he deserved
He paid off.
You know what this means?
What? I can step back.
Really? Yes. Come
I want to show you something.
It was nice to see you.
It is a lot of work.
Well, if I do go.
Is there much change.
Of course.
You have complex, Tommy
- And Victor is very loyal.
They do everything you ask,
You're the boss.
Can we start?
Hey, listen to. You should really
not drive this car.
The inventory has arrived.
Is it readable?
Looks good.
Good.
Keep it up.
- Yes.
Hey, Nikita, I have something for you.
Yes you see it here?
I Sat chains.
But not this one.
You know why?
It is a detection device.
It is rather ugly.
- Turn around?
You know what that means?
Wherever you go
I can find.
That tickles.
What is it?
You do not fall on women?
Yes, I love women.
What?
Come on, we are waiting.
Coming.
You're the boss his daughter.
Come on put them urgently.
You look good.
Will he last?
Yes, he is coming.
Who is there?
Do you know him?
Jason Cross.
He is a very powerful man.
Very dangerous.
Should I be scared?
You might not?
Makes it fun. I shall return.
- Be careful with him.
Ok. Let me try!
By that bastard over there and
you get in big trouble.
Mason?
I need you to talk.
Right now? Yes, right now.
I've never
just ask ...
not to do what you want.
I want you to consider
for me.
Think of your boxing career.
That is fun for us all.
If you understand where I
talking about?
Want to rumble with the chip?
Take it easy.
I do not want to pe
any problems.
I joined the Boy Scouts expelled
for eating cookies.
That sounds so stupid.
What you doing?
Come on.
You look like
'Jip and Janneke.
You dare to say much.
I am not.
Would you stay?
Where to go not the car
and give us the space.
Or drive to the chemist
or something?
I would not do
if I were you!
Hey, Nikita.
Where are you going, man?
What you, man?
They were friends of mine.
Stay away.
That is no excuse
for their behavior.
Where you going, huh?
Are you going with him now?
What would you do?
That sounds great.
Have fun together.
See the man.
- We go.
Come on.
No, Daddy, Mason is out of control.
I bale of the time I
I lost to him.
Nikita?
Papa, he is in love with Esfane.
He is no different than other
men his age.
Men who quickly veelte
get everything ...
are always easy.
I wished him Roland
had given a beating.
- What?
Was that a smile?
Yes that's right.
Where is the former agent?
It is always Detective.
Jup, where he is, Victor?
He is to meet the city medicine.
Do you want to talk about ...
the fight in the bar?
Fight.
People from L.A.
What can I say?
Ballistic Nylon.
Popular stuff.
Smart boy.
He knows a lot.
Look out for him ..
If it is a problem.
You and your boss paid the price.
I'll let you know.
Yes do that.
I thought you forgot me?
I have some questions about
the kidnapping?
Mr. Wells has many enemies.
Most come from former
business agreements.
Where else has he
you for?
We are just friends.
I feel that I am a little
can help ...
with security problems
and the like.
We have been both agent.
He is not an agent anymore.
I no longer.
Your friend is associated
with rough people.
So if Cross?
Previously she acted together ...
When Conner's father
ran the business.
Can I ask you something?
What do you know about Cross?
He is organized.
And I think he's a
species is racist?
He believes that white and Mexicans
can not coexist.
That is crazy.
We were chasing him for years.
And no one was there to man
something about him.
- Listen!
You want your friend to help.
And I want Cross.
I do not know whether we met
help?
That's what I say.
Both agents bring together
their own man.
Then we have a super deal.
Agreed.
Hey, Nikita!
Roland is back.
Is everything okay?
Feel your own safe now?
I do.
I like him, Dad.
Yeah I like him.
He gives me a secure feeling.
I guess I never updated as
someone I've felt so safe?
Except for you, Dad.
But something about him cross.
He is lonely.
But he will not
show it.
I really think he is okay,
otherwise I trusted him.
I know.
I think I'm going step.
Good.
I'm glad you're yourself again.
After all this misery.
I am proud of you.
Thank you
I'm looking behind me as you.
That is good.
Hello.
I'm hungry.
There is no food.
Do you want half of this?
Okay then.
And Tory?
Well you know what it is?
People who are bodyguards know ...
that they are at risk and
sometimes they pay ...
the ultimate price.
And I suggest that he did.
The only good reason for
innocence, seems to die?
You gave him ...
the maximum credit.
You know Manuello and Jorga
half brothers?
No.
He told me once, ...
but that he kept hidden ...
because he lives here, and ...
He is afraid to be recognized.
They have never told anyone ...
about private matters because ...
they did not trust.
I find that pretty cool.
I mean people like it ...
the way they are.
Every time I close my eyes ...
I see those men in ...
the garage shoot him ..
It is a terrible thing
for one ...
young girl like you because
experience.
It has great impact.
- Yes.
The paparazzi caused
that Mason ...
The car did stop.
Look, there is one thing.
I am now.
Things will change.
It is just a nightmare.
It is not over yet, either?
It is not over.
But I care about is the rapid,
I promise.
Look, I ...
I'm sorry: that I own
behave so stupid sometimes.
I want you to know that I ...
really appreciate what you
is doing for me.
You are welcome.
Very Cool what you did with
Mason his friends.
There are so few
can fight.
Just amazing.
I have just one religion.
You know what your doing.
I was lucky.
Do you always eat that?
No.
That I wanted to say.
Are you sure you do not want to drink?
Among the work not drink young.
Why not?
You're bodyguard?
And I'm only driver.
We do not drink while working.
- Understand?
I drink well water.
Yes, that's good.
Do they often?
Every Friday.
Are you serious?
Loose Saturdays.
Sometimes on Tuesday.
That is not good buddy.
Are you okay?
Is she okay?
Mason remained in the club
with his friends ...
and now he takes his
mobile no.
You know what?
He will call you soon.
There is something you have given me ...
when I was a little girl.
You're still small.
What was it?
It was an umbrella,
I think that yes.
He was very very nice.
He was hand made and ...
completely painted.
I can not believe you
still remembered.
You said in the North
owning land
You always told
fat stories.
That was really cool.
You said that you a while
have lived in Asia.
After your service.
Am I right? Yes, ma'am.
The good old days.
That was ... Chang Sahaia.
I still have that umbrella
in my room.
He is as pretty as ever.
I have great difficulty
the issue.
Maybe you me
then one day bring?
With all the love.
I mean like 'm bodyguard.
Is my best.
I find that funny.
Can I bring you home now?
- Yes.
Come on.
Is look what you plan.
How are you?
You're late fighter.
What is it?
Why should I come?
- Hey!
We need to talk.
Where is Mr. Cross?
I am.
Okay, I understand.
I tell you or.
Tell Mr. Cross:
I thank him for his offer.
But no thanks.
- What?
Hear that?
He thinks he is cool.
Keep your hands off me.
Have you ever seen this?
Note.
- No.
Are you psychopaths?
Keep your hands ...
- Quiet.
Okay, man. Listen.
You want the girl, right?
Nikita.
I know what is on his land.
It just interests me
as much as you.
If you do this between us and the pause,
we do business.
You want the girl.
Then you get them.
We wait for your call.
Have a nice day, huh.
You are on my list man.
Hey, I have time for.
We all Controlling
who comes here, so your well.
Standard procedure.
Come, now get out here.
Roland will be angry
we have gone away.
What do you care
what he thinks?
Are your best friends now?
Why not?
He is a good score.
Jesus Christ
Where are we going?
Calm down.
This is faster, baby.
Mason?
Get out of the car, now?
I said, come from that car?
Mason do something?
Do what they say.
Roland?
Help me?
Sit firmly.
These guards chasing me
get it behind me away?
I head towards the North,
at Florett
Go back. No.
Roland?
Help me.
Get on that bike.
Keep your hands where I can see them.
Come on now.
Get on your knees.
Those guys wanted to murder me.
And they have a friend kidnapped.
Get on your knees. Yes, sir.
Give me coverage?
He is now in custody.
Report it here.
Roland, are you okay?
There are many people here ...
I think that you ...
am interviewing ...
tied to a stable chair.
I do this out of professional
Recital
and that's all I
can do.
I appreciate that.
I suggest that you contact
record with your lawyer.
This is perhaps, Texas ...
but not the Wild West
You can not just people
shoot on the street,
and then get away.
Look.
Even a citizen who witnesses
of an abduction ...
can see what is possible
what to do about it.
That's what I did.
That the court decides.
And let me tell you this:
Their death ...
and not you.
That is exactly what I say.
There is no case.
It was self defense.
John if you think:
he is wrong ...
he will avoid.
I give you my word.
Exactly.
Thanks Johnny
We have time for.
They work for Cross.
I know.
I've seen them together.
Tory Harris.
He is a lieutenant of Cross?
- Yes, and?
Something intervened.
I'll be back.
Please, stay here?
Now what agent was.
He has three people slain.
Excuse me.
You're free to go.
Sodeju.
I talked to him
as you requested.
He was happy to see him today
in the church could meet.
What do you exactly
to find my daughter?
We could not find her, to
We know where she is taken.
You said that no ransom
was required.
Three of the kidnappers dead ...
were employees of
Jason Cross.
Forgive me that I am not blind.
We know of your past business
with Mr. Cross.
For your daughter in hell.
I urgently request you not
for us to hide.
Thank you.
You know what you should know
Nikita finds it.
There is another thing.
Roland Sallinger was released this afternoon
to help and I am sure ...
of a phone call from you.
Do you really think it wise?
The Chief was disappointed ...
but he knows that my word,
my deposit is
You should leave him alone he
has nothing to do.
That is not what Mason Silver
says.
He is not trustworthy.
If you have no idea who
has done or why ...
are you so sure that
he is innocent?
Because I trust him.
Now please go away.
It is late and other things ...
also need attention.
If the kidnappers contact
with you ...
I want to know immediately.
Hello?
Are you now so far
to talk?
Where is my daughter?
Safe.
Thank you.
But its still up to you?
Look, it takes more time they can
not getting found.
24 hours Conner.
And not a minute longer.
It does not take long before
it also gets the news.
Intelligence equals power.
Conner.
I do want from the uranium.
And if you dear Nikita
To look back,
give you my land ...
and 5 million in diamonds.
How can I be sure that
she still alive?
Cross you hear me?
Let's go.
Have you been able to contact them?
Yes sir, Manu is all there.
She says.
I do not know where he is?
Just keep sitting patiently.
I'll be back, okay?
Victor says he wants the items
and 5 million within 24 hours.
Have you the address of Mason?
Yes, I have an address.
I thought you do
could use?
Your religion is a
low ebb.
I did not know where else
I had to give you.
I'm nervous, okay?
Good evening.
How are you?
Well. It's better now.
And you?
Very good.
How many brothers do you?
But two.
That hurts.
They are in order and are ready
if you need them.
Are you sure?
I'm sure.
Are you sure? I know
sure. I owe you.
Thanks for yesterday.
No, thank you.
Yes I keep it.
Now do not you move?
This is good shit.
Keep it up.
Can you see it?
Man go by with cards,
I had no choice.
They said I had to testify.
- I said I would not do.
I put my pride aside.
- I screwed up.
Let me ask you a question.
Were you proud of your cross and then ...
you have arranged her abduction?
Look man, they said:
she would murder me.
I know you do not believe me.
But I love Nikita, and I
would never inflict anything.
She said she
would do nothing.
It was him or me, you understand?
If you love her,
protect your hair, you understand that?
Well where is she?
I do not know?
See these two dead here?
You are also like this
about 5 min
We had agreed
in the restaurant ...
on the other side of town.
Let me ask you something.
Go down here.
What is wrong here?
She sits on his lap.
You know what's wrong?
Nikita, running all kinds
danger at this moment ...
and you are home to the festivities.
Now I leave you the same risk
run as it does.
Understood? We go.
Yes, hello?
Your time is running out now.
I'm working on it.
- Good.
Are we on schedule?
- Yes.
I want Nikita talk?
She is not now available.
Do not worry you'll see her soon.
Where? Tomorrow 20:00.
I want some real estate deal.
Ma'am?
Will you hold him now?
No, I do not.
Cross is not stupid.
I make that mistake.
There is no police presence.
What will you do?
Just chase.
Thank you very much. Good evening.
Was it so hard to do
what we asked?
We have a problem.
You go that way Manuello.
Roland I'm touched.
Get out.
I think we need to talk?
Roland, how do you get in?
Well I have the restraint
regulated.
I know that.
I invented that
Mason has screwed you.
But I think you already know?
I had my suspicion.
My daughter trusted him
information to,
which he used against us.
What information would that be?
- Where is he looking for?
5 million in diamonds.
Manuello thought I told you that?
You know?
I think there is much more
going on?
5 million is not much when you
compares with a similar robbery.
Tell me what's going on?
I understand what you meant?
I feel that we do not
on one line.
We are friends.
Sorry.
Cross and I grew up together.
He chose to become criminals
I and a policeman.
You know my family
much as owner.
One is located in Oldfield.
He is not interested in the ground.
Are interested in where he is,
this.
We were looking to
for oil ...
but we found something else
precious.
Uranium.
To cut a long story
short.
I found the largest uranium field ...
history in North America.
And that's you doing
dearly.
Bit.
We have much work
to do.
That sounds logical.
I knew that something was.
If I sign tomorrow is very
my life's work in one blow away.
I do not shit about him.
I just want Nikita back.
But I have no choice.
You have a choice.
And you sign any papers.
Where is the transmission.
Above the hills.
He is on the building.
I'm known there.
I had plants.
You get your daughter back.
You have nothing sure
about.
I give you my word.
He talks with me.
Think you have me?
Yes, I think so.
You know how many men there are?
Enough to make it interesting.
Thank you, Tory.
A few hours sweetheart
it's all over.
I miss my dad. Yes, you do.
- I promise.
Mason?
I've taken a big risk
for Mr. Cross,
I want to know when I
get paid?
You get your money tonight,
as promised.
Well Mason, please ...
get out of here.
Mason, where he talking about?
Mason, answer?
I want my bodyguard also died
have, Cross!
We are looking at him.
Do you worry about.
He was dead before morning.
Well, let's go?
You dirty bastard.
I hope you die.
With emotions get you nowhere.
Neeeeeeee.
Let's do it,
come.
Yes, inside.
I AM BLJ RANCH OF THE CROSS
OM: 08:00, ROLAND.
Fucking.
Okay, guys, we did it,
let's go.
You see your father again almost.
Listen is here?
If we are like you
your eyes open.
Shop around.
He will certainly not come alone.
He is not alone.
You keep your eyes open.
Come let's go, hurry.
What is the plan? Stay views
until I let you know.
You know those guns ...
Iijken that of the silver war ...
do you think they work?
They will do well,
I promise.
Okay, then.
Papa?
Frost?
No need to shout.
What are you an asshole.
You should respect me more
can show old man.
Young, you can kiss my ass.
Where is Nikita?
First, other things.
Let me see the documents.
The transfer is now.
Pay attention to the bodyguard.
It looks like you were a time
your appointment are met.
What about the money,
Cross?
Satisfied?
Papa?
It's okay, joke.
Everything will be okay.
You got what you wanted, well
let her go.
You get your daughter is.
This is Lucian.
Say it again.
Lucian?
What is going on?
A problem?
There's right.
Who is this?
Now you tell everyone that
they lay down their arms.
If I kill you all.
That sucks bodyguard is here.
What a waste.
What a sad, pathetic, wasteful.
Mr. Cross we miss pages
the contract is so useless.
You're really dumb.
Kill her, Tory?
No.
Wait.
Come over here?
Come on.
I kill you.
Roland?
There they are. Come on.
Ok. If your tractor
persuades ...
you never see your daughter.
This is the police!
Put your gun away?
We know how you feel, but you
should let us handle.
I can not.
No, you wrong.
Come here. Hide.
- Take him out.
Keep your mouth shut.
Let me go?
Stay there.
Okay, I give up.
Yes ... or ...
after you've beaten to death.
Get some.
My house your house, asshole.
Keep your hands off me.
It's okay. Okay?
You saved me.
Yes.
Conner?
We have enough evidence
to condemn him.
Well, put the gun away?
Come on we are Conner
together police?
Well, put the gun away.
Listen to me.
Put it away?
You're a pig.
Listen!
Tell him nothing.
Take him away.
Quickly it.
Everything is okay here.
Nikita, you okay?
I was so scared.
I'm so sorry.
I am in your debt.
THE END
Subtitles by: