Dreams are
like stars.
You can't touch them,
but if you follow them,
they will lead you to your destiny.
I used to dream of being the first
dogmonaut to walk on the Moon.
And now, I dream of going home
to my boy, Sasha.
It's incredible.
[groans quietly]
You two astronauts
need to get some sleep.
- You've got a big day tomorrow, Sam.
- It's gonna be the coolest.
I've never seen
a real spaceship before.
[groans]
I wish you could come too.
But I've already asked school
like 12 times.
No pets.
Look, a shooting star, Buddha.
[barks]
Make a wish.
I wish to one day touch the Moon.
Sam, honey, come to bed.
Goodnight, Buddha.
[Buddha groans]
Launch. [mimics rocket]
I wish that all your dreams come true.
Sorry you can't come, Buddha.
Namaste.
Not to worry.
I have a plan of my own.
[whimpers]
[kisses, blows]
- [girl] Catch!
- [groans]
Bye, Rosebud!
Rosebud, where are you?
Come on, sis. I've got a plan
for a rainy day field trip.
Gross! No way I'm going out
in that rain. It'll wreck my furdo.
Come on, let's go!
[Rosebud sighs]
OK, Budderball,
see you after school, big fella.
[groans]
Oh, sweet mama.
[barking]
[Buddha] Psst, Budderball.
We're on a journey
of ginormous proportions.
I'm about to eat some
ginormous proportions myself.
I'll see you guys later.
Budderball, there's no time
for breakfast.
Breakfast is the most important
meal of the day!
[Buddha] Come on!
Oh, bother.
[groans]
[hip-hop music plays]
[music scratches]
[barks]
[boy] A little moonwalk.
[barking]
[groans]
Hit it, B.
See ya. I've gotta bounce.
I've got a field trip today.
[humming]
[music continues]
[grunting]
- B-Dawg!
- [gasps]
Sorry, I didn't mean to scare you.
Pshaw. You didn't scare me.
I was just busting a new move.
What's the hip-hop happening,
home dogs?
We're not really sure, but
Buddha sure is excited about it.
All I can say is it's gonna be a blast.
Who put the Red Bull
in Buddha's doggy bowl?
Let's go!
[whimpers]
Not again!
You've gotta have a B-A-T-H
before Mum and Dad see you.
B-A-T-H... [gasps]
You just spelled the B word!
Mudbud, come back!
Dude, step away from the couch.
[whimpers]
[gasps]
[barks]
[both gasp]
- Oh!
- [gasps]
[whimpers]
[barks]
Looks like he got a time out.
When it rains Mudbud gets grounded.
He's a repeat offender.
Remember the time I sampled
the Thanksgiving turkey?
I got a serious time out for that too.
Sample schmample. You ate
the whole Butterball turkey, dawg.
Kind of embarrassing
to be named after a turkey.
Guys, what about Mudbud?
[groans]
Am I ever glad to see you dudes.
Shh. I've gotta jimmy the lock.
Come on, you guys, we've gotta hurry.
We might miss it.
[all groan]
- Watch it, dude!
- Move over, guys!
Hurry! There's not a minute to spare!
Oh, yeah!
[Buddha] Come on,
Mudbud, we've gotta go!
[woman] Come along, people!
The launch won't wait on us
if we're tardy now, will it?
The window of opportunity
is upon us. Let's seize it.
[groans]
We are the one lucky Fernfield class
who is going to see a real, live
- spaceship launch.
- [all] Yeah!
So that's where
you're taking us, Buddha?
Surprise!
Vision Enterprises is going to make
space travel available to anyone.
I'm in bagged lunch heaven.
Oh, Mama!
Budderball, quiet!
- [zipper opening]
- [gobbling]
[continues gobbling]
[sneezes]
Oh, my goodness!
My allergy to dander
is really acting up. I...
[sneezes]
Come on.
[squeaks]
Ready, Gravity?
Let's go do this, old buddy.
[clicks teeth]
On behalf of everyone
at Vision Enterprises,
we would like to thank you
for your continued support
on the Vision One project.
And gentlemen, we give you
the Vision One spacecraft.
She's...
she's beautiful, isn't she?
[squeaks]
Uh... The... The Vision One
The... The design is an amalgamation
of an air travel vehicle
and space design rocket.
The vehicle will
comfortably carry two pilots
and four passengers into space.
The Vision One will land on the Moon,
permitting our customers the opportunity
to walk on the surface.
Hi, Finkel.
- Dr. Finkel, nice of you to join us.
- Of course.
Dr. Finkel. Dr. Finkel.
It is my pleasure, Mr. Wolfson,
until you fail and I take over,
of course.
[growls]
Gravity, behave.
I don't know what's more unsettling,
that you accessorize
with that brainless rodent,
or that you converse with it too.
[man laughs]
I like ferrets.
I've never been terribly fond
of rats or weasels.
Nothing personal.
Well, out with the old,
in with the new, as they say.
Let's get on with it. Karl, why is
a cappuccino not touching my lips?
- Uh...
- Don't speak.
Uh, let me introduce you
to some members of our team.
[woman's voice]
Fueling in progress.
Uh, Slats Bentley
is our Flight Dynamics Officer.
He will give you some details
on today's mission.
[voice]
Executing override sequence.
...approximately four days
to get to the Moon and back.
Once we land on the surface
we'll stay for 30 minutes,
then re-launch back into space
and head back home.
Good. Uh, over here.
Uh, this is Astro Spaulding.
Uh, she is our pilot for the mission.
The pilot will be flying the spacecraft
using a vectra system,
vision-enabled control
technology response array.
Um, the, uh, systems will be
controlled with the blink of an eye,
It just scans your retina.
It's all hands-free.
I thought there were no life forms
on this mission, not even a pilot.
Astro will remotely pilot
Vision One from Mission Control.
Ultimately, when we begin
commercial travel, uh... uh...
...the remote system
will serve as a backup
in the event of a malfunction
or a pilot illness or...
Sir, there's been a break
in the weather.
Ah, well, excuse us, gentlemen.
Uh, this is our big moment.
Dr. Finkel, could you check and see
if the tour group has arrived,
and then greet them and help
the kids if they have any questions.
Certainly, Mr. Wolfson.
Sir!
[kids shout]
[woman sneezes]
OK, people, off the bus.
Don't forget your lunch...
- [kids scream]
- [screams]
OK, stop right here, kids.
Welcome to Vision Enterprises.
Everyone in. Don't touch anything.
We don't want to miss
the launch. This way!
[woman screams]
My! Oh, dog germs!
Again, please refrain from touching
anything with your hands,
you slimy,
little germ-infested creatures.
OK.
Our goal here, at Vision
Enterprises, for some reason,
is to make space travel
accessible for everyone,
including the family pet.
[Buddha]
Let's hide over there, dudes.
[Rosebud]
Quiet. They'll hear us.
[electronic humming]
[voice] Scanning.
- Wow.
- [voice] Human boy.
This is awesome.
As you can see, we have some
specifically designed space suits.
...and then do whatever you'd like...
- Excuse me.
- Huh?
Please step away from the circle.
That device scans a life form
and determines the right size suit.
It is highly sophisticated.
So please step away.
Can I get a picture with the suit?
No, you cannot have a picture
with the suit.
Please, just take it off immediately.
Uh, all right, you know what?
It's fine, it's fine.
You can keep the suit on.
You probably already contaminated it.
- Just come back to the group.
- Yeah.
Children, this portion of the tour
is over. Please follow me.
Thank you.
Excuse me. Thank you.
[B-Dawg]
Check out the fly gear.
[Rosebud] Oh, my gosh!
These outfits are so to die for.
[Buddha]
Rosebud, where are you going?
[voice] Device on.
Scanning.
- Wow.
- Canine puppy.
Whoa, dudes.
Will one of you boys zip me up?
[groans]
I've gotta try this.
[voice] Scanning.
So, how do I look?
Uh, like our sister in a space suit.
I know I look tight.
[groans]
Mine's a little too tight.
Someone give me a paw.
Don't pull his paw!
[farts]
[sighs]
Check it. It's the Goodyear blimp.
[groans]
Let's go see the spacecraft up close.
Golly gosh, maybe we could stop
at the lunch pad for a snack,
if it's on the way.
Budderball, that says "launch pad".
Oxidize and loading is complete.
And voila,
the spacecraft.
T-minus three minutes to launch.
Wow. I wish Buddha
was here to see this.
Let's just take a quick look inside,
then we'll come back
and watch the launch.
Uh...
Do you think it's safe?
You never know how deep
a puddle is until you jump in.
Huh?
Uh... I'll be right back.
Seriously, dawg, what does a puddle
have to do with the spaceship?
Whoo-hoo! Oh, yeah!
Come on, let's go.
[voice]
T- minus two minutes to launch.
[Buddha] Whoa. It's amazing.
I would've blinged it out
a little more.
I call shotgun.
Wish us luck.
[squeaks]
Hmm, Lunch-O-Matic.
OK, guys, we've seen
the ship. We better go.
Check out these retro shades.
Dude, you shouldn't
be touching those.
I could fly this thing, no problem.
Piece of cake.
Yeah, there's cake.
Ooh, donut!
But I think I'll start with
the chili cheese dog, then steak
and finish with a bean burrito.
[Buddies] No beans!
[bleeps]
Hey, this does not look like
a chili cheese dog.
All systems diagnostics check.
I want a go or no go for launch.
Uh, guys, someone
just closed the door.
[voice] Airlock door closed.
- [voice] Airlock door secured.
- [man] Copy that.
[voice]
Launch platform activated.
Are we moving?
[Mudbud]
Dudes, this is not good.
B-Dawg, what did you press?
I didn't press anything.
- Boosters.
- Go flight.
Budderball, my instincts tell me
you should take a seat, fast!
- But I was just getting to dessert.
- Hurry.
- Flight out.
- It's a go.
[groans]
Guidance, uh, navigation.
- Go.
- Propulsion and trajectory.
Everything's a go, sir.
That bird is ready to fly.
- [man] Vision One in launch position.
- We are a "go" for launch.
- We're "go" for auto sequence.
- Start, sir.
T-minus 30 seconds and counting.
[engine roars]
Guys, I hear a low rumbling sound.
Hey, don't look at me.
Guys, I think we might be
going on a road trip.
[voice] Restraints activated.
T-minus ten, nine,
eight, seven,
six, five...
[voice]... four, three
...two, one and...
- [beep]
...ignition.
We're moving!
Gravity, we have lift-off.
[all] Yeah!
Yeah!
It feels like my stomach
is in my throat!
This is like a ride on Space Mountain!
Dad always said I should be
more down to Earth.
Why didn't I listen?
[voice]
Leaving Earth's atmosphere.
That was a radical ride.
I don't recommend lift-off
on a full stomach.
That was heavenly.
[bleeping]
[voice] Zero gravity.
Huh?
[voice]
Restraints released.
I'm floating like a balloon.
Wha... What's happening?
Zero gravity.
[chuckling] This is out
of this world, literally.
This is incredible.
You can say that again.
Even I'm lighter than a feather.
This is off the chain, dawgs.
I could slam dunk in space.
[voice]
Graviton reverser activate.
That doesn't sound good.
[all] Whoa!
[voice] Gravity normal.
Hey, hey, I thought we were always
supposed to land on our feet.
Who turned off that zero grav stuff?
[moans]
[voice] Warning, fuel low.
Sir, I don't like what I see.
Somehow, we are short
a quarter of our fuel supply.
[voice] Fuel low.
Well, first things first.
Identify the source of the problem.
I know what the problem is.
Tank three was never
completely filled.
The registries were blank.
It doesn't make any sense.
She'll never make it to the Moon
and back with that kind of shortage.
Hmm, it pains me to say this,
but I don't think we have any other
option here but to abort the mission.
[squeaks]
[sighs]
Astro, how much time
before we have to abort?
- [taps on keyboard]
- Approximately ten hours, sir.
Good. Stay on course. Um...
OK... We have some time to solve
this, people. I need solutions.
Buddha, I'm home.
- Buddha?
- Yo, B-Dawg.
I'm back in the crib.
Let's bust some moves.
Rosebud, come on,
let's go get a mani pedi
and a blow dry.
Rosebud?
Budderball, I have your favorite dinner.
Budderball?
I knew we shouldn't have
made him take a bath.
I think we're getting further
and further away from home.
And further and further
away from dinner.
I take full responsibility.
Sir, I think we may have finally
figured out a solution.
Great. I... I... knew you would.
Nice work. Let's hear it.
OK, we think that we can refuel at
the old Russian research space station.
But that space station disintegrated
into the Earth's atmosphere
like years ago.
Well, yeah, but you said to check
everything, so I checked everything,
including the conspiracy websites,
which said the station, still in space.
The reason that no one has been
able to find the space station
is because it's not
in it's original position.
Somehow, it has gotten out
of geostationary orbit.
And one of the Russian
cosmonauts, he survived,
and he's still living onboard, alone.
- [voice] Incoming communication.
- Hold on.
Yuri, this is Slats
from Vision Enterprises
Do you read me?
American blue jeans!
How are you?!
Um, look, I'm just confirming
that you do have fuel
and are able to assist our spacecraft.
Of course I help you, my comrades.
Yuri, this is Pi.
Uh, I am the spacecraft's designer
and mission flight director.
In exchange for the 3,000 pounds
of fuel, uh, I would like to offer...
No, comrade, in return
for the fuel forget everything.
My location, forget it.
Consider this information gone,
kaput, okee-dokee, pumpkin pie?
You have our word.
[classical music plays]
So, we are going
to have visitors. Good.
[groans]
Oh, don't worry, old pal.
They promised not to tell
anyone about us.
So we are free to live
peacefully in space
forever and ever and ever!
[groans]
Dudes, what is this place?
Whatever it is, it's getting closer.
I hope it's not an alien's house.
Not that I'd be scared,
or anything.
I hope it's a Denny's.
I could sure go for a Moons
Over My Hammy right about now.
OK, Yuri, are you ready
to receive the spacecraft. Over.
I've never been so ready
in all of my life.
Come and get it, rhinestone cowboy.
Oh, right, uh...
Let's switch from autopilot
to remote pilot.
Switching now, sir.
Astro, she's all yours.
[voice]
Docking maneuver initiated.
Remote pilot engaged, sir.
[beeping]
[bleeping]
[air hissing]
[voice] Docking in progress.
Docking successful.
OK, Yuri, we're locked in.
Uh, we can begin fueling.
[speaks Russian]
OK.
[humming]
[continues humming]
- What?
- Huh?
[groans]
OK.
We should explore
and broaden our horizons.
Broaden our horizons?
We're lost in space, dawg.
I think our horizons are broad enough.
[beeps]
I ain't going nowhere.
Good call, bro,
if there's an alien intruder,
we'll need someone
to defend the spaceship.
Did... Did you say aliens?
Uh, guys, uh, come on, uh...
[rumbling]
OK.
Come on, follow me.
Dudes, where are we going?
Yo, dawgs, hold up!
OK, the gas is pumping
like an American discotheque.
All right, well, when we get
our 3,000 pounds of fuel...
...we are going to the Moon.
[squeaks]
[loud rumbling]
Dawgs?
Come on, aliens, I...
I ain't scared of nothing
because I float like a butterfly
and... and sting like a bee, dawg.
What is this place?
Huh?
[screams]
It's an alien!
- [B-Dawg screams]
- It's B-Dawg! He's in trouble!
Y... You don't wanna eat me!
I'm all scrawny and boney.
Eat him! He has plenty
of meat on them bones!
[B-Dawg screams]
- [sighs]
- Uh...
I am no alien.
Though I suppose if I stay in space
any longer I may qualify.
The name is Spudnick.
We're the Buddies. The pup
in the chicken suit is B-Dawg,
the dirty dude is Mudbud,
the Zen pup is Buddha
and Rosebud is our little sis.
Oh, and, uh, me, I'm Budderball.
And I'm starving.
Nice to meet you.
I'm a Russian dogmonaut.
We kind of got on the ship by accident.
And now, we have no idea where we are.
You're aboard the RRSS,
the old Russian Research Space Station.
You want me to show you around?
Follow me.
In this module, we have our garden,
where we grow all our food in space.
The added benefit is the plants
filter out CO2 gas and produce oxygen.
And we also use them
to create fuel for the station.
Now this joint is
off the chain insane, cuz.
Yes, we've been off the orbital grid
for quite some time,
if that's what you mean.
Over here, we have our solar panels,
which produce all our energy.
So you can keep the stereo
pumpin' 24l7. That's wicked.
Right over here is the kitchen.
[Budderball]
My favorite room in the house.
Huh?
Hmm. Where's the beef?
[bubbling]
- Dude, what is that?
- Space juice.
Pee-yoo! It stinks.
Who'd wanna drink that?
Well, Yuri seems to like it.
And we use it for fuel.
Who's Yuri?
He's the Russian cosmonaut
I live with up here.
How long have you been up here, dude?
Not really sure. It's all
one long night in space.
I was only supposed to be
on this station for a six month mission
but I'm sure it's been years and years.
Spudnick?
Spudnick? Where has
my little puppy puppy gone?
Spudnick...
Yaaa-hoo! [chuckles]
[hums]
[barking]
Can you believe it, Spudnick?
Our American comrades
have given us a surprise gift!
Five fluffy puppies to keep us
company here in space.
[speaks Russian]
Thank you! Thank you!
He doesn't understand, Spudnick.
We're not staying long.
Where that spaceship goes, we go.
- All right, come on, Spudnick.
- [groans]
Good.
We will finish refueling
and then... we will celebrate.
Dude, you have to help us.
[groans]
[speaks Russian]
Puppy puppies!
Dudes, we've been hoodwinked.
You're telling me!
OK, this food is all vegetables.
Now what?
Uh, we'll be ready to leave
in less than 30 minutes.
The sooner we can get refueled
and get away from this bucket
of bolts the happier I will be.
[rumbling]
[hissing]
To life in space
for eternity and forever.
And to you, Spudnick.
A spaceman's best friend.
And to the new puppy puppies.
We will live together
as a happy family, till the end.
[whimpers]
Ah. Whoo!
[uptempo classical music]
You want to get the dancing started?
That's a good idea, Spudnick.
Let's get jiggle with it.
[hums]
[music, humming continues]
Yeah, I'm not sure
he's flying with a full jetpack.
He's crazy.
- [music ends]
- Oh ho!
Another, you party animal?
- I am sorry, old pal. I am pooped.
- [traditional Russian music]
- [barks]
- All right, one more, one more.
OK, let's do it.
- Well...
- [Yuri humming]
Dudes, I saw the Jamaican
bobsled team do this.
Three, two, one, push!
[groaning]
[Budderball] Wait, guys!
I changed my mind!
[gasping]
- [thud]
- [Budderball groans]
I told you guys this was a bad idea.
- [groaning]
- The dog's down for the count.
What a shame, 'cause
these space nachos are gnarly.
Huh, space nachos?!
He's OK.
[music continues]
[music speeds up]
[barks]
These are gonna be the longest
11 minutes in my life.
- Ah!
- [barks]
Oooh.
Oo-y kapoo-y!
Yuri is knicker knackered.
- [groans]
- Spudnick, you know Yuri.
Too much dancing,
Yuri gets too much sleepy.
[lullaby music plays]
Oh, that's nice.
Hold me closer, tiny dancer.
[toy squeaks]
[sighs]
Oh, that's nice.
- Little Yuri. That's very nice.
- [squeaks]
[whimpers]
Oh, Spudnick.
My blanky.
[Yuri sighs]
Maybe Yuri take 40 blinks.
Just until the refueling is done.
[whimpers]
[snoring]
[music continues]
Hmm.
[snoring continues]
[thumping]
Huh?
Quick! It's Yuri!
Hide!
Buddies, where are you?
Spudnick.
[hissing]
Sir, I'm showing that the tanks are
full but the pressure is building.
- What happened to the crazy cosmonaut?
- He's asleep.
Yuri, this is, uh,
Vision Enterprises,
do you hear me?
[continues snoring]
This is my last chance
to go home to my boy, Sasha.
The station is falling apart anyhow.
And Yuri's plan
is to go down with the ship.
Can you hear me? Wake up.
Da. Da. Yuri is just
having a little kitty nap.
- Can I hitch a ride home with you guys?
- For shizzle, dawg.
I hope I never need it,
but better safe than sorry.
Refueling is complete.
Can we disconnect the ship?
What?
The puppies are loose!
- You American dognappers!
- What?
[loud beeping]
Oh no! The station is going
into lockdown! Yuri's on to us.
Dudes, I say we make like
a bread truck and haul buns!
[Yuri grunts]
[Yuri] No! No, come back! Puppy! No!
You guys, where's Budderball?
Huh?
We can't leave without him.
You know our motto, dudes:
No pup left behind.
[Rosebud] Budderball, come on!
Not without my broccoli.
[speaks Russian]
[Yuri gasps]
No! Please! Don't take away
my puppy puppy pups!
Wait a second?
Is he talking about puppies?
He's got more screws loose
than the space station.
[shouts in Russian]
Come back! You cannot leave!
You cannot take
my gift away from me!
I think he might be trying
to shanghai the Vision One.
Enact emergency evacuation measures.
[grunts]
Let's detach from the station now.
Copy that.
That's not good.
Whoa!
[gasping]
[screams]
Dude, it's coming apart!
Wow! That's the Cosmopod
escape vessel. He made it!
[Yuri howls]
[voice] Signal lost.
[voice] Termination detected.
RRSS destruction confirmed.
You guys find anything?
Nope, haven't seen
hide nor fur of them.
Don't worry. We'll find them.
Where there's a will, there's a way.
- Mm-hm.
- Yeah.
Are you ready to go home, Spudnick?
Buddies, we are not heading to Earth.
The coordinates show
we are going to the Moon.
The Moon?
The ship is being controlled from Earth.
Yes, it seems as though
it is taking us to the Moon.
I'm sure Buddha
and the other Buddies
are out there on some
wonderful adventure.
I feel like he's a million miles away.
I know, sweetie.
We'll find him.
Let's get some sleep now.
Come home soon.
[snoring]
Spudnick, are you awake?
Yeah.
What are you thinking about?
I was thinking about my boy, Sasha.
I hope he's still waiting for me.
We are nearing lunar orbit, sir.
[bleeping]
Let's get ready to initiate
landing procedure.
Switch from autopilot
to remote, Astro, please.
I am now in control of the ship
and am prepared to land.
Surface of the Moon, here we come.
[loud rumbling]
[all] huh?!
Wha...
Wha... What was that?
[voice] Night shade deactivated.
[screams] The Death Star!
B-Dawg, it's the Moon.
It looks a lot bigger up here than
when we used to howl at it from home.
Aw, goodness! All the blue cheese
a fella can eat!
We are heading for it, and fast.
Buckle up, guys.
[voice]
Restraint activated.
Onboard vectra activated
Whoa! Weird!
Wait, this is unbelievable.
- I've lost control of the ship.
- Talk to me.
I don't know. Somehow,
the onboard vectra system
has overridden the remote pilot.
- [Buddies scream]
- [Rosebud] B-Dawg, what are you doing?
Stop the spinning!
A thousand feet and gaining speed, sir.
[Buddies scream]
If we don't get control soon and adjust
our course, the Vision One's a goner.
Who turned on the spin cycle?!
- Slats, time?
- 57 seconds till impact.
[screaming]
We're going in circles!
Someone do something!
This is a highly advanced
piloting system.
- There we go.
- Yeah, I could've done that.
Just need a little practice, that's all.
That was furry.
Good job, Spudnick.
Thanks, Rosebud, but I'm
turning it over to the experts.
[voice] Remote pilot engaged.
Whoa! Whoa!
Yes, I have control back.
- How?
- I have no idea, sir.
I'm just going with it.
Something very strange
is happening up there.
OK, initiate lunar landing procedure.
[voice] Initiating.
OK, we're at 400 feet.
[squeaks]
200.
[voice] Lunar landing...
[Slats] Astro, easy. 100 and counting.
50 feet.
And...
Touchdown.
[all cheer]
- We're on the Moon.
- Yes!
Ahh!
[squeaks]
- Yes!
- [groans]
Good job.
Wow, the Moon.
Buddies, are you ready to go
for the walk of your lives?
Good idea, 'cause I've gotta
take a whiz something fierce.
Well, let's suit up.
Wait a second. The system
shows the airlock door is opening.
Spudnick, you go first.
[echoing thud]
One small step for dog,
one giant leap for dogkind.
Sir, you've gotta take a look at this.
What?
[squeaks]
It's a... Well, I think it's a... um...
I have no idea, sir.
There's some sort of four-legged
creatures surrounding the ship.
Sir, I think we've discovered
alien life forms.
OK, uh, Chuck,
zoom in on that, would ya?
[Chuck] Roger.
I don't think it's cheese,
but I don't even care.
This is the first time in my life
I haven't been hungry.
Thank you, buddies,
for making dreams come true.
If they are extraterrestrial beings,
why are they wearing
Vision Enterprises spacesuits?
Open up the communication line
on their helmets.
[Buddies barking]
[squeaks]
It appears we have canine stowaways?
Ah, so maybe Yuri
wasn't so crazy after all.
Those look like puppy puppies.
And they're walking on the Moon.
[chuckling]
We're walking on the Moon!
Whoa! Amazing!
Check it. I'm doing the moonwalk.
Totally awesome.
[chuckling] Whoa! This is so cool.
How does something like this happen?
And more importantly, how on earth
are we going to bring them home?
Yeah, leaving five puppies on the Moon,
it's not real good for PR.
No, it is certainly not.
We could run an ad campaign.
- Oh.
- Let me see.
Fly with us,
we launched six poor
innocent puppies into space
and then bid them farewell
for eternity.
The bottom line is
we can't leave them there.
How do you plan on coaxing
a bunch of moronic animals
into a spacecraft
from 228,536 miles away?
[squeaking]
Where's Buddha?
Om.
A view that will change
your perspective forever.
This is totally unreal.
This one's for my boy Sasha.
Yo, dogs, I hate to crash the party but,
how we gonna get home this time?
[indistinct chatter]
[squeaking]
Galactic Canines, do you read me?
- Does anyone else hear that?
- Dogs, I think I hear an alien.
Dude, there's no aliens.
It must be Mission Control.
They know we're here.
I'm Gravity,
Mission Commander's assistant.
Who are you doglings
and how in the universe
did you get on board
the Vision One?
I'm dogmonaut Spudnick,
Russian Space Agency.
And these are the buddies.
I got on at the Russian Space Station.
These pups, uh, they saved my life.
We got on at Vision Headquarters.
A field trip gone awry.
Dogs, listen, I can help you
get back to Earth.
Dude, are we over-stoked
to hear a voice from home.
The Vision One will be departing
for Earth in 15 minutes and 32 seconds.
So head back to the spaceship
before your oxygen is depleted
and get ready for lunar lift off.
- [squeaks]
- Until we get the puppies home safely,
we keep this quiet. OK?
I mean, I need full confidentiality
on this. If this story were to leak,
it would spread like wildfire and that
would cause irreparable damage
to Vision Enterprises.
Uh, guys, guys! The, uh, d-dogs
are going back on board.
[exclaims]
Let's launch before they decide
to go exploring again.
All right people, we know the drill.
Boosters are a go,
V-1 is a go for lunar launch.
[door shuts]
[voice] Robot arm activated.
Time to bring home a souvenir.
Preparing to launch.
[Astro] Ready to launch, sir.
We will be out of
communication with you
for approximately 12 minutes
while you circle
the backside of the Moon.
All right, we're back in business.
Now, let's get these puppies
safely home.
We're live at Vision Enterprises
where quite a tale is unfolding.
It seems that five golden
retriever puppies
have been accidentally
launched into space.
Mom!
Along with a bull terrier,
they are going
- where no dog has gone before.
- What?
[speaking in foreign languages]
[TV reporter speaking in Spanish]
[whimpering]
[speaking in Spanish]
[TV reporter] It is believed
the pups rendezvoused
with the Russian dogmonaut
at the long-thought destroyed
Russian Research Space Station.
- [kids] Wow!
- They made history
by being the first animals
to walk on the Moon.
[speaking in a foreign language]
[gasps] Spudnick!
[indistinct chattering]
You know, I have no idea how these
guys could have gotten a hold of this.
Hackers, these days.
Probably got into the system
and jacked our video feed.
[inhales] It's very off-putting.
[zooming]
- Come on, guys.
- [man] Live for KTLA,
- I'm Doug...
- Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Where do you think you're going?
We're here to talk about our pups
that you guys shot into space.
Absolutely no one gets through.
Then, we'll go talk
to the newsman instead.
- [man] Satellite is up in 8 seconds.
- Hang on a second.
- [woman] We have a live wire.
- Dr. Finkel?
I have a bunch of kids here
that claim the alleged puppies
in space are their dogs.
I thought you'd like to know.
- [over the radio] Send them in.
- Yes, sir.
Dr. Finkel would like
to have a word with you.
Follow me.
[panting]
[man] Next is Steve with sports.
[indistinct chattering]
Excuse me, Pi.
I'd like to introduce you to
the children whose lives you've ruined
by launching their puppies
up into space.
As you can imagine,
they're quite traumatized.
Pi, wow, it's an honor
to meet you, sir.
Buddha and I are your hugest fans.
I'm sure he's thrilled to be
on your ship.
Thank you.
[stammers] This is Gravity.
- My assistant.
- [squeaks]
Kids, uh, be assured that,
um, we're doing everything
in our power to bring
your puppies home safely.
Um, hey, guys...
I'm Slats.
I'm the flight dynamics officer.
That's, uh, FIDO for short.
Oh, and over there, that's Astro.
She actually is the pilot of
the Vision One. How cool is that, huh?
I'm Sam.
My pup is Buddha.
That's Pete.
His bro is Mudbud.
Bartelby's fella is Butterball.
Billy's homepup is B-Dawg
- and Alice's BFF is Rosebud.
- Mm-hmm.
Slats, why don't you get them up
to speed on the current plan.
Um, yeah. Oh, yeah, guys, come on
over here. Check this out. Very cool.
OK, well, all the vital stats
are on the big board as we call it.
The ETA is tomorrow morning
at 1100 hours.
That's 11:00am.
- [typing on keyboard]
- [beeps]
Well, this ought to ensure
this is a one way trip.
[voice] Critical course error.
You see that right up there?
[voice] Current telemetry
unsafe. Confirm change.
- Dr. Fecal?
- Yes?
[stammers] Uh, I mean, it's Finkel.
Dr. Finkel. Yes, what is it?
What are you doing?
- I'm not doing anything.
- [voice] Telemetry changed.
You shouldn't concern yourself.
You're just a child. Excuse me. Karl.
- Yeah, me too.
- If I come back.
[Slats] No, no.
We'd bring you back for sure.
[beeps]
[gasps] What's that?
- Ah, it's just a meteor.
- Just a meteor?
- Collision alert! Collision alert!
- What?
- Collison alert!
- [squeaks]
Oh! I thought our course was set
to avoid the meteor shower.
I don't know, sir. Somehow
the telemetry has been modified.
Well, looks like we're going
to test our auto-avoidance system.
Engaging auto-avoidance system.
[voice] Auto-avoidance
system activated.
Buddies, you're right in the middle
of a meteor shower.
[squeaks]
[beeping]
Hang on!
[all] Whoa!
Whoa!
[beeping]
[Mudbud] Oh, no!
Ah!
- OK, looks like we made it, people.
- [exhales]
Buddies, looks like
you're in the clear.
That was close.
[voice] Collision alert!
Collision alert!
[squeaks]
[beeps]
[thumps]
What was that?
[voice] Data communications terminated.
Go to back up.
The back up is down as well, sir.
[man] Reporting a total failure
in signal strength.
[squeaks] Buddies, the Vision One
has been struck by a meteor.
All our system tests confirm
that the data communication
antenna is damaged.
All we have left is
audio communication
and that doesn't help us at all.
And the only way to fix it,
is for an astronaut to do it externally.
[squeaking]
We're gonna need one of you
to do a spacewalk to fix the damage.
Without the data communication antenna
we can't control the ship from Earth.
Roger that, Mission Control.
I should go. I've been in space
the longest and know this stuff well.
Dude, if something happens
to you, we're all doomed.
I'll do it! The sooner we get home,
the sooner I'll get some food.
I was just gonna raise my paw.
But, you beat me to it, dawg.
As far as we can tell,
all the functions of the Vision One
are normal and the hull is intact
but its telemetry
has been diverted
and it's way off course
and our re-entry angle
is dangerously shallow.
The Vision One could skip off
into the atmosphere
and tumble out into space.
- Oh.
- [sighs]
Well, for the sake
of those five kids...
...we cannot give up.
We can't.
The puppies along
with their Russian comrade
are in great peril.
An unprecedented disaster has
occurred aboard the Vision One.
The spacecraft has been
struck by a meteor
and we are awaiting word
if the damage is repairable.
Oh, my goodness.
[speaking in a foreign language]
[sobbing]
To control your movement,
you have four small jets.
Move your right hind leg, you go back.
Move your left hind leg,
you go forward.
Wiggle your right front paw,
you go left.
Your left front paw, you go right.
Look, you'll be tethered to the ship
so you don't float off
into outer space. Got it?
Uh, which one is my left paw again?
We're doomed.
What? It's not my fault I'm dyslexic!
Just remember, your right back leg,
you lift to take a wizzo.
Left back, you use
to scratch your tummy.
Left front paw,
you use to beg for food.
And the right front paw,
is for snackin'.
OK, scratch, forward.
Wizzo equals backwards.
Begging, go right
and snacking go left.
See, I got it.
The target is a data
communications antenna.
Place it back into position
and we should be able
to control the ship again.
Budderball, did you eat
all the bean burritos?
What can I say?
I'm a nervous eater.
And walking in space
makes me especially nervous.
Oh, sweet mama. This is beautiful.
[sputtering]
Budderball, can you read us?
Roger, Rosebud.
OK, now gently move forward.
Uh, how do I do that again?
Scratch leg, dude. Scratch leg.
Oh, right!
All this talk about scratching,
and now I've got an itch.
Budderball, don't scratch.
But, it's so itchy.
If you scratch,
you'll spin out of control.
I can't help myself.
Don't do it, dawg.
Must scratch.
Budderball, no!
Oh, mama. Ah!
Ah!
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Whoaah! Ah!
[yelling]
Whoa!
Ah! Ow!
[gasping]
In life, sometimes you're the bug,
sometimes you're the windshield.
Did somebody catch
the license plate on that UFO?
Quit messing around, dude.
[Rosebud] Go to the antenna.
[beeps]
[stalls]
Guys, we have a problem.
It's not working.
You've got to be kidding, dawg.
I swear. Cross my stomach
and hope to starve.
The scratching episode
used up all your fuel.
Now what are we gonna do?
I got it! Budderball just ate
a dozen bean burritos, right?
Dude, this is no time to be cryptic.
We're gonna have to pull his paw.
Dawg, he'll be asphyxiated.
Trust me, I know what I'm doing.
Huh?
- [beeps]
- [gasps]
[voice] Robot arm engaged.
[B-Dawg] Easy.
- [flatulence]
- [grunts]
- Whoa, dudes.
- Budderball, are you with us?
I don't know what you guys
are complaining about.
It's really not that bad.
OK, now the methane gas
you just produced
should give you enough fuel
to fire up your jet pack.
Budderball, that little bit
of fuel won't last.
You have to fix the antenna.
- [beeps]
- [sputters]
I see the problem.
[Spudnick]
OK, what does it look like?
It kind of does a dog leg
to the wizzo side.
He means it's crooked to the right.
See if you can move it
back into position.
Roger that.
Great news, everybody.
Data communications
has been restored to the ship.
Budderball, you should be proud.
[squeaking]
[stammers]
[voice] Data communication restored.
- Unbelievable.
- [Slats] She's back online.
Yeah!
[clapping]
Let's not, uh, celebrate too much here.
We still have a ship
to get back on course. Slats?
Telemetry correction
uplink underway, sir.
Firing thrusters, course
correction to 152.2 over 5.
Vision One course correction
confirmed, sir.
OK, Slats?
Find out how we could have
gotten so off course.
- [keyboard strokes]
- I don't know, sir.
Doesn't make any sense.
We were on course to avoid
the meteor shower.
The last print-out showed us
right on track. Look!
[beeps]
Wait a minute.
The log shows an adjustment...
...made from the main terminal,
yesterday at 19:49.
Main terminal?
It was him!
Hm? Excuse me.
[scoffs]
Please, you can't be serious.
You don't think I would
ever do such a thing?
Are you sure, Sam?
I saw him at the computer earlier.
I knew he was up to something.
Oh, is that right?
[stammers] Pi, you can't
believe him over me.
He's an ignorant child.
OK, then what's this?
[stammers] Uh, I'm not...
I don't know what is.
I've never seen that before.
- It's your USB key, sir.
- Please, Karl, don't speak.
Sorry, sir.
Ah! Hm. Security?
Can you give me playback of yesterday
19:49 hours of the main terminal?
Put it up in the Mission Control
large screen.
Oh, and security,
you might want to join us.
That won't be necessary.
[man over radio] Uh, it's up
on the big board now, sir.
Good. Fast forward this.
Freeze frame!
- Good, now zoom in on that.
- [chuckles]
[sighs]
[stammers] I...
Darn! Karl!
- Oh!
- [Wolfson] Security!
Take Dr. Finkel away.
Bye-bye, Dr. Stinkel.
It's Finkel.
- Finkel!
- [door shuts]
Faster than you can say, "Fetch,"
it brings me great delight
to let you that this mission
is back on track.
[speaking in a foreign language]
[cheering]
[zooms]
I have never been so hungry.
I think I might have to actually
eat that broccoli to stay alive.
[Rosebud] Budderball?
- [crumpling]
- [slurps]
[Budderball] This is good.
[grunting]
Aw, dude, I can't believe
you ate the whole thing.
Well, I always said I'd eat
broccoli when puppies fly.
[beeps]
What?
- Excuse me, Mr. Slats, sir?
- Yeah.
What's that approaching
to Vision One?
- [voice] Warning! Warning!
- Aw, snap, it just doesn't stop!
[voice] Unidentified object
approaching Vision One.
Whatever it is, it's on a collision
course with our spaceship.
- Take evasive action! Stat!
- Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa. OK.
It's the Cosmopod, Yuri.
He's gonna crash into us.
[grunts]
- American comrades, this is Yuri.
- Is that Yuri?
He must have had an escape pod.
My Cosmopod is not irresponsible.
- Slats, any ideas.
- Negative, sir.
The Russian pod is out of control.
It's entering the atmosphere
at a dangerous entry level
at high speed.
It's pretty much
an impossible rescue, sir.
Yuri will burn up, if you don't
change his trajectory.
- I'm taking over.
- Whoa, I've lost control.
I'm going to have to dodge
the Cosmopod to change it's course.
Let's do it, dude. I mean, comrade.
Hang on!
All right, we've made contact.
It's crucial you level off
the Cosmopod at 30 degrees.
Give me a countdown on re-entry.
I'll pull up at the last second.
In six, five, four, three, two, one...
...activate thrusters.
[zooms]
[voice] Course corrected.
How did they know to level off
the Russian escape pod
to those exact coordinates.
[squeaks]
- [man] Eyes on scopes, people.
- [squeaks]
[grunts]
Whoa!
You guys ready to go home?
Yo, dawg, I was born ready.
All right, my friends,
I'm relinquishing controls.
- [powers down]
- [voice] Remote activated.
- Hey, I got control back.
- [voice 2] Remote pilot engaged.
Well, let's bring this puppy home.
Uh, puppies, that is.
The re-entry sequence
in three, two, one.
[rumbling]
We've lost them in the blackout zone.
We won't have a visual
for T-minus four minutes.
[squeaks]
It's out of our hands.
Now, uh, we can't do anything
but hope for the best.
[squeaks]
The spacecraft has
re-entered the atmosphere
and is now hurdling
mercilessly towards Earth.
[reporter] Communication
is now in the blackout zone.
[speaking in Spanish]
All of us here
at Channel Four Fernfield,
along with the world,
collectively hold our breath,
as we watch anxiously,
awaiting a sign from the sky
that the puppies, our space heroes,
have survived the fiery re-entry
into the Earth's atmosphere.
All we can do is pray.
Please protect Spudnick
and his friends.
[beeping]
[man] Stand by for reference.
[zooming]
- [voice] Re-entry successful.
- OK, we have visual, people.
Buddies, we did it!
[cheering]
[all] Whoo!
- [squeaks]
- [all] Yeah!
Whoo!
See, space travel ain't nothing.
- [sputters]
- [B-Dawg] Whoa!
What was that?
That was a sonic boom.
We just broke the sound barrier.
I knew that.
I was just joshing you, dawg.
[man] Engaging landing sequence.
Good job, Astro.
[beeps]
[tires screech]
- Touchdown, whoo!
- [cheering]
- Yes!
- We're home!
- Congratulations, dogs.
- You did it.
- [laughing]
[cheering]
They made it! They made it!
Yes! They made it!
[guffaws]
- They've done it!
- Jolly good! Bravo! Bravo!
- [barking]
- [speaking in Spanish]
[speaking in Spanish]
[barking]
- [B-Dawg] Touchdown!
- [Rosebud] Way to go, guys.
I have a feeling, you and your
furry friends had more to do
with this mission's success
than we will ever know.
Come on, come on.
[squeaking]
Come on, kids,
let's go greet the new heroes.
- Let's go.
- Come on!
- Yeah!
- [laughing]
[sirens blare]
Here you go, Gravity,
greet your new friends.
[squeaking]
Welcome home, Buddies.
Spudnick, that was some fancy
seat-of-the-pants aviation
you demonstrated.
Whoa, you're a ferret?
Yo, dawg, you mean to tell me
we had a rodent
as our flight director?
Hey, I'm not a rodent.
I'm related to the mustela
family of mammals,
which includes minks and skunks.
Hey, I'm told I'm related to skunks too.
We couldn't have made it home
without your help, Gravity.
Thank you, comrade.
[squeaks]
[whimpers]
[cheering]
- [barking]
- Budderball.
Rosebud! Mudbud!
- B-Dawg! B-Dawg!
- Namaste Buddha!
[laughs] Hey!
Oh, I'm so happy you're home.
- [laughing]
- [squeaks]
- [laughing] Yeah.
- B-Dawg! B-Dawg!
- Oh.
- Yeah.
Oh, and one last thing...
It seems a boy named Sasha
is trying to contact you.
Really?
He's been waiting for you.
Oh, hey, hey. Oh.
Where am I? What?
Mother Russia.
[laughing]
How are you? Nice to see you.
I come from space.
How are you?
[cheering]
This is more like it.
I feel much prettier in pink.
Aw!
[harmonica sounding]
[music stops]
Uh, thank you.
Thank you for being here.
I would like to present wings,
the symbol of true heroism in space...
...to our dogmonauts.
[cheering]
Here they are. The Space Buddies.
- Yeah!
- [laughing]
Ah! Rosebud.
Congratulations.
And B-Dawg.
Budderball.
[laughing]
Ah, Mudbud. [chuckles]
I'm gonna miss Spudnick.
Spudnick is now officially
part of my entourage.
I'll never forget he taught me
to eat my vegetables.
He was a rad comrade.
He'll have a space
in our hearts forever.
[cheering]
[gasps]
[Sasha laughs]
Spudnick!
[clapping]
[whimpers]
I always dreamt I'd hold you
in my arms again.
Aw.
[crickets chirping]
Whoa.
This rock.
Is from the Moon?
[barks]
I got to touch the Moon too.
I guess dreams really do come true.
I fulfilled my dream of being the first
dogmonaut to walk on the Moon.
But in returning home,
I realized it is the journey
and the new friendships
I made that matter the most.
[# Alyson Stoner:
Dancin' in the Moonlight]
Subtitles by LeapinLar