watch your speed, Diaz.
we don't need the cops pulling you over.
-How far's the turnoff?
-Couple of miles.
Puts you right on the interstate
out of Gotham.
what was that?
It's Batman, ain't it?
Jeez Louise, it's a woman!
what are you sitting there for?
Get out!
whoa, who's having the light show?
Haven't seen her around the cave.
Could she have been an old opponent
in a new disguise? Perhaps Catwoman.
No, even Selina Kyle has
more regard for human life.
This is someone entirely new, Alfred.
The last thing Gotham needs
is a vigilante running amuck.
As they say on the streets,
''I ain't touching that one.''
The point is, her costume links her
to me. why?
what does she have planned?
How far will she go?
Do be careful. Remember, there are
many species in which the female...
...is deadlier than the male.
He's been waiting.
It still lists to the right.
See what you can do.
Penguin.
Mr. Duquesne. I hear we had
an unpropitious setback.
If you mean we got hit, yeah.
And how exactly could that
have happened?
I don't know yet. No one but us even knew
the shipment was going out last night.
well, someone did.
-A Batwoman?
-That's what my man said, Thorne.
Batman, Batgirl, Batwoman!
what is it about this city? The water?
Fortunately, it was only one truckload.
I've doubled the manpower
at our warehouse sites.
No way she can get to the rest.
Forgive me if I'm not so sanguine.
Our overseas consortium has paid us
a half-billion dollars for these arms.
If we don't deliver, they'll want their
money back. Since we've spent it...
...that would present a problem,
wouldn't it?
I want the rest of it to be out
within the week...
...which means take care
of this bat-clone now.
You're supposed to be our muscle,
Mr. Duquesne. Start flexing.
well, someone talked!
Someone dropped a dime!
-we find out who, we'll find her.
-Daddy!
Hold on.
-where you been?
-Don't worry, Daddy.
I brought your lapdogs with me.
For once, they came in handy.
Shoo.
So Raoul, my favorite hairdresser,
had a spiritual rebirth last week...
...and left for an ashram in Bukittinggi.
-How was your day?
-You should tell me when you go out.
who's on the phone?
Business. Nothing for you
to worry about.
I guess I should be going then.
we're getting dangerously close
to a conversation.
Do whatever it takes. I want you
to find her. Find her and finish her!
Today on Bat-watch, everyone wonders
who the mysterious Batwoman could be.
Batman's new partner? Batgirl grown up?
We asked Police Commissioner Gordon.
All I can say is,
she's not affiliated with Batman.
Otherwise, I have no comment.
Det. Bullock! Harvey!
I think we got enough bat-freaks
in Gotham already.
I mean, what's next? Bat-hound?
Come on, Bullock, throw us
a bone here, will you?
You know, I've been thinking about getting
a dog. He could help us sniff out clues.
-Bruce wayne here.
-Bruce, it's Barbara.
Hey, Barb.
-She misses you.
-How's college?
Not bad, though the nightlife here
can't compare with kicking butt as Batgirl.
But spring break'll be coming up soon, and
I'll be back in Gotham for two whole weeks.
won't that be nice?
Yes, we'll all be happy to see you.
Don't drag me into this.
Anyway, that's not the reason I called.
I just saw the news and was wondering
if you got a new partner.
Someone a little older?
I have no idea who she is.
Because if you had,
I'd be really upset...
...because I thought you and I were,
you know....
Barb, we're going through
the East Tunnel now.
Afraid signal's breaking up.
Talk later.
Squeaked through again, didn't you?
I never fail to marvel
at your narrow escapes, sir.
One female bat at a time.
In discussing this new alloy,
I brought some charts...
...to demonstrate the care and precision
we bring to our work at wayne Tech.
So as you can see, the alloy's tensile
malleability is remarkably high...
...given its density
and homeotropic structure.
Meaning that the flexible
molecular stacking will...
...provide considerable morphological
adaptability...
...through the electromagnetic
manipulation of the quantum states!
See this chunk of metal?
I can program it to change shape.
-Oh, fantastic.
-That's fantastic.
I thought she said it was metal.
-Look at that.
-It's beautiful.
Just with one touch?
So exciting.
Actually, the technology's pretty simple.
It's just imprinting morph lines
with a pressure point.
-I'm not sure what it's good for.
-I happen to have a silent partner...
-...who I'm sure will find some use for it.
-That's great.
It's so cool to be in an R&D company
that takes young women seriously...
...especially blonds.
At wayne Tech, it's what's under
the hair that counts, Dr. Ballantine.
It's Rocky. Actually, Roxanne...
...but people have always called me
Rocky for some reason.
Look! It's the bat signal!
-where?
-Right there!
what's going on over there?
wow! I've never seen it before!
Isn't it exciting?
Every time. Check.
He'll get here. And remember,
when he does, I'll do the talking.
what is it, commissioner?
I had Bullock collect the remains
of the contraband destroyed.
I thought you might like to take a look.
Stuff's out of Star Trek. I thought
maybe someone broke into a toy store.
These aren't toys, Bullock.
This is a plasma rifle.
It could take out a tank at 200 yards.
More like 500.
I measured the clip size.
Sonia Alcana, Bullock's new partner.
There are also EK4 lasers and a barrel
from a surface-to-air missile launcher.
-who's behind this?
-The truck driver ain't talking...
...but I got some leads. Can't say
anything definite right now.
we have nothing.
-where'd you get this?
-From the guy's truck...
...when I had it impounded.
I'll get back to you.
what's got his tights in a twist?
Penguin owns this place?
Along with Duquesne and Thorne.
-what do they make here?
-Trinkets, figurines...
...weapons of mass destruction.
I don't see any of his goons around.
There she is!
See her?
Over there!
So you like to play rough, huh, sweetie?
welcome to superhero team-up!
Get them!
Come on!
-You shouldn't be here.
-Likewise.
No. I mean, I've set a charge.
where?
Below us.
A munitions room.
Let's get out of here!
where'd she go?
Up there!
Let's move!
They were making arms for Kasnia...
...something the State Department would
frown upon. This was their weapons plant.
-It would be a little hard to prove that now.
-Doesn't matter. They were finished here.
But I've just begun.
who are you? why are you doing this?
You're the great detective. Figure it out.
Gotta jet.
who? The Batwoman?
what do you mean it's gone?
The whole building?
You got a lot of nerve, freak!
You and your woman have caused me
enough grief for one night.
It's my home, my family! Get out!
I heard a commotion last night.
who was here?
Nobody.
Did nobody do that too?
Nothing for you to worry about.
As if I ever.
-where you going?
-Nowhere.
Do they have to come?
Just for the next couple days.
I'm having trouble with some people.
I don't want you to have any problems.
You mean like Mama problems?
You live under my roof in my town.
You do what I say!
Fetch.
That's her.
Exactly what is it you hope
to discover?
what a beautiful young woman does
in her free time.
A pleasure drive then.
I see why Dennis the Menace
is one step closer to juvenile hall.
-How many stores does this make so far?
-Including the nail boutique, seven.
And not one sale on explosives.
You know, Alfred, I think I could use
a new watch.
You deserve it, sir.
Brown taffeta? what are they thinking?
It's a dressing room! The worst that
can happen is, I'll need a size 8!
why don't you go rob gift wrap
or something?
I miss working for The Joker.
-Sir, could you help me?
-Sorry, I don't work here.
No, not that. See those men?
I'd rather they not see me.
If you could just help me get
to the escalator....
Okay. Usually, you only see things
like this in the movies.
Hey, wait! Miss Duquesne!
who's she with?
Keep going.
Oh, dear.
You're good.
Here they come.
Hurry, get in. Unless you want
that lovely face rearranged.
-Hey, stop!
-You crazy?
-who were they?
-Daddy's bodyguards.
You've just run off
with a very notorious woman.
I'm Kathy Duquesne,
daughter of Carlton Duquesne.
The gangster?
Yes, but we try not to use
the G word in front of Daddy.
This is interesting.
I think we're being followed.
Doesn't look like Daddy's goon squad.
Hope you're not expected anywhere.
You're on your own, Master Bruce.
we having fun yet?
Bruce wayne?
what a photo op!
The most respected man in Gotham with
the daughter of the most disrespected.
Your father has a lot of competition
for that title.
I know. Most of them come to dinner
from time to time.
I used to wonder what it's like to come
from a respectable family...
...where there's no violence,
no vendettas, no victims.
what must that feel like?
I wish I could tell you.
It must feel like freedom.
Kathy, be careful.
You sound like my mama. ''Be careful,
Kathy. Don't go scaring me, girl.''
This was our favorite spot.
we used to come out here to paint.
She was a great artist.
She said I had the eye.
She said, ''Honey, you could be
another Carrie Mae weems.''
what happened?
She died. Isn't that
what always happens?
I'm sorry.
Everyone's sorry.
It doesn't make any difference.
Here. Bring it back sometime.
Or not. There's always plenty more.
Down, boys.
I met Batwoman. She confirmed they were
making the weapons at Penguin's factory.
-who is she?
-I think Carlton Duquesne's daughter.
Remember the assassination attempt
on him 1 0 years ago?
Yeah, they missed him.
Hit his wife instead.
I think Kathy Duquesne blames her father
for that and a lot more.
Come on, she'd be biting
the hand that feeds her.
Think of the dough her old man has.
You can't buy peace of mind, Bullock.
Let's keep a tail on her.
I see Miss Duquesne is gifted
in other sports besides extreme shopping.
This bodes well for your suspicions,
does it not, Master Bruce?
Yes, Alfred.
-what's with him?
-I think he has some affection for this one.
He sure can pick them.
Relax, Penguin. we were gonna torch
the place for the money anyway.
I don't think you appreciate
the precariousness of our perch, Thorne...
...especially now that we have no factory!
If we're unable to deliver the rest
of our stockpile, we're dead.
The Kasnians will come after us
like wolverines.
we'll be begging for prison.
Duquesne says he can handle
the bat-broad.
She almost killed Batman,
for heaven's sake!
Normally, I would find
that commendable...
...but now it just proves
that Duquesne is out of his league.
we need some real muscle.
whoever you want to bring in,
Penguin, is fine with me.
I can't believe this!
who are they getting?
who's better than you?
Penguin's not saying.
Get out. Get out!
First you click on the red crystal, then
the blue, then hold down the shift key.
whoa! You got in!
I've raided a few tombs in my time.
She found the secret bonus level
to ''Death Castle 3000'' !
Nobody at school can figure it out.
The guys are gonna flip.
So is Alfred. He's been waiting
in the car for you all this time.
Thanks.
-working late again?
-Yeah.
Fortunately, my boyfriend
is very understanding. what about yours?
Girlfriend! I mean, of course girlfriend.
After all, considering your reputation.
Not that it's bad or anything or any
of my business, because it's not.
I was just curious.
How red is my face?
Crimson. And no, I don't
have anybody special.
Am I that forgettable, Bruce?
I've managed to lose my shadows
for a while...
...and I thought I'd paint the town red.
want to come along
and empty a few spray cans?
Excuse me, Kathy Duquesne,
Roxanne Ballantine.
-Pleased to meet you.
-Yes, I'm sorry.
-About what?
-I don't know.
So you never got married, huh?
Hard to believe. Here she comes.
well, what do you know?
It's the trash picking up the trash.
Hey, K.D.
Looking hot.
You got some fries with that shake?
I know, not exactly
the book-club crowd.
-I suppose you know who owns this place.
-She should. I bought her her first parasol.
-Kathleen.
-Ozzie.
And Mr. wayne.
It's been quite a while, hasn't it?
Yes. The last time was when
you stole plutonium...
...from one of my labs
and threatened to blow up the city.
Oh, yes, my more
rambunctious days.
Sir, your call just came in.
The vagaries of a restaurateur.
You understand.
Didn't know you and Penguin
had issues.
It's not the bird
that's bothering me, it's you.
-what kind of game are you playing?
-Game?
You dump your guards for a night,
and where do you go?
A club where the patrons
are your father's cronies.
It's like you want him to hear about it.
I'm not sure I like your tone.
I think I'll decide in the powder room.
So you've already landed. Splendid.
How soon before we can commiserate?
I can drop by your club tonight.
I assume you have a back entrance.
Oh, yes. I use it so much,
I'm thinking of installing a revolving door.
See you then.
-I said I wasn't to be disturbed.
-Oh, am I disturbing you?
Can't have that, can we?
How dare you? Release me at once,
you harridan, or I'll--
They're constricting.
They'll slice a penguin like a turkey,
unless you tell me who your new player is.
who, Penguin?
who's the big, bad boogeyman?
I can't hear you.
-Bane.
-Bane?!
No, run this way.
A bat-seeking missile for you, my dear.
You hear that?
Call for backup!
Time to burn a bat.
Come on, let's see those
pointy little ears.
-Stay together, come on.
-Hurry!
It must've been a heck of a floorshow.
I have to admit, not every date
I have ends with a police investigation.
You poor thing. Every time we're
together I seem to risk your life.
I'm sorry about tonight.
You were right about me.
No, no, don't say that.
I jumped to conclusions.
I was wrong about you. And tonight....
Tonight turned out wonderfully.
The old man wants you.
I'd invite you in, but I think
it's going to be chilly upstairs.
Souvenir?
I found it in the Penguin's club.
How about an autograph?
Make it a real collector's item.
-what did you learn at the lounge?
-Other than the fact...
...that Kathy Duquesne
can't be Batwoman, not much.
I found this in his office. I think
Batwoman used it on him. I kept a piece.
You know removing evidence
from the scene of a crime is...
...probably not gonna lose you
any sleep.
Call it a souvenir.
You saved my life once.
Nine years ago. Arsonists,
they burned my parents' shop.
I was sleeping.
we lived on the second floor.
My room was filled with smoke.
I couldn't find the window.
The floor was hot, flames shooting
between the floorboards.
And then, there you were.
I remember. The arsonists
were working for Rupert Thorne.
Part of his protection racket.
The DA couldn't make the case stick.
Yeah, that's why I decided
to become a cop.
I just thought you should know.
That's tight. what's it mean?
The wire from Penguin's office is identical
to the alloy Dr. Ballantine developed.
Rocky? You think someone's
using her stuff?
Arms up.
Proceed.
-Kevin, are you okay?
-No, Rocky, I'm not okay.
I'm so far from okay,
I can't even see it.
Don't give up. we're close.
Really close.
Once someone in Penguin's
organization is willing to talk--
You can't keep doing this.
It's too dangerous.
-If Penguin finds out you're spying on him--
-He won't. I can take care of myself.
I'm not the wimp I used to be.
I've changed. I've had to.
You'd have to be Supergirl
to stand a chance.
You don't know what I've been doing.
Look, Rocky, I don't want
to see you anymore.
-You aren't--
-Serious? I'm dead serious.
I've got five more years here
before I get a shot at parole.
It's stupid to waste your life
waiting for me.
-It's my life. I can waste it any way I want.
-Don't come here again, Rocky.
-If you do, I won't see you.
-Kevin?
Kevin, no! Listen to me.
Kevin!
You have no new messages.
-Batman?
-Nice moves for a computer geek.
I used to-- I mean--
well, so what?
I took self-defense classes,
like millions of women.
Now it's your turn.
why are you in my apartment?
Checking out your new designs.
They're beyond what you're doing
for wayne.
-You were--? You had no right to--
-where were you last night?
-I was at wayne Tech.
-You left by 7:00.
-well, I went for a walk.
-To the lceberg Lounge?
wait a minute, are you trying
to say I'm Batwoman? You're not serious.
Recognize this? Batwoman used it.
It has the same configuration
as the alloy you developed for wayne Tech.
So? I'm hardly the only one
working in metallurgy.
True, but you're the right body type.
And you have a motive.
Your fiancé was framed
for smuggling by the Penguin.
And I know someone
broke into the Penguin's files.
Yeah? So what? Of course I'm trying
to get Kevin's sentence commuted...
...but I'm not doing anything illegal.
Here's a radical notion:
Instead of me, how about you
investigate the birdman?
I bet there's lots more
incriminating evidence on his hard drives.
This game you're playing has high stakes,
higher than you know.
You could get hurt or worse.
You sound just like him.
I checked the warehouses
this morning.
-No reports of any trouble.
-Yet.
There's our cheerful associate.
Shall we meet and greet, gentlemen?
Penguin, I have reviewed your proposal
for my employment.
I'm sorry, but your terms
are not acceptable.
I want carte blanche,
complete control of the operation.
I answer to no one.
Now wait, you can't just
roll in here and give orders.
I just did, Se?or Duquesne.
Do not worry. If this Batwoman
attempts any interference at all....
He has a way with words.
Now, shall we discuss the shipment?
This time we have spared no expense.
we're using a luxury cruise liner
as our cover, and the ship sails tonight.
-what's the matter?
-The night you and I saw Batwoman...
...Rocky Ballantine was working
late at wayne Tech.
I knew she couldn't be Batwoman.
She's too nice.
I was so sure this time.
well, she can't be
in two places at once...
...unless she has the power
to duplicate herself.
Robin, get on the computer.
I need you to cross-reference all databases
on Kathy Duquesne and Roxanne Ballantine.
Find anything that connects them.
Anything.
-where are you going?
-To make a house call.
I've got it all: Their plans, the timetable,
the manpower, Bane's agenda--
-He's onto me.
-what?
Batman, he knows everything about me:
where I work, what I do,
all about Kevin. It's uncanny.
-So what?
-So what? He's gonna ruin everything!
I told you we should've created
a new identity, not just spun it off him.
She's right, look at how fast he caught
onto me. we didn't count on this.
So he thinks you're Batwoman.
Two days ago he thought it was you.
Tomorrow he'll think
it's someone else.
Trust me, if he really had any idea
what's going on, I would know.
we are so close to our goal. we stop them
tonight, and we've broken them.
-Tonight?
-They're moving that fast?
Not fast enough for us, Rocky.
Never fast enough for us.
Somebody in here?
-Something wrong?
-Nope.
-Yes.
-I got some bad news for you.
Or maybe good. There's no connection
between Kathy and Rocky.
Different cities, circles and planets.
No way they could've
known each other.
Yes, there is.
All they needed was someone
to introduce them.
Remember, once they load the ship...
...Bane will station himself
in the pilot's cabin...
...with guards at checkpoints.
You get past this one...
...and it's straight to the atrium
and the weapons.
And the gift boutiques.
Kathy, the detonator
has a failsafe countdown.
I wouldn't shop too long.
I guess this is it.
You sure you're gonna be all right?
Don't worry, I'll be back.
Se?orita.
would you stop that infernal tapping?
In a few minutes the ship will be...
...in international waters,
and we'll be very rich men.
Gin.
Yes. Yes, he's here. we're all here.
She did?
No. You want us now?
-Is the shipment--?
-It's fine...
...but he's not leaving the harbor yet.
He has Batwoman.
Mustn't keep the lady waiting.
-Batman?
-You knew Kathy Duquesne.
-what?
-You both took art classes together.
She sketched your face. It was years ago,
but it's you. Kathy had a good eye.
-You also knew Rocky Ballantine.
-who?
Let me jog your memory.
State University, freshman year.
Same dorm, same floor, same room.
You've been a busy bat.
You each brought something
to the party. Kathy had money...
...Rocky had the genius
and you had the scheme...
...and the will to make it happen.
when that fire destroyed my folks'
business, they never recovered.
They'd worked their whole lives,
and then it was ashes, just like that.
It tore our family apart.
Everyone knew it was Rupert Thorne,
but there was no way to prove it.
Now he's gonna know how it feels
to see his life go up in smoke.
Three Batwomen. It was just a matter
of disguising your voices and taking turns.
And you know what? It almost worked.
where is Kathy Duquesne?
-I'm here.
-Something's definitely wrong.
There's no report
of any ship in distress.
I radioed Kathy, but she's not responding.
She's in trouble, I can feel it.
what're we gonna do?
Sonia?
Olé, se?or. Exemplary work.
I wanted you here
when I realized who she was.
I felt a certain caution was in order.
So who is she?
-Kathy?
-what's going on, Duquesne?
-No wonder she always knew our plans.
-what? You think I told her?
She planned to use this.
Don't let the size fool you, se?ores,
it's a carbonite bomb.
It can take out this
entire chamber and more.
Are you crazy?
How could you do this to me?!
It was easy, Daddy. You made it easy,
because of the kind of man you are.
A man whose wife is killed
just because she stands next to him.
The kind of man who makes a prison
out of his own house...
...a prisoner out of his own child.
The kind of man who spreads misery
to everything he touches.
-And for what? For them?!
-Shut up!
-This doesn't make sense!
-On that we agree...
...because I distinctly remember
your daughter at my lounge...
...the same night Batwoman
assaulted me.
You're not in this alone,
are you, Kathleen?
who else?
Penguin, no!
No, don't!
Tell me who else is involved
while Daddy still has a neck.
Bon voyage, Se?or Batman.
Bridge, head out to sea.
I want us in international waters now.
-They're heading to sea. what do you think?
-Batman said he'd give a signal...
...but that doesn't mean
we can't take a closer look.
You're out, Duquesne.
I shouldn't have got mixed up
with you.
well, that'll give you and your brat
something to talk about in family therapy.
where's the bomb? wasn't it here?
It's not over yet, amigo.
-Here.
-I could've gotten out of them.
No doubt, since you
got yourself into them.
Your friends are waiting to rescue you.
Let's not disappoint them.
No, let's not.
Don't! Break the magnets,
and it'll go off.
There's no way to stop it
without the code...
...which escapes me at the moment.
I'm sorry, but one way
or another it has to end.
Even if she doesn't have the bomb I suggest
we act like cautious birds and head south.
well, what do you know?
Our two favorite felons.
Egads, they're multiplying.
That felt so good.
Now where's Kathy Duquesne?
Daddy!
I knew sooner or later we would
face each other, Batman. I prayed for it.
This ship is going down
in less than a minute.
That's all the time I need.
Should've saved those prayers.
-Abandon ship?
-You think?
Let's go. Double-time it.
Come on now.
-would you move it?
-Get over. I wanna get out of here.
Let's get going. Get out of here!
Come on, lower, lower, lower.
Sonia!
-I got her.
-Don't worry about me.
Just get them!
The ship's going down, Penguin.
Our only consolation is that
it will take a few bats with it.
what?
And I thought penguins liked the water.
Estupido! No bonds can hold me!
what?
No!
I can still crush you!
Sonia?
I've got you.
Maybe I should write the report
this time, huh, Bullock?
For what it's worth,
the city's losing a good cop.
Condoning vigilantes is one thing...
...but even Com. Gordon
draws the line at employing them.
we're just lucky the DA's
looking the other way.
Someday you'll have to tell me
how you do it.
How you keep from crossing the line.
when I put on the mask,
I couldn't even see the line.
-Maybe I don't take it as personally.
-Somehow I doubt that.
-where will you go?
-I'm not sure.
Someplace simpler, where capes
aren't the prevailing fashion.
-Don't tell me you came to wish me luck.
-That, and to give you this.
Exculpatory evidence that should help
release Dr. Ballantine's fiancé from jail.
-I thought it should come from you.
-I-- Thank you.
I'm sure she'll appreciate it.
I think I'm gonna miss that.
I hated who he was, what he did,
the hurt he brought to people.
But now that he's in here, I feel bad.
At least we talk. He's making a deal
to testify against Thorne and Penguin.
Maybe he hated his life
as much as you hated yours.
For a computer geek,
you're pretty smart.
-By the way, how's Bruce?
-Mr. wayne? Fine, I guess.
-You haven't heard from him?
-I think he's been reading the papers.
Rocky!
Kevin!
Kevin.
-About time I returned this.
-what are you doing here?
Funny thing. This morning I got up
thinking, ''Something's wrong.''
And then I realized: No gunfire,
no explosions, no goons out to do me in.
Everything was peaceful and quiet.
And that's when I realized
how much I missed you.
You poor thing. But that was the old
Kathy Duquesne. The new one is different.
She intends to live a life
of complete respectability.
-All the time?
-Afraid so.
well, maybe an explosion now and then.
[ENGLISH]