(crickets chirping)
(dog barks)
(footsteps approach)
(woman screaming)
I SAID BEDTIME.
WHAT AM I, 5?
IT'S 10:00.
YOU KNOW THE RULES.
I GET IT.
DAVID'S COMING,
AND YOU'RE GETTING SOME.
BEDTIME!
... AND YOU'RE WRONG.
I KNOW I'M RIGHT.
(grunts)
(dog barking)
(thud)
WHAT WAS THAT?
IT'S THE PINE OAKS SLASHER.
AND HE'S COMING FOR YOU
IF YOU DON'T GO TO BED.
I HEARD A NOISE.
WELL, I DIDN'T
HEAR ANYTHING.
YOU'RE STALLING. NOW GO.
(sighs)
(telephone rings)
FINALLY.
(sighs)
DAVID IS COMING.
NO, SHE'S UPSTAIRS.
SKANK.
(door squeaks)
SO WHEN ARE YOU
GONNA GET HERE?
(doorbell rings)
SILLY.
HEY, BABE-OH. MY GOD.
I'M SORRY, OFFICER.
(man)
SORRY TO BOTHER YOU, MISS,
BUT WE'VE BEEN GETTING
REPORTS ABOUT A PROWLER.
OH. UH, WHERE?
WELL, WE'VE GOTTEN
A FEW CALLS.
MAY I COME IN?
NO, YOU MAY NOT.
UM, I GUESS, SURE.
COME ON, ELLEN.
(door squeaks)
IS THERE ANYONE ELSE
IN THE HOUSE?
JUST MY SISTER.
IS THIS GONNA TAKE LONG?
WE HAVE
TO CHECK IT OUT, MISS.
UH, I'M EXPECTING SOMEBODY,
SO IF WE'RE GOOD...
ARE ALL THE DOORS LOCKED?
YES.
AND THE WINDOWS ARE SECURED?
YES, THE HOUSE IS
PRACTICALLY AIRTIGHT.
GOOD.
ONE.
TWO.
(muffled groan)
SHH, SHH, SHH.
COME ON, BEAUTIFUL,
DON'T BE LIKE THAT.
(grunting)
OW!
JENNY, RUN!
(door squeaks)
(grunting)
(whimpers) OW.
(telephone rings)
(screams)
(ring)
(screaming)
(gunshot)
(siren wailing)
(siren stops)
(chatter over police radio)
WE'RE TOO LATE.
(sighs)
YOU GOT HIM, TOM.
IT'S OVER.
(telephone rings)
(ring)
(cell phone ringing)
("Something That's Real"
by AnnMarie Milazzo)
¶¶ MY CURIOSITY ¶¶
¶¶ HAS PULLED ME BY THE HAND ¶¶
¶¶ AND SPINS ME DIZZY ¶¶
¶¶ EXPOSING ME AGAIN ¶¶
¶¶ AM I TRIPPING
ON WHAT'S BEHIND ME? ¶¶
¶¶ CARELESSLY ¶¶
¶¶ GIVE ME SOMETHIN'
THAT'S REAL ¶¶
¶¶ TO FILL MY SOUL ¶¶
¶¶ GIVE ME SOMETHIN'
THAT'S REAL ¶¶
¶¶ TO BE MYSELF ¶¶
¶¶ IT'S A MATTER OF FAITH ¶¶
¶¶ IT'S A MATTER OF TRUST ¶¶
¶¶ I CAN'T FIND MY WAY, LOVE ¶¶
¶¶ SO I'M REACHIN' OUT ¶¶
¶¶ JUST TO GIVE ME
SOMETHIN' TO FEEL ¶¶
¶¶¶¶¶¶
¶¶ CATCH MY BREATH ¶¶
¶¶ WHEN THE WALL
STARTS TO CRACK ¶¶
¶¶ KNOW THAT WHAT HOLDS YA ¶¶
¶¶ WILL HOLD YOU BACK ¶¶
¶¶¶¶¶¶
¶¶ GIVE ME SOMETHIN'
THAT'S REAL ¶¶
¶¶ SOMETHIN' THAT'S REAL ¶¶
¶¶ GIVE ME SOMETHIN' ¶¶
¶¶ TO FEEL ¶¶
¶¶ HEY, HEY, HEY ¶¶
¶¶ AH, REAL ¶¶
¶¶ GIVE ME SOMETHIN'
THAT'S REAL ¶¶
(AnGELa humming)
(scoffs)
FINALLY.
WHAT TOOK YOU SO LONG?
UH, YOU MUST BE ANGELA?
NO, NO.
I'M AN-GEL-A. (giggles)
OH, HI.
HI.
HUH. DRAMA MAJOR?
¶¶ WELCOME ¶¶
HUH, THANKS.
OKAY, I WANT US
TO BE FRIENDS.
OH, OKAY.
I WANT US TO BE CLOSE.
OH.
BY THE END OF THE YEAR,
WE ARE GONNA BE LIKE SISTERS.
OH, SORRY.
WHAT?
LOOK, ANGELA, I DON'T KNOW
WHAT YOU'VE HEARD OR...
I GOOGLED YOU.
I WANTED TO KNOW WHO
MY ROOMMATE WAS. (giggles)
OH.
YOU ARE ELLEN TRAYLOR'S
SISTER, RIGHT?
YEAH.
OH, COME ON.
IT'S PUBLIC KNOWLEDGE.
DON'T BE ALL PARANOID.
SO HOW MUCH OF IT
DID YOU ACTUALLY SEE?
GEE, ANGELA, UH...
(clears throat)
ALL THE GOOD PARTS.
I'M SORRY.
(sighs)
IT'S JUST THAT ALL
MY ACTING TEACHERS LAST YEAR
TOLD ME THAT I NEED
MORE LIFE EXPERIENCE.
YOU ARE LIKE MY OWN
PERSONAL GOLD MINE.
(giggles)
AH! YOU MUST BE
JENNY TRAYLOR.
HOW THE HELL
DO YOU KNOW MY NAME?
I'M TIM
YOUR RESIDENT ADVISOR.
OH, YEAH, RIGHT.
OH, I'M SORRY.
UH, HI. HI.
OKAY. (sighs)
FIRST TIME AWAY FROM HOME.
GOLD MINE!
HEY, NEW YORK CAN BE,
YOU KNOW, INTENSE.
GIVE IT A FEW WEEKS.
IT'LL LOVE YOU BACK.
UNLIKE CERTAIN
EX-BOYFRIENDS.
YOU DIDN'T ASK TO BE PUT
ON MY FLOOR THIS YEAR, DID YA?
LIFE EXPERIENCE.
WELL, ANYWAY,
MAKE SURE YOU CHECK OUT
THE ORIENTATION ISSUE
OF THE PAPER.
AND, UH, CAN I SIGN YOU UP
FOR THE BACK-TO-SCHOOL
SCAVENGER HUNT?
IT'S THE BEST.
(laughs)
OH.
TIM THINKS HE'S PUTTING
TOGETHER A REALITY SHOW.
(laughing) YOU... SERIOUSLY,
SCAVENGER HUNT ROCKS.
SIGN-UP SHEET
DOWN THE HALL.
OH, NO, I'M-I'M OKAY,
ACTUALLY. I DON'T-
KEEP IT.
OKAY, THANK YOU.
JUST IN CASE. SHH.
JUST IN CASE.
OKAY.
THANKS.
SMALL PENIS.
NO, NOT AT ALL.
(laughs)
(speaking indistinctly)
YEAH, REALLY.
(laughs)
OH, SORRY.
I KINDA DID IT ON PURPOSE.
OH.
(playing "Red"
by Cassandra Kubinski)
¶¶ WHEN I MET YOU
FOR THE FIRST TIME, BABY ¶¶
¶¶ YOU SMILED,
AND MY WORLD OPENED UP ¶¶
¶¶ IT DIDN'T TAKE ME LONG... ¶¶
HEY. OH, UM,
THIS SHOULD WORK.
MY OLDER BROTHER SAYS
THAT PROFESSOR HENDERSON
GIVES OUT THE SAME ASSIGNMENTS,
LIKE, EVERY YEAR.
SO NOW YOU ARE
GUARANTEED AN "A."
IF I DON'T,
IT'S YOUR BALLS.
OH, OKAY. (chuckles)
I MEAN, PROMISE?
(chuckles)
WHEN I GET MY "A,"
WE CAN NEGOTIATE.
UH, NO, YOU CAN'T.
OH.
¶¶ HOW COULD YOU DO IT TO ME?
I'M SEEIN' RED... ¶¶
YOU HAVE SO NOT EARNED
THE RIGHT TO BE JEALOUS.
WHY WOULD YOU
LEAD THIS GUY ON?
YOU GOT BETTER OPTIONS.
YOUR BEST OPTION'S RIGHT HERE.
HE'S DOING ME A FAVOR.
YOU SEEM SMART ENOUGH. WHY DON'T
YOU WRITE YOUR OWN PAPERS?
BECAUSE I CAN GET HIM TO.
I HAD GUYS LIKE THAT
ALL THROUGH HIGH SCHOOL.
DID YOU HAVE A LOT OF GUYS
IN HIGH SCHOOL?
I'LL NEVER TELL.
¶¶... LOVE THAT
WE LOST THAT NIGHT ¶¶
¶¶ BOY, YOU TRICKED ME ¶¶
¶¶ OH, BOY, YOU TRICKED ME ¶¶
WHAT'S YOUR
MAJOR MALFUNCTION?
CHAPPY. ARE YOU SCARED
OF GOING OUTSIDE?
NO... (scoffs)
NOT AT ALL.
THEN GO.
(sighs)
(cell phone rings)
MOM.
(rings)
(playing "Disco Pigs"
by Paparazzi Whore)
¶¶ HEY ¶¶
¶¶ HEY... ¶¶
THAT'S MY SEAT.
IT'S A PUBLIC SPACE.
SHE REALLY LIKES
SITTING THERE.
I SAT THERE
BEFORE I HAD MY INTERVIEW
FOR THE HONORS PROGRAM.
YOU GOT IN.
BECAUSE YOU SAT
IN THIS SEAT?
OH.
¶¶ HEY ¶¶
(singing indistinctly)
¶¶ GONNA WAKE UP... ¶¶
¶¶ NOW THAT WE FLAUNT THE TRUTH ¶¶
¶¶ AND UNDERSTAND US ¶¶
(muffled groans)
(banging noises)
(AnGELa) ¶¶ NO MORE... ¶¶
(sighs)
(singing indistinctly)
¶¶ NO MORE QUIET INSIDE... ¶¶
THREE MINUTES TO GO.
YEAH. (scoffs)
THANKS.
YOU SHOULD GO IN ANYWAYS.
YEAH, NO, THOUGH, 'CAUSE,
UM, 'CAUSE I'M SCARED OF HER,
SO, YEAH.
BESIDES, ANG-ANGELA
NEEDS HER TIME.
WELL, YOU CAN WAIT
IN MY ROOM,
AND THAT'S NOT
A PICKUP LINE OR ANYTHING.
I LIKE
BIGGER GIRLS.
OH.
OH. I-I MEAN,
THAT'S, YOU KNOW, UM,
I'M FROM NORTH CAROLINA.
OH.
HEY, WHAT YA HIDIN'
UNDERNEATH THE TOWEL?
AH, OW.
NOTHING FOR YOU.
HEY, YOU'RE COMIN'
TO THE SCAVENGER HUNT, RIGHT?
OF COURSE.
I'M SUCH A JOINER.
OW.
OH, HI.
I'M JUST WAITING
FOR MY...
GOD, YOU ARE SO LOUD.
ROOMMATE. (clears throat)
DID I INTERRUPT SOMETHING?
NO.
GAVIN, YOU STAY.
I- I-I CAN-I CAN TAKE CARE
OF THE-THE WINK-WINK
AND THE NUDGE-NUDGE...
(laughs) MYSELF, MAN.
BYE.
(scoffs)
I SHOULD GO. BYE.
SHE'S SHY...
AND KIND OF A FREAK.
(chuckles)
HE IS SO PAINFULLY
INTO YOU.
(chuckles)
I KNOW.
PLAYING HARD TO GET?
UM, NO, I AM HARD TO GET.
THAT CAME OUT WRONG.
(laughs)
I... I'M JUST-
I'M-I'M UNDATABLE.
(scoffs)
TRUST ISSUES.
(water running)
(squeaking sound)
(clinking sounds)
AAH!
THERE'S SOMEBODY IN THERE!
WHOA, WHOA, WHOA.
THERE'S-THERE'S SOMEBODY
IN THE BATHROOM.
OKAY.
THERE'S SOMEONE-
(Tim) WHAT'S WRONG?
JENNY SAW SOMEONE
IN THE BATHROOM.
ARE-ARE YOU SURE?
IF SHE SAYS SHE IS,
SHE IS.
YOU TOLD ME
I COULD GO IN NOW.
(laughter)
(sighs) OH.
ARE YOU OKAY?
(laughs)
(sighs)
(scoffs)
SOME PEOPLE ARE JUST
TOO HIGH-STRUNG.
(indistinct conversations)
HEY, JENNY.
OH.
WAIT, WAIT, WAIT, WAIT,
WAIT, WAIT, WAIT.
WHAT? WHAT?
WAIT. LOOK, I'M SORRY.
YOU ARE A CREEP.
I SWEAR I DIDN'T KNOW
IT WAS YOU.
WAIT, SO YOU WANTED THAT GUY
TO WALK IN ON SOMEBODY?
HE'S LONELY.
(scoffs)
I KID. I JOKE.
THAT'S WHAT I DO.
YOU'RE DISGUSTING. YOU'RE
SUPPOSED TO BE IN CHARGE.
IT'S WELCOME WEEK.
YOU'RE SUPPOSED TO PULL PRANKS
AND STUFF LIKE THAT.
OKAY, WOULD IT HELP
IF I SAID THAT I AM SORRY
THAT I TARGETED YOU?
BAD JUDGMENT CALL. WHAT?
UM, NO.
I'M A DICK.
I CROSSED THE LINE.
I AM SORRY. I-I WON'T
DO IT TO YOU AGAIN.
AND WHY SHOULD I
TRUST YOU?
I PROMISE NOT TO BE A DICK
AGAIN, SO SAFE, RIGHT?
CAN I MAKE IT UP TO YOU?
HOW?
THERE'S STILL TIME TO SIGN UP
FOR THE SCAVENGER HUNT.
(chuckles)
YOU'LL MA-
YOU'LL MAKE NEW FRIENDS,
AND, HELL, IF YOU WIN,
YOU WILL ERASE THAT-
THIS WHOLE PARANOID
REPUTATION THING.
BYE, TIM.
OKAY, I'LL CATCH YOU
LATER ON. BYE.
HEY, GUYS, SIGN UP
FOR THE SCAVENGER HUNT.
THERE'S ONLY FOUR
MORE DAYS LEFT, HUH?
OKAY, GREAT.
(voices overlapping)
CAN I...
(chuckles)
GAVIN.
WANT TO PULL UP A SEAT?
I'M OKAY. I'M JUST-I'M GETTING
A HEAD START ON SOME READING.
I CAN BE YOUR CLIFF NOTES
IF YOU WANT.
AH.
(laughs)
(playing "Anything But Ordinary"
by AnnMarie Milazzo)
¶¶ HEY ¶¶
¶¶ HEY... ¶¶
I'LL BET THEY DON'T HAVE
THIS IN THE SUBURBS.
NO, YOU'RE RIGHT.
WE DON'T.
KINDA WISH I'D GROWN UP
IN THE SUBURBS.
SPEND 18 YEARS
IN NORTH CAROLINA,
AND YOU JUST WANT MORE.
¶¶ JUST THE PAIN THAT COMES
FROM LOOKIN' BACK ¶¶
¶¶ BORN, BUT NOT FOR LIVIN',
AS OUR MOTHERS... ¶¶
HEY, UH,
DO YOU KNOW WHY
THERE ARE-SO MANY
NEW YORKERS ARE DEPRESSED?
NO.
IT'S 'CAUSE THE LIGHT AT THE END
OF THE TUNNEL IS NEW JERSEY.
(laughs)
¶¶ YOU MOVE FORWARD,
AND I MOVE DESPERATELY ¶¶
IT'S STARTING TO RAIN.
¶¶ AND THE NOISE DROWNS ME ¶¶
¶¶ YEAH, THE DREAM... ¶¶
WHERE WERE YOU WHEN...
I WAS UP AT SCHOOL
IN THE BRONX.
¶¶... FOOLIN' MYSELF,
JUST LIKE EVERYBODY... ¶¶
YOU MUST HAVE BEEN...
I CAN'T IMAGINE
LIVIN' ANYWHERE ELSE.
(thunder rolls)
MY BROTHER DIED HERE.
IT'S LIKE
HE'S BURIED HERE.
¶¶ ORDINARY... ¶¶
I'M SORRY.
YEAH, I DON'T USUALLY LEAD OFF
WITH THAT ON A FIRST DATE.
OH, REALLY?
NO.
NICE.
YOU SEEM KINDA MORBID
AND TWISTED, TOO.
THANK YOU.
YOU'RE WELCOME.
YEAH, DEAD SIBLINGS HAVE,
UH, THAT AFFECT ON YOU.
DID ANGELA TELL YOU?
YEAH.
SHE KINDA TOLD EVERYBODY
ABOUT YOU BEFORE YOU GOT HERE.
NICE.
WOULD YOU BELIEVE IT
IF I TOLD YOU THAT
I'M KINDA GLAD SHE DID?
¶¶ AND THE NOISE DROWNS ME ¶¶
¶¶ YEAH, THE DREAM ¶¶
¶¶ HASN'T FOUND ME A WAY ¶¶
¶¶ DON'T WANT
TO BE FULL OF MYSELF ¶¶
¶¶ JUST LIKE EVERYBODY ELSE ¶¶
¶¶ IT'S GETTING HARDER... ¶¶
WHAT DO YOU WANT?
I DON'T KNOW.
¶¶ TO BE ANYTHING
BUT ORDINARY ¶¶
DO YOU WANT
TO HOLD MY HAND?
I DO.
UM, THIS.
DO YOU WANT SOME-
SOME SORT OF BACON?
YOU WANT SOME?
CHICKEN?
(chuckles)
FRIED RICE?
WHAT DO YOU THINK?
(gunshot, screaming)
(breathing heavily)
MONEY!
DOWN! DOWN!
(screaming)
OH, MY GOD!
DOWN!
(cash register dings)
FASTER! FASTER!
(gunshot)
(screaming)
DOWN!
(gun cocks)
(gunshot)
(screams)
(breathing heavily)
(cell phone rings)
MOM.
(ring)
IF I TELL HER
WHAT HAPPENED...
(ring)
THEN I'VE LOST.
YOU DON'T HAVE
TO GO HOME.
(ring)
YOU'VE LOST IF YOU
NEVER LEAVE THIS ROOM,
AND ANGELA
NEEDS HER SPACE.
(ring)
HI, MOM.
NO, I'M FINE. I'M FINE.
YEAH, IT'S GREAT.
I LOVE NEW YORK.
YEAH, I-I EVEN
BOUGHT THE T-SHIRT.
(laughs) YEAH.
LISTEN, I HAVE
TO GO, THOUGH,
BECAUSE, UM, THERE'S
A NEW STUDENT BARBECUE,
SO, UM, I'LL TALK
TO YOU LATER, OKAY?
YEAH, YEAH.
TELL-TELL DAD
I SAID HI.
I LOVE YOU, TOO. BYE.
WHAT? YOU'RE NOT THE ONLY
ACTRESS IN THIS ROOM.
(scoffs) YES, BUT THIS ONE
HAS AN AUDITION TOMORROW,
YOU'RE LEAVING SCHOOL?
HELLO,
IT'S A BROADWAY SHOW.
IF I BOOK IT,
I WILL NOT NEED COLLEGE.
HEY, ANGELA.
NOT INTERESTED,
NOT ANYMORE.
HEY, GUYS.
LOOK, YOU HAVE NO IDEA HOW
MUCH FUN THIS IS GONNA BE.
DON'T EVEN-NO IDEA.
IT-IT'S GONNA BE LIKE CAMP.
THIS IS EXACTLY WHY PEOPLE
THINK YOU'RE UNAPPROACHABLE!
OH!
(playing "Here For You"
by Jeremy Kushnier)
YOU WANT ME TO GO?
YOU DON'T HAVE TO.
HOW ARE YOU DOING
WITH ALL OF THIS?
¶¶ DAYS DRIFT BY,
AND I DON'T KNOW... ¶¶
I'M WITH YOU.
¶¶ WHERE I'LL BE
COME TOMORROW ¶¶
¶¶ BUT TONIGHT ¶¶
¶¶ I'M HERE WITH YOU... ¶¶
OW.
OH, I'M SORRY.
SORRY.
IT'S BEAUTIFUL.
MM. IT'S A HAND-ME-DOWN
FROM MY BROTHER.
¶¶ SO TONIGHT ¶¶
¶¶ I AM HERE FOR YOU ¶¶
¶¶ I'M HERE FOR YOU ¶¶
(AnGELa sings)
¶¶ DON'T RUN AWAY,
AND DON'T LOSE YOUR BREAKFAST ¶¶
¶¶ HAVE A CONVERSATION,
LOOK HIM IN THE EYE ¶¶
¶¶ BE A LITTLE WHILE... ¶¶
YEAH, I-I DON'T-I DON'T
WANT TO BE HER PARTNER.
OH, COME ON. YOU GET TO BE
WITH A SOPHOMORE.
SHE'S A LOT OF FUN,
TRUST ME. I DID HER.
YEAH, RIGHT.
PAULA.
NO.
I THINK
THAT THE SCAVENGER HUNT
WOULD MAKE AN EXCELLENT STORY
FOR THE "DAILY YORKER."
RELEVANT TO ME HOW?
I CAN, UH,
GET YOU ON STAFF.
YOU COULD GET ME
ON THE PAPER?
GOD, PAULA,
FOR SOMEONE SO TOUGH,
YOU CAN BE SO NAIVE.
OH, PLUS I SCORED
WHITE STRIPES TICKETS
FOR THE PRIZE.
BACKSTAGE PASSES, TOO.
YOU KNOW, I HAVE IT
ON STRONG AUTHORITY
THAT SOME EXECS
FROM WARNER MUSIC
ARE GOING TO BE THERE.
IF YOU WIN THE TICKETS,
YOU DON'T HAVE TO TAKE HER,
OKAY? TAKE SOMEBODY ELSE.
OH, HEY, CAMILLE.
WHOA, THAT-THAT-
THAT CONCERT'S SOLD OUT.
EVEN MY DAD'S FIRM
CAN'T GET THEIR HANDS ON TICKETS
TO THE WHITE STRIPES CONCERT.
THE WINNING TEAM
GETS THE TICKETS.
WHAT DID YOU SAY?
HE SAID HE'S GONNA WIN
THE SCAVENGER HUNT,
OH, AND CAMILLE.
YOU GONNA LET THAT HAPPEN?
YEAH, CHAPPY, ARE YOU
GONNA LET THAT HAPPEN?
YOU WOULD DO THAT FOR ME?
IF YOU'RE THE WINNER.
I'M IN.
NOBODY'S GETTING THEIR HANDS
ON ANYTHING BUT ME.
I'LL DO IT.
I'LL PLAY YOUR
LITTLE GAME, TIM.
I...
THAT MAN HAS
BECOME A PUTZ.
(sighs)
YOU HAVE BEEN
REALLY PATIENT WITH ME.
THANK YOU.
HEY, I WAS THERE.
BUT YOU HANDLE IT
WAY BETTER THAN I DO.
WELL, FOR ONE,
I LEAVE MY ROOM.
OKAY, IF YOU-IF YOU WANT TO GO
ON THE SCAVENGER HUNT THING,
THEN GO,
WIN THE CONCERT TICKETS.
WILL YOU LEAVE YOUR ROOM
TO GO WITH ME?
MM.
I DON'T WANT THE TICKETS,
AND I DON'T WANT TO BE
ON SOME STUPID SCAVENGER HUNT
WITHOUT YOU.
BUT...
YOU CAN'T STAY IN HERE
FOREVER, JENNY.
STOPPING YOUR LIFE
LIKE THIS
MEANS YOU'RE NO BETTER OFF
THAN YOUR SISTER.
HOW COULD YOU
SAY THAT...
TO ME?
BECAUSE I SAY IT
TO MYSELF EVERY DAY.
IT'S LIKE...
IF I GO OUTSIDE,
I'LL GET KILLED.
(scoffs)
OH, IS THAT THE STUPIDEST
THING YOU'VE EVER HEARD?
NO,
BECAUSE YOU COULD BE KILLED
INSIDE THE ROOM.
YOU'RE BAD.
WELL, YOU ASKED ME
HOW I GET THROUGH IT.
YOU GOTTA HAVE
A SENSE OF HUMOR.
SO DID YOU...
REALLY WANT TO GO
ON THAT SCAVENGER HUNT?
ONLY WITH YOU.
(door squeaks)
(door slams shut)
(cell phone rings)
(playing
"She's Gonna Make You Want Her"
by Cassandra Kubinski)
¶¶ DON'T THINK I DON'T NOTICE
HOW YOUR MOUTH FELL OPEN ¶¶
¶¶ WHEN SHE CAUGHT YOUR... ¶¶
(cell phone rings)
¶¶ EYE ¶¶
¶¶ WEARIN' JEANS ¶¶
¶¶ JUST TIGHT ENOUGH ¶¶
¶¶ SO YOU CAN SEE
WHAT'S SHAPIN' THEM INSIDE ¶¶
WHAT'S UP?
HI.
¶¶ OH, SHE'S GOT YOU BLIND... ¶¶
HEY.
I LIKE YOUR SHIRT.
HEY, THANKS, IT'S
A JOHNNY DEPP PROPS THING.
HERE.
HEY, CAMILLE.
(cell phone rings)
OH, SORRY.
BE RIGHT BACK.
(ring)
WHAT ARE YOU LOOKIN' AT?
OOH, OKAY,
SORRY, EVERYONE.
SORRY. SORRY, EVERYBODY.
SORRY I WAS LATE.
I HOPE YOU DIDN'T START
WITHOUT ME, BUT IF YOU DID,
I'M SURE SOMEBODY CAN CATCH
ME UP. ALL RIGHT, GO AHEAD.
WE HAVEN'T STARTED YET.
OH, GOOD. DO YOU WANT
TO KNOW WHY I WAS LATE?
NO.
I TOTALLY STOOD IN LINE
FOR THE OPEN CALL
FOR "SPRING AWAKENING."
OH, WOW, DID YOU GET
TO "SING" FOR THEM?
UH, "THAT'S
SO NOT THE POINT."
DOES HE HAVE
TO BE MY PARTNER?
HE SO DOESN'T GET ME,
AND, P.S., YOU HAVE GOT
TO MAKE A COSTUME CHANGE
BEFORE YOU'RE GOING TO BE SEEN
ANYWHERE IN THE CITY NEAR ME.
BUT THIS IS
MY "JOHNNY DEPP"-
IT IS
UNFORTUNATELY WRONG.
ALL WE'RE MISSING
IS GAVIN AND JENNY.
OH, YEAH, SHE CAME OUT,
UNLIKE CERTAIN PEOPLE WE KNOW.
(giggles)
(imitates
AnGELa's giggle)
HI, GUYS.
(sighs)
WHERE'S GAVIN?
WELL, YOU-YOU SNOOZE, YOU LOSE.
START WITHOUT HIM.
IT'S FIVE AFTER.
HE SAID
HE WOULD BE HERE.
IS SHE GONNA FREAK OUT?
OH, NO, SHE DOESN'T FREAK OUT.
SHE IMPLODES.
GUYS, I AM RIGHT HERE.
I'M NOT DEAF.
I'M BACK. LET'S START.
YOU ALL, THIS GAME'S SUPPOSED
TO BRING US CLOSER, OKAY?
YOU KNOW, SORRY, JENNY,
WE GOTTA START.
OKAY, YOU CAN FILL IN GAVIN
WHEN HE GETS HERE, ALL RIGHT?
WELCOME, EVERYONE,
TO THE 12 TO 12
SCAVENGER HUNT.
(cheering)
(speaking indistinctly)
SO ALL OF YOU
CHECK YOUR CELL PHONES.
YOU SHOULD ALL BE
RECEIVING A MESSAGE
FROM RED HOOK.
(cell phones ringing)
I DON'T HAVE A MESSAGE.
YEAH, I JUST
SENT IT TO YOU.
OH, NO,
I MEAN FROM GAVIN.
HE SAID THAT HE WAS
GONNA BE HERE AT NOON,
AND HE'S NOT HERE, SO...
OKAY, WELL,
WHAT DO YOU WANT TO DO?
(scoffs) FREAK.
SAVE RED HOOK
TO YOUR PHONE BOOK.
TRUST ME.
GONNA COME IN VERY HANDY.
NOW EACH OF YOU
SHOULD HAVE A CLUE,
SOME THE SAME,
SOME DIFFERENT.
YOU MAY INTERSECT ONE ANOTHER,
YOU MAY NOT.
YOU EACH HAVE 12 TO SOLVE.
"WASHINGTON SQUARE ARCH."
THAT'S OUR FIRST CLUE.
SHH!
SO SHE THINKS. WHEN YOU
ACTUALLY FIND OUT THE CLUE,
YOU GO TO A LOCATION
WHERE YOU LOOK FOR AN OBJECT.
A POM-POM?
WAIT, THAT'S-THAT'S NOT
THE OBJECT IN THE CLUE, IS IT?
LET'S LISTEN, PEOPLE.
YOU THEN HAVE TO TAKE
A PICTURE OF YOURSELF
WITH THE OBJECT
AT THE LOCATION
AND THEN SEND IT
VIA TEXT MESSAGE TO RED HOOK.
I WILL THEN TEXT YOU BACK
WITH YOUR NEXT CLUE TO YOUR NEXT
LOCATION AND OBJECT AND SO ON.
I MEAN, I DON'T WANT
TO GO TO...
GRANT'S TOMB WITHOUT GAVIN.
OKAY, FOR THOSE OF US
WHO ARE GOING TO PLAY,
WHAT'S THE CATCH?
ALL RIGHT,
IT'S 12 TO 12.
THE FIRST TEAM TO GET
TO THE FINAL DESTINATION
BY MIDNIGHT WINS.
WHERE IS THAT?
HE'S NOT GONNA TELL US.
IT'S A SCAVENGER HUNT. WE'RE
SUPPOSED TO FIGURE IT OUT.
I'LL GIVE YOU PART
OF THE ANSWER, OKAY?
FOR ALL OF YOU, YOUR FIRST
LOCATION IS IN MANHATTAN.
IT'S NOT FAR FROM CAMPUS,
BUT BY MIDNIGHT TONIGHT,
YOU WILL FIND YOUR WAY
TO A LOCATION
IN ONE OF
THE OTHER FOUR BOROUGHS.
THE WINNING TEAM
GETS THE TICKETS.
ALL RIGHT, HOW ABOUT
A LITTLE FLOOR SPIRIT?
(laughs uncomfortably)
HUH? FLOOR SPIRIT!
FLOOR SPIRIT, COME ON!
COME ON, IT'S ALL PART OF
THE BONDING. WHAT DO YOU SAY?
HONEY, HONEY, HONEY.
ALL RIGHT,
ONE, TWO, THREE...
(all) BREAK!
(laughs)
ALL RIGHT, SERIOUSLY,
WHERE'S YOUR CLOSET?
YOU GONNA BE ALL RIGHT?
OH... (laughs)
CRAP. I GOTTA
GO PLANT A...
YEAH, LIKE I'M GONNA TELL YOU
WHAT THE CLUE IS.
(cell phone rings)
HI, GAVIN, IT'S JENNY.
UH, I GOT THE FIRST CLUE,
BUT I NEED A NEW YORKER
TO HELP FIGURE IT OUT,
SO COULD YOU CALL ME?
SEE?
I THOUGHT
YOU SAID PIANO BAR.
UM, I WAS
IN THE RIGHT VICINITY-
THE WEST VILLAGE,
A PIANO AND A BAR.
SO WHAT THE HELL DOES
"SING FOR THE CAMERA" MEAN?
DO YOU PLAY THE PIANO?
DEPENDS.
GIVE ANGELA YOUR PHONE.
OKAY, BUT I HAD
TO DESIGN FIVE WEB SITES
TO AFFORD
THAT PHONE, SO...
EXACTLY.
TIM KNOWS YOU HAVE A VIDEO
PHONE. SING FOR THE CAMERA.
HI, COULD YOU
DO US A FAVOR?
(sighs)
OH, YAY.
HELLO, NEW YORK.
LIVE FROM THE DUPLEX...
SO, SERIOUSLY, THAT
PHONE'S REALLY EXPENSIVE.
HOW DO YOU
USE THIS THING?
(hums)
¶¶ IS THIS THING ON? ¶¶
ARE YOU KIDDING ME
WITH THIS?
SOME KID CAME BY A WEEK AGO,
TALKED TO THE NIGHT GUY,
CONVINCED HIM
TO LET OUR PLACE
BE A PART
OF THE SCAVENGER HUNT THING.
NOW WAS THE KID
REALLY, REALLY CUTE?
A REGULAR BRAD PITT.
YOU KNOW, I ALWAYS PICTURED TIM
AS MORE OF AN ADAM BRODY TYPE.
YEAH.
(scoffs) THIS IS SO TIM.
HIT IT.
MM-HMM.
OKAY.
¶¶ OH, AN INTERNET CAFé ¶¶
¶¶ IS THE NEXT PLACE
YOU'VE GOTTA SEEK ¶¶
¶¶ THERE'S A GIRL
BEHIND THE COUNTER THERE ¶¶
¶¶ WHOSE NAME
IS QUITE UNIQUE ¶¶
¶¶ FIND ASMERET ¶¶
¶¶ IT MIGHT NOT BE EASY,
BUT ASMERET HAS A HINT FOR YOU ¶¶
¶¶ SHE'LL HAND YOU A CD ¶¶
¶¶ OH, GO ANGELA
AND HIGGINBOTHAM, TOO ¶¶
¶¶ GET YOUR ASSES
OFF THAT STAGE ¶¶
¶¶ AND FIND YOURSELF
ANOTHER CLUE ¶¶
(laughs)
OKAY.
ARE YOU COMING?
DON'T FORGET MY PURSE.
(Jenny) HI, IT'S ME AGAIN.
I FEEL LIKE A STALKER.
UM, CALL ME.
WELL, ACTUALLY, DON'T CALL ME.
JUST COME TO MY DORM ROOM.
PAULA AND ROY ARE GONNA WIN
THE SCAVENGER HUNT ANYWAY.
I... (sighs)
I- I REALLY WANT TO SEE YOU.
(sighs)
(cell phone rings)
THANK YOU, TIM.
I AM NOT PICKING UP A USED
CONDOM FROM THE GROUND.
UGH, DIRT.
YEAH, BUT THE CLUE SAYS
WE NEED TO FIND
SOMETHING MADE OF LATEX.
WAIT, I HAVE A CONDOM
IN MY PURSE.
BUT IT HAS TO BE USED.
HMM.
(scoffs)
(knock on door)
(cell phone rings)
(sighs)
WHAT, WHAT?
GAVIN?
TIM?
I TOLD YOU WE WERE
IN THE RIGHT PLACE.
LET'S JUST GET THE CLUE.
TIM SENT THE P.D.F. HERE, SO IT
SHOULD PRINT OUT BEHIND US.
I KNOW MY WAY AROUND
A NEWSPAPER OFFICE.
I WAS EDITOR.
YEAH, THIS IS
"THE NEW YORK TIMES."
AND WHILE I'M HERE,
WHO CAN I TALK TO
ABOUT AN INTERNSHIP?
(scoffs)
LEAD THE WAY.
UM, NEED HELP?
I GOT IT.
(clears throat)
PAULA, LOOK AT HER.
IT'S CAMILLE.
YOU KNOW, I CAN-
I CAN KINDA SEE WHY
THE FAGS LIKE DOIN' IT HERE.
CHAPPY.
WHAT? I HEARD
ABOUT THIS PLACE.
YOU KNOW, I MEAN, LIKE,
WHY DO THE DUDES DOING DUDES
GET TO BE THE ONLY ONES
WHO GET TO ENJOY THE OUTDOORS?
I DON'T KNOW.
COULD BE KINDA HOT
DOING IT IN PUBLIC.
YEAH, KNOWING
YOU CAN GET CAUGHT.
AND ARRESTED.
DIRTY.
THE GROUND IS SOFT.
OH, YOU OKAY?
YEAH, YEAH, I'M FINE.
(clears throat)
SO, UH, WHERE ARE WE-WHERE ARE
WE GONNA FIND A USED CONDOM?
AROUND...
HERE.
ARE YOU SERIOUS?
THE SOONER WE GET IT,
THE SOONER WE CAN
WIN THOSE TICKETS.
(chuckles)
(giggles)
OH, WHOA, IT LOOKS LIKE
SOMEBODY ELSE HAS BEEN HERE.
GOD, IT'S DIRTY.
(Roy)
THAT'S REALLY CREEPY.
(Paula) YEAH.
TIM IS REALLY GOOD
AT PHOTOSHOP.
"COMING TO A VIDEO STORE
NEAR YOU"?
OH, LOOK, HE PUT OUR NAMES
ON TWO BOOTS.
WHY?
OH, I GET IT.
TWO BOOTS-UH, THE-
THE PIZZA PLACE.
DO I EXIST?
BUT WHAT DOES THAT HAVE TO DO
WITH A VIDEO STORE?
TWO BOOTS
IN THE EAST VILLAGE-
THEY SHOW MOVIES.
EXCUSE ME?
TWO BOOTS.
OH, I HEARD
WHAT YOU SAID.
I JUST DIDN'T THINK PEOPLE
WERE SUPPOSED TO HELP US
ON A SCAVENGER HUNT.
I GOT WORK TO DO,
AND YOU'RE IN MY WAY.
I LIKE THE WAY YOU THINK.
LET'S GET A PICTURE.
(clears throat)
OH.
(camera shutter clicks)
(giggles)
(chuckles)
OH, MY-OH, MY GOD.
I WOULD KILL TO SEE TIM'S FACE
WHEN HE GETS OUR PICTURE.
(cell phone rings)
(ring)
WHO IS THAT?
MUST BE THE NEXT CLUE.
NO, NO, THE CLUE CAME
ON MY PHONE.
WHO-WHO THE HELL
IS ASMERET?
THEN I MUST HAVE GOTTEN
A WRONG NUMBER.
THEN WHY DID YOU
TURN IT OFF SO FAST?
ARE YOU ALWAYS
THIS CRANKY AFTER SEX?
YEAH, I GUESS.
OH, MY GOD. (scoffs)
IS THIS YOUR FIRST TIME?
CAMILLE, WHO TEXTED YOU?
NO ONE.
GIVE IT UP, OKAY?
LOOK, I KNOW YOU WEREN'T AT HOME
WITH A COLD THE OTHER NIGHT.
(sighs) WHAT DO YOU
WANT ME TO SAY?
JUST TELL ME THE TRUTH.
YOU CAN FIGURE IT OUT.
LOOK, YOU KNOW WHAT?
I'M OUT OF HERE. YOU...
I'M GONNA GO FIND
THE NEXT CLUE.
IF YOU WANT
TO FIGURE IT OUT,
YOU KNOW
WHERE TO FIND ME.
(scoffs)
CHAPPY?
(sighs)
COME ON,
GIVE ME MY SHIRT.
LOOK, I'M SORRY, OKAY?
NOW IT'S EVEN DIRTIER.
(gasps)
(knock on door)
(footsteps retreating)
(door squeaks)
(cell phone rings)
STILL NO SIGN?
GOOD GOD, TIM. WHAT-
OH. (chuckles)
PLANTING CLUES.
WHY'D YOU SEND ME
THOSE TEXT MESSAGES?
THEY'RE YOUR CLUES
TO START THE GAME.
BUT GAVIN WAS NOT
IN HIS ROOM,
AND WHY DID YOU
SEND ME "OOPS"?
THAT WAS
REALLY, REALLY CRUEL.
IT WASN'T ME.
THE MESSAGES ARE
FROM RED HOOK.
LOOK, I DON'T KNOW. "OOPS"
IS ONE OF MY QUICK NOTES.
I MIGHT HAVE ACCIDENTALLY
SENT THAT INSTEAD OF A CLUE.
ALL THE CLUES ARE
PROGRAMMED IN, SEE?
"GAVIN IS IN HIS ROOM."
MUST HAVE BEEN
AN OLD MESSAGE.
LOOK, IT HAD-IT HAD NOTHING
TO DO WITH YOUR FIRST CLUE.
GRANT'S TOMB?
YOU HAVE TO ADMIT
YOU'RE PRETTY MORBID.
WHAT DOES THAT HAVE
TO DO WITH ANYTHING?
I INTENTIONALLY MATCHED
ALL OF THE CLUES
WITH EACH PERSON
IN THE GAME.
UM, I DON'T GET IT.
ALL THE PICTURES THAT
EVERYONE IS SENDING ME-
I'M PUTTING THEM
ALL TOGETHER.
IT'S KIND OF LIKE A MOVIE,
YOU KNOW, DRAMA, RIGHT?
LIKE, I HAVE IT SET UP
SO THE CHAPPY HAS TO MEET UP
WITH HIGGINBOTHAM AND ANGELA
AT AN INTERNET CAFé
FOR A SURPRISE CLUE.
WE GET TO SEE
HOW THEY GET ALONG.
SO WAIT,
WHAT KIND OF SITUATION
WERE YOU PLANNING
ON PUTTING ME AND GAVIN INTO?
I THOUGHT GRANT'S TOMB MIGHT
GET YOU ALL HOT FOR EACH OTHER.
DO YOU ACTUALLY
ENJOY BEING A DICK?
CUT YOUR LOSSES.
SO YOU GOT STOOD UP.
YOU STILL HAVE
PLENTY OF TIME
TO FIND ANOTHER PARTNER
FOR THE GAME.
I GUARANTEE YOU
IT IS SO WORTH IT.
THE FINAL DESTINATION-
SO COOL.
TELL ME WHAT IT IS.
WHAT IS IT?
YOU'LL JUST HAVE
TO BE THERE BY MIDNIGHT.
A HINT, A HINT.
OH, THE HINT-
THE CLUE IS IN THE CLUES.
(gasps)
WAIT, WAIT,
SO ALL OF MY CLUES,
WHAT DID YOU SAY, THEY'RE-
THEY'RE GONNA BE MATCHED TO ME?
JOIN THE GAME
AND FIND OUT!
COME ON, GOD!
(breathing heavily)
JENNY!
(grunts)
YOU WANT TO TELL ME
WHY YOU'RE CHASING JENNY
AND HOW THE HELL
YOU GOT IN?
IT'S OKAY DEENA, DEENA.
SO DO YOU, UH,
WANT TO TELL ME
WHY YOU'RE CHASING ME
AND HOW THE HELL YOU GOT IN?
UH, YEAH.
OW.
(speaking indistinctly)
THAT'S ALL RIGHT.
YEAH, UM, YOUR PARENTS
WERE WORRIED ABOUT YOU,
AND THEY KNEW I'D RETIRED UP
HERE, SO THEY CALLED ME.
(scoffs) WHY DIDN'T YOU
JUST TELL ME?
BECAUSE THEY DIDN'T
WANT TO MAKE IT SEEM
LIKE THEY WERE
CHECKIN' UP ON YOU.
SO WHERE WERE YOU
WHEN I WAS BEING SHOT AT?
SHOT AT?
JENNY, YOUR PARENTS
CALLED ME TWO DAYS AGO.
OKAY, THEN SOME-SOMEBODY
HAS BEEN FOLLOWING ME AROUND
SINCE THE DAY
THAT I GOT HERE.
OKAY, HAVE YOU SEEN HIM?
NO? ANY DESCRIPTION?
UH, THAT'S THE THING.
I HAVEN'T-
I HAVEN'T REALLY
SEEN ANYBODY,
BUT IT'S JUST
THIS FEELING THAT I GET.
OR MAYBE I'M CRAZY.
AFTER WHAT
YOU'VE BEEN THROUGH,
YOU'VE GOT A RIGHT TO JUMP
AT EVERY NOISE YOU HEAR.
WHY DIDN'T YOU
JUST SHOW YOURSELF?
I WAS PUTTIN' YOUR PARENTS
BEFORE YOU, AND I'M SORRY.
THAT WON'T HAPPEN AGAIN.
CAN YOU DO ME A FAVOR?
CAN YOU TELL MY PARENTS
THAT YOU LOST MY TRAIL
BECAUSE I STARTED
SELLING DRUGS,
AND I JOINED A CULT,
AND MY PIMP REALLY
DOESN'T APPRECIATE
YOU FOLLOWING ME AROUND.
OKAY, I GET IT.
IF YOU NEED ME,
PLEASE, CALL ME.
I WILL.
I WILL CALL YOU
IF SOMETHING REAL HAPPENS.
OKAY.
AND YOU LOOK LIKE YOU'RE
IN PRETTY GOOD HANDS
WITH, UH, ANNIE OAKLEY
HERE ANYWAY.
(chuckles)
YOU WERE LEAVING.
YEAH, YEAH.
THANK YOU.
LOOK AT YOU,
ALL GROWN UP.
EW.
BYE.
YEAH, AND YOU'RE WELCOME,
BY THE WAY.
(scoffs)
OH, THANK YOU
FOR LOOKING OUT FOR ME.
(laughs)
OH, YEAH, DON'T WAIT UP.
DON'T BE SLOW.
ARE YOU GONNA TREAT ME
LIKE THIS ALL DAY?
HELL, ARE YOU GONNA
TREAT ME LIKE THIS
OUR WHOLE LIFE TOGETHER?
ARE YOU COMING IN?
YEAH.
WELL, SO NOW THAT YOU KNOW YOUR
STALKER'S NOT REALLY A STALKER,
ARE YOU GONNA FINALLY
LEAVE YOUR ROOM?
YEAH, I'M TOTALLY CURED.
(scoffs)
IT SO WORKS THAT WAY.
OH, WHEN DID THAT
GET THERE?
HELLO, I CALLED YOU
ABOUT THE VIDEO DROP BOX.
WAIT, WHEN DID YOU-
WHEN YOU WERE NEGOTIATING
WITH THE CAB DRIVER,
I CALLED AHEAD.
YOU DIDN'T HEAR ME
BECAUSE, WELL, HEARING ME'S
NOT ONE OF YOUR STRONG SUITS.
ANYWAY, UH, WE'RE HERE
ON A SCAVENGER HUNT
THAT I'M SURE THAT OUR R.A.
TOLD SOMEONE HERE TO PUT
SOMETHING IN A VIDEO DROP BOX.
SO IF YOU COULD
JUST OPEN SAID DROP BOX,
WE'LL BE OUT OF YOUR HAIR,
AND I'M SURE THAT SHE'LL BE
OUT OF YOUR HAIR EVEN SOONER,
'CAUSE SHE'S ALWAYS
FIVE PACES AHEAD OF ME.
YEP, THAT GUY
WAS JUST HERE.
WELL, SHOW US.
YEAH, APPARENTLY,
THIS IS A SCAVENGER HUNT.
YOU'RE SUPPOSED TO LOOK.
(Jenny)
I'M NOT OPENING IT.
HINT-IF HE WAS GONNA
BREAK UP WITH YOU IN A LETTER,
HE'D LEAVE IT
ON YOUR DOOR.
THAT'S WEIRD.
"FIND JENNY TRAYLOR."
(scoffs)
THIS HAD BETTER BE
THE RIGHT ONE,
'CAUSE IF I GO TO ANOTHER
INTERNET CAFé, I WILL SCREAM.
I WAS STARTING TO THINK
WE WERE NEVER GONNA FIND SOMEONE
REALLY NAMED ASMER-MER-MER...
(giggles)
YOU MUST BE
FROM THE SCAVENGER HUNT.
YES, WE ARE.
WAIT, THAT'S MINE!
WE-WE GOT HERE FIRST.
HEY, HOW MANY OF THESE CAFéS
HAVE YOU BEEN TO?
SIX.
AND HOW MANY ASMERETS
HAVE YOU TALKED TO?
ACTUALLY,
SHE IS THE FIRST. YOU?
SEVEN.
(laughs)
I HAVE OTHER CUSTOMERS.
OH.
IT'S TOO SMALL
FOR A DOOR.
I'M SO TIRED
OF TIM'S GAMES.
YEAH... (sighs)
UH, SINCE NO ONE WANTED TO BE
MY PARTNER FOR THE HUNT,
AND SINCE
YOU'VE BEEN STOOD UP,
YOU'RE AS BIG A LOSER
AS I AM.
I SAY WE SCREW 'EM ALL,
WIN THE TICKETS,
WIN THE HUNT,
GO TO THE CONCERT.
JACK WHITE COULD TURN ME.
(Paula) OF COURSE
SHE'LL BE HERE.
SHE'S ALWAYS IN HER ROOM.
HI.
OH, PLEASE,
TAKE YOUR TIME.
(thud)
OH, MY GOD.
OH, MY GOD,
IT'S A FINGER.
GOD.
WHO WOULD DO THAT?
DON'T-DON'T- DON'T TOUCH IT.
DON'T TOUCH IT.
OH!
"FOLLOW THE CLUES
AND GAVIN LIVES.
"FIND THE FINAL
DESTINATION
BEFORE GAVIN MEETS HIS."
OH, COME ON.
THIS IS NOT
A REAL FINGER.
IT KINDA LOOKS LIKE THE CADAVER
WE STUDIED LAST SUMMER.
OH, AND I ASSUME
THE WRITING IS BLOOD?
THIS IS PLASTIC.
I- IT'S A SHARPIE.
REAL BLOOD WOULD BLEED.
HEY, WHERE'S CAMILLE?
BONING SOMEBODY ELSE,
I GUESS.
THEN WHY ARE YOU HERE?
I'M WINNING
THOSE TICKETS,
AND WHEN CAMILLE GETS
EXCITED THAT I DID,
I'M GONNA TAKE
SOMEBODY ELSE.
TAKE ME. WE COULD
ALSO PISS OFF TIM.
HEY, I THOUGHT
WE WERE A TEAM HERE.
OH, COME ON. YOU'D MOW ME
DOWN TO TAKE CAMILLE.
I- I WOULDN'T. I WOULD NOT.
I- I WOULDN'T.
YOU CAN HAVE HER.
WHICH HER,
CAMILLE OR ANGELA?
I'LL BE DONE
IN A MINUTE.
FABULOUS.
GAVIN COULD BE
REALLY HURT RIGHT NOW.
I HATE TO SAY IT, BUT GAVIN'S
PROBABLY IN ON THIS, TOO.
IT IS NOT A JOKE. GAVIN WOULD
NOT CUT HIS OWN FINGER OFF.
IF IT EVEN IS A FINGER.
JENNY, IT LOOKS PRETTY...
(sniffs) FAKE TO ME.
NOW YOU WANT TO CALL THE COPS,
WE'LL CALL THE COPS.
I'M GONNA TAKE A PICTURE
OF THE FINGER AND ALL OF US.
COME ON. COME ON.
SO YOU REALLY
DON'T CARE ABOUT JENNY.
YOU JUST-YOU JUST
WANT TO WIN THE GAME.
(camera shutter clicks)
ACTUALLY, I DO CARE.
I DON'T WANT
TO SEE YOU GET INTO
YET ANOTHER ONE
OF YOUR "CRY WOLF" MOMENTS.
SERIOUSLY, I KNOW
YOU'VE BEEN THROUGH A LOT,
BUT YOU REALLY NEED TO GET
OVER THIS PARANOIA THING.
OH, MY GOD.
OKAY, SHE'S
KINDA RIGHT.
YOU DID THINK
LIEUTENANT FOX WAS A STALKER.
DOES ANYBODY THINK THAT MAYBE
GAVIN IS ACTUALLY IN TROUBLE?
AND THAT-THAT WHETHER
THIS FINGER IS REAL OR NOT,
THAT WE NEED
TO FIND HIM?
ALL RIGHT, LISTEN,
EITHER WAY,
TIM WAS
WAY OUT OF LINE.
(mumbles)
DON'T DELETE
THE PICTURE.
(cell phone rings)
TIM, IT-IT'S ROY.
PLEASE CALL ONE OF US BACK.
OH, MY GOD.
IT'S GAVIN'S RING.
STAY CALM.
LET'S FIND TIM.
OKAY,
GO, GO, GO, GO.
ALL RIGHT.
STICK IT IN.
I KNOW. OKAY.
TIMMY!
(scoffs)
OKAY.
COME ON. TIM!
WHAT?
HE'S NOT HERE.
YEAH, WELL, I DON'T KNOW
WHERE ELSE TO LOOK.
HEY, IT'S...
(AnGELa and Higginbotham) WHAT?
ARE YOU INSANE?
OH, COME ON.
THIS IS TIM
WE'RE TALKING ABOUT,
TOTAL DRAMA QUEEN
CINEMA GEEK.
WHAT THE HELL IS THIS?
LOOK AT THE TRIPOD LEG.
HE STAGED IT.
LOOK AT THE PICTURES.
THE GUY IN THE SWEATSHIRT'S
IN ON IT.
OH, HE IS SO OVER THE TOP.
I LOVE HIM.
(giggles)
WHAT DO WE DO?
WELL, OBVIOUSLY, HE WANTS ME
TO KEEP PLAYING THE GAME.
MEN AND THEIR GAMES. MM.
OKAY, TIM, I ADMIT IT.
YOU GOT ME.
(giggles)
(cell phones rings)
OH.
I'M GOING BACK TO CAMPUS.
WE NEED TO FIND TIM.
COME ON. YOU DON'T
REALLY THINK HE'S DEAD.
IF HE'S NOT,
THEN WHY HASN'T HE
SENT US HIS NEXT CLUE?
(cell phone rings)
HA! SEE?
"SAY OM WITH
'THE PRINCESS AND THE PEA.'"
"THE DRAMA BOOKS HOP."
"THE GATE"...
"OF HELL"...
"IS OPEN."
THE GATE OF HELL
IS OPEN.
NO, NOT "BOOKS HOP."
BOOK SHOP.
THE DRAMA BOOKSHOP.
IT'S WHERE TIM AND I
HAD OUR FIRST DATE.
GOD, HE IS SO OBVIOUS
AND SO ALIVE. ARE YOU COMING?
DOESN'T CAMILLE DO YOGA?
YEAH, AT A PLACE CALLED
THE OHM STUDIO.
AND YOU HAVEN'T TALKED TO HER
AT ALL SINCE YOU LEFT HER?
HELLO! WHO'S
COMING WITH ME?
YOU GO AHEAD.
BYE, LOSERS.
GATE OF HELL...
HELLGATE.
THERE'S A BRIDGE.
YOU CAN SEE IT
FROM THE UPPER EAST SIDE.
OKAY, I'M FROM THERE.
MY PARENTS HAVE A DOORMAN,
AND I WENT TO SPENCE. WHAT?
(cell phone rings)
DO YOU GUYS REALLY STILL THINK
THAT THIS IS JUST A GAME?
IF IT IS,
I'M GONNA WIN IT.
LOOK.
OH, GOD.
WELL, WE BETTER
FIND HIM.
(cell phone rings)
(sighs)
"CALL THE COPS,
AND HER BOYFRIEND DIES."
PRETTY CLEAR TO ME.
WHO SENT YOU
THAT TEXT?
UM, RED HOOK.
OKAY, PEOPLE,
TIM IS SOMEWHERE,
AND HE'S STILL BEING
DORK DUNGEON-MASTER.
I SAY WE KEEP PLAYING.
OKAY, BUT DEENA NEVER
SIGNED UP FOR THIS GAME.
IT'S TIM'S WAY
OF GETTING HER INVOLVED.
OKAY, OKAY.
UM, VINDIGO SAYS THAT
THERE IS A BAR CALLED HELLGATE.
IT'S IN ASTORIA.
1230th AVENUE.
SEE? IT'S A 12 THING.
(groans)
I LOATHE ASTORIA.
SO WHY DON'T YOU GUYS
GO TO THE BAR.
(groans)
AND JENNY AND I WILL
WALK AROUND THE BRIDGE.
ROY, WHERE IN ASTORIA
DID YOU SAY THAT BAR WAS?
PAULA!
WHETHER IT'S A GAME
OR SOMETHING ELSE,
WE HAVE TO WIN.
I'M NOT FUCKING AROUND.
COME ON, ROY.
YOU COMING?
HEY, IF THERE'S
SOMETHING UP WITH CAMILLE,
I WANT TO KNOW.
HEY, DUDE, PLEASE.
YOU NEVER HAD A CHANCE.
"HAD"?
OKAY, LISTEN.
CAMILLE MIGHT HAVE BEEN
A RAMPANT SLUT,
BUT SHE NEVER WOULD HAVE
IN HER WILDEST DREAMS
LOWERED HERSELF
TO GET IT ON WITH YOU.
"MIGHT HAVE BEEN."
WHAT? IS SHE, LIKE, DEAD?
SHE'S DEAD TO ME.
YOU WANT HER, YOU GOT HER.
I'M GOING BACK TO CAMPUS.
WELL, YOU'RE NOT GONNA
FIND TIM THERE.
WHY NOT?
IT'S GETTING LATE,
AND HE'S PROBABLY ALREADY
AT THE FINAL DESTINATION.
ARE YOU STILL
PLAYING THIS GAME?
HELL, YEAH.
YOU SHOULD, TOO.
WHY DON'T YOU
GO FIND ANGELA?
THERE'S SOMEONE
WHO'D GET IT ON WITH YOU.
CALL OR TEXT ME IF YOU
FIND OUT ANYTHING ON CAMILLE!
OOH, I THINK...
(door squeaks)
(grunts)
(cell phone beeps)
(groans)
OH.
UM, HELLO?
SOMEBODY?
OH, THEY'RE VINTAGE!
OKAY, I GOT 'EM IN CHINATOWN,
BUT THEY'RE ONE OF A KIND.
ANYONE?
OW.
IDIOT YOGAS.
"PRINCESS AND THE PEA."
(groans)
(grunting)
(screams)
(gasps)
(mumbling)
(screaming)
AAH!
(AnGELa and Camille moaning)
(grunts)
(gasping)
ANGELA.
(cell phone rings)
"THE PRIZE IS YOUR LIFE."
"THE DESTINATION...
IS THE CLUE."
(cell phone rings)
"FIND JENNY TRAYLOR,
OR SHE DIES."
(cell phone rings)
SHE'S DEAD. SH-SHE-
CAMILLE!
WHAT?
DEAD!
I JUST-
PLEASE, STOP.
MY FRIEND NEEDS HELP!
(cell phone rings)
JENNY.
JENNY TRAYLOR.
(Deena) COME ON, JENNY,
BE HONEST.
(Jenny) YOU'RE
A BROKEN RECORD.
YES, DEENA, I REALLY THINK
THAT GAVIN IS IN TROUBLE.
THE PICTURE WAS REAL.
HOW CAN YOU TRUST GAVIN?
I JUST GET HIM, OKAY?
OKAY, THERE'S
NO CLUE HERE.
LET'S JUST MEET UP
WITH PAULA AND ROY.
(playing "No More" by ism)
¶¶ I SAID NO MORE ¶¶
¶¶ NO MORE ¶¶
¶¶ I'M GONNA RISE UP, RISE UP ¶¶
¶¶ DON'T YOU SEE
IT AIN'T WORKIN'... ¶¶
WHAT WAS THAT NOISE?
WHAT NOISE?
THERE WAS A NOISE.
OKAY, I DON'T GET YOU.
YOU FREAK OUT
OVER EVERY NOISE,
AND YET YOU TRUST
SOME KID YOU JUST MET.
SHH!
(whispering) KEEP YOUR VOICE
DOWN. THERE'S SOMEONE.
(groans)
WELL, DO YOU
TRUST ME, JENNY?
¶¶¶¶¶¶
THANKS.
UH-HUH.
WHAT WAS THAT?
IT'S-I WAS
TEXTING CAMILLE.
WHY?
YOU HAVE TO ADMIT
THIS IS WEIRD.
THAT POSTER
WITH THE PICTURE OF CAMILLE
AND THE FINGER.
YEAH.
I'M STARTING TO THINK
GAVIN MIGHT REALLY BE
IN TROUBLE.
WOW.
COMPASSION BECOMES YOU.
I'M REALLY GLAD
THAT YOU'RE WORRIED ABOUT JENNY.
OH. SURE, THAT, TOO.
WAIT, WHAT?
OH, COME ON.
YOU HAVE TO ADMIT
THIS WOULD MAKE
A GREAT STORY FOR THE PAPER.
PRICELESS.
REALLY, PAULA.
THANKS.
I'M GOING
TO THE BATHROOM.
OKAY.
¶¶ IN THE MOONLIGHT
SOMETHING'S HIDING ¶¶
(whispering)
THERE'S SOMEBODY OVER THERE.
WHAT?
THERE'S SOMEBODY
OVER THERE.
OKAY, I'LL GO LOOK.
(toilet paper roll squeaking)
(cell phone rings)
"WHERE ARE YOU, TIM?"
(gasps)
(dog barking)
(screaming)
GET OUT OF HERE!
(chuckles)
(dog whimpers)
THAT WAS AWESOME.
OH, MY GOD.
I'LL GET IT.
ARE YOU OKAY?
YEAH.
HE WAS MORE SCARED OF YOU
THAN WE WERE OF HIM.
YEAH.
SPEAK FOR YOURSELF.
YOU KNOW, THIS IS SUPPOSED
TO BE A SAFE NEIGHBORHOOD.
YOU'RE WELCOME,
BY THE WAY.
WELL, YOU'RE RIGHT.
THANK YOU.
(Jenny) IF THERE IS
ONE THING I LEARNED-
JUST BECAUSE
YOU'RE PARANOID,
IT DOESN'T MEAN
THEY'RE NOT AFTER YOU.
UH...
YEAH.
(chuckles)
AND... YES.
YES?
(chuckles)
Y- Y-YES, I TRUST YOU.
MM.
JENNY! DEENA!
ROY'S GONE!
DID HE
FINALLY BREAK UP WITH YOU?
I DON'T KNOW.
H- HE WENT TO THE MEN'S ROOM.
I WENT TO CHECK ON HIM.
HE'S NOT THERE.
OKAY, THAT'S IT.
I'M CALLING LIEUTENANT FOX.
JENNY! OPEN THE...
NO!
LOOK, LOOK, LOOK,
SHE'S NOT THERE.
WHERE THE HELL
HAVE YOU BEEN?
LOOKING FOR THE SHITHEAD
WHO KILLED CAMILLE.
HOW DO I KNOW YOU'RE NOT
THE ONE DOING ALL THIS?
WHY WOULD I KILL HER?!
I'M GOING TO SEND
A TEXT MESSAGE TO RED HOOK.
WHY?
TO SEE IF YOUR CELL PHONE
GOES OFF.
AND WHILE YOU'RE WAITING,
JENNY TRAYLOR'S GONNA
GET HERSELF KILLED!
I HAVE TRIED CALLING JENNY
A THOUSAND TIMES OVER
FROM ANGELA'S PHONE.
LOOK, MY CELL PHONE
IS NOT GOING OFF.
D- DO YOU TRUST ME YET?
I HAVE ALL FIVE BARS.
OH.
OKAY. SO WHAT
DO WE DO NOW?
(sighs)
WE HAVE TO-WE HAVE TO FIND-
FIND THE FINAL DESTINATION.
DO YOU HAVE ANY IDEAS?
"THE-THE DESTINATION
IS THE CLUE."
WHAT THE HELL
DOES THAT MEAN?
FRICKIN' NEW YORK CITY!
YOU'D THINK YOU'D GET
SOME FRICKIN' SERVICE!
GOT IT.
GOT IT, GOT IT, GOT IT,
GOT IT, GOT IT. I GOT IT.
MOM? HI. HI.
N- N-NO, NO.
I'M FINE. I'M FINE.
I JUST-I-HELLO? HI.
I NEED, UM, I NEED
LIEUTENANT FOX'S PHONE NUMBER.
DON'T BUG ME.
I'M SCANNING.
IT'S NOT GONNA WORK.
I ALREADY TRIED MINE.
BUT YOU'RE SMARTER.
'CAUSE I SAW HIM TODAY.
YEAH, HE'S IN NEW YORK.
YEAH, 'CAUSE YOU SENT HIM
HERE TO CHECK UP ON ME.
I'M-I'M NOT MAD.
JUST CAN YOU-
CAN YOU PLEASE-
CAN YOU-CAN YOU
GIVE ME THE NUMBER?
OH, MY GOD.
I'M AN IDIOT.
BROOKLYN.
PLEASE TELL ME
THAT YOU'RE LYING.
THEY DIDN'T SEND HIM.
WHAT?
I KNEW HE WAS A PSYCHO,
BUT HOW...
WHOEVER IS DOING THIS
HAS SOME SICK FASCINATION
WITH HER.
OKAY, BUT HOW WOULD HE KNOW
WHERE YOU ARE?
'CAUSE MY PARENTS
GOT ME...
(groans) A GPS PHONE
WHEN ELLEN WAS KILLED.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
I'M PLAYING THEIR GAME.
(camera shutter clicks)
SOMEBODY
OBVIOUSLY WANTS ME TO.
(cell phones ring)
"DON'T TAKE THE SUBWAY."
"DON'T TAKE A BUS."
"SO PICK UP YOUR CAR
AND COME TO US."
(Jenny)
I FOUND THE CLUE.
(groans)
I LOATHE BROOKLYN.
(cell phone rings)
MOM?
HELLO?
WHAT'S WRONG?
OKAY, CAN YOU HEAR ME?
WHERE-WHERE ARE YOU?
LISTEN TO ME,
ANGELA IS DEAD.
CAMILLE, TOO.
AND... HELLO?
WHAT'S WRONG?
IT'S-IT'S HIGGINBOTHAM.
CAMILLE'S DEAD...
AND ANGELA.
OKAY, ARE YOU SURE
HE'S NOT PART OF THE JOKE?
THERE IS NO JOKE!
THEN WHY ARE WE
HEADING INTO A TRAP?
I- I NEED
TO FIND GAVIN.
HOW DO YOU KNOW HE'S NOT
BEHIND THIS WHOLE THING?
HE'S NOT!
HOW DO YOU KNOW THAT?
BECAUSE I DO.
OKAY, WELL, WE'RE HERE.
WHAT DO YOU WANT TO DO?
UM, I'M GONNA
CALL THE COPS,
AND I WANT TO TELL THEM
WHERE WE ARE,
AND I WANT
TO HAVE SERVICE.
DOES ANYBODY
HAVE SERVICE?
UM, NOPE.
MNH-MNH.
I'LL GO CHECK OUTSIDE.
D- D-DON'T-DON'T-
DON'T GO OUT THERE.
OH, IT'S FINE.
NOTHIN'.
(car door thuds)
(thud)
WHAT WAS THAT NOISE?
I JUST SHUT THE DOOR.
(thud)
OKAY, NOW I HEAR IT.
(groans) WHAT?
DID I HIT SOMETHING?
LET'S GET OUT OF HERE.
I'M GONNA
GO CHECK IT OUT.
DON'T.
COME ON!
TWO PEOPLE ARE DEAD.
YEAH. HOW DID WE
FIND THAT OUT?
FROM A PRETTY SHADY SOURCE.
IT'S NOTHING.
(gasps)
(sobs)
WELL?
STAY IN THE CAR.
OH, GOD.
(crying) YOU DON'T WANT
TO SEE THIS.
(grunting)
WHAT IS IT?
START THE CAR!
WHERE ARE THE KEYS?
(grunts)
WHERE ARE THE KEYS?!
I DON'T HAVE THE KEYS!
(grunting)
WHERE ARE THEY?
DEENA, YOU HAVE THE KEYS!
YOU WANT TO KILL ME?
DO SOMETHING!
(grunting)
(grunts) FUCKER!
DEENA!
(gasping)
OH, MY...
NO.
(gasps)
(both scream)
AAH!
OH, MY GOD! OH, MY GOD!
(both screaming)
GET OFF HER!
(grunts)
COME ON!
NO!
(Jenny)... TWO.
THREE. FOUR.
FIVE. SIX. SEVEN.
EIGHT. NINE.
TEN.
ELEVEN.
THERE'S NO SIGNAL.
IT'S WORSE IN HERE!
WE GOTTA GET OUT OF HERE.
JENNY. JENNY. JENNY.
WE GOTTA
GET OUT OF HERE, OKAY?
SO JUST-JUST
PULL YOURSELF TOGETHER.
FIND A DOOR, UM...
JENNY!
OKAY. OKAY.
YOU JUST STAY HERE.
AND I'M GONNA
FIGURE THIS OUT.
THERE'S A CLUE, P-PAULA.
PAULA?
(gasps) COME-GET-
THERE'S SOMEBODY BEHIND YOU.
THERE'S-THERE'S
SOMEBODY BEHIND YOU!
LOOK! THERE'S SOMEBODY
RIGHT BEHIND YOU!
SOMEBODY HELP!
COME BACK DOWN HERE!
PAULA!
(screaming)
GET OFF OF HER!
JENNY! (screaming)
OH, MY GOD! OH, MY GOD!
(Lieutenant Fox) JENNY?
JENNY, ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
(gasps)
IT'S LIEUTENANT FOX.
(Gavin)
JENNY? ARE YOU THERE?
GAVIN.
LET ME KNOW
WHERE YOU ARE, PLEASE.
JENNY, HELP ME.
(coughs)
GAVIN!
I JUST WANT TO KNOW
YOU'RE ALL RIGHT.
THAT'S ALL
I CARE ABOUT, OKAY?
JENNY?
GAVIN!
JENNY. (coughs)
HEY.
(whimpers)
I DIDN'T THINK
YOU WOULD MAKE IT.
(whispers)
IT'S OKAY. I'M HERE.
JENNY.
(normal voice)
COME ON. HURRY UP.
OKAY.
THIS WAY.
(AnGELa) NOW WAS THE KID
REALLY, REALLY CUTE?
(bartender)
A REGULAR BRAD PITT.
YOU KNOW, I ALWAYS PICTURED TIM
AS MORE OF AN ADAM BRODY TYPE.
(scoffs) THIS IS SO TIM.
HIT IT.
(Higginbotham) MM-HMM.
(clears throat)
¶¶ OH, AN INTERNET CAFE ¶¶
¶¶ IS THE NEXT PLACE
YOU'VE GOTTA SEEK ¶¶
¶¶ THERE'S A GIRL
BEHIND THE COUNTER THERE ¶¶
¶¶ WHOSE NAME
IS QUITE UNIQUE ¶¶
¶¶ FIND ASMERET ¶¶
¶¶ IT MIGHT NOT BE EASY ¶¶
¶¶ BUT ASMERET HAS
A CLUE FOR YOU ¶¶
¶¶ SHE'LL HAND YOU A CD ¶¶
¶¶ OH, GO ANGELA,
AND HIGGINBOTHAM, TOO ¶¶
¶¶ GET YOUR ASSES
OFF THAT STAGE ¶¶
¶¶ AND FIND YOURSELVES
ANOTHER CLUE ¶¶
(screams)
(moaning)
I THOUGHT
YOU SAID PIANO BAR.
(Chappy) TIM, SHOW YOUR FACE,
YOU FREAK.
(Higginbotham) TIM!
TIM!
(groaning)
WHERE ARE YOU,
YOU ASSHOLE?
TIM?
(gasping)
JENNY, ARE YOU OKAY?
(voices speaking indistinctly)
HE SAID,
"IT WAS LIKE A MOVIE."
(woman groaning)
OH, MY GOD.
WE'RE ALL A PART OF IT.
HE HAD CAMERAS
SET UP EVERYWHERE.
(voices speaking indistinctly)
OKAY, WELL, HE'S
STILL OUT THERE, SO...
TIM?
NO. N-NO, NO, NOT TIM.
LIEUTENANT FOX.
WHO?
N- N-N-NO, NO, NO.
TIM'S THE TWISTED LITTLE FUCK
WHO D-
TIM? NO...
OKAY, WELL, WE NEED
TO GET TO A HOSPITAL.
I'M FINE.
NO, YOU'RE NOT.
THIS IS REALLY BAD.
IT WAS WORTH IT.
WHAT?
WHAT DO YOU-
WHAT DO-WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
YOU-YOU CAME
AND FOUND ME.
ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
JENNY, WHAT'S WRONG?
D- DID YOU DO THIS?
DON'T LOOK SAD.
TELL ME
YOU DID NOT DO THIS.
(Chappy) PSYCHO!
NO! DON'T HURT HIM!
GO GET HELP!
(grunting)
GAVIN!
(voices speaking indistinctly)
OH, MY GOD, GAVIN.
AFTER WHAT YOU AND I
WENT THROUGH...
NOBODY CARED.
BUT THEY
DIDN'T HAVE TO DIE.
THEY WOULD'VE
JUST LIVED THEIR LIVES
LIKE NOTHING BAD
EVER HAPPENED TO ANYBODY.
HAVE ANY OF THEM-
ANY OF THEM
EVER LOST ANYONE?
DO THEY KNOW WHAT YOU AND I
HAVE TO LIVE WITH EVERY DAY?
GAVIN.
NO, IT'S OKAY.
IT'S OKAY.
SHH. I KNEW
YOU'D UNDERSTAND.
IT'S ALL RIGHT.
THAT'S WHY I LOVE YOU.
I KNEW WHEN I MET YOU.
ARE YOU GONNA KILL ME?
NO.
(chuckling) GOD, NO.
I DID THIS
FOR US TO SURVIVE TOGETHER.
WHAT IF I DON'T WANT
TO BE WITH YOU?
YOU DON'T MEAN THAT.
WE'RE SOUL MATES.
JENNY!
(gasps)
BACK AWAY
FROM HIM, JENNY.
BACK AWAY FROM HIM.
NO.
(gasps) NO!
YOU'RE SAFE NOW.
NO, I'M NOT.
¶¶¶¶¶¶
(playing "Spin" by NLX)
¶¶ SPIN ¶¶
¶¶ WON'T YOU SPIN
HERE WITH ME? ¶¶
¶¶ I REGRET TO INFORM YOU ¶¶
¶¶ I'M GOING TO ADORE YOU ¶¶
¶¶ YEAH, SPIN ¶¶
¶¶ AND RELEASE ¶¶
¶¶ JUST SAY PLEASE ¶¶
¶¶ I'LL GIVE YOU THE POWER ¶¶
¶¶ JUST ORPHAN AN HOUR ¶¶
¶¶ YEAH, SPIN ¶¶
¶¶ YOU'RE ¶¶
¶¶ YOU'RE NOT ALONE ¶¶
¶¶ AND IT'S KILLIN' ME
THAT I'M THE ONLY ONE THERE ¶¶
¶¶ IT'S KILLIN' ME THAT I KNOW
NONE OF YOUR FRIENDS ¶¶
¶¶ AND THEY NEVER SAY
ANYTHING GOOD ¶¶
¶¶ 'BOUT YOUR GIRL ¶¶
¶¶ AND YOU RISK ¶¶
¶¶ WOULD YOU RISK ¶¶
¶¶ IT FOR BLISS? ¶¶
¶¶ WE'LL BE DAY DRUNKS
BY NOON ¶¶
¶¶ WE'LL MEET AT THE SALOON ¶¶
¶¶ AND WE'LL RISK ¶¶
¶¶ YOU'RE ¶¶
¶¶ YOU'RE NOT ALONE ¶¶
¶¶ AND IT'S KILLIN' ME
THAT I'M THE ONLY ONE THERE ¶¶
¶¶ IT'S KILLIN' ME THAT I KNOW
NONE OF YOUR FRIENDS ¶¶
¶¶ AND THEY NEVER SAY
ANYTHING GOOD ¶¶
¶¶ 'BOUT YOUR GIRL ¶¶
(playing "Independence Day"
by Bryan Fenkart)
¶¶ SORRY I'M STARING ¶¶
¶¶ I'M JUST TRYING TO SEE ¶¶
¶¶ WHAT EVERYONE SAYS ¶¶
¶¶ IS UNDER ME ¶¶
¶¶ CAUGHT YOU BLUFFING ¶¶
¶¶ YOU WERE LYING
THROUGH YOUR TEETH ¶¶
¶¶ YOU SAID
THAT THIS PLACE ¶¶
¶¶ WOULD SET ME FREE ¶¶
¶¶ BUT IT'S KILLIN' ME ¶¶
¶¶ I'M NOT TRYIN'
TO BREAK THIS WHEEL ¶¶
¶¶ NEVER DID, NEVER WILL ¶¶
¶¶ I'M JUST TRYIN'
TO LAY STILL ¶¶
¶¶ AND IT'S THE 4th OF JULY ¶¶
¶¶ IT'S THE 4th OF JULY ¶¶
¶¶ BUT I DON'T FEEL
FREE AT ALL ¶¶
¶¶ AT ALL ¶¶
¶¶ OOH, OOH ¶¶
¶¶ OOH ¶¶