PRIME SUSPECT
Episode 4 - Part 2
Inner Circles
Is that the one we ordered?
Oh, good, yes, thank you very much.
Darling?
- Paul.
- James.
- Can I offer you a glass of this?
- Not just at the moment, thanks.
Not again!
Mum...
- Mum, come on!
- No!
Please!
I need to go to the toilet.
I have to go now, Mum.
Can´t wait to get away, can you?
I´ve got an appointment.
I´ll sort things out, I promise.
You won´t.
Oh, go, go on, go!
I don´t want you here, anyway.
Denis will be along in a minute.
Mother...
I am Denis.
- The police are on their way.
- There are two of them. I heard voices.
Let´s go roud the back. Come on.
Right? These bastards aren´t going anywhere.
Alan, you go roud the front.
Norman, you stay here.
Shit!
- Micky...
- Shut up!
Alan! He´s here!
Alan, he´s coming out.
Bastards...
Get your....
hands off me!
- Norman, check inside the house.
- Bastards!
- I´ll kill you!
- Listen, you!
We don´t want your type aroud here.
Understand?
Just so you remember...
I´d put that away if I was you.
Denis?
Are you there, Denis?
Oh, my God...
Everybody knows who´s doing it.
It´s those kids from the bloody estate.
- Still no word from Raymond?
- Zilch.
Typical.
- What are we gona do, then?
- Not a lot we can do.
Phone it in, I suppose.
What´s the betting we get lumbered
with some berk from AMIP?
Oh, come on, Mike.
I´m a copper, not a bloody accountant.
Look, I forecast the budget.
Don´t expect me to sell the bloody thing.
Yeah, all right.
All right, 9:00am tomorrow morning.
Thank you and good night.
- Hello?
- Yeah, Tennison.
Oh, yes, ma´am.
Hadley Green have called for help.
- There´s been a murder.
- Where?
- 17 Moss Bank Drive
- Mmm-hmm.
That´s EN4.
- Right.
- Tearing you away from your desk?
Believe me, it will be a pleasure.
- See you.
- Good night, ma´am.
Thank you.
- Where´s Forensic?
- He´s on his way, ma´am.
- What, SO3?
- He was out.
He´s picking his cameras
and his stuff up now.
I see.
What do you think of that scarf?
Fashion victim?
I´m a member of the Neighbourhood Watch.
- Denis Carradine lived here alone?
- Yeah.
His mum went into a nursing home
about a year ago.
Carradine was the manager
at the Hutingon Coutry Club.
- How did you know that?
- The neighbours.
Very helpful. Concerned about the state
of his garden. That sort of area.
- Who´s your DCI?
- Peter Raymond.
- Do you know him, ma´am?
- Yes, we´re acquainted.
All right, get the male
suspect´s ID circulated.
Keep this area completely sealed off
till Forensic gets here. If ever!
Oh, Detective.
Better get the mother informed.
Send someone over. Not a complete plank.
- I´ll do it myself.
- See you back at the nick.
Where is the nick?
Sergeant?
Why wasn´t I told she could be uderage?
Listen, if she doesn´t want to talk,
how are you or I supposed to know?
What´s that supposed to mean?
All I´m saying is,
she may or may not be uderage,
therefore we may not need a parent or...
I want the duty social worker down
here immediately, please.
You do have an incident room available?
Good, I want it up and runing
by 9:00 tomorrow morning.
Get a hold of these two officers from AMIP.
That´s tonight, Sergeant.
Denis is...
Denis is not coming back, Olive.
I... I don´t uderstand.
Why should anyone want to do that
to my Denis?
- They were trying to rob him, Olive.
- He´s dead?!
Yeah.
Yeah, I´m afraid he is.
They didn´t hurt him, did they?
It´s good to have you with us, Richard.
- How are the twins?
- Certifiable.
Nothing´s changed, then.
Good morning.
Richard, this is DS Booth, DC Bakari.
- Hiya.
- All right.
- You know Toby from AMIP.
- Yeah.
Find it all right, Rich?
Yeah, with the aid of a Sherpa.
Right, where´s DS Cromwell?
I thought he was supposed to be here.
She is. Morning, ma´am.
DS Christine Cromwell.
You´re late.
Someone took my parking place.
Probably me.
Looking forward to working
with you, Christine.
- Optimist, are you?
- Try my best.
Right...
Denis Arthur Carradine.
Quiet, respectable,
all the middle-class values.
Approximate time of death,
between 8:00 and 9:15pm.
He was strug up with
a piece of electrical flex.
Now, we have two suspects,
one in custody, Sheila Bower.
She´s not talking. We are treating it
as a drug-related burglary.
However, the way he was strug up
and his clothes
suggest some sort of sexual dimensión.
- What, with that filth?
- No, that´s not what I´m suggesting.
Hang on a minute,
you´re saying he did it himself.
All I´m saying is that the scarf
and the clothes suggest...
- It´s a possibility.
- Oh, come on.
The girl was as high as a kite.
They had the poor bastard strung up.
- They could´ve done anything to him.
- Right!
Let´s not jump to conclusions
till we get Pathology.
Our first priority is to pick up the youth.
Uniform is at the Larchmont Estate.
The description is vague at best,
so what can you do? Check with neighbours.
Also, let´s build up a profile
of Denis Carradine.
Check with his workmates,
friends at the club. What is it?
- The Hutington Coutry Club.
- Right, the Hutington Coutry Club.
- Did you get anything from the mother?
- Not a lot
The woman who runs the nursing home
said he´d been made redundant.
He was behind with his mother´s fees.
Check into that. Come on! Come on!
Let´s get going.
I... understood DCI Raymond
would be runing the investigation.
Not from me, you didn´t.
Oh, lan. Lan. Larchmont Estate.
Tell Uniform it´s door-to-door enquiries,
not mob-handed, OK?
- Soflly, Soflly?
- Not The A Team.
Sheila Carol Bower.
Born 25/10/77, Highbury, London.
Catalogue of juvenile offences
In care since ´89.
But you listen to me , we´re not talking
about petty thieving here.
Forget about coning some old fart
on a magistrates bench. This is murder!
That means prison. For life.
Not probation on some nice
little holiday camp somewhere.
We never done him.
What? You were out collecting
for the elderly?
We never even touched him.
So who pulled his pants down?
You enjoy that, Sheila?
Yeah, of course you did.
Old man like that.
Make him squirm.
Have some fun.
- Micky.
- Yes?
- Ask Micky.
- Who´s Micky?
Sheila...
8:42, DCI Raymond entering interview room.
This her, is it, Jane?
- Sheila...
- We never did him, all right?!
Liar.
- It´s the truth.
- The truth?
You wouldn´t know
the truth if you fell on it.
Bang her up.
DC Raymond,
could I have a word with you for a minute?
8:43, Superintendent Tennison
and DCI Raymond leaving interview room.
Another piece of shit from the Larchmont.
They´re scum, the lot of them.
Where were you last night?
My pager was knackered.
- I just handed it in.
- Well...
Well, if it was knackered,
why didn´t you call?
Because I didn´t know it was knackered
until this morning.
Jane, you came here last night
and did us a favour.
Thank you very much. But I´m back
on the case so we needn´t detain you, alright..
You´re understaffed.
You asked for assistance.
I didn´t ask for anything.
This is a straightforward case.
- Oh, I´m not of that opinion.
- Bullshit!
I´m also not of the opinion that
this nick can handle this investigation.
Until I am, DCI Raymond,
I shall be handling things.
And in future,
when I am interviewing a suspect,
you do not interrupt.
Soup spoons on the right.
Right.
Outside in.
Do them again.
Can I help you?
I take it you are members.
Police, sir. You in charge here?
I´ll get Mr Greenlees.
Prat...
Morning. Lords and masters
keeping you at it, are they?
Did you see much of Mr Carradine?
I thought you weren´t going to...
p- press charges.
- How do you mean?
- Isn´t that what you´re here for?
Hamish!
You can wait in Mr Greenlees´ office.
They held him on the chair,
then hauled him up and tied him off.
The face of the door is scored and you can see
the upper length of this flex is damaged.
It picked up traces of the paint.
I think we´ll find they match.
So you´re ruling out autostrangulation?
For his own sexual gratification?
No, no semen stains.
- Pathology will tell us definitely.
- Can I get down now?
I thought you liked hanging around, Rich.
Yeah, she´s got it written all over her.
No life but the job.
Sounds familiar.
Mind you, nice legs for a superintendent.
Still... No job for a woman, is it?
Originality is not your strong point, is it?
Oh, hello. Carradine. Carradine.
- Oh...
- Here, leave it out.
He´s dead. He´s not gona complain, is he?
Good morning. How can I help you, officers?
DS Cromwell. DC Bakari, sir.
James Greenlees, managing director.
We´re all obviously totally shocked
and angered by the news.
I understand you´ve already
apprehended the culprits.
- Who told you that?
- It´s close-knit commuity.
Bad news travels fast.
I also have friends in the force.
I understand these two creatures
were found in the house with Denis´s body
and that they´d... defiled it?
I´m afraid I can´t comment on that, sir.
We´re merely gathering background
information on Mr Carradine.
Um...
How well did you know him?
Oh, Denis was liked by everybody.
- He was a fine man.
- He wasn´t married, was he?
Did he have any women friends?
What are you suggesting?
We´re just trying to build up
a profile sir.
- Mr Carradine retired?
- Oh, quite recently.
His mother was in a nursing home.
He´d been under stress.
- He hadn´t been made redundant?
- On the contrary.
He was a great loss. A great loss.
Oh. We understood he was having difficulties
paying his mother´s nursing bills.
Did he have any financial difficulties
you were aware of?
No. But then one wouldn´t, of course,
encourage that kind of familiarity.
We´d heard there´d been
some sort of problem with his work.
Something about some charges being dropped.
We had a problem with our VAT return,
Constable.
Can I ask you on whose authority
you are making these enquiries?
- I´m sure DCI Raymond...
DCI Raymond isn´t in charge of the case, Sir.
- Well, who is?
- Superintendent Tennison sir
She´s been seconded in.
- Right, any prints?
- There´s prints all over the shop.
We´ll run them through the computer,
but it´ll take time.
Oh... Did you get this?
Do it, would you? Anything else?
Well, it´s probably nothing,
but we didn´t get any off the flex.
Must´ve wiped them.
Hmm, money problems?
Didn´t leave him much, did they?
What they can´t steal, they smash.
Christ, that´s sad.
- What´s that?
- His favourite band was Status Quo.
- Who´s that?
- Guv.
I think I´ve got
a more detailed description.
So, have you got that, lan?
Long hair, an earring
Scar on his arm.
It´s not a lot to go on, Guv.
Yeah, right. Right, I´ll tell them
to take it easy. See you later.
We´re making enquiries about somebody
we believe to be in this area.
- I don´t live here?
- What´s going on? Polly?
Dope?
Yeah?
He´s up above. Get up the stairs.
I´ll stay this end, cut him off.
Hold it! Stop! Police!
Oi! Get somebody down below!
Block off all the stairwells!
Don´t let him get down!
Shit! We´re gona lose him.
There´s too many exits.
Oi, stop!
- Stay back!
- Just take it easy!
Come here!
Come on, don´t just stand there!
You asked for house-to-house enquired
and that´s what you got.
I didn´t want them to go in mob-handed.
The Larchmont, in case you hadn´t realised,
is a hostile environment.
I´m not sending my officers in
without adequate protection.
You asked for Michael Thomas
and you´ve got him.
In a coma, thank you very much.
Whatever happened to community policing?
So where does that leave us
with these kids?
One half-dead,
the other scared shitless.
You´re breaking my heart!
They didn´t need to be in there!
All right, all right!
What else have we got?
We have his correspondence.
Looks like he remortgaged
his mother´s house.
I thought the old lady owned it.
More to the point, where´s the money gone?
180,000 quid. That´s a lot of money.
Yeah, and he certainly wasn´t using it
to pay off his debt.
He had final demands all over the shop.
Check his bank statements,
talk to his solicitor,
find out exactly when Denis took possessión
of his mother´s house.
A visitor, ma´am.
Superintendent´s Office.
A Mr Greenlees.
Of course, feel free to say anything
you think necessary...
Ah, Superintendent. Mr Greenlees.
How do you do, Mr Greenlees?
I´m Chairman
of the Police Consultative Committee.
Well, I´ll leave you to it.
Nice to see you, Bob. Peter.
Well, what can I do for you, Mr Greenlees?
Well, you may not be aware, Superintendent,
but there´s a lot of fear in this community.
Some would say justifiably so.
People here feel police are fighting
a losing battle against crime.
Public confidence is very low.
Well, we do our best.
Do you?
This morning, Superintendent,
two of your officers,
DS Cromwell and a coloured chap,
came to see me in my office.
I found them rifling through
a pile of the club´s private correspondence.
Really? Did you confront the officers?
I didn´t.
To be honest, I couldn´t believe
what was happening.
It´s not the such of behaviour you expect
from police officers.
Quite. I appreciate that.
Well, I assure you, I´ll look into the matter
and speak to the officers.
I do apologise.
Fine. We´ll say no more about it, then.
We all want you to apprehend the murderers,
Superintendent, but...
we are not the criminals.
I see no reason
why we should be treated as such.
Quite.
I wasn´t rifling his office.
- I just picked it up.
- So you don´t deny it, then?
It wasn´t his property.
It was addressed to Carradine.
Do you really think
he´d have given it to us?
- You didn´t give him a chance, did you ?
- He´s the Chairman of the PCC.
- That doesn´t make him God.
- Or make him a criminal either.
are you listen to me, you may behave like this
with DCI Raymond but you do not with me.
- Do you uderstand?
- Yes, Guv.
Lucky he didn´t make a complaint.
Go on, out, the pair of you.
If you´re looking for any favours,
you´re looking in the wrong place.
Understand?
One more, you´re out.
Basically, Denis was a very kind man.
He had his problems. But then we all do.
Problems?
Well, he was 46 years old
and still living with his mother.
I think underneath
he was quite a lonely person.
We were actually at school together.
My father was his parents´ solicitor.
It seemed like a natural progressión
that I should take over.
- It´s very sad.
- It is.
Well, thanks for your help, Mrs Henry.
- I won´t keep you any Ionger.
- My pleasure. Let me show you out.
Polly. What are you doing?
Borrowing a fiver. You were busy, Mummy.
I´m not supposed to disturb you
when you´re busy, remember?
- Children. Who´d have them?
- Not me.
- Bye-bye.
Yes, well, will you make sure
the magistrate understands
we need Sheila Bower in our custody.
Thank you, Constable.
Christ, whose side are they on?
Definitely not ours.
I get the distinct impressión
that we´re the bad guys.
Richard.
Do you fancy a drink?
I´ve got to re-tile the bathroom.
Guv, are you all right?
All right? What do you mean?
Of course I´m all right.
- See you tomorrow.
- Yeah, see you tomorrow.
Micky Thomas, ma´am. He´s dead.
- Thank you, Sergeant.
- Saves us the expense of a trial.
Oh, shit!
Yes?
- A whiskey and soda, please.
- Ice?
No.
I hear young Micky´s turned terminal.
Looks like there´ll be an inquiry.
I´ll manage. No thanks to wallies like you.
You won´t.
A word of advice.
Don´t think you can come down here
and teach us how to do our jobs.
I´m gona have to go, Pete. Bye.
- It´s not what you think.
- How´s your wife, by the way?
She´s fine. Still getting it regularly.
Which you´re obviously not.
Large Scotch, Scotch and soda
and a gin and tonic.
Yes, all right, I´m coming.
Large Scotch, Scotch and soda
and a gin and tonic.
There is a queue, you know.
Dad, please. People are complaining.
Who? I own 30% of this club.
I greatly resent being told how to behave
by my son in my own club.
- Now, I´ll have my drinks, please.
- Dad!
P- Please!
PauI´s under enormous stress.
You know, with this inquiry business.
You should stop him drinking.
- I mean, you are his wife.
- What difference does that make?
I tell you, I´ve had four months of hell
since he was suspended.
Our sex life is practically nonexistent.
Some nights,
he doesn´t even bother to come home.
Come on, Hamish. Get it right.
For Pete´s sake.
No, no. Your money is no good around here,
Paul. These are on me.
Do the honours, Hamish.
The boys in blue taking a night off,
are they, Pete?
I´m sure that would make
Denis Carradine very happy.
- Oh, hello...
- This is Dr Patrick Schofield.
Could you please leave a message
after the tone?
Hello, Dr Patrick Schofield.
This is...
Superintendent Jane Tennison calling.
Um...
I just want...
I was going to leave a message that...
Er... I´ll call you back.
Bye.
You idiot.
I hope he´s not driving tonight.
- We´ll get a cab.
- Very wise.
- Good-Iooking man.
- He´s a wanker.
Paul, will you stop using such language?
- I can´t bear it.
- Oh, dear! You can´t bear it?
How infra-dig of me!
If you´ll excuse me, Maria.
Sorry.
- I´m sorry.
- Don´t apologise to me. I´m not your wife.
Do yourself a favour, Paul.
Stop drinking before you really blow it.
- Now, listen.
- I´m sorry.
It´s just that Denis being
murdered like that...
Paul, listen. I´ve got to talk to you.
Er... Lyne gone?
She had a headache. Everyone´s upset
about what happened to poor Denis.
I know, I know, it´s beyond belief.
Peter Raymond tells me one of the thugs
jumped off a balcony at the Larchmont,
trying to escape.
- Did they catch him?
- Well, he died, ufortuately.
I suppose that´s some sort of justice.
There are two distinct lines
of bruises on the neck.
One upper, one lower.
Note the particlary hemorraging
flowering up from the lower contusions
to cover the neck and face.
This is absolutely consistent
with death by strangulation.
The pressure of blood
in the vessels above the ligature
is massively increased and they burst.
However, in this case, the flex was found
around the upper area of bruising.
There should be no haemorrhaging below it.
Any significance
to the scarf tied around the flex?
Stops the skin burning.
It´s not ucommon in autostrangulation.
The person wants the sexual stimulation
of the hypoxic state,
but he also wants to control the pain.
I thought you said
this wasn´t self-inflicted.
It wasn´t.
Whoever did this was trying
to make it look as though it was.
Scratches and abrasions
to the rear of the neck
and bruising to the shins.
Looks as if he was garrotted from behind.
So the assailant is likely
to have been a man?
That´s a very sexist assumption,
Superintendent.
Well, I´m so sorry.
86.7%  likely to have been a man.
Hmm.
Ah, Jane, fancy a spot of breakfast?
- Do I have a choice?
- No.
- Well, I hope you´re paying, Mike.
- I am.
So, to what do I owe this honour?
Michael Thomas... You realise
there is going to have to be an inquiry.
Good. Superintendent Mallory
and his mates deserve all they get.
- You were heading the investigation, Jane.
- That wasn´t down to me.
- That was down to the local plod.
- Not what I hear from DCI Raymond.
DCI Raymond´s an arsehole.
Been transferred out
of every nick he´s been in.
Hold on. Your opinion of him
is totally irrelevant.
He is the local DCI
and you´ve overstayed your welcome.
Now, you´ve nicked the culprits,
so let him get on with it.
I´m very sorry to tell you this, Mike,
but Micky Thomas
did not kill Denis Carradine.
- What do you mean?
- Look
He wasn´t tortured.
He was not sexually abused.
- Can I help you?
- I´ll have the full breakfast, please.
And for me, please.
Whoever did this strangled him,
then made it look like a sex game. Why?
Plus he´s remortgaged
his mother´s house for 180 grand
and he can´t pay his bills.
Where´s that money gone? Doesn´t add up.
All right... All right,
but you´ve got two days, Jane.
- And I want a favour in return.
- What?
The Police Consultative Committee
meet tonight.
I told Mr Greenlees
you would be their guest.
Greenlees? Has he spoken to you?
Someone seems to have got up his nose.
So keep him sweet, all right?
Politics, Jane.
It´s what this job´s all about.
Use your social skills.
If you´ve got any.
- I know there´s gona be an inquiry.
- You´re absolutely right there will.
Thomas died whilst you were arresting him.
So get your story straight.
- The van just came out of nowhere.
- Write it down.
Good morning.
Oh, contrary to rumour,
I am still on the case,
so let´s go on with it.
Get off the phone, Christine.
The pathologist has confirmed murder.
He sets the time of death
at approximately 8pm.
now, can we place Sheila Bower
at the scene of the crime at that time?
A woman was seen at the house
earlier that day. Well-dressed, 40ish.
So, no, we can´t.
And Micky Thomas does not have
a scar on his arm or an earring.
So, if our witness is to be believed,
it´s not him either.
I don´t buy it.
Thomas´s prints were all over the place.
- Yeah, but not on the flex.
- He probably wiped it.
And left the rest?
No, my guess is they only just got there.
The pathologist has said he was
strangled first and strung up after,
to make it look like some sex game.
Can you imagine a pair of kids doing that?
Might´ve bashed his head in,
but not that, that´s too calculated.
Brilliant. So where does that leave us?
Looking for the real killer, lan.
Not just easy targets.
Novel idea, isn´t it?
Micky Thomas is dead, Sheila.
I´m sorry.
You bastards! You bloody bastards!
You bastards!
You bastards! You bastards!
- Put her in the chair. All right.
- You bastards...
She´s now sitting in the chair.
Let her go. Let her go.
You couldn´t get him one way
so you got him another.
It was an accident, Sheila,
and that´s the truth.
You would say that.
And those bastards didn´t do this to my leg,
did they?
- Do you want to make a complaint?
- So you can say I fell over a wall?
Forget it, you ain´t stitching me up.
I didn´t see nothing and
I didn´t do anything!
What you looking at?
Squatting with Micky, were you, Sheila?
Samuel Johston House?
Micky claiming the housing, was he?
Yeah, up to your neck in shit and syringes.
And hawking your dole cards come Fridays.
- Know it, do you?
- I grew up there!
So stop pissing about
with all this stitch-me-up bullshit.
You were there. Micky was there.
His prints were all over the shop.
Bollocks!
You don´t get it, do you?
You think these bastards
are stitching you up,
all the time you´re doing it for them!
They want you to be guilty, Sheila.
They all do, everyone.
You´re just another piece of shit
from the Larchmont.
And they´re gona flush you away.
Where were you 8pm Sunday night?
Doing a house in Turner St.
Micky got in through the kitchen
but an alarm went off, so we legged it.
That´s why we tried the other place.
We were speeding.
We didn´t even know he was there.
You knew what you were
talking about in there.
That´s always an advantage.
Turner Close.
Uniform confirmed a break-in
at 8:10 on Sunday night.
The alarm was triggered.
I knew it.
Raymond didn´t.
Look, I slept with him, ma´am,
but I´m not in his pocket.
So, do you really believe all that?
To the Country Club lot,
if you´re Larchmont, you´re guilty.
Yeah, but they´re not running  the case.
I am.
And do you think
you´re gona get thanked for this?
I´m telling you, these people think
they own the place, and us.
I mean, Greenlees complains about
the letter, but is he coming clean?
- About what?
- There was no VAT investigation.
I checked.
- Oh, really?
- Guv?
Come on in, Rich, you´re one of the giris.
Sorry, but there´s something
you should take a look at.
On 23rd June, 180 grand gets paid
into Carradine´s bank account.
Right, and on the very same day,
he writes a cheque for the same amount
to an H Torres.
Hernandez Torres & Partners
are the company that bought Burdett House.
I got the details from the Land Registry.
They´re based in the Bahamas.
Their contact number in this country
is Pitt, Henry, James & Partners.
Maria Henry. Denis´s solicitor.
See what she knows.
Get this VAT business sorted out,
once and for all. Not you, Chris.
Not with your sneaky little fingers.
Don´t want another complaint, do we?
Thank you, Jane.
So, you can tell us nothing
of Hernandez Torres & Partners, then?
Other than they use this firm
as a local office, no.
It´s quite a common practice.
Why would it be common practice
for Panamanian lawyers to do that?
I´m afraid I can´t answer that, Sergeant.
I´m bound by the Client Confidentiality Act.
You´d get me struck off.
Look, can I ask what all this is about?
Mr Carradine seems to have paid
a large sum of money to this company.
- We´d like to know why.
- I´m sorry.
- As I say, I can´t comment on that.
- I don´t follow, Mrs Henry.
You represented Denis and his mother.
You also represent the Torres Partners.
Denis pays Torres £180,000.
And yet you seem to be saying
you knew nothing about it.
What I´m actually saying, Sergeant,
is that for me to make any comment at all
would be a breach
of my client´s confidentiality
and therefore unlawful.
Look, off the record,
if, as I think you´re suggesting, Sergeant,
Denis chose to buy into an offshore company,
then he probably did so
to keep his investment private.
He´s quite within his rights.
It´s perfectly legal.
I wouldn´t have to know about it.
Well, thank you
for being so frank, Mrs Henry.
Could you tell us anything
about the sale of Burdett House?
Not really.
Other than some minor conveyancing,
the office had nothing to do with it.
Any idea how much they paid for it?
Somewhere in the region of £300,000.
Jane I said no calls
Look, I´m sorry to be blunt,
and believe me, I´d like to help,
but what´s all this
got to do with Denis´s murder?
That´s what we need to find out.
Hamish, either the police
were called in or they weren´t.
Now, which one was it?
Look, I´ve been told
n- not to say anything, all right?
No, it´s not all right.
If no-one is gona talk to us,
how the hell are we expected to find
who murdered Denis Carradine?
I thought you already had.
Are you gona tell us?
They treated him like shit.
You know, a bit like me, really.
They used to laugh
and say we´d make a good team.
He showed them, though,
he had his hand in the till for m-months.
They never even knew.
He used to fiddle the accounts to h-hide it.
So, when did they discover this?
Last week. They got Raymond
in to sort it out.
DCI Raymond?
- Yeah...
- Hamish!
Look, I´ve g-g...
- Got to go.
- Yo, yo!
These are firing, man!
- You can do this professional.
- Yeah? Tell my old m-man.
He thinks working here is all I´m good for.
Well, he´s wrong. Who is your dad?
P- Paul.
- Paul Endicott.
- Hey, I know her.
That´s... What´s her name? Polly.
- The daughter of that solicitor.
- Hamish!
Maria Henry, yeah. Yeah. Nice woman.
Close friend of my father´s.
No, I´m just her daughter.
I´m not responsible for the telephone bill.
Look, I´m gona have to go, OK?
Yeah, I´ll tell her.
- Your mum not in?
- No. She was.
- She´s gone to work.
- Good.
Hair´s nice.
You gona invite me in, then?
Why wasn´t I told that Carradine...
was caught embezzling funds from the club?
- What?
- You heard me.
You went there last week.
You interviewed him.
He was subsequently sacked.
Who told you that?
They wanted it kept discreet.
- I didn´t think it was relevant.
- Bollocks!
I´m the senior officer.
I´ll decide what´s relevant.
If you´re covering up for someone,
I swear, I´ll mark your card good.
- I´ve got a tener. What is it?
- Speed or something. Who cares?
A tener. We´re not gona get
very much with that, are we?
Look, I don´t like him coming here, Poll.
Don´t be stupid. These old farts
will never know the difference.
My old man would.
Any old excuse and I´ll be out on my ear.
Yeah, well, he´s all talk.
One of these days,
he´ll open his lying mouth
and I´m gona put my fist in it.
- Hello?
Er... Yeah?
Hello?
- She was being cagey.
- Come off it, she´s a solicitor.
She has a responsibility
to protect her clients´ interests.
- Fancy her, do you?
- I´d show her the error of her ways.
Richard, Burdett House.
You heard anything from the Coucil?
Ten minutes of Mantovani,
then the line went dead.
- Someone must know something.
- If they do, they´re not saying.
H Torres,
a partnership of Panamanian lawyers.
Totally legit and totally uninterested
in answering questions.
- Surprise
- What about this woman at Denis´s?
- Got a description?
- Not much.
I rechecked.
She could´ve had red hair.
Maria Henry has got red hair.
Denis had been phoning her all week.
- We got a printout from BT.
- Now, that´s interesting.
Richard, let´s pay her a social visit.
Anyone been to Burdett House yet?
For God´s sake. Come on, Richard.
Come on!
They all lock the same
and smell the same.
Know what the Russians call them?
- No what?
- Stack a prole
- What´s this one called again?
- Fort Larchmont.
- Also known as the Larchmont Estate.
- Larchmont Estate...
Makes it sound pretty. Like somewhere
you might actually want to live.
300 grand for this lot.
Someone´s having us on.
I think it´s time to have a talk
to Mrs Henry.
I understand that for legal reasons,
you feel unable
to comment on this case
or grant us access to any of your files.
That´s correct. I honestly feel
I´ve been as frank as I dare be.
You´re divorced, aren´t you, Mrs Henry?
I´m sorry, but what´s my private life
got to do with this investigation?
Well, we´re trying to build a profile
of Denis Carradine and his friends.
Now, when was the last time
you spoke to Mr Carradine?
Well, I don´t really know.
Over a week ago. It was at the club.
Oh...
We have...
We have a record of Denis Carradine´s
phone calls...
that show that he called you three times
on the day he was murdered.
Really?
Do they show I actually spoke to him?
I do have a secretary, you know.
I do have an answerphone.
Messages are all logged in the diary.
Please be my guest.
This is just a formality
and I´m sorry to have to ask you this,
but could you tell me where you were
on the night that Denis was murdered,
that is, between about 7:00 and 9:00?
Am I a suspect in this case?
No. I don´t think anyone is suggesting that.
Good. Having diner
with Paul Endicott and his wife at the club.
20 or 30 people can give us an alibi,
if you really think it´s necessary.
You may find it quaint, Superintendent,
but I have a reputation in this town.
And it´s very important to me.
In future, before you doubt my honesty,
please check your facts first
Now, if you´ll excuse me, I am rather busy.
Are we to understand
that the girl you arrested...
in conection with this murder
has been released?
Yes, we couldn´t hold her any longer.
She was charged
with breaking-and-entering.
We all know what that means.
I understand your disappointment
but burglary is not murder.
Now, Michael Thomas is already dead.
I´m sure you wouldn´t want us to charge
Sheila with something she didn´t do,
upon which we could get no conviction.
It´s easy to ridicule
middle-class values.
But we have rights too.
We want to protect what we worked for.
Actually, we´ve been
relatively lucky so far.
If we´d have had the Ranleigh Housing
Association right on our doorstep,
we´d have been in trouble
- Housing association?
- There was a dreadful fuss
There´s been an investigation
into the sale of Burdett House.
The Chief Planing Officer,
Paul Endicott, was suspended.
- Investigation?
- A witchhut, more like!
Ask James Greenlees. He´ll tell you.
He´s Chairman of the Housing Committee.
He had to head the damn thing.
It was absurd, do you remember?
Burdett House. OK, let´s assume
Denis put his 180 grand into buying it.
Thanks. It was 300,000.
Where did the other 120 come from?
- He must´ve had a partner.
- Well done, Sherlock.
- Right. Anything else? Anyone?
- Maybe he offered Denis some deal?
- Maria did the conveyancing.
- Run a financial check on her.
I want to see those office files.
Get a court order. See how she reacts.
Tennison.
Greenlees is chairman of the Housing Committee.
He´s Endicott´s boss.
- He´s got to be involved.
- Chris, you´ve no proof of that.
I want Greenlees interviewed,
here at the nick, not all comfy at home.
Christ, being a Tory coucillor is not a sin.
- He lied about Denis getting sacked.
- That don´t mean he killed him!
Shut up, please!
Sorry, not you. What did you say?
Well, thank you.
Denis Carradine´s car was found torched
outside Maria Henry´s house last night.
I want that court order.
So why should someone
steal Denis Carradine´s car,
park it outside your house
...and then set light to it?
For God´s sake, I keep telling you!
I´ve no idea!
It´s probably those yobs
on the estate that you let go.
It was all a coincidence, was it?
You don´t really expect us to believe that,
do you, Mrs Henry?
Quite frankly, I don´t care what
you believe. It happens to be the truth.
Mrs Henry, I´m obliged to inform you
that we´ve applied for a court order
to search your premises, and impound
any documents relevant to this case.
- Thank you.
- This is outrageous!
Some joyrider leaves a car outside my house
and you raid my office?
You leave us no alternative.
I hope it doesn´t damage your reputation.
- Hello.
What´s going on?
Where the hell were you last night?
With friends.
I told you I was staying over...
You liar!
You were at the Larchmont Estate.
If you´re using drugs, I´ll kill you!
Polly... I´m sorry...
Please, darling...
Sit down, please.
Well...
This is absurd! Good God,
can´t we leave the man some dignity?
All right, all right.
Denis was...
...homosexual.
He was seen at certain pubs and clubs.
That´s why he needed the money,
to pay for their services.
Now you know why I would have preferred
to keep this private.
Really? And who saw him at these clubs?
The Chief Inspector
would like a word in his office.
Yeah. When we´re finished.
So? Who saw him, Mr Greenlees?
Now, Inspector.
I´ll be back in five minutes.
I expect Mr Greenlees to be here
when I get back.
Eight quid? You gotta be joking!
It´s all I´ve g-got.
Please, Geoff.
Oh, go on, then. Seeing as it´s you.
Santa´s arrived.
Do the honours, then, Hamish.
Chop, chop, couple of Bacardi and Cokes.
- That all right for you, Poll?
- Yeah, great.
Well, come on, then, Hamish.
Chop, chop, on the double.
Polly. S-She´s underage.
You wana get that s-seen to, mate.
Two B-Bacardi and C-Cokes, all right?
N- No, I c-can´t.
Right, well, I´ll s-serve myself, then.
Fast hands, boy.
- Fast hands.
- Put that b-back!
M- Make me.
Hamish, is your father here?
Mum, this is Geoff.
I don´t believe it. I mean,
look at you two, you could be sisters.
- Can I get you a drink, Mrs Henry?
- No thank you
Polly and I are leaving
Surely you could stop for a drink,
Mrs Henry. I´m buying.
Now, Polly. Please, darling, come on.
Mrs Henry,
I have the police on the phone.
Your secretary gave them the number.
It´s urgent.
Right I´d better be going
See you later Mrs Henry
- Polly.
- Wait, I´ll come with you, Geoff.
Polly, wait, please!
Yes, three o´clock. I´ll be there, OK.
Polly! Polly!
So we´re just coming up
behind the stolen car.
And moving alongside.
This is the frame we´ve got.
That´s it after enhacement.
- Do you recognise him, Mrs Henry?
- No.
I´m sure I´ve never seen him before.
No. I´m positive.
Lyne?
- Lyne?
- Hamish cut his hand.
Well, he´s dropped blood
all over the carpet.
- Hamish!
- Paul! He´s hurt his hand.
- Hamish, why aren´t you at work?
- I...
- Oh, for God´s sake.
...w- was.
You weren´t. I was just there.
I thought you weren´t going
to the club, Paul.
I had to talk to Jimmy Greenlees
about that Coucil meeting tonight.
Hamish!
Mr Endicott?
Superintendent Tennison.
This is Detective Sergeant Cromwell.
Well, we didn´t see him socially.
We might occasionally bump into him
at the club. That was all.
- So you had no business conection?
- No why?
You were involved in the sale
of Burdett House
Did you know that Denis was involved
in the development company that bought it?
No, I didn´t.
Was the sale of Burdett House your decisión?
Mine?
You obviously have no idea
how local government works, do you?
Perhaps you should go on
a course, Sergeant.
Do you think people have courses
on things like that?
Or would you like me to lecture on one?
I am tremendously available.
No, a vote was taken. A democratic vote
of the whole Planing Committee.
And who decided the selling price?
Look, you and I both know that
this has got bugger all to do with Denis.
This is an abuse of my privacy
and I´m not gona have it.
Mr Carradine´s solicitor puts
the selling price at around £300,000.
For 200 acres of prime land.
Would you not agree that
that´s well below the market price?
There´s a Coucil meeting tonight.
Why don´t you ask them?
Now, if you will excuse me.
Denis Carradine´s solicitor, Maria Henry.
She´s... a friend of yours, isn´t she?
My private life is my own affair.
It´s got sod all to do with you lot.
Lyne, these ladies are leaving.
Once again, Mr Chairman,
we discover a favoured developer
bidding less
and still being awarded the contract
And not because of the efficacy
of its proposal, oh, no.
Because it suits the political aspirations
of this Coucil.
Point of order! Point of order!
Mr Mason, sit down.
It is exactly this climate of witchhunt...
...and hysteria, whipped up
by the opposition and the press,
that has hampered this internal inquiry.
And... And caused the delay
in the publication of our findings.
Yet again we are faced with the evidence
of the corrupt and secretive way
this Coucil conducts its business.
Withdraw that remark.
Why? It´s the truth.
Order! Point of order!
Mr Mason, if you don´t sit down,
I shall have to have you removed.
- You should be removed.
- Point of order!
Stewards! Clear the chamber.
Out, out!
This meeting is now formally adjourned.
Out, out, out!
Just sit her down, please.
Police officer!
She´s got a warrant, you pillock!
This is typical of your conduct
sice you arrived in this borough.
From your failure to control your officers
to harrying inocent people.
I believe your entire agenda
has been politically motivated.
Got any comment to make about that,
Superintendent? Superintendent!
You wanted to see me?
What is this all about?
Democracy in action?
- It didn´t happen like that.
- A politically-motivated witchhunt?
- Greenlees wants us off the case.
- He´s not the only one
Cromwell´s suspended, you´re back here, now.
- Raymond´s taking over.
- Look!
No, you look!
You´ve got no bloody case.
- Burdett House is a part of...
- Don´t give me that conspiracy crap.
I don´t want to hear it.
All right.
All right. Well, let me put it this way.
Supposing some hairy leflwing journalist
got hold of the story
that the Met did nothing
about a major Coucil fraud...
associated with a murder?
Conspiracy is exactly what they´d call it.
I don´t know, but the press
do have a funy way
of finding out about these things,
don´t they?
Are you threatening me?
I want Cromwell back on the case.
Politics, Mike. It´s what it´s all about.
- Get a result, Jane.
- Of course, sir.
Where´ve you been?
You´ve had me worried sick.
- Drink too much, did he?
- Don´t be so bloody facetious.
- I asked you a question.
- With Geoff, all right?
I stayed with Geoff.
You´ve got your lover and I´ve got mine.
You stupid little slut.
Yeah, well, at least mine´s
not cheating on his wife.
Polly! Polly, please!
- What are we gona do?
- For God´s sake, stop your snivelling!
Christine.
I want to have a few words
about personal security.
Yeah, you may well laugh, lads,
but it´s better safe than sorry.
Look, about this damage-limitation stuff...
Taken to wearing nappies, Josh?
All right, out, the lot of you.
Sparing my feelings?
Greenlees phoned Kernan,
Kernan saw the newspaper.
So I´m off the case?
Look, Chris, Greenlees has set himself up...
as the unofficial
spokesman of this community,
and this community, for reasons best known
to itself, accepts him as such.
Now, we serve this community,
so regardless of our opinion of him,
he is entitled to our courtesy.
Oh, you were there. Bloody hell!
His sort are so good at yelling
for their courtesy,
there´s sod all lefl for anyone else.
- He´s scared you off.
- You were out of line in his office.
- You were out of line last night.
- You finished?
No, I have not, so shut up and sit down!
I put my job on the line for you
this morning.
Don´t know why. You sure as hell
haven´t earned it. So start.
- I´m not suspended?
- It´s on hold.
I want Denis Carradine´s killers.
Chris, I want them all.
I know you can help us get them.
Just don´t let your pride blow it
for us, all right?
Right.
Well, where´s Raymond?
He´s not gona be pleased.
You bastards...
Police! Open the door!
Right, in you go.
Get off!
Geoff?
That is why they call them the filth!
Right little slag, ain´t you?
Geoff...
All right. How much?
Come on, you don´t think
I´m gona do it for nothing, do you?
Can´t afford it, eh?
You got your mummy´s problem.
Two slags in one family.
I should´ve known.
I don´t understand.
Why are you doing this to me?
Aw...
Does little Polly want to know why?
Denis knew about the Coucil fraud.
We knew he was desperate for money.
We´re still no closer to the actual killers.
Maria and Endicott have both got alibis.
They could´ve paid someone.
Yeah, why pay someone
to kill the blackmailer?
- Just pay the blackmailer.
- They couldn´t anyway,  Guv.
She´s skint. We´ve checked her accounts.
And Endicott is in the middle
of this inquiry. He´d dare not.
Which puts us back to square one.
Pull Maria in, Guv. What we got to lose?
A lot. She´s been to law school.
She´ll run legal rings around us.
Got a female downstairs, name of Henry.
Doesn´t look too good.
- She´s brought herself in.
- Diner on a plate.
The doctor´s on his way.
- Who did this to you, Polly?
- A man.
Geoffrey Brenan.
I want him arrested.
- Bastard.
- All right, OK...
- Does your mother know you´re here?
- What does she care?
She wanted this to happen.
- What are you talking about?
- He got thrown out of the army.
She kept telling me not to go near him,
acted like she hated him.
All right, now, look. Just calm down.
Tell me what happened.
She saw us at the club yesterday.
She freaked. I went back with him.
Stayed the night.
When she found out, she went mad.
Completely mad.
Called me a slut in front of Paul.
Paul? Who´s Paul?
Her boyfriend. Paul Endicott.
It´s all right for her,
she can do whatever she likes,
but when it´s me,
she starts screaming and shouting.
Right...
So you went back to Geoff?
I thought he wanted me.
He called me a slag.
He kept laughing and sneering.
He said he´d only done it with me
to get at my mother.
I wanted to kill him.
And where did this happen?
A flat on the Larchmont Estate.
Dragonda House.
Polly, can you describe Geoff for me?
- Got him! Josh, get Maria Henry in.
- What on?
Nothing. Tell her her daughter´s
been beaten up but keep them apart.
Lan, you entertain her.
Rest of you come with me.
Where?
To arrest Geoffrey Brenan
for the murder of Denis Carradine.
- Who the hell´s Geoffrey Brenan?
- Bound to be a Tory coucillor!
Hey, Derek!
- What´s going on?
- DCI Raymond nicked Sheila Bower.
- It´s not a great idea.
- Who sanctioned this?
Your chief superintendent felt the squatter
and drug problem was getting out-of-hand.
Oi!
- Excuse me.
- It´s all a bloody game, isn´t it?
Guv.
Mr Brenan! Police.
Police!
Anyone?
Guv.
It´ll be half an hour soon.
Where the hell is he?
Oh, it´s all right. Here he is.
Two in a week.
Still, think of the overtime, eh?
Ma´am, looks like
we may have a witness.
Then there was this couple
in this green Jeep-type thing.
Parked up in the middle of
all the aggravation.
I thought to myself, ´´You leave it there,
you´re asking for trouble. ´´
- Then this bloke gets out.
- This Jeep, was it a Range Rover?
Oh, I don´t know.
And when I came back up again,
he was banging on matey boy´s door.
George, would you recognise this man again?
Well, I was keeping my head down.
- He was tall... Yeah, maybe.
- What about the other person?
No, I only saw her for a second.
- Lovely red hair though
- Long?
No! Only to about here.
If I´ve been dragged down here
under false pretences,
I shall be making a complaint.
That is your prerogative.
Burdett House. We know Denis Carradine
bought it from the Coucil.
It cost somewhere in the region of £300,000.
Cheap for such a large property,
wouldn´t you say?
I wouldn´t really know.
We were only involved in the conveyancing.
- It was a crumbling heap.
- With planing permissión for luxury homes.
Inside information that you knew.
Paul Endicott told you.
The Coucil had to sell Burdett House
as quickly as possible,
to stop a housing cooperative
from buying it.
Not the right kind of people.
The buyers stood to make a fortue.
You and Denis.
Were you his silent partner, Maria?
No! That would be both
illegal and unethical!
Yes, exactly what the Coucil´s
gerrymandering policy was.
When it blew up in their faces
and they withheld planing permissión,
you and Denis were left
holding a property worth nothing
That is pure speculation and you know it.
Um...
How would you define your relationship
with Paul Endicott?
He´s a friend.
Our families meet socially.
So any suggestion that you are
involved in a sexual relationship...
would be quite utrue?
His wife is a friend of mine,
Superintendent.
I see.
And when did you last see Mr Endicott?
- I don´t know. A few days ago.
- Didn´t you see him this morning?
Absolutely not! Who told you that?
Your daughter Polly
You see, she seems to think
the two of you having been
having an affair for months.
Mrs Henry?
Have you interviewed her?
Polly is 15, Superintendent. She´s a minor.
It is unlawful to interview a minor
without a parent or guardian present.
- You are aware of that?
- Polly came to us with a complaint.
We investigated. She wasn´t interviewed.
I hope not. For your sake.
- And Mr Endicott?
- Is a friend. That´s all.
I see.
We´ve compiled an ID of a man seen earlier
at Denis Carradine´s house
on the night of the murder.
The description matches a man
called Geoffrey Brenan. Do you know him?
No.
This is Geoffrey Brenan.
This is the man who stole Denis´s car
and set fire to it outside your house.
The man we showed you
on the video.
Do you still maintain
you do not recognise him?
Yes, I´ve already told you.
Did you know your daughter
was sleeping with him?
What are you talking about? She´s 15!
She says you met them together yesterday.
Yesterday?
Yes, at the Huntington Club.
Yes, I met someone there,
but he didn´t look like that.
You´re going to have to do
better than that, Maria.
The only way you could have obtained
this so-called information,
Superintendent, is illegally.
If so, you´ll be in a great deal of trouble.
Your daughter came here
with her face in a mess
and accused Brenan of attacking her.
We went to arrest him and found him dead.
- It´s as simple as that.
- I don´t believe that.
You believe what you like.
You see, we have a description
of a man and a woman,
seen at the time of Brenan´s murder,
that matches you and Paul Endicott.
I think that you and your lover
conspired to murder Denis Carradine
and employed Geoffrey Brenan
to do it.
And subsequently, when he threatened you...
...the pair of you got rid of him.
If you really believed that,
you´d charge me.
Right, so she´s not going
to stick her hand up.
Maybe there´s something in her office.
No way, she´s too sure of herself.
Covered her tracks.
- God, what a bitch.
- So what now?
Richard, any news from Brenan´s flat?
Looks like he was attacked with a hammer.
We should get something off it.
Forensic reckon he was given
a right whacking.
Let´s get Maria printed. Get a court order.
- Where´s Endicott?
- Interview room, Guv.
- He´s got a solicitor with him.
- Right, let´s have a crack at him.
Good luck, Guv.
Geoffrey Brenan was found
murdered at his flat...
on the Larchmont Estate at 1:15 today.
God...
Well, it wasn´t me.
Maria Henry and you are good friends,
aren´t you?
Er... Yes, yes, we are.
Very... good friends.
- She is a family friend.
- That you sleep with.
Were the two of you involved in
the fraudulent purchase of Burdett House?
No, that´s not true.
Wasn´t it you who recommended the sale
to the Planing Committee?
- I told you, it was a vote.
- The whole scam was your idea.
We know there is a conection
between the sale of Burdett House
and Geoffrey Brenan´s murder.
Well, it wasn´t me. I didn´t... kill him.
We have a witness who saw a tall man
and a red-haired woman
in a green four-wheel-drive
at the time of the murder.
- My client is under no obligation...
- Your friend Maria has red hair.
You drive a green Monterey.
- Look, I wasn´t there!
- Where were you at 12:00?
I went out for a walk.
Where? Did anyone see you?
Um... No.
My client is under no obligation
to answer these questions.
That´s right. That´s a very good idea.
Say nothing, Paul.
Because I think you and Maria paid
Brenan to murder Denis Carradine.
And whateveryou say
that´s what I´ll charge you with
We´d better get his prints done.
- Um!
- I´ll get a court order
Um...
Look...
I didn´t even know this Geoffrey Brenan
even existed until today.
That´s the truth. Um...
Maria was frightened.
She said someone was threatening her
and she asked me to stay over.
Anyway
...that was when she told me.
Maria... That she said she´d done it.
Done what?
That she´d hired Brenan to kill Denis.
Why?
Because he was going to expose
the Burdett House deal.
He wanted her to bail him out,
but she didn´t have the money.
If she didn´t have it,
where did she find the cash to hire Brenan?
- You?
- No! No!
I knew nothing about it!
Maria said she was going to pay Brenan.
She promised him £2,000,
was going to give him half of it up front.
She did that, but she didn´t have the rest.
He... Well, he threatened her.
He wouldn´t wait. He was furious.
Brenan, he was just
completely out of control and um...
She said that I should pay him off or...
Or we´d have to get rid of him too.
Is that what you did?
No...
All right.
Paul, if it wasn´t you driving your car
with Maria Henry...
...who do you think it was?
I don´t know. I really don´t.
Look... The...
The Coucil inquiry is going to exonerate me.
So why would I risk all that?
I think we´d better take a statement.
You´ve got to hand it to her.
We had the kids marked down for that.
- You did.
- Is there enough to make it stick?
- Forensic will sort it out.
- If he ever gets his act together.
Greenlees is gona exonerate him?
Guv, he´s got to be involved.
Chris, I know he´s an arrogant shit.
That doesn´t make him an accessory.
Forget him. We haven´t got
enough to prosecute these two yet.
- About time!
- Right.
- The good news or the bad news?
- The good news.
That hammer we found,
the pathologist thinks it´s a reasonable bet.
The blood grouping looks good
and it´s covered in prints.
Yes!
The bad news is
none of them match Paul Endicott´s.
- Well... What about Maria Henry?
- Sorry.
So far, there´s no forensic evidence
to put either of them near that flat.
Not finished yet.
This is Detective Sergeant Cromwell.
A continuation of the interview
with Maria Henry.
The time is 18:32.
Entering the room, Superintendent Tennison.
Well, it´s not gona work, Maria.
Paul Endicott has made a statement.
He says the murders are all down to you.
- Rubbish.
- He´s signed it.
´´Brenan strung Denis up
and then pulled down his trousers
and his underpants to make it
look like some kind a sex game. ´´
He was your oldest friend.
Was that your idea?
You even went to see him earlier that day.
We´ve got an ID, Maria.
Why did you do that?
The right to remain silent seems to be
a concept you don´t fully understand.
Why remain silent
if you have nothing to hide?
Why lie?
All right.
I admit I visited Denis.
Look, let´s try and clear this up
once and for all.
Denis had been caught embezzling money
from the Huntington Club.
Well. That´s why all the phone calls.
I didn´t tell you because...
Well, quite frankly, I was embarrassed.
I mean, I´ve got friends at the club
and I didn´t want the police
crawling all over my private affairs.
I offered to lend him some money.
Oh, and did Denis accept
your kind offer of help?
Of course he didn´t,
because you didn´t make one, did you?
You can´t, Maria. You´re broke.
We know, we´ve checked.
Your money is tied up
in the Burdett House scam.
You couldn´t even afford to pay Brenan.
That´s completely untrue.
I know nothing about that.
It´s all down here in black and white.
Paul Endicott is a drunk and a liar.
He´s also totally corrupt
and I can prove it.
He was the one that approached Denis about
Burdett House. I had nothing to do with it!
In Fact, if you check my files, I actually
advised Denis against the purchase.
Endicott´s been taking kickbacks for years.
I absolutely deny everything he says
and you can´t prove otherwise.
Now, I´d like to see my daughter, please.
It´s all circumstantial.
And Polly? We have to let her see her.
- Not yet. Not yet.
- Oh, Superintendent.
Paul Endicott´s wife phoned me.
She was very upset.
- She told me he´d been arrested.
- Yes, yes, that´s correct.
There was a murder on the Larchmont...
So I understand.
You´ve got the wrong man, Superintendent.
I can assure you, Paul wouldn´t be seen dead
on the Larchmont Estate.
Thank you, we´ll bear that in mind.
I take it this is just an informal interview,
then, and you´ll be releasing him shortly?
Mr Greenlees, someone is dead.
He may not have been part
of your iner circle of friends,
but he still had rights
and someone caved his head in.
I´m in charge of this case and I will decide
who gets released and when! All right?
I knew you´d blow it.
Yeah... He hums it, you sing it.
- Dick.
- Guv!
Hamish Endicott.
I found him down by the canal
behind the estate.
When I walked up to him,
he turns around and says,
´´I´ve killed someone.
You better lock me up. ´´
Why did you want to kill him, Hamish?
He´s a b-b-b-b...
He´s a bastard!
He d-didn´t deserve to live
after what he d-did.
- What did he do?
- You know, to P-P...
...Polly.
- What did he do to Polly?
- He
...r- raped her.
And I´d do it again.
Who told you that, Hamish?
Who told you that Brenan raped Polly?
Was it Maria?
No.
- She told me.
- Cos that wasn´t true.
S- Sh...
- She told me.
- Hamish, she was lying.
N- n...
N... I´m n-not saying any m-more.
Hamish, who was it in that car with you?
The red-haired woman.
Who was that? Was that Polly?
- No!
- Was it Maria?
I told you, it was m-me!
I did it! On my own! Me!
- All right...
- It was me!
- Yeah, all right. All right!
- I did it.
- Superintendent Tennison, 7:22.
I´m suspending this interview.
Hamish, look, I´m turning the tape off.
Get him a tea.
Hot tea with lots of sugar.
Hamish.
Come and sit down. Come on.
Come on.
Come on, it´s all right.
Look. Denis was a friend of yours,
wasn´t he?
Yeah.
- He was all right.
- Hmm.
He was a friend of Maria´s too.
Until she had him killed.
No.
She couldn´t.
Listen, you know that Maria and your father
were lovers, don´t you?
Well, she and your father
were involved in a fraud.
And Denis was the front man.
We´ve got your father here.
Hamish, he´s...
helping us with our enquiries.
I don´t...
...b- believe you.
It´s the truth.
Maria had Denis killed
to stop him from talking.
Here.
You see, she paid Brenan to kill him.
And then she got you get rid of him.
Oh, she used you, my love.
She used you, just like she used Denis,
like she used your father.
For Christ´s sake,
why are you trying to protect her?
But she...
All right! All right, play the martyr.
Let me tell you,
if you don´t start talking soon,
Polly is gona go down
as an accessory to murder.
And do you know what that means, Hamish?
That means, Polly is gona go to prison.
- Prison.
- It wasn´t her, all right?
Well, who was it?
I want to see my daughter.
I keep telling you, that is not possible.
Where were you this afternoon?
Superintendent Tennison
entering the room at 7:42pm.
At 1:00 today, you were with Hamish Endicott
on the Larchmont Estate.
I was not!
You lied about your daughter being raped...
and then you sent that boy out
to do your dirty work for you.
He bungled it, Maria. He dropped the hammer.
Then he got himself arrested.
He´s here. He´s told us everything.
Are you saying Hamish murdered
Geoffrey Brenan?
Well, as if you didn´t know!
Because you were with him.
You were seen. We have a witness
who saw a red-haired woman with him.
Did he say it was me?
Did Hamish say it was me?
- Exactly.
- Who else could it have been?
I haven´t the faintest idea. It could
just as easily have been my daughter.
Oh, God, you´d do anything, wouldn´t you?
I haven´t done anything, Sergeant.
You´ve manufactureda lot of hearsay evidence
that you know won´t hold up in court
and you´re panicking.
Polly!
Can you come with us, please?
You too. Come on.
Geoffrey Brenan is dead Polly
What?
No.
No, he can´t be!
He was murdered.
Hamish Endicott killed him.
We know that.
We also know that there was
a red-haired female with him.
It wasn´t me! I didn´t do it! I didn´t!
Darling, they´re just trying
to frighten you. Now, say nothing.
We want you to answer some questions.
- Mummy! Help me!
- It´s all right!
Mummy won´t let them hurt you, darling.
She´s underage.
You can´t touch her and you know it.
But I didn´t do it! I didn´t do it!
Polly! Where were you at 1:00 today, Polly?
- I don´t know.
- For God´s sake, stop this!
- Why aren´t you stopping this?
- Where were you?
Why are you doing this to me?
You´re under 16, Polly.
They can´t touch you. Say nothing.
Did you tell Hamish that you´d been raped?
What?
Well, who told Hamish
that Geoff had raped you?
Who knew how much he loved you?
Who went cut there with him in
his father´s car, this red-haired woman?
Who gave him a hammer
and who told him to bash Geoff´s head in?
- It wasn´t me!
- For God´s sake, she´s just a child.
Mummy, I didn´t do it!
What sort of a person would lie like that
and let Hamish take the blame?
Stop this. Leave her alone!
You know Hamish
is going to go to prison, don´t you?
You´re going with him.
Do you know why?
Because the woman who was with him
is going to let you.
That´s a lie!
I never said it was her and you know it
Oh, no... No, they´re lying.
Darling, I love you.
I wouldn´t let anything happen to you.
Someone must have made Hamish kill Geoff,
Polly.
Oh, Polly, please!
- You slept with him.
- I didn´t
- Polly, I love you.
- Liar!
Geoff told me, Mum.
All right, so if it wasn´t you,
who was that red-haired woman?
Oh, all right!
All right...
I´ll tell you. Just stop this.
Please
You did it. She´s admitted everything.
Well done.
She used her daughter and we did the same.
What´s the difference?
Another retirement due to ill health?
Give Greenlees a month and it´ll be
as if none of this ever happened.
Well, it´s not our job, is it?
- Should be. He´s as guilty as...
- Politics is what it´s all about.
Politics!
- Give me a cigarette, would you?
- I didn´t know you smoked.
I don´t.