Tensions between the US and North Korea
have reached an all-time high.
Newly released intelligence suggests
that Russian or Chinese interests...
may have sold sophisticated
defense technology to the rogue state.
North Korea continues to deny
all allegations...
and have staged mass rallies of support...
for its fight
against so-called foreign imperialism.
This, as the UN Security Council
meets today...
for an emergency session
to decide on a resolution...
calling for a naval blockade of North Korea.
Back to our top story
on the crisis in North Korea.
The U.S. Pacific Command has increased
its presence in the Sea of Japan...
with a carrier task force
and heightened security at the DMZ.
The Pentagon says that
satellites have detected evidence...
of two ballistic missile bases
under construction in the North...
capable of reaching targets
in Guam, Okinawa, Alaska, and even Hawaii.
Cmdr. Habley.
Yes, sir, I'm watching.
...but the President has reaffirmed
the United States will not....
It's our job to make them think twice.
This latest escalation in rhetoric...
Yes, sir.
...has left the tides of diplomacy
in its wake...
and has brought us even closer
to the tides of war.
Oh, I'm sorry, Captain.
I didn't realize you were working out.
It's all right. I'm pretty done.
Whose idea was it to have pizza night
every Saturday?
It was your idea, sir.
Yes, I know.
This your first tour?
Petty Officer Murray.
Second tour, sir.
Food is great on this boat.
I promised my wife this time I'd come back
without the extra pounds.
I'll get you home, son.
The rest is up to you.
-Carry on.
-Thank you, sir.
You're relieved.
Chief of the Boat?
How did you pull Diving Officer duty again?
Let's just say I like to be
where the action is, sir.
Action? Well, when we get back to Pearl...
the Captain and I are going to have to
take you to Luana Hills.
It's the most beautiful course around.
I sank a hole-in-one last time I was there...
and beat Vice Admiral Sommerville.
Was that a smart move, sir?
His short game needs work.
Did you tell him that?
No. I want to keep my job.
Conn, Radio.
We have an incoming download...
via satellite link
from National Military Command Center.
Request to raise UHF antenna.
Radio, Conn. Prepare for download.
Chief of the Watch, raise the UHF antenna.
Diving Officer, slow us to 12 knots,
and bring us up to 60 feet.
Church-mouse quiet.
Aye, sir.
1 2 knots, 60 feet, church-mouse quiet.
Navigation Officer has the Conn.
Enter.
How do you do that?
I never get a chance to knock.
I was looking forward to some quality time
on the links.
I guess we're not going back to Pearl.
Doesn't look good, Tom.
These are holding launch orders.
We sit, wait for confirmation,
and if it comes...
we shoot and scoot.
Target baggage?
Missile base is at Yangdok,
50 miles east of Pyongyang.
The other base is at Honchon.
Full-deployment attack.
Your dad was here, right,
during the Korean War?
Yeah, he was an ensign on a destroyer.
Saw action at lnchon.
Fifty years
and we still got trouble over here.
You think we're going to war, Frank?
-I'll be up in a couple of minutes.
-Right.
Murray.
Okay.
-Afternoon, Captain.
-Afternoon.
-I have the Conn.
-Captain has the Conn.
Diving Officer, what's our depth?
Depth 60 feet, sir.
Speed, five knots.
Satellite mast is up, periscope's ready, sir.
WEPS, are the VLS tubes ready?
All 12 Tomahawks ready to be delivered, sir.
Gentlemen, we're awaiting confirmation
of our orders.
We could be here five minutes or five days.
Sonar, Conn. Any broadband contacts?
Anything?
Conn...
Sonar. No contact.
What is it, Captain? Did you see something?
No. That's the problem.
We are 10 miles within the North Korean
military zone and not one ship.
Conn, Radio.
We're picking up increased chatter
from the submarine base at Wonsan.
Radio, Conn.
Continue to log all transmissions.
Sonar, Conn. Any broadband contacts?
Conn, Sonar. Nothing, sir. No contacts.
Battaglia, are you absolutely sure?
Yes, sir.
Where the hell did she come from?
Sir?
It's not a Russian Akula or a Kilo.
She's not a Chinese Han Class, either.
-Korean Shark Class?
-No, too large.
Whoever she is,
there's no acoustic fingerprint.
-Emergency deep.
Gentlemen, we have a submarine
at 4,000 yards.
Dive, dive, dive.
Diving Officer, take her down to 500 feet.
-We'll hide out in the Chousan Trench.
-Chousan Trench?
Aye, sir.
Diving to 500 feet.
Man battle stations.
Repeat, man battle stations.
This is not a drill.
Right where we started.
Conn, Sonar. Torpedo in the water.
Just came out of nowhere.
-Bearing?
-050.
Range 3,500 yards and closing fast.
Sonar, Conn.
Lock in torpedo's sonar signature.
COB, get us in that trench.
300 feet, Captain.
WEPS, give me fish in Tubes 2 and 4
and stand ready.
Torpedo bearing steady at 050.
Range 2,500 yards and closing.
Depth, 400 feet.
We'll lose them in the trench.
It's our best chance.
Conn, Sonar.
Estimated impact in 60 seconds.
Depth, 450 feet.
All ahead full. Give me 25 knots.
Diving Officer, right full rudder.
Come to course 180.
Aye, sir. Right full rudder. Course 180.
Launch countermeasures.
Chief of the Watch, sound collision alarm.
Rig ship for impact.
All stations, damage report to control.
Conn, Engine Room. We've got
a little flooding in the rear bilge tank.
Conn, Reactor. We're okay.
Conn, Torpedo Room. We're still here.
Conn, Radio. Reporting to Com Sub Pac
in Pearl by floating wire.
WEPS, do we have a firing solution?
Yes, sir. It'll be like shooting blind,
but I think we can score a hit.
We have a firing solution.
Fire Tubes 2 and 4.
Murray, how long
before international waters?
At our speed...
9,000 yards, about 10 minutes, sir.
Murray, are you a religious man?
I am now, sir.
Good. Say a prayer,
and plot us a course out of here.
Aye, aye.
Conn, Sonar.
Torpedoes 1,000 yards and closing.
Impact in 30 seconds.
XO, take the Conn.
Torpedoes exploded?
No, it's their countermeasures.
Sir, these torpedoes are being dropped
from an ASW plane, aren't they?
No, we've got a new class of submarine
out there, Battaglia.
Right now, she's calling the shots.
-A submarine, sir?
-That's right.
You find me that sub.
Working on it, Captain.
International waters, five minutes.
I have the Conn.
Captain has the Conn.
Torpedoes in the water, bearing 205.
Range 1,500 yards and closing.
Chief of the Watch, sound collision alarm.
Talk to me, Murray.
2,000 yards until international waters, sir.
Just under two minutes.
-Launch countermeasures.
-Countermeasures being deployed, sir.
Diving Officer, right full rudder.
Come to course 180.
Conn, Sonar.
Torpedoes 500 yards.
Impact in 20 seconds.
It's gonna be close.
Is everyone okay?
-Switch.
-Yes.
All stations damage report to control.
Conn, Engine Room. This is Savage.
The turbine generator is on fire.
And we've got broken pipes
spraying hydraulic fluids everywhere.
Engineering Officer Makwana
is badly injured.
We need to put this fire out now!
This is the XO.
Fire team to the Engine Room.
Be careful, Tom.
We will.
Conn, Torpedo Room, no damage.
Conn, Reactor, no damage.
If they attack us in international waters,
it'll be a war.
Yeah.
Conn, Engine Room.
We're at 50% turbine power...
and sliding.
We gotta get this fire out now!
COB, bring her up to 300 feet.
300 feet, sir.
Okay, everybody, suit up.
Savage, you're the nozzle man!
I'm going ahead.
What's our depth?
250 feet, sir.
Gotta get these hatches open
to vent the toxic air.
Approaching international waters
in 30 seconds, sir.
Engine Room, damage report.
Rerouting. Rerouting.
Better.
Engine Room, can you hear me?
Engine Room!
Sonar, Conn. Any contacts?
Conn, Sonar. No contacts, sir.
Petty Officer Murray,
give me some good news.
We've crossed into international waters, sir.
Do we have a choice?
No, sir.
This is the Captain. Prepare to surface.
COB, emergency blow.
Chief of the Watch, blow the ballast tanks.
Hold on, gentlemen.
Petty Officer Savage, you and your men
saved the ship. Well done.
Thank you, sir.
We've got two with moderate injuries.
Engineering Officer Makwana is deceased.
And the XO is critical.
I've done everything I can for him, Captain.
He's on morphine, so he's not in any pain.
I've put him on the wardroom table for now.
Hey, Tom.
Captain.
Did we put the fire out?
Yes, the fire's out.
Your surface medevac chopper's on the way.
I don't think I'm going to make it, Frank.
Of course you're going to make it.
You never were a good liar.
You still have it.
I should have kept it with me.
You keep it in your hand
and everything will be fine.
Promise me you'll find that submarine.
I will. You have my word.
They ambushed us.
You save your strength. All right?
I'm so cold, Frank.
Hang in there, Tom.
It's been great.
Tom, you stay with me.
Tom, stay with me.
Okay.
Tom.
Tom!
He's gone, sir.
I'm sorry, Captain.
Captain to the Conn.
We're preparing for medevac.
Repeat, Captain to the Conn.
This is the Captain. I'm on my way.
I have the Conn.
Captain has the Conn.
Captain, a message from Com Sub Pac
in Pearl.
Murray.
Plot a course of rendezvous
with the battle group from Yokohama.
They'll escort us into port.
I'm very sorry, Captain.
Don't you men have work to do?
What's our speed?
Only five knots.
The propeller's been severely damaged.
All ahead full.
Give me what you can.
All ahead full with what we can.
Sir, recommend course 150.
COB, come right, 15-degree rudder.
Steady course, 150.
Aye, sir.
Right, 15-degree rudder.
Steady course at 150.
XO has....
Navigation Officer has the Conn.
Fire present.
Fire commence.
Lt. Trifoli, on behalf of a grateful nation
and a proud Navy...
I present this flag to you
in recognition of your brother's years...
of honorable and faithful service
to his country.
Thank you.
I'm Cmdr. Frank Habley.
Your brother was my executive officer.
Lt. Claire Trifoli, Naval lntelligence.
I would like to offer
my sincere condolences.
Thank you, sir.
Tom and I were good friends for many years.
I'm sorry we never met before.
My brother and I were estranged
for a very long time, Commander.
Yes, I know.
Both of our parents died
when we were quite young.
We lived with our grandparents,
and Tom joined the Navy.
I didn't hear from him for a lot of years.
I know he wanted to make it up to you.
You know, the funny thing is we spoke
just a couple of months ago.
We were going to try to see each other
when this tour was through.
I guess that's not going to happen now,
is it, sir?
If you'll excuse me, sir,
my husband's waiting for me.
I understand.
Lt. Trifoli.
Perhaps we could meet over coffee.
I'd like to tell you about your brother,
about the fine man that I knew.
With all due respect, sir,
I don't think that's necessary.
Good day, Commander.
I'll take you home.
Lt. Trifoli blames me for Tom's death,
I know it.
Did she say that?
She didn't have to say anything.
I saw it on her face.
It wasn't your fault.
We were attacked and you did your best.
-Did l?
-Yes, you did.
And you shouldn't question that.
You saved the boat.
The men who saved the boat
are either dead or dying.
It was my decision to head for the trench.
And it was the right decision.
All right.
I bury Makwana tomorrow in Washington.
I spoke with his mother
for about an hour today.
She's devastated.
Her whole world is turning upside down.
These are hard times...
and there's a whole lot of pain to go around.
I saw that boat, Dizzy.
I saw it as plainly
as I see you standing next to me.
It's a phantom, waiting out there,
posing a danger to our entire fleet.
The Navy thinks I'm lying
to cover up my mistakes.
I believe you, Captain.
And I've always been proud
to serve by your side.
You're my rock, Dizzy.
Thank you for being my friend.
After extensive interviews with your crew...
and a collection
of your mission intelligence...
our initial conclusion
is that you were attacked...
by a North Korean
antisubmarine warfare plane.
Your location was discovered
when you went to periscope depth...
and they launched a torpedo attack
from the air.
This accounts
for the lack of a sonar signature.
We examined your sonar logs...
we tested the equipment...
and we found it to be properly calibrated
and in working order.
So, let me ask you this, Commander:
if you did see a submarine, why didn't you
capture it on the periscope camera?
Lt. Cmdr. Palatonio manned that scope, sir.
I don't know
why he didn't record the sighting.
He confirmed the visual contact
was an unknown class of submarine.
It wasn't Russian, Chinese,
or a Korean design.
It was a class of submarine
we had never seen before.
Because the visibility was poor...
isn't it possible
that you really don't know what you saw?
No, sir.
I know I saw that submarine.
Perhaps its stealth technology...
is something
our intelligence hasn't identified yet.
I hardly think that's possible, Commander.
If the North Koreans had a stealth weapon,
we would know about it.
Commander, we suggest
you take some time for yourself.
Losing your executive officer
has to have been rough.
We realize that you were close friends.
Take your leave, Commander.
Go practice your swing.
Are you relieving me of my duty, sir?
How'd it go, Commander?
Twenty-one years, Dizzy. It's over in a flash.
What did they say?
Their minds are made up.
Two men are dead and a $1 billion boat
is severely damaged.
They don't usually give you
the keys to another submarine.
Your record as a naval commander
is second to none.
Dereliction of duty with deaths involved
is grounds for a court martial.
They want me to take some time off.
I think you should do what they say.
It's out of your hands now.
Launch the alert fighter.
Possible bogeys, bearing 360.
Smoke 1 1, airborne.
Strike copies.
Smoke 1 1, proceed north
and get a visual ID when able.
Smoke 1 1, copy. Negative radar contact.
I want you to be straight
with me, Commander.
I want you to tell me
what really happened out there.
I can't discuss the details
of the mission, Lieutenant.
Court of lnquiry's deliberating...
and I have nothing to say
until the verdict is handed down.
I would have expected
a different response from you.
I lost my closest friend, Lieutenant.
When I sleep, I see Tom calling out to me
from the flames, and I can't reach him.
No matter how hard I try, I can't reach him.
My team has been asked
to break down intel in that area.
Everything points
to your submarine being detected.
And instead of going
into international waters...
you made the decision
to go deeper into the military zone...
right into the Chousan Trench.
I didn't know you were an expert
in submarine tactics, Lieutenant.
Sir, if there would have been
a stealth submarine...
we would have learned about it
long before it was even operational.
I know what I saw.
I'm gonna find out the truth, Cmdr. Habley.
I would expect nothing less. That's your job.
Yes, sir,
and yours is to make the right decisions...
every hour, 100% of the time.
I'm fully aware of my job, Lieutenant.
I've just spent the entire week in front
of a Court of lnquiry being reminded of it.
Yes, sir.
Good day, Commander.
Smoke 11. I've got four,
repeat, four Korean MiGs on my tail.
We are defensive.
Smoke 1 1, Strike copies.
I've got Smoke 21, flight of two,
heading your way.
Smoke 21 flight, burners now.
Smoke 21 radar contact, bearing 360.
We'll be there in a few.
Smoke 1 1, still defensive.
I can't shake this guy.
I need your help.
Smoke 1 1, I'm in a gut defense.
Smoke 21 flight, cut right.
We got you covered. You're cleared off.
I'm hit. I'm hit!
Smoke 1 1, shut down my right engine.
Smoke 21, this is Strike.
We're showing the remaining MiGs
bugging out.
Smoke 1 1, I'm returning to base.
Smoke 21 is trailing one. Engaging.
Smoke 21 is pulling for a shot.
We've confirmed reports
that a US Navy Tomcat...
on routine patrol over the Sea of Japan...
was attacked by North Korean MiG fighters.
The Pentagon stated that US warplanes...
quickly came to the pilot's aid
and shot down one of the attackers.
North Korea claims the US plane
had invaded its airspace...
and is calling the action a provocation
for war and is threatening retaliation.
Lt. Cmdr. Barker.
You've come very highly recommended
from all your previous commanders.
I see you've served on three boats
with tours in the Mediterranean...
the Persian Gulf and the Atlantic.
I've been very fortunate, sir.
I see you also graduated from your
Prospective Commanding Officer course...
in the top of your class.
Looks like you're ready
to command your own boat.
It's been a lifelong dream, Admiral.
I'm sure it has been.
Are you aware of the situation
with North Korea?
Yes, sir.
What I'm about to ask you
isn't gonna be easy.
We need you to be part of a team...
for a covert operation
off the coast of North Korea.
But we need Cmdr. Habley to be the captain.
You want me to be his executive officer?
Yes.
How's it going?
-I'm Lt. Cmdr. Steven Barker.
-Cmdr. Frank Habley.
I know. It's a pleasure.
Have we met?
No. I've actually been following your career
for quite some time.
It's been an inspiration to me.
You know anything about the Commander?
I just know what I've heard.
They say he's a solid officer.
He's seen combat.
His men respect him and they're very loyal.
Some say he's been at sea too long,
that he spooks easily.
The jury's still out on that one.
Well, it's very flattering, Mr. Barker,
but you might want to change your mind.
I'm sure you've heard.
Just bits and pieces.
I can't imagine what you're going through.
A captain has to make hard decisions,
has to trust his instincts.
Navy thinks I got it wrong.
I'm in a tough spot.
Habley's an expert at navigating
those waters and we need his experience.
But if I ask him,
I doubt that he'd agree to another mission.
That's where you come into play.
I've been asked by Admiral Sommerville
to put together a team...
for a Special Projects mission
off North Korea.
I told him I wanted you
to command the boat.
We need you to approach him
as though this was your idea.
You tell him that you've patterned
your career after his...
that you hold him in such high regard
that you want him to command the boat.
I'm about to face a court martial trial,
Mr. Barker.
I don't think the Admiral
would even consider your request.
If you accept my offer,
he's authorized you to command the boat.
He's in a bad place right now.
But we need him.
You're an expert in navigating those waters.
I need you on my team, sir.
Just not going to happen.
Please, think about it.
A lot of your crew are already
on the Poseidon awaiting a captain.
He's still the Captain of the boat.
Officially...
you'll share all command decisions
with regard to the overall mission...
with our full support.
Unofficially, you're to do what's ever
necessary to take control of the boat...
so that nothing impedes the mission...
particularly Cmdr. Habley's
psychological state.
It's never the same after you lose men.
Commander, we can honor those men
with a successful mission.
Look, give me a call either way.
Do you understand your orders,
Lieutenant Commander?
Yes, sir.
By the way, it's an honor
to finally meet you, Cmdr. Habley.
I asked around.
This Barker graduated the top of his class.
Came up the hard way.
He's by the book, with no gray areas.
He seems sharp and confident.
Food's up.
-Here.
-Thanks.
This is wonderful, Becky...
but you shouldn't have gone
to all this trouble.
It's no trouble, Frank. I know
you must get sick of your TV dinners.
So, are you going?
I don't know.
This could be a good chance
for you to prove them wrong.
Can I have the soy sauce? Thanks.
This mission sounds pretty important.
I haven't decided yet.
Frank, we've known you for a long time.
We've never doubted you or your choices.
Every time you and Dizzy go on duty...
I trust you with the man I love
more than anyone in this world.
Thank you, Becky.
I know that Tom would have wanted you
to return.
Yeah. That's what I promised him.
-...or will you do it?
-Yes, sir.
Cmdr. Habley. Welcome back.
-Good to have you on board.
-Thank you, sir.
This is Capt. Galasso
from Naval lntelligence.
-Captain.
-Commander.
Gentlemen, let's get started.
The North Koreans have threatened
to retaliate for this latest incident.
As we speak, they're mobilizing their forces
throughout the Northern peninsula.
We've been tracking a major deployment
in their diesel submarine fleet...
away from their base at Namp'o.
Our mission is to place a tap
on their communications cable...
Ieading away from their submarine base
at Namp'o, here off the Bay of Korea.
The cable runs here, through
the Yellow Sea, to the Chinese mainland.
This is one of the largest shallow areas
of continental shelf in the world.
Cmdr. Habley, would you like
to talk about this a little bit?
I've been through
the Yellow River channel many times.
The depth of the Yellow Sea is shallow.
About 500 feet.
The waters over the shelf are noisy...
so sound waves are distorted
in this coastal zone.
Plus, there's lots of traffic.
These factors should help us avoid
detection and complete the mission.
There's been an increase
in the amount of chatter.
We need a detailed account
of those communications...
and to know where their subs are going.
Your mission tactics are based
on our success during the Cold War...
when we tapped the Soviets' cable.
You're gonna be carrying
a newly developed submersible.
Capt. Galasso will brief us
on that aspect of the mission.
We'll be deploying a remote control
submersible we call the "Crab."
Basically, it's a $5 million video camera
with robotic arms.
Normally, we'd have to use divers for this.
But now we can place the tap with the robot,
bring it back to the submarine...
and leave, undetected.
I can't stress enough
the importance of this mission.
Due to the highly classified equipment
and the files on board...
should you become trapped
by hostile forces...
we can't allow you to be boarded
or to be taken alive.
Cmdr. Habley and Lt. Cmdr. Barker...
will each have keys
to arm a self-destruct timer.
You both must initiate
the command together.
Is that understood, gentlemen?
Yes, sir.
Good luck and Godspeed.
Heard any more about the new XO?
Sommerville's given him equal command
on the mission.
They've brought in a babysitter
because they don't trust me out there.
Barker's a decent enough guy, I'm told,
but he's their man.
Think he'll be trouble?
I just hope he's smart enough
to stay out of my way.
Attention on deck.
At ease. Good morning, gentlemen.
-Morning, Captain.
-Good morning, sir.
All crew present and accounted for, sir.
COB, this is our new XO,
Lt. Cmdr. Steven Barker.
Mr. Barker,
this is Chief of the Boat, Dizzy Malone.
Best COB in the submarine fleet.
Dizzy and I served on three tours together.
Pleasure, sir. Welcome aboard.
Thank you. So why do they call you Dizzy?
Well, sir, when I was in naval flight school,
I suffered from vertigo.
That's not good for a pilot...
so I thought maybe going the other way
might make a better choice.
All right.
XO, why's the entry hatch still open
and the mooring lines attached?
We're waiting for the
Special Projects Team, Captain.
Waiting? We're supposed
to be getting underway.
Yes, sir. I know.
Do you have any idea
when they're supposed to arrive...
or would you like me
to shut down the reactor and wait?
I'll radio Command
and get that information, Captain.
Very good, Mr. Barker. XO has the Conn.
I have the Conn.
Capt. Galasso,
I would have appreciated a heads-up.
We're late getting underway.
Adm. Sommerville kept me longer
than expected with some last-minute details.
You understand.
Capt. Habley, this is Agt. Winters,
special operative with the NSA.
He's an expert in communication
surveillance and he speaks fluent Korean.
Winters. Welcome aboard, gentlemen.
Good to be here, Captain.
This is Lt. Claire Trifoli, Naval lntelligence.
Capt. Habley. My orders, sir.
Trifoli's testing classified equipment.
This is unprecedented.
Admiral Sommerville's orders.
Welcome aboard, Lt. Trifoli.
Thank you, sir.
We should get settled.
Follow me, please.
Ma'am.
Captain didn't seem too happy to see you,
Trifoli. He know you?
We met once before.
These sub commanders are a different
breed.
Never know what to expect.
Stuck for six months in this tube,
make anybody crazy.
Reminds me of summer camp.
Hey, we're lucky.
Forty percent of the enlisted crew have to
share bunks, rotate sleeping schedules.
It's called hot bunking.
Nice.
Navy. "It's not just a job, it's an adventure."
All right, gentlemen, we're underway.
Let's get down to business.
I have the Conn.
Captain has the Conn.
Up periscope.
Approaching dive point, Captain.
XO, submerge the boat.
Diving Officer, submerge the boat.
Submerging the boat. Dive, dive, dive.
Make your depth 150 feet.
Diving to 150 feet.
150 feet, aye.
Deck's awash.
All vents open.
Scope's under.
All ahead full, course 175.
175, Captain.
Sir, we just got word our carrier battle
group has just entered the Yellow Sea.
That's good news. We may need the backup.
Are you expecting trouble?
We're going behind enemy lines, Mr. Barker.
It will be good to know we've got support
if we need to change tactics.
Well, sir, our mission orders are set.
We have our job,
the carrier group has theirs.
Battle is fluid. Things change.
This is a covert mission, sir.
We get in and out
without slamming the door.
That's the idea.
Okay?
"...what's up with you?"
I said, "Not much, you know...."
Hey, Savage. Wonder what kind of slop
they're gonna feed us today.
Hey, guys, you heard about our Captain?
He hears things that go bump in the deep.
He has a sixth sense.
Yeah? Let's just hope
he doesn't see dead people, too.
He's one of the best captains in the fleet.
I'm sorry. Was I talking to you, Savage?
I served with him on the Santa Maria.
Yeah, I'm sure you guys became very close.
I just thought if you wanted to gossip,
you might as well get your story straight.
Well, if word gets out
how big your mouth is...
somebody's gonna put it to good use.
-Come on, guys! Take it easy.
-Take it easy.
-Hey, Savage, get in there, man.
-That's enough.
Get in there, Savage!
Break it up now! Come on!
Come here.
What the hell is going on here, Savage?
Sorry, Chief. It was just a misunderstanding.
I don't wanna see this again.
That goes for all of you.
You think this is a playground?
You're responsible for each other's lives!
-You understand that?
-Yes, Chief.
You watch your tone, Buckley.
Aye, sir.
I should write you both up,
but I'm not going to.
Kitchen duty for two days,
and clean this mess up!
Aye, sir.
Trouble, Chief?
Everything's fine, sir.
The men are just a little on edge.
Can't have our crew
fighting with each other.
No, sir. They understand.
Just the same, put those two men on report.
Sir, I gave them kitchen duty for two days.
Put them on report.
It'll let everyone know that things
are tightening up around here.
And let's find out how ready our fire team is.
Fire drill in one hour.
Captain usually waits
until we're a few days out, sir.
I want my fire team ready.
One hour, Chief.
Yes, sir.
So, how close do we have to get
to the cable?
Well, the Crab has a range
of about 4,000 yards on remote control.
I like to run about half that just to be safe.
Good. The further we are
from the channel, the better.
The North Koreans are running submarine
maneuvers from their base at Namp'o.
They brought out their diesel clunkers?
They might be old compared to ours,
but they still pose a threat.
Remember when we tracked
one of their subs for two hours...
just by listening to the noise
from their toilets?
I figured a lot of them must have had
something really bad to eat that day.
I'm sorry. Tell me, Captain...
I've heard you submariners
get so familiar with the sea...
you can hear some things that we can't.
That's right.
Down here, you become in tune
with your surroundings.
Becomes instinctual.
It's true, your ears get bigger down here.
I can track a surface ship and tell exactly
how many blades are on its propeller.
I don't have much faith
in something I can't see.
You're not a religious man?
I trust science.
Either you have proof or you don't.
The gray areas are just puzzles
that science hasn't solved yet.
Not much mystery in your world.
Guess that's why we have
the most sophisticated equipment onboard.
Amen to that.
I'll trust my computer over anyone.
A machine is only as good as its operator.
Couldn't agree with you more, Captain.
What exactly
is your mission onboard, Lieutenant?
Actually, I'm operating a prototype
that analyzes underwater color gradations.
It also reports the data
on thermocline layers.
I'm really excited about this, actually.
If it's successful,
it will become standard on all submarines.
This is just a drill.
I gave the orders for 1800...
but evidently
the Chief misunderstood those orders.
This is the XO. This is a drill.
I repeat, this is a drill.
Firefighting team,
meet me in the Engine Room, now.
I don't like surprises,
Lieutenant Commander.
Neither do l, sir.
If you'll excuse me.
Enter.
I know what you're gonna say.
Fire drill? Take a seat, Dizzy.
Look, right after the XO saw the fight,
he gave the order to run the drill.
What fight?
It was nothing.
I didn't wanna bother you with it.
Some of the men were blowing off steam
in the galley.
One of the new petty officers, Buckley,
was talking smack about you.
Savage decided to shut him up.
Is this a problem?
No, sir. Just an idiot running his big mouth.
I gave them kitchen duty,
but the XO wanted me to write them up.
He told me you misunderstood
when he wanted to call the drill.
No, sir. Right after the fight,
he ordered me to run the drill in an hour.
Seems Mr. Barker is flexing his command,
and he's got the Admiral to back him up.
You let me know about any other surprises.
Yes, sir.
I'm getting that strange feeling, Dizzy.
It's too quiet out there.
You know what I mean?
Yeah, it's eerie.
I'm getting North Korean
ship-to-ship communications.
Now they're saying something
about floating wreckage.
Sea of Japan.
They're giving longitude and latitude.
Say what it was?
No, hold on, hold on.
What?
They're reporting an oil slick and bodies.
Keep on it.
Sir, I'm getting some
interesting findings here.
I've been tracking these color changes
for the past hour. You see here?
This water displacement's been
continually changing in a zigzag pattern.
What is that, a whale?
It would be the biggest whale
known to man.
There's over 8,000 tons of displacement.
A whale is about 45 tons, max.
Currents in this area
are known to be very strong.
Yes, I'm aware of that.
Should I check with the sonar officer,
see if they reported anything?
No. No, we'll track it from here.
Relaying message from base at Yokosuka...
to carriers and subs in the Yellow Sea.
Urgent relay.
Sir, I just received an urgent message
from the base at Yokosuka.
Read it.
"Japanese Yushio class submarine Osaka
reported missing in the Sea of Japan.
"Search underway. Will advise."
Sir, should I notify the Captain?
No. I have the Conn. I'll take care of this.
This information is not to leave your room.
Is that understood, Roperto?
Yes, sir.
Dismissed.
I have the Conn.
Captain has the Conn.
XO.
Captain?
How did your firefighting team score?
Top marks, sir.
I shaved five minutes off their time.
Good. Helmsman, what's our depth?
-200 feet, Captain.
-Speed?
20 knots, sir.
Slow to 10 knots and turn on my mark.
Come right, 15-degree rudder. Course 180.
Slowing to 10 knots, turning on your mark,
right 15-degree rudder.
Course 180, Captain.
180. Aye.
Sir, why are we heading to 180?
The underwater mountains
in this area are dangerous.
Some of the peaks rise 100 feet or more.
The currents are strong.
We could run right into the mountainside.
We'll bypass this ridge,
go around here, and then turn back.
Diving Officer, make your turn...
come right, 180.
Right, 15-degree rudder.
Course, 180, Captain.
Sir, I'd appreciate...
if you'd notify me of any operational
changes before you made them.
I'm glad we're in agreement, Mr. Barker.
Conn, Sonar.
Permission to play the whale song.
This is my favorite time of the voyage.
It's migration season, Mr. Barker.
We're not the only ones down here.
Sonar, Conn. Proceed.
Captain, unless you need me,
I request permission to go below.
No, I don't need you. Dismissed.
Jeez!
Looks like we got a Japanese submarine
missing, Yushio class.
-Does Captain know?
-I held the message.
Good. We just intercepted
a North Korean report.
Floating wreckage and bodies
in the Sea of Japan.
Is it the Japanese submarine?
We don't know yet.
I don't think we need to bother the Captain
with this.
We need to keep him
focused on the mission.
Excuse me, sir.
Sir, I think you might be interested in this.
Been tracking a massive turbulent wake,
5,000, 10,000 yards off the port side.
The water's been cavitating with bubbles
from something mechanical, like a propeller.
Well, our propellers
will kick up more bubbles...
as we get into the shallows
of the Yellow Sea.
The currents, the sea traffic there,
they play havoc on our readings.
We're in a whales' migration path.
Sir, this displacement is much too large
for whales.
Is this your first sea trials?
Yes, sir, it is.
I think that we should contact
the sonar officer with our reports.
You can't trust these readings...
and I don't want you interrupting anyone
in the control room with this.
-Sir--
-ls that understood?
Yes, sir.
Lieutenant Commander.
Why have we changed course?
The Captain says we're navigating
around some strong currents.
We'll be back on course
as soon as he gets around this area.
You keep a tight leash on him,
Lt. Cmdr. Barker.
I've got him contained.
Message from
National Military Command Center, sir.
"Update on previous communication.
"Missing Japanese
Yushio class submarine Osaka confirmed.
"Attacked and sunk in the Sea of Japan.
"There are no survivors.
Proceed with caution."
-Why wasn't I informed of this?
-I don't know, sir.
Get Roperto in here.
Corey.
Captain?
Roperto, why wasn't I informed
of the original message?
Sir?
The missing Yushio class submarine.
Sir, I gave that message to the XO.
He told me he'd take care of it.
I want every communication
to go through me first. Is that understood?
-Yes, Captain.
-Dismissed, Roperto.
That submarine was sunk within 50 miles
from where they hit us.
Deploy sonar array,
starboard side, maximum range.
Maximum range, Captain.
Just between us, I think the Admiral
has a soft spot for her.
So, when she lobbied for the position
and he agreed...
he thought it would help her
work through her brother's death.
-Her brother?
-Palatonio.
That explains the attitude.
If it was left up to me, I would have
never brought the excess baggage.
XO to the Conn.
Captain?
All communications are to go through me
first. Is that clear, Mr. Barker?
Yes, sir.
I think it's important to know
when an allied submarine is missing.
I'm sorry, Captain. I figured you had enough
to worry about with the navigation.
I was gonna relay the message
as soon as you had a spare moment.
We just received confirmation.
It was attacked and sunk
by unknown forces.
There were no survivors.
Captain, towed sonar array
reaching maximum deployment.
We're rigged for silent running.
I don't think that's a good idea.
I think it's a good idea.
Conn, Sonar. The cable hit something big.
Designate contact Sierra 1. Bearing 050.
Estimated range 1,000 yards.
WEPS, start your track
for a fire control solution on Sierra 1.
Make Tubes 1 and 4 ready in all respects.
Captain, exactly what are you doing?
I don't want them to get the jump on us.
Who? We don't have a positive identification
on any contact.
Conn, Sonar. Sierra 1 has disappeared.
Last known bearing: 059.
She's gone, sir.
COB, turn right. Course, 130.
Make your depth 400 feet.
Course 130. Depth 400 feet, Captain.
400 feet, aye.
Chief of the Boat, cut the sonar cable.
Chief of the Boat, I gave you a direct order.
Did you not understand those orders?
Cut that damn cable.
We have operational orders, Captain,
to stay on course.
And that's exactly what we're gonna do.
Tactical decisions
override operational considerations.
Until we have a positive identification
on that contact, we are to stay on course.
You agreed to those terms
before we left Pearl.
I don't take chances with my crew
or my boat, Mr. Barker.
You shouldn't, either.
What's your best guess?
Could be an underwater sonar buoy
or garbage, maybe some wreckage.
I'm working on it.
Sir, my readings are off the chart here.
There's a massive turbulence
on the starboard side--
We're in a strong current area, Trifoli.
Please just put it in the report.
I'll read it later.
First it's there, then it vanishes.
I have no explanation whatsoever.
Well, find one.
Where you going?
I need a shower.
It's been a really long two days.
Yeah? Well, I need to go with you.
Why? You gonna wash my back for me?
There's 130 men on this boat, Lieutenant.
I think you'll appreciate the escort.
Aye, Captain.
I don't need her talking to any officers.
You keep on this.
Got it.
Hello, Captain. You waiting on the head?
No, I'm just waiting for someone in there.
They been in there long?
Yeah. It was a long shower.
This is Chief of the Boat. No Hollywood
showers. Come on, there, make it quick.
I'll be right there.
Sorry about that, COB.
No, ma'am. I'm sorry.
I didn't know it was you, Lieutenant.
All right. Well, we need to get back.
Sure thing. COB, you need some more
paper towels in there.
I'll have the seaman on bathroom detail
handle that, ma'am.
Actually, would you help me out?
I hate a dirty bathroom.
You know, it's a girl thing.
Why don't you do it?
Okay, Lieutenant. I'll take care of that.
We've got work to do, Lieutenant.
Lt. Trifoli...
I just wanted to say
I served with your brother on three tours.
He was always a good friend.
A man of integrity and a fine officer.
He would've been proud
that you're serving on a submarine.
Thanks, COB. I appreciate that.
Trifoli's dead-on with these findings.
Something displacing over 8,000 tons
has been hunting us for the past five days.
It's that submarine, COB.
They're collecting as much information
about us as possible.
But why haven't they attacked yet?
They want us to lead them
to our carrier group in the Yellow Sea.
I'm not gonna do that.
What are we going to do?
First we have to find
how they evade our sonar.
In the meantime, if they wanna hunt us,
we'll lead them back to the Sea of Japan.
The XO won't approve.
The XO's not running this boat.
I have the Conn.
Captain has the Conn. Quartermaster, aye.
Where we at?
Here, sir.
Diving Officer, make our course 075.
Rigged for ultra-quiet.
-Course 075, sir.
-075, aye.
This is the Captain. Rig for ultra-quiet.
-Repeat, rig for ultra-quiet.
-What the hell is he doing?
We're 40 miles off-course
and headed for the Sea of Japan.
The Admiral was afraid of this
exact scenario. He's chasing a ghost.
Well, I thought you were given
operational command authority.
I was, but the tactical decisions
are still the Captain's.
What do you want me to do?
Physically throw him off the Conn?
I'm picking up a North Korean
ship-to-ship communication.
They have orders to attack any vessel
entering the coastal military zone.
This Captain's jeopardizing my mission.
Up to now I've let you handle things
your way, Mr. Barker...
but now we're gonna do it my way.
You were given explicit authority
by the Admiral...
to relieve Capt. Habley of his duty
if necessary.
I suggest you do so.
With all due respect, sir...
I suggest you never feel the need to
remind me of what my responsibilities are.
This is my boat.
Captain.
Gentlemen.
As of now,
under direct authority from the Admiral...
I am relieving you of your command
for dereliction of duty.
We're being hunted, Lieutenant Commander.
I'm trying to prevent this boat
from being attacked.
Unfortunately, your instincts
won't do this time.
Do you know these waters?
'Cause if you don't know
what you're doing...
these underwater canyons
can tear a boat to pieces.
You are relieved of your command, Captain.
And what if I don't comply?
As your superior officer, Captain,
I'm ordering you to stand down.
You don't know what you're doing.
Do you? We're 40 miles off-course.
So you choose to endanger this boat
and the lives of this crew...
because you don't agree with my command?
We have orders
that aren't open to your interpretation.
You know, you can really tell
a man's character when you give him power.
Captain, we're close to placing a track
on the enemy submarine.
-lf we turn back now--
-Chief of the Watch...
have someone relieve the helmsman.
Captain. Your keys.
Your keys, Captain.
Seems you got your boat after all,
Mr. Barker.
Petty Officer Buckley, take Capt. Habley
below and lock him in his stateroom.
Aye, sir.
If you don't use your instincts,
we're all dead.
I have the Conn.
XO has the Conn.
Let's get back to work, gentlemen.
Diving Officer, left full rudder.
Change our course back to 150 at 20 knots.
Left full rudder, course 150, 20 knots, sir.
Sir, that bearing will take us about 1,000
yards into the North Korean military zone.
I don't have a choice, Murray.
The Captain got us into this mess.
We have to maneuver around these peaks.
I don't know this area well enough
to get us straight through.
Yes, sir.
The keys, Commander.
Wipe that smirk off your face, son.
-No one gets in here without my permission.
-Yes, sir.
You know, I would like to read your report
on all this, Lieutenant.
Lieutenant?
I have a report for Capt. Habley.
I'm sorry, ma'am, but no one's allowed
to see Capt. Habley...
without Capt. Galasso's authority.
I actually just passed Capt. Galasso.
He asked me to give this to Capt. Habley.
It's very important.
Just following orders, ma'am.
That's good to hear.
Would you like me to go get Capt. Galasso?
I'm sure he doesn't have anything
better to do in the control room.
I can give Capt. Habley your report.
It's secret.
Have you been cleared for security,
Petty Officer Buckley?
No, Lieutenant.
Well, then I guess you can't give it to him,
can you?
I'll call Capt. Galasso.
We're rigged for silent running.
You think that's a good idea?
-I guess not, ma'am.
-No, I guess not.
I gave you your chance.
Lieutenant.
You can give your report to the Captain.
Thank you.
Capt. Habley.
Chief of the Boat Malone
gave me your findings.
-Thank you, Lieutenant.
-I'm glad, sir.
Capt. Habley, I need to apologize to you.
I really had no right
to treat you the way that I did.
You don't have to apologize.
I know what you're going through.
Thank you, sir.
This is my latest tracking report.
I've got the submarine 3,000 yards
and closing off of our starboard side.
We've got to find out
how they remain undetectable.
This technology could sink our entire fleet.
Does Galasso know you're gone?
I don't think so, sir.
Better get back.
Lieutenant.
Your brother scored a hole-in-one
with this ball. Called it his lucky charm.
I thought you might like to have it.
Thank you, sir. It means a lot to me.
Let's hope it's lucky for us, too.
Conn, Sonar. Broadband contact.
Designates Sierra 10, Sierra 11.
Both bearings 150.
Sir, it's a North Korean
frigate and patrol boat, speed 15 knots.
I think they're onto us.
How deep is this canyon?
600 feet, sir.
Diving Officer, take us down to 500 feet.
Ten degree down bubble.
Down to 500 feet,
10 degree down bubble, sir.
What's your plan, Mr. Barker?
Well, we're sure as hell
can't outrun those surface ships.
So I'm gonna take us and park us here,
right near this peak.
Look, I don't care how you do it,
you just get us out of this situation.
Sir. Our depth is currently down at 500 feet.
WEPS, load Tubes 2 and 3 with Tomahawks,
seekers on short range.
Mr. Barker.
If they find us with active sonar
in this canyon...
we're gonna be totally vulnerable.
And I wanna be ready
to eliminate that threat.
All stop!
What the hell happened?
Conn, Sonar. We hit a rock surface.
The aft fin is damaged.
Sierra 10 and Sierra 11, bearing 160.
Conn, Sonar. Torpedoes in the water.
Bearing 150.
Range 2,000 yards...
-and closing fast.
-Man battle stations.
Man battle stations.
Conn, Sonar.
Torpedoes made wide turn, now bearing...
250, range 1,000 yards.
Time of impact, 30 seconds.
WEPS, deploy countermeasures.
Diving Officer, bring us back up to 200 feet.
Back to 200 feet, sir.
Chief of the Boat,
you get Capt. Habley up here immediately.
-You got it, sir.
-What are you doing, Mr. Barker?
He's the one who got us into this mess.
You're right.
And he's the only one who can get us out.
Attention on deck.
I have the Conn.
Capt. Habley has the Conn.
Captain, by the way, I was wrong.
We are being hunted.
Where are we?
You can plug into the GPS system
over there.
Yes, sir.
Around this peak here, sir.
Lt. Trifoli, when you get a displacement
reading, we'll lock in the coordinates.
I should have it in just a minute, Captain.
There'll be hell to pay
when we get back to Pearl, Captain.
You better pray we can get back to Pearl.
Conn, Sonar.
Sierra 10 and 11 are within 500 yards...
and closing.
Captain, I've got two Tomahawks
for those ships.
WEPS, lock Tomahawks
onto Sierra 10 and 11.
Targeting Sierra 10 and 11, sir.
We're never gonna make it
out of this canyon before they get here.
I'm parking us beneath the shelf.
When they use active sonar to find us,
we'll have a better chance of hiding.
Captain, sir,
I've got a fix on a large displacement.
It's 1,000 yards to our port side, bearing 160.
That's it.
Galasso.
Can you maneuver that toy of yours
right up to the submarine?
It's a $5 million piece of equipment, Captain.
It's not a toy.
I need you to run a pattern around the sub.
If we can get video footage
of the hull and its propellers...
we can figure out its stealth capability.
That's not what it was
designed for, Captain.
This is the grand slam
of intelligence-gathering.
Imagine what the Admiral will say...
when you bring him information
that can save our entire fleet.
There she is.
Sonar, Conn.
Keep a track on the Crab's position.
Conn, Sonar. Yes, sir.
WEPS, are Tubes 1 and 4 ready?
Breach door on Tube 1 is jammed.
Damn! Get it fixed.
Can you get under the hull?
It's hard to maneuver.
She's got 8,000 pounds of wake
pushing me around.
Those ships have a fix on us.
Sub's approaching 3,000 yards.
I'm almost at my control limit.
-Stay with her.
-Aye.
Conn, Sonar.
Reporting splashes in the water.
Depth charges on the way.
WEPS, make Tomahawks ready
in all respects.
Making Tomahawks ready in all respects.
Targeting Sierra 10 and 1 1.
She's almost home.
All stations, report damage to control.
I'm bringing her back, Captain.
-How long will it take?
-lf everything goes well, a couple minutes.
Lt. Trifoli.
Lt. Trifoli, do you still have
the displacement reading?
It's questionable, sir.
I'm getting a lot of interference.
-Let me just keep trying.
-WEPS, how's that breach door coming?
They're working on it, sir.
I want a firing solution on that sub.
Conn, Sonar.
Four more depth charges on the way.
-I can't wait any longer.
-Just give me a little more time.
It's endgame. WEPS, fire Tomahawks.
Fire Tomahawks.
On their way, bearing 150.
Estimated time of arrival, 30 seconds.
COB, on my mark.
All ahead full and bring us up to 200 feet.
Conn, Sonar. Direct hit!
Quiet! Quiet! It's not over! All ahead full.
All ahead full, Captain.
-Trifoli, do you have a distance for us?
-Yes, sir, 500 yards, starboard side.
Bearing 190.
Are Tubes 1 and 4 ready?
Ready in all respects, sir.
Fire Tubes 1 and 4.
Yes.
Twenty-one years, Mr. Barker...
I've trained and prepared for this.
Doesn't make it any easier.
I understand, Captain.
We did what we had to do.
We laid the hard choice.
Let's get back to work. XO has the Conn.
...and such heroes as Cmdr. Frank Habley...
of the US Navy Pacific Submarine Force.
The Secretary of the Navy
awarded the Presidential Unit Citation...
for extraordinary heroism,
and outstanding performance of duty...
during a recent operation
that remains classified.
Go, Habley!
-To the Commander.
-Hear, hear.
Hello, Commander.
Lt. Trifoli.
Claire.
I come up here almost every day.
I really miss him.
I think about all the times
we could have had together.
I know. I miss him, too.
I heard you're leaving the Navy, huh?
You're retiring?
It was time.
You take care of yourself.
Commander.
It's just Frank now.
Goodbye, Frank.
Claire.
You don't lose that fighting spirit.
We need more people like you.
You stick to your beliefs.
Make your brother proud.
Hey, Frank.
Yeah?
You have time for that cup of coffee?
Sure, I'd like that.
THE END
Subtitles by: Reklame11