Hey! Hey!
- Did you talking to me?
Yes, I was talking to you, freak.
- You want some of this? Come on, motherfucker ...
In America, more than 60% of prisoners
from ethnic minority ...
... Three quarters of all people for drugs cases
in prison are people of color.
I am a sinner, a good life
trying to drive.
THE REVENGE OF CAIN
I hear drums in my head.
I live in a jungle
horn and drums.
The drums speak with me.
The drums come, baby.
Nothing can be done.
My son Ricky sells
drugs to survive.
He is a threat to society.
Not see his own mistakes.
James said in the Bible:
"We know we have passed
from death to life ...
because we love our brothers.
Who does not love staying at the death. "
Death, after this torture ...
... sounds almost like a warm bed with comfortable
I can crawl under the sheets.
It must be nice
to the bathroom just for you to have.
I said "it should be fine ..."
- I heard you. Why are you talking to me, asshole?
Sorry, I just tried to enter into a conversation,
I'm just here.
You say something like what you asked, understand?
So you know the bastard?
Yes, Red. I got it checked.
He has been detained along with my cousin.
Let your cousin strain.
How do you know him?
I know him from the neighborhood, Red.
Sleepy ...?
- Yes.
Try this deal not only by pressing
for you will be shortened.
No, man.
He can be trusted, Red, Red.
I tell you: it is reliable.
Sleepy, how are you?
-T. Bone. Look, matured.
You look good.
- You look good too. What is it?
T-bone, this is my true friend
I was talking about, Redfoot.
What is it?
What's wrong with that husband of yours?
There is nothing wrong with me, asshole
and ask me again.
This is negative, this is not good.
- Shut up and let me see the money.
Yes, let the money.
What did I do, Red?
It's all good.
Perfect.
- Perfect.
Next time, less tense.
Until then, Sleepy.
I'll see you again, T.
What did I do?
What did I tell you, Red?
Okay, okay.
- So I want to hear.
Police! Stand.
- Try not to move.
Do not do it, Sleepy.
Sit down.
Prisoner!
I hope you like it here.
Over there.
I do not know what you've done outside,
but you're in my house.
Your house? By the end of the week
I'm here to say.
I said you should keep your mouth.
Hey, Cain.
Derek said I should give you this.
Redfoot.
The peace is over.
I've already covered.
I'm going to Redfoot.
I want to make sure that
what happened is past.
You know, that shit was just anything for.
Get out, Redfoot.
I said get out.
I don
bag how to solve ...
So, think about it, and let me know.
I've broken your leg so you do not
more drugs in my club can bring ...
so my case in the spotlight.
Tell the men to go home.
You have his legs broken?
More or less.
That was one of Redfoot's men.
To the club?
- Yes.
I gotta tell you something here, Red.
I just want you to bring that mess in my club.
You put my case in the spotlight.
Your club is in my part of town.
And your part of town
ends at my front door.
We need a kind of agreement.
- We have an agreement.
You know, your husband ...?
- Yes.
He's in the alley, he can see all
give details. Okay? Be careful, mate.
He's inside.
Bring your other girls too.
Call me when you're at the door.
Shit! I'll call you back.
Breathing, baby.
Stay there. Stay there!
- Dad!
hold him back.
Welcome to the prison.
I am the director of this facility.
My friend Joe and I want to make sure
this is the last place where you will end up.
You are here because of robberies,
abuse, gang activity ...
Here, you are slaves of the system.
Your choice.
You can be free or you may be slaves.
This house, these walls
and the prison ...
give you a name, your slave name
and number.
The director here, is your boss. He is the one that
tells you when you eat, sleep and shit.
I am the bastard, Fredrick Douglas ...
kick you to the underground,
to the freedom outside these walls ...
to projects,
as "One Unity" and "Pipeline".
Today make a choice.
Live free or die within these walls.
Life is choices ...
... Choose the right one.
He walks and talks ...
"You know."
What's up, Sleepy?
- Hey, Red.
So you're finally here too.
- Man, they had me in jail forever.
Was it so?
For as I've heard that you tried
transferred to be anywhere but here ...
... With me.
Every Thurs not dead, Ed. Why should I
not want to be my size?
I do not know
perhaps because I am sitting here because of you.
But it's just the way, right?
Red, you know I will compensate you sure, man.
- You're going to compensate me? How?
This is my third time, Sleepy.
- What?
You know I've got 203 years?
As if I live long.
The judge thought sure I was a tree, huh?
How long did you have?
23 months.
Why?!
- Red, I was not the one who tackled the money.
Sleepy?
- Yes.
If you are true, and I need out
these walls have done something ...
then you had better
make it happen.
Whatever you want, Red.
Sleepy?
- Yes.
I love you.
- I love you. We have the same ...
I know.
Okay.
I love you.
Red, do not go along ...
Red ...
Troy say that I need his help.
I'm going to Redfoot ass.
One against one.
Troy say that I did for this
A owe.
Tell Derek that I need cash.
Tell him that
for me is worthwhile.
And that's me guilty.
I will collect.
Many of my soldiers are in here.
It's like a family reunion.
Cain!
There's nothing you can do
I fear for hunting.
And I am afraid.
I would have to give up four months
but given the current circumstances, two.
You lose all privileges: music,
recreation, nothing. You may not leave the cell.
Cain, the time you have left
you forced me to one third of your
remaining away life.
If weather does something,
I hope you think about it.
Hey, that girl there?
- She has just been on.
Hey, dude.
- How are you, boy?
Respect.
It's about Ricky.
Do you think I should talk to him?
I was thinking, he has everything
From East to 3rd Street.
And you have everything else.
Why do not you come together?
What?
So you're saying that the negro and I
to do business together?
Only, you lead the
two main areas.
And together you can take the
whole city to take over. Do you understand me?
Listen, I want that best control.
Hi, Mike?
- How are you?
You have everything arranged for his birthday our homie?
You know who I am. I have more women
he knows not what he should do.
Whose birthday?
- My size, Robert.
Oh, yes,
You all go back to childhood.
Make sure you but you're there.
- Definitely.
Where is Ricky?
- In the back room.
Homie ...
What is it?
- You need to come and watch.
Get out.
I told the homie said,
JD that he did not need balls.
Here is my answer
That negro is a barbarian, homie.
It is time that he was on "vacation" is involved.
What do you have today, big man?
Cain, you okay there?
Willie?
Yes?
- Is anybody here with me?
I see none.
You know, you've always tried
me to read the Bible.
Yes.
- Today is the day.
It's a great day for you, Cain
Still play sax
in the recording room?
No ...
The director forbade.
He said he has no manpower had.
For additional activities.
I'll never leave here.
I have accepted.
It is very difficult without my music.
When I play it's like I'm not.
- Yes.
Damn, I miss that.
I gotta go.
See you next week.
I heard that you provide for Cain.
Yes.
- Now is your big chance to impress him.
You have a long time
been held in isolation, Cain.
Every time I let you out,
you get something stupid.
I know you usually defend yourself
as you are the 'big boss' are.
There are plenty of people who think
that if you down ...
that they be famous or infamous, or something.
Why you always keep going to the hole,
year after year.
You know, we have
those children who come here.
Half of them want to know if this
Cain trapped.
They see you as a movie star.
You and I know that your life
is not so glamorous.
If I were to tell you a
chance to make ...
that this does not happen again with these guys from
come close? What if you could help?
What if you can pick up life
you've wasted ...
and used that to save them?
What if I tell you:
you have a chance to save your son.
You hesitate?
What's in it for me?
What do you mean?
- If I use these little boxes pus, what good is this?
The ability to help
is already a reward in itself.
Okay, what do you want?
I want you back Willie gives his saxophone
and to let him play.
You want me to give Willie his saxophone back
and to let him play?
I can not do.
This is a security risk. We do not
enough staff to allow such a thing.
Let him play in the hole section.
There is no safety,
because we are locked 23 hours a day.
That is outrageous.
Well, take it or not.
Note to director ...
It's for the children.
Good. But if there is a blunder ...
then it's over.
Cool.
JD Parker, drug dealer,
armed assassin ...
... and like all of us fed
by power and greed.
But the difference with him is that nobody
more safe when he is on the street.
What is it?
Let's go drink something first with the homies,
and we go to one of your student bars.
Okay, JD, serious, man.
Come with me to Berkeley.
I have that very flat.
Remember that you have paid my tuition fees?
As I said, do not say it to the boys.
I do not want everyone to stop his hand.
You know, one of us must fit the neighborhood.
Come with me, the homies are waiting for us.
What's up, guys?
Is that one of the homies?
Damn no! Come on!
- Happy birthday!
I build a party with my homies
Is that so? Now?
Okay, thanks.
We take a look.
My mate said they have a party at their club.
- Yes?
That bastard thinks he has done Mike,
can get away.
Screw this with him and his homies.
112, what is your emergency?
Only JD.
I do not want the whole gang killing
I want nothing to do.
Come on, why do you feel
really worried about the idiots?
You heard what I said.
Yes, yes.
I've told you so, just JD.
- I told you, Mike!
Drop your weapon.
- Drop your weapon!
Your hands and dare not move around.
I will direct the point.
Your son Ricky has just been tried.
Accessory to murder.
Seven and half years.
Sorry, Cain.
I'm sorry that this is happening right now, but ...
- No, I have my son talk.
We will guide you to the courtyard
there you can talk to him.
But you have to behave.
How you doing, son?
Do not call me son.
What is it?
This all works not with me. What is it?
- Look ...
We are on my site,
We do it by my rules.
Fuck me your rules.
- You're a gangster, huh? What are you doing here?
Listen, do you get the clothes.
Fuck rules.
Who wants to talk, homie.
- Like father like son.
Is that your explanation?
- I do not have time for that nonsense, man.
No.
All you have here is time.
What do you want from me, partner?
Life is choices.
I hope you choose to forgive me.
The easy way or
hard, I do not bag.
Go fuck yourself with.
not do it, Motherfuckers!
Don'ts Jesus
I have already completed this project sucks.
See all those assholes here?
Let them get the discount,
understand what I mean?
You got gum?
My name is Cain.
Yes, I know, the Seas Tones ...
You there, why do you talk so loud?
I'm here, just talking asshole.
Coming from the Seas Tones.
Before?
I always heard the stories
of how crazy you are not there.
From my Uncle. You remember him
perhaps. His name was Big Al.
Yes, I remember Big Al ...
A stupid idiot.
- That's heavy balls, man. He's dead.
Yes, I know.
He was slain during a robbery
at a liquor store next to the police station.
As I said, an idiot.
Apparently you're just as stupid.
The 'Unity One' and 'Pipeline'
are interested in you.
I ...
Sit still, you bastard!
I do not bag for you.
I am here to tell you
what is happening to you ...
if you end up in a cell,
with a nigger like me.
Returning to the dentist?
- Yes.
Say Aaa ...
Open your mouth further open.
Keep in mind that position.
And you, nigger, put your hat off.
Oh, yes ...
Put your hair down.
Hang it forward.
You have that beautiful hair ...
Oh, yeah, that's really beautiful.
Are you part Indian?
- Yes.
What? you have a problem with something, nigga.
I have a crush on you.
We go to your ass, rookie.
I bow but no one, nigga.
What ...?
That's enough.
Stop it. You go back into the cell.
Go back in line.
- Your days are numbered.
Keep moving. Now!
Or I turn this thing around your head!
Do not be afraid, Mama's boy.
Let alone the black.
Yes, I remember your first day here.
You were just like that little fucking bag.
Tall, handsome, black, nice and fresh.
I wanted you to take your ass,
but did not do it.
Now you must reciprocate.
What are you doing?
Back to work.
And hell out of here you two.
Thanks, Cain.
Do not thank me, nigga.
You only care for personal protection.
I just want to serve my time,
and get out of here
I have no interest to me
with someone in order.
It does not work, boy.
Like when I said Thank you, Caine.
Listen, I want you to clean up.
I'll be back.
All this stuff?
- Everything.
What is going on here?
You back, back inside. Hurry.
Clear the mess. Forward.
Back to work.
It looks stupid
You understand me?
Listen nigga, that's why we're here.
Can you help me with?
It is about survival, Homie.
On the side, nigga.
I need two of you together uilskuikens spades.
I can not let you do, brother.
Let's keep the peace.
If someone goes to my son
to balls, there will be no peace.
You're the boss
because I am not.
But if I'm going to do it again ...
I swear to God, it's bad ending
for those who they involve.
Do you understand me?
I heard what you
have done for me, homie.
Listen, man.
You do not save me, nigga,
I'll take care of myself, okay?
You're my son. I make sure that you
nothing happens whether you like it or not.
What, nigga?
You're the reason my mother died.
What are you talking about?
Come on, talk.
Why a life anyway?
A kind of fake Bonnie and Clyde.
A novelty, nigga.
They died together.
And you still alive and remains dead.
And you have slain her.
I thought so
You know me, dick.
I have nothing to say, nigga.
As for me,
My mother and father are dead.
Prisoners, stop that nonsense!
- We are good friends.
I told them to stop.
- Whatever you want, boss.
I must speak Cain.
- Where are you going, slut?
I want to thank you
for me trying to do.
Keep going, man.
How many times have I told you
you should do as I tell you?
Now I see that we have naughty sissy.
I've had visitors last night.
- Last night? From whom?
William ... Big Phil.
Southside? You have slain them years ago.
They're all dead.
I know.
But his still came by.
I've heard you again, Willie.
Cain ...
... I am grateful.
You have brought me back into music.
Another song request?
- Surprise me.
Sure, Cain.
Sure, man.
I know why you're here.
And I know who you are.
You are my sin.
A family that is complete.
My sin ....
... Has finally caught up with me.
Mr. Parker, on behalf of the state are
I am here to represent you.
I think you have to admit guilt.
I'm sorry, Mr.. Parker, I can not understand.
- Thurs here!
Thurs here!
Cain!
I have right now need help!
You have to take.
What?
You do not know yet?
- What do not I?
How long do you have?
- I've got 127 years to go.
I have good news and bad news.
The good news is
that your punishment is significantly reduced.
The bad news is that you
a brain tumor.
What?
It's just one convicted.
He gets what he deserves.
How do you feel, Mr. Skinner.
- How do you think I feel?
I'm Dr. Zeltzer, your neurosurgeon.
What one day.
I have successfully
biopsy samples taken.
But your tumor was
large to remove it.
He was as big as a tangerine.
What are you talking about?
Tell me honestly.
I am sorry to have to say, Mr. Skinner.
The prospects are not good.
You have about six months to live.
I am really sorry.
All favors are, Chain.
I still need one.
I need to talk with my son.
Take it out.
Damn, man. You have to really start
to take your pills.
I take no pills.
No, man.
Because the pills I feel like a plant.
I'd rather feel the pain.
Pain lets me feel alive.
I'd rather hurt.
Good.
What is this?
I gotta talk to you, Ricky.
- I do not talk to you, nigga.
Hey! Who do you think who you talk to?
- That's between me and my father.
If you keep your head,
you learn things a bit.
Of this nigga here?
- Are you smarter?
Certainly not more stupid than this clown.
Yes, you're so smart, you've stumbled here.
- He's still here too.
Yes, and he was also an asshole.
But now he has at least
experience on his side.
Amen.
Sit down.
Listen ...
I'm only half as large as
90% of the prisoners here
I guarantee you that I am the last
person I want to piss you off.
Ricky, you must shut up.
Can I just be alone with my son, please?
I'll wait in the hallway.
What do you say nigga?
You mean nothing to me.
I know. I know I have nothing proposal.
And I know I mean nothing to you,
I know what you mean.
Why do you always talk to me?
- Because there no longer will be. Therefore.
Are you being transferred?
- Yes, I am transferred.
That's good, because then I
no more to do with you.
Where they send you the way to go?
I have a brain tumor.
What?
- I have a brain tumor.
Damn!
Why are you telling me this?
You expect me to pity you do?
- No, not me, nigga.
No, I do not pity.
We are father and son.
During the last days
I have left on earth,
I thought that we normally
call could carry.
And I said all this nonsense
you die for me ..
That shit was true.
No, that shit was true.
I was really dying for you.
I was not for you.
I was dead to me.
I was dead for my family.
You're right.
That I earned.
God works in mysterious ways.
I had a lump in my family.
So God sent me "blessed" with cancer.
So God's ways, son.
You get back what you provided.
What are you doing?
Listen, brothers ...
God will forgive you everything ...
you if you repent from your heart.
It must come from your heart.
The pain from your heart.
And the conversion must also come from your heart.
And he will not just forgive.
So our man, just.
You make a mistake on this planet,
, and connect you through life.
Do you understand me?
- Yes.
Son, I'm not saying I
do not know what love is ...
I do not know if I ever have loved someone.
But ...
... I feel something in my heart for you.
I'm a sissy, I'm not saying I do yours.
I say something in my heart I feel for you.
Do you understand me?
- Sure, Dad.
Cain?
Here is the book you've asked me.
BRAIN TUMORS
Cain, everything okay there?
Willie?
- Yes?
Can you play something quiet today?
Yeah, right.
Sure.
Smoke there is only one.
- Thanks.
Have you been removed from the hole?
Yes, the director has given me one hour with you,
but I had some company with you.
- That's right.
Does it hurt?
Yes, it takes a while before the pain goes away.
Did she tell you how long you have left?
Long enough.
Son, I want you to promise me something.
Is your sentence here.
And promise me you'll never come back.
And you also ensure that others
not reach here.
Screw this with the elite.
Cain ...
- Yes.
I need a favor.
- For Harlow?
I see that you can handle right now.
The favor ... I'll collect.
- What favor?
I'm not talking to you, nigga.
- Watch what you say, pal.
So that's the deal?
- Yes, that's about it, what do you doing?
My favor.
- Let us know.
I need help
to "stuff" to get inside.
What "stuff"?
Same as always.
I'm 23 hours a day in solitary.
How do I get your stuff in here?
That's not my problem.
When you asked me for help, I asked
not "How do I manage that?"
I just did it.
- I hear you, homie.
You see, loyal soldiers.
So they are gone.
I understand, it continues,
but then we're done with that bastard.
With everything.
- Do it, nigga.
Cain, you have to take medicines.
You need a lot of pain.
- I take no medication.
I know you do not want to take,
but you have to take them.
Shut up.
Cain, the medications are not
only for pain relief.
Raise your hand against me.
Get out.
I take no medication
Call monitor so I can get away.
Security!
The blood of Jesus.
- How you doing, Dad?
Tell me, son?
- What did the doctor say?
It does not matter.
The Lord will never give
if you can bear.
Remember that.
The life I lead,
is the life I was given ...
In the name of Jesus.
Amen.
You know son, this is a blessing in disguise.
This is God's way to allow me
in contact with my son to come.
A band to build.
I understand that.
- Pray with me?
Yes, we can pray together.
Your hand ...
Lord Jesus ...
Thank you for your time
I gave up on this planet ...
a bond with my son to build.
In Jez ...
- Dad!
Dad!
Guard!
He's under a heavy anesthetic.
- How long do you think this will take?
It's hard to say,
if and when he wakes up.
He should at least put continue
to take his medication.
Okay.
They told me you were the bastard in here.
- And you are?
The bastard out.
- That means nothing to the asshole in here.
What if me and my boys
outside triple your profit?
As for myself I take away from some,
but a little ...
Because I want that in here
try to be the bastard.
I thought you were looking for
a bastard who can arrange this for you.
My asshole.
The session today was good, man.
I think we have approached the children well.
A life of crime is real shit man.
Going to end up in such a place like this,
Hellegatsplein this kind.
Joe ...
I need a favor.
Give this to my soldier, Derek.
Cain is at your visit.
Cain sits in solitary.
He has asked the director
or you can join the pipeline project.
So you can meet.
Brother Cain ...
What's wrong?
I want someone to ass.
But it does not have to do with you.
Who are we?
And why?
JD Parker. I'll tell you no details
but nobody fucking with my son.
I do business with JD.
- Not anymore.
Is that so?
So my word is nothing now?
Your word for me
what does not.
Therefore you had to come alone.
I thought that a card would have to choose.
Do not be like I did not protect,
do you remember?
You run the drug trade because I allow.
But JD ...
is a dead guy.
And try not to turn ...
do not you dare to think that a nigga like me
permission to ask a nigga like you ...
to get something done.
It's time for some to do.
- For sure.
Cain, the bastard of a son, Derek,
I want them all dead.
Damn, homie, Cain
something like a legend here.
You are about to become history.
take that motherfucker to graze. And hell out now.
Got it?
I warned you, nigga,
watch what I do with that sissy.
Do you understand me?
Let me not to fool.
Spread the word.
- Yes.
Yes, I'll tell you about.
- Get out of here.
How did my deal for you?
- Better than expected.
I got 25% for you.
Sit down.
You know what? Let 20% of it.
Consider it a favor.
And give me the opportunity
to do business with you.
This is the plan what we're doing.
You may have Ricky.
But Cain, that crazy dick will come after you.
Do not worry about.
We need this in the right way.
Do you understand me?
Cain has some followers here
and war is bad for business.
I control where and when.
You take Ricky to your account
I assume that a gorilla Cain on me.
You and I are going together with money.
That is agreed.
Cain, I need to know the truth.
Everyone is silent on this,
but I know it's going to come.
I hear drums in my head.
I live in the jungle when I hear the drums.
The drums talk to me.
The storm is coming, baby.
And there's nothing you can do about.
Nothing.
And I'm the one who has the most to lose.
We are talking about my son.
We are still talking about my son.
I know you like
the palm of my hand.
And I know there is nothing
you would not do for your son.
Includes self sacrifice.
You can not do that.
- You might be put aside.
This is a prison, Cain.
Some of the most dangerous criminals
walking around here. We can not do.
That JD ...
... Is a killer.
I see it in his eyes.
You know what that means.
I have to kill JD.
- No. No.
Yes.
- That will not happen in this prison.
This is exactly the kind of behavior
so you back straight the hole goes.
Would you do what I should do?
Would you return?
I try very patient with you again.
- Can I go?
... I know how you look at me
as those who sit in the tubs ...
and when the morning brings me the news,
your unrequited love.
About Who are they?
- His name is JD.
Is there another
way to solve this problem?
Not when the lives of
my son is on the set.
What about you to me?
- I thought we were headed a different direction.
We read the Bible, pray and
trying to save another's soul.
I do not want no bad reason.
It's not that I'm scared or anything.
You're one of the hardest
I know gangsters.
I know you're not afraid.
You've grown.
God has a route for you sometimes secretly approaching.
Follow me as a better leader.
I must do this.
Do you have that thing for me?
I'll handle it.
What now?
- You tell me.
How you've slain my friend?
- I have not slain.
I tried to say that asshole.
- You should have done.
The only thing I think
is to take your address.
Ricky, I'm so glad to see you.
I can think of nothing else.
Money, freedom, hookers ...
... To nowhere, just to you.
- I have not slain your partner.
What happened, happened. We had
Mike does not like you had not been murdered.
Right now, I am not interested
what brought us here.
The only thing I care about is that we are here.
there should you worry about it.
Look, nigga. I had to say that homie
you wait until we had spoken.
But he suddenly began to shoot. I wanted you
partner is not dead. I just wanted to scare you.
Let's see how fast you come here.
What you want, nigga,
but I tell you once thing.
Your tired ... your father ...
and your fucking kids ...
assist your coffin nigga,
and watching bloody dead body.
That is the key you just
have turned the lock.
What are you doing here, Brenda,
- It's about my son.
He is in prison, Cain.
He's here with you.
I'm sorry to hear that.
I want you it is quite capable
while sitting here, Cain. Please.
I'm just a sinner who
righteous living.
Cain ...
You're a man with authority.
You're dangerous, Cain.
You're a 'boss'
No one dares to come on your path.
Tell me ...
you're still that person?
I see what I can do.
Remember me
I went to Arizona?
When I left I was pregnant.
I carried our baby.
- What?
He is your son, Cain.
- Our child?
It's your blood, Cain.
He is the only thing I have, Cain.
I want you to fit him, Cain.
Please.
His name is JD.
His name is JD Parker.
Cain ...
Please.
Your buddy Derek is dead.
Something is happening with your son.
Troy thinks he can fuck with those bastards,
and then it can get away.
What are you talking about?
- It's none of your business.
You get restrictions.
Go back to your cell!
Sissy.
I'll show you something.
Cain!
Brenda, your mother ...
... Came to visit me.
You know my mother.
- I've known her for years.
You are my son.
And you are my son.
Pa.
It's not your fault.
Let my sins on my
sons sent down, God.
You are brothers.
Dad!
After the death of Cain, his next Ricky
father's wishes and changed his lifestyle,
ended his vicious circle
drugs and gang violence.
Now he stands at the head of the Pipeline
project by helping children at risk,
and makes a positive impact
the community.
JD changed his life in prison and
was previously released for good behavior.
He is currently working with Ricky all mentor
Pipeline youth gang intervention project.
Prison Director Dean continues his fight against
gang violence in the Pipeline and Unity One programs.
Ricky and JD and his new partners,
their success continues year after year, to grow ...