Bombay, 2006
Jamal Malik is one question away
from winning 20 million rupees.
How did he do it?
A: He cheated
B: He's lucky
C: He's a genius
D: It is written
Good evening! (speaks Hindi)
Welcome to "Who Wants To Be A Millionaire"!
Are you ready?
Yes.
Please give a big round of applause
to a very first contestant of the night
Jamal Malik from our very
own... (speaks Hindi) Mumbay!
Hello, let's play.
Smile, you'll be fine.
Name.
Motherchud, name!
Jamal Malik.
You have a name. Good. Stop crying.
Thank you. Thank you. Thank you very much.
So, Jamal...
tell me something about yourself.
I work in a call-center
in Juhu. - Good.
A phone basher..
And what type of call-center should that be?
XL5 mobile phones.
So you are the one who calls me up
every single day of my life
with special offers, huh?
No, actually I am an assistant.
An assistant phone basher?
And what does an assistant
phone basher do exactly?
I get tea for people and...
Chaiwalla. A chaiwalla.
Well, ladies and gentlemen,
Jamal Malik... (speaks Hindi)
chaiwalla from Mumbay,
let's play "Who Wants To Be A Millionaire?"!
So, has he confessed yet?
Except his name I could not get
anything of him.
You have been here the whole bloody
night, Srinivas. What have you been doing?
He's a tough guy.
A little electricity will
loosen his tongue, give him.
Yes sir.
So, were you wired up?
Mobile phone or a pager?
Or coughing accomplice in the audience?
Or microchip under your skin, huh?
The chip is not here.
Not here? Ok, leave it.
It's hot, and my wife is giving me hell.
I've got a desk full of murderers, rapists,
extortionists, bomb bandits, and you.
So why don't you save us both a lot of time
and tell me how you cheated.
I'm done sir.
Now listen.
Hello!
He's is unconscious,
chutiya. What good is that?
How many times have I told
you, you should once...
I'm sorry sir.
(Speaks Hindi)
Now we'll have Amnesty International here
peeing in their pants about human rights.
Sir I was thinking...
Get him down, tidy him up please.
For God's sake!
Sir, what if he did know whe answers?
Professors, doctors, lawyers,
general knowledge-wallas
never get beyond 60000 rupees.
He's on 10 million.
What can a slumdog possibly know?
The answers.
I knew the answers.
Slumdog Millionaire.
Jamal, catch it!
Jamal, it's yours!
How did you manage to drop
a sitter like that, damn it?
Private ka-land!
Catch him!
The dogs are coming! Run!
If the planes won't kill you, we will!
Hey brother!
Sorry!
I'm very sorry.
Oh shit, it's Mum.
You want me to wallop you to death, huh?
Brother, leave these two to me.
Come on.
Athos.
The Three Musketeers.
Repeat it!
"You have sent for me, Sir?" said Athos.
Ah, here come our very own musketeers.
Thank you for gracing us all
with your presence.
Porthos!
Well, open it, Salim.
Stop doing that and open the book, Jamal.
Athos?
So... Mr. Malik
the man who knows all the answers.
Talk.
(Speaks Hindi) Talk!
So Jamal, are you ready for the
first question, for 1000 rupees?
Yes.
Not bad money to sit on a chair
and answer a question.
Better than making tea, no?
No. Yes. No.
No? Yes? No? Is that your final answer?
So remember. You have three lifelines.
Ask the audience, fifty-fifty
and call a friend.
So the first question, for 1000 rupees,
here we go.
Who was the star in the 1973
hit-film "Zanjeer"?
I'm in trouble, here...
Here... Money. Take the money...
Get out of there, Jamal.
Prakash wants a big one.
Not finished.
Stop your time-pass boys. This is urgent...
It's a shy one...
and since when there is
a time limit on a crap?
This is borderline kid. Get a move on...
Since there was a customer waiting,
that's when Jamal!
Give me the money back!
Give! I'll go elsewhere.
Bloody idiot.
You just lost me a bloody customer.
Amitabh's helicopter!
That's Amitabh's helicopter!
Amitabh!
Amitabh Bachchan!
Salim, open it!
My Amitabh sir!
Move, move! Out of the way!
Please wait, I am coming for you!
Amitabh sir, please give me your autograph
You've got it now have you?
Amitabh's autograph?
That was my autograph!
Amitabh gave it to me!
I'll never get another!
He offered a good price, so I sold it.
But it was mine...
A, Amitabh Bachchan.
Guess what, you're right.
You just won 1,000 rupees.
You don't have to be a genius.
I knew it was Amitabh Bachchan.
Like I said, you do not have to be a genius.
He's the most famous man in India.
A picture of three lions, as seen
on the national emblem of India.
What is written underneath?
A: The truth alone triumphs
B: Lies alone triumph
C: Fashion alone triumphs
D: Money alone triumphs
What do you think, Jamal?
The most famous phrase of our country.
Do you like to call a friend?
Ask the audience.
Who'd put him out of his
misery, ladies and gentlemen?
My five-year old daughter
can answer that question,
but you couldn't.
That's strange for a millionaire genius.
What happened?
Your accomplice sneaked out for a piss?
The inspector is asking something.
How much is panipuri at
Dharisha store on Chowpatty?
What?
Panipuri. One plate. How much?
- 10 rupees.
- Wrong.
15 since Diwali.
Who stole Constable Varmy's bicycle
outside Santa Cruz station last Thursday?
You know who that was?
Everyone in Juhu knows that.
Even five year olds.
Congratulations, Jamal.
You just won 4,000 rupees.
A 16 thousand rupees.
Religion. Interesting.
In depictions of God Rama he is
famously holding what in his right hand?
Run!
Salim, Jamal! Run!
They're Muslims, get them!
Get a move on! Come with us!
Hey, get lost!
Are you deaf? I said piss off!
Come with us.
I wake up every morning wishing I did
not know the answer to that question.
If it wasn't for Rama and Allah...
I would still have a mother.
A bow and arrow.
Final answer?
Final answer.
Computer, (speaks Hindi) D (speaks Hindi)?
You just won 16000 rupees.
Well done, my friend.
Time for commercial break.
Don't go away now.
You got lucky, huh?
If I were you I'd take the money and run.
You're not going to the next one.
Piss off!
She'll have the security guard on us!
Let her in.
She could be the third musketeer.
I'm the elder in this family now,
and I say, she's not coming in, okay?
In any case...
We don't even know the name
of the third bloody musketeer.
Salim?
Come over here.
Where's your mother?
Your father?
I'm Jamal.
This is my brother Salim.
I'm Latika.
You can sleep here if you want.
Thank you Jamal.
Welcome back to "Who
Wants To Be A Milionaire?"
Our contestant, Jamal Malik,
call-center assistant from Mumbay,
is on 16 thousand rupees,
and has already used only one
lifeline, ask the audience.
So my friend, you're into serious money.
Shall we play?
Yes.
The song "Darshan Do Ghanshyam" was
written by which famous Indian poet?
A: Surdas
B: Tulsidas
C: Mira Bai
D: Kabir
It's hot, huh?
The way he's taking care of
us, he must be a good man.
Must be a bloody saint
We're not allowed to talk to the others.
Why?
If we get seconds, then
he really must be a saint.
Very good, Arvind. Very good.
Laughing at me. I'll kill you.
Hey, get off her.
Don't touch me!
You fat bastard!
You big tree!
Punnoose, I think you've found your dog.
Okay, time to go. Get to work.
Think you're here for a picnic?
What do you think this is, a holiday?
And what are you laughing at?
Give me that.
Shut up!
Brother Salim.
What's up little brother, you got a problem?
Hey take her. She's yours today.
I don't want her.
Take her. It's for your own
good. Babies earn double.
She said she doesn't want her.
Shut it Jamal!
Take her now or i'll drop her.
Keep her crying, and you'll earn triple.
Come on! Get to work!
We'll use the hottest ones.
Chillies on his willy!
I'll get you back!
Go back to sleep all of you!
Very good. I am happy.
He's ready. - I'm ready as well.
Come on, move the lamp.
Okay.
Bring Jamal over.
Listen, kid. It's decision time.
You want the life of a slumdog
or the life of a man, huh?
A real man. A gunfighter.
Your destiny is in your hands, brother.
You can be like me or...
Understand?
I understand.
Go. Get Jamal.
I just need Maman to like my
singing, and we're in the money.
Big money, Latika.
And then what? Can we stop begging?
Begging? Are you kidding?
We'll live in a big house on Harbour Road.
You, me and Salim. The Three Musketeers.
Harbour Road. Really?
Yes.
In the moonlight...
You and me.
You'll dance with me won't you?
I hope you sing better than you dance.
It's my turn. - Sing well.
So this is it huh, brother?
The good life here we come.
Athos.
Porthos?
When I say
It's time to get professional.
What? Really?
First, let me hear that song...
Darshan to Ghanshyam.
That's my favourite.
Fifty rupees.
Now I'm a professional, what can I do?
Cheeky little bugger.
Here you go.
Jamal, go. Run!
Hold on! Catch them!
Get the torches! Get them!
Latika, run!
Come on, Latika! Grab his hand!
What happened, what happened?
She let go!
We've got to go back,
brother. We've got to go.
Go back and we're dead.
Have you gone mad?
He was going to take your eyes out!
With a spoon.
Don't worry about her. She'll be fine.
She always is.
Surdas.
Surdas?
Surdas (speaks Hindi) final answer?
Yes.
Guess what, you're right!
Blind singers earn double you know that?
What happened to a girl?
They blinded her too?
They had other plans.
Well it took me a long time to find out.
Got to let it go.
Come on.
Where? - I'm starving.
Get up!
So is it your Dad's train then?
Is this heaven?
You are not dead, Jamal.
What is it?
Some hotel huh?
The Taj Mahal is considered the
finest example of modern architecture.
...was completed around 1648 using
the labour force of 20'000 workers.
In 1980 it became a UNESCO
World Heritage Site and was cited...
Official tour guide.
Please take off your shoes
Please, please.
What time is the next tour?
We are on tight schedule.
We have to see the Red
Fort this afternoon.
VISITORS ARE REQUESTED TO COLLECT RECEIPT
No, I... - Please, would it be possibló
to show us up round now?
Obviously we understand that it
costs more for just the two of us.
But of course madam!
Please follow me.
The Taj Mahal was built by Emperor Khurrama
for his wife Mumtaz, who was the
maximum beautiful woman in the world.
Then when she died, the emperor
decided to build this five-star hotel,
for everyone who would
like to visit her tomb.
But he died in 1587 before any of the
rooms were built, or any of the lifts.
But this swimming pool as you can see was
completed on schedule in top class fashion.
Is says nothing of this in the guide book.
The guide book was written by a bunch
of lazy good-for-nothing Indian beggars.
And this lady and gentlemen
is the burial place of Mumtaz.
How did she die?
A road traffic accident. - Really?
Maximum pile-up.
I thought she died in childbirth.
Exactly sir. She was on the way
to hospital when it happened.
Ready?
Smile.
Shoes! American brands!
This, Mr David, is the biggest
Dhobi Ghat in the whole of India.
That's amazing.
Come on, take a real good look at this.
They say that every man in Uttar Pradesh
is wearing a kurta that has been
at least washed once out here.
Move it around! Pit-stop's god
speed! Schumacher got style!
There are the cows or are those
buffalos... What are those over there?
Oh, shit.
What the hell happened here?
Ok. Hold it!
You've got the insurance don't you?
Are you ok?
You wanted to see a bit
of real India? Here it is!
Well, here is a bit of
the real America, son.
("Money")
Oh, yes, yes! Jesus...
Here.
On an american 100 dollar bill
there's a portrait of
which american statesman?
A: George Washington
B: Franklin Roosevelt
C: Benjamin Franklin
D: Abraham Lincoln
Pay or play, Jamal?
You decide.
Oh god he's looking at the
camera. He hasn't got a clue.
This is gonna be a walk away. Stand by.
No, he's gonna play with him first.
Jamal?
Get a lot of 100 dollar bills
in your in your line of work?
A minimum tip for my services.
Oh, now I know why my
cellphone bills are so high.
They tip the chaiwalla
with 100 dollar bills.
It's C. Benjamin Franklin.
You're gonna play, huh?
I think I've just had, hadn't I?
So you exactly have C, right?
Who's on 1,000 rupee note?
I don't know.
You don't know?
Ghandi is he.
Oh, I have heard of him.
Don't get clever
or I'll get the electricity out again.
Look.
They didn't ask me that
question. I don't know why.
Ask them.
It's funny, you don't seem
like you're interested in money.
By the fact you have...
one million rupees!
Explain the 100 dollar bill.
Bombay had turned name to Mumbay.
Why don't you understand?
A girl lived here. As tall as me perhaps.
Her name was Latika.
Don't know anyone of that name.
Two chicken burgers, two
fries, one diet cola, one coke!
One mineral water!
Shimla.
I'm going to Chowpatty, ok? Wanna come?
For god's sake, you've got some disease?
You're forcing back to this shithole.
We leave our friends, a good life,
lots of money. For this?!
We came back to find her.
You did. I don't give a shit about her.
Plenty of pussy in Bombay for Salim.
Oh yes!
You should come back to
the Cages on Saturday night,
instead of ghost searching
for your lost love.
I'm going to Chowpatty.
I'm going to Chowpatty!
There are 19 million
people in this city, Jamal.
Forget about her.
She's a "stree"(? = young
indian female dancer).
Greetings, Sir.
Blessings be unto those
who do good for others.
Dollars. How much?
100. - So you take me for a fool.
Honestly. I swear on my mothers soul.
What's on this note? Whose picture is it?
There's an old man...
He's bald on top with long
hair on the sides, like a girl.
Benjamin Franklin.
So you're a big guy now, Jamal.
I'm happy for you.
I'm sorry...
You got saved my friend. I wasn't so lucky.
That's the only difference.
Arvind, I'm trying to find...
You owe Maman. Stay away.
He never forgets.
I owe Latika.
She's alive isn't she?
More than alive. She's on Pila
street. They call her Cherry.
Thanks.
I'll be singing at your funeral.
So, is it her or not?