#  When l met you in the restaurant #
#  You could tell l
was no debutante #
#  You asked me what's
my pleasure #
.t A moyie or ft meftsure? .t
#  l'll have a cup of tea #
#  And tell you of my dreaming #
#  Dreaming is free #
#  Dreaming #
#  l don't want to live on charity #
#  Pleasure's real or is it fantasy? #
Hey, check this out.
Everywhere l go, people
totally lose it.
l'm Victoria English...
sorority princess of
South Beach University.
And, oh, yeah, this year l've
gotta makeover a bunch...
of clueless freshmen into
Gamma Gamma girls.
Oh, look at this
Shakira wannabe.
See what l mean?
She's taking a freaking
cab instead of a limo.
Not hot.
See, Gamma Gamma
sorority is in a contest...
to become FHM Magazine's
hottest sorority in the country.
Everyone wants to go to
South Beach University.
A couple of years ago, they
Iet unhot people in here...
and things haven't been the same.
l guess i'll just have to put
a blonde wig on this one.
Daddy, stop the car here.
- But there's a spot up front.
- Dad, this car is embarrassing.
l don't want people to
think that l'm poor.
Well, honey, you are poor.
Look at this little minx.
This is Kristen Ass.
lf l'd have known she'd
come in that car,
l would have never
Iet her pledge.
Excuse me.
So there you have it.
A mission to turn the ''wannabes''
into the ''be wanteds.''
Should be fun.
Smell that?
That, my friends, is the
smell of opportunity.
Fresh, un-tapped poon tang.
Did you just say poon tang?
l mean, that's why they
call them freshmen!
Because their coochies
are fresh for all us men.
What's going on?
- Hello, ladies.
- Hi.
Welcome to South Beach.
l love fresh coochy!
Victoria will be here in 45
seconds, ladies, so smarten up.
#  Whoa, whoa, whoa #
#  Got somebody, she's a beauty #
#  Very special, really and truly #
#  Take good care of me,
like it's her duty #
Every year, school starts
when l pop out of my limo
and see my shadow.
But l can't see my shadow
because l'm so thin.
Gamma Gamma pledges
ready for inspection.
People say l shouldn't
torture my pledges.
But l say, who says
Iearning can't be fun?
Sweetie, do you have
any idea who l am?
You're Victoria English.
And what do l do here?
You're the president of the
Gamma Gamma house?
And the ultimate role model
for every college girl
on the face of the earth.
Starting to like this one.
Wait. Whose top is that?
- Mine?
- No.
Whose top is that,
gamma pledge?
Dolce and Gabbana.
Ma'am, my top is Dolce
and Gabbana, ma'am.
- It's Dolce and Gabbana.
- Don't you forget it.
What the hell kind of
nail color is that?
- It's ''cherries in the snow. ''
- So last week.
Suck it off, Gamma pledge.
l will, ma'am.
You. The shoes.
l saw those on sale
Iast week, didn't i?
No. My mom sent 'em to me.
Those shoes are expired.
Totally unhot.
Two out of three,
this is a disaster.
- Morgan?
- Yes, Victoria? Ma'am.
Please explain to these jackasses
what's at stake this year.
Listen up, ladies.
This year, FHM Magazine will be
selecting the hottest sorority
in the nation to be
featured on their cover...
and we are one of
five finalists.
And l'm not gonna let a bunch
of clueless pledges stand...
in between me and the number
one spot in the country.
- Is that clear?
- Yes, ma'am!
Victoria, we may have
a little problem here.
What?
''This year, the winning sorority
must embody diversification.''
ln other words, geeks, nerds,
scientists--everybody.
Problem solved.
We'll just pledge some geeks.
We will?
And when we win the magazine
cover, let the fun begin.
Gamma Gamma Girl group hug!
All right, that's enough.
l like the love...
but let's not get all Ellen
DeGeneres about it, okay?
lt's so good.
- Kristen?
- Gloria.
Hi. What are you doing here?
Surprise!
- Mr. Haas.
- Oh, hey, Gloria.
- Hi.
- How are you? Nice to see you.
Whoo!
How are you doing?
- l'm great.
- What is this?
Well, l ran into Gloria's mom a
while back, and she mentioned...
she was coming to South Beach,
so l made a few phone calls...
and we arranged for
you two to live together.
- Bingo!
- Wow, thanks, dad.
- Yeah, unexpected.
- Full of surprises.
Well, l know what good
friends you two are.
- Were.
- Like, in the ninth grade.
You two get reacquainted...
l'll go get the rest
of the bags, okay?
- Sure.
- l'll be right back.
Are you sure this is
what you really want?
l don't understand why you
have to live in the dorms...
when we live in Coral Gables.
Oh, you don't understand.
'Cause l don't understand why
you had to park your car...
in someone else's garage.
And by car, l mean cock.
- Mommy, what's a--
- It's a rooster, honey.
Kathy, what do you
want me to say?
l keep telling you l'm sorry.
Yeah, you're sorry all right--
a sorry excuse for a husband.
Kids, mommy's going
away to college.
And you know why?
Daddy decided to sleep with some
little tramp from his office!
Well, see you Thanksgiving.
- Bye, kids.
- Bye. Love you.
Hey, football, huh?
Anybody up for a gangbang?
Kathy, Jesus Christ!
- Victoria.
- Baby Dick, l missed
you so much.
Not as much as l missed you,
my little English muffin.
This is my new
boyfriend in training.
He's already progressed
to week three.
Wow.
And, ladies, he's my property,
so hands and eyes off.
Well, you can look.
Now go and be a good boy,
and go get my luggage.
lt's been on the sidewalk
for ten minutes.
Right away, princess.
Oh, and Baby D?
Gamsie needs to go potty.
Okay.
Thanks, bitch.
Hi there! l'm Kathy!
l'm your roommate!
Well, come here, you!
Oh, it is so good to meet you.
We are gonna be
BFF, you and me.
- Maxine. Nice to meet you.
- Ooh, who's the hottie?
- That's my daddy.
- Dirty son of a bitch.
Hey, roomie, do you know where
l could find some pot?
- No.
- Ludes?
- Meth? Lsd? Pcp? Crack rocks?
No!
Well, looks like l'm gonna
have to kick it old school.
Ugh!
- Here, let me help you unpack.
- No, not that bag!
Hey, good idea. Sugar buzz!
This fool's lucky he didn't
walk into Gamma.
His pee-pee would've
Ieft on a stretcher.
Don't forget to call every night.
l promise, Mom. Goodbye.
Keep an eye on that girl.
l think she might be disturbed.
Mom!
l'm so sorry about that.
You know what moms are like.
Yeah. Drunks with guns.
- l'm Babs.
- Tonya.
Open!
Um, hi there. l think we
found your roommate.
Yeah, we can't pronounce her
name. It sounds very exotic.
- Uh, Senagarvar--
- Senagarvarapoopoo Ghandasini.
Oh, PooPoo! That's cute.
Very nice to make the
acquaintance to you.
'Sup? Monique. l like your style.
Hi, l'm Maxine.
'Sup, Maxine?
l'm Kathy, and l like to party.
Good to know.
l'm here studying music.
Word, homey.
l'm just here to get even
with my husband.
l'm gonna nail as many
guys as possible.
l'm just here for general
studies, for now.
Hey, you girls wanna check
out my new boob job?
Doctor says they should
realign themselves...
and the scarring should go
down in a few months.
l'm sure to land some man meat
with these milk bags, huh?
When living together, blondes
and brunettes will always fight.
You look a lot different than
the last time l saw you.
My solution? Let the blonde win.
No, l mean you look good.
Yeah.
Listen, let's just be clear.
We're not in ninth grade
anymore, okay?
We're different people now.
At least l am.
So let's not pretend we're gonna
be college buddies, okay?
Just because you got yourself
some new clothes,
and bleached your teeth,
and fixed your nose.
l didn't get my nose fixed!
God!
Level-one, level-two,
Ievel-three, level-four.
One, two, three, four.
How many Red Bulls
did she drink?
About the same as
me--nine or ten.
One, two, three, four.
One--ooh!
No-no-no-no-no-no! PooPoo.
No, honey. That's a vibrator.
Without my guidance...
girls look for love in
all the wrong places.
lt's called the Platapussy.
What is a Platapussy, please?
Well... No-no-no.
lt's okay, it won't hurt you.
Who thinks it's time for PooPoo
to meet her special little friend?
- Ooh, l do.
- Right here.
Well, it is an important
American tradition.
Come on, sweetie.
- Bye!
- Bye.
- Have a good time!
No! No! No!
Going at it like a little
hamster in there.
- Yes! Yes! Oh! Oh!
- Poo! Poo! Poo! Poo! Poo!
USA!
Oh! l love this country.
Oh! Ah, ah, ah!
Go, America!
l like this new
American Tradition.
Let's check those
bad boys out.
- Ready?
- Oh, yeah.
Look over here.
A time-honored college tradition
is ignoring the three-way...
in the bathroom
stall behind you.
How much does he wish these
lips were in that stall with him?
What are you doing?
My dog is such a perv.
l love it.
Mmm. Now l'm craving sushi.
Moshi Moshi.
Paging Plumber Jones.
Plumber Jones.
What is the problem? Over.
There's a pipe blockage
in the girl's bathroom.
We need you to
go check it out.
This problem is solved.
Signing off.
Son, l realize you always wanted
to be a plumber like your old man.
As long as people remain full of
shit, we'll have job security.
Stay here.
l'm coming!
lt's a lovely smile, isn't it?
Now, cleanliness is
next to godliness.
l have been supervisor of this
dorm for over 27 years...
and l take personal pride in
maintaining a sanitary
and a wholesome environment.
The rules of the dormitory
are very simple.
One: Although this is
a coed college...
this is not a coed dormitory.
Any sexual touching
is forbidden.
Two: a good student
is a clean student...
and that must be reflected
in their environment.
What is wrong with you?
l gotta pee so bad my
back teeth are floating.
Lucky there's a
potty right here.
Hurry. We don't
want any accidents.
Sit on the paper if
you are going to sit.
l think she needs
more toilet paper.
Help!
Go, go! Hurry!
l'm going down the gurgler.
Grab her legs.
Just hold on.
l don't want to die.
Oh, sweet Jesus, do not
Iet me die in here.
l'm stuck, and the
toilet's eating me.
- Can you please hurry up?
- We're gonna get you outta there.
You hang on.
Oh, no!
lt's a 10.2 on the shitter scale!
lt's never gone this high before!
l have no idea what that means.
Everybody run!
What the hell is wrong
with that man?
Get down!
Oh, shit!
Oh, my god!
l am closing down
this dormitory.
All of you get out!
lt's just like when l used to live
next to the methane plant.
Please step back. We just had
a plumbing emergency....
causing the fat girl
to go sky high.
Strangely we found a
Dolce & Gabbana top...
stuffed down the pipes.
Holy shit.
This stuff happens all the time.
There's nothing to see here.
School'll take care of
all your bathroom needs.
Why does it smell
like hot ass?
That would be the
gas escaping.
So where are we gonna
stay 'til it gets fixed?
School has arranged
for housing vouchers.
l can't believe the school is
only giving us _200 a month.
You can't even get a
cardboard box for that.
What if we pool all our money?
Don't look at me, guys. l'm still
saving up for ass implants.
There's nothing affordable unless
you commute from the swamp.
Hey, girls.
What about a sorority?
Hey, great idea. A sorority.
That's like flypaper
for horny guys.
Yeah.
lf we all did it
together, it'd be fun.
l don't know, Max.
l don't think l'm really down
with the whole sorority thing.
Aren't sororities supposed to be
about friendships and bonding?
We could at least check it out.
lt's either that or a commute
from the swamp.
There are so many
temptations out there...
like drugs, alcohol, and boys.
l'd like to introduce you
to a different kind of boy.
l think you're really
gonna like him.
He's smart, he's funny,
and he's really cool.
The coolest.
His name is Jesus, and he just
wants to hang with you guys.
Welcome to Kappa!
Can l ask a question?
Was he circumcised?
l mean, he's a Jew,
but he's a Christian.
What's the deal with that?
No, l, uh...
Very nice to meet you.
They're dykes.
l love curry fish.
l think we've taken up enough
of these ladies' valuable time.
Where you going?
We're gonna play spin the bottle!
You guys can pledge if you want.
We only have one rule.
lf you're gonna kill yourselves,
make sure you tell us in advance.
So we can plan the party.
Yeah.
Love what you've
done with the place.
Very cozy.
Once you cross the doors at Phi
Iota Gamma, you will never again
have to worry about what to
wear in order to be accepted.
Big hug!
Oh, my god.
We're so out of here.
No, girls., come back.
Please. The sisterhood needs you.
#  One, two, three four #
#  l did something last night
that you don't know #
Hey, it's the madman.
- Check it, dog.
- Yeah, what up?
Listen. Huge party at
the Gamma's house.
You're going.
Don't say nothing, all right?
You know l'm gonna
sign that check, dog.
Check you later, dude.
#  If only l could tell you
one, two, three, four #
Oh, snap!
Rappers!
Chicks love rappers, right?
Yeah, yeah. In those videos
they always got bitches.
Bitches and hoes.
Check this out.
Yo, yo, you're cold.
You're old.
Your mom's got mold. Her teeth
are gold, and brown and...
That didn't rhyme.
l'm gonna check that out.
l'm gonna fix that,
but it's gonna be good.
Yeah.
What's crackin' there, baby?
We're in South Beach...
where it's so hot the girls
get undressed naturally.
l was thinking about
taking a swim...
but now i'll have to drain
and disinfect the pool.
What?
ls everyone from
MySpace in my pool?
Oh, my God.
l know for a fact that
girl has syphilis.
She's so beautiful.
l'm gonna pull a muscle if l
have to keep smiling like this.
l heard her dad
is a billionaire.
l heard her dad bought France.
Have you seen her boyfriend?
He's hot.
Clue, what's up?
Howsa howsa?
Who let that loser in here?
Big-ass titties for ya!
That's hot.
Aw, man.
This is embarrassing.
lf l was a real queen, l'd have
that dickless wonder beheaded.
Speaking of dickless.
Why do you have always
have to bring Dax here?
Baby.
Princess.
Dax is my boy.
We go way back, like... car seats.
That is so corny.
Where you going?
Downstairs.
l have people waiting for me.
Come here for a sec, baby.
l got something l
want to show you.
And it rhymes with ''my renis.''
And keep my public waiting?
Unlikely, Derek.
Come on, baby.
We haven't hooked
up in like a week.
My balls miss your chin.
You know l can't
resist Little Derek.
Little?
Tiny. Like a baby's dick.
Who's your baby dick?
- You are.
- Yeah.
- Tie me up, huh?
- Oh, yeah. Baby.
- Tie it up.
Close your eyes.
Okay.
Oh, baby.
- You like that?
- Yeah.
Oh, baby, you're
driving me crazy.
Oh, Hell no.
The whipped cream?
Baby, you're bringing
out the freak in me.
You be a good little boy
and keep your eyes closed.
l'm gonna keep one eye open,
if you know what l'm sayin'.
Huh?
Just don't open
them or l'll stop.
Okay.
God, you're driving me crazy.
Oh, yeah.
Come over here and get
some of this baby dick.
Close your eyes.
Aw, l hate giving my dog
such a small bone.
Baby.
Oh, god! Feels so good.
You're an animal.
Whoo!
Sandpaper time.
l like that shit.
Ow, that hurts! Do it again.
Oh, my God.
Did you hear his accent?
l know. l love irish accents.
l would totally let him
do me in the butt.
Ew!
Me, too.
lrish accent.
Butt sex.
l need an Irish accent.
World famous DJ Clue,
Desert Storm...
Scott Danimal in the building.
And Gamma Gammas, l would
like introduce your princess,
the lovely Victoria English.
Thank you.
l have an announcement to make.
Gamma Gamma was
selected as a finalist
in FHM's hottest sorority contest.
Everybody have a great
time at my party.
Rock on to DJ Clue.
Yeah, ya'll, let's get the party
started Desert Storm-style, baby!
Someone's getting
their stick licked.
Fuck, that hurt! Do that again.
Oh, yeah.
Don't fucking look at me like that.
Sounds like my mom and dad.
Oh, yeah.
Go under the carriage, baby.
God, baby, that feels
so fucking good.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, my God.
Fuck, that hurt.
Do that again.
Oh, yeah.
Damn.
lt's a fucking dog, dude!
Oh, baby.
Oh, my god.
- Fuck, that hurt!
- That's nasty.
Put your pointer in my
purple starfish, baby.
Oh, yeah, that's it.
l think.
Are you ready for the smoothie?
Come here, gamsie.
Come here.
What's up, derek?
How's your girl? l
mean, your bitch.
l heard they've got a fine cocker
spaniel at the Kappa house.
And you know what?
She likes it ruff!
Say, we're just doggin' with ya.
Yeah, yuk it up all
you want, clowns.
'Cause at the end of the
day, l still got Victoria,
and you got fingered by
Father Mulrooney.
Fuck you!
Bro, you gotta leave
your past behind.
That was interesting.
Top o' the mornin' to ya!
l'm an exchange student
from the Emerald Isle.
You're from Ireland?
Aye! That l am--from Ireland.
That's such a coincidence.
She's from Ireland, too.
That's right.
l'm from Galway.
Where you hail from?
Uh, l'm from, uh,
South... Middle Earth.
Nice try, Frodo.
Later.
Wait!
Don't leave yet.
Don't you want to
taste my shillaley?
You're disgustin'.
When l look around this class of
talented students, what do l see?
l see a future of Dolce's,
Gabbana's, Chloe's and Prada's.
lf l wanted to get an
''A'' in fashion class,
l would have walked in naked.
This slow motion helps, so you
can get a good look, you pervs.
So sorry l'm late, Lisa.
The lady doing my
pedicure took forever.
Hi, Victoria. We were just
discussing your work.
- Nice job as always.
- Thank you.
However, l was especially
impressed by the freshness
of this designer's work.
Are those clothes for Muppets?
Now who may l say is
responsible for these?
Gloria Torres.
Great job, Gloria.
Thanks.
Note to self: fire design team.
Check out these freshman.
They're so hot.
Cut it out, man.
You're gonna get me in trouble.
What happened to you, man?
What ever happened to the guy
that fucked Denise Reynolds
in front of her grandparents?
l miss that guy.
l'm still here.
Ugh. Shoot.
Damn.
That's hot.
- Think she's hot?
- Who?
That Mexican broad
you were staring at.
Actually, l think
she's Portuguese.
Shut the fuck up, Dax!
And you... you stay
away from that bitch.
Bye.
Daddy, darling, will you do Queen
Victoria the hugest favor?
l need my fashion design
teacher killed.
Oh, really?
Well then l want that
fucking bitch fired.
Thank you, Daddy.
l love you.
#  Back home #
You know what, girls?
There is one place that
we haven't tried yet.
Wow.
Gamma Gamma.
Damn, It looks like
some MTV crib shit.
My cooter's tingling.
l think there might
be boys in there.
We need to get a door guy.
Better yet, a human bug zapper.
Oh, my God, that dress is so hot.
Thank you.
That must have cost
hundreds of dollars.
Try thousands of hundreds.
So don't go looking for
it in any Sears catalog.
That's what l meant.
Thousands... hundreds.
Oh, Morgan.
We'd like to pledge
your sorority, please.
lf it's not too much trouble,
l'd like a room with a bidet.
Could you guys hold
on for a second?
l think she likes us.
Someone left a mess on our front
door, and it wants to pledge.
Look at this place.
It's just heaven on earth.
And it's so pink.
We could have one hell
of an orgy in here, gals.
What do you think, girls?
Are they Gamma material?
l think we should let them pledge.
- And you are?
- Kristen.
Kristen Haas.
And why do you think we should
Iet them pledge, Kristen _ss?
Because, um... because they
could be our diversity.
Hot.
She's right.
Gamma's about acceptance
and individuality.
Who are we to discriminate?
Bring them in.
Good idea, Kristen Haas.
Nice hair.
Yeah, thanks. Shut the door.
Morgan, can you get the girls
some champagne, please?
l'd like to lick her all over.
l heard about your
housing situation.
lt's so unfortunate.
And that's why we'd like
to offer you an early bid.
Normally we don't let
pledges move right in...
but in your case, l think we're
gonna make an exception.
Why don't you girls go
check out the house.
Let us know by the
end of the night.
l don't know.
You guys really think this
place is right for us?
Are you kidding me?
This is the most beautiful
place l ever seen.
lts beauty puts the
Taj Mahal to shame.
- All right?
- All right. Fuck it.
l'm in.
This place is insane!
Have you ladies come
to a decision yet?
l think we're in!
Welcome to gamma.
Why don't you guys get
changed for dinner?
With their diversity, we
can win the FHM contest.
But they'll never be
Gamma Gammas.
That was a great idea, Kristen.
And if the freak show
make it through hell week?
You're in.
Wait!
l thought l already was in.
Good luck.
Wait. Wait. Wait.
So you tried the rapper
thing, the jackass thing.
- Nothing worked?
- Nothing.
l really liked that Irish thing.
That was good.
l liked it, too. l just don't get it.
- Maybe l'm ugly.
- No.
A little.
l think she's the one.
What? Who's the one?
Victoria, dick.
Victoria? No, man.
- She's the hottest girl in school.
- She's the craziest girl in school.
Yeah, crazy for me.
Yeah, so crazy for you she
got her dog to blow you.
She's sharing.
So crazy for you that she
emptied your bank account...
and bought a ticket for her
ex-boyfriend to visit her.
They're friends.
l steal her panties.
She puts pictures of
me on the internet.
lt's a relationship.
It's a two way street, dick!
l gotta go.
Victoria's gonna let
me be on top this time.
But there's only one bed.
That's okay, because you ladies
will be sleeping in there.
But don't worry, there's
plenty of room.
Okay? l'll see you at dinner.
- Bye.
We are so flattered...
that you all want to be
a part of Gamma Gamma.
l think that Jackie Onassis
said it best when she said--
Thanks, Morgan.
l think we know what you mean.
You pledges are our future,
and that's why it's important...
you live up to the
highest of standards.
Because we are the
hottest sorority eyer.
So you're asking, if l keep
treating pledges like shit...
won't they just leave?
Will fat chicks ever stop
squeezing into low rise jeans?
Will hairy chicks
ever stop waxing?
No.
The more l humiliate them, the
more they're gonna love me.
Sick, huh?
Gross.
Be sure to lick your
bowls clean, girls.
And don't use your hands.
By the way, that's
not dog food.
lt's yesterday's sushi.
Eat up.
Damn, Maxine, move over.
l'm sorry.
l'm just big boned is all.
FYl, the ass is not a bone.
Babs, would you please
stop rubbing my butt?
l though that was my ass.
Oh, yeah, baby.
Oh, that's good.
Suck on my titties.
Someone seriously has to take
that thing away from her.
Get up, get up,
get up, get up.
Sleep is for gammas,
not pledges.
Now, we have a little sexual
awareness exercise for you guys.
Good morning.
Gammas must learn all aspects of
condom use and proper disposal.
How many of these
do we have to find?
Just 50.
And how many do we have?
Three.
Why don't we just buy
some condoms...
and jerk off some
homeless guys?
Like that didn't occur
to anyone else.
l think l found one.
Where?
Ew. Get it off. Get it off!
Wait! Poops don't lose that one!
Wait! Stop!
We need it! Get back!
Excuse me. Uh, gays?
You think we could
get your condom?
You know, after?
We'll bring you two, sweetie.
Two!
You got it.
You almost gave
me a heart attack.
Sorry.
You're Derek, right?
Victoria's boyfriend.
What the hell are you doing
here at 4:OO in the morning?
We got in a fight.
She kicked me out.
Well, that sucks.
Happens all the time.
She kicks me out, l come
Iay here for a while...
and then l go to my room.
Why do you take it?
l guess l'm addicted and
Victoria's the drug.
That is so refreshingly honest...
and tear-jerkingly pathetic
at the same time.
- Pathetic?
- At the same time.
Not that l'm not enjoying
this conversation...
with you or anything...
but there's something about a
woman wearing rubber gloves...
and carrying tongs at
four in the morning...
that naturally scares
the shit out of a guy.
Victoria has us pledges
collecting used condoms.
Oh, right.
That exercise she
likes to give.
Any luck?
No, not really.
lt's not like l'm trying
all that hard, either.
You know, l may be able to
help you out with this.
- Excuse me?
- No, not like that.
Just come with me.
Wait a minute.
Where are you going?
Just trust me. Come on.
- l'm not gonna bite.
- All right.
No, l want to be on
''The Real World''!
You're all gonna be there.
- Oh, shit! John!
- Derek.
What the fuck are you
doing here, dude?
Derek!
Of course. l'm outta here.
No, wait a second.
John, get the hell out of here.
It's my night.
Hey, l'm sorry.
l live here, too, man.
Uh, my night.
Girls, this is derek.
Introduce yourself.
Hi.
l'm Brenda.
All of you, out!
And he's not even
on ''The Real World.''
What? You're an asshole!
Ow!
Wait. Wait.
l had a callback. Wait, girls.
l apologize.
Okay, what am l doing here?
Oh, right.
Think fast.
Yeah, my roommate John's
a bit of a weirdo.
- He keeps them after he fucks.
- l get the picture.
John, will you get
out of here, man?
Come on. Open up, Baby Dick.
One minute, Angel Tits!
- Get under the bed.
- What!?
Just trust me, okay?
My old look was bad,
so the ka-ka came...
but it's not raining
ka-ka anymore.
- Okay, will you trust me?
- No.
Just get under the bed.
lt's raining... sperm.
Why do l have to
get under the bed?
l think it's raining sperm.
Open the door immediately,
or i'll tell everyone.
lt is raining sperm.
Open the door.
Come on, Baby Dick.
- Victoria.
- Hi, Baby Dick.
l missed you.
Put this on, now.
Just this.
No. l'm not gonna do it.
l'm not gonna be your little
boy toy anymore, okay?
l'm not gonna be your
little sex slave anymore.
l'm sta... l'm standing up
for myself this time...
and l'm not gonna do it.
Oh, really? How about now?
Never mind.
l'm sportin' wood.
Oh, my god! Blow my rooster!
You're such a hot tool.
Screw me, baby.
Pull out your tape
MeftSU re n OW.
Oh, yeah. Oh, my.
Oh, yeah.
Nail me.
Oh, yeah. Oh, god.
l'm gonna tile your house.
Jackhammer.
Rub it.
Oh, my god.
Feels so good.
Take me to the
construction site!
Nail me, baby. Nail me.
Raise my roof, baby.
Oh, yeah.
Bad-ass sex every night, sweet
pledge torture every day.
lt's so good to be me.
Hello, Sister Victoria, Sister
Morgan, Sister Trista.
How do the pledges greet
their Gamma sisters?
Gamma girls are so sweet.
May we please kiss your feet?
Okay.
- Ooh, l kinda like that.
- You may rise.
So, how did your
first mission go?
Trista, count them.
l count six.
Let's hope you do
better on the next one.
We're rooting for you.
You girls make me sick.
Yeah, you're sick.
Wait for me.
Hey, boys, you
know you want it!
l'm the horn of plenty!
Nice legs!
How'd you like me to
fill your diaper?
Hey, boys.
Mommy needs a diaper change.
Part of becoming a gamma
is learning sophistication.
Like mother here.
And part of being
sophisticated is knowing...
how to properly entertain
nice, young gentlemen.
Oh, my God.
Make with the rub-a-dub.
We were promised a
sensual foot experience.
l will burn in hell first.
l really want to be nice, but the
smell is just... unbearable.
You like that, baby?
You like that?
Mommy's gonna make you a man.
Whoo!
Okay.
Who's next?
Oh, yeah!
lf you see, see, see, see seamen.
Won't you free, free,
free, free them?
l'm such a humanitarian...
so l decided to mark her
friends up, Victoria-style.
You don't have to do this, Max.
l'm all right.
Wow.
What do we have here?
Mother?
These girls were
such a mess...
it was easier to mark the
places that were okay.
- No!
- You can do it.
Give me that!
Who the hell do
you think you are?
Excuse me?
You can't treat us like this.
We're just trying to help you.
lt's bullshit.
You and your fembots just
want to make fun of us.
Well, mission accomplished.
You know what?
l quit.
Sayonara, puta.
Three days before initiation,
and what does she do?
Quits. Know why?
Because she doesn't have the
dedication to be a Gamma.
Anyone else want to drop out?
Yes. If one goes, we all go.
Yeah.
They walked out on me.
l'll get those bitches.
Victoria... l'm still in, right?
Kristen, you're my favorite,
and l love you, but she bailed.
Sorry, maybe next year.
What if l can get her back?
lf you can get her back...
then l'd say welcome back
to Gamma Gamma.
Okay.
Those nerds should have known
not to go to a real estate agent...
that also sold churros.
Allow me to introduce myself.
My name is Buford Gomez.
l'm a former border patrol agent.
l used to put the
panic to Hispanic.
l put the pepper spray to Jos.
l put the baton to Juan.
That's all behind me.
l'm helping people now.
Look at you, look,
you soul sister.
Them braids real? That's amazing.
Okay, you must be
the Appalachian.
Like a like a whack mohawk
thing going on there.
You're like a little
redneck peacock.
What the hell
happened there, girl?
l don't know if
l'm comin' or goin'.
How you doin'?
You don't eat pork, do you?
l'd like to pork you. Porky Pig.
Whoa, a big girl!
You done beat anorexia!
l'm so glad you're a
strong, healthy girl.
And look at... okay.
You ever been with a man?
You ever been the man?
Never mind.
Buford, can you show us
something we could live in?
Okay, you need
a place to stay.
Got it: Super Pollo Loco.
ls it a boat? Is it a restaurant?
Who cares!?
lt's a hybrid with a history dating
back to pre-revolutionary Cuba.
Smell the black
beans and rice.
Taste the tostitos.
Babalo, babalo, babalo.
They don't make structures
like this anymore.
l'm not sure they ever did.
Two converted sleeping
bedrooms, a dining room...
and a working deep fryer.
Hey, great!
l just wanted to
say that l'm sorry.
l'm not in the mood, Kristen.
Victoria feels really bad
about what happened.
Please.
She thinks you'd be a
really great Gamma.
She told me that.
You're the only reason...
she let the other girls
pledge in the first place.
lt's too late anyway.
You could come back.
Just think about it.
l'm feeling this shit.
l mean, metrosexuals
are where it's at.
''Queer Eye'' is the shit.
You got the queer
part down good.
Big time.
You know what?
Screw you guys, okay?
See who's laughing when l'm
getting laid in five minutes.
By a dude.
l think the shirt works.
There's no way
it's gonna work.
Excuse me, could l
get an apple martini?
Thanks.
l'm Jessica.
Hey, Jessica.
l'm Dax.
Nice and fruity.
So have you
got a boyfriend?
- No! No!
- l'm sorry, l thought you--
No, see, l'm not, um...
Um, l mean, l'm not
speaking to him right now.
l caught him with another guy.
- Really?
- Yeah.
Man, that sucks.
Guys can be such assholes.
You're preaching
to the choir, sister.
The gay man's choir,
which l'm a member of.
Can l ask you a
personal question?
Ten inches, and that's
after a cold shower.
Have you ever been
with a woman?
Oh, l...
Have you ever kissed a girl?
Here.
l want you take this.
lt enhances sexual experience.
You take it orally.
That's right. l do.
How does that feel?
lt's okay.
lt doesn't feel wrong?
Yeah, it does, but it's
the right kind of wrong.
lt's okay.
l'll show you what to do.
Oh, wow.
You're really hard.
Oh, my God!
l've been living a lie!
l'm a straight man trapped in a
gay, homosexual's fabulous body!
Set me free, child!
Set me free!
Hallelujah!
Victoria's dog is missing!
Get the cock out of your mouth!
Gamsie?
Before it starts
running, right now!
Wait a second.
No, no. You can't go.
You gotta help me
figure out who l am!
l still don't know
if l'm gay or not.
l'm sorry. Maybe another time.
No, don't go.
Please, don't go!
Come back! ! !
l want you to take this.
lt enhances sexual experience.
Hi.
Your bodies are so beautiful.
Can l touch them?
Well, well, well.
lf it isn't Mr. Brad Pitt
ready to invade Troy.
And by ''Troy,''
l mean my vagina.
That's right, baby.
Mamma's got some
brand new bags.
Why don't you grab a handful?
What the fuck?
Morning, lover.
Hungry?
Do you want a muffin?
Do you want butter
or cream cheese?
Where are my clothes?
Where's my underwear?
l ate them.
No!!!
Call me.
- Hey, Gloria.
- Hey, baby.
Have you seen my mom?
l think she's back at
the chicken boat.
- Thanks, Gloria.
- It's all right.
- Hey, Gloria.
- Mm-hm?
What's a rim job?
Um, that's when you have your
tire changed in your car.
- Thanks, Gloria.
- It's all right.
- l got worried.
- Me, too.
- A boy in my class said it was a--
- Oh, never mind!
He's a bad boy,
and he's wrong.
Why don't you go
Iook for your mommy?
- Okay.
- Okay?
Bye.
Hey, there you are.
Been looking all over for you.
l'm sorry about the other night.
l do appreciate you
trying to help me out.
You have a huge
problem, derek.
You should seriously consider
seeing a shrink or something.
Do some serious couch time.
l did warn you.
True.
You know what?
lt doesn't even matter.
l don't care anymore.
Gamma Gamma can
kiss my butta butta.
No, no, no, no.
You can't quit, 'cause if you
Ieave now, then she wins.
Wait a minute.
Why are you taking our
side against her?
To hell with Victoria.
What about your addiction?
l'm cured.
l found somebody that l
care about so much more.
We're gonna kiss, aren't we?
God, l hope so.
- Oh, my little--
- Promise me something?
- Anything.
- No more pet names.
Think of it as step
one of your recovery.
#  Because it's
gonna be beautiful #
The Kama Sutra was originally
written in Sanskrit...
by an indian man
called Vatsyayana...
whose name literally means
''split the bamboo.''
lmagine, if you will...
a young man and a young
woman like yourself...
in the full thrush of a passionate
intensely sexual embrace...
all being watched by Garuda,
the bird of Vishnu.
- As those juices...
- Hey, kristen.
Nice legs.
What time do they open?
Disgusting.
Dude! Great line!
Que pasa, mommy?
Trista, Morgan is a total freak.
She wants to remove her rib.
Ow, that must really hurt.
How do you know?
Because l'm IM'ing her right now.
Wow, that's so great.
How do you even know that?
Duh. NetZero, loser.
Miss English, l'm sorry,
are we bothering you?
Oh, not at all
Professor Milch'ik.
Just keep it soft and quiet.
Thanks.
Where was i?
Yes.
Fruition.
That woman is bringing that
man to fruition through a series
of very mysterious and intensely
complex moves called--
Mysterious? Complex?
Men are dogs.
Observe.
Lights, please.
Look who's teaching now.
You like that, don't you?
Bet you wish l was yours.
Hot, aren't i?
What do we have here?
A little bit of this.
Yeah.
And a little bit of that.
l'm making you
so hot right now.
Yeah.
l bet you really wish that
l was your girlfriend.
Too bad.
Mystery solved.
Now let's see what you
guys have learned.
Okay, girls.
Here's to life on a
crappy-assed boat.
l think l'm having
the bed spins,
and not the good kind.
lt's the boat.
Our investment is being
tossed around like a mud hut...
i n m o n s o o n seas o n .
You'll get used to it.
l think l need to bow to
the porcelain goddess.
Sounds like she's
getting used to it.
She acts like she's never
been on a roller coaster...
with a bean burrito
in her belly.
Oh, crap.
l think l'm gonna
Iose my lunch.
Or taken a sip from
someone else's seven-up...
that they backwashed into.
Stop it, Gloria.
You're gonna make me hurl.
Ooh, you know what's
really gross?
When you take the
Iast sips of milk...
and then found out
there was chunks in it.
The FHM judges were
coming the next day...
and without those
geeky girls...
l wouldn't have my diversity.
l had to get them
back to Gamma.
So, of course, l
make Kristen do it.
You ready, Kristen?
l don't know, Victoria.
This is pretty fucked up.
l invite these girls
into my house...
and they have zero appreciation
for anything l've done.
And, Kristen,
need l remind you...
that this entire thing
was your idea?
You know, normally, l
would ask Morgan to come.
But there's something
special about you...
Kristen Haas.
Something special enough
to be Gamma president.
What?
l think you have
what it takes.
Or at least l
thought l did.
Now, l'm beginning to
second guess your loyalty.
No, no, no.
l'm-l'm loyal.
Then act like a
future Gamma pres...
and go and protect
your sisters.
Go!
Oh, Gamsie.
They'll do whatever
we tell them to.
Well, looks like chicken
boat's going for a swim.
Oh!
Oh, no!
Please don't send me
back to Gamma, Krishna.
Oh, no.
Welcome.
Those evil Gamma bitches
will eat me alive.
Oh, please no.
Oh!
lt's the evilest bitch
of all, Victoria!
Please, krishna, no!
No!
My physics test!
Motherfucker, shit!
Shit, motherfucker, shit!
Ow!
Fucking cock, man.
l lost my platapussy.
Somebody get me a chair.
l got a signal.
Fuck!
lt's gone.
What in god's
name is that?
Sure ain't no bird.
l think we're
being watched.
Who's watching?
Who-wee!
You ladies need
a tug, do ya?
We'll tug ya.
l'd love a tug.
Uh-huh.
lt's gonna cost
you though.
A little money up front.
Plus, Randy here gets to look
through all your clothes.
Dirty honky.
What did you say,
you little bitch?
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
You motherfucker!
Oh, my god.
l swear to god.
All right, let's get
this boat roped up.
Come on, ladies.
Give me some help!
Let's tow this
motherfucker out of here.
The boat is leaking.
We've got nowhere to stay.
lt looks like we may
have to ask Victoria...
to take us back.
Oh, and you can imagine
how excited l am...
to have that conversation.
What conversation
might that be, Bitch?
l, um, l just wanted to
know if l can have
another chance to come back.
You think you can just
waltz back in here?
Yeah.
Can you waltz?
So, what do you
think, Kristen?
Has she learned
her lesson?
l think so.
Welcome back to Gamma.
Yeah!
Are her nipples hard?
Wait those are mine.
Gamma Gamma was selected
as a finalist in FHM's...
hottest sorority contest.
Then, guess what?
We won.
Thank you, thank you.
Gamma!
Before l was
elected president,
Gamma Gamma threw
average parties...
and made below
average impressions.
Not hot.
But since the dawn of
what i'd like to call...
the Victorian era, we have
achieved total hotness.
And we're going to be
on the cover of FHM.
lt's important that future
Gammas are the most poised...
sophisticated, and
beautiful girls on campus...
ftS yOU Cftn See.
And these are the kind of
freaks that will never get in!
Yeah!
l can't believe they
actually thought...
they were going to get in.
Let's hear it for the
Gamma girls, guys.
How hot is this?
Girls, paint them up.
Why won't you run?
This ain't right.
Take this!
l can't believe l let
her play me like that.
Why don't we pick
up this stuff...
and set the dang
house on fire?
And after that, we'll set
the whole campus on fire!
At least we'll have
somewhere to stay.
l hear the beds are very
comfortable in jail.
And we get used
to the rough sex.
Babs, not now.
Our possessions have
been strewn in the dirt...
like our hopes
and our dreams!
Oh, Krishna.
Why have you deserted us?
Why?
Gloria, l am so sorry.
Forget it, Derek.
l don't even
wanna hear it.
Well, you don't actually
think l had something...
to do with that, do you?
lt was all a big ploy...
to make us look like fools
in front of everyone.
You disgust me.
l swear to you l had
nothing to do with that.
How do l make you
understand this?
l have no loyalty
to her anymore.
Okay.
Prove it.
What's the most
important thing to her...
in her shallow life?
Besides making us
Iook like fools?
l don't know.
l really don't know.
FHM magazine.
Getting on the cover has
been an obsession of hers...
since i've known her.
For the last three years
all she wants to do..
is win this stupid
contest, and l know how...
to make that dream
turn into a nightmare.
This party is gonna be the
biggest night of her life.
You wanna get back at her?
The keys to Gamma Gamma.
Let's do it, Gloria.
-Give me that.
-Yes!
Just like everyone,
Kristen let me down.
But if being mean to
people turned her off...
then why the hell did
she become a Gamma?
You are not welcome
here, stabber of backs.
l have a good mind to
put you over my knee...
and give you the spanking
of your life, young lady.
Oh, i've been bad, too.
l just wanted to
say that l'm sorry.
l don't know what
l was thinking...
and l don't blame
you for hating me...
but l know what
l did was wrong...
and l want to make
it up to you.
Pledging a sorority isn't
worth hurting other people...
especially people who
used to be your friends.
l forgive you, my child.
Excuse me.
l know, l wouldn't
trust me either.
But l've changed.
l want to help you guys
get back at the Gammas.
Let's get 'em.
Hello, my beautiful,
beautiful bitches.
Welcome to the
FHM beauty shoot...
because we're going to
make you on the cover...
of the world's best
men's magazine.
You are going to
absolutely look gorgeous.
Give me sex.
Give me love.
Give it to me.
This is what l want
you bitches to do.
Victoria, you stand
in the middle...
you lovely, lovely
goddess of light.
The rest of you bitches,
go around in a circle.
ln a circle!
Okay.
Yes.
Now, dance around
like a horse.
You want to be in
the picture show...
you have to do it like
you're on a horse.
All of you are creatures,
except for Victoria.
You stay in the middle.
All of you creatures.
Victoria, l
swear to Versace...
if you weren't here, l'd be
like a banana.. l'd do a split.
Get out of here.
Please, Just stay
in the middle.
l need to take some
pictures of you.
He loves me.
l'll make him give
me that cover.
Those bitches, they
snuck into Gamma
during our group
liposuction night.
These are the smallest
cameras known to man.
The lenses are the
size of a-of a-a pinhead.
Virtually undetectable.
You can hide these
bad boys anywhere.
Picture frames, sunglasses...
You can even hide
them in a pet's fur.
Hey, will you be able to
find anything on Victoria?
Yes.
You guys aren't gonna
believe what l just found.
We got something.
Look what l found...
bonner central.
We're coming to you live
from the world famous...
South Beach Miami, for
what promises to be...
the hottest party of the year,
the unveiling of the new...
FHM sorority of the
year magazine cover.
Gamma Gamma sorority
won the contest...
and we can't wait to see
what they're wearing...
or not wearing.
Tonight.
Come on in girls, these guys
are gonna help you on out.
They're my little
temp service here.
This is Jos, he
testified in trial...
for me with the border
patrol back in the day...
you know what l'm saying?
That guy with the
turban did it.
Now these guys wanna get
back at them Gamma bitches.
The Gammas turned
em on in to the INS...
so they wanna get
back at the girls too.
Thank you.
Anything you need
they're gonna help you.
l get hepatitis.
No Poops.
Damn!
l mean this is
like a buffet.
Oh my god, that's
Carmen Electra.
She's my fantasy
girlfriend.
She's coming here.
Hey.
Um...nice legs.
Thanks.
What time do they open?
l was thinking maybe we
could go somewhere...
and, uh...talk.
Oh, Dax!
Oh God.
Hey!
Step away from my man!
l don't know her.
Kids this is Dax,
he's your new daddy.
What?
No, l don't have kids!
Pony ride!
No-no, don't leave!
Wait, Carmen!
By any chance
are you jewish?
No, l'm methodist.
That'll do.
What's up, hottie?
Word.
You ever been in the
back of a pickup truck?
What's a pickup truck?
You're about to find out.
You're not gonna be
needing this shit.
Hi.
Would you like a drink?
Su-sure.
Champagne's really good
for the complexion.
Just kiss her
allready you big puss!
Wooo!
Oh, God, somebody kill me!
l'm a pony!
And now the moment
you've been waiting for...
FHM presents the
girls of Gamma Gamma.
And now, here's your
host for the evening...
Sofia Vergara!
We have searched far and
wide to find a sorority...
that will represent
everything...
that you have come
to love about FHM...
sex apeal, power,
style and respect.
Let me present to you
FHM's hottest sorority...
Gamma Gamma!
Congratulations!
Thank you.
People told me, ''Victoria
no question about it...
''you're the hottest
sorority leader...
''at South Beach University.''
But the entire country, l
just knew l could do it.
And this is only the beginning
of Victoria English.
This is supposed to be
about Gamma, not just her.
Sofia, you are so hot.
We should totally like
do a show together.
Oh my god, thank
you, of course.
Wouldn't that
be so hot guys?
Do her!
Hi, l have a really
big favor to ask you...
l seem to have dropped my
earring backing over here.
l was wondering if you
could help me find it.
All right Gammas, do you
wanna see your cover?
We're not even on it.
Victoria looks
really beautiful.
God l look hot.
Backstabbing little bitch!
And now lets take a
Iook behind the scenes...
at the hottest
sorority in America.
Hey everybody, l'm
Victoria English...
president of Gamma Gamma and
l wanna show you around.
This is the
master bedroom.
And this is Gamsie, my dog.
#  Twinkle-twinkle little... #
They showed me
on the potty.
What are you doing
you ugly ass?
You poor thing, there
you go you're better.
You are looking so thin.
Thank you.
Probably had
another abortion.
Uh-oh.
You fucking bitches.
Stop the video!
l did not approve of this!
Oh my God!
That's my school picture!
Oh, my God.
Where did you find that?
Stop the video, l did
not approve of this.
Very, very
interesting but...
This isn't the right tape.
l was obviously joking.
Everybody knows what a
great sense of humor l have.
You can't walk out on me!
Where are you all going?
None of this is true!
Don't you know who l am?
l'm Victoria English!
Those bitches just set this
up because their jealous!
Oh Shit.
Hey, any of you broads...
wanna eat sushi off
my naked body?
l am the one.
Oh, yes.
Aren't you one of those
Gamma Gamma girls?
Oh, darlin', l'm not just one
of the Gamma Gamma girls...
l'm victoria english.
Right, and l'm
Paris Hilton.
Where have you
been baby dick?
Victoria, it's all over.
l deserve better.
Better than me?
There's no one
better than me.
And there's no
way l'm gonna let...
some dumbass pledge
ruin my relationship...
with this worthless
piece of shit.
Victoria...
-Pledge this.
Derek disapointed me.
He was too clueless
to know what he had.
As far as l'm concerned, she
can have that tiny bastard.
That was great,
baby, fantastic.
Ari Belinsky producer
E channel Los Angeles.
So, where you really
an ugly kid, or what?
lt's all lies!
Oh, it's too bad.
l was hoping we could
do a reality show,
back to basic's
kind of thing...
but if it isn't true...
A show about me?
lt's all true!
A true Gamma Gamma
never quits...
so l gave them the
ending they wanted.
Well, l guess now you
all know the real me.
Pretty huh?
Sometimes it's hard
for me to remember...
what it was like
all those years...
of being ridiculed
and laughed at.
l struggled to erase that
girl you saw up there...
and become the one that
you see down here.
Respected, admired, hot.
But l guess somewhere
along the way...
l became like one of those
people that caused me...
so much pain and that
is totally not hot.
lt's not about how you
Iook or building your body...
or straighting your nose
or getting bigger boobs.
lt's about your attitude
and that's what's hot...
and l should know
because l invented it.
Morgan?
You're a bitch!
You tell me now about this
hot attitude bullshit!
l spent my life savings
fixing my nose...
and my entire body
to look like you!
Now you tell me to
be me and not you.
You're a disgrace.
l hate you!
Hey, lady, get a life.
So, l made a nice speech
about having a good attitude...
and inner beauty.
But l can't figure out...
if l was mad at those girls
for showing me up...
or proud that they
actually managed...
to totally minipulate me.
What the heck?
The next year Gloria became the
president of Gamma Gamma.
And me, l loved
my cover so much...
l bought FHM magazine.