Is Mr. Tendo safe?
Yes.
Where is the man who saved me?
He refuses to answer.
Anything to say to me?
I had nothing to do with it.
We know you betrayed us.
No. Not me.
We know that you're lying to us.
You're working for Campanela.
I swear...
I'm not working for Campanela!
This is your last chance.
Just tell me the truth!
You're making a mistake.
You're very brave.
I regret having to
put you through this.
I regret it also.
Some hero...
He smells like a cheeseburger.
I will be assassinated.
We've taken every precaution.
Still, it will happen.
I will put Kazuo by your side.
But Campanela has the advantage.
This was their territory.
The desire to protect it
will drive them harder.
We will only survive
if we make no mistakes.
Then we will make no mistakes.
What about this new man?
Is he loyal?
Yes.
But he is an outsider.
We are all outsiders here.
Yuko seems to like Nick.
There is much to like about him.
Can you understand me?
No...?
I could never tell you this...
But even in this short time...
I know in my heart...
That I could spend
the rest of my life with you.
I will not let you kill yourself!
Yes, I speak Japanese.
The FBl demands
a lot from its agents.
Get down!