Have you ever been outside?
I mean not temporarily.
I mean born outside,
never been inside,
never been petted, not even once.
Yes?
Then you know about the darkness
that is not appropriate to talk about.
I had a bloody paw
when they found me
and carried me in a towel
to the cageatorium.
It was not cool there,
but they said, "We'll come back
for you, Paw Paw."
"Paw Paw"--
That's what they called me,
and they called each other
Sophie and Jason.
Can you get me some water?
I'm not getting up.
I'm just shifting my position.
If we had a crane,
then we could get water
without getting up.
We could just...
How would you turn the faucet on?
Just with my mind.
It's such a shame that the only thing
you can do with your mind
is something that you could
just do with your hand.
Well, at least I have that,
you know?
You can't really do anything
special with your mind?
Well, except stop time.
Oh, really?
I wasn't aware of that.
Can I see an example?
Turn the faucet on.
I don't want to waste water.
You really want me to stop time?
Yeah.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
Yeah? All right.
1...
2...
3.
You're so bad at this.
Really?
I thought I was doing good.
Hello, and thank you
for calling Horizicom.
My name is Jason.
Can I have your service lD number?
What operating system are you...
And hop, hop, hop.
Keep on hopping.
And up, up,
and run under!
Look how dark it is.
I know.
Sign out.
My video got over 10,000 hits.
Did you see it yet?
No, l--no.
That's okay.
It wouldn't really
be your thing anyways.
And what operating system
are you running?
Okay, great.
Uh, can you go to mail?
And then click on
"Preferences."
Now read to me what it says there.
There you go.
Is there anything else
I can help you with today?
Thank you for calling Horizicom.
Have a nice day.
How was class?
It was canceled
on account of me
being overqualified.
Really?
Yes.
It was very satisfying actually.
The president was there.
Obama?
Exactly.
And he declared me,
on behalf of all the principalities,
free to dance
or do whatever I want.
Like if you just want to be
on Facebook all the time, he's--
he's cool with that?
Well, he knows that
I've been gearing up
to do something really incredible
for the last 1 5 years.
Did he say anything
about your little friend?
No.
He doesn't know about Shirty.
Shirty is private,
not that I'm embarrassed
or anything.
Yeah. I think that place is definitely
gonna put him to sleep.
So then we're totally doing
the right thing?
I think we are. Yeah.
I think we're ready.
Ready for...
Hey, well, you know I think we are.
Anyways, it's just for six months.
Yeah. At the most.
- At the most, six months.
- And then we can
do whatever we want
for the rest of our lives.
Is this even big enough?
Yeah.
Hi. We're here for an adoption.
Okay.
The doctor's running behind,
so it'll be a few minutes.
All right, thanks.
I'm gonna go to the bathroom.
Okay.
Thanks.
Do you want to buy that?
My dad drew it.
I live with him because my mom's
a free spirit.
Does it look like me?
Uh, yeah, it does.
I wrote my mom's and dad's
phone numbers on the back
so if someone buys it
and they decide they don't want it,
they can give it back to us.
That's a good idea.
I know,
but no one wanted it.
So many of the other ones
got bought,
but ours is still here.
Well, maybe it's just
no one's cup of tea.
It's my cup of tea.
Oh, you don't have to do that.
No, I want it.
Um, guess I pay for it up front.
Well, take your time.
There's no pressure.
Come on.
He's doing much better
since you brought him in,
but he does have renal failure.
That's what this is for.
When you pull the needle out,
you might see a drop or two of blood.
That's normal.
He gets the sub-cu once a day,
and rotate the pill sequence
on alternating days,
so Monday, Monday,
Thursday,
Friday, Friday, and so on.
Right.
Oh, no.
We can't release him
until this comes off.
He has about a month to go.
You can pick him up on the 26th,
but please don't be late.
We're overcrowded,
and we euthanize.
Take a moment with him.
Okay. Hey.
Hey, we are gonna bring you home
and adore you and take care of you
for the rest of your life.
No matter what you do.
Yeah.
Because he could be wild.
You know, we don't
really know for sure.
Well, I don't think they would have
taken him if he was wild.
Uh, the woman
that was here before
said that he only had
five or six months left,
so is that including the--
Well, of course, if you take
really good care of him
and he bonds with you, he could
easily hang on for years,
but probably no more than five.
They came back,
and they petted me,
and I accidentally
made the sound
that means I am
cat which is belonging to you.
And upon making the sound,
I felt it to be true.
It was a warm type of feeling
that would have been unwise
to have outside at night,
but it suddenly seemed
that I would not be outside
at night ever again.
It could just be six months.
That's if we do a bad job.
We're not gonna do a bad job.
Well, I have to be able to go
to New York. My parents--
No, one of us always
has to be here now.
So I always have to be home?
What if I don't want to be doing
tech support for five more years?
We'll be 40 in 5 years.
Oh. 40 is basically 50,
and then after 50,
the rest is just...
Ioose change.
Loose change?
Like not quite enough to get
anything you really want.
Oh, God.
So for all practical purposes,
in a month,
that's it for us.
God, I always thought
I'd be smarter.
I also thought
eventually we'd be rich.
I always want
to follow the news,
you know, but then
I'm so far behind,
and now it's just like,
what's the point?
I actually thought I'd end up
being a world leader.
Oh, yeah, that's not gonna happen.
It's too late for us.
At least we have a month.
You know, that's actually a long time
when you think about it.
Like, we thought
we'd have him home today,
but instead we have
a whole month to...
- To what?
- I don't know, but,
I mean, if this is our last month ever,
shouldn't we...
Yeah.
Yeah, right.
I mean, if we were
dying in a month,
we would definitely reprioritize.
Right.
What? It's work.
That was so easy.
Was that easy for you?
Not really.
Yeah, but now
you're free to do your--
I know. I can't wait.
Do you know what
you're gonna do?
No, but that's what's great.
I'm gonna let it choose me.
I just have to be alert
and listen for it.
But what if it doesn't--
Shh! I'm listening.
Hey, do you have a moment
to help stop global warming?
No, thank you.
This looks kind of fantastic on me.
You're not environmental.
Yes, I am.
Oh, really?
So you're, like, into nature
and going outside?
Well, I'm glad the outside's there.
I wouldn't want
there to only be inside.
I mean, besides, it doesn't matter,
you know, what I do.
The point is to be alert
and to notice everything.
I'm gonna pay special attention
if somebody gives me something
or says something to me,
especially if they do it with their hand
on a doorknob.
On a--
Also coincidences,
um, or, like, mistakes.
Doubles of anything,
flares and glares,
just flashes of light of any kind.
It could come from anywhere.
And what will it be, do you think?
I don't know.
Probably something profound.
Well, hopefully not so profound
that you forget about me.
I don't see
how that could happen,
unless I had some kind
of head injury or...
What if you did get a head injury,
you know, or I did,
and we couldn't even
recognize each other?
We could come up with a signal.
No, because if I have amnesia,
then, you know, I would just be, like,
"Who are you?" you know,
and, "What is this signal?
Why are you signaling me?"
it would have to be something
that just cuts through everything.
It seems we've stood and talked
Iike this before.
This is the signal?
- We Iooked at each other...
- Yeah.
...in the same way then,
but I can't remember where or when.
Hi. Uh, I'm with--
Uh, my--my name
is Jason, and l--
Oh, I'm sorry.
I didn't see your sign.
I think I'm--
I'm a solicitor.
You are?
I mean, I haven't, uh--
You would be my first solicitation.
Or not.
Yeah, we try to stick to that.
Oh, yeah.
Yes?
Hi. My name is Jason,
and I'm with Tree by Tree.
Do you have a moment to help
reduce global warming?
Um, we're helping to fulfill
the mayor's vision
to plant a million trees
in Los Angeles,
and for a small donation,
we'll give you a healthy young tree.
Thank you.
Do you mind throwing this out?
Sure.
Hi.
What's wrong?
Okay, so the lnternet's
gonna be turned off
in the next hour,
so the second
you get in the door,
you'll want to look up anything
you need to look up.
I'm saving time here
by telling you en route.
Wait. Why is it being shut off?
I had to do it.
It's just for the next 30 days, okay?
Are you noticing these posters?
I'm the only one doing that,
that many.
But I need it.
Well, but not really, you know,
'cause we can just go to a cafe.
That's what I'm gonna do
to upload my dances.
Is it still on?
So at any second?
It could just go off at any second?
By 6:00, they said.
We should be looking up useful things,
you know, like flu warnings.
Well, what are you looking up?
I don't know, MapQuest.
- MapQuest? To where?
- I don't know.
See, this isn't even safe.
I mean, what if there's an accident
and we have to find something?
I thought of that. I thought,
"What if there's something
we really need to know?"
and then I thought, well,
we could just ask someone, or...
we could not know.
Christmas falls on a Tuesday this year.
- Don't look that up!
- Well, I don't know.
Look up things that are only online.
Okay, okay.
How long is 30 days?
It was turning out to be
a little bit longer
than, say, for example,
the day after tomorrow.
Outside, there was no time, no hours,
just alive or not alive
or bird.
Now there was
this new thing, waiting,
waiting for them to come get me,
waiting for my real life to begin.
I learned to count the seconds.
Now, now, now...
Hi, person.
Hi.
Okay. Okay. Here we go.
Here we go.
This is it.
Fuck!
I'm sorry.
I sort of signed up on a whim.
Could one of the other people
just cover my area?
What other people?
The other volunteers
going door to door.
There is nobody else.
You're our guy
for face-to-face education.
For all of Los Angeles?
We're about to witness
a massive shift in consciousness.
I mean, who knows?
You could be the guy
to bring us over the threshold,
the hundredth monkey.
I'm so jealous, man.
You get to walk
across this entire city
house by house,
all the way to the ocean.
You seemed really happy
to have the place to yourself.
How would you know
if I was happy?
Your footsteps and your movements
sounded happy.
Well, I wasn't.
I was wondering where you were.
I was actually starting
to get a little worried.
Well, don't be angry at me.
I wasn't trying to hide.
I couldn't make a sound.
I tried to,
and I couldn't make a sound.
You had a good day.
Oh, wow.
You really did have a good day.
You're out there having
fulfilling experiences.
What are you reading?
"Hair dryer, $3.00 or best offer."
That woman really
has her shit together.
You can tell she's
just totally "carpe diem."
She's a lonely spinster.
No, that is one tough cookie.
You should get out.
Maybe call Tammy or Sasha.
What would I say to them?
Just hi.
"30 days, 30 dances."
I e-mailed everyone.
They're all waiting for it.
No one cares.
I know.
I'm sure it's not
as bad as you think.
I mean, you still have 28 left.
Hi.
Ah, it's you.
I'll turn the water off.
We can go into the house.
It's a heavy-duty one,
but I'm getting rid of it,
because in fact
I got a couple others
that are more heavy-duty.
They're professional models.
But it's been
reconditioned and that,
and it's worth 1 0 times
what I'm charging you for it.
As far as the wire
with the tape on it,
it had a little cut in the wire,
but I put this piece of tape on there
as a safety measure.
This is the on and off switch,
but you leave it off
until you make up your mind
whether you want heat
or you just want air,
but none of it will work unless you push--
turn it to the on position.
Right, the on.
But these always are
the best on the market.
$3.00.
Portable hair dryer.
I do all kinds of electrical work
around the house and that
and repairing that.
That's why I never
have to buy anything.
I've re-fixed this VCRr and the stereo
and all that stuff.
As long as you can get it working,
why not get it free?
Oh, there's one more thing,
if you're interested.
It's okay. I think I'm good.
You can always call back
when you're ready.
If you don't start
on the count of three,
that's it. It's over.
You don't talk to me.
You don't know me.
You don't ever look
at me again, okay?
You understand?
Yeah.
Here we go. 1...
2...
3.
Hello.
Hi.
Um, my name is Sophie.
I bought your--
My boyfriend bought
this drawing that you made
at the animal shelter. I--
Are you calling to return it?
No. No, no.
We like it a lot.
Okay.
So you're calling because...
Oh, are you busy?
Well, no, I'm--
I'm working, but l--
Where do you work?
I own a chain of companies
that makes signs and banners
for trade shows
and corporate events.
Oh.
So...
it's overcast.
I can see a little bit of sun
about to poke out.
Yeah.
No, from where I am,
I can see, like, some flat clouds,
and then there's a puffier one,
and the sun is about to come
around the puffy one.
You must be facing
the same direction as me.
I'm facing east.
Oh, yeah, me, too.
I'm facing east, too.
So we're both in Los Angeles,
and we're both facing east.
Maybe we're neighbors.
Where do you live?
I'm sorry.
You don't have to tell me
where you live.
No, that's all right.
How 'bout this?
How 'bout I'll just
open the window and yell,
and you just see
if you can hear me?
But won't I just hear it
through the phone?
Right.
Okay, so let's hang up,
and I'll yell, and if--
You call me back, and you tell me
if you can hear me.
If I hear it, I'll just yell back.
That's great.
Okay.
Bye.
Hi!
Hey!
Uh, I got this for you.
Ahh, what are you doing?
What was that?
It was a release.
You seem--
Was it a good day?
Yeah.
You--did you
have a good day?
Um, yeah.
You sold a tree?
Yeah.
Oh, let me do that.
It's okay.
Hello.
Hi.
I wasn't able to yell
at that exact time.
There was a delay.
Yeah, I didn't hear anything,
but I didn't know if it was
because you didn't--
Yeah.
That was a funny conversation.
So what do you do
for a living, Sophie?
I'm a dance teacher
for little kids.
Ah, a dancer.
No, just a teacher.
Oh, don't forget your--
and your...
I'm not leaving. I--
Am I in a hurry?
What? No.
No, stay, stay, stay.
Maybe I should order a tree.
How much are they?
Uh, $1 0.
Do I get a discount for three?
Never mind.
Okay, what is
your home address?
Right. You know what?
I'm gonna do this later, so...
Okay.
Bye.
Hello.
Hi.
I'm sorry to bother you again,
but I wanted to ask,
do you own a factory or...
It's more like a warehouse.
Right now,
I'm in my office at home.
Okay, so if a person needed a sign,
they could get it from you?
These are cards
that I make for my wife
at all the nine different holidays,
like our anniversary
and Fourth of July and Easter
and all them.
And I make her a nice poem
about our everyday life.
Then I make 15 limericks up,
and they're all different.
I never made 'em the same.
I've probably got between 500
and 600 of them and that,
so there's quite a few of 'em.
"Mrs. Claus, she pranced around
in red sheer lace,
"and every move she made
was really in good grace,
"so Santa got sexually aroused
really, really strong,
"and he ended up with
a really nice big dong,
so she removed her nice teddy
and sat on his face."
Wow.
H-how long have
you guys been together?
Well, we've been together since 1 948.
That's 62 years, but we've only
been married 60 years.
Do you have a lady friend?
Uh, yeah. We've only been together,
like, four years.
Oh. It can be very hard
in the beginning.
Maybe one of you does
something terrible,
and that might be
the hardest to get used to.
We didn't have those kind of problems
in the beginning.
Well, the thing is you're just in the middle
of the beginning right now.
Okay.
Come in.
My office is right back here.
We'll get you all set up.
Can I take your coat?
It's, um, kind of part of my outfit.
Okay.
Who is that?
It's a friend.
She has a cold. She's supposed
to be taking a nap.
Can I see her?
Voilà.
Hi.
So this is a basic
indoor/outdoor banner.
And of course you can
have any font you want.
You can even bring in your own font,
and we'll use that.
What'd you want it to say?
Yeah, I'm not sure yet.
Okay.
Well, do you have any idea how big
a banner you might want?
Um, not yet.
Okay.
Why don't you start
by filling that out?
Dear persons,
I am writing this to you,
a letter with no pencil,
so I hope that you are able to read it.
By day, I know I am yours,
but when night comes, I am alone
and always have been
and always will be wild,
so it is only the sun
that returns the wonderful feeling
of being pet again.
Please come soon.
Nights are getting longer.
Yours, Paw Paw.
21 days till Paw Paw.
So you've done,
what, nine dances?
I wish I was just
one notch prettier.
I'm right on the edge, you know,
where it's up to each person
to decide for themselves.
I have to make my case
with each new person.
Is that Tammy or Sasha?
Let's not get it.
Let's just not get it.
Hello.
I think we should play the song.
You know, the signal.
Really?
Where's the charger cord?
I don't know.
Uh, I think it's in my car.
Well, do you want to go get it?
Not really.
But, you know,
if you do, you should.
Never mind. It's not--
Hold on.
Well, I should probably go.
Well, wait a minute,
I have something
I want to give you,
so I'll be right back.
For your cat.
Hi!
What's this?
You don't like my chain?
Ah, it's a little sleazy.
Good. Then you're receiving
the message.
What's--
It means...
It means I'm ready to fuck.
Oh.
Is that, like, a secret message?
Does everyone know that?
No.
Some women look at a chain,
and they just see
a guy wearing a chain.
Yeah? I think of myself
as one of those women.
Can't believe I'm not
one of those women.
Cat's out of the bag.
Are you hungry?
You want a tangerine?
I also have some lemonade.
Something happened today.
To you?
To me, yeah.
We have some time,
more than a month.
This is really just the beginning.
I mean, we have, like,
50 more years together,
and it's just gonna get better.
This is actually the worst time
we're in right now.
It is?
I guess so.
You know, we'll do
some terrible things, but--
And you know all this...
just by being alert?
And noticing everything, yeah.
Why is this here?
I don't know.
Me either.
Maybe we don't know everything.
I was cleaning the kitchen,
and I felt like you were watching me
wipe the counter,
but like--like as if it was fascinating,
you know?
Like when a celebrity walks their dog
or buys groceries or something like that.
That's how I felt all day.
And that's good?
Maybe we can work out
an arrangement,
because I'd like to watch you.
Yeah, I think that would
be very boring for you,
especially when I sleep.
No, it wouldn't.
It would make me very happy
to watch you all the time.
You'd like that?
Well...
I mean, if it was really all the time,
then I wouldn't have to do anything ever.
I wouldn't have to try.
I had you totally wrong.
I thought you were more...
What?
I don't know.
Independent.
Yeah.
Well...
I mean, now that this has happened,
what are my options?
Well, traditionally
people either tell the truth,
or they lie.
Oh, yeah, I could never...
do that.
Jason and I are really close.
I could never do
either of those things.
Hey, your heart, it's racing.
I have to tell you something.
What?
Okay.
One thing...
is--
One thing is that I'm wild.
O-okay.
No.
It's not okay.
When I tell you, l--
Don't blame him,
because it's me.
Him, who?
Marshall.
Who?
But we don't know him.
You look so weird.
If you could see your face, you'd laugh.
I'll leave in the morning.
Hold on.
Just hold on for a sec.
Okay. All right.
I don't know what's going on
right now, but, um,
okay, if you're gonna say
something really bad,
could you just wait a moment?
I just need a moment, okay?
Just give me one moment
before you say what you're saying.
I just want you to kno--
That's enough.
You're free.
Go. Hang out with Gabi.
Act naturally.
Wave.
What am I doing?
You're trying to get to China?
What?
You're like--
You know, when you--
I think that might be racist.
Don't move.
Is it a bee?
The way you look in the light
is perfect.
I like these sheets.
They're 1,000 thread count.
What happens now?
Now we have sex,
and you eat ice cream.
You watch TV, and I watch you.
Wait. Is there really ice cream?
So, here we are.
What's your plan
for the long run?
I think I can just switch back again
when this one gets tired.
But you can't just keep
switching hands forever.
What are you doing?
Sorry.
I forgot something.
What?
It's nothing.
Everything would be perfect there,
Iike a dream,
but not a dream,
because I would never wake up,
and soon I would not even be able
to remember my old life.
Do you think if I moved my hand,
it would be morning by now?
- Morning?
- lt'd be Friday.
What?
It's been 3:1 4 for days now.
But if I moved my hand,
we'd just start from here, right? Um...
I move my hand, and she sits up,
and we just finish talking.
No, it'd be Friday.
Then she's gone!
I move my hand, and she's gone!
But she--she's fucking!
I move my hand,
she's fucking him.
But maybe not.
It could be okay.
You don't know
what will happen at 3:15.
Yes, I do. I know exactly
At 3:15, we aren't going
to get back in bed together,
and she isn't gonna wrap
her legs around my legs,
and we aren't gonna fall asleep.
And then in the morning,
she isn't gonna say, "Hi, person,"
and then we aren't
gonna have another day,
just an ordinary, boring day.
And then we aren't gonna have kids,
and then we aren't
gonna grow old together.
And we aren't gonna
look back on our lives,
because we aren't even
gonna know each other.
That is what is gonna happen at 3:1 5.
You don't know for sure, though.
It could work out in the end.
Yeah, or not.
Or not.
Well, I couldn't bear it.
But you could.
Mom says you're picking me up.
You got your backpack?
It's in the car.
I usually get home by 5:30 or 6:00.
- Open, please!
- Oh.
When do you get home?
Um, around the same time,
5:30 or 6:00,
maybe 4:00.
Bye.
I can tell you right now
they won't be needing anyone
for at least six months.
Really?
I--I can do Frisky Feet.
Frisky Feet is covered.
They have a new girl now.
She was in Circus de Soleil.
She can walk on her thumbs.
- Oh.
- Yeah.
Okay.
There is one opening.
Tammy.
Hey. And Sasha.
Wow.
You're pregnant.
We both are.
But h-how did it happen so quickly?
Well it's been a while
since we've seen you.
Yeah, I know.
I keep meaning to--
It's only been
a few weeks, though.
How does it feel?
It's a drag, but it's also amazing.
That's exactly it.
I--I thought you were--
Barry and Carrie,
this is Sophie.
Hi.
- Hi.
So you're still working here?
Yeah. Um...
but I work up here now, yeah,
which is kind of a drag.
It's a drag, but it's amazing?
Not really.
Wh-where are your mothers?
Oh, well, they passed away
a few years ago.
I--I guess you kind of
lost touch with them.
Anyway, we're here to enroll
our daughter Jayleen
in pre-ballet.
Okay.
If you could just fill out
the top part of this form.
Sure.
You're so tired,
and your arm is so heavy.
Just put it down.
If it's gonna work out,
could you just give me
a little indication,
Iike some sort of signal?
I don't know anything.
I'm just a rock in the sky.
O-okay.
Let's go.
Start it up.
Me?
I was waiting for you to do it.
Wait. So this is it?
It's just this from now on?
I guess so.
Well, what about--
What about--
Did this day already happen?
That day would be today,
but it's almost over.
I can't believe you can't do this.
You do the seasons,
day and night, the tides!
I know, but the ocean's so big,
and I'm so far away.
I could use a little help.
Beautiful day, isn't it?
Yeah.
A beautiful day
A beautiful girl
Come into my arms
Come into my life
You light up my days
You heat up my nights
You make my world
More than all right
Wow.
All original lyrics.
I didn't know you sang.
You bring out that side in me.
I don't know.
Do you believe in soul mates?
Stop!
Okay, kiddo.
Flashlight or no flashlight?
No flashlight.
Sweet dreams.
What? She can't sleep in there.
Yes, I can.
She can get out.
But it's cold.
What about when you have to pee?
I'll pee in here, like a soldier.
She's okay.
Okay, just come in
when you get sick of it.
Please, go.
Is it too hot?
Can I have the drawing back?
Of me.
It's--
It's where I used to live.
Oh.
That guy has it.
I'm his cup of tea.
He said that?
In the moment before it happened,
I kept thinking, "But I'm theirs.
I belong to them."
And then it happened.
I died.
Really.
But even dead, I stayed in my cage,
because I just couldn't believe it.
I wasn't done waiting for them.
Just let me wait forever,
knowing they will one day come.
But that was our cat.
He was already ours.
I'm sorry.
We even waited an extra day.
I just told your husband all this.
Yeah?
Hi. My name's Jason,
and I'm with Tree by Tree.
Do you have a moment
to help reduce--
Yeah, I'm not interested.
That's all right.
I mean, it's probably too late
for all this anyway.
What?
Well, you know how--
how like in the cartoons,
when the building gets hit
with the wrecking ball,
right before the building falls down,
there's always like this moment
where it's perfectly still,
right before it collapses?
We're in that moment.
The wrecking ball
has already hit all of this,
and this is just the moment
before it all falls down.
Is that the official word?
No, that's just my gut feeling.
So why are you going around, then?
I thought this was great, all this...
uh, the air and the grass, yeah,
but it was just the people
and the houses
and the cars and the TV
and the music.
I mean, I just--
I love this place.
I'm sorry. What are you...
We're selling trees.
That's okay.
No--no, thanks.
Where does he live?
Tarzana.
Where is that again?
It's in the Valley.
All my stuff's in my car, though.
Okay.
Everything must look
so familiar to you, hmm?
You must feel like you're coming back
to the place that you left.
That must be nice.
But it's gone, by the way.
This is a totally new land now.
Okay.
Okay what?
You can't agree to anything,
because I haven't proposed anything.
My whole point is that there
is nothing here
for you to come back to,
if that's what you're doing.
There's just--
there's nothing.
Okay, I know.
I'm saying okay to nothing.
I went back for him.
I know. I did, too.
We were too late.
Just one night...
and then in the morning, you go.
After a long time,
a long, long time,
I give up.
Not waiting anymore.
As it turns out,
Iiving is just the beginning,
and so the beginning is over.
I'm cat of nobody.
I'm not even cat.
I'm not even l.
It's warm. It's light.
It goes on and on
and on and on...
It seems we stood and talked
Iike this before.
We Iooked at each other
in the same way then,
but I can't remember where
or when.
The clothes you're wearing
are the clothes you wore.
The smile you are smiling
you were smiling then,
but I can't remember where
or when.
Some things that happened
for the first time
seem to be happening
again.
And so it seems
that we've met before
and Iaughed before
and Ioved before.
But who knows
where
or when?