Subtitled by Yannick Lefoulon
(Alias: Kortess, Sairek, Oxytess).
http://www.tf-world.fr
Our world was created by
a miraculous force called "The AllSpark".
With the AllSpark, there was no strife,
no inequity and no need for war.
In my life time and that of a generation
before me, we knew only peace.
A peace that flourished
under the reign of Optimus Prime...
... and the Lord high protector,
Megatron.
At first, Prime and Megatron
ruled as equals, ...
... the one fair, the other firm.
Then something changed in Megatron.
And what happened next
none of us saw coming.
He struck us from within, his goal
to possess the all-powerful AllSpark...
... for his own twisted purposes.
Those of us loyal to Optimus Prime, ...
... swore to defend the AllSpark
at all costs.
None of our lives matter!
The AllSpark is all.
With the AllSpark...
... new life can arise.
Whether here or elsewhere.
Only a trusted few know this...
... but preperations are underway
to send the AllSpark into deep space.
Better that than allow,
Lord Megatron to possess it, to corrupt it.
Remember, as long as
there is hope...
... there is life.
The AllSpark!
Prime, you fool!
Even now you underestimate me!
My job is done. The AllSpark is
finally beyond your reach.
You! You have cost me
the AllSpark! You!
It seems I must do this
the hard way.
It may take longer,
the result will be the same.
On the day I claim
the AllSpark as my own...
... all of Cybertron will fall
and the universe itself will tremble.
My arm has eventually reattached...
... but my voice capacitor
had shattered beyond repair.
It is decided, we too must venture
out beyond Cybertronium space...
... to find the AllSpark before Megatron.
I still wonder,
did I do enough?
Perhaps like Megatron said,
all I did...
... was delay the inevitable.
And perhaps helped spread our war...
... to other worlds.
It is near.
It calls to me.
The AllSpark!
Terra firma...
Seems anything but to me.
The matter beneath my feet
is both unknown and unstable.
Too late. I realize, my own massive
and external body temperature...
... spell my downfall!
No! The AllSpark!
Not when I was so close!
Over here!
What is it, Danko?
Something under the ice, captain.
Whatever it is, it set the dogs off
something rotten.
It's big. Must be down,
what, ten, fifteen feet?
- Winky, hand me a pick.
- Captain Witwicky, wait!
We had more'n our share
bad luck this vogaye.
Perhaps it's the Fates, telling us
to leave well 'nuff alone.
Sorry, Danko.
But I didn't come all this way
to be well 'nuff alone.
I tell you,
I saw the face of the devil!
It's eyes burned.
And that...
was the last thing that I saw.
That's not quite true,
is it Captain Witwicky?
In fact, according to those members
of your crew we interviewed...
... you retained measure of sight
for some three months after the incident...
... in the Arctic Circle,
during which time...
... you filled no less than
176 sheets of these papers...
... with these curious designs.
Care to tell us what they mean?
Mean?
I... I...
I was possessed.
That thing... looked into my soul!
I saw the future.
Their war. Our world.
Yes, well...
We'll get back to you.
- Well?
- Irredeemably insane.
Brought on by the extreme
rigors of the voyage.
At least that we'll put out.
- So, you believe him, then?
- Oh, yes. He saw something.
It's just the matter what exactly?
What about Witwicky's
personal effects?
They can go to the family, after all
he's hardly likely to be needing these.
When do we leave?
Morning tide. The legislature
has granted us unlimited funds.
And kiss your wife and children if I were you,
you may not be seeing them for some time.
Call this intuition but I have
a feeling that after this one...
... nothing will ever be same again.
Where is he?
Where'd you think?
- He's talking to it again, is he?
- Ah-ha. Downright strange, if you ask me.
I didn't.
Won't be long now.
As soon as the environment dome is complete,
we can begin the excavation properly.
You and I,
we're going to make history.
You what? No.
No, honestly I don't think...
... he'll care what you've
found in Colorado.
Wild horses couldn't drag him away
from his so-called "Mega-man".
Symbols, you say.
I don't...
I thought that'd get your attention.
Whatever's down there, is not only
generating more power than Chicago...
... it's covered with the same symbols
your Captain Witwicky got all worked up about.
- Quite something, isn't it?
- Yes, I suppose it is.
You were there, weren't you?
When they dug him out of the ice?
Yes, I was there.
In many ways "Project Mega-man"
has been my life's work.
And now he is coming here,
to the Hover Dam.
Yes.
Do you know what
Captain Archibald Witwicky was...
... purported to have said after they dragged
him screaming from that icy crevasse.
No. What?
"Mine eyes have seen the glory!"
I believe I know what he meant.
Do you think they'll come? Others?
Not in my lifetime, maybe not even
in yours but they will come.
We could pour other six million tons
of concrete on top of it...
... and they still sniff it out.
- If they do find it...
- Not if... when?
Uplink enabled. Downloading
images to your VTP site now.
Roger, Hubble.
Processing data stream.
Get me the watch commander!
It's confirmed.
We have a visitor.
We sectioned all of Hubble's
routine surveillance footage of Mars...
... for the immediate period
before and after the planetfall.
As you can see,
it's what we've been waiting for.
- Same species?
- Looks that way.
As far as we can tell...
... it arrived under it's own steam,
within some kind of space going carapace.
On touchdown, it transformed.
- Then Mega-man has a relative?
- Exactly.
Tactical teams are on stand by.
As soon as the visitor makes his move...
... we make ours.
Now, that is
what I called a sand trap.
Hilarious.
This is him, right? N. B. E-2?
Right. But where is he?
We tracked him the entire way down...
... and had the impact area
secured within ten minutes.
It should be still here,
inside our perimeter.
What's over there,
beyond those trees?
The I-64.
Come on, come on.
Damn!
Get me satellite surveillance!
Target is mobile.
I repeat, target is mobile!
Show me.
Here's the specific grid vector
surveillance footage you wanted.
Based on your rough time frame.
I've enlarged
and enchanced the image.
What? What am I
supposed to be looking at?
I'll freeze the image.
There.
Yellow Chevy Camaro number 1.
We figure it for a '75 or a '76.
Then exactly
fifty-eight seconds later...
... Chevy Camaro number 2.
- Well, I'll be...
Our boy is a mimic. He must have, what,
scanned first Camaro and then transformed.
I want a team of six, scrutinizing
every inch of traffic camera footage...
... from I-64 to west.
Try and track his progress.
- Where do you think he's headed?
- No idea. Chances are he doesn't, either.
But we have to assume he has
the wherewithal to find his way there.
My legacy?
I have a legacy?
That's right son. Courtesy of
my great grandfather...
... your great great grandfather
Captain Archibald Witwicky.
- He was an explorer.
- Fantastic!
What is it?
Gold coins? Rubies?
- Junk?
- That junk, Sam, ...
... is all that's left of Archibald's
last great voyage to the arctic circle.
He was a true pioneer.
A trailblazer, he was...
Insane? According to this, they
stuck him in a mental hospital...
... and pretty much
threw away the key.
Great. I'm descended
from a madman.
Hey, hey! No one ever proved
there was any actual mental illness.
My father told me
he was just traumatized.
# I haven't found...
#... what I'm looking for
So, who is this guy
they're sending in?
A specialist.
That's all they told me.
Seems he's to be in overall
charge of the operation.
Say that's Oppenheimer, isn't it?
What's the connection?
He was part of the original think-tank.
Set up to analyse and apply
the science behind N. B. E-1.
- N. B. E. -1?
- Yep.
How else do you think
we won space race?
So, all these...
Gentleman.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
I am Agent Simmons.
- Right. The specialist. And this?
- This is... bait.
- Where are we headed?
- New Mexico.
An old cold war bunker. It's been adapted
for our use in exactly this kind of scenario.
And you figure
you can just reel him in?
Absolutely. N. B. E. -2 is here
for the same reason N. B. E-1 was.
He's looking for the cube.
And we are gonna let him think...
... he's found it.
Is that simple, huh?
We just wait for him to show up
and than tag and bag.
Yeah. It's that simple.
Look, it's not like we don't know
what we're dealing with here.
Primitive.
Yes but evidence of
intelligent life nonetheless.
We'll need to proceed
with caution.
Fine. As long as we get to kill
something along the way.
Say again,
Bravo-Echo-Niner-Six.
I repeat, I have
an uniditified impact...
... within Raptor designated test area.
I'm detouring to investigate.
Bravo-Echo-Niner-Six, please give us
your current course and position.
Roger, control.
I switched to bearing...
What the...
I have what I need.
You can go now.
Report!
Blackout here. Planetfall
was clean. No witnesses.
Local camouflage enabled.
- Barricade?
- Yeah. Same.
Well, no living witnesses.
What's our next move Starscream?
Lock onto my position and reunify.
Then we find ourselves the AllSpark.
- And Megatron?
- Right, yeah. Him, too.
What is it?
An isotope, derived from
the sub-atomic matter of the Cube.
It's artificial, of course.
Last time someone tried...
... to actually substract matter
from the Cube itself...
... well, three mile island anyone?
So this isotope, it's giving off the same
sort of energy signature as the Cube?
Almost identical. And when
N. B. E. -2 picks up the scent...
... we'll be ready.
# There's one more ghost here
# And he sits in your chair
They're coming. None of us safe here.
They're coming here.
# And he lays down his head
# On your...
Two days now and nothing.
Maybe only the real deal will do.
Patience. Patience. We waited
over a hundred years for this...
... another day or so won't hurt.
You know something, Agent Simmons?
More time I spend with you...
... more I think this is,
well, personal somehow.
You could say bagging N. B. E. 's
runs in the family.
Wait, you aren't...
Ever since that first one
came out of the ice...
... under the watchful eye
of my great grandfather...
... it's been a waiting game.
Sir, delta-seven eye reports
a positive sighting.
N. B. E. -2 is within the perimeter.
Alert all Tac-Teams.
But tell them to hold position.
No one is going to engage
until I give the signal.
Yes, sir. I'll...
MM. Go ahead delta-seven.
- Understood.
- What is it?
Local law enforcement in pursuit.
Get rid of them. Invoke whatever
national security protocols you see fit...
... but have them
brake of the pursuit, now!
Yes, sir.
According to this...
... none of the New Mexico divisions
has an unit in the area.
- Out of state?
- No. Nothing.
- It's another one.
- N. B. E. -3?
Or more.
So much for the element of surprise!
All teams, converge
on the acquisition site!
Target is now a MH-53 helicopter.
I repeat, a MH-53 helicopter.
Starscream, whatever downs there,
it's not the AllSpark! This is a set-up!
Intelligent and prepared, huh?
I'm started to like it here.
Ready catch nets and prepare
for cyro-immobilization.
Roger that.
Huh. Not on your best day.
Sir, we've lost
Apaches One and Two!
- Have the other squads move in.
- But sir...
Do it!
I can do this all day.
But it occurs to me...
... if these beings knew enough to simulate
AllSpark's resonant energy signature, ...
... it's likely they know
where the actual AllSpark is.
You keep them busy, Starscream.
- What's happening?
- Something is in our network.
It's going through our security
firewalls like they weren't there!
Break our connection
to the S-7 mainframe.
Purge all on-site systems.
Do it, now!
Damn! Starscream...
... they cut me off.
- Get anything?
- Not much. A name, Sector Seven.
Otherwise, it's a dead end.
- Maybe not.
- Barricade?
I was tracking an Autobot
in local camouflage.
Only he got wise to me
before I could take him out.
- And?
- And...
Now I figure to maybe
cut him loose, let him run.
No telling how long
he's been here, on this planet...
... and what other leads
he may have.
So we sit back and let him
lead us to the AllSpark.
Do it but make it look convincing.
# I get knocked down
but I get up again
# You're not gonna
keep me down
# The road keeps winding
# I get just a little closer
Subtitled by Yannick Lefoulon
(Alias: Kortess, Sairek, Oxytess).
http://www.tf-world.fr