Subtitles by josmndsn
Shining.
Shining,
come back here.
Come back here
Daddy!
Daddy! ... Daddy! ... Daddy!
Get in here.
- Fuck, you.
Jeez... baby Jesus!
It's coming down out there the like a
shit load of bricks.
Come on you guys,
were you born in a barn?
Oh, nice one, Hawkins.
- Blow it out your your ass, Gulloy.
That is very inappropriate language.
Hey, don't make me shove those fucking
scissors where the sun don't shine.
Also, very inappropriate language.
- All right, Calm down, Gulloy.
You! Leave him alone.
It's going to be a long night.
Merry Christmas.
Jesus, Gulloy, crank the fucking heat down,
it's like Christmas in Auschwitz in here
for fucks sakes.
Why'd we wait til the end of the
year to finish this crap?
Because we're lazy.
Hey!
Speak for yourself.
Come on, Jeannie.
- Hooo! ...
Careful there, Jeannie.
Robin Hood here is notorious for putting
an arrow through a young maiden's heart.
Well, trust me, I'm pretty
good at dodging arrows.
Uh, oh, was that an
uncomfortable silence?
Yeah.
Speaking of silence, what's with the
cell phones not working tonight?
Hey, you guys got reception?
- No, not for hours.
Fucking storm.
- Okay, get out of my desk.
Fuck you.
To erase this message press 3.
To save the message press 2.
To replay the message press 1.
Alex, ... I need some time
to think, okay?
I just need some time.
Since Mary passed away,
its never been the same.
I'm taking the kids to my
parents for the holidays.
End of message
For the best daddy in the world.
Shining.
Mary.
Can I help you?
Uh ...
Yes, I'd like to make a confession.
Confession?
- I'm here to make a confession.
Confess to what?
Murder.
Somebody, get over here,
I need some help.
I'll get it.
Gulloy. Jesus.
What the fuck is the problem?
- Get over here!
Watch, whoa, hey.
What's going on?
Who are you?
Huh, I thought Dick Tracy
went home for the night?
Aren't the kids
waiting up for you?
No, they're at the in-laws, tonight.
I'm going to join them in the morning.
Ooh.
Dead man's hand. - Bad luck, looks
like you're not going home tonight.
Graveyard shift could use a little
company. Yeah, just like old times Black.
I'm gonna go check on Hawkins.
Excuse me.
What's happening here, Gulloy?
Get over here.
What in the hell's going on here?
- This guy said he killed somebody.
All right, just let's
take it easy, Gulloy.
Gulloy, put that gun down.
You, hands on your head!
Who are you?
Hands on your head.
I said, put the gun down!
- He hasn't put his hands on his head!
Gulloy, put Goddamn gun down.
Hey, hey, hey!
What is this?
Gulloy says this guy walked in
here and said he killed somebody.
Gulloy, put that gun down before I
shove it down your throat.
You. Put your hands on your head.
I said put your hands above your head.
Okay. Tough guy.
Take him to the interrogation room.
Watch him.
What were you gonna do?
Shoot him?
No, just ...
Just go back to sharpening
your pencils
and leave the gun play for
the grownups, will ya.
Ah, what brings the local storm
troopers in tonight.
How's it hanging, boys?
Fratelli, what's up? - We got a
bad accident on the interstate.
It's going to take most of the night
to clear it up. So, we're
diverting traffic and we're
going to close the off ramp.
You guys are going to have
quiet night around here.
- It's already pretty quiet
with the holidays.
I thought you'd be home
wrapping presents.
Yeah.
Well, you and your merry men,
have a good night.
You guys, keep warm.
So, who'd ya kill?
What!?
He's gaslighting you,
let it go.
Hey, I don't like the way
you're eyeballing me.
Come on, Jack.
Everything is in the eyes ...
your eyes ... are full of fear.
You think I'm afraid of you?
- You're afraid of everybody.
Right back to the schoolyard.
That's were you hid first,
right, bully.
Afraid of what ... all the children
will say behind your back.
Right, bully?
- Shut the fuck up!
Come on, Jack,
don't let this guy
push your buttons with
some dimestore psychology.
Fuck you!
- Hey, hey!
Are we okay in here?
Okay.
- Hawkins?
Yeah.
All right, name?
I said name?
What's your Goddamn name?
Noboby ...
That doesn't exactly help me.
All rights.
Nobody, huh.
All right, have it your way.
Mr Nobody. Who exactly do you
claim to have murdered?
Or, am I missing something here?
Yes, you are.
Are you going to confess something,
or is this just a stunt?
I could charge you with making
a false statement, if you prefer.
Detective ...
...be careful what you wish for.
You may get it.
What I can assure you, that before
the evening is out
You will know I'm telling the truth,
that I have committed murder.
Well, let's just stick with the basics.
Get his prints.
Let's see ...
If Mr Nobody here is in the system.
- Pleasure.
Detective, I like that pen,
especially the inscription:
'To the best Daddy
in the world.'
By the way ...
I murdered six people.
"To the best daddy in the world."
Come on, Jeannie.
Why do bachelors always
make such terrible coffee?
Because they don't have women to show
them how to do it the right way.
You know in a round about way,
that's pretty damn insulting.
You know what they say
about mistletoe?
Yeah, some cultures consider being
kissed under the mistletoe
to be the 'Kiss of Death'
Yeah, well, that's just superstition.
In some cultures, being kissed under the
mistletoe, is the 'Kiss of Love.'
Well, there's no mistletoe
here, anyway.
Voilà!
What if somebody sees us?
- It's mistletoe. It's the law.
Yeah.
- Yeah.
What's the matter?
I thought I saw that guy.
I thought I saw him standing right there.
Hawkins and Pine took
him to processing.
Hey, there's nobody here.
You okay?
- Yeah ... too much caffeine.
I'm going to cut down. I ...
I'm going to check something.
Okay. Face front.
Something wrong, deputy?
Are you done?
Jack ... are you done?
Yeah, I'm done.
- Okay, right index finger.
Left.
Give me your other hand.
What?
This guy's got no prints.
Well, how the hell can that be?
I do not know.
I'm going to tell Black.
Lock him up.
Gulloy, get in here!
Do me a favor, lock him up, okay?
Come on. I got to get up on some bulbs.
They all burned out. What are they ...
Just do it, all right?
All right, come on.
Gosh, darn it.
- All the the
bulbs burning out at the
same time. Odds are against it.
Yeah.
- What do you make of it?
I do not know.
Perhaps, it's a warning.
- A warning?
About ... about what?
Did you forget something?
No prints. - Yeah, I'm telling
you, the guy's got no fingerprints.
You can burn prints off with acid.
- Yeah, but it's not permanent.
The pattern goes down several layers of
the skin, but it always grows back.
Yeah, and it would have left some scaring.
- Maybe he cut them off.
The skin grows back along
with the prints.
Yeah, skin's got growth memory.
No shit.
Yeah?
Somebody out there loves cops, makes
sure we always find the bad guys.
All right, so what do you want us
do with this guy?
Aah ...
Look, I'll go over him again in a
minute. I have to make a phone call first.
Hey, Jack, you all right?
You feeling what I'm feeling?
What?
That stranger, Mr Nobody,
gives me the creeps.
Black's starting to make me nervous, too,
if you know what I mean. - Yeah, right.
There's something about this prisoner.
I ... I don't know.
I Can't put my finger on it, but ...
I can't fucking work like this.
Bulbs are burning out
in here, too, Gulloy.
You're just going to have to live
with it. We're all out of bulbs.
There are none in the storage
locker downstairs?
They've all been smashed.
What?
How did that happen?
- I ... I don't know ...
I'm going to go finish processing
Mr. Nobody. - Mr Nobody?
Yeah, he wouldn't give us his name.
So, is he the real deal?
- I don't know.
Black hasn't broken him yet.
We don't want go through that
with Black, again. - No, we don't.
Anyway, this time of year there's always
a lot of lonely people
that false alarms so they can have
somebody to spend Christmas with.
That's so sad.
Yeah?
I got a funny feeling this guy
ain't in no holiday spirit.
Who are you?
Nobody.
Are you okay, deputy?
You look like you've seen a ghost.
What is it?
What is that? ...
That tune.
The Lacrimosa.
Mozart's Requiem, the death mass.
Some say it was commissioned
by a messenger from beyond
for his funeral.
What do you think? Do you think
there's any truth to that?
Yes.
Yes, I know.
Could you please ...
just ...
Look I miss Mary too, you know.
Very much.
Could you please just put the kids
on the phone? Could you do that?
Hey! Hi, guys, how you doing?
Well, uh, Daddy's got some
work to do tonight. So ...
Yes, I will be there for Christmas.
I promise.
You're my best friend.
Daddy look at Shining.
Daddy? ... Daddy? ...
Daddy?
Shining, Shining!
Shining, come back here.
Come back.
I love you guys, too.
Goodbye.
Go get our friend.
You sure? He could cool his heels
until after the holiday.
No, go get him. I need
somebody to work over.
All right.
Hey, Black wants us to
bring the prisoner up.
I need a smoke.
What the fuck?
I'll give you a hand.
Okay, has anybody
seen my scissors?
Gulloy, what cell did you put that guy in?
- Cell four.
Let's go.
Oh, fuck.
One of us must have got the fuse box.
Jesus Christ. Fuck.
Gulloy said cell number 4.
Were you looking for me?
Fuck, Gulloy can at least count.
Hey, ...
Is that my deck of cards?
Where'd you get those?
I said where'd you
fucking get those?
Move it, dipshit.
You tell me all right? -Please.
This is your last chance.
Is she alive?
Where is my little girl?
You're gonna start talking.
- No, I do not know any little girl.
You can't do this.
- Whip him, whip him.
Hit him, hit him, one more, again.
- Where is his daughter?
You know where his daughter is, or
I cut your fucking tongue out.
I'm innocent, I'm innocent...
I'm innocent.
Hawkins come back yet?
- No, I haven't seen him.
All right, do me a favor, Jeannie,
help Sherwood with Houdini here, okay.
Sure.
- Thanks.
Hey, what crawled up you rusty ass
and fucking died?
Did that guy look familiar to you?
Who? Our Mr. Nodbody?
He looks like that drifter.
- What drifter?
The drifter Black made us beat the shit
out of, that's who.
Come on, Jack, that's
not possible.
You better not let Black hear
you talk like that.
I'm telling you, Jerry, I looked in
his fucking eyes, all right. It's him.
Now, you listen to me.
That was a bad situation.
We were all stressed. That's it.
You need to let it go.
You know what's strange?
- What?
It was all of use who were
here that night ...
That's all of us who
are here tonight.
Me, you, Sherwood, Jeannie and
Gulloy and fucking Black.
Some coincidence, huh?
Come on pal, let's get back inside,
it's fucking pissing out.
Come on.
I'll buy you a couple Christmas
drinks after work, all right?
It's about time.
- Fuck you.
You feel like talking yet?
Red dress, blue hair, long legs.
Winking at me.
Who's that. The victim?
You talk too much.
When was the last time you
ever paid for anything, huh?
What are you doing?
I'm going to go check on something.
- All right, I'll see you in a bit.
I stalked ... the victim.
I waited ...
Gulloy!
You better not be fucking
around, Gulloy!
I waited for the fear to set in.
Gulloy!
I'm in no fucking mood.
What's with the lights?
It was dark.
Then I attacked.
I'm innocent.
Gulloy!
- I am innocent.
Let me out, damn, let me out.
Gulloy!
- I am innocent.
Help
You can't do this. I'm innocent.
- Whip him!
Do it, hit him!
Hit him!
Help me!
Where was I?
What the fuck?
Dream.
Watch him.
Fucking, make him talk!
Tell me where his daughter is, or
I cut your fucking tongue out.
I'm innocent.
Jesus! Talk, or I cut your tongue out!
He does not scream no more.
Hey, Pine, did you hear that?
- Yeah, I fucking heard that.
Definitely came from downstairs.
Oh my God.
Jesus.
Red dress, blue hair, long legs
winking at me.
Come on,
let's go, let's go.
Let's go, Gulloy!
Come on, Pine, come on.
- What ...?
Jesus, Black.
Black
What's happening?
How did you do that?
Get both hands flat on the table.
Do it!
What the fuck is going on, Black?
Cuff him, cuff him. Do it!
Both hands. Just do it!
So quickly to violence.
All right. Let's go.
What about him?
Just leave him.
Let's go.
Lock it.
- What for, both his hands were cuffed.
No arguments, do it.
Are you going to tell us what
the hell's going on here, Black?
Hawkins is dead.
What?
Oh my God.
We searched downstairs, the entire
first floor ... nothing.
Okay, how about about outside?
- We're on our way.
Listen, M ...M ... Maybe we should
call for help.
Help? We're the Goddamned
police, Gulloy. GO!
Go cover Pine's back,
get out of here!
All right, you go that way,
check the perimeter.
Listen, M ... m ... maybe it's
better if we don't split up.
Come on. Fuck it.
Get it off.
Get it off!
What is it?
- Where the fuck did that come from?
It fucking came from the roof.
What the fuck ... what is it?
Fucking tag says, Shining.
That was Mary Black's cat.
We need to go up to the roof.
- No, man, no, I'm not going up there.
The fucking roof, get up.
Let's go to the fucking roof.
Did you find anything?
- We're checking the roof.
Jesus, Gulloy, what happened?
- You tell him.
We found a cat.
- A cat?
A dead cat.
The, the collar, the, the tag said
it belonged to ... Mary.
That can't be.
Can somebody just please tell
me what the hell is going on?
There's something I should to tell you.
- What?
Hawkins was acting all weird,
before he ...
What, Pine?
- Well, he just ...
He just thought that ...
Mr Nobody reminded him of ...
...the drifter.
Goddamn it.
Get him in there!
Watch the door, Gulloy!
Get him in there! Get him in there!
Hit him! Turn him around,
turn him around.
Where is she? Hit him again.
Get him up, get him up.
- Where is she? - Innocent!
He's got my little girl.
- You sure? - Yes!
Come on, start talking!
- I am innocent.
Come on. Come on. Look, Black,
maybe she just ran away.
If she's alive, we'll find her.
This is the guy.
I swear, this is the guy.
Look, you can't do this.
...suck it up? You, want to go upstairs?
- No,I'm good. - Good.
I'm innocent, I'm innocent.
- Where is she?
I swear to God,
you tell me where she is.
You heard him!
Where is she?
Look I know that you were spotted in
the same place she was last seen.
Where is she?
- I am innocent.
Just tell me ... is she alive.
Just tell me is she alive.
All right, this is your last chance, man.
Just tell me is she still alive?
Hey, look up, my friend,
look up, huh.
String him up! String him up!
- Come on, Black.
String him up!
Come on, do it. Do it!
- Put it on, Gulloy.
All right.
That's it ...
I'm innocent.
- String him up.
Where is she?
Hit him.
Again, ... again.
I'll fucking make him talk.
- Where is she?
Look at me.
- Hawkins, come on.
Tell me where his daughter is or
I'll cut your fucking tongue out.
Talk, or I'll cut your tongue out.
Where is his daughter?
Where is his fucking daughter?
- Whip him, whip him.
Do it! Hit him!
Hit him!
- Where is his fucking daughter?
Where is she?
Jeannie, put it on his head.
Put it on his head.
I'm innocent.
- Put it on, tight. Tight.
Eye for an eye,
tooth for a tooth ...
More.
Again. Where is she?
You know stranger,
I can do whatever I want.
You know why?
Because you're a nobody.
And that little girl, she's my flesh
and blood. Do you understand?
I'm innocent.
- Everyone ... get out!
Please.
You can't do this. I'm innocent.
- See this? - I'm innocent.
My little girl gave me this pen.
Gulloy, I never meant
for it to go that far.
I was just trying to
save my daughter.
Now, shut up, Gulloy, there was a good
chance that she was still alive.
Yeah, but she wasn't!
Because she was already
fucking dead.
The State Police shot and killed the
guilty fucker who did it.
They even found little Mary's
locket on his person.
We know what happened, Gulloy! A
Goddamn history lesson isn't needed!
That drifter was innocent.
God, you fucking asshole!
Gulloy.
Put it down.
Please.
You snivelling fat fuck.
I may not be much ...
but all I got to do
is pull the trigger.
That's enough!
We all knew what was on the
line that night, right?!
I'm positive.
All of us.
We were all guilty for what
happened that night.
If you didn't like it,
you could have stopped it,
but you didn't.
Did you?
He ...
he's still in a coma, you know.
- How do you know that?
I checked up on him.
He's in Crestdale.
You, what?
Look, you might be able to
live with it, but I ...
...I, I can't live with the lies.
It was you, Black.
It was you who made all of
us swear to that story.
You made us swear that he attacked us
and we were forced to defend ourselves.
Jesus, who have we got locked away?
Pine ... Gulloy, you go
check out the roof.
You two come with me.
We're going to check our Mr. Nobody.
All right.
Let's move out.
Black
- Is he in there?
Open it.
What the fuck was that?
What?
Stay here! - What?
Just fucking stay here.
Pine!
Time to start talking, pal.
My second victim was ...
- Need.
He was a coward.
I came up behind him.
Why are you doing this?
He who does nothing
still faces consequences.
Watch the door, Gulloy!
- What the hell's going on here?
Look, you can't do this.
- Hey, Gulloy, I want you to suck it up!
I'm innocent.
Who are you?
Gulloy!
Gulloy, where the fuck are you?
String him up! String him up!
- Come on, Black!
String him up!
Do it! Do it!
Get that noose on him!
Come on! - I'm innocent!
Don't do this ... Please!
So, with a length of rope ...
I strangled him.
I hung him out to dry.
Fuck!
Oh, Christ.
Pine! Pine!
What happened?
I do not know, we only split
up for a second, man. Fuck me.
Somebody had to be up there.
- I tell you, there's nobody up there.
There wasn't anybody?
- Nobody!
Fuck it. Nobody.
Fuck.
- Come on.
Through all this, it makes me
wonder if God really exists.
Baby, don't fill your head
with all that freaking shit.
Hey, I want that son of
a bitch locked up.
Now! I mean it!
Let's go!
Goddamn.
Jesus Christ
Let he who is without sin
cast the first stone.
You better shut your pie hole.
It's ironic, isn't it? The Old
Testament had a rathful God, but ...
...people became uneasy with the
concept, needed a bestseller.
So they came up with the New Testament.
Suddenly, God was loving
and forgiving.
I'm old school, myself.
I prefer the Old Testament.
I mean, you got to love a God who's not
afraid to meet out a little vengeance
when the need arises.
Get him out of here.
Does the name Mary Black,
mean anything to you?
She was a little girl who
was murdered last year.
She was my daughter.
We arrested a drifter.
We ran his fingerprints,
but they weren't in the system.
Oh, so he was a Nobody.
Yeah.
Lock him up.
Get in there.
The drifter's in a coma, right?
I mean, he's been locked up the whole time,
so how can he kill Hawkins and Gulloy?
Then this guy walks in here with
his Prince of Darkness routine
and has an accomplice knock us
off one by one ...
I don't think the one has
anything to do with the other.
What do you say, Black?
I don't know.
That's it!
What?
Pine, what is it?
Gulloy said he checked up on the drifter
on a regular basis.
Said he was at ... a ...
Crestdale.
- Crestdale.
- Yeah. Crestdale.
Let's see if he came
out of his coma recently.
Yeah, yeah, maybe he's on the loose.
- Wouldn't that be nice.
Crestdale Care Centre,
409 Beatty Street, New York.
Yes, hello, this is deputy Pine.
I'm inquiring about one of your patients.
One of our deputies checked
up on a regular basis.
Yes, that'll be deputy Gulloy.
That's right, the "John Doe."
He died earlier this evening?
You wouldn't happen to know the
exact time of death would you?
Thank you.
The drifter died at 8:14 p.m.
8:14 Stranger enters. Held for questioning.
Gulloy has recorded here
in his log ...
that Mr. Nobody walked through
that door at 8:14 p.m.
All right ... all right.
Uh ...
Look, we need to call
in some help.
Call, uh, Douglas. Get Sheriff McArthur
on the line. - It's Christmas Eve.
I don't give a damn!
We got two dead deputies!
It's dead. - What?
- We were just fucking using it!
It's fucking dead!
- Maybe it's the rain. Just keep trying.
It's dead.
- They're all dead.
Hey, look, I saw some lights when
I was up on the roof.
Maybe it was the state
troopers from before.
Yeah, that's right, they closed
the off ramp for the town.
...that accident on the highway.
Pine and I can go up there.
Use the radio. Call for some back up.
That's a good idea. Do it.
- I'll go with you.
You don't have to do.
- I want to.
I guess we just wait, huh?
Pine ...
Yeah?
...between you and me ...
who do you think we got
locked up down there?
I'm a fucking blank.
Part of me doesn't want to know.
This fucking weather out there?
Black, where are you going?
- I need you to know who the stranger is.
Why?
- You know why.
There they are.
I don't see anybody.
- Turn on your brights.
Okay, where the fuck are they?
- Over here.
I'm waiting for you.
What is that, Goddamn ventriloquist?
- I'm over here.
Help me.
And we're the dummies.
Yeah?
Oh, shit.
- All right.
Slow down.
- I waiting for you.
It was this one.
Look!
- I'm over here.
Fuck.
All right.
This ... a drifter, you mentioned.
Did he have a name?
No.
Why is that?
He wouldn't give it to us.
- He wouldn't give it to you ...
What happened to him?
It was an accident.
- There was an accident ...
Well, I'm ready to continue
with my confession.
My next victim was a married man ...
Get Sherwood and Jeannie on the radio
and get them over here, ASAP! GO!
Hey, where are you guys!
Jeannie, Sherwood, come in.
Jeannie, Sherwood, come in, over!
Did you hear that?
I'll check it out.
Jeannie, Sherwood, come in, over.
- Mary is found, you got that?
Pine?
This is Pine, come in, over.
- Pine, is that you?
Stop it.
- I was hiding ...
...in the shadows.
I found Mary Black's body.
She's cut up, dead. It's awful.
Oh God, who's going to tell Black.
Who is this? - It's awful.
- Identify yourself.
She's cut up, dead.
- Who is this!
Pine, Sherwood, come in, over!
- Mary is found, you got that?
Sherwood, do you hear me?
Sherwood!
Goddamn it.
You persecuted the poor and protected
the rich. - Shut up. Shut up!
Fuck ... Fuck.
Fuck!
Guys?
Guys?!
This is your last chance.
- I was behind him.
He didn't see me.
Black! Black, what the
fuck are you doing?
No! No! Pine, you don't understand!
- What are you doing?
You do not understand.
Come on, play with me, motherfuckers!
You want to play? Come on!
Show yourself!
Show yourself.
Wait, where is he?
Relax, there's nothing.
Look, there's nothing.
There's nothing, nothing there.
Nothing.
...and then I attacked!
Fuck.
What the fuck?
Sherwood?
Sherwood!
Come on. Come on.
Jesus Christ. Fucker.
NO!
Okay, Sherwood. Hit him!
Hit him!
I said, hit him!
Jesus.
No?
No! No!
Sherwood!
Sherwood, where are you?
Of all my merry men's Robin
to run in Sherwood Forest free.
Strife will soon befall them all,
leaving them dead and not married.
Again!
Sherwood!
Please, answer me!
Aaaah!
Goddamn it, Black. You mind
telling me what you were
trying to accomplish down there?
Black, what are you doing?
Jesus Christ.
Jeannie!
He's dead.
- Who? Sherwood?
Jeannie, look at me! Look at me!
Tell me what happened.
We found the troopers cruiser.
It was empty. Nobody there.
I heard the radio and left him.
I'm sorry, honey.
- What's happening?
I don't the fuck know.
Mr. Nobody.
His confessions. Every time he
confesses it comes true.
What, the fuck, are you talking about?
- He's killing us with his confessions.
Jesus Christ.
Look.
Why did executioners where hoods?
- Huh?
Why firing squads only load one gun,
and leave the rest blank?
I mean, why, why did three
guys throw the switch for
the electric chair, and only
one of them had juice?
So nobody had to live with the guilt?
No, it's superstition.
In England ...
the executioners who were
working the guillotine
even though their faces were
shrouded in a black cloth
they would run home. Barricade
themselves behind the door, and hide.
They were hiding from their victims.
Why?
Because they believed that
the victims, the condemned,
would come back as vengeful spirits and
hunt them in the middle of the night.
Even though they covered their faces,
their identities.
That was how they felt they got their
strength. By being nobody.
It gave them freedom from repraisal.
- And the drifter, he's one of them?
Yeah. He's using his cloak of anonymity.
To hunt us from the shadows.
And he's come back to pay us back
for what we did to him.
And we let him walk right through
that fucking door.
But we didn't execute him.
Oh, didn't we. Deny it.
You got us into this. You get us out.
- Hey, I was trying to save my daughter.
All right, that's enough!
Enough. Then, what do we do?
What do we do?
Hell, when I was in Desert Storm
we were hit, I tell you we
were hit hard, right.
Don't believe all that shit
about Saddam's guys just giving up
All right, we were close
to being overrun ...
But our CO, he told us ...
that there was no shame in retreating,
when the decks were stacked against you.
So, I tell you what...
we live to fight another
day, all right?
I think I'll move back that fucking
squad car, all right. Let's go.
Let's go!
Go ahead, push it out.
Back it up, Jeannie.
Fuck.
- What the ...
What am I doing wrong?
- Pop the hood.
Okay. Try it again,
Turn it over, Jeannie.
- Come on!
It don't work.
- Fuck!
Ready to hear my confession?
It's awful.
Ha, ha, ha ...
Coming.
All right, Jeannie, hold on! - Jeannie!
- The fucking door's locked.
Open the door, Jeannie.
She had long golden hair, blue eyes.
I couldn't wait to suffocate her.
Jeannie, open the door.
I don't know
All right, this is your last chance, man.
You just tell me, is she alive?
Listen, I'm innocent.
- No, I'm good!
Jeannie, put it on his head!
Put it on his head.
Ass wipe, tell me where she is.
I don't know
I know it, you were spotted in the
same place she was last seen.
Where is she!
Go back, Jeannie.
You're about to take a high seat
among the Devils of the Dark.
Jeanie, get down!
Poor girl, the powers of darkness
have claimed you for their own.
Come on, motherfucker.
- Christ.
You know what, stranger. I can do
what ever I want and you know why?
Because you're a nobody!
No solid pavement beneath your feet.
No kind neighbors to cheer you on.
Jeannie, get down!
Jeannie!
You are now between the gallows
and the lunatic asylum.
On the way to the silence.
Utter silence.
Jeannie!
No warning voice ...
...no whispering your fate.
You are being assaulted by
the powers of darkness.
The rage from the back of nowhere,
has come to bury you in death.
Poor girl. She lost her head.
Pine ...
Pine!
Pine, what do you think you're doing?
You, shut up! They're dead.
They're all dead.
I'm going to get this son of a bitch!
- Pine!
Fuck.
Were you looking for me?
Time for another confession.
Can't hide in the dark.
The shadows.
Watch the shadows.
The next victim didn't
see it coming.
Dead man's hand.
Pine!
What the heck is going on, man?
Hit him! Hit him!
Turn around!
Where is she?
Get him up! Get him up!
- Where is she?
Shit.
Hey, Look up.
Look up. Huh.
Don't do this.
- String him up!
Put it on! - An eye for eye,
tooth for a tooth.
One more!
I can't see anything.
- I have that eye now.
An eye for an eye,
a tooth for a tooth.
Are you ready to hear my
final confession, Detective?
Let he who is without sin,
cast the first stone.
Stay away from me.
You stay away!
You can't escape.
All roads lead to me.
Leave me alone!
You can't hide in the dark.
I told you.
All roads lead to me tonight.
Where it all started and
where it all ends.
Confession time.
I confess!
I confess that I wronged you.
I confess, all right?
I confess that I wronged an
innocent man, all right.
I have another
confession to make.
I wasn't innocent.
You did it?
Yes.
Hey, little girl.
No?
You did it?
Hey, little girl, good jumping.
Hi.
- Hi.
You have a beautiful cat.
No?
Her name is Shining.
- Shining, that's a nice name.
I have a cat, you want to see it?
- I've got to get home.
Daddy!
The state troopers ...
they shot to kill him.
They found her locket?
- I tossed the locket.
Some poor bastard probably
picked it up.
Some ... drifter ...
some ... stranger.
So, you were guilty.
- Afraid so.
You swore you were innocent.
- What did you expect?
Why?
Why are you killing us?
- Revenge.
I laid in that coma for a year and
all I dreamed about was vengeance.
Do you have any idea how powerful a
dream can be if you can't escape from it.
It takes on a life of its own.
You son of a bitch.
My last victim was
Detective Alexander Black.
He was a righteous man.
Loved his kids.
They'll miss him.
See this? My little girl
gave me a pen.
I'm sorry.
I'm not going to be able
to hear your condfession.
Aaah!
Detective Black, you're dead.
Yours is an impenetrable darkness.
Aaah!
I look at you as a man who is
lying at the bottom of a
precipice where the
sun never shines.
There are not enough tears for
all the sorrow you have wrought.
You are all numbered with the dead.
It's strange how I have to accept
this unforeseen partnership, this ...
choice of nightmares forced
upon me in this place.
Invaded by these men.
These mean and greedy phantoms,
filled with hate.
What ... Who ... Why?
I should have come earlier,
but I was afraid.
I love you.
- I came to help you, Daddy.
I can hear you.
He's a bad man.
- Yes, yes he is, honey.
He scares me.
No?
No, he can't hurt you anymore, honey.
He can't hurt you anymore.
You're going to stop him, Daddy?
I wish I could.
- You can.
Just like the others.
I walked through the valley of death
and became the Shadow of evil.
How?
How can I stop him?
Please, honey. Please tell me
how can I stop him.
He doesn't like his name.
He doesn't want people to know it.
He hides. He hides in the shadows.
It's where he's strong.
Nobody makes him strong.
Uh, huh.
I know his name.
Put ...
that ...
down.
Well, well, well, look who
decided to come out and play.
Stanley Harperton.
That is your name, isn't?
How?
Stanley Harperton, child killer.
- Stop.
Murderer.
- I can't.
Coward.
- Wait ...
Sorry, ... I can't hear you.
Thank you, Daddy.
I love you.
I have to go now.
Mary ...
I love you, too, sweety.
Very much.
Subtitles by josmndsn