[Gunshots]
Check the replay.
Slow-mo.
I told you that motherfucker
was scandalous.
Now we get
to break him off some.
He wouldn't have did it ifhe
didn't have somebody in Houston
to help him get that package.
I wanna know who it is.
Wickey, set it up for Saturday.
I wanna do it someplace way out,
where nobody is, off the track.
I got just the ticket, K.J.
[Grunting]
- Stay back.
- Shit!
Here! I stole
from Jesus Christ. I hid it!
Fifth floor, my apartment.
I never told. Here, take it.
Take it!
Save my soul!
Take it easy, we'll get ya out.
Come on!
Oh, forgive me, Jesus!
- We're tryin' to save your life!
- [Screaming]
God! Agh!
[Beeping]
[Beeping Continues]
[Fire Truck Horn Blowing]
Hey, Don, rememberwhat
that old guy said about
burnin' in hell and all?
This envelope here.
I've been goin' through it,
fillin' out the report.
I think I figured out what
he meant. Is pretty wild.
"Orgill Brothers and Company.
Eugene Delong Employee I.D. Card."
Eugene Delong was
the old man. Read this.
"St. Louis Herald,
February 23rd, 1940.
"Catholic Church
Looted And Vandalized.
"Thieves broke into
St. Anthony's Church
last night...
"and made off with a fortune
in religious articles.
Objects, most of which
were pure gold, were on
special exhibit from Europe."
Is gold, solid gold.
SweetJesus.
I think it was old Eugene
that robbed this church.
Shoot, I'd say there
ain't no question about it.
Wejust solved a crime,
a 50-year-old crime.
Wow, thas pretty wild.
Hey, Vince.
I think our ship
just come in.
This, my friend,
is a treasure map.
## [Country]
[Don]
All I'm saying is, come Saturday
why not drive to East St. Louis,
find this factory
and take a look around?
I got a metal detector at home.
This buddy and I used to go
prospectin' with it.
We bring some tools.
We check out the floor.
If there ain't nothin' there,
it ain't no loss.
If there is, like I said,
why not?
Because is crazy, Don.
We can't walk in a factory
and rip up their floor.
I already called information.
There ain't no listin'
for Orgill Brothers Company.
They're outta business.
Don, the deal is
the guy robbed a church.
Even if the stuff
was still there, we couldn't
just take it for ourselves.
Why not?
Statute oflimitations
on burglary is what,
ten, fifteen years max.
Well, I mean, they
probably already collected
on the insurance anyhow.
You bet yourass
they did.
Is a million dollars
in gold, Vince.
It could be just layin' there
waitin' for us. This could be
the greatest thing we ever did.
##
[Boat Horn Blowing]
I'm pretty sure we head south
once we get over the bridge.
Thas East St. Louis
over there on the left.
Orgill Brothers should be
about a mile south of town.
South it is, parï.
Hey, you tell your girl
where we're goin' today?
You kidding?
I don't want her to think
I'm completely nuts.
I told herwe were goin'
on a department field exercise.
Oh, so is serious
between you two, huh?
Weddin' bells?
Yeah, maybe.
We've been gettin' along
pretty good lately.
She's been real nice.
I hope you have
better luck than I did.
What happened with you two?
Just couldn't get along?
Yeah, I guess
that about explains it.
What the hell ya gonna do?
At least we didn't have kids.
Hey, rememberwhat I said
about keepin' quiet...
if we score so
the I.R.S. Don't find out?
That goes double for Becky.
I don't want her gettin' her hands
on my share, not one thin dime.
[Don]
Don't look like nobody
lives there, does it?
I guess that figures.
We're about a mile
off the highway...
and close to two miles
outside of town.
That means if we find it,
we don't have to cut anybody in.
Les see.
Old Eugene's map has got it
between these two others.
I'd make it that building
there with the fire escape.
Fifth floor, right?
Yeah.
Thad be where
those arch windows are.
Ain't gonna leave it
parked out here though.
Somebody comes along,
the vandal's gonna have
a field day with this thing.
Les pull around back.
See if we can park
out of sight.
We'll have to cut through
the basement of that
buildin' back there.
But at least
the truck'll be safe.
Goddamn. You always
drive around packin'?
Like the man says,
"Don't leave home without it."
Especially when you
go to East St. Louis.
Lfigure Eugene's tenemens
just the other side
of that buildin' behind us.
All we gotta do is
find the fifth floor.
Vince, old buddy,
les get rich.
Les cut on
through here.
When I was a kid, I loved
breakin' in empty buildings
and goin' explorin'.
I always wanted
to find some lost
treasure or dead body...
or a ghost so I could get my
picture in the local paper.
"Local kid finds
JesseJames' gun."
Be a big hero.
Yes, sir, when I was ten,
I'd have thought this was
the greatest place on Earth.
When we find that gold,
it will be.
I'll tell you one thing,
guys that built this place
sure knew construction.
Is like the damn pyramids,
gonna outlast all of us.
Here, les try
on up this way.
Careful, step's loose.
Man, this place
is really wild.
All these stairways
and passages.
No wonder old Eugene
had to draw himself a map.
[Indistinct Creaking]
Hey, you hear that?
What do you think it is?
Shh.
[Creaking Continues]
Behind this door.
Jesus Christ.
Oh, God, that stinks.
Oh, God, oh.
[Coughing]
What was that you
said about wantin'
to find a body?
What the hell
happened to his face?
Rats must have chewed it.
His hands too.
God, thas rank.
Look, poor bastard even had
his shoes on the wrong feet.
Yeah. Draft in here
is makin' the body swing.
Come on,
les close this up.
I guess
we gotta report this.
We better find some
local cop and tell him...
Hey, bullshit.
This ain't none of our business.
East St. Louis cops can solve
their own damn cases.
How long you think that
guy's been hangin' there?
Couple of months maybe.
Maybe a little more.
Suicide, I figure.
Suicide? How do you
know it wasn't murder?
Nobody murders somebody
by hanging 'em.
Yeah, but people that kill
themselves like to be found.
They leave notes or somethin'.
What ifit was murder?
You've been watching
too much TV, Vince.
You're beginnin'
to sound like Geraldo.
All I'm sayin' is,
I think we oughta report it.
Look, I didn't come all
the way up here to worry
about some old stiff...
who's probably
been dead for months.
You want to report it,
fine. But les report
it on the way home.
I mean, the guy
ain't goin' anywhere.
Okay. Okay,
I guess you're right.
Damn right I'm right.
I'll tell ya something else
I'm right about.
This is the fifth floor
and behind that door...
thas where Eugene
stashed his gold.
Whad I tell you, Vince?
This vestibule must lead
to where the apartments were.
I'd say old Eugene knew
what he was talkin' about.
Hey, look at that.
Peep slot.
Old-fashioned security.
We're gonna find that gold.
I'm tellin'you
I can smell it.
All right now, here we are.
We're back from
the third window.
I'd make that one the third.
So maybe 'round there, huh?
Les find out.
[Beeping]
[Beeping Increasing]
There it is, Vince.
I told ya.
Didn't I tell ya it
was gonna be here?
Stand back.
Go on. Go on.
Hit that thing.
Come on, Vince.
[Laughing]
I knew we was
gonna find it.
Come on!
Shit! Just some pipe
and an old junction box.
You know, we're probably gonna
find lots of this kind of stuff.
Maybe this is gonna take
longer than we thought.
I'm gonna keep scannin'
the floor. If I get
a signal, you dig it up.
If you see anything,
you let me know.
Okay.
Hey, how come
you get the easy job?
Is my metal detector.
Shi...
## [Indistinct Rap]
##
Whose wheels, man?
I don't know.
I'm gonna drive
all around this place...
and I better not see any
more cars other than
Wickey's, right?
Why are you goin' off on me,
Goose? I don't know
whose car that is, all right?
Give me a break.
All right, Lucky.
Don't let this
be no okey-doke.
[Grunting]
Hey, Don,
find anything?
Just some more damn pipe.
I'm gonna check
on through there.
Yeah, you do that.
Don! Goddamn!
Get him off me.
Don.
Freeze, asshole.
Don't shoot me!
Get up! Get up!
What the hell you doin'
jumpin' him like that?
I piss on him.
I thought
he was a crackhead
tryin'to steal my money.
Who are you? Talk.
Is my money.
Is all the money I got.
What are you doin' here?
I live here.
What you think, dumb ass?
I've been hidin'
ever since you come.
Whas your name?
Bradlee.
Guess what, Mr Bradlee?
You're trespassin' here.
You're full of shit.
Don't nobody own
these old buildings.
I got a good mind to take
you down and bust you.
Give me a break!
You ain't gonna
bust me for nothin'.
I oughta run your ass in.
I ain't gonna give you a break.
I'm gonna take you down.
[Bradlee]
Get yourfuckin'hands off me, man.
Get up!
As soon as I do,
I'm gonna kick your butt!
I'm gonna blow
your fuckin' head off!
You got no right to be messin...
Get in there!
Sit down!
You got no right to be
treatin' me like this!
Who do you think you are?
Now, cover him.
You know how to use this thing?
What are you askin' me for?
Do you know
how to use it?
Of course I know.
I was four fuckin'years
in the State Guard, but I
don't want any part of this.
You're already part of it.
Take it and keep him covered.
Take it!
Look, Don, he's just an old
tramp. I don't see why
we just can't let him go.
What, so he can come
back with the cops and a
whole bunch ofhis friends?
Hey, man, I ain't
goin' back to no cops.
I ain't goin' to no cops!
I don't care
what you're doin'here.
I don't know nothin'.
- Cross your hands. Cross 'em!
- We're gettin' in awful deep.
I thought we agreed.
We found somebody here,
we cut 'em in on it.
I say he ain't
entitled to jack shit.
You wanna cut him into
your share, you go right away.
Share of what?
What you gray boys
cookin' up?
Keep your mouth shut, old man.
Now you listen to me,
Vince.
I got mortgage
payments on a house
I just got kicked out of,
plus my own rent money
which they just jacked up on me,
plus fuckin' taxes that get
higher every fuckin'year...
just so that guys
like him can keep eatin'
without doin' any work.
Now if that loot is here,
buddy, I want it.
And I'm not gonna share it
with some old bum.
[Clicking]
Look, I...
I don't like this at all.
But you don't have to worry,
'cause nobody's gonna hurt ya,
I promise.
What right you got
to come bustin' in here,
messin' with a man's shit
and fuck it all up?
Look what you done
to my floor.
How am I gonna live here?
Just look what you done.
I said I was sorry.
Look, I'll make it up to ya,
all right?
Here's 40 bucks, okay?
40 bucks!
What, you gonna give me
a mule too? Fuck you.
Shit, if you don't want it,
I'll keep it.
We... Well.
Yeah, wait, I'll take it.
[Grunting]
[Indistinct Noise]
[Pick Pounding]
Don! Don!
Somebody's comin'!
## [Indistinct Rap]
##
All right, he makes any noise,
you shut him up.
How am I supposed
to do that?
Oh, shit.
He's a tied-up old man.
How hard can it be?
Bust him in the face
ifhe gets outta hand.
Untie me and I'll bust you.
Don, I'm not gonna
duke out some crazy old man.
Christ!
Will you understand
the fuckin' situation here?
I understand fine.
I got two white
motherfuckers breakin'...
[Bradlee Muffled]
And you, I'm gonna go
through you like Ex-Lax.
[Muffled]
Hey! Come back here!
Fuck you!
##
Hey, Don, this whole deal's
goin' south. Les get
the hell outta here.
I'm not leavin' here
without that gold.
You stay here.
I'm gonna take a look around.
Anybody else live
in this building?
Come on, just shake
your head yes or no.
Shit, I gave
you 40 bucks!
[Muffled]
Fuck you.
All right, he'll be
here any minute. Wickey
don't break his word.
He better or
I'm gonna kick your crippled
ass back down those stairs.
Hey, man, why don't you
relax, Goose? I'm just
tryin' to set things up.
[Indistinct Chatter]
He's right there.
Funny you picked up here.
This is where KingJames
keeps his stash at.
What you talkin' about?
Is right over there
in the airvent.
Don't be bullshittin' me.
Man, I ain't.
I'll go get it foryou.
Yo, whoa, whas up?
You think I'm stupid, Lucky?
You think I'm gonna let you
walk over there, put your hand
and pull a piece out on me?
Yo, Wickey, keep your snake ass
where I can see ya, all right?
[Screaming]
- [Screaming]
- Goose!
Don't you be gettin'
outta hand now.
Lucky's just got a real
nasty sense ofhumor.
Yo, Goose, I think you need to
leave my little brother alone.
Come here.
You all right?
Yeah, I'm cool.
Turns out the other night
you wasn't alone. Remember
the other night, Goose?
One of my boys got killed.
K.J.'s right.
Video never lies,
Goose.
I was there the whole time
tapin'your punk ass.
I don't know what
you're talkin' about.
Ain't that amazing? Now
the nigger don't know nothin'.
[Phone Ringing]
[Ringing, Beeping]
Whas up? Yo, Marvin,
I can't talk right now.
We're gonna handle that
business, but not right now.
I'm in the middle of somethin'.
Call me back, man.
Yeah, later.
What the hell's
goin' on up there?
Where's Don?
Y'all makin' a big mistake.
I don't know nothin'
about nobody gettin' offed.
I don't think so, bitch.
You're the one made
the mistake, motherfucker.
[Goose]
Hey, K.J., you got
to slow this shit down.
This situation does
have an explanation.
Now, who you
been workin' for, man?
Who you sold us out to, punk?
Why are you
sweatin' me, man, huh?
You can kiss my black ass.
Now get on your little
phone and run tell that.
[K.J.]
You ain't gonna make
this easy, huh?
[Goose] No,
this ain't gonna be easy.
Yo, Cletus, les show
this man your shoes.
Be real fucked up
ifhe had to use 'em on you.
Stomp a mud hole on that
ugly-ass face of yours.
[Growling]
[Screaming]
Goddamn.
Hey, motherfucker!
What the fuck you doin'?
I said, what you doin'?
Nothin'.
Cool, it works.
Watch out, man, watch out.
I thought...
You thought what?
I saw... I saw
your friend fall.
Niggerwasn't my friend.
Who are you, man?
What you doin' here?
Huh?
What the fuck you
lookin' at me for?
The man asked you
a question. What the
hell are you doin' here?
Nothin', I'm just here.
I'm not lookin' for trouble.
Is that right?
You fuckin' with us,
white boy?
No, man, like I said,
I'm not lookin' for trouble.
Bullshit.
I'm gonna ask one more time.
What the fuck you doin'?
He's spying.
I'm not spyin'.
I don't wanna get in the
middle of no big gang hassle.
Gang? You think we're
some big punk-ass gang?
I'm a businessman.
These are my associates.
Whateveryou say, man,
no problem.
Back off!
All of ya!
Get outta here, or I'll
blow his fuckin'head off!
Don! Don!
Come on!
[Don]
Back off! You clearoutta
here, or I'll kill him.
I swear I will!
[Indistinct Shouting]
K. J!
Hurry, Don!
Come on, man!
Make a run for it!
I mean it, man!
Back off!
Don't shoot!
He's got Lucky, man!
[Gunfire]
Don't shoot!
Hold your fire!
I'll blow his head off!
[K.J.]
Stop. Stop shootin', man.
Stop shootin'.
Fuck!
Don.
Jesus Christ.
We gotta get out.
The fire escape,
the window. Go!
Savon, go downstairs.
Make sure nobody's tryin'
to get out the window.
All right.
[K.J.]
Calm down. No more shootin'.
What you want?
Come on, stand up.
Have you got a weapon?
Huh?
I ain't got nothin'!
You got a weapon?
Huh?
Don't fuck with me, man.
I ain't got shit.
Yeah, whas this?
[Beeping, Ringing]
[Ringing]
Yo, Savon?
Yeah?
What was that?
That was me.
I blasted at him
tryin' to come down
the fire escape.
Get him?
Nah.
All right, stay posted
down there. No more
shootin' unless I tell ya.
I don't wanna spook'em
any more than they already are.
All right, all right.
Shit.
Goddamn it, Vince.
Why didn't you stay put
like I said?
'Cause I thought
you were in trouble, thas why.
Where the hell did you
go all that time? Shit!
All right, Cletus, Wickey,
les try this door.
They got Lucky in there.
They're probably tryin'
to get out the back way.
[Wickey]
All right, cool.
Come on.
[Phone Ringing]
Shit!
[Ringing Continues]
Now back off, all of ya!
You come any closer,
he's a dead man!
Go on, get back.
Get back.
[Ringing continues]
Yeah? Marvin, goddamn it!
This ain't the time!
I got some problems right now.
Yeah, we're gonna handle
business on that package.
But I gotta get back
with your ass.
Wickey, you know yourway around
here. Any otherway out beside
the door and fire escape?
Hell, no. There
ain't no otherway out.
All right, check this out.
Cletus, go downstairs.
Get rid of Goose's body.
Then go to the car,
get the M-16. But go out
the same way we came in.
I don't want nobody to see us,
all right? Go on, man,
get the fuck out.
Yo, hey in there,
how do we know Lucky's okay?
Tell him.
Hey, man, I'm cool,
but this motherfucker's crazy.
Don't worry about it, man.
We're gonna get you outta there.
Check his fanny pack
down on the floor.
See ifhe's got a gun.
I told you
I ain't strapped.
Shut up.
Anything?
Don, this guy's
some kind of dope addict.
Figures!
All right, cut me
two six-foot lengths
of that rope in my bag.
Come on, move.
Wickey, go down there,
use Savon's phone.
Call up Luther, Moon
and Davis and tell 'em to get
their ass over here right now.
- You got it.
- Yo, also call up Raymond.
Tell him I need some
of that goddamn heavy
artillery he's got.
Raymond?
You sure you want him
in on this?
Yeah, goddamn it! Don't give
me no more fuckin' shit.
Get that goddamn camera
outta my face.
Von, give me your phone.
Forwhat?
K.J. Wants Raymond here.
Finally got some guns
comin' up here.
Shis gettin' hectic.
[Beeping]
Figure they're the police
up there, man?
Ain't got no fuckin' idea.
Hello, Raymond?
Your name is Lucky, huh?
I ain't talkin' to you.
I ain't tellin'you shit.
[Don]
Fine. Vince.
How many did you see out there?
Five. Tie his arm
to that door.
There's gonna be
more than that...
'cause my big brotherJames
down there, fool,
he's a king around here.
He'll spread the word.
Your big brother, huh?
Thas right. Let me tell
you white boys somethin'.
You don't let me go,
he's gonna fry your
motherfuckin' asses.
I thought you
weren't talkin'.
Hey, James, we got
your kid brother tied
spread-eagle against this door.
That means anybody
shoots at the door,
they're gonna kill him.
Anybody tries to break it down,
they're gonna rip his arms
outta their sockets. Got that?
I hearya.
Just don't do anything
stupid in there.
You gotta tell us, Bradlee, is
there anotherway outta here?
I don't gotta tell you shit.
Goddamn it.
Don, these bars
are pretty solid.
Hey, Vince.
Over here.
Vince, that catwalk there
goes out to another building.
Lfwe can get to it, there's
gotta be anotherstairway in
there. We can get to the truck.
Yo, Cletus, go on top.
Keep it secure.
I wanna keep 'em boxed in.
Go, man.
Come on, go.
[Don]
Careful.
Okay.
[Crashing]
- Yo, Lucky! Y'all right?
- Yeah, man, I'm all right.
Shit!
Fuck that plan.
Them motherfuckers
still alive in there?
Yeah!
How many in there with ya?
There's three,
but one of'em was tied...
He can't talk right now!
Yo, man.
Listen, man.
We don't want no trouble.
We just want my brother back.
Just let him out.
Why don't you come out?
We could discuss this.
You just bring the cops.
We'll discuss it with them!
They're drug dealers.
They just threw a guy off the roof.
They ain't gonna call the cops.
Yo, man, that ain't
necessary. All we want
is my brother back, man.
- All we want is Lucky, man!
- Find me a rag.
You heard him. As long as
you got me, they're gonna be
on your asses like glue.
They already got the place
surrounded, and my brothers
will be here with more soldiers.
Yeah? As long as
we got you, they ain't gonna
be shootin' at us, are they?
I ain't scared of shit.
You know why?
I've been through three drive-bys,
and I ain't never been hit.
Bullets just go around me.
Thas why they call me Lucky.
Lucky! Motherfucker.
Look, all they want
is the kid.
Now they know we got a gun.
Maybe if we let him go,
they'll back off!
Damn it, Vince.
They want us dead.
We're witnesses.
As long as he's alive,
we got a chance.
If we let him go, they're
gonna kill us for sure.
[Honking]
## [Indistinct Rap]
##
Is about time
you guys got here.
So, whas up?
You got a problem?
Yeah, we got a problem.
Shit, three more.
Makes eight of'em.
We're screwed, Don.
[Footsteps]
Hey, yo, K.J.,
Man, whas up?
Three white motherfuckers,
they got my kid brother in there.
Three?
I didn't see but two.
Lucky said there was three.
You get Raymond?
Yeah, man, he'll be here.
White motherfuckers?
Down here?
Who are they, the man?
Hell, no. They just asked me
for cops. If they want cops,
they can't be cops.
[Grunting]
Damn it!
Shit.
Let me try that Halligan.
[Don]
Come on. Here we go.
All right.
[Grunting]
You fucker!
## [Indistinct Rap]
##
Shit, another one.
Looks like
some fuckin' pimp.
#Leave me alone I got posse
bust the bets #
#You betterwatch me
I gotta do what I gotta do #
#So who the hell is you to
tell me how my song is wrong #
#You don't know#
[Beeping]
Yo, Wickey, this is Raymond.
Where do you want me to park?
What do you
think's goin' on?
Nothin' good.
[Laughing]
I think I finally figured out...
how you boys are gonna
get a chance to get outta here.
Body bags!
[Laughing]
[Savon]
Oh, shit. Pussy in the trunk.
[K.J.]
Raymonïs good forsomethin'.
All right. This shit here
takes out a ras ass
at 300 yards.
Shit, I'll take that. I was
a sharpshooter in the army.
You don't look like
no sharpshooter.
I was the best in my company.
Ease back, motherfuckers.
This is mine.
You know what I'm sayin'?
[Raymond]
Go, Wickey, dive in there.
I don't need no big-ass gun.
Mess up my suit. This right
here will do me just fine.
[Raymond Laughing]
All right, all right,
Mr Leader Man.
Whas your plan?
Come on over here.
Them country motherfuckers
was cryin' about the police, right?
They want cops?
Give 'em cops.
[Raymond Laughing]
Yeah.
[Video Man]
Hello, Officer Friend.
How are you?
Hold it, hold it.
Hold it.
This ain't gettin' us anywhere.
This place is
too goddamn secure.
At least the good news is,
they can't get in either.
That means we just sit tight
and wait 'til the cops show up.
[Laughing]
What are you
laughin' about?
Who's gonna call the cops,
the pigeons or the rats?
What about a patrol car?
Don't patrol cars come
around here?
Think they'd throw a guy off the
roof in broad daylight if there
was a chance cops would come?
Cops ain't comin' by, Vince.
We're on our own here.
We got 21 shells.
I'm gonna take 11.
You're gonna take 10.
That way whoever's
got the gun can reload.
Listen, I got an idea.
Why don't we bust down
through this floor...
and drop down to the
apartment right below us?
That ain't gonna work.
Lfthe layous the same
as it is up here,
we're gonna be stuck
without our hostage.
We'll be dead meat.
Bradlee, you ever been
down to the fourth floor?
Is there a back stairway?
Fuck you.
[DoorOpening]
Anything happen?
No, all quiet, K.J.
Go downstairs, help 'em out.
Tell Wickey to call me up
when he gets it set up.
Is this gonna work?
It better.
I'm gettin' tired of this.
##
[Footsteps]
Man, those are some
weird, fuckin' footsteps.
What is that?
Spikes. One of the guys
was wearin' baseball shoes.
Big son of a bitch.
[Phone Ringing]
[Ringing Continues]
Yeah?
[Video Man]
Savon, what up, man?
Shit, we're ready.
Les just do it.
They're gettin' close.
This shis got me pissed off.
Man, this is stupid.
[K.J.]
Got everything goin'good,
then two stupid-ass honkies...
come up in here
and fuck up everything over
some dumb nigger named Goose...
that nobody gives
a fuck about dead oralive.
Only thing keepin'
'em alive's my brother.
Savon said thas
a bunch ofbullshit.
Says you and Lucky
ain't even got the same pops.
He's my brother, man.
I been takin' care ofhim ever
since he was born and I was 15.
All right, man.
We hot, we goin'.
[Siren Wailing]
Stop, this is the police!
Stop! You there!
Nigger! Freeze!
Fucker! Spread your legs!
Spread 'em!
Take it easy, man.
Gotta make this shit
look real, man.
Where you got the dope,
boy?
Don, there's a cop
out there!
[Cocking]
Help! Hey, Don!
Get me out!
Someone come back here!
Come back!
Get me outta this cha...
Shit. Come on.
Go. Go.
Fuckers, move.
Go!
Go, man!
[Gunfire]
Get me the fuck outta here!
[Muffled Shouting]
Shit. They got Davis.
Fuck!
[Bradlee]
Come here, you two idiots.
Come over here.
Bring your asses in here
right now! Move! Move!
Get me off this damn floor.
Come on, get me up off here.
What the hell?
Move it, both of ya!
Hurry up!
What the fuck you tryin'
to do, get me killed?
I thought he was a cop.
You stupid peckerwood.
You'd fall for that shit?
He was wearin' a uniform!
You're just a stupid,
dumb-ass redneck!
You shut your goddamn mouth,
you black son of a bitch.
Black son of a bitch?
Fuck you! Kiss my black ass.
Goddamn...
Hey! Hey!
Hey!
Vince!
Lfhe doesn't shut up,
I'm gonna shut him up.
Man, what the fuck was that
bullshit goin' on over there?
I told you not to shoot
'til you got a clean shot.
You got Davis killed.
Fuck that.
It wasn't my fault. It was
that motherfuckin' Luther!
It was both you
dumb motherfuckers.
Okay, we fucked up.
But you fucked up too.
Ain't none of your shit
worked all day.
The point is,
what you gonna do now?
I'm gonna go up under them
so they don't dig no tunnel.
You need to go
get rid ofDavis'body.
I ain't the garbage man.
Moon, go get rid ofhim.
Bullshit. That ain't
my motherfuckin'job.
No, Moon, go do it.
At least I know the
shill get done right.
Now you, you keep this
trigger-happy shit up, you're
gonna get all of us killed.
I don't know how.
I ain't the leader.
[Beeping]
I'm not gettin' anything.
Is not gonna work. There
ain't no apartments up there.
Is just attic.
No pipes, no plumbin'.
And I don't remember seein'
no metal on the floor.
Yeah, but shit,
tryin' to pick up metal cleats?
[Beeping]
Nothin' here.
I'm goin', Vince.
Wait a second,
les stick to the plan.
I'm goin'.
Lfhe's down by
that window, he can
still get a shot at you.
Just let me keep scannin'
the floor'til I find him.
That way we'll be sure.
All right.
Find him, will ya?
What are you guys doin' now?
Where'd you get all this shit from?
- Anything yet?
- No, nothing.
Man, you know I'm gonna be
there. Raymond ain't gonna
let you down. What you need?
- Yo, Raymond?
- Hang on a second, man.
I need you to do some
recon for me. Figure out
how them fools got here.
- I know they didn't walk.
- I ain't got time to be playin' army...
with you trigger-happy motherfuckers.
I got business to take care of.
Yo, cancel it.
You're workin' for me now.
I'm hirin'you
for the rest of the day.
What the fuck you waitin' on?
Get to work, motherfucker.
Yo, we're gonna have to
reschedule that thing.
[Beeping Increasing]
I got him!
- Whereabouts?
- Right over here.
All right, I'm goin'.
Wait a second.
He's movin'.
[Beeping Increasing]
Jesus Christ.
Give me that.
[Bradlee]
What are you gonna do?
Wait a minute.
Don't cut me! Don't cut!
I'm gonna cut you loose,
old man.
I need your chair,
but you better behave yourself.
Yeah, I'll behave myself.
You can have the chair.
I got a table downstairs
you can have.
Go!
Yeah, you can have it!
Careful.
Halligan.
[DoorCreaking]
Whas up, man?
You dump the body?
Yeah, I threw him
in the trunk of your car.
What?
You heard me.
Man, fuck you.
[Blowing]
Flashlight.
Something here.
[Laughing]
Holy shit.
[Don]
There's more, Vince.
Lord have mercy.
I've been sleepin' under
all this all these nights.
I don't believe it.
This is it, Vince.
This is it. There's
a treasure trove up here.
Is all here. Just
like the newspaper said.
You're damn right.
Ourship's come in, buddy.
We're rich.
Now you peckerwoods are startin'
to make sense. I can see why
you was tearin' up this place.
Though I can't figure...
If is in the ceiling, why'd
he say it was in the floor?
I mean, we both heard him.
The man's dyin' words:
"Is in the floor."
Wait a second.
Is a map of the ceilin',
not the floor. Look.
Hold it up.
Is right as rain. He
drew it layin' on his back.
Oh, Eugene, you dumb fuck,
that ain't no way to draw a map.
Wow, this stuff's been
in there over 50 years.
Is not even tarnished.
[Bradlee]
You don't know nothin', do ya?
Thas the beauty of gold.
It never tarnishes,
lasts forever too.
You can melt it down,
pound it, twist it, piss on it,
but is always the same gold.
It was here long before we were;
be here long afterwe're gone.
Bet you a lot of men have died
for the gold thas just in this piece.
How'd you get to be
such an expert on the subject?
He probably heard it in
some pawnshop somewhere.
[Laughing]
You don't know nothin',
neither one of you.
Is all here, Vince.
Is all here.
All we gotta do is pack it up
and get to that catwalk.
We'll get our butts outta here.
I told you.
I told you we're rich.
We're rich, buddy! We're rich!
[Screaming, Groaning]
Hey, you broke
my rockin' chair.
Hey, man, you all right?
[Laughing]
[Kicking Feet]
What the fuck they doin' up
there? Havin' a party?
[Laughing]
I don't know.
Is the last one
they ever gonna have.
Don't even trip, Savon.
Now, you ain't the boss.
Now, the man said
no shootin'.
Don't you ever draw down
on me, motherfucker.
[Muffled Grunting]
Christ, what now?
Come on, man,
just let me go. Please!
I'm sick.
What do you mean
you're sick?
[Bradlee]
He's ajunkie.
He needs his dope.
They get sick all the time,
they don't get a fix.
Shakin', pukin'.
Geez, thas too bad.
Fuck you.
You just remember that
that gold is ours.
- Yeah, how do you figure?
- This is our territory.
You don't live here. We do.
[Bradlee]
Bullshit. I live here.
All your kind ever does is fuck
everything up. I got a better
claim to that gold than you.
You?
Thas a hot one.
Thas really fucked up,
man.
Only time you white boys
ever come down here is when
you wanna rip us off.
We didn't come down here to rip
you off. We're just tryin' to
get ahead like everybody else.
Look, motherfucker,
the gold is ours.
You let it go.
Maybe I can talk my brother
into keepin'you boys alive.
You mean that?
[Don]
He's talking through his ass.
Gag him, or I'll come over there
and shut him up myself.
Didn't I tell you to kill
that cowboy crap?
Yo, man, I just shot
the catwalk out there.
We gotta discourage 'em
from gettin' across somehow.
You need to stop thinkin'
with your trigger finger
and use your brain.
- You're gonna get my brother killed!
- All right, man. Fuck it.
Bradlee, you sure
there ain't nobody else
livin'around here?
Somebody like you
who mighve heard
that shootin'?
Fella used to live around
named Thomas.
He'd go twice a month
to give blood.
Thas how he got money.
They told him not
to come back no more. He was
a real sad fella, no family.
He never could get
his shoes on right.
That was summertime.
I ain't seen him since.
Yo, Luther.
Where are you, man?
[Luther]
Over here, on the catwalk.
What you doin' here?
KingJames sent me
to help you look out.
I don't need no help.
I got this covered.
Go on back.
Okay, call KingJames
and tell him...
that you think his plan
is full of shit.
You crazy?
Know whas gonna happen?
Motherfuckin' police gonna
be around here.
You think this on now?
Is really gonna be on then.
King. James. Like he's
king ofthe street orsomethin'.
Ain't nobody king of the street.
Is all about survival.
Is all about gettin'yours.
It ain't about takin' no chances,
and it sure ain't about
jeopardizing yourwhole crew.
I like Savon, man.
I like him a lot.
He's just a hothead.
He thinks he knows it all.
I used to be just like
Savon when I was comin' up.
You gotta be philosophical
about this shit. Is all crazy.
As long as you know is crazy,
you're all right.
But soon as you try
to make logic outta this,
you're fucked up...
'cause it don't make
no sense.
The white man makes dope,
right? Then he gives it to us.
Then he wants to buy it
from us.
Then he puts us in jail
when we sell it to him.
It don't make no fuckin' sense.
Only thing a man's got
is his family and his pride.
Thas all he's got.
[Don]
I don't know what
this stuff is anymore.
Goïs gold, our gold,
fool's gold.
About all we can do...
is take as many of'em
with us as we can,
and hope forthe best.
Maybe we could try
walkin' outta here,
usin' Lucky as a shield.
Not with just one gun.
Be better tryin' to nail
one of them first,
get ourselves
anotherweapon.
What about tradin' the gold
to 'em for our safety?
They'd kill us anyway.
I would if I was them.
Truth is, I don't see
any way we're gonna
get outta here quiet.
A fortune in gold, and
is just plain worthless.
We might as well
let Bradlee go.
Yeah.
Hey, Bradlee.
We got no reason
to hold you here anymore.
You're free to go.
Hey, wait a minute.
I got a proposition forya.
That gold laying over there
is worth a million dollars.
You can have all of it.
You can take it all with ya.
You just promise one thing:
You're gonna call the cops for us.
It ain't gonna do me
no damn bit of good.
How am I supposed
to get outta here?
They're gonna kill me
as soon as I step
one foot outside the door.
Them niggers'd kill anybody,
including their own grandma.
You haven't got
much of a chance
in here with us.
If I can figure a way
to get us outta here,
do I get the gold?
You know a way out?
Do I get the gold?
Hell, yes!
Les hear'im out!
Wait a minute!
You know a way for us
to get outta here, we
split the gold three ways!
We're in this together.
Thas not what you said
a minute ago.
A minute ago we was all dead.
Now, take it or leave it.
I'll take it.
The chimney.
There's a chimney behind
the wall. We could get out
through the chimney.
Well, here it is.
We still got a deal?
## [Indistinct Rap]
##
#... and keep all the shit
under my control #
#Thas how I'm livin'
I check my bank #
## [Rap Continues]
##
#Most ofthe time
I can't be stopped#
#A word to my enemies
I don't drop flop #
#A word to the Klan
I don't pick crops #
#You can run up with your
whippertojust run up
'til you're hot #
#A word to the tipper... #
#A word to the bourgeois
Fuck off, y'all #
#A word to apartheid
You bounced the ball #
## [Rap Continues]
##
This is gonna work,
Vince.
We gotta go up,
but there's an access door,
put us right on the roof.
[Siren]
Shit!
Don, hold it.
[Siren]
[Police Radio: Indistinct]
Cops!
Vince, no! Wait!
Is a police car!
Is the real police!
We don't need 'em!
You're crazy!
Hey...
Hey, poli...
Listen to me, Vince.
We got a million dollars
worth of gold here!
If the cops get in,
they're gonna take it.
Fuck the goddamn gold!
No, fuck you!
You aren't gonna
fuck this up for me, Vince.
I want that gold!
We're in this shit because you
fucked up. If you didn't go out
there when they killed that man,
none of this
woulïve happened.
I can get outta here
on my own, Vince.
Are you with me or not?
Them cops'd come in here,
shoot us and take
the gold for themselves!
Keep an eye on Lucky.
Keep him fuckin' quiet!
Shut up!
We don't want those
police in here!
[Mumbling]
Shit, man. You ain't gonna
waste 'em, are you?
Take your hands off the wheel.
Roll yourwindow down.
I do somethin' wrong,
officer?
Mind tellin' me what
you're doin' around here?
I was just lookin'
for a place to take a leak.
Mm-hmm.
Step on outta the car,
Hoss.
Man, somethin' ain't right.
Don't them fools know
the police're out there?
Why ain't they
sayin' nothin'?
I hope Luther doesn't
take a shot at 'em.
Do you want me
to call him?
No. Even he
ain't that stupid.
We got a report of
some shots being fired
in the area.
You wouldn't know
nothin' about that,
though, would ya?
No, sir. Like I said,
I was just lookin' for
a place to take a leak.
Turn around.
Put your hands
on top of the car.
[Honking]
[Police Radio: Indistinct]
Whas up?
We got a call.
Is a 10-85.
Whas up with
this guy?
Him? Nothin'.
Just hangin'.
Les get the hell
outta here, man.
All right.
Here, man.
Look, this ain't
no public outhouse.
There's some gas stations
along the highway.
Why don't you find one?
[Engines Rewing]
[DoorClosing]
Cool.
They're steppin' off, man.
Yeah, cool.
[Yelling]
Hey!
They're gone, and there's
nothin'you can do about it.
Now, we're goin' outta here
with the gold... together.
[K.J.]
What the fuck is that?
What does it look like, man?
I found their car.
Don't worry about it.
It ain't goin' nowhere.
From Arkansas?
That means they came
at least 200 miles.
These fools from outta town?
What the fuck's up?
I don't know.
What they doin' here,
Raymond?
Why didn't they call
for those fuckin' pigs?
I got no idea, man.
What am I
payin'you for then?
Maybe they didn't see the cops.
They saw the cops,
ain't no doubt about that.
Look, I can't give a fuck
what they're doin' here.
I say we handle these
motherfuckers right now!
How we gonna do that?
Simple.
We burn 'em.
Shit, nigger. We go in there
smokin' them motherfuckers,
we gonna get burned too.
I'm talkin' 'bout fire!
I'm talkin' 'bout burnin'
this place to the ground!
Ain't nobody gonna care,
'cause these places
go up every day.
That ain't bad, K.J.
That ain't bad at all.
But what about
Lucky, man?
Lfhe's really lucky,
he'll walk away from this.
If not...
I'm callin' a truce.
What for?
I wanna talk to 'em.
You wanna talk!
I wanna burn!
Look, just give me
five minutes.
Man, thas bullshit!
Your shis been
bullshit all day!
Look, Von, you gonna do
what the hell I say,
oryou gonna be
a dead man.
Come on, man.
I'll go down with ya.
Come on.
Man, fuck you.
Yeah, I'm right here,
nigger.
Come on.
Hey, listen up, man.
You gotta keep cool.
Don't touch me,
motherfucker!
You got me all wrong.
You the only one around here
makin' any sense.
KingJames is losin' it.
I can't deal with
the motherfucker no more.
Ain't that the truth.
Thas why I
figured you the only one
around here I can trust.
You and me, we got
the same interests.
Interests?
What interests?
Interest in makin' sure
them white motherfuckers
don't walk outta here.
You wanna know why
they didn't signal the police?
'Cause they found somethin',
somethin' so valuable
they don't want
nobody else in on it.
Is that right?
Now, the way
lfigure,
you and me, we work this out,
we come out lookin' real nice.
[Chuckling]
Gold!
Hey, you in there!
I need to talk to you guys.
Hey, you in there.
We gotta talk right now.
What do you want?
We need to talk about a truce.
I want a truce.
Bullshit!
What about?
About this situation.
You're either gonna talk
to me right now, or fuck you!
I'm finished playin' with your ass.
Les hear him out.
Is a damn trick.
You can't trust
these bastards.
He's right!
Why don't you open the slot
in that door so we can talk,
motherfucker?
Maybe I can get
a clear shot at him
through the peep slot,
blow his head off.
He says
he wants a truce.
Whas it gonna hurt
to talk to him?
Is a trick, thas why!
We're gonna talk to him,
goddamn it, hearwhas
on his mind.
Maybe he wants out
of this whole situation
just like we do.
He don't know nothin'
about the gold.
Sure as hell
ain't gonna hurt
to talk to him.
Okay, is open.
You try anything,
your brother's gonna get
a bullet in the head.
All right.
I'm steppin' out
here in the open...
to let you know I ain't got
no bad intentions, okay?
Start talkin', James.
Look, we both got
a problem, right?
We didn't come here
lookin' for trouble.
This whole thing's
just a big misunderstanding.
Okay, misunderstanding.
All I want to know is
who the fuck are you?
What the fuck
are you doin'here?
What are we
gonna tell him?
We're just visitin'.
Bullshit.
White guys don't come up here
unless they're cops,
and you ain't cops.
- What the fuck's goin' on?
- We're just lookin' around.
You better give me
some straight answers!
You don't own this place.
We got as much right
to be here as anybody else.
Case you ain't heard,
this is still a free country.
This is my goddamn territory.
You don't come up here
wavin' no guns around,
fuckin' with my family,
taking hostages and shit!
[Beeping]
[Ringing]
Yeah, whas up?
Luther, Raymond.
Whas goin' on up there, man?
[Luther, Indistinct]
Everything fine?
Look, you let us go,
we let him go.
Everybody just walks away.
We're not goin' to the cops,
I swear.
Is that right?
Swear to God, man.
You give me a Bible,
we'll swear on it.
Thas too easy.
Why you didn't call for
the cops when they were here?
You heard the deal.
Take it or leave it!
I want some straight
fuckin' answers.
Luther, one of'em's trying
to get out the fire escape.
Shoot him!
Where?
One of those snow boys
tried to kick it out
the fire escape.
They fuckin' with you, K.J.,
laughin' behind your back,
tryin' to pull some shit on ya.
Luther said the dude
got back in before
he could nail his ass.
Tell Moon to get
his ass up here now.
Luther, tell Moon to get
his ass up here.
Son of a bitch
set us up.
Shit, I thought he was
goin' for it too.
I told you it was a trick.
Did you hit 'im?
No, I missed.
Shit!
Savon, move!
Go get some gas.
Oh, shit! Finally we doin'
some shit right...
like I been tellin'you
all day.
All right, all right.
This is what I want you
to do. Get some grease,
some of that C-four.
Hook up some of them specials.
We're gonna blow
this piece of shit up...
and burn it
to the fuckin' ground.
I know what time it is.
Check this out, Wickey.
Talk to Cletus, call Luther.
Yeah.
Make sure that dumb motherfucker
knows whas goin' on.
Word.
Hey, Video,
you goin' orwhat?
We need some help.
No, I'm stayin'
with K.J.
Aw, man, you lazy punk.
Stop actin' like a girl.
Get off K.J.'s junk.
## [Indistinct Rap]
[Mumbling, Groaning]
Those handholds
look solid to me.
Lfigure we can
make it up okay.
Bradlee, hurry up
and pack that gold.
Supposin' those fuckers
bust in here while we're
halfway up the chimney?
That kiïs gonna start
yappin', and our ass
is gonna be cooked.
[Lucky Groaning]
Yeah.
You got a point.
We gotta
shut him up.
Yeah.
Sure, Don, kill him.
Kill him in cold blood.
What choice have we got?
This is survival, Vince.
He's just a junkie.
He's gonna die anyway.
We got a fuckin' choice!
I'm open to suggestions.
You got any bright ideas?
Shit, we could
knock him out!
Here.
Les see you do it.
Take this in the other room,
and hit him on the head
with it.
Wait a second.
Aw, shit!
[Footsteps]
Look, he's got cocaine
or heroin, orwhatever
the hell this stuff is.
What if we dope him up?
I don't want nothin' to do
with no dope!
Bradlee, finish
packin' the gold.
At least is not
murder, Don.
You know anything
about doin' this?
No...
but he does.
[Lucky Groaning]
Hey, man.
Be careful, man.
Thas all I got.
How long is it
supposed to heat?
[Lucky]
Until it gets milky, man.
Strain it with that cotton ball.
Is milky.
[Lucky]
Put the cotton ball on top.
[Sighs]
Bradlee may need
some help in there.
Keep an eye on the gold.
Make sure it all gets
in the sack.
Okay.
You got no idea
how lucky you are, mister.
Come on, please, man.
Let me do that.
Let me do it by myself.
You don't know
what you're doing.
Hey, man, you could hurt me
if you do it wrong, you know?
Come on, man, listen.
Just untie me.
Look, I swearyou
won't have no trouble.
Come on. Please, man.
Come on.
You might mess up
one of my veins, man.
Come on.
All right. All right.
Please.
One arm!
Cool.
Come on, hurry up.
Here.
What are you waitin' for?
I'm just waitin'
for the vein to pop up.
[Screaming]
Don!
Oh, shit!
Help me get him
on his back!
Don, you okay, man?
Oh, my God!
[Vince]
Hang on.
You're gonna be okay.
You're gonna be
all right, man.
You'll be okay.
James!
James.
Hang on.
Let me get it out, huh?
Is gonna be okay.
Fucker!
Get off, motherfucker!
[Lucky]
James... James.
[Groans]
[Beeping, Ringing]
Wickey! Man,
I think I got Lucky.
What? What are you
talkin' about?
It wasn't my fault, man.
The white dude turned him.
You tell KingJames
it wasn't my fault.
Lucky's dead?
Are you sure?
No, man, he's dead.
I'm tellin'you.
I'm gettin' outta here.
You tell KingJames
it wasn't my fault.
I'm outta here.
Vince. Vince.
Get me outta here.
You just fuckin' hang on.
I'm gonna get you out.
Just hang on.
Hey, you can mix some
of this shit in there,
make it like napalm.
[K.J.]
Just hurry up.
Whas goin' on with that
C-four over there?
This shis waterproof
and fireproof,
but it ain't gonna blow
'til I say so.
Word.
[Video]
Hold up a stick ofthe
C-four. I need a close-up.
Shut up, bitch.
[Panting]
Luther says Lucky's dead.
- He said them white dudes shot him.
- Get the fuck out.
It can't be.
You sure, man?
He says is no mistake, man.
Who shot him?
Which one did it?
He didn't...
He didn't say.
Guess he wasn't
too lucky, huh?
I'll go up the chimney.
Pick him up, take him into
that room over there,
seal yourself in and
don't make a sound.
I don't figure jumpin'
across the rooftops
is gonna work.
- But maybe I can rappel down.
- What you talkin', rappel?
Neveryou mind. Now, listen
to me. When they break in,
they're gonna see that hole
and think all three of us went up.
Thas gonna senïem
outta here lookin'for us.
Just sit tight.
Wait 'til I come back
with some help.
How do I know you ain't
gonna leave us here?
After all, you don't owe
him nothin', or me either.
You're just gonna
have to trust me.
Yo, Moon.
Spread these cocktails
all through the building.
Make sure this motherfucker
blow up.
Video, what the fuck you doin'?
You ain't done shit all day.
I'm tapin'.
Get the...
My fuckin' camera!
Look what you did
to my fuckin' camera!
Show's canceled, punk.
Now is blowin' up
with everything else.
Now, goddamn it, Video,
you help Moon spread
the fuckin' grease.
[Shotgun Blasts]
K. J!
Les use this.
Where's the gold?
The gold?
Shit!
Ah, man, this shit
didn't have to happen.
I'm sorry, Luck.
L... I'm sorry, Luck.
[Raymond]
Afteryou set that timer, meet
me downstairs in the basement.
[Rifle Cocking]
Hold up, Superfly.
Les get one thing straight.
I done did all the work.
I done took all the risk.
When we spread that gold around,
90 percent of is mine.
You know what I'm sayin'?
I understand
your argument.
[Grunting]
K.J., come here!
Look at this!
The chimney!
They got up
the chimney!
Damn!
They're on the roof.
I'm gonna finish this.
Hold on!
What you want me to do?
Stay here.
Watch the chimney and
stay with Lucky, man.
Don't let him burn, man.
Don't let him burn.
But Lucky's de...
dead.
Savon!
That you?
Ohh! Shit!
[Crashing]
[Wickey Grunting]
Agh!
- You're gonna die, motherfucker.
- I'll take you with me.
Whas this all about, man?
What the hell you white boys
doin' up here anyway?
Gold! Is all about gold.
Gold? You crazy!
Aaah!
[Phone Ringing]
[Ringing]
Hello?
No, KingJames can't
come to the phone!
[Marvin Indistinct]
Because he's dead,
thas why!
[Beeping]
Hello, 9-1-1?
Hello?
[Loud Crashing]
[Savon]
K. J...
K. J!
KingJames is dead, man.
No!
Back off!
He's a brother.
I thought we were poppin'
white boys, not brothers.
I'm sick of it, Moon.
I say we shoot him.
He can identify us.
Look at 'im.
Where's he goin'?
He ain't gonna identify us.
I'm sick of it.
If you wanna pop him,
you go ahead and pop him.
I'm outta here.
You better get outta here, old man.
The whole place is goin' up.
No!
No! Oh, shit!
Who you, old man?
What you doin'
with my bag?
I left that here.
Put it down.
This here's my
personal stuff.
This is all I got!
Is that right? I think
you got some gold in there.
Put it down!
I don't know nothin' about
no gold! What would I
be doin' with some gold?
Don't fuck with me, old man.
I know you got
somethin' in there.
That golïs goin' with me,
or I'm gonna bust a cap
in your ass. Put it down!
You want it, take it.
I don't wanna die
for no sack of goods.
You got that right,
old fool.
[Crashing]
Fuck it.
You can burn up
with everything else!
Oh, shit!
[Ticking]
Where you goin', Von?
I see you found the gold.
Thought you were supposed to
have your ass in the basement?
I know where I'm
supposed to be.
What the fuck you wanna
pimp me off for? You
wouldn't have known shit...
about that gold
ifit hadn't been for me.
Lfigure that entitles me
to a little bit more than
ten percent.
- Hell no!
- Superfly this, motherfucker!
Hey. Hey, man.
Hey.
Thas my gold, man.
Thas my gold.
Hey, motherf...
fucker, thas...
Agh.
[Ticking]
Hey! You better
get outta here
while you got a chance.
Bradlee, are you okay?
I was afraid you guys
didn't get out.
I went down the chimney and
got out through the furnace.
Now, get outta here!
Where's Don?
He's dead.
Blew up with the gold.
I'm tellin'you,
you better get outta here
before them niggers catch you.
What about you?
They don't care
about me.
But they will kill you.
Now, move.
Come with me, man.
I can't keep up.
Get outta here.
Come on.
Run! Don't worry
about me. Go on!
Move. Move.
Go on, run!
[Chuckling]
#How many bullets can
your back hold, sucker
from the H.K. #
#The red dots you have drawn
from the light ray#
#Boom-bam-bust, oh damn, kid
your head is a pile ofpus #
#I'm kickin'up much stuff
The brotheryou can't trust #
#This is my hood
my gold, my turf#
#My stash, my grip
Whateverthe hell is worth #
#I don't need nobody
comin'in my territory#
#Tryin'to rip a brotheroff
a killer, damn sob story#
#Take a good look
see I'm nothin'but ajacker#
#About to fill the rap
ofa greedy-ass cracker#
#Hell, whas new so you know
the punks stand out #
#Comin'in my hood
with his handout #
#Tryin'to get over
on the black but
they don't do that #
#I'll put a damn slug
in his back #
#And with a boom ping-ping
It ain't no thing #
#To blast the greedy little
suckers that trespass #
##
#Ollie-ollie ox
I'm free, here comes the G #
#I'm saggin'and enter
the dragon like Bruce Lee #
#I got to get more money
more money#
#Can't get sex
with no money#
#See, I'm kind of greedy'cause
all my heroes got zeroes #
#Numberone is my gun
About to get paid at last #
#But now I'm gettin'covered
in dirt and grass, kick it #
#The madder I get
the higherthe debt
the deeperyou get #
#The thickerthe sweat
'cause I'm the brother
with fat clout #
#Put you in
but you gotta get back out #
#No easyjob forsome suckers
thas out to rob #
#Cross hairon yourdome
and your minïs blown #
#You wanna go home #
#Ain't that a bitch
Q dig this pitch #
#Don't trespass #
#I got a full-timejob
takin'suckers out
breakin"em off, yeah word#
#I love revokin'clout
Yeah, test me, stress me #
#Who could the best be
Who #
#The teflon nine
got the best, G #
#But when you're greedy
you don't care about life itself#
#You're chasin'
extreme wealth #
#You can't be trusteïcause
trust ain't in the damn game #
#"Scandalous"is
your middle name #
#I'm the black brother
you're stuck with #
#Ice Cube, a.k.a.
The Wrong Brotherto Fuck With #
#I'm rich, pitchin'a bitch
about gettin'more #
#The big fish
swimmin'in big dough #
#You can't back stab her
I've got to have a Lexus coupe #
#When I trip with the ski mask
gotta get the cash #
#My homeboy ain't home
so now I trespass #
#Trespass ##