The legendary number 1 headband.
It promises to power, kaikkivoipaisuutta,
immortality.
But the price is high.
Greater than anyone can imagine.
And heavier than the man
will be able to withstand.
Headbands Nauha will be ...
... ours.
Touche!
... bastard.
Son.
Father.
Afro.
Jinno?
Do you remember me?
I will remember you and
all of your actions.
The killer, a monster.
How many hundreds of life
you've chosen?
How many thousands have been
rakkaimpiaan miss.
Now it's your turn.
I know the only thing that you care.
And when you raise him up to life;
he becomes a toy.
Kidutan him.
Your father is suffering from penalty,
your sins.
Afro Samurai.
If you do not find the number 2 headband tape
and try to stop me.
Can we find your eggs in it?
So the area to search for the boy.
Come to see Afro Samurai.
Number 1 headband otsallani,
you are bound by rules of samurai.
Swallow the bait to look for the number 2
Come to me, --
so I can destroy your heart and body.
As the destroyed mine.
You look quite karsealta.
How is it gone?
Not to be seen in recent times.
You are apparently outdated.
Look at this pathetic blade
lovilla far.
Things did not really have shifted.
Why you do not like the headbands nro.1 tape?
I got a punishment.
Have you not learned anything?
Was the fault of the problem, but
pidettyäsi headband tape --
you can not quit.
On the other. How Teddy Bear man
is still alive?
Did not you kill him yet?
You 've since he made his return and
kicked persustas black.
What about the baby, who was
accompanied him.
He has a new nro.1.
Damn, what ryntäät was.
And takalisto was phenomenal.
Even in a cold fury
got me hot.
- It will start again.
- Great!
Homma my taste.
The road is being turned on again.
Have these pieces certainly enough?
I can assure you that within 2 weeks
inside are witnessing a miracle.
Sio.
I feel gratitude for helping
My research work.
The perfect creature is finished, --
we are striving for a self -
God's strength.
The world is in our hand's reach.
I will finish what we use
this miracle, professor.
And it is you who will help us.
Do not forget that.
Apologize to your Excellency,
šio damsel.
Interest only met
this perfectly.
I declare that I use all its resources
advantage of you, --
beautiful and precious šio mistress.
The wise solution kannaltasi.
Preparation for construction has been completed.
Te three. Watch Afroa, and hold
I was informed of his movements.
Understood.
The time has finally come.
All preparations have been made.
Kostoomme Afro Samurai for.
You look a little pirteämmältä, even though
huuhtonutkaan sour your face off.
Your father remnants theft
the center of the storm.
It is scary.
Mädäntymisjuttuja and more.
Who semmoista really do?
But I understand tekojasi.
Suutuit so much, to leave
On the road again.
To find again No.2 headband tape
so that you can fight back against nro.1.
- All just to get your father's skull.
- There is no alternative.
My dad must have a rest in peace.
Only in the blade is clean now. End
it's your job.
Afro on the move.
Keep up the vigilance.
We are not obliged to do this.
You should just take it easy.
Changes the state of mind, to go huorissa
or something.
Wait a minute!
This is the first time that
when I see you without No.2 headband tape.
And you know what? You look
very strange.
I knew something was wrong.
Otsasi is huge.
I thought your hair a vast,
but blimey!
Otsasi is many times
outsized.
You mean when he said the principal,
Prime Minister, the shrew.
Shut up.
Where should we go?
Is that true? He
is coming here?
He is it. Eyes and hair
can not get it wrong.
Cursed creature who silpoi Sumin.
Demon that killed their loved ones.
We do not get this chance to go.
Revenge is ours.
He is coming!
Afro Samurai is coming!
Hey Afro.
You might need this.
You murdered my father.
- You murdered him!
- You killed the only brother!
- And the best of my friend!
- Revenge imprisonment.
Be damned demon.
Cuts in hell. Hukut innocent
the blood, which you are slaughtered.
We suffer from miekkojen attacks
even after death.
Curse wear, Afro Samurai.
Goddamn it. Now begins
look good.
To have a little skin.
Afro Samurai is here.
Send him up.
The plan is as follows,
You do something --
I get lap dances, and
we meet at 5 minutes' time.
And then you went.
Greetings.
No.2 headband.
Unfortunately, I can not give it
location, therefore, free of charge.
But if you win me.
No, no, no ... not a sword.
We play in these.
If you win, I tell what is No.2.
If I win, I get reached.
Is that agreed?
Guide to the Afro Mr gaming area.
Contrary to what you brother Wong, I play
Only if you know win.
It was fantastic!
I got 2 for one price of dance.
I was ... Hey, where not only property?
We play gambling games.
Awesome.
Place the game got under way.
Play the black.
Oh, right the wrong game.
Which one?
Odd.
Even.
Two ykköstä, even.
Afro Samurai.
Now, when you lose a little more than a game, --
I ask you to fill ...
Fair?
Huijaava huoranpenikka. Free
lap dances for the good.
No.2 headband?
No.2 is ownerless Samurai
Shichigoro named.
He is the west, the village
Machi named City.
Is not oltaisi could be Tovi
longer gambling site.
This shit is boring,
and you, too.
In fact, vengeance demon,
God is looking for guidance from.
You think you cleaned sins, --
carving silly toys.
This does not tell every day.
Where is the cold-blooded killer,
Every time you were?
Do you not stand up to fight anymore?
Keep a coward,
even if your father is suffering from?
That was not nice.
Does that shit to listen to?
And you are so long
travel ahead.
Save your father tortured.
I have raised almost
her life.
He comes to life again.
Know their pain,
kärsiäkseen.
And you do not even have
No.2 headband tape yet.
So, I have a few
days or even weeks --
when your father to enjoy the pain, before
you have the right to sue me.
Beware puheitasi.
Since I am coming.
We will, yes, bitch.
You are worse than the anger, love.
Now begins care less.
Not likely to understand who
with kidding.
Jinno.
At last he makes a move. All
goes according to plan.
We get kostomme.
To succeed, my beloved, we are
demoneiksi change.
I'm sorry --
but it is the only way to get
he was always feeling for surullisuutta --
which we have known.
To get him to suffer, such as
we have suffered.
So, please, and
Forgive me.
Keep in mind that there was no alternative.
I will always love you.
My dear brother.
Your luck sucks.
Everyone knows that here is a ravet
underway at this time.
You may not, those who are celebrating
No.2 information otsanauhasta.
His name was Shichigoro?
You know, even what he looks like,
because I did not.
How do we know that it is even
is his real name?
Help!
Get out of my way!
Daylight kidnapping.
I hate to do the job.
Oh, shit.
Afro Samurai.
Get out of the way!
I told you to move!
Afro-gun, the gun!
Decent gun yet.
Kitaro!
Father.
Kitaro, advice
to remain in the vicinity.
I'm sorry.
For my gratitude.
This coward kidnapped son ...
Anti be.
I offer you a drink.
I know the place likeltä.
I would lose ninjakenkäni.
Wait, hukun here!
Do not dismiss the brothers!
I came back, old man.
- You brought your friend with you.
- He saved my life Kitaro.
So it seems strong enough,
not dying muhennokseesi.
Speak with caution ruuistani Shichigoro,
or you find a hot pepper on your bowl.
I came back!
Nuuskin tieni unto.
You seem to murkinaa.
Something smells vängälle.
Damn, that is the target.
What should be the guy?
- Sukiyaki.
- Put double.
Here you.
You are not drinking men. You do not know
where not only the ice.
Limpparia ago?
As long as joking.
You don 't be because of the festival here.
Me neither. I am
passing through.
But we linger too long.
We saw the fun festival.
But it seems best to go forward.
The evil thing that you need
to kill him.
He seems
really good guy.
It is always one of them after the festival.
At the very least, do not need to eat
toxins since then.
Teen best muhennosta
miles radius.
When you come back, remind
that charge you double.
This is the best?
It should also kill it
Martha Stewart liar.
This stew stinks.
Limpparia.
Drink out of time.
The man before. The fact that
paloittelit.
- Do you know why he is kidnapped by Kitaro?
- Not a clue.
Want to know why the effort to see
street boy, and the likes juopon why.
- Shichigoro ...
- All very well.
Well tell us.
I have something to
all want.
First, fill his stomach, and
Tovi only so is the dream.
It is not even mine, but an orphan.
Tapatutti father himself.
Promised to look after Kitaro;
if he should die.
We were as brothers.
He was a man tappaneella
reportedly had a strange appearance.
Afro, a green tint
likeltä view.
Now listen carefully.
The world can be found in the blood ties deeper.
What?
It is a stupid friend had as many
Other bands headbands suit.
Nettosi only their own demise.
Do you know what he said
dying?
"Not anymore," she whispered.
Then I got No.2 headband strap themselves
and hide it.
And I have fled since then.
But now you came from.
And now we're even.
So I think all managed
you're out below.
Drat.
Now begins the event and
ends sentimentality.
Shichigoro.
Keep the boy worry.
Back.
I figured that if you just stick
Kitaro motion with --
people forget that and my friends
your wish a reality.
But fate is not ambiguous,
escape.
Damn.
These forehead strips make
Only death and orphans.
Afro hear?
Death and orphans.
I will not give you a tape of forehead, but you have to
to kill me for it.
I do not play forehead strip rules
or save the world.
Afro! Why official position?
After all, he is cool, but
none of your friends.
Hoida just do the job.
Because I promise, I think.
Do not think that I feel
you Afro Samurai.
Thus what you did to bridge. Killed without
the slightest hesitation.
As he would have only
pesky fly.
Maybe someone should whack you.
Perhaps I believe to be true
get a man.
Will you let him throw the läppää.
Diced him already!
Goodbye, Afro Samurai.
Talking crazy. Death
Expects weirdo.
Damn.
Äijähän part of the movement.
Impressive. He may not be able
even kill you.
Pakenetko are you? You may us
disrepute.
I knew you spoof.
We do not ever escape.
We do not learn it now.
Heiluttele sword so
I virittäydyn mood.
Celebrations under way!
Damn! Everybody likes rock stars.
Lighting, lighting control.
Put the motion.
"Destroy all the Afro Samurai"
Now the party is at its height.
Below is a man
No.2 otsanauhassaan.
Do not stop ...
Where do these ilmeistyivät?
Father.
Kitaro.
Killed the music. Ainako keep
ruin the festivities.
It was an unnecessary distraction.
Still want to die?
You want it around a lot. It is
only a piece of fabric for an idiot.
If you trust onneesi, come on
to apply for it.
What vit ...?
Peace soul.
Every time you have to
to suspend the fun.
I was going to jorata until morning, valotikut
and all was.
Did it spoil. Withdrew the whole
the job and it is your fault.
And one thing yet.
Do not let reaching No.2
rise hat.
Älyätkö to walk again demonien
the trail. It is not the right direction.
Anyhow.
Where to go from here? How does it
kuulostais tuuppailu?
We never have fun.
Damn. This does not
belonged to the plans.
Did not those already pieksäneet you?
Perääsi came again.
Sword tuhrii the world in blood.
What then?
Only to kill their own,
invalid because of syittesi.
Do you not own hearts?
It is not true. What the hell
these people are!
That is impossible!
Do not think so either.
Hold yourself or nöyrryt
pieksäntään another.
Do not want a new leluni rikkoutuvan?
He is so fragile, yet.
Go to Cherry Hill cent, or
he will die again.
But this time, a very
much more slowly.
Keep a smaller mouth.
Ben!
Valtiattareni, step backwards.
Damn.
- Are you okay?
- No.
Jinno!
Easy, the little sister.
Long time šio. How
you've been able to princess?
- Fine.
- And what are the ottovanhempamme?
They are awesome. Just as the
real parents.
They have a son of Bin, a little
harsh and frightening.
Another boy is playing with Michael
a lot with me.
And Miss Tomosan teach me
have as the right princess
I learned to dance, to drink
tea and everything else.
That 's fine.
I hope that you could be here.
I know, but you're safe here.
The family wanted a daughter
lost farm.
I notice that they have accepted
you own.
We both should be grateful.
I try to visit more often.
I want you to meet one.
This is Afro.
Afro, here is my sister šio.
Afro healthy.
He is a newcomer sword in school --
but it is almost as good
than I do, and like a brother to me.
A brother?
So it makes you
including my brother.
Yeah, I guess?
- Cool. I just received a new brother.
- Exactly.
Can I look at the sword to school sometimes?
- Yes. Like at any time.
- You are shy.
And your hair is funny.
Nice to meet you'll.
You will soon be free.
You can not play with the science around.
Are you crazy?
After graduating, he may well be
be the perfect samurai.
If he is to grow, harassed, he
can become a useless pile of protein.
Crazy? A strange word madness
kuvajaisen mouth.
But the plan would be
unable to self-destruction.
Dear Professor, it is
Part of the process.
The more kiusaan Afroa,
the better.
I want her suffering
lasting a long time.
His death is not an end. It is
only a point of GDP on.
Do you not understand me now?
Of course, šio mistress. You have
kieroitunut indeed.
But there are risks.
How refreshing experience.
I do kieroitunut. World kieroin
scientist has impressed me kieroudesta.
Do not be afraid my friend round.
Everything is going very
According to the plans.
You could count on a bit.
Yes valtiattareni.
My advice and it does not end
failure as Kuma.
He repaired so many times that
he is no longer people are left.
He is just misguided samurai doll.
Soulless, dead.
But now, meat, bone ...
... blood. Life in developing nano-technology.
Chemically active nerve endings.
And unlawful science that it is
alkemiaa more than biotechnology.
You are indeed the world kieroin,
shit-faced, and a genius scientist.
Cuts in hell tekosistasi
nature.
Praise me so well,
šio mistress.
- I am not worthy ylistyksienne.
- You filth.
History of mourning hirmutekojasi,
that you do.
You have to burn alive.
Afro chasing me and my brother ...?
When he arrives, he sees
syntiensä sanctions.
His twice killing the only friend, the --
and my dear father, increase
sword revenge.
And at the last moment, these hands will be
to decide on Afro Samurai life.
Damn!
Here is hot!
Is it not a faster route to Cherry
Hill Siin? It is certainly Sion win.
And it was really weird
a family gathering. Did not Afro?
I think most excited when
the father is alive, but --
I do not believe in a living head, which excrete
ällöä töhnää, the more sense.
How he could be with be alive?
Would kusettaa.
Huijasivat. Maybe it was a robot, such as
it tappamasi afro-robot once.
Or maybe it was a dummy,
liikuteltiin by hand.
Is granted, it was stupid.
No, it was a doll.
It had any,
One thing is for sure.
Suttura It is crazy.
And what else are you going to do
beyond the next penskalle?
You killed his father, so the
He tried to nirhata you.
So to me, at least influence.
Anyway, puppy
will not last long.
It is raahautunut behind this
the heat for days.
He died on the morning at the latest.
Father forgive.
You would have seen his appearance, --
when I showed him, he died in
The son of live downstream.
Do not forget that Afro Samurai
you did what you have today.
He experiences the land of hell, it
What good did to us.
Enjoy every seconds of pain,
the production of him.
We believe when a lot of his
leaking blood.
We listen to his murtuvien
bones sound.
Haistelemme his pelkoaan
and the burning of its meat.
His death is so terrible --
that it is remembered legend.
And I was his legendary
executioner.
Mountain climbing and not
even qualify for a joke.
We do not have the tools and
I need a drink.
Do you have a rope? Shall
certainly the right direction?
I'm just a country. Perhaps I
get slaagin.
You make me nervous.
I hate high places.
Is this is a disaster, the Central?
Damn! Once this place
was wonderful.
Just as it would need to
played violent games.
Is there a
huumehörhöjä, gangs?
If you were so have moved.
What has happened here?
Disgust watch.
Who did this?
Afro-bye.
Is this is certainly the place
in which he said looked forward to.
Look at this.
Here is Justice.
You will not otherwise polls directions along the way.
Afro Hey!
Keitäs are these?
Naamiaiskulkue? Welcome Committee?
Comedy Team?
Thanks, but no thanks. We
There is a pressing meeting.
Let's see.
Funny Face. Have you seen the crazy sexy
ämmää teddykarhunpää hemmon with.
I did not mean evil.
What the ...?
Afro? Kuolenko me?
Damn!
Vatiatar šio not here.
You don 't remember us from Afro Samurai?
Who would have imagined that the son of a
once knew it would return executioner.
The only motivation
killer frenzy
To bring death and
world of chaos.
Reveal the sword Afro Samurai.
Now, you die.
- Professor.
- What is it mistress?
Rejoice because Afron father's life
campaign is nearing completion.
However, this is a sensitive phase and
the slightest mistake can ruin everything.
- They are gone.
- What do you mean?
They were not doing anything
without any commands. What have you done?
Maybe they left the city.
What do you mean?
Or maybe they sued Afro
Samurai alone.
Do not be afraid. Perhaps they
may even win.
Yllätyt perhaps kuullessasi, but they
is a lot of hardware --
connected to them in the trunk. And
Furthermore, are full of drugs.
Šio mistress?
What does this mean?
May wonder how the princess Rushing
we have.
Regeneration has not yet ...
You have done a splendid job, Professor.
You did everything as I wanted.
For thanks.
Now it is time well
ansaitulle lomallesi.
Good night, Professor.
Another executioners
starts to wake up.
Aikomuksistasi viis. There are things that are
we do not allow you to do.
We can not allow the queen bee of Sion
sink into darkness.
A wonderful young lady, when you have.
We will not allow his ylväytensä suffer.
We are a sinner factors
on his behalf.
I wanted to Afron, only to see
tuhoamansa city.
I wanted to see syntiensä sanctions,
throat before cutting.
But now we are vasallini
probably dead.
Hölmöt the road, which is only
angels would saunter.
Michael, shoot him.
What are you waiting for?
Do it.
Shoot 'em. He is
already dead.
Do-it-mistress Sion behalf.
Go away.
Afro Samurai ...
I knew that before long
such a day would be affected.
We die together.
Afro you made it.
How did you do it?
Why not only property?
I got hit, and the arrow on it.
Fortunately, I am steel.
Teilasit the comedy of the pump?
What the ...?
Follow me, son.
It is not my God!
I have officially seen it all.
Sio, Jinno.
Afro-bye! Why do you need to walk
each trap.
Are you latvasta rotten?
Here can be found in the wires
vetelevä crazy bitch.
And once again come to life robottikamusi,
who does not like you.
Kirsikkana cake turned on a freak,
you think you isäksesi.
That is the right father.
Wrong answer, and it
makes you idiots.
And beyond that I do not come.
See you.
I came to my father, and
nro.1 forehead because of the tape.
Surprise, surprise.
What can you do, the body of a
that right?
We kidutamme you. Death
will be a slow process.
Why not have nro.1 forehead tape?
I just wanted to take revenge on you.
Was the reason for the removal, the fate of the burden
must assume the forehead after receiving the tape.
You should know this by now.
Nro.1 can never escape from
vuodatusta blood.
Nro.1 kill or
will be killed.
You can not pick and choose who
blood hides.
Take Back otsanauhasi.
Take the fear son.
Father wait.
Father.
See, see my dear brother.
Afro Samurai loppunsa points,
Just as I planned.
For your own father's hands through.
He finally paid with pain, which
returned to us, and thousands of others.
Jinno, Jinno!
Kill him.
Kill him once!
A brother ...
Kill her Afro, teilaa! It does not
your father's right.
Just so, do it.
I do not intend to kill my dad.
Then came their way into Afro head.
Did you see that Jinno?
We did it. We shared at last
right for him.
And we killed him.
See, see the blast brother.
Jinno ...
A brother ...
A brother ...!
What have you done?
What have you done Afrolle!
Why?
Jinno! Why protect Afroa now?
He is dead.
It is useless!
Have you forgotten what the
Afro did to us?
Did you?
Jinno!
Afro. Watch me
dearest brother.
I need to protect
sword master dojoa.
Must protect all.
Including brother, Afroa.
I love you, my Jinnoni.
My brother.
It is the time elapsed.
Is not it so šio?
How could you, princess?
Jinno.
You can not win the Afro.
To escape the hell kind.
It is too strong overcome. It does not
not a human being.
Do not, do not!
Shut up.
It is a point over.
Excuse me, but not my father.
My father died a long time ago.
Do not be afraid.
Father.
As soon as you're ready.
Naama Stasi was judging
hellish bad day.
I noticed, right. You knew that
it will never end.
But do not turn back.
Otherwise, to hell ryntäät.
I have been waiting for you a long time.