Can I get another
When Crazy Music
Can I get more
Of coffee, please?
Where do you go?
Sorry
Hello
Is anyone here?
Wait
Hello
What is this nonsense?
I told you honestly, if you continue
Sleep here will be fired
Sorry
This will not happen again
Okay?
OK
(Nancy) -
Hi (Chrissy) You can request the usual -
(In fact I'm here to interview (the religion of
Is there
Thank you
Why do you ... ? -
If I did not sleep during the past 3 days -
Religion) What's going on? )
Sorry, Do you want to request anything?
Here is your friend
Hi -
Do I bring anything to you?
No, I think we are fine here
Now we will take account
...........
Stupid
What they (Chrissy) and (Religion)?
OK
Come on
To get out from here
For what was this?
GIS) was upset because (Chrissy) separated by
I did not know that they jointly
I think I will keep the rest
... Yes, look
I apologize about the chaos
......
40th
Not become tired from working here all weekend?
41st
Not get tired of coming here every weekend?
42nd
And that) you come or not? )
I apologize
Keep the rest
I see later -
To the meeting -
Listen, maybe it is better to speak with someone
I've done
Believe that my problems come from my past
Any of what happened in my childhood
When I started this
What you started?
Nightmares
Nightmares?
So what, you can not sleep?
I can sleep
I do not want this
Well (Religion) Hear Me
It's only dreams
Well, it's not real
These dreams
Real
Is not it?
It's true
Sorry
Well You know, there is nothing wrong
I
I'm going to clean myself
There is nothing wrong
67th
You are not real
I'm not a real
I am now
Religion) What do you do? )
You are not real -
Religion) Please stop) -
Religion) hangs)
A great tragedy shaking hearts
But can we collected during our grief
Today we gather to unite and we bid farewell to
The life of a young man who lived with us
Let us pray
Dear God I made the specter of death
To the light of the new day
We gather to say goodbye to a debt
Come on honey
We have concluded
Let's go to take the peace
Gwen) Hi, how are you? )
It has been a long time -
Yes, but the situation particularly in such circumstances -
................ G
I'm fine thank you
We are sitting on top of school
Know where is my true (Nancy)?
Yes
Do we go now, Take care of yourself
G ..............
Oh my God, this man-
But I do not know how I got there
I did not get to know (religion) until
We Baltanuep
Come on
Dean) told me anything before he died)
Please do not do this
I have said, it's not real
Has continued to re-phrase that has repeatedly
Do you have any idea about the meaning of this?
No
I do not know
Only intellectual in the sense that (religion) was subject
Drug-drug Nunn
I have seen the situation there
If anyone would cause him to drop it
But no one there
Jesse) You need to believe me)
Chrissy) has been delayed for the time)
I know that she heard
You're imagination -
Honest with you -
Really?
I have seen everything
110th
..... I have seen -
You did not see anything -
You are you're not there
But (Chris) was
(Are you delirious (Raymond
.............
Let's go home
Hi -
Illiterate
Where are all the pictures of my childhood
It is not here
Who knows?
Probably remained in moving boxes, why?
... I today, in the burial ceremony
I saw a picture of me and for (religion) when you
.... In the fifth, but
You know the situation, it's funny man
I do not remember knowing him through high school
Who can remember everything
Occurred with the enactment of the Fifth
Why do not these things now Toillin
Dinner is ready
You become the best dear
Otaatzkrini?
Chris) Are you okay? )
?? ????
None
Just draw a Krikaturi
?? ??? ?????
Yes, I'm fine
Is it a problem with me?
Yes
You know if you need one
Or you want to speak with one of the
I am sure ... There are many people
If you want to talk anything
Thank you
And that) we are waiting in line, Come on)
OK
I know
Open your books to page 84
Awake, Awake, Awake,
You should not sleep in class
(Hi (Chris
Who are you?
You are really beautiful
Long
You do not have anxiety
This will not hurt
.....
Are you okay Miss (foul)?
I'm sorry
(Chris)
(Roffic)
Come here!
Come on
(Roffic)
Day evening to fly to London
OK
Will you be so good?
Yes, I'm fine
You'll be just fine
No Tvoti the plane
I am worried about you no more
Try to sleep, okay?
I'll call you when I arrive Anz
I love you
God, you (Jesse)?
What are you doing here?
Would like not to enter?
Yes, please
Well I know I was and tomorrow
Jealous and mad
But (religion) was also my friend
Please tell me, what's going on?
Tantabni these dreams
I'm scared
And I think that (religion) was suffering from them also
Chris) Listen, I know)
I know what you want to say
Every time I dream of the
I will always be a man
... Is
And it is seared
And insoluble
.... And is always trying to bait me into coming b
Knives on his fingers
Why?
Oh my God
Tantabni the same dreams
Chris) This is not possible) -
But it is possible -
It is only just dreams
Oh my God, I'm very scared
All I want to do is sleep and that
(I did this will kill me (such as religion
Let's stop talking about this, okay?
If you continue to talk about, we will follow
Thinking about him and therefore we will follow those dreams
See the
Would you stay with me?
Of course, I will stay with you
(Roffic)
Roffic) was admitted to here)
Heck
(Roffic)
Roffic) Come here)
Here
(Roffic)
I have just Ozvth
Please help me, help me
Come on
We are late
Are you ready or not?
Here I am coming
(Jesse)
(GIS)
....
Chris) Malmcklp? )
(Chris)
Chris) Awake)
Oh my God
Awake
Heck
Oh my God
Well, Well, Well
Hey you
Dear
(Nancy)
Yes
It is the middle of the night, dear
Should Tkhaldi to sleep
Well, I'll do
Now -
Well -
Nancy) that I)
Asamaini only, okay?
What happened to you?
What is this blood that is on your body?
Please Asamaini
Hope
I have been with (Chris) tonight -
What did you do it? -
I did not do anything for her
This is what I'm trying to tell you by
Asamaini, something has happened
Tell me what happened?
One killed in her sleep
Why?
What do you speak?
I tell you this because you know
I have said in the ceremony of burial
Someone is trying to kill us in our dreams,
This is what he says this?
Why?
Many
Fred) coming from you)
(Freddie)
It has become the past
(Nancy)
No
(Nancy) -
Heck -
We will stop this
How? -
I do not know -
Only .... Do not sleep
If you die within a dream
You will die on the ground
Heck
Decreased
I did not do anything
Asamaoni, did not do anything
I swear
Please -
Down -
You have to kill her, man
You have to kill her
I did not do anything
Stop
I did not Kill her, you know -
Shut up -
Come on, to tend to the prison
Nancy) you know)
You know who did it
Open the gate
Hello
(Hey you (Nancy
Hi
Are you sure that I can contact
You if you need to speak with one of the
Yes
Chris) was dead)
Stay Iqdha
Shut up
Speechless
Medicines sleep deprivation
Negative impact of the thinner you
The desire not to sleep
Causing disorder mania and mental functions
Risk of disease
Are there nightmares?
Yes
(Freddie)
Stand Up
Your parents pushed Kvaltk
(Jesse)
Me
Come here!
(Chris)
Oh my God
No
I was just
What do you want from me?
(Hi (Jesse
Do you think that you can return the time?
Reply to my question
No
Can you return the dead to life?.
And I did not think this is also
No
Why do you scream
Not yet Oqtek
I did not do it
I do it, took me out of here
They took me out
Did you know?
...........
..........
?? ??? ?????
Yes, but no more burdensome
Take
?? ????
Medicine
It is a kind of drugs, I am
Capturing the fifteenth ago
No, no, thank you
Do not like to sleep now
Are you sure?
Yes, I'm good so far
............
Valuation of faith must be something
What's here?
A book about the family
Women dream of betraying the man who
So revenge by taking all children
I dream of children also
And the school also
This must mean something
But we did not go to school until sixth grade
..........
When a person think that this abnormal dreams
Ungovernable This is called insomnia has
Insomnia and hold for 70 hours
The brain will shut down its
For a few minutes, which means
You are you dream .... But do not know the difference
Even if you are awake
After this ... Your brain will depend
For having interfered in the lethargy of
Only easily
(Nancy)
Yes
Hi
?? ??? ?????
I have been in the place of books
Well, I did not know where you are
And I feel .... Despite all that happened
With your friends
Oh, my mother .... Is there a connection between me
(And between (Chris
(Religion) and (Jesse)
Something, Kzhabna to school
When smallness, or something like that?
Nothing to my knowledge
Do you know any man named
(Freddie)
I do not think this
OK
You become the best
Dear
(HI I (Gwen
Nancy) began to remember)
Honey, are you okay?
Yes, I'm fine, Mom
Well, I'm going to sleep
OK
(Hi (Nancy
I grew up
It's just a nightmare
That's right
No one that I am here
Who are you?
You do not you remember
You must remember that
You're the one for me
· Would you?
You know (Nancy)?
I do not know you
None did
In your dreams
Friends and also
Nancy) Come here)
Jesse) had died)
He died in his sleep
I saw him
He said that his name
(Freddie)
384th
Well, I'm coming
OK
My father ... I'm going to the house
(Nancy)
There is a school for children here in the town
Have been closed for many years
I can not find any image
Wait .... Come here!
I have this fee after those dreams
I do not know, I did not see this before
I think that the man is connected to this school
I do not know
I know that my mother tried to hide
About Me
There's nothing here
Me
?? ????
We are all here
(Chris), (Jesse), (Religion)
I, you, ?????
What are you doing?
Nancy), what is going on? )
Give me a picture
I do not understand this
I said
I said we did not know each other
But all of us in this school
And this image together
Give me a picture
There is nothing wrong
Why did you lie to? -
But he did not lie -
Here she is, Why did you lie to?
Stop lying -
I did not lie -
I did not want that the Chair continue with your life
These memories
I did not want to remember
I wanted you to oblivion
Say what?
What happened to this school?
There was a man
Primary school
(Name (Fred McGregor
It was Alhaddaiki
I have lived in the basement of the school
You and you children as his life
We did not want the ratification of this first
Ready or not?
You have all innocent
(And you (Nancy
What Tersminh?
This is very beautiful
And you'll be a favorite for him
...........
Then we began to notice several things
Yes, it is strange recently
We have taken the secret to the cave
There is nothing wrong
Why did not you contact the police then?
He has left the city before we can
Be confronted
He has gone, can not anymore Ovetk
If your dreams that, Sandra
Are just memories
Of a very difficult time
I wish you to be right
We must find the rest of the children of the picture
I do not know
Can not be the full story
Probably no more
I have heard what she said "Your mother, it's just
Bad memories
I do not care, you may be mistaken -
It does not matter is the memory only -
How do you know this?
Memories do not kill you
Come, enter the car
It is my father, to go
We must do something -
Stop -
This is madness, Ansti for yourself
Sorry
I need to focus a good
And they do it properly
Come on
Hey guys, come on
To the beginning
Take your positions
..... Man killed by
You must stay under the water
Arise, and rapid spin
And hit the wall Bakdmkm
To give a push
Go on, you guys are going to do
So many times
Let's get out, your reasons
Come on
465th
Stand
Take your positions
Come on guys have followed the
Come on
Come on, Come on now
Have followed the progress
Come on
Wait
O wretched, Come here!
Dear low place
Open the door you despicable
I did not do so
Open the door fuck
I had not done
Be sure to not coming from the rear
Stop
What are you doing?
No, no, this method is not valid
481st
You have to -
What if this method is correct? -
Our children in school with this guy
Contact us state this is not the proper way
This is for my son
(Out (Kruger
?? ??? ?????
Brought the nurse
Breathe, breathe
Come on, come on
489th
Come, come
"Nightmares again, a man burnt face"
I have another nightmare last night I heard
Burnt face man trying to kill me
I realized this time that the incident
Got middle school
I woke up before finding out anything
But mostly this means something
He does Btaatbai to school this time
And had fled to the basement
What apparently is willing to go
To that place
If he wants me to find something
I started the dream and my eyes wide open
I can not tell you if it is real
I did not sleep during the last 3 days
502nd
The grown the dream
If you make this dream mean that I was going to die
Is there any one place with him the same thing?
Can anyone help me?
Hope
He died for all
(I know what happened to (Freddie
I chased him
We have imprisoned him and even death Hrgueth
You caused him to do that
We have not fired at him at
We have already Bhamaitkm -
What? -
Him and from what you do
You have talked a lot about him -
We have been Bavp -
Did not say anything
Why not go to police
Oh my God allay -
And the things that we do that -
Cave
By creating Have you?
No
How do you know that he was guilty?
Oh my God
You have killed an innocent man
There are no night to pass on
Without that I think about it
525th
..........
When you grow up and will become your children
Starwv feeling over the protection
Do not Bc
Asamaini well
As known to everyone here (Fred Kurger) did not
Inojd even
(Curtin)
Wait
532nd
Wait -
Why? -
Stop -
We have made to kill him -
Our story, we lied
What if we were able to stop him? -
What if we can not -
What about the elementary school?
Wish (Freddie) that we find something
OK
(Nancy)
(Not like to live here (Nancy
What are you doing?
I saw (Chris) Kjtp bag
Obsession has happened to you
Let us go
To find that school
What do we do now?
More grain
Can I get more?
Hope
For this, I can not
I've finished only certain groups to get them
Should call the doctor first
Should not call the doctor
I do take them since I was 15 PAL
There is nothing wrong I have to go back
I'm fine
Only a couple of pills, please
No, no, I'm sorry
(Curtin)
Just fill
No
(Courten)
559th
You bleed
Sweater
Well, it's here
562nd
It has really Bovetk
Let's go to the hospital
Come on
Dear
Baby, what happened?.
Who did this to you?
Mom, you know the perpetrator
You know who did it
Baby
What are you doing?
I'll give you something relieves pain
Will be very Biraank
No, no, I do not want
I do not want my mother
I do not want
There is nothing wrong
No mom, I do not want
I do not want
Let's let's bet
No No -
Well -
Where is (Curtin)?
Can I see you abroad?
Not Trhali Mom, do not Trhali
583rd
Your daughter suffers from mental obsession
But I can not do it without your consent
I would like to not feel pain
Good, Sign on to this
She will be just fine
Well
?? ????
It is medicine -
Where brought him? -
Stolen from a vehicle nurse
You can not take this and according to
You do not know what he would do this your
I do not know but I'll have little to
Convenience, Do you want?
Are you okay.?
Yes, I'm fine
Let's go
How much we have left? -
We're about to access -
Would you spoke to me so do not sleep
What do you like to talk?
I do not know
Your favorite color?
Blue
Why over the years, each time
I invite you to come out not surprised that your presence
I do not know if you notice that
But I do not easily integrate into
Well, that survived in the hours following
I'm going to date by making the real
What if she refuses?
Then we will stand here
?? ??? ????? -
Yes -
I saw him
There has been
We have to go
Come on
This is
This is the school
?? ??? ?????
I do not know what is real anymore
Come on
Follow Me
I do not know why there are
I do not remember any of this
This most likely his room
We brought here for the reason
This room, sure that
624th
(Curtin)
625th
There is something back of
We have been here in the past
If kept secret
By making the Boqom to a secret place
These images
All yours
I would like to see it -
No -
We were wrong
Is not behind us, because we lied
Is behind us for we were told the truth
Is brought here to show us
What did the Us
Heck
What he wants from us?
It will not stop
I know what we can do
Come on
You must be a good idea
............
I have to do that
I withdrew from Knzath
What if I could bring?
Nancy) I can not let you growing)
What if I did not get up?
I know you will not let this happen
Then please wake me all your strength
Must do something
I'll be here when you wake up
We would do
Heck
You
You can not rescue them
O wretched
(Kruger)
Your friend here
I'll be back soon
(Hello (Nancy
And now, as you come
What do you want to Tlobei?
Woe to you,
This seems fun
661st
.........
What about the ball first?
No No
It is true
I'm real
Is this fun for you?
This dress
Has always been my favorite
Otaatzkrin this (Nancy)?
Of course, you remember the
You remember you now everything
Is not it?
Memories is what feeds and Judy
674th
No, please
Do not do
Your mind says, "
But your body says, yes
Look at what I've done my
Now, it's time to play
Do you enjoy your time?
Dirty Girl
You can not Oveti
You are in a global
And you can not get out
What do you do?
You can not wake up
Ali to maintaining you awake as much as possible
When long will you sleep will not get up again
Awake, Nancy
Awake
The time has come
Nancy, please
Do you think that your friend is unable to wake you up?
Do not do this
Hope
I am your friend now
Nancy, a recursive
Please wake up
Beautiful dreams
(Curtin)
It will not be
O accursed scoundrel
This is true (Nancy), let me extend my
More
Why was not it?
It hurts, right?
This is because you are in a world now, ye accursed
Wait
There is no one in any place
Hello, Gordon
We ended up
Make sure that you go to sleep, okay?
OK
My mom
You just know you are trying to protect me
Thanks!
I'm happy you are safe now and for the