Come and see.
Riders
Hello.
Pap need food for break fast.
- Since When is this here
- On Tuesday.
Detective we have a report
at 59.
Detective Breslin.
For here.
Someone moved the body
- No but ...
-  Know the cause of death
No we have determined
officially.
Was or.
What the fuck is that
We think we should call it
by his experience with ...
oral ...
- Orthodontist forensics.
- Someone had a very bad day.
- As is.
The victims are men in their thirties
smoker drinker ...
or upper middle class lives in the city
and is clearly not a vegetarian.
-  You are sure of that
- clear.
Every thing indicates that about 32 years
4 or less to you.
I am waiting for results
to be exact but "you see this
Is a trademark of trauma.
Ah the attacker was wrong.
The victims offered resistance
when they are extracted.
You can live to be n
soft diet but .
Come and see.
It was written in four trees
around the pond ...
in the north south
and in the east and west.
Do you know what that means
What took a br Jula
Estn How the kids going
- Okay.
- Must be a difficult weeks for them.
With years of Karen's birthday.
S.
Sleep a little Bres.
Yo ya me voy.
S.
You're almost finished here.
Come on you accompanied o.
What is my strength to even wait
Is my strength the strength of the rock
Is my flesh bronze
• For what I get breast
Will have died without
I saw ning n eye;
will be as if there existed
my belly will be carried
to the grave.
There are many measures of my existence
Land of darkness and disorder
where it is clearly the calgine.
God has given to the impossible
and into the hands of the wicked.
Jes s.
Come and see
'S blood
No painting.
Died about twelve hours.
I do not know long resisted cunt alive.
Arrived How ah
- Drag on ...
- I'm not saying that.
It takes more than one person
to do this.
Make sure that we send rate of a
report of morphologic Huellas.
And is this.
Pair seems to be here to watch.
Com is a pattern n.
The video all of this.
-  Cunt children have
- Three Are down.
Let me do it.
I will.
Who found this
Her daughter.
Cul
The greatest.
Is adopted.
Thanks for your input.
Hello.
I am the detective Breslin
to lead the investigation.
And I want you to know that ...
-  Dnde estn!
- Daddy!
Daddy!  Daddy!
All right.
Have to check that
before we do something about it.
S we will.
What happens
They took something.
What do they take
They took something from it.
Was pregnant.
Detective.
I did not interrupt.
Is good.
Can I help you
Going to catch the person
who did this
I will try.
Kristin.
If you need something if you need to talk
Questions or ...
Call this n mere.
For whatever.
Thank you.
What got to me
Fishing hooks in ankle
detrs the knees ...
two in the rear of
each thigh one on each side ...
and three in the back and also this.
The apu Alaron's chest
a very sharp and elongated.
Perforates the pulmn.
The purpose of the arteries LACER
bronchial and bronchial ...
that is one of the most important
by which the air reaches the lungs.
As the blood began to gush
the artery to cut ...
channel passage of air and
was hurt.
The lungs were flooded.
Have you had accidentally ido
water by the respiratory vas
Imagine that on a continuous
for one hour.
So is murder
with torture
Well ...
if it was intentional called him
torture but was not.
So make incisions in
the place is almost impossible ...
do intentionally.
Probably only Quera
it bleeds.
What is that
Inyeccin of tranquilizer.
-  Was drugged
- S.
To be able to hang.
Or to understand each
things less and less.
Crap.
Look at the Metropolitan Theater
ah your mother knows.
I know I say every time you
pass by here.
S of course.
Want to come to the game tonight
What game
Is ... tena Friend tickets
for the game of the season ...
I thought you would like to come and
I gave him money for them.
• By dnde get so much Alex
You every time we let planted.
S true.
What is the game
The Red Wings.
Red Wings.
- If you can not go because they have a job ...
- No no no.
Go.
Why not
- Sean!
-  S
Guess who is in town
tonight.
- Who
- The Red Wings.
- Great.
- Come to the game.
S!
- S!  S!
- Well!
- Come on!
- S!
- Hi Rose.
- Hey Mr. Breslin.
- Have fun.
- Go to prepare.
- Pap.
- Pap pap look!
Twins appear.
-  S
- It Stingray found another dead.
-  Dnde
- In the 18 Broadway.
We received a call annima.
You must come now.
Ah I'm away.
Steven Silva 23 single teacher
second grade.
- You want this for your teeth.
- No thanks.
There are footprints
No fingerprints but s shoes four.
Looked and acted a three.
And a trpode just in front of him ...
pointing to the windows.
Come and see.
S Well give me a little.
- Is painting again
- S.
What discovery of this gear
They are not cheap. Each hook
placed at points of stamina.
Is made to suit the consumer. I said
this is a connoisseur of suspense.
Knows
The suspension is a cult that is based
in an ancient rite of various religions.
Is the next step in elevacin
after the tattoos and piercings.
Well ah start.
Visit all sites do
tattoos in the city.
We are into that.
Bres.
What
Look at that.
Second grade teacher.
Whoever is doing this is inhuman.
Tuck call the paramedics.
How we did not see this
Damn police work.
Come on promptly!
Northwest Corridor.
- It's good tenant pay rent ...
- Oh wait.
What 'pas  What not to image
Wait "what time was that
At exactly 4:00.
Crap.
Adelntelo again.
Well ah.
At what time did that happen
At 7:00 a.m. sharp.
- Tuck.
- Bres.
What is the hour of death for Silva
The estimated time is between
5:00 and 6:00.
We address the local
where did the tattoo.
Is on the corner of Main and 10.
Well.
Hello. • I can help
S I am looking for something.
Suspension
- S we do.
-  Really
Hey Banksy!
What happens
-  Know who did this
- S.
Yo.
- And When was it
- A month ago or a month and a half.
- You simply called him and never saw him
- No.
Called me and told me what I want and
not fax your requirements.
Do not you find or extra
Please come here doctors
lawyers business leaders to get things
thermal implants stretching
penis everything.
It does not mean that you want
know.
-  Cunt done
- What
Cunt suspension gear made
Brother it is midnight and I'm still
ayudndolo at work ...
when I want to be home
belladonna consuming.
May have to relax if you want
I cooperate  Capisco
S perhaps or perhaps out of here
and review it for you and your car ...
in search of banned substances.
What do you think
Four I made four gears.
Thank you.
Stingray wake
you have to listen.
Made four gears
and we have two victims.
Shit there are two ms.
What you discovered about
the girl's closet
Bready is called Jacobs. Is very
dehydrated and still unconscious.
The drug greatly.
Recently discovered
Garrison divorces Jacobs.
They share custody of you or
that they are now with their grandparents.
• Two children  Guess Garrison
has a son in second grade "no
S.
Discovers that his wife ah state
going to too many conferences.
- And Garrison Jacobs is now ...
- Missing.
We're going to find it.
Forensic Orthodontist
Case Studies and Applications.
- Come and see.
- Hey you should not watch it.
Come and see what
I do not know.
Dictionary of Quotations and Phrases.
"Come and see"
Revelation 6
Sean get away from my stuff.
Karen objects.
Revelation 6.
Revelation.
Come and see.
You gotta be kidding.
It is ceremonial.
The tray teeth.
It estn announcing want
we know that they are here.
Who
Revelation 6:
Bean and I watched a white horse;
and that tena him a bow ...
was given a crown and left as the winner.
When I opened the second seal
or second living deca: >
Then went out another horse red;
which was granted him ...
Remove the earth peace
and was given a large sword.
• You remember that
When he opened the third seal
or third-living deca: >
I looked and then a horse black beans
him that the tena
a balance in hand.
The estn ticking.
The quarter horse is the PLID.
The name that sat on him was Death
Hades and you.
They are the Four Horsemen of the Apocalypse.
The book of Revelation is the vision
Apstol of John.
Gives a vision of the final
seg n reveals Jes s.
The riders of the first four
seven prophets of doom.
Well la Muerte
PLID horse goes.
- That in fact is green.
- Pestilence in the black horse.
- And the red horse is ...
- War.
What is the difference between death
and the War
I believe that war is a good
no concept of the men ...
killing one of them but of conflicts.
Death is something physical and
War a state minimum.
And the rider of the white horse
The white horse rider is lder.
Some believe it is the Antichrist
others believe that Jesus Christ is the same.
Aidan these people chose to
riders as models for a reason.
If you really understand the symbolism
of riders and apparently is as ...
should expect that things
pondrn is much worse.
We are looking for a
team of four people.
They have the intention to charge
two more victims.
My intention is to stop them.
The first suspect is the smaller
weighs between 100 and 115 pounds.
The other three while he watched
Marianne tortured Spitz.
The suspects were arrested
much time around his head.
Must have been having
conversacin tremendous.
The second suspect is Garrison Jacobs
whose whereabouts are unknown.
The third suspect deals
the death blow for both.
I think the horse PLID.
- Death.
- Why
Because the fourth suspect is nico
that on both occasions did not move.
Not even an inch.
The fourth suspect is that the
have to worry about.
Is the group lder.
If you're ending it.
Breslin.
Bres another body at the Bell Hotel.
What got to me
Hello Garrison.
Bres.
You remember when you spoke of
pu winged and the ...
it was intentional
- S said it was impossible.
Retreat this.
- Is the same
- Almost exactly.
It means we are looking for someone
with medical knowledge.
Or a penchant for medicine.
Same thing.
There is no rigging.
Arrived on Monday afternoon
with a single suitcase.
The register is said to be
indefinitely.
Nobody lives in a hotel unless
is home or is hiding from someone.
L É saba was the next.
And the only person who saba why
saba he is in a bag plstico.
- Excuse me.
- Now the only person ...
mvil one is in a bag plstico.
All tracks that tenamos ...
estn bags plstico.
What
Sean told me to help you today.
- I was very excited.
- S.
Perhaps the next time you should not
or a show or a seven-ye ...
photos of the scene of a murder.
Alex is not showed he found them
and I will remove them.
Whatever.
Hey Alex.
Thank you for caring so well for Sean
has been very good with him.
The meeting of parents of school
is tonight.
- Last week I remembered.
-  What time
- Like five minutes ago.
- Shit!  Shit!  Shit!
Alex has a lot of potential and
that is why it is so frustrating.
- Do not you do right
- It is wonderfully where is.
But that's not very often.
Alex is what we call a student
High performance ...
without effort.
You do not have to work hard
to do well who does not.
Well that ...
It's my fault. Not so long step
with them as I wanted.
The therapist of the group to attend
that deca ...
Moreover to be frank I think
is that Alex is good to try at least.
It is not very common in boys than
have lost one parent.
S.
I'm sure.
Ya est.
Well go to bed.
I was thinking that maybe Sean and
I can take you to school ma ana.
- To make sure you go.
- good.
Good night.
Thanks for coming to see me.
Nothing to do but Kristin I do not think
be the person I should talk.
- I'm not trained for ...
- I want to talk to a normal person ...
not with a man wearing starched
and a recorder.
Agreed.
But I tell you
I'm not very good with no os.
- I'm not an a.
- No of course not.
• You have children
I have two children.
What do things together
Actually we do
many things together.
Why not
For many things.
Sean was and still small or
I am known.
Alex ... I was so concentrated
in my work ...
I lost a child.
My parents did.
They thought that my mam was sterile
e iban to choose a baby ...
but then my mam knew of orphanages
us the great ms.
I remember the first time I saw her.
Tena eight when I came to you.
I want to take it.
Could not decrselo but just did.
These measures were my parents
and I was her daughter.
It was as it always is so.
By following a birth or Teresa.
Doctors said it was a miracle.
It must have been difficult.
Why people do
things you do
I do not know.
Sorry.
I feel
Why you feel it
Not that saba
this was in it.
No saba saba not ...
Why waste their time
I know what I am going to ask ...
five minutes before you.
Detective Breslin.
If you say some things.
Aidan I wonder what you think about m.
Pens that was a sweet or slo ita
mistreated by the world
- What do think now
- Still the same.
You would
As you know I knew that
have a special relationship.
Why your mother
- Because I hate my father.
- Why not him
You prefer to be dead or
live the rest of his life without his beloved
I prefer to be dead.
Can be Kristin
You realize
Why you delivered
Longed to have a good conversacin.
No eres la Muerte.
Know the difference between death
and War detective
S Death is a physical
War and a state minimum.
He has reason.
Death is what happens in the end
War is what others.
What is the EDDM
I want to say that he has not found
Books trophies
mu FFS clowns terrifying.
Clothing mu Equitas.
Mu fair
- S.
- It is big enough for mu Equitas.
Here is another.
Garrison Jacobs.
Mary Anne Spitz.
No wait.
What are you feeling
It seems that podrs survive
Should feel that justice exists.
Still you do not feel dispensable
Tu coraz?n te said that it
When your end
Oh God!
Now I feel like I was myself.
Over the past 10 ye
You know what he does.
- And if you've forgiven.
- No no.
No sorry.
I am your daughter and let them suffer.
T suffer now ...
The worst thing you can know
War and then death.
Now you'll drown mam.
Oh God mo.
Victims of crmenes:
Per region.
Stingray!
Dnde You are devils
Saba who were not here.
I thought it was one of them.
I know what you did.
What the hell ...
Came to find this
What is manipulating detective.
What is manipulated to create
what she wants.
Stingray why not call
Children's Services to reflect ...
the daughters of Spitz
Mr. Spitz prisin go.
I will.
Let me tell you something.
She is a fucking monster.
Your room is very red.
Aidan I know what it means
are doing.
No I do not understand.
No lie he saw the photos
and you know what I did.
They know as well as I do.
Llevrsela it was not enough.
É he needs to know that he Dola
inside as a m.
Twelve hours in exchange for ten to you
I think it is a business
quite favorable.
And the other Kristin
Garrison Jacobs    Steven Silva
What made you
And there will be more "is not as
Three people do not make an apocalypse.
Cunt Kristin
Four riders four offerings
that's all.
Aidan you will not find them.
Happy birthday you mam.
You forget
Do not forget me.
I never forget.
Is ...
Alex we can not continue
all this to you.
Is ...
Hey sometimes I do not know cunt
to explain that ...
the fact that not showing
does not mean that the extra e.
- Do not know what it pas.
- I was ah!
Was all the biopsies ah!
To all chemotherapies!
Were not needed when HACA!
The case in which we work
while mam was mora ...
worth it
Bres.
The Four Horsemen of the Apocalypse
Aubrick of Dura.
Was done in 1488.
Handsome no
Got this from estmago
Garrison Jacobs.
I think that made him.
É xodo 9:15
What is the computer dnde
from which it emerged this.
Can you crawl
We can connect
the chip to the IP address.
And you dnde dir
Probably if the IP address was
issued by the OC ...
We can locate the physical address.
Do it.
The informtico has
the location for the chip.
Come on.
Qutense!
Close all going to escape!
Fled by callejn Est!
All Out!
Clear the place!
Move!
Go!
We are nothing.
Bres!
Bres leave it!
Go!
Very interesting.
Bres the suspect escaped.
I am establishing a permetro.
At least we were lucky with something.
Dile.
Used magnesium in the discs around
of RAM. It burns at 4000 degrees.
Quite intelligent but the magnesium
not enter that.
- It gives me a good start.
- I saw a web page on this monitor:
"We're nowhere." If you were
on the disk  can find it
- Give me some time.
- Do it quickly.
Black black black ...
Red red red ...
Green ...
Ped you a coffee.
- Like two packages az car ...
-  Well
What do you want
Me mam and pap supporters.
I do not understand why you are concerned.
Mam pap and you support them
No.
Mam and pap not understand this.
They do not understand why you do this
I do not understand.
Even affects them
or yourself.
Do not affect us
Jdete!
Do not affect us!  Jdete!
They have no idea! I'm going down the street
and people say:
"Ah will Kurth Taylor. Sabas that
maricn your brother is  "
I do not like people to talk
walk fuck my blood ...
and know that they have reason.
Jdete!
What the fuck You are doing
Stop mourn maldicin.
Leave maldicin!
I do not go ...
What the fuck for!
Go clean something!
Stop it!
Comprtate like a man!
For once in your life!
He added that things were
as tonight.
What expecting Cor
What change believed
What you say I am happy
that my brother give up his ass
Come on.
No slo ...
- We do not want you to come to ...
- Seriously cllate.
According
I'm not exhausted take me home.
Take me home.
I want to go home and get into bed.
God.
You are right
I do not touch it!
Is yours
- S.
- Okay.
Sorry.
Cow your pockets and quickly.
Listen if you go back another step
you open like a pig.
- I continue to Hades.
-  Do you mean
I said: "I continue to Hades."
Man 35 background
of assault and attempted robbery.
Tonight intent to rob
the wrong guy.
The victims resisted and
hole is made in the side.
Y. ..
Dile.
I said I did not worry because
beans do not hurt my organs.
-  See his face
- S.
-  You can make a picture talk
Get the best cartoonist I want
is promptly right now.
And by sending fax to all the portrait
hospitals within a radius of 200 km.
Comparing it with the employees
residents stretcher with everyone.
- Find him.
- Right away.
Hi this is Detective Breslin.
Hi this is Lee Shoemaker am
nurse at the teaching hospital.
I know Corey.
Know his surname
Thank you.
Kurth Kurth Corey.
K-U-R-T-H
Detective Breslin we
direction of Corey Kurth.
555 Canal Street.
Estn reinforcements on their way.
Find something green
but not the rider.
Somebody help me
I leave here.
Corey Corey.
Corey!
By God someone zafe of me here!
Oh shit you are t
Corey Scame of here.
What You are doing
Scame of here Scame of here.
Why do this
You are not understand what I am doing.
S understand.
Sorry!  Sorry!
Sorry!
I did not mean anything I said!
Nothing was serious!
Sorry!
Is one I ask!
I am your brother Corey!
- What You are doing
- I can not live as.
• You can not have a big brother
I support and feel happy ...
m and I for him
I admire you very much!
Let's Talk!
Sorry!
No!
No no more conversations!
What the hell are you doing!
- The pain has to disappear.
- Sorry!  Sorry!
- The pain away tonight.
- Corey zfame now!
Zfame now!
To!
Corey do not do that!
Come and see
I am the detective Breslin.
I have to do some questions.
You hear me
-  Taylor
- I hear.
• You can not tell what
I want to hear how
I hung my brother ...
or how I have to look ... look ...
Taylor I need you to help me
understand why he did.
Because it's a damn maricn.
It's a damn maricn.
You madito maricn
maricn a damn!
Qutenle hooks.
How could that be
• With CFC
Enough sleep
an elephant.
It is more like what I've seen
someone to start an coraz?n.
As he found Corey
Tell me.
dead.
- Corey was an amazing person.
- No doubt.
Corey and T are different worlds.
How do two people
as you know
Want to know how people like
we can know
We are nowhere  Cmo
not going to be
The world from my room
and from Corey ...
and that of anyone
looking for something or someone ...
not found in your home.
And Taylor suffering
S is pretty screwed.
That makes you happy
Is that what you think  What is
we do is for our happiness
Do not know anything about suffering.
But now is giving attention "no
Now I'm giving
attention Kristin.
I have four victims and
only two riders.
Can save much time
and energy now.
Never catch the plague never.
And the white horse rider ...
Can not find someone as
someone as you find yourself.
You would    It was as it happened
• The horse rider of the horse
White found you ...
and organizes all of this growth
a frmula to show the world
S that is what makes a lder.
Can learn a lot from him.
Not as.
Dnde is Sean
I left to go to dinner at a friend's house.
I did not think you came.
We talk
This place is good.
Come with your friends
S sometimes with my friends but
Last I do alone.
Sometimes I come after school
when Sean is at a friend's house ...
t working.
Should start to come together ...
once a week
and may do so ...
something of ours.
Clear.
Pap Sean has started to
many questions.
Why You are not ever
And stuff.
They can answer them but will
begin to ask mam.
Alex I want you to know that ...
'm sorry you had to
spend that time alone with your mam.
But you know anything that will
because they were all rather than you.
Not that you have not been ah
That night it's not back.
Everything you not with your mam
was difficult for everyone.
But since I came back I am
you said that back.
Alex if I am
Work is bad very bad.
But now nearly complete and when finished
all be different.
-  Everyone differently
- I promise.
The division of the West needs you
in a case of attempted violacin.
Instruccin of the meeting is tonight.
Hey Krupa wait wait.
I do not have time for this.
There are still two riders all out.
We were told that there will be four victims
and we have four victims.
No still have not finished.
Let me explain something.
Chose the Four Horsemen
of Revelation for a reason.
Sabas that the word "Apocalypse"
not even mean the end of the world
- No.
- The literal translation is ...
"lifting the cloak."
All this time have been trying
show us something.
They have left tracks and all that.
Look for AC. É this is the website
connected to the computer.
It is a template.
There are thousands of members.
See that date
Is new not ah.
When I first saw was the
space to write the pass a.
January 21
It ma ana.
All this time has tried to
lead to something.
Bring something  Not you see
- What will come
- I do not know but pass ma ana.
We know two of them. If we could
discover what connects them ...
That leads us to the other two.
- And I need more time for that.
- We have no more time.
- Stop!
- Krupa!
The Four Horsemen of the Apocalypse
were sent ...
to create Hell on Earth.
And being ma ana.
Well you have 24 hours.
We have been leaving bread crumbs.
I guess we have lost some
because ...
Bres
Four ales are all indicating
directions.
Mary Anne Spitz one two three four.
Silva's apartment one
two three four.
Garrison room Jacobs ...
There are only three.
S that is why there is no rigging
no ceremony no paint no collar ...
nor removed anything to the body.
That is why n is not to lift the veil
Garrison Jacobs is not the third victims.
And what was it
Garrison Jacobs is the pestilence.
I was trying to take
my beauty nap.
Garrison Jacobs forced us to punish
the innocent.
What they said
Who was bothering his son.
- I lied I was ...
- Spite mint.
- As it bled.
- And do pruning because ...
not needed to pestilence
as much as the others.
- Slo l  operating computers.
- It would have been nice to make ...
the rite of pestilence complete.
Three riders does not sound the same.
That only means that
There is a rider less.
So there will be other victims.
It is not Bresli detective
Three of four of us no longer estn
out and you had nothing to do.
To have stuck.
Really.
Adis Kristin.
Because it's your Great Da
clergy "and who could stand
Who could stand
That's why they use the gear.
Find anything
- Both were in group therapy.
- Who are the doctors
Anette Richardson.
Y. ..
We will make a visit.
Oh God.
We think we should call it
by his experience with ...
Forensic Orthodontist.
Bres what happens
Kristin acted like I knew
since the delivery.
And it's because I know.
Put teeth into the pond to
I assigned the case.
Estn m behind and my family.
I want to make me a favor
go to my house and care for Alex.
- I will pick Sean.
- What happens Bres
When Karen died
Alex went to group therapy.
With the same doctor.
Sean Breslin for all I
I am your father.
I need to say
If you are in her classroom.
Call home.
Bres.
-  Stingray
- Me I'm at home.
What the hell ...
Stingray
Stingray!
Stingray.
Emergency  How can I help
Aidan Breslin speaks detective.
There is an officer badly injured in
28 Nancy Street.
Can not find someone as.
What you find as you.
Will wonders where is.
But that's not very often.
Come and see.
Alex!
Alex respndeme!
-  Pap
- All right Alex.
I'm going to get!
Resist!
All right!  Gonna be okay!
I'm bleeding!
It is supposed to drown me
no bleeding.
- No!
Has to know!
This does not stop us!
There are only four horsemen
millions!
Born in this rotten world with parents
that did not even try to understand them!
- I understand.
- And do not finish ...
until all the parents of this
rotten society they realize ...
that can happen to them.
We estn watching.
Estn waiting for the last
rider made the ultimate sacrifice.
Estn waiting to be my death
to begin the Apocalypse.
The veil was lifted and
People finally see.
Alex please tell me
that you did not do these things.
And you do not do that.
Why
Because I'm your son
Three will not go to
my room.
Lo nico Tenas to do that
was to go to my room.
Alex
I told you it will be different.
Still can be.
Alex.
Alex. Alex!
No Alex!
No!
Alex
Alex!
Open your eyes mrame!
Pap ...
You have reason you have reason.
After the death of your mother
never returned.
Ah never for you and Sean.
Please I'm sorry
please perdname.
Give me the opportunity to behave
as a father.
Mrame whatever happens
never leave you again.
All right.
Do not let them die.
Sean.
Papi
I had a night mare.
yas
Now I'm here.
Dnde Alex
Do not worry about Alex.
Alex will be fine.
I love you Sean.
Also I love you Daddy.