(CHRISTMAS MUSIC PLAYING)
(ALL SINGING)
# Smurf the halls with boughs of holly
# Fa la la la la la la la la!
# 'Tis the season to be jolly
# Don we now our white apparel
# Fa la la la la la la la la!
# Smurf the ancient
Yuletide carol
# Fa la la la la la la la... #
What in
the blue blazes?
Grouchy's house is as bare
as a Smurfling's bottom.
(GASPS)
Oh, my.
(KNOCKS)
Grouchy, what's wrong?
GROUCHY: Oh, you mean other
than being bothered by carolers,
who aren't even
in tune, by the way.
Ooh, what's gotten
into him?
What do you mean?
He's always,
uh, Grouchy.
CLUMSY: Yeah, but
not at the holidays.
Yeah. You always
decorate for the holidays.
I hate decorations.
Okay. But you're still coming
to the big party tonight, right?
Every Smurf helps
decorate the tree.
You call that puny twig a tree?
(LAUGHS SCORNFULLY)
Count me out.
But we always
decorate as a family.
Yeah. And you always put
the star on top of the tree.
He's right, Grouchy. That very
important task belongs to you.
You know what,
I hate tasks.
I hate stars, mistletoe, candy
canes, stockings, and fruitcake.
I hate Christmas.
How can someone hate
fruitcake? It's delicious.
Oh, Papa, you need
to do something.
It just won't be the same if
we can't all celebrate together.
Hmm.
I have an idea.
PAPA: Ooh.
A dash of nutmeg,
a touch of holly.
What exactly is
this potion, Papa?
The Christmas spirit,
designed to show him the
true meaning of the holiday.
And now the final ingredient,
essence
of smurfberry.
- Wow!
- (CHUCKLING)
Whoa! (GIGGLING)
(GROUCHY MAKING
AIRPLANE NOISES)
(SINGING)
# Fa la la la la la la la lame! #
How do you smurf
a hall anyway?
Ugh.
I hate warm
smurfberry nog.
Oh. But I also
hate being thirsty.
Huh?
Hmm.
Eh?
Hmm!
I suddenly
feel sleep...
(GROUCHY YAWNING)
Who turned out the lights?
Oh!
Wow.
Heh.
My stomach is
looking flat.
What's up there?
I got a blue belt in smurf-fu
and I'm not afraid to use it.
Ha-hi!
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
- Oh!
- (FEMALE COUGHING)
You really should sweep
that thing once in a while.
(GROANING)
- Smurfette?
- I'm the Smurf of Christmas past.
Don't you see
my smurfy wings?
(GIGGLES)
Oh, my.
I shouldn't have had that
second glass of smurfberry nog.
Oh, go away.
You're just a figment
of my indigestion.
No! I'm one of three spirits
that's going to visit you tonight.
It seems that you lost the
true meaning of Christmas.
So our job is
to help you find it.
Argh.
I think I'll pass.
Feel free to use the
door on your way out.
Oh, I'm not leaving
until I take you
on a magical journey
back in time.
Congratulations!
Nothing happened.
(BELL RINGING)
What the smurf?
Oh, I hate mornings.
Except for
Christmas morning.
- Hey, it's me.
- It is you.
But a you from
long, long ago.
Presents, here I come.
Christmas was always
the one time of year
when you put your
grouchiness aside.
# ...jingle Smurfs
Jingle all the way! #
- (HUMMING)
- Ugh.
The past me
is so annoying.
Whoa!
Weird, right?
(CHUCKLES)
Wait till you see this.
(GIGGLING)
Neat, huh?
(CHEERING AND LAUGHING)
(YELLING)
Mmm.
Ah!
(GIGGLING)
(CLEARS THROAT)
Oh!
Ha!
Whoo!
Hey, I remember this.
And here you
come now.
(CHUCKLING)
(WHISTLING)
- Merry Christmas, Grouchy.
- Yeah. Merry Christmas.
Merry Christmas.
The sooner I get to my chair, the
sooner I get to open my presents.
- Merry Christmas, Grouchy.
- Merry Christmas.
Yeah. Merry
Christmas. Ah!
Merry Christmas,
Grouchy.
Yep. Whatever. Merry...
- (GROANING)
- (LAUGHING)
- Ah!
- (GIGGLING)
(HUMMING)
Hmm?
(GROWLING)
(LAUGHING)
(GIGGLING)
Oh!
GROUCHY: I don't
have time for this.
Seriously!
We got to get to our seats
now. Enough is enough.
Whoa! Whoa,
whoa, whoa!
(SINGING)
# Fa la la la la la la la! #
Come on.
Let's dance.
- I hate dancing.
- Really?
That's not what
it looks like to me.
Ooh!
Oh. Hey!
(WE WISH YOU A MERRY CHRISTMAS
PLAYING)
(GARBLED HUMMING)
(LAUGHING)
- Whoo!
PAPA: Gather around, Smurfs.
Gather around, everyone.
(CHUCKLING)
Hurry up, Grouchy. It's
time to open your presents.
Ha, ha, ha!
(LAUGHING)
Oh. This was
a long time ago.
Please let me get it. Please let
me get it. Please let me get it.
- Get what?
- What I'd asked for for Christmas.
A hang glider.
Whoa! It's like a giant
paper airplane you can fly in.
I know. It's gonna
be the smurf.
And for you.
And for you,
and for you.
Merry Christmas.
For you.
And for you.
It's not very big.
PAPA: All right.
Open them up.
- (ALL GASPING)
- Whoa!
A new hat.
- A new hat.
A hat.
Whoa! A new hat.
A new hat.
Again.
All I ever wanted
was that hang glider.
Every year I ask Papa for it,
but did he ever come through?
Let's find out.
SMURFETTE: And then a few years later,
and every year after that.
Seriously!
SMURFETTE: And then
there was last year.
Hey, look. Papa asked
me to give this to you.
Look!
(GASPING)
Finally!
(LAUGHING)
Kidding! Here's
your real gift.
BRAINY: Whoa!
A new hat!
(GROWLING)
Isn't Christmas about
getting what you want?
Well, I want
a hang glider.
Why do I even bother
to celebrate Christmas
if all I ever
get is this?
The same old
boring, useless hat.
I mean, how many hats
does a Smurf need?
Oh, who asked you?
I hate hats.
(SIGHS)
(MUTTERING ANGRILY)
Oh!
And that's why you
decided to hate Christmas?
Why get your hopes up if
all you get is disappointed?
What's there to be
disappointed about
when you're surrounded
by such a smurfy family?
Ha. More like
an annoying family.
I could have used that hang glider
to fly away for some peace and quiet.
Well, if you wanted
to fly, then let's go.
You've got
somewhere to be.
Hey!
Oh, man. You are heavier than you look.
- Whoa.
- Whoa!
Sorry! I'm new
at this.
(YELLING)
Hey! Wedgie!
Wedgie! Wedgie!
Watch where you're going!
Whoa!
Ah!
SMURFETTE: Sorry!
Whoa!
(GROUCHY YELLING)
Ow! Oh! Ah!
(SMURFETTE LAUGHING)
Whoa, whoa! Oh! Oh!
Ah!
Oh. Oops.
Whoa!
I hate falling!
Ooh!
BRAINY: Nice of you
to drop in.
Brainy?
I'm afraid you are
incorrect in your assumption,
for I am the Smurf
of Christmas present.
Then where are
the presents?
I'm here to show you how
your hatred of Christmas
is going to affect
the whole village.
GROUCHY: What are
you talking about?
Every Christmas, I would just
put up a couple of decorations.
And Papa would make me put
a star on top of the tree.
Every action, no matter
how small, has a reaction.
Behold!
Because you decided not
to help decorate the tree,
Chef had to step in and
help with the ornaments
instead of baking his
traditional gingersmurf cookies,
which had an exponential effect on
the rate of Christmas cheer per Smurf
that when multiplied by the square
root of total chaos to the...
Grouchy, why do
I bother? Just watch.
I have more Christmas
decorations. Whoa!
Ooh!
Oh, the star for the top of the tree.
Oh, but Grouchy
isn't here.
Hey! Hey, I'll take care of it.
- No, Clumsy.
- No, no, no!
Ooh!
(POPPING)
(ALL GASPING)
Whoa!
- The stockings!
Hey!
Well, at least the
fire's out. (CHUCKLES)
- (ALL GASPING)
- No!
Out of
the way, Smurfs!
This wouldn't have happened
if Grouchy were here.
Every Smurf plays an
important part, you see?
Yeah. I see.
Not yet,
you don't.
PAPA: There we are. Now it's
just the way Greedy likes it,
with a little pocket inside
to keep extra smurfberries.
And Tailor will be delighted with
the extra-large built-in pin cushion.
Papa makes all of our hats himself?
And crafts each one to meet the
particular needs of every Smurf.
Takes him all year.
Grouchy, I've made a
hat I know you'll love,
if only you'd
give it a chance.
Well, maybe
this year.
Papa, I didn't know.
He can't hear you.
It's time to go.
(WIND WHOOSHING)
Hey, Brainy!
Where did you go?
Ahh!
(MUFFLED YELLING)
Brainy,
is that you?
Ah!
Sorry, bro, just finishing
up the holiday fruitcake.
But I already know
your feelings on that.
- Hefty?
- Oh, not Hefty, you lump of coal.
I am the Smurf
of Christmas future.
And the future is...
This?
This is
the future?
In a manner
of speaking.
It's tomorrow.
It's
Christmas Day.
Christmas Day?
Then where
is everyone?
They all left
this morning.
They wanted to do something to help
you get your Christmas spirit back.
CLUMSY: I know what
would make Grouchy happy.
How about we
all go get a new tree in the morning?
One of the huge smurfy ones
from the west forest.
- That'll cheer him up.
FARMER: That's a great idea.
SMURF 1: For Grouchy.
SMURF 2: Let's do it for Grouchy.
SMURFETTE: This will make everyone happy.
(LAUGHING)
And what happened?
They never came back.
Never came back?
What do you mean?
The west forest.
(HUFFING)
Smurfette!
Brainy!
Clumsy...
(GRUNTING)
Oof!
Need to do
more cardio, bro.
(GROANING)
Brainy wouldn't go
anywhere without these.
(GASPING)
Where are they?
No!
Gargamel's lair.
It can't be.
It can, actually.
What about
the others?
I thought you were going
to take me to the others.
Oh, I have.
GROUCHY: Oh, no.
All of them.
They were
all captured.
Trying to make
me happy.
When Papa came looking for
them, Gargamel got him, too.
(SIGHING)
I've been so selfish.
Well, on
the bright side,
looks like you'll all get to spend
one last Christmas together after all.
Merry Christmas to me!
- (CACKLING)
- Hefty! Hefty!
- Yeah!
- Whoa!
Ow!
Whoa!
Ah!
Oh!
(PANTING)
I see you've met
Santa Claws.
(GRUNTING)
Ha!
Oh!
(CACKLING)
Ah!
You are going to look
great on top of my tree.
(SCREAMING)
Ah!
Help!
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
Oh, no!
Ahh!
No!
It can't end
like this.
I can change!
Oof!
I can change.
(SIGHING)
Where am I?
I'm back
and I'm alive.
(GRUNTING)
It's not Christmas
morning yet.
There's still time
to set things right.
(DISTANT SINGING)
(CHUCKLING)
(YAWNING)
What is that?
(GROUCHY HUMMING)
- Oh!
- Whoa!
Huh?
- That's incredible.
- Look at this.
(HUMMING)
Well, well. Look who's finally up.
Grouchy,
you did all this?
I even baked
a fruitcake.
(ALL GASPING)
And I was wrong.
Christmas isn't
a time for hating.
That's what all
the other days are for.
I was so busy focusing
on what I wanted
that I didn't see
the real gift
was having a family
that cares,
even though
I'm Grouchy.
Merry Christmas.
I know it's not the hang
glider you always asked for,
but I made it
just for you.
Thanks, Papa.
A new hat!
(CHUCKLES)
Oh!
I made it
for all of us.
Merry Christmas,
everyone.
(ALL) Yeah!
Merry Christmas.
Hey, wait a minute. If Papa
knew I wanted a hang glider...
PAPA: Remember,
it's just for you.
Merry Christmas,
everyone.
Whoo-hoo!
(LAUGHING)
Whoo!
Whoa!
Oh!
(GASPS) Oh, no.
Ugh! I hate snow.
And I hate being cold,
and I hate carrots.
But most of all, I hate that
Christmas is only once a year.
(ALL LAUGHING)
(ALL SINGING)
# Smurf the halls with boughs of holly
# Fa la la la la
la la la la! #
PAPA: Merry Christmas.
(PAPA CHUCKLING)