You move over.
Hey, this is Luke. This is my film.
Let me ask you a couple of questions.
Why do you dance?
Because it's like breathing,
it's like walking to me.
I'm not pretending.
When I dance I don't pretend.
l'm more myself when l dance
than any other moment of the day.
I dance to become someone else.
There are so many things in this world
that want to push down on you,
but when you dance you are free.
We started dancing at the age of seven
in our house, in the living room.
Just dancing, dancing,
copying Michael Jackson.
And I'm just like listening to the music
in the grocery store,
just like dancing through the aisles
and stuff like that,
and she's like,
"Contain yourself, calm down."
And l'm like, "l can't stop,
I have to do it, I have to do it."
After everybody went to sleep I would
open the garage and just practise.
That's pretty much when I knew
I loved it because I had never dedicated
so much time and effort
into something like that.
It's not us just jumping around.
Dance has vocabulary.
- lnglewood.
- I'm from Argentina.
I'm from northern Uganda.
- Miami, Florida.
- Koreatown, Los Angeles.
There's a lot of gangs and violence.
I couldn't be stuck there all my life.
My village was attacked.
My parents didn't even want me
around any more.
She actually kicked me out of the house.
- l had to go.
- Dance saved me.
Dance definitely saved me.
lf it wasn't for dance,
I don't know what we'd be doing right now.
I didn't have anything,
I didn't have money.
I was living with $1 5 a week
in New York City.
Dance brought us together too,
all around the world. We're here.
Truth is everybody is a dancer inside.
We all have a heartbeat.
We all have a rhythm inside.
Boom-boom, boom-boom.
- What's that one thing you say?
- Yeah, what do you call us?
- (Luke) Born from a boombox?
- Yes.
- Born from a boombox.
- That's pretty good.
Born from a boombox.
(Luke) It sounds stupid,
but I do feeI Iike that.
And if we listen hard enough,
we realise that maybe we're all
pIugged into the same song.
(♪ Dance music)
New York University freshmen,
welcome to Washington Square Park.
It's the central hub of our urban campus,
and to the right...
Mom? Dad? You guys can really go.
No! We're gonna take you
and Camille out for dinner.
We promised her parents we'd feed her.
We're already paying for our meal plans.
It's all good.
Yeah, we're fine, we really are, Mrs A.
- We should go.
- All right. One last picture.
OK. One last picture.
Get together, you're best friends,
you could drive a truck through you.
- We're close.
- Get closer! Put your arm around her.
- OK.
- Good boy.
All right. Ready? Say, "Mom is pretty."
- (Both) Mom is pretty.
- Thank you.
(Laughs) Ready? And... Oop.
Oh. Look at this. Picture of a hat.
I got a hat with hair.
lf my father could see me now saying
goodbye to my son, a future engineer...
l'm just so happy you're done
with that dance business, I can't tell you.
Oh, but you have...
- OK, all right. You make me proud.
- OK. This is it.
Could I get in your backpack? Come on.
- That's too tight. OK. All right.
- Come on.
I'll make you proud
if I could just go to orientation.
- No! You're my baby.
- Everybody left already.
- All right. OK.
- I'll call you when I get to the dorm.
- Wear deodorant, deodorant. Every day.
- Come on.
- OK, honey? It's important.
- Come on, honey.
- Cos you're a man now.
- Honey, we got to beat the traffic.
All right.
- Wow! They really...
- Are embarrassing.
- I was gonna say "love you".
- Sorry.
Hey, Cam, check those out.
Those are the limited edition
gunmetal Nike Dunks.
Uh-oh. I know that look. OK, Moose,
seriously, next on the tour, Union Square.
I just wanna get a closer look.
I'm gonna be right back. OK? Cover me.
I guess.
(Cheering)
(♪ NASA: Whatchadoin?)
(Bookie) All right, let's go, who you got?
- I want 25 on Kid Darkness.
- 25 on Darkness, let's go, let's go.
(Cheering)
- Give my money.
- Sorry, guy, I got you.
Oh, snap! Did you see that?
Yo, I want ten on the skinny kid.
Give me 20.
Give me that 20.
Yo, you see that?
Oh, whoo-hoo-hoo!
It's over, it's over, that's it!
Go home! Go home!
Come on, new kid, get in there!
Come on, let's see what you got.
I think we're done here.
He ain't got no flava.
- Yo, look at the kid!
- He moves pretty good for a geek.
Buddy, that kid is real!
Been holding out!
I didn't know that dude
could dance like that.
Let's go, new kid,
let's see what you got.
Hey, you give me five on that.
Give me five on that.
Let's go, Darkness!
(Crowd) Oh!
(Cheering)
Buddy, that kid is real!
(Laughs)
(Crowd) Oh!
Who's gonna pay for my balloons?
Hey, he's right here!
- Get this guy.
- Stop! Police! Hold it right there!
Come on, man. They're after you.
Go. Come on!
Come on, kid.
Come on, let's go.
All right, man, time-out. I can't.
We don't have time for that. Come on!
- Police!
- Get out of the way!
What are you doing? What are you doing?
Jump first, fear later.
Whoa.
- Get out of the way!
- (Luke) Come on, come on!
(Moose) Excuse me!
Out of the way! Out of the way, folks.
(Moose) Oh. Ah.
My ribcage. I feel like
I just threw up in my mouth.
- lt's burning.
- (Car horns beeping)
Where are you going?
Yo.
How did you just do that back there?
I mean, you were like freaking flying, man.
You're like a ninja.
- Luke.
- No, it's like this. You gotta blow it up.
(Makes explosive noise)
Ah, come on.
How's that?
All right.
I'm Robert Alexander the Third,
by the way.
Just since you ask.
But you can just call me Moose.
- I haven't seen you around.
- I'm just starting at NYU.
- I'm actually an engineering major.
- But you're gonna be dancing too.
No, no, no, not any more.
I mean, dancing was cool in high school,
but it's time for me to face the real world.
You really have no idea
what you did back there, do you?
- You're B-FAB.
- What's a B-FAB?
- Born from a boombox.
- (Laughs)
Like, some people learn to dance,
others are born to.
And you're in New York City,
the dance centre of the world.
Check this.
It's the biggest battle ever.
There's never been this kind of prize money.
And those guys in the park,
they're gearing up for this.
You're good enough.
You should be in this.
(Moose) This your car?
Oh, my God, that's so sick!
Get in.
What you saw in the park today
is just the beginning.
(♪ Jay-Z & Alicia Keys:
Empire State of Mind)
This is it.
- What the heck is this place?
- Come on.
Welcome to my house.
The House of Pirates.
(Muffled music)
Nice place. It's a little small to live in.
(Clanging)
My parents converted this place years ago.
We all live and train upstairs and run a club
downstairs to make ends meet.
Kinda like a secret hideout.
Right, this is it.
We call this the Vault.
(♪ K'naan: ABC's)
Around here, dance is your identity.
We live together, work together,
battle together.
But unlike other crews,
we all have different styles.
I found all these guys out in the city.
Crazy talent but no place to go.
We've become kind of a pseudo family here
where we can be ourselves
and rules don't apply.
This place is off the chain.
Thing 1 and Thing 2 over there,
that's the Santiago twins.
You, man, you... We saw you dancing
at the park this morning. You were...
- Amazing!
- You are from another planet.
- Your own planet! You're amazing, man.
- l have a question...
No, no, no, guys. Come on. No questions.
I gotta show him around.
Got it! Come on.
You're great!
- Luke.
- Jacob!
What's up, brother?
- Meet Moose.
- Pleased to meet you, Moose.
This guy right here,
he's the captain of the ship.
More like the first mate. I heard you did
some impressive work in the park today.
How does everybody know that?
News travels fast when you beat someone
like Kid Darkness.
But, Luke, l need to borrow you
for one second. We've got some things...
- Can we wait? I've got to show him around.
- We'll take him.
Let us show him around.
- I don't know about that, guys.
- Please!
- Please. What would Jesus do?
- Come on.
- All right. Don't hurt him, all right?
- Promise.
Moose, this is the Ticks. Good luck.
(Excited chatter)
This came from the bank today.
We're six months late on our payments.
- We paid them last month.
- What about the other five?
We're working on it.
The club's not making the money it used to.
The bank doesn't want to hear that.
If they don't get the money they're going
to put the Vault up for public auction.
Listen, don't I always have a plan?
This kid, Moose, he beat Kid Darkness
today, and he did it with style.
With a little bit of training,
he could be the spark that we need
to win the hundred grand from
the World Jam and pay back what we owe.
Jacob, we're not gonna lose the Vault,
all right? We won't let that happen.
(Tick 2) You don't understand. Nobody ever
smoked Kid Darkness and got it on tape.
(Pirates) Whoo!
- That was serious.
- You're the man.
You think the Samurais
are gonna let you go like that?
They'll find you and they'll batter you again.
- Sam who?
- The House of Samurai.
The most cut-throat house in the city.
- Our fiercest rival.
- Yeah.
They're gonna find me?
They got technology out there,
like the bears with a little GPS inside.
- Watch out, they're right behind you!
- (Laughter)
Come on, that's enough.
Don't let them freak you out.
- You're with us now.
- And nobody messes with us.
- Not even the Samurai.
- Not unless you want to get roasted!
(Cheering)
Unless they want to get
a big patata in their traste!
(Both speaking Spanish)
- What?
- OK, you don't get it
but I know what I'm saying.
(Chatter continues)
(Twins) You got it.
- That's not boring.
- (Tick 2) Losers.
(Chatter continues)
She's back.
The one I've been telling you about.
Hey, Moose. Come on,
I'll show you round the club downstairs.
- Party pooper!
- (Tick 3) Come on, Luke.
Come on, this way.
(♪ T-Pain: Take Your Shirt Off)
Oh!
What? What?
(Luke) Watch out, they bite.
(Cheering)
Crazy, right? Hang out, take a look around.
I'll be back in a second.
(♪ Static Revenger & Richard Vission
ft. Luciana: l Like That)
(Cheering)
(Crowd groans)
(Muffled music)
(Toilet flushes)
Nobody battles the Samurai just once.
Now it's time for the real battle.
- (Samurai laughs)
- Come on, now, you scared?
Come here, man.
(♪ Dance music)
Where do you think you're goin'?
This ain't over yet.
Get him, Baba, get him.
Ow!
Go get the kid!
(Cheering)
I just want a few rounds with the kid.
We got some unfinished business.
You wanna get to him,
you gotta go through us.
Come on, Luke. Be a good sport.
- What are you doing here, Julien?
- Nice to see you, too.
Get your boys and get off our property.
Your property? It's not gonna be
your property for much longer.
And don't worry. When I buy this place,
I'll take good care of it.
When we win the World Jam, you and your
trust fund won't be able to touch us.
(Crowd) Whoa.
That's cute.
Your boy can't even finish his battles.
Bubbles and balloons? That's so amateur.
Enough, man. He will finish it
at the World Jam and so will we.
I don't even know what you just said.
Yo, man, stop being disrespectful
to my crew, yo.
(Hubbub)
Get off!
Hey.
Come on, I'll get you out of here.
Get off her, man.
- Are you OK?
- Yeah.
Thank you.
I'm Luke.
I'm Natalie.
So, what's with the bags?
Oh. I'm supposed to be meeting my friend
here but I guess she's a no-show.
Well, what are you gonna do?
I don't know, I haven't figured that out yet.
You could stay here.
- What, in the club?
- No, I mean upstairs, in the living room.
You don't even know me.
Yeah, I do. Your name's Natalie
and you need a place to sleep.
OK. Sure, thank you.
OK. Grab your stuff.
(Shouting)
Are you sure they won't mind?
Everyone here knows what it's like
to be a nomad.
- So where are you from?
- Here.
But I've been living in London
the last few years.
Wow.
Well, this place'll be a departure.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
So, are you ready?
For bed?
No, for the battle. The World Jam?
We could really use someone like you.
- Are you up for a little competition?
- lt's what l live for.
- Been competing my whole life.
- Do you win?
I never lose.
Good.
I'll see you in the morning.
We have a lot of work to do.
Moose. Where were you yesterday?
I thought we had plans.
- I know, I know. I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
- Sorry?
I had to eat dinner with my freakazoid
roommate who smells so badly.
And she would not stop yammering
about her pet rat's blog.
We should hook our roommates
up together.
Mine looks like a pet rat.
He's got the nose and everything,
- he's got, like, the claws. Ugh!
- (Laughs)
Oh. There you go!
Now I need you to help me find
this engineering lab.
- Moose.
- What?
(Sighs)
- What would I do without you?
- l don't know. l really don't.
(She sighs)
Later, gator.
(Muffled music)
(♪ Dance music)
I see you've found the speaker room.
- Yeah.
- (Music stops)
I built this myself when we could actually
find boomboxes in the city.
- Impressive.
- (Laughs)
- You're up early.
- Already warmed up.
Good. Cos you're my new recruit.
It's my responsibility to get you up to speed.
- Then let's train.
- No, no, no. We're not training here.
OK. Then where?
Out there.
Just try to keep up.
(♪ Dance music)
Before we divide up into lab groups
and begin the work, though,
I wanna talk to you about,
well, what engineering means to me.
What's your name?
(Teacher) And what hopefully engineering
will mean to you.
Silence, that's my name.
- Silence during class.
- (Teacher) Second of all...
(Phone ringing)
Go answer it, Mr Popular.
(Laughs) What?
Open up the cages, boys. Show these
newbies why we call this the Vault.
(Twin 1 ) OK.
(Both) Hey.
Moose boy. How are you, my friend?
- Oh. What a beautiful senorita.
- Por favor.
Nice to meet you.
- Can I give you two?
- (Laughs)
Come on.
- You gonna get mad at me?
- I'm not gonna get mad at you.
I'm just saying hi to her, man.
- I'm introducing myself.
- No, no, no.
You stopped me when I'm introducing
myself to this beautiful...
- Don't listen to him. Don't listen.
- You are so cute.
- (Both speak Spanish)
- OK.
Ladies and gentlemen,
our most prized possessions.
Check it out.
(Twin 2) If dance is our weapon,
then this is our armour.
These are the most beautiful shoes
in the world.
- The way they smell, the way they fit.
- (Twin 1 ) You're sounding like a girl, man.
You're like, "I love the shoes."
You gotta say, "I love the shoes,"
like a macho man. OK, bro.
Luke's lucky shoes? Smart boy.
(Luke) OK, Moose, don't get too attached,
you gotta earn your kicks in this house.
And beyond door number two,
the Graffiti room.
Oh, what?
- Who's that guy?
- That? That's Jason.
He's our graffiti guru. l'm talking
electronic billboard hacks, LED lights,
anything to mark who we are.
Dudes! Excellent timing. l have been
working on a portable light tagging system
and I can't figure out how to get it to stick
to 12V batteries...
- You got any electrical tape?
- Yeah, there you go.
Tape it right there, wrap it round
and it creates a snug fit.
- You know lights?
- Yeah, I dabble.
Check it out.
You... Yes! Yes! I love this kid!
Fix the LED to the battery to the magnet.
They're beautiful.
Like neon fireflies.
- Neoflies.
- Yeah, neoflies.
Neoflies. I like it.
(Chatter)
Cool. Check it out.
Yeah, we could do something with this.
- (Carlos whistles)
- Neoflies.
Listen up. World Jam
is right around the corner,
but to get there, we got to get through
the two qualifying rounds, which means...
Which means
we got a lot of work cut out for us.
Moose, Natalie. Are you guys in?
(Plays suspenseful music)
Erm...
I don't know,
I mean, I have to go to school...
We'll figure something out.
Pirates... Pirates...
(Chanting) Pirates! Pirates! Pirates!
- I can do one battle, guys.
- (Cheering)
All right, all right. Natalie?
House of Pirates!
(Cheering)
(♪ Chromeo: Fancy Footwork)
(He laughs)
(Twin 2) Go, go, go, go, go.
(Tick) Owww!
Whoo!
Yeah!
Whoo-hoo!
(AnaIa) l'm more of myself when
l dance than any other moment of the day.
(Vlado) I dance to become someone eIse.
(Jacob) They aIways think that we are just
a bunch of kids with no direction,
but what we do is very hard.
We make it Iook easy.
You spin and your equilibrium is off
and you stand up,
and aII you have to reIy on
is how well you know your body
and you place your two feet on the floor,
finding your horizon within yourself.
- Wow.
- Hey.
- This is quite the setup.
- Thanks.
I collect footage of dancers who inspire me.
Clearly. (Laughs)
What are you gonna do with it all?
l don't know. Nothing.
I just play around with it.
(Jason beatboxing)
Check this out... Check...
Check-check...
I dance...dance...
..become someone eIse.
We were born...
b-b-born from a boombox.
- I had no idea.
- They're amazing, aren't they?
I mean you.
You're a film-maker.
- What's wrong?
- Nothing, I...
usually don't show people this stuff.
It's just me.
All right.
- You're gonna show me?
- Yeah.
OK.
- Promise not to laugh?
- Oh, I promise.
..or to choose a hobby,
or something Iike that.
lt's another thing for that thing
to choose you.
- (Laughter)
- Jitterbug... Booty shake!
- Yes!
- OK, OK.
This is... This is our teacher in fifth grade.
- Face-lift!
- Yes!
Go. What are you?
- Raptor!
- Yes!
Whoo!
How do you guys even do that?
We can read each other's minds.
Aw, you guys are so cute.
How long have you been dating?
- Oh. No, no, no. It's not like that.
- (Phone rings)
We're just...friends.
(Clears throat) No.
- Correction, everyone. We're best friends.
- (Both) Aw.
Anyway, sorry, guys,
I have to go, I'm in a rush.
- You're leaving? We just started.
- I'll call you later, though. Have fun.
You guys lost.
(Girls) Whatever!
Uh... OK...
Gotcha.
Oh, wow. lt's so obvious,
it makes so much sense now.
- What?
- You're totally in love with him, aren't you?
- No! No, no, no. It's...
- Yes, yes, yes.
..not like that, we're just...
Like, one of those, we grew up together.
No, that would be really weird.
Um... (Clears throat)
I think it's your turn.
- So...
- Me?
Yeah, you're up. You're up.
- OK.
- You go first.
Um... Squirrel. Kangaroo?
Keep trying.
Hey. Look who's up early now.
Actually, I haven't been to sleep yet.
- Can I join you?
- Sure.
- What are you looking at?
- l come out here to listen.
The river, the traffic, the birds.
Make me feel like
I'm part of something bigger.
Traffic makes you feel like
you're a part of something bigger?
That is deep.
Like I said, I've been up all night.
So I've been thinking about your video
from last night.
Like, l think you should finish it.
And you should show it to people.
- Yeah, I don't know about that.
- Clearly you love it, right?
Look at you, you've been up all night
and you're like...
l don't know,
you're glowing or something.
Glowing? (Laughs)
I see a glow.
We should get to Red Hook.
You're right.
(Cheering)
(Announcer) Welcome to Red Hook!
The first round of World Jam!
- Are y'all ready for battle?
- (Cheering)
Red Hook, are you ready?
Pirates, you ready?
Let's get 'em!
(Roaring)
(♪ MIMS: Move [If You Wanna])
(Cheering)
- Yaaargh!
- (Cheering)
(♪ Busta Rhymes: Tear Da Roof Off)
(Cheering)
(All shouting)
(Crowd cheering)
Back up.
And the winner is...
the Pirates!
(Cheering)
The Pirates are now into the next round
of the World Jam!
(Crowd chants) Pirates! Pirates! Pirates!
(Luke) No, no, no.
(Twin 1 ) Yeah. Yeah!
Now it's time for you to be in front
of the camera, my good-looking Pirate.
Do you want some make-up, baby?
(Laughter)
- (Natalie) So, Captain Luke...
- Gimme the camera.
- (Twins) No, no, no.
- It's not that easy on this side, huh?
- It's uncomfortable.
- (Luke) Yeah, why don't you keep walking?
- (Jason) Oh, look at this guy.
- (Natalie laughs)
What do you love about dance?
l don't know. Dance music,
it's just always been there for me, I guess.
(Natalie) Is that it?
What? (Laughs)
(Laughs) I know you can do better than that.
- Come on.
- All right.
My parents used to be dancers.
And they started this place
for people like them,
but that didn't just want to be
backup dancers.
You know, do their own thing,
build their own respect.
l thought that was cool, so l wanted
to carry on the tradition, in my own way,
but for them, you know?
So what do they think of you
turning this place into a madhouse?
They never got to see it.
I'm so sorry.
No, don't be. It's OK.
So that's why you're
so devoted to this place,
carrying on what your parents wanted?
Family is family, you know?
The Vault used to be their life,
and now it's mine.
It's amazing what we do for family
sometimes.
So, tell me about your parents.
(Laughs)
They split up a while back.
And me and my older brother, we were sort
of the dice that got rolled between them.
Where's your brother now?
We're still close.
I mean, he pretty much raised me.
So I owe him everything.
So, Tarantino, are you planning on
blackmailing us with all that footage?
No.
Just you.
Hi. So, I'm sorry for being late, OK?
l won't...
Oh! I'm so sorry.
I thought you were somebody else.
I'm sorry.
- OK...
- (Girls chatting)
- Do you know that trick when they take...
- Really?
They kinda look alike,
l think they're twins.
Camille! What's going on?
I thought we had lunch.
Is it lunch time?
Whoa! Um...
Wow, we got so carried away
with the costumes, I lost track of time.
Costumes for what?
It's for the dorm Halloween party. People
plan their costumes like all semester.
All right. So what are we going to go as?
Oh, um...
Well, actually...
I tried calling you but you didn't pick up,
so Kristin and I are gonna be
the Olsen Twins.
Wait, wait, wait. Kristin?
Kristin?
Camille, Kristin?
What about Moose?
Go ahead, you guys.
You haven't exactly been around lately.
I mean, I couldn't wait forever.
OK, well, hey, Camille,
look, I'm here now.
Come on, what do you say?
You know you're gonna have
way more fun with me than...
Kristin.
Are you asking me to the dance?
(Scoffs)
Camillian? You know that I was born
to be the Ashley to your Mary-Kate.
- Oh, really?
- Yes, really.
OK, OK, fine.
- I'll cancel with Kristin.
- Yes!
I'll see you later.
Guess I'll see you later, then.
Get back to your frie...
- Hey, Kristin! In your face!
- Bye.
(Luke) OK, you gotta stop complaining.
(Natalie) I'm sorry.
I just feel ridiculous holding this giant cup.
Whoever said it was OK to have a small,
medium, large and then ginormous?
Hey, look.
- That's you.
- What are you talking about?
- This guy looks exactly like you.
- He doesn't.
He's got a camera popping out of his head,
pretty little cheekbones.
It does not look like me, and I would not
be caught dead with those culture vultures.
I've seen your work,
and you don't fool me.
Yeah, but it's just for fun.
lt's nothing professional.
Well, what if the Pirates
and the rivalry didn't exist?
Wouldn't you give your film-making a shot?
That film academy sounds amazing.
Yeah, but it's not an option,
so l don't think about it.
The World Jam's our main focus.
- OK, so, tell me, then, how do you do it?
- Do what?
Get all your amazing footage.
I don't know. I just try to see things
that people don't normally see.
Show me.
All right, come here.
(Natalie laughs)
Where are you taking me?
(Luke) Just trust me. Come on.
- Hurry up.
- All right.
(♪ Laza Morgan: This Girl)
- Just wait for it.
- For what?
- What? (Laughs)
- Watch this.
How did you do that? I'm going to do it.
- OK.
- Try it.
OK.
See that? I did it!
- There's Slurpee everywhere!
- (Laughs)
Oh, my God, my straw! I lost my straw!
l think it was just being in my living room,
and me and my brother
were just playing around together,
- and l always tried to...
- (Phone ringing)
..match him.
- Moose.
- Yo. Hey, what time is the battle, again?
- Eight o'clock. Why? You ready for it?
- Eight o'clock?
lt all goes down in Chinatown.
This is the House of Gwai.
They're champions of Asia,
so I hope you're prepared.
- We've got a problem.
- No, this is round two. You gotta be there.
We can't have any missing Iinks or we
could get eliminated from the World Jam.
l know, l know.
I have a test on the same exact day.
I don't know if I can...
Listen, we need you.
Do whatever you can to make it work.
(Teacher) l'm sure l don't need to
remind you how much this test counts.
This is worth 25 per cent of your grade.
Take your time. You may begin.
(Phone vibrates)
(Cheering)
- Yo, where's Moose at?
- I don't know, man.
(♪ Madcon: Beggin')
- Show me something.
- (Speaks Spanish)
(Cheering)
(Shouting)
I'll go get a towel. I'll be right back.
Where you been, bro?
You just ruined the floor.
(Cheering)
(Screams)
(Groaning, jeers)
(Cheering)
What? What?
You the man.
(Announcer speaking
in foreign language)
..World Jam!
(Singing
Hit Me With Your Best Shot)
Whoo!
- Can I talk to you for a minute?
- Yeah, sure.
- Alone?
- Yeah, hold on.
Yo, hold up. Cut the music.
- Cut the music.
- (Music stops)
You guys need to see this.
(Tick 1 ) What is this?
(Anala) Our entire routine.
(Twin 1 ) lt's online?
(Jason) They know our whole set.
- Who would do that?
- Julien and the Samurai.
- How could they get our rehearsal footage?
- Does everyone have their DVDs?
- You have the DVD?
- Yeah, I put them in the room.
(Luke) We're still in this, all right?
We just got to figure something out.
OK, see there? If you could just let go
of that spin, we can land this thing.
Those guys may have our tapes,
but that won't stop us. Trust me.
Luke, l don't know.
Maybe somebody else should do it.
If we pull this off, we'll kill it on stage.
Julien won't even know what hit him.
Whatever happened between you two?
Me and Julien?
He used to be a Pirate.
We used to be best friends back in the day.
But as time went on, things changed.
How do you mean, they changed?
We found out he had a gambling problem.
He wound up in debt. He bet against our
house and threw the battle to win the bet.
He threw a battle to win a bet?
The whole house was devastated,
so we had to kick him out.
He's been trying to take us down
ever since.
The crazy thing is, if we don't win
the World Jam he could actually do it.
Hey.
- Welcome home.
- You lied to me.
You told me Luke kicked you out
because he was jealous.
But it wasn't that, was it?
You threw a battle for a bet?
- Natalie...
- Don't! I went in there for you, Julien.
I can't believe you stole that DVD
and put it online.
What are you talking about?
What kind of BS did he say about me now?
Luke was jealous. He wanted to be
the leader, so he kicked me out.
He used me and he kicked me out.
I'm sorry.
We have to stick together,
Natalie, you know that.
I don't like to be lied to.
I just want our house
to win the World Jam. OK?
We have too much in this.
We've worked too hard.
Despite what Mom and Dad say,
it doesn't always have to be about winning.
You're starting to sound like him. You need
to remember whose side you're on.
Friggin' ridiculous!
Luke isn't some monster, Julien.
He's a good guy.
He takes care of the people that he loves.
Who are you going to believe?
Him or your family?
You're going to talk to me about family?
When Luke isn't even related to any of
those dancers, he would never lie to them.
Oh. I'm a liar? What about you?
How do you think your precious Luke
is going to feel when he finds out
that you have been playing him?
Actually, now that I think of it...
you should come clean.
That might be what I need
to throw his game off for World Jam.
Thanks, sis. You really helped me.
You're not putting him out on the streets
over some stupid rivalry.
I will not be part of it.
Jacob. You scared me.
You don't seem like a girl
that's easily scared.
Tell Luke I'm sorry.
You have a choice, you know?
It's not that easy.
The most important decisions in life
are never easy.
(Jason) Dance can reveaI a Iot
about a person,
the way they move,
the way they learn new steps.
l mean, if you're dancing for real, it comes
from the most truthfuI part of your souI.
I dance to express how I feel inside,
whether it's anger, happiness,
loneliness.
Once I found the Vault,
it was like coming home.
This is where I feel safe.
This is where l belong.
This is where my family is.
This place is special. It's our world.
I think, finally,
I had somewhere I could be myself.
People say that you don't
really choose your family. We did.
- If you are one of us, Luke will find you.
- Yeah.
- Luke.
- Why would she just leave like this?
I don't know. But for the moment,
we've got bigger problems than that.
The bank's put our house up for auction.
- What?
- They're selling it.
I'm going to deal with this, all right?
- What the hell, Walter?
- Hey, Luke. How are you? Sit down.
I don't want to sit down.
I understand how hard this must be.
If you can just wait a few days,
we'll have the money.
You're five months behind
on your mortgage.
Unless you catch up with your payments,
I'm afraid there's nothing more
l can do for you.
The warehouse sits on prime property.
The bank is well aware
what it's going to go for at auction.
- I need more time.
- I'll see if I can suspend the foreclosure.
But don't get your hopes up.
They could take
your warehouse today, Luke.
That's not gonna happen
cos it's not for sale.
(Luke) Look what I just got from Natalie.
What does it mean?
I don't know, but I'm going to find out.
- Come with me.
- Who, me?
- Yeah, I need you.
- I have a Halloween party tonight.
I mean, I would, but I can't miss it.
College parties start late.
l'll get you back in time.
I'm supposed to be Ashley Olsen, man.
Ashley Olsen?
Yeah. You know how long it takes
to straighten this hair?
Come on. You're my boy.
It's been a long day, man.
I need a good friend right now.
All right, I got your back.
Oh. Invitations, please.
- Invitations? I got one on my cellphone.
- No invite, no entry.
Can you guys push off, please?
- Just over there.
- My name's right there. It's Jeff Bernstein.
- Check...Mr Bernstein.
- You know what?
Thank you.
Hey, how are you doing?
There's got to be another way.
Let's go.
(Announcer) And now, the broken tango.
Take it away.
(Luke) Look, at this place, Moose. Come on.
(Moose) Where you going? Luke? Luke!
(♪ Jazmine Sullivan:
Bust Your Windows)
- Luke.
- I got you.
Come with me.
(Phone rings)
(Chatter)
Hey, Camille, we're all ready for the party.
You coming?
l'm gonna meet you guys there.
Moose'll be here like any minute.
Giddy up, girl! Yee-ha!
I got something for you.
I hope you like it.
Your film?
- You did it?
- Yeah.
Luke.
I'm so happy you finished it.
Let's get out of here.
- No one can see us. We're fine.
- No, l mean let's leave.
We could go anywhere. California, even.
Come on, you can go to film school.
We can start fresh.
(He sighs)
Luke. I'm so glad you made it.
You know, l was a little concerned
that you wouldn't get the invitation in time.
- What are you doing here?
- Julien, you invited him?
What? I just wanted to invite him
to come celebrate the birthday
of my amazing and lovely sister.
He's... He's joking, right?
Wow.
- I'm so sorry.
- Sorry?
- This was all a lie, wasn't it?
- Yes, it was.
- Shut up, Julien.
- Why? It was.
Listen, at first it was,
and then I got to know you, OK?
And I...
I started to fall for you.
And that was real,
that's why I had to leave.
I'm... I'm so sorry.
- Please tell me you believe me.
- Don't touch me.
Luke, you...
- You don't need to deal with...
- Don't, Julien!
Don't worry about him. He's a loser.
Natalie, are you really
getting mad about that?
Camille.
- Camille, I thought that you...
- I'm over it.
You clearly have better things to do.
- No, Camille, it's not like that.
- (Sighs)
- Come on, I got caught up.
- Great. Thanks.
I... I've been dancing.
Before school, during school and after.
So you've been lying to me
and ditching me for some secret life?
I mean, you could have at least told me.
But I guess I'm not important enough
in your new cool life to know.
I should have just told you. I know.
But I'm sorry, OK?
And it's all over now.
You're right. It's over now.
- Luke. Luke, Luke.
- What the hell?
- Hey, man, this is bullshit.
- (Jason) We tried to stop them,
but there was nothing we could do.
(Luke) We gotta get in there!
They can't do this to us!
Luke! Hey.
I grabbed as much as I could.
It's Julien.
- Julien's trying to buy the house.
- So what are we going to do now?
Can't you see? We're finished.
But the World Jam is just around the corner.
- But if we have nowhere to rehearse...
- We have nowhere to sleep.
We're fooling ourselves,
thinking this place was going to last.
I'm out.
Anyone else?
Hey, it's not your fault.
Julien started this.
You guys deserve better than this.
There's nothing more I can do.
l screwed up.
The Pirates are done.
We tried.
(♪ Jessie J Cornish: Who You Are)
Hi.
So, on a scale of one to ten...
how much do you hate me?
I don't hate you, Moose.
I miss you.
And what's worse,
feeling like you don't miss me at all.
I don't even matter to you any more.
We spent all senior year
talking about NYU,
the real world, facing it together.
What changed?
You're my best friend
in the whole wide world, Camille.
And I never want to let that go.
My mom just sent this in the mail.
(Laughs)
Oh, wow.
That's priceless.
Cam...
I'm sorry.
I missed dancing,
but...
I'm going to have to say
l miss you more.
Really?
Really, really.
(Faint music)
- You hear that?
- What?
- Do you hear that right now?
- Come here.
- What?
What?
Are you serious? No, back of the line.
Just one second, little girl. One moment.
- l'm sorry.
- Hey, can you turn that song up a bit?
Do I look like a jukebox to you, pal?
Um...
How about five bucks?
- Give me that. I'll be right back.
- OK.
(Music gets louder)
(They laugh)
- Oh, my gosh.
- MSA freshmen year. We met...
(Both) To this song!
- This is ridiculous.
- (Moose) Remember the choreography?
- Step forward... Come on, let's try it.
- No, not a chance.
Dance with him! Please!
- Go.
- You heard the kid. Come on.
All right.
(♪ I Won't Dance)
Moose, stop! Oh, my gosh!
OK, not in public.
I'm sorry.
I'm not doing this.
Whoa! (Laughs)
Moose!
Hey!
Give me my hat back!
Whoo!
What are you doing? Get out of here!
Oh, man, you know what?
I'm gonna squirt you.
I'm gonna squirt you! Get out of here!
- Get outta here!
- Hey!
I'm sorry.
Come on! Come on! Get outta here.
- Come on, gimme your scooter, kid.
- Hey, that's my scooter!
You dented it, you freak!
(She laughs, he cheers)
Oh, my gosh,
you have leaves all over you.
Oh, wow.
(They sigh)
You can never give it up.
You were born to dance.
Give it up. You suck!
Really?
- Don't listen to them.
- (Laughs)
- l know, but you gave it up.
- Yeah, cos I'm not like you.
l'm a good dancer,
but, Moose, you're a great dancer.
- My parents gave up everything...
- So you wouldn't have to. I know, I know.
We can figure this out.
Together.
OK.
(Makes explosive sound)
- OK.
- Come on. Like my new hat?
Hey, Vince,
I need a coffee on table eight.
Everything all right?
What do I have to do to get a menu here?
- What are you doing here?
- I have two things to say to you.
I'll have an egg salad sandwich,
and I still think we can win the World Jam
and get the house back.
I'm out of egg salad sandwiches
and you're out of your mind.
- l thought that's why you liked me.
- You're crazy. We have nobody left.
But I'm here. Means we got one back.
Luke, you're the only one that can get
everybody back together to save your house.
- The Pirates just need your leadership.
- They don't need me.
I took what my parents gave me
and threw it away.
You don't know what you've done.
Luke, you gave these people a place
where they can live out their dreams.
- Sit down, man.
- Dude, I got tables to work.
No, no, no, just take a seat.
- This better be quick.
- You never asked why I wanted to dance.
You want to know why?
l dance
because dance can change things.
One move can set
a whole generation free, like Elvis.
Uh-huh.
One move can make you believe there's
something more. Remember this one?
Ow!
Moose, sit down before
you make a fool out of both of us.
And some moves...
can give a skinny, curly-haired kid...
that just wants to dance...
some...some hope.
Hope that he's actually special.
Excuse me! Excuse me! Hello? Coffee?
Decaf, don't want it. Regular.
I'm sorry, I can't. I can't do regular.
I tried. It's just not me.
- I've been waiting here for 30 minutes.
- Hey, he can't do regular, the man said.
Great, Fred Astaire. l didn't pay
for a floorshow. I paid for some coffee.
OK, that's cool, Moose, but how are we
going to get everyone together?
I had to get everybody here somehow.
Man, did I miss you guys!
My mornings are way too quiet
without you guys yapping.
- You see? I told you he would miss us.
- Yeah, OK, OK, you're right.
Look, I know the odds are against us.
We have no house, no routine.
Hell, l don't even know
how we're going to do this.
But I believe in us, and I know you do too.
That's what I'm talking about.
We've come way too far to stop now.
l know we can win this.
(All sing) We be the Pirates!
We be the Pirates!
We still don't have a place to rehearse.
Don't worry about it.
Moose said he found us a place.
Moose!
- Kido!
- Doggone! There you are!
(Both make explosive sound)
- What's up?
- I miss you.
I miss you. Come here, give me a hug.
Guys, hey, this is Kido.
We used to dance together in high school.
Am I missing something? What do these
games have to do with the World Jam?
You said you needed space, right?
l got you, brother.
- Brother?
- Come on.
Nice to meet you.
Come on. This way, watch your step.
You're gonna like this place.
Just come.
Da-da!
See, I told you.
Whoo-hoo! OK, I like it, man.
(Tick 1 ) I used to love this game
when I was little.
Who do they belong to?
Oh, me. I watch them after school
because their parents work here.
(Tick 1 ) l don't know.
Do you think this is gonna work?
And there's so much junk. There's no room,
and we barely have any dancers.
Yeah, and the Samurai,
they outnumber us two to one.
- (Buzzer)
- He has a point.
(Buzzer continues)
Hold that thought.
Come on.
(♪ J. Cole: Who Dat)
Oh, my God! MSA Crew!
Long time, no see!
Kido! You ruined our slow-motion thing!
Guys, I thought you might need
some extra dancers.
Pirates, meet the MSA Crew.
Hey, let's show them what we got.
(Moose) A highly good idea, Kido.
All right, so first up we got,
we got a floor master, Monster.
(Jason) Yeah, that's tight.
(Pirates) Whoo!
We got Cable, the man with no bones.
Whoo!
Fly, Fly can groove and shake.
(Wolf-whistling)
The popping tapper, Hair.
(Cheering, applause)
Last but not least, Smiles,
ladies and gentlemen.
All right, guys, I think this is gonna work.
Work? We gonna kick some ass!
(♪ Flo Rida: Club Can't Handle Me)
(Dancers) Whoo!
Will we win the World Jam?
You may have...
Hey.
Hey, yo! Zoltan!
Hey, machine!
Yo, give me my money back, man.
Hey, guys, check this out.
This is for the World Jam.
Imagine these lights on this shirt.
Oh! Oh!
Oh God! Oh God!
(Screams)
(Coughing)
That didn't work.
(Video game) Game over.
- I like your dance moves.
- I like your accent.
You like my accent? That's good.
I like yours.
I don't have a accent.
(Snoring)
(Phone ringing)
(Luke) Carlos. I knew you'd come back.
- We need you, man.
- You need me, huh?
- Yeah.
- Well, check this out.
I got a message from Julien.
- I've been training with the Samurais, right?
- What?
- They want to offer you a deal.
- Is this a joke?
If you want the house back,
you can have it back, free and clear.
- What's the catch?
- Throw the battle.
- (Laughs) Throw the battle?
- Yeah.
Can't you see? I'm trying to give you all
a chance to have what you want.
- How could you do this?
- This is real life, Luke.
When you gonna wake your ass up
and see that?
It's time to grow up.
The Samurai will win at any cost.
You need to leave now.
Think about it. The offer stands.
Or you can take your chances
at the battle. (Laughs)
What's up, everybody?
My name is Grandmaster Caz,
and l'd like to welcome you
to the biggest dance battle on Planet Earth.
Ladies and gentlemen,
this is the World Jam!
(Cheering, screaming)
Let's go!
(♪ Dance music)
(Cheering)
(Caz) Coming up next, our main event,
the World Jam Championship Matchup.
The House of Pirates
versus the House of Samurai.
And this battle
is the battle you won't forget.
Stick around.
(Cheering)
Don't worry about those guys, we got this.
- Yeah, baby!
- (Cheering)
Yes! Are you all excited?
Luke.
I'm so sorry.
Look, I know I lied to you.
But everything we had was real.
I'm leaving tomorrow.
I'm taking a train to California.
And I wouldn't have the courage to do that
without you.
I know you have dreams, too.
This is crazy...
but come with me.
What makes you think
I would trust you again?
Because that person
that I was only with you...
(Sighs)
..that's who I really am.
(Caz) Right about now,
Pirates to the stage!
- Let's hear it for the Pirates, y'all.
- (Cheering)
Luke!
Good luck today.
(Caz) Here they come.
Here they come. Here come the Pirates.
They look determined, they look ready.
But is it enough
to upset the mighty Samurai?
Only time will tell.
Samurai, to the stage!
And here they come,
in the black and gold, the Samurai!
Looks like they mean serious business.
Let's go!
(♪ Dance music)
(Cheering)
(Caz) Pirates, come on.
First round, there it is.
(Cheering)
(Caz) Here come the Samurai.
Let's see what they're working with, people.
(♪ Get Cool featuring Petey Pablo:
Let Me C lt)
(Cheering)
(Caz) Uh-oh. This looks personal.
(♪ Timbaland: Ease Off The Liquor)
(Cheering)
(♪ The Roots: Here I Come)
(Caz) Walk. I'm feeling that.
That's old school. That's old school.
(Cheering)
(Caz) Oh, my God,
it's a freak show out there, people.
(♪ Outkast: Ghetto Musick)
(♪ Rye Rye: Bang)
(Cheering)
(Caz) Look, Ma! No hands!
This is a massacre, people.
(Cheering)
(Caz) Samurai's wiping up the floor
with these guys.
lt looks like it's over.
It looks like it's over, people.
- Hey, we can take 'em.
- You said so yourself, we're not ready.
You can trust me.
(Caz) It looks like it's over. There's no way
the Pirates can come back from this.
What's this?
The Pirates are answering back.
- Get off the stage.
- Get off me!
- Stop it!
- What are you doing?
- You can't do this. You're Samurai.
- Not any more.
- What happened to family?
- This is my family, Julien.
Get off me.
(Caz) Let's get back to business, people.
(♪ Ericka June: Work The Middle)
Yeah. That's what I'm talking about.
Yeah!
(Cheering)
(Caz) Oh, no! Here she comes!
Go, go, go!
Perfect landing, baby.
I give that a ten. I give that a ten.
(Cheering)
(Luke) All right, y'all, let's go.
(Caz) What are they doing?
What are they trying now? It ain't over yet.
(♪ Fly Stylz: Crush The Floor)
Whoa! Oh!
Are you kidding me?
(Cheering)
(Caz) You can't get those shoes
at Foot Locker, people.
It's getting tribal in here.
(♪ DJ Laz & Flo Rida:
Move Shake Drop)
(Cheering)
(Caz) Now, here's the Pirate shorties!
Oh, my!
(Cheering)
(♪ David Rush: Shooting Star
[Party Rock mix])
(Caz) Boom! In your face!
(Cheering)
(Caz) That's it, that's it. It's a wrap.
And both of our finalists did their thing.
But now it's time for our judges to decide
who's going home
with this hundred thousand dollars.
Judges, are you ready with your decision?
Whose flag you gonna raise?
Black and gold for the Samurai,
or red and black for the Pirates?
- Pirates! There it is!
- (Cheering)
The House... Oh, my God!
The House of Pirates
are the winners
of the first annual World Jam!
It's over. One hundred thousand dollars
to the House of Pirates!
(Indistinct)
Dear Luke, your film was so great,
I had to share it.
l hope you give yourself the chance
to live your dream.
Love, NataIie.
You can go to her if you want to.
I will take care of everything
until you get back.
You gave us the chance to live our dreams,
and now it is time for you to go
and live your dreams.
(Caz) There it is! There it is!
The winners of the first annual World Jam
is the House of Pirates!
(Moose) You know,
some famous guy once said,
"To traveI is better than to arrive."
And I was Iike, "What?"
Because l used to think that there is only
one path to take to where you want
to get to be in life.
But if you choose that one path,
that doesn't mean you have to
abandon aII the other ones.
l realise that it's actually what happens
along the way that counts.
The stumbIes
and the faIIs
and the friendships.
lt's the journey, not the destination.
You just gotta, l guess,
trust that the future wiII work itseIf out
Iike it's supposed to.
I mean, I guess I'm asking the school
to kinda go freestyle with me here,
but I'm ready to jump.
What you're asking for here
is a double major in engineering...
and dance.
Yeah.
Well, it's certainly a first.
So?
Yeah, l mean, l...
I'm a double major, so...
No way, Moose! Oh, my gosh!
Oh, my gosh! I can't believe it.
I can't believe it.
What do you mean, you can't believe it?
Cam, thank you,
thank you for being there.
You're welcome.
(Man over PA)
May l have your attention, please?
Westbound train 745 to Los Angeles,
final destination Los Angeles,
will be departing in 1 5 minutes
from track eight.
What happened? Did you forget something?
- I think you forgot to say goodbye.
- Yeah.
Don't leave me, don't leave me, please!
Senorita, please.
Come to Buenos Aires...
- Don't listen to him.
- No, listen. I kissed your hand, remember?
I'm going to miss you guys.
Give me a hug, give me a hug.
Come on, don't cry. Don't cry.
Where's Luke?
(♪ Scott Mallone:
What We Are Made Of)
(Pirates squealing)
He goin' hard!
- (Laughs)
- All right, all right.
Crazy. Don't listen to them, OK?
(Pirates) Oh.
Whoa!
Oh! What?
Can I kiss somebody right now?
Hang on a second, OK? I'll be right back.
This is for you, man.
I'll see you soon. Blow it up.
(Makes explosive sound)
You're B-FAB. Remember that.
Take care of the house, guys.
Open it.
(Pirates) Ooh.
- You ready?
- Yeah.
- Let's go party, people.
Whoo!
(♪ Get Cool: Shawty Get Moves)