Hey, Ron, is it okay if l
take off a little early today?
l'm having dinner with my folks,
and they're way out in the suburbs, so--
No way. Everybody gonna stay late,
do inventory tonight.
Nobody leaves early.
Are you kidding me?
-But that's your job.
-Yeah, but l gotta leave early.
l got a hot date.
With big phony jugs, the kind l like.
That jerk. He's always doing this to us.
Clearly this calls for drastic action.
Okay, everybody, work's over.
- And nobody saw anything, right?
- Right!
That was great.
You're the Spartacus of us wage slaves.
Thanks. l always thought
of myself more as Popeye...
...but Spartacus is good too.
Though it's not really fair...
...to compare them because
they lived in different times and--
Would you like to go out
on a date with me?
Yeah. Sure. Yeah, l'd love to.
How about Saturday?
My roommates and l are having a party.
Would you like to come as my date
instead of as my coworker?
So when you put the moves on me
it won't be sexual harassment?
-Exactly.
-lt's a date.
Hey, look out.
- Hey, wanna buy an air conditioner?
- No, thanks.
Sit still, please.
-Calm down.
-Hey, Natalie.
-You want some help with those?
-Thanks, yeah.
Carlos and l have just been exhausted
lately with the baby's schedule...
-...and the noise in this building.
-l know.
l could barely get to sleep with
the sound of Gus and Wally fighting.
What are you looking at? We made up.
Sorry about all the brouhaha last night.
You been in a relationship this long,
you're bound to have a few beefs.
We'd have a few less beefs if someone
would learn to pick up after himself.
l said l would use the hamper. Enough!
Posey? Jim? Anybody home?
Jim!
-Hello?
-Down here.
Oh, hey. What's going on?
Wanna drive me to my parents' house?
They're moving, l have to pick up the dog.
Right, your dog.
Hey, does he still get drunk
like when we were in high school?
Are you kidding? Dad had to spray
the liquor cabinet with dog repellent.
l'll get the keys.
What happened to the couch?
We moved it over there last week,
remember?
Oh, yeah.
So the family's moving?
-Your little brother too?
-Kevin? Oh, yes.
He'll be 1 000 miles away.
Did you know he had a T-shirt
made with his SAT scores on it?
-How did he do?
-l don't know.
l don't care. l didn't look.
Much better than me.
Well, l'm pretty excited
about this transfer.
Wyoming may seem civilized
these days...
...but when it comes to direct mail marketing,
it's still the Wild West.
Awesome.
What about Kevin? lsn't he eating?
He's busy packing. He'll be--
Stogie, down.
You wanna go back in the basement?
Jeez, Mom! His brains are
damaged enough as it is!
Come here, boy. lt's okay.
We're gonna have so much fun
in the city together.
No more mean Mom and Dad.
l'm gonna take care of you
all by myself.
You know, it's funny
that you mention that because....
-Well, would you be willing to--?
-Did you tell him yet?
Hi, Andy. So, guys,
are we going to be roommates?
-What?!
-Kevin, honey...
...please go wait in the other room.
Here's some fig bars.
Wait a minute.
You want Kevin to come live with me?
lt'll just be till he graduates
and goes off to college.
You see, he wasn't thrilled
about moving to Wyoming, and--
Were you ever planning
on consulting me about this?
l have better things to do than
take care of my stupid kid brother.
A 1 460 combined SAT is not stupid.
A dog who eats mothballs,
that's stupid.
A dog, l might add, who you're rolling
out the freaking red carpet for!
But your own brother, who loves you...
...he gets a knife in the back
from Andy French!
Look, Kevin and l
have never gotten along, and--
Honey, we're taking the piano.
You don't need to practice anymore.
Why would he even want to do this?
- lt was his idea.
- He thinks you're cool.
What? No, he doesn't.
Oh, sure. He's always talking
about his cool big brother...
...who moved to the city
to be a cartoonist.
But l'm not a cartoonist yet,
l just sell waterbeds.
Does he really think l'm cool?
Yes, and you are cool.
You are my big cool baby cupcake.
-Do l even have a choice?
-No, not really.
Kevin, come in here. Andy would love
to have you come live with him.
Son, we're very proud of you
for being so mature about--
Crap! You did that on purpose,
you little creep.
Well, your big feet were in the way.
Mom, he said ''crap.''
You broke my feet
and you're not even sorry.
You're losing your mind.
l'm getting away from you.
Come here.
Boys! Boys!
Stop hitting yourself.
Why you hitting yourself?
Get off me!
Stop drooling on me.
Oh, they'll be fine.
What time do the movers get here?
So this is Mission Hill.
Don't get excited.
lt doesn't have anything you would like.
Well, it looks very colorful.
l think it's important to embrace
as many ideas and cultures as one can.
-Mom, Dad, and l went to see Il Postino--
-Shut up.
- You are so lame. Shut up.
-Maybe you should shut up.
No, you. l'm not the one who's--
All right, you two.
l'm gonna pull this car over right now.
What? Don't let me stop your arguing.
Oh, my-- Away you go.
That wolf is attacking my plant.
Go on back to the woods now.
Posey, that's not a wolf.
That's my dog, Stogie.
And this is my brother, Kevin.
They're both coming to live here.
Oh, a female roommate.
l've never lived with a girl before.
But l assure you
l am a perfect gentleman.
Yes. l can tell by your inner light
that you're a good person.
But Stogie, there are dark forces
at work within him.
My new school.
l smell fresh opportunities.
Excuse me?
Could you tell me where Room 41 0 is?
l think it's in my pants, man.
Why don't you take a look?
l'm pretty sure it's not there.
The ''four'' indicates
it's on the fourth floor and--
You're wack, man.
Okay. Have a good time
at the ski tournament.
Excuse me, were you asking
about Room 41 0?
Because l'm on my way to 41 0.
Oh, thanks. l'm Kevin.
This is my first day.
l'm picking up something
with my ''Obviometer,'' captain:
No duh!
l like that one.
Kevin, this is George.
George has a girlfriend in Singapore.
Singapore. At my old school l told people
l had a girlfriend in Canada...
...because it's so far away
no one could ever check.
ls your Singapore girlfriend
the same thing?
lt's a more believable ethnic variation.
Stop bragging about your girlfriends!
All right, people, settle down.
We have a new transfer student
joining us today.
Kevin, why don't you tell us
a little bit about yourself?
Hello, everybody.
My name is Kevin French.
l moved here from Briarhurst
or as you probably know it, Exit 1 8.
l live with my brother Andy,
who is a cartoonist here in Mission Hill.
Some of my interests are miniature golf...
...Robert Heinlein novels
and collecting novelty neckties.
l have an extra Dilbert tie
if any of you would like to trade.
Okay.
Since you all paid such close attention
to that presentation...
...l'm sure you won't mind
taking a quiz on it!
Take out a piece of paper.
Question one:
What is the new student's name?
Kicking back, eh? May l join you?
Sure. Have a seat.
-Did l just see you drinking?
-Yeah.
-So? l can drink. l'm 24.
-l don't think you should drink...
-...if you can't drink responsibly.
-What?!
You've had too many.
You're getting abusive.
-Will you get lost, douche bag!
-You're the one who's acting douche bag.
You are wack.
You don't know what either
of those words means, do you?
You are so lame. Go away.
You've lost this fight.
No, l haven't.
-Mom and Dad would like to speak to you.
-Honey? Is everything all right?
Well, no. No, not really.
l don't think l can take much more of this.
Kevin is driving me nuts.
Oh, he just needs some time to adjust.
Yes, I imagine your neighborhood
is a bit different than what he's used to.
New condoms? What's wrong
with our regular brand of condoms?
Nothing, but these were on special,
that's all.
You cheap gay bastard.
These things are gonna fly right off!
l'm just glad we snuck out
without running into--
Well, hello.
Where are you guys going?
-Nowhere.
-We're going over to Backwash...
...to see Silly Rabbit.
They're a ska band.
l don't think l've heard ska before.
-Do the Beatles do any ska?
-No. And neither does Scott Joplin...
...or Gordon Lightfoot
or any of your other ''faves.''
Well, if you like it,
l'm sure it's interesting.
-May l come along?
-Sure.
No one under 21 is allowed.
l'd better go home.
Don't worry about that. Everything
will be fine if you just stay cool.
Okay.
l shouldn't be in here. l feel guilty.
l'm in here under false pretenses.
Sit still and stop attracting attention.
But what if they ask for my lD?
l could get arrested.
l'll never get into a good college.
-All because l wanted to hear ska!
-Crap! Now the bouncer's coming over.
Be cool, or you're gonna
get us all kicked out.
Good evening, gentlemen.
l see some lD there, sir?
How flattering you should ask.
Ever since l shaved my beard,
everyone has been--
Sir, if you're not 21 ...
-...l'm gonna have to ask you--
-lt's happening! Please don't arrest me!
l wanna go to Yale or Amherst!
Don't call my mother. l didn't know!
He made me do it!
Well, congratulations, you little dork.
You've ruined my life
in less than a week.
-l didn't--
-Shut up! l did you a big favor...
...by letting you move in with me.
You should be down on your knees,
kissing my ass!
Oops, l'm sorry, l said ''ass.''
Please tattle on me.
Please give me a preachy speech.
Won't you show me the way,
Reverend Goody McFreaking-Gumdrops?
-Mom and Dad said--
-Mom and Dad aren't here.
They're 1 000 miles away.
Why don't you take advantage of that?
Stop ruining my fun and have
some for yourself, for God's sake.
You're right.
That's the first time you've ever said
l was right.
That's the first time you've
ever been right about anything.
But seriously, it's time l start
taking advantage of all this freedom...
...do things l could never do
with Mom and Dad around.
That's the spirit!
Good. Now let's get home
so l can start masturbating.
Kevin, is everything okay?
Are you sick or something?
No. l stayed up until 4:30 last night.
-Mast--?
-No. Just researching how to be cool.
The lnternet's not as helpful
as you'd think.
Kevin! Oh, my goodness.
-What's happened to your inner light?
-What? ls it stained or something?
Well, no-- Well, no, but it's become
dim and venal and wicked.
Like Andy's.
Way to go, Kev. You burned out
your inner light in one evening.
lmagine what we can
accomplish this weekend.
l'm really looking forward
to your party tomorrow.
Oh, me too. We deserve a break
from this frenzied go-go...
...corporate rat race.
Ron's Waterbed World.
Yes, this is Andy French.
Hey, idiot, no personal calls.
Kevin? Yes, he's my brother.
No way! Are you sure?
Yes. Okay.
l'll be right down.
Mr. French, l've called you here
because Kevin was caught sleeping...
...during his fourth period
AP Chemistry class.
When awakened, he flew into a rage
and called the teacher a--
A graphic expletive.
-A what?
-A foul term. This.
This is what he called his teacher.
Sir! l don't know how you did
things in the suburbs...
...but we don't use those words
here in the inner city.
l'm-- l'm sorry. l've just--
-l've never seen it written so neatly.
-Oh, my.
Perhaps l should just call
your parents in Wyoming...
...and discuss discipline with them.
-No! That won't be necessary!
-Crap, no.
Please, l'll punish him. l promise.
l'm gonna give you some serious
discipline... young man.
See that you do. Kevin is suspended
for the rest of today.
l'm glad you got suspended. l could never
carry all this booze home myself.
Will you buy this for me?
l want to have some beer at the party.
Now you're drinking? You're serious
about this new attitude, huh?
-Yes.
-Excellent. l was afraid you'd wuss out.
But drinking shows a real commitment
to becoming a cooler person.
-So will you buy me this?
-Sure, but that's olive oil.
That's maple syrup. That's shampoo.
Look, if you want a good first beer,
try Gruberhof.
That's what l started with.
Hey, guys.
Welcome to party central.
You dudes want a beer?
-No, thanks. Drinking is for waste-oids.
-We don't need liquor to have fun.
Not when we have the
Babylon 5 Collectible Card Game.
-Hey, great apartment.
-Thanks.
There's a rumor that Sid Vicious
once threw up in the bathtub.
-Bitchen!
-Hello.
Oh, hi, you must be Kevin.
How do you like Mission Hill so far?
lt's far out. l--
Oh, l-- Excuse me. l'll be right back.
Hey, man. Lay off the Gruberhof.
-That's my private reserve.
-Who the hell are you?
l'm the Grubermeister.
And that's all you need to know.
Now get out of here
before l kick your ass.
That's right.
Those are some of my cartoons.
And those are some designs for an
animated TV series l was thinking about.
Oh, God. Not another animated series.
l know. lt's like everyone
and their brother has one now.
-Hey.
-Yeah.
And l know you're gay, okay?
But, like, l don't even have a problem with it.
-All right already.
-Because history is full of great homos.
Oscar Wilde was a homo.
Alexander the Great was a homo.
And you know who else is great?
-You, you big homo.
-That is a hurtful term.
Please stop using it,
or l will be forced to clobber you.
Bite me.
All right!
Everybody ska!
Hey...
...who wants to get it on
with the Grubermeister, huh?
You do.
-That sounds like Kevin.
-l'm sure he's asleep by now. Come on.
That is Kevin.
Well, he's probably a little drunk.
Forget about it.
l'd feel better if l could just check.
Well, l do not feel better.
You will in a second. l promise.
l'm sorry.
He's my brother.
What's he saying?
He's saying he's the Grubermeister.
Do any of you have a problem with that?
-No, sir.
-Not at all.
Good. Now l think
it's time for you to leave.
See you later.
Hey, Andy.
This apartment sure spins a lot.
Yeah.
lt tends to do that after a good party.
l'm sorry for being so pathetic.
Hey, cheer up. lt's not everybody
who can outdo Sid Vicious.
-Here you go. ls everything okay?
-Yeah.
-He just got a little carried away is all.
-lt runs in the family.
Every time somebody put down a cup,
your dog ran up and drank it.
Well, l better get going.
See you tomorrow.
Well, l guess my experiment
in being cool has failed.
-Miserably.
-So you're gonna call it quits?
lt's too hard being like you.
l don't know if l can do it.
Maybe you'd be happier
just being the old Kevin?
Well, it's certainly the easy choice.
ls the douche-bag aspect
going to be a problem?
l can learn to live with it.
Thanks. And let's just try
to forget about last night.
Oh, God. At least Mom and Dad
will never find out.
Sunday, 3:30 a.m.
Yo, dudes! It's Kevin.
Hey, could you send me
my birth certificate?
Because I wanna change my name
to the Grubermeister!
I love being drunk.
I wanna stay drunk forever.
Subtitles by
BloodLogic
[ENGLlSH]