Subtitled by:
Dejavu, Gonnie and Martien
Are you ready?
It does not be long now.
You two go that way.
Do you care?
You and I go inside.
Let's go.
Are you afraid to really
to be free?
What did you do to her
done, asshole?
Can you hear it?
Whatever I wanted.
That was the point, right?
You, Devil!
Yes, that's it, guys.
Let's nice to party,
bitches.
We are really close to the beach.
This is really nice.
Open up.
We are there.
Welcome, my dear Kat,
your bachelor paradise,
Mexico style.
I can not believe you
have done all this for me.
Thank Sophia. All this would not
have been possible without her.
That is not true.
Amber had found the house and Beth ...
Stop it. You're my
all the best friend in the world
and we know it all.
- Okay, enough.
Okay, can we stop for time?
Let's go.
Light packed as usual?
- Hey, be nice to me. This is my week.
Hi handsome.
I thought you were the decorations of
would take them home.
Margareta everyone?
Do mine but twice.
Or a triple.
Okay, calm
there, vodka.
The sugar in those things you will
a magnificent hangover.
And let me not start on
the empty calories.
I will do mine well.
Insert the penis in a
Mexican guest?
Nice.
Can we play now?
I call that my parents
well we arrived.
Come on, Beth. You can have a night
without calling your parents.
Take something to drink
and that dick to puncture
that wall.
I want you all to promise
I like my phone to try to put
that you tear it from my hand and
throw him into the sea.
Okay, enough talk. Can
we wrote our first bar inside?
Not until we have pulled.
I am the bride.
You do understand that I
course will never attract, right?
Come on, Jess. We do
it all. It's fun.
Prima, never after this
weekend, okay?
Wait.
You must not forget.
Good Lord.
You fuck with someone, or
you like it or not.
Come on.
- Give me only.
My penises are broken.
Ladies, let's do this!
Trying to keep girls.
I keep drinking until sunrise.
She has lost 8 pounds
since they went out together.
And then she just
went to drink.
Have you tried to
to talk to her?
Maybe, I do not know. If I did it
she immediately changed the subject,
and she became very defensive.
Is this not beautiful?
Let me see.
No.
Here.
The pub is right here.
Stop for time.
I just want to have something
for the trip to remember ...
something I'm not in New York
can get.
You can exact same bracelet
get on Canal Street.
Since when are you in
Canal Street was?
Like it? For you, $ 10.
Thank you.
Do you take American Express?
Yes.
You seem like a very nice girl.
Very clever.
I will read your palm?
I will predict the future.
I believe they hand you
reading.
You have a very strong
love line.
You're very passionate, right?
Men like very
very yours.
You meet a rapidly ...
Let's go.
- What did she say?
I see a dark road
front of you.
Listen not to, or
death will devour you.
Yes, that was a bit scary.
Come on.
Who cares what she says?
We waste valuable
drinking time.
Let's go.
"Without a word,
looking for a man who buys you a drink. "
Oh, that is for me.
Are they a men
version of this game?
I can not even keep the version.
You're doing well.
Great.
Here we go.
She is fantastic.
You're the bomb.
Well, please encourage her
not.
Did she just say out
sucked his pants?
Got something to what
more challenge?
Yeah, try not
such a huge plague to men.
Whatever. Maybe you should
just try it.
Guys, I think that
boys there to watch us.
I think it here
to come.
Good evening ladies.
I'm Jeremy ...
Jeremy Spencer,
and man with two first names.
This here is my best friend
of the whole wide
weird world ... Rob Aimsley.
May we join you?
Please tell me
that you're not Kathleen.
No, I'm Beth.
I'm Kathleen.
- Nice, baby.
Hi, I'm Jessica.
Hi.
So, where do you
all come from?
New York, Boston,
Providence.
World. We are
from Texas.
I have been in Dallas for a
real estate convention last fall ...
a lot of cowboy hats.
Really?
That's cool.
We come from Audtion, so there
not really much cowboys.
But we can cowboys
if you wish.
If you are not cowboys,
what do you do?
We work in television.
Rob is now a producer.
He was the big boss man.
Not really the boss.
Come to size,
not so modest.
So what brings you
two of you here?
We are celebrating. Rob,
has also just had a big promotion.
Congratulations. Then
you pay us all drinks.
Perfect.
Ok.
So, what would it cost for a
kiss from you get?
Listen, I think you really
very nice,
I'm just ...
so you know,
I'm not going to bed.
You take no leaf
for your mouth, do you?
Can I?
It's just that I,
just,
Never would.
It's okay.
Are you with someone, or play
just hard to get?
It is simply not
happen.
What about this? What happens here?
What are we doing?
The thing is that I
go dancing with my girlfriends.
And if you are looking for someone
to go to bed,
then I drunk girl
for which there is
and her band is top.
Hi.
How about
this dope?
I do not know why,
but I think I like him.
If we thought that al
I did not know better,
I think you really considered
him with you to take home.
Oh no, not our
Betty-Wetty.
Part of me
do want.
What?
Go away.
Are you serious? Frost in the
hell or something?
Just boys.
View only boys.
Stop.
Come on,
let's go dancing.
So how is it to work
on television?
Well, you know, it's ...
I'm not ...
... real TV show producer?
Yes. I'm sorry, really.
Jeremy has convinced me that
it would be a good idea ...
... to help you with
the girls to decorate.
I need all the help
I can get.
What do you really?
Tenth-grade
English teacher.
Really?
You know,
I was greatly in love
on my tenth class
English teacher.
Look.
Look what I got.
Where did you get?
- I guess from him.
You're smart.
He is smart.
Sorry.
What about those
love?
You know, it happened
on a trip to the beach
I am sure we
find a beach somewhere.
Really?
Will you walk a bit?
Yes.
Give me a moment.
Hey you. There, please.
Hey, how you doing
with the boss-man?
So far good.
Sophia and the boss-man
sitting in a tree,
N-E-U-K-E-N.
My god, you would be so
brains need fucking him.
Because what happened in Mexico,
remain in Mexico, right?
So you do not mind
if I go with him?
Go!
One of us would turn
should be tonight.
Are you sure?
This is your week.
Go and do it.
Have fun.
See you in time
for breakfast.
Okay, bye guys.
- Bye.
That was cool.
How would you find
to teach me
somewhere with more privacy?
I believe that we have away.
Already?
I only had a few drinks.
We know that.
Come on, it is useless to
any fun at all to the first night.
Sorry dibs.
This dance is about.
Who says that?
- We're going home.
I think I
should leave now.
What the hell
your problem?
She goes next
week married, motherfucker.
I'm getting laid tonight,
So fuck you, bitch.
Damn.
That was cool.
- That was not fun.
I should have had done.
- That was hilarious.
Every time we go out,
is one of us into trouble.
And do you know anyone in
his balls.
It's fun.
It's like a tradition.
I wish we
one could go out once
and just a nice, quiet
night could have.
Because that would be only one
bachelor party are real cool.
Well, we now
Just go home, please?
Give me a dick to
to pierce that wall down.
Hello.
Finally.
- Took them this time?
Sorry, Beth.
it goes well with me.
Do you thank her for
the spoiling of my week?
She sounds very angry.
She has a hangover. Create
you worry about.
See you there in 15 minutes.
We are not in the house.
We have guides who met
there at the beach and we
go look around a bit.
Okay, I see you there.
Beth, you let me have
in the lurch? Let's go.
Sorry. We can
not wait.
You know how it is.
But we see you at the cottage
for dinner.
Promise. Have fun. And
Take care.
That we do.
Bye.
Thank you.
What is going on?
My friends, we dumped
before noon.
Would you like to have a
eat?
A morning quickie first.
Fast enough for you?
Maybe a little
too fast.
I now take a shower.
Great. I
There also one can use.
Hair of the dog?
No.
That is why you should never
drinking on an empty stomach.
This tour is
a little boring.
I do not believe this
the tour is.
I think this is just one
wretched-looking country.
Can you not simply return to us
bringing the beach or something?
Are there no nice
landscapes or something?
Yes, yes.
We will take you to
bring a nice place ...
... very nice ...
just like you, right?
I think he'll like it.
Fuck you.
- Fuck yourself.
Fuck yourself.
What is your problem?
I have no problem.
You're such a bitch.
Let's do it now, man.
I would not get too close.
You think we're far enough?
It is good. Let
do it now.
Thanks for the tacos. That
was a great restaurant.
I only wished
you'd let me pay.
Why?
Is this not technically
our first date?
I would say that
Bar was our first date.
Yesterday was our second
be.
That makes this ...
- Our third.
You know what
that means.
Your home, or
mine?
Mine is closer.
So I walk inside
and the guy is
Kathleen her bed
and he is naked
and tied.
And the best part is ...
he cries,
blubbering like a baby.
He said I
to mean.
So there you have it
just left?
That you never told me.
That is so funny.
Why are we stopping?
Since this is your stop, whore.
Get out of the van.
Get out!
Kathleen!
No. Let me go.
Take it!
Hi, Beth.
- Sophia, they have shot Kat!
I do not know where they are! |
What?
Where are you?
He drove laps with us.
There is a palm tree and ...
My heavens,
He is coming.
Beth?
Throw that damn phone down!
Oh, shit.
My girlfriend called me.
It sounds like they are in trouble Sat
- I think something has happened.
- Are they missing?
Yes, they are missing.
And said that a friend was shot.
Señorita, you should calm down a bit.
I can not help you if you do not get quiet.
Ok,
Sorry.
Well, how long are your friends already missing?
They were four hours ago
avoided, I think.
They have only four hours away?
Is this a joke?
No no, she said
they saw a building
and palm trees
and a bell or something.
- He hung up.
- What?
Police
Just hung up.
Damn Mexico.
All I want is a little help ..
Where is the U.S. embassy?
They will do something.
There is no embassy here.
You must
Mexico City call themselves.
But I think
that not much will help.
It was only a few hours.
Maybe they
have a joke with you.
A joke?
Why would they do that?
Maybe your back
address because you went out with me.
You said Kathleen
very angry.
Kathleen would never ...
Okay, maybe that would do Kathleen,
but Beth would never go.
Let's ask around.
Maybe someone saw
they do at the beach.
Ok.
Yes, I could take a few pictures to show.
How is your Spanish?
They will not fight.
Cord her mouth.
Who did you call hell,
little girl?
Does not stand, do you?
Give me your money and jewelry.
Phones too.
I have mine with me.
Check it.
No, no, please.
You're lucky you're so thin,
not worth further
are for rape.
Your ring. Give me your purse.
He wants you ring.
Just give it to him.
But it is my
engagement ring.
Grab it!
No, please do not.
Bye, bitches.
Watch out
for coyotes, huh?
Wait.
Stop the car!
You can not simply just leave us here!
What do we do now?
Come here and help me.
Keep the pressure on it,
okay?
My ring.
Priorities ...
you are fucking shot.
Those damn bastards ...
When I see them again,
I'll kill them.
Is it bad?
She was shot.
That is not good.
Am I dead?
No, you will not die.
What are you doing?
I make a bottleneck link.
We must stop the bleeding.
Ok.
It is good.
Til.
I'm dying or not then?
I'm dying.
Shut up. I told you,
You will not die.
Yell at me.
Do we know what road to the town?
I do not know.
I'm really confused.
- Sophia will call for help.
- And we wait then?
How should they know where we are?
There ...
I see a reflection
No, it is not.
What do you what it is?
I do not know the
looks like a building.
Perhaps there is someone who can help.
-Can you stand?
- No.
I'll help you.
I told Sophia about.
I told her that I've seen.
Quiet. You can.
Damn, man.
You know damn what time it is?
It is 6:30 P.M., Jeremy.
What?
Really?
Sorry.
Are you still drunk?
A small cat that's all.
I mean, I was a little
went crazy when you say, ...
Sophia.
Hi. Ok.
Hi again.
How's Beth?
We hope in us
can help with something.
Listen, I do not cross swords with you.
- So if we make it up ...
- You speak Spanish, right?
We need you to take the
city people talking ... City folk ...
because we think that her friends
abducts his
and we can not talk to him.
- Good night.
- No, please.
What is this place?
Perhaps a kind of army camp?
Who cares?
Let's go fuck in this heat.
We will see if anyone is home.
We can a little from the sun
and we at Kat's leg elevation.
Hello?
It looks abandoned.
I do not like what this place looks like.
Where should we go?
Let Kat to bring inside.
Here, here.
Put her down here.
Damn.
Keep your leg to high.
It appears to heal,
which is good.
Try not to move otherwise
the wound is open again, okay?
Try to be strong.
Can you do that?
Well.
Why does this happen to me?
What kind of church is this?
Weird.
It seems as if they hurt each other.
I just do not understand
Why anyone would want to live here
in limbo.
I've found some candles
and lanterns or something.
We can use them
to walk back to town.
We must stay here tonight.
What?
Why?
When the sun sets, we
can see the lights of the city, right?
We do not know where the city is.
Did not look out there?
We are in the medium
of nowhere.
Let us try.
I do not like.
All I want is to
place with a good bed
I feel safe.
Safe? This is the safest
place we could find.
We can not in the dark cat to wear.
That is too dangerous.
And I do not even agree what
direction I should go.
We do not further
what has come in the night ...
coyotes, snakes,
I do not know.
But I would not take that risk. You?
And what now?
Hold your leg up.
So what we look for stocks.
You do not leave me alone, do you?
I love your company.
Well. Beth and I will look
what we can find ...
Hopefully some
water, and blankets,
Stuff to camp here tonight.
Promise me only that you return.
Trust me.
We come back.
Come on.
These girls ...
Have you seen them?
Sorry, I have not seen them.
Okay, he has not seen them.
Can we get a drink?
Let it rest.
I am well with you.
Ask him if he knows something about
the building in the desert
with the palm trees.
Do you know of a place in the
desert
with palm trees and
a bell tower
No, I do not know.
Thank you, sir.
Dick.
That is strange.
Why did he so weird?
Everyone here is strange.
That is what "Mexico" means
in the Mexican ... "weird."
Can we get a drink?
Well.
Let the questions continue.
I said that somewhere in
the beach to the drinking,
that's what
we should be.
Thank God.
Cunt.
No.
No phone, no water.
We have found no food,
just empty rooms.
We should never stop.
What would we have done ...
Kathleen drag
bleeding from the desert
until they fall away?
And what then? Sitting in the dark
while death and wait
the coyotes would come?
Would you have preferred,
you aching, stiff
little bitch?!
Sorry.
I murder you!
Jess, what are you doing?
Sorry.
We are all stressed.
That is the ... I am ...
Return to Kathleen
and Amber.
Should not we be together?
I can take care of myself, but I know
not certain of Kathleen and Amber.
You should go back to a
eye to keep.
What are you doing?
There must be something here ...
water, first aid ...
whatever.
And tomorrow we can try
follow the sun
and to the west trying
to go to the coast to find.
But we have to find material
because we will not sustain
without equipment.
Be careful.
Not a very homey place, right?
Can it be
We clean it up.
I think candles are fun.
I saw this past sandstone Mon
The previous owner loved it ...
and I mean loved candlelight.
He had this individual candlesticks
in the hall and on the stairs.
It was really fun.
The people I sold it to
thought it was to die.
This place ...
I just do not understand
something which so far
can build
and then decorate
with such artifacts.
It just has no sense.
I mean, where they used
this place?
What think you, Kat?
Kathleen, is everything okay?
It would be much better to me,
if you still would be.
You know, I talk when I'm nervous.
The pond outside is fun,
although,
lined with trees.
There is at least one landscape.
Who first used this place
was certainly not a good decorator.
I can not imagine
that many people here have been ...
Jesus Christ.
No wonder Ryan deceived you,
you stupid girl.
What do you mean it?
I mean that men
not like
as their friend
but constantly talking
about nothing.
The only thing they want
is a beautiful sight,
a nice ass and a place
their dick to keep warm.
And the way you look,
that a man can not help it.
Why do you say this?
The guide did not even rape you.
Your boobs have shrunk to nothing.
Selfish cunt.
Think you can sit there but
and evaluate me
and treat everyone like shit?
I do not know why Sophia
always come to you.
I am not more
baby-sit your ass.
You can just sit here
and I bleed to death for something to give.
Where you going?
You can not leave me here.
I would say, "Eat me,"
but I know you do not,
'because you eat anything!
Fuck you.
Great bachelor party,
by the way.
You're a great friend.
I can not believe that
nobody has seen him.
nobody has seen them.
I have 20 drinks of your credit.
Can you give me more money?
I can use it for good ...
a whore, maybe.
Why are they so afraid when we
the bell to ask?
I do not know, but we
keep doing this?
Prefer to go inside
to party?
It is her.
Where you going?
You.
Darkness is now very strong
inside you.
What did she say?
I do not know.
Something about a shadow, I think.
Ask her what she said last night.
What have you told her last night?
I saw it in her hand.
There is a very bad place in
waiting for her and her friends
and, if they continue,
death will come.
What is it?
What did she say?
Something about you and your friends
die in a bad spot.
What? Which place?
The spot with the bell?
Which place?
With the palm trees?
Yes, yes. South of the border,
at the old resort.
An old resort
south of the city.
Resort?
What kind of resort?
Why does she think it scary?
Why is it ... why is it evil?
It was long ago,
but bad things happen here,
and what comes in,
will never get out.
Where are you?
Beth.
Amber.
Where are you?
I need you.
Jessica.
Rot Mexico.
We had to go to Vegas.
Stupid bitching.
Great.
This is my party.
It is mine.
Hello.
Are you there?
God, what happens to me?
"This community is formed
hoping to find a new world
with no rules,
no boundaries,
no social ...
and escape for those
their deepest desires
wanted to explore
a life that our
will allow all
to live a life without fear ...
opinion and fear of ridicule.
They came here to be the person
she always dreamed to be.
Expenses have gone in
the wind.
They make their clothes ...
uncontrolled sexual urge,
take what you want when you want.
Groan, scream of ecstasy,
the delicious pain behind each door.
We devoured everything in sight ...
eat, drink, life itself
have irresistible forces.
It was inevitable ...
death followed us all here
with the wind.
And we can not be
might escape. "
"I can no longer control.
Passions are strong.
My need for power
about life itself
is just too strong.
It whispers to me.
They are those out there
paradise that we will not understand.
They will never understand
the soul that is innovative
and those damned
to hell. "
"It will never stop.
I will never stop. "
Oh, God.
Are you there?
Jess.
Amber.
You're it.
Where the hell have you been?
It's just a story.
You do not really believe in
those things, well then?
They seem to believe it.
That old bag is really
angered.
Go get some shots for us.
And what nacho `s.
- Good.
- I'm with you.
What do you need?
Two ... three tequila `s. ..
nacho and what `s.
Have you seen these girls?
No.
Excuse me, ma'am.
Everything good?
Yes, go Jeremy
bring his drink.
Is that your friend?
Sorry. I do not speak Spanish.
Let me ...
No, no, no.
I speak English.
I thought you might ...
I've often.
What did you show the bartender?
My friends ...
they are gone.
I wonder if somebody can
tell where they are
or who they are gone.
No, I have not seen them.
- Have you seen these women?
- No.
Sorry.
Thanks.
You know someone might take me to
south of the city can bring?
South of the city?
Where?
I heard that this
resort.
I think she can be.
You have problems finding people
that can bring you there.
I know.
I've heard.
I think we maybe
can bring ...
for a small fee,
of course.
Wait, you know where it is?
You know how to get there?
Everyone here knows where it is.
They will just not go.
- So you going tonight?
- Not the evening.
Nobody goes there the evening before.
That place has a bad reputation, chica.
We wait for the sunrise.
No, but I can pay you. What does it cost
tonight to go there?
Dangerous objects come here `s night.
Go home, take a
shower and relax.
See you here tomorrow morning.
Then we go, okay?
Ok.
What did she say?
She thinks her friend at
The hotel is old.
- How do they know?
- She said no.
But I bet that bitch
has called her
and said she was.
Do you think they suspect us?
Why does that matter?
I care for them tomorrow.
Cheers.
We know these guys do not.
How can we trust them?
- I have no choice.
- How much money do they want?
It is a scammer.
You do not have to come
if you do not want.
These are my friends.
This is my problem.
No, no, of course, we go.
We show you not just go.
Okay?
Why should I go?
You ok there?
Fuck you.
When was the last time
your friends that you saw?
Two nights ago. I did yesterday morning
talked to them,
but I have since not
seen.
That is not good.
Has anyone else seen them?
One American tourist
they like each other.
We have called the police.
She would not be bothered.
What she said about the police?
Do not worry, they help her
with the search.
They do not find them, even though
they knew it.
You know where you're going, right?
Goddamn.
Oh, God.
Oh my God.
Shit.
- You should call a doctor.
- Keep quiet.
We have nothing to do.
You turned the gun on us, remember?
We must leave here.
What should we do?
Oh, God,
what have we done?
They have put them away ...
Beth and everyone ...
and they have over them.
You killed us, just like you to
our friends did, right?
We have never seen your friends.
Stop it. Stop it.
Let me think.
Ok,
we tie him up
and we take him to the resort.
No, let me not go.
Beautiful thieves with shot wounds
impose no requirements.
Cunt.
- What have you done to him?
- No, no, no, nothing.
We took their money and everything,
but we left him lying on the side.
We did not kill him.
Beth said you Cat lap.
I did not.
She wanted to run away.
What have you done with them?
No doctor for you until
We have found them.
Take us to the resort.
You go there not
inside, well then?
- Shut up.
- You can not enter.
- That place lets you do things.
- Look,
I'm not leaving without
my friends.
Take him away.
What? No, no,
I brought you here,
but I'm not going inside.
Come on. I need a doctor, man.
There is no doctor to
we have our friends.
I do not go inside.
Well. If you are not inside
to go
You can stay here.
Let me not alone.
Please, leave me alone.
Leave me alone.
Hello.
After you.
What is that?
Is there anyone?
Has anyone a buggy?
What if they are not here?
What if they roam out there?
How do we find them?
Just try not to think.
They are here somewhere.
You must.
Beth.
Amber.
Jessica.
Kathleen.
No need to shout.
I'm here.
Cat.
Luckily everything is well with you.
Beth said you're fired.
Shot?
I'm not fired.
I've never felt so good.
Where are the others?
They are here somewhere.
We have a bus.
Let us get back and go to town.
Would you all away so quickly?
You should now see the stars the evening.
It is so peaceful.
What, Cat?
Why are you so strange?
I do not know what you mean.
Want to look the other girls.
Ok.
Follow me.
Kat, what happens?
Then Beth said she called for help ...
Is not this place beautiful?
Of course.
How did you find?
We looked for help.
And we found it.
Onze Vader Die in de Hemelen zijt,
Hallowed be thy name.
Your kingdom come,
Your name will be done,
In Heaven as on Earth.
Give us this day our daily bread ...
And it does us all
much help.
What are you talking about?
Find out.
You lead.
If you insist.
- Untranslated --
It can help you all.
What happens there?
- Untranslated --
Sophie.
Jeremy?
We are here to bring you home.
I want to go home.
We must get the other and
you get here.
The other?
Amber and Jessica ...
where are they?
I do not know.
What is going on here?
It is strange,
Sophie ... I ...
What?
I will not tell you.
Do not be afraid.
Tell me.
Where's your other friend go?
What? Jesus.
Cat!
- Come on, we gotta go.
- I 'm not going anywhere.
We have to.
It is not safe.
I'm not!
Sophie, I do not know what
happen to me.
Leave me alone.
You know what?
You find the other.
I'll stay here with her.
Take care.
We do. And let her
clothes to keep, okay?
We are back soon.
It is good.
Please, I need a doctor.
Listen
I'm ready.
Are you that?
Amber.
Jessica.
Kathleen.
- No!
- Jesus Christ.
Eat!
Amber, what are you doing?
What have you done?
What the hell is this?
No, that's my girlfriend.
Amber, I am ... Sophia.
Listen to me.
Stop it.
- I do not think they can hear you.
- Stop it!
Stop it!
Pick the furniture.
She has lost her mind.
They let it go.
We all.
We are all relieved.
Jess, you do not.
We are in trouble.
We should not trust.
But I've made.
I took care of that bastard.
I can not do much without it.
Can you hear them ...
the voices in the wind?
They call you.
I hear nothing.
Want to know why you are afraid ...
afraid to be free?
Go here, damn.
Just in the bus.
And do not stop.
Get away from me.
Just go now. Do not stop.
Beth!
Jeremy!
Beth.
Jeremy.
What have you done?
Why?
Why not?
You're not Beth.
Where is she?
Of course I am.
Sophie, I am.
- You're not yourself.
- I know.
But everyone can change.
Let me hurt you.
Why would you do?
We are friends, but ...
best friends?
Remember what you said to me
You and Sarah were the seventh grade
after you had helped me
with a small problem?
You said you felt you free.
Go away from me.
Now I know what really means Fri.
Now I know what I missed.
Get the fuck away from me!
Please try again.
Can you hear?
It is so loud.
Can not you hear?
You try not to
the bus to go, right?
You should know that it does not work.
There is only one thing
what you can do.
Sophie.
Where were you?
Why you left us?
Leave me if not.
Sophie.
I am so sorry.
Oh, God, no.
Want to save yourself?
What you are.
All your friends are dead
second.
You can not make me
her murder.
Really, darling, stop running.
There is only one thing
what you can do.
No.
No, no!
Can you hear it?
I can hear.
Stay there.
Stop there.
I can not stop.
No one can.
Jessica, I am.
Do you remember me?
Why are you doing this?
Because you are free.
That is the point.
That is nonsense.
I am free to do
what I want!
You will never hurt me.
It wants me.
I thought you could hear.
Stop, please.
I want to do this.
Let me do this.
You will, if you would just listen.
Listen.
Listen!
Jess.
Oh, God, Jess.
Sophie?
Sophia.
- Oh, God.
- What is going on?
- What happens to me?
It is good.
You're okay.
You're alive.
That is all that counts.
Okay, okay.
Kathleen ...
where is she?
She is okay.
Everyone is okay.
I do not want anymore.
I want to go home.
- I want to go home.
I will take care of you, okay?
Okay?
Everything is good.
Yes.
Sophia.
Wait.
Wait, what are you ...?
Subtitled by:
Dejavu, Gonnie and Martien
Downloaded from www.ondertitel.com