No, not again!
You're on the wrong
side of the tracks, Neil!
Run, Neil, Run!
Why can't you sleep
like a normal person?
Do you have nightmares
every freakin' night, or what?
It... it all seemed so real.
Well listen Neil, you gotta
stop wakin' me up like this.
I need my beauty sleep!
I'm about ready to kick
you out of my apartment.
I'm sorry,
its just your apartment?
I'm the one who's been paying
rent since you lost your job.
Hey, hey-- don't turn this
around on me, man--
you're the one who has
the problem, not me...
- I don't have the problem.
- Okay, cut the bullshi--
You gonna get that?
Hello?
Oh, hey, Neil.
I didn't wake you, did I?
No, another damn
nightmare woke me up.
Again? Are you okay?
Yeah, I guess. It was so real,
I could have sworn it
was really happening,
I felt like this guy was
really going to kill me.
You've just gotta relax.
Bad dreams are just a
result of too much stress.
You've just got to figure out
what in your life is bothering you.
Why are you eating my cereal?
I bought this! For me!
- Relax.
- And you're eating out of a cup!
Well, all the dishes are dirty.
Maybe you could lift a
finger and actually wash--
No, I was talking to Chuck...
no, he hasn't found a job yet!
Anyway, I've gotta get going,
Eddie's train gets in later today,
and I've gotta go pick him up.
Ed Spengler? From high school?
I haven't seen him in five years!
- What has he been up to?
- He's been working
for his uncle in New York,
doing some scientific stuff.
I guess he's gonna
be conducting
some kind of experiments
in the area.
- What kind of experiments?
- Oh, you know Eddie,
wherever he goes,
weird things follow.
That's funny, I've always thought
the same thing about you.
Yeah, I suppose.
Anyway, here's Chuck--
I've got to get going.
Oh, hey babe-- what's up?
Why do you always talk
to Neil for so long?
Ye gods! My uncle was right!
Denver is crawling with
paranormal activity!
I don't understand why
I had to come all the way
here with you, just to look
at blips on a scanner.
This isn't a scanne--
it's a digital PKE meter,
and these aren't just
any old blips! They're--
I know, I know, they're
electro-phantasmal shadows
that indicate the presence
of ghosts. I get it.
I can't believe
your uncle talked me
into dropping my psych
major and chasing spooks.
Eugene, you're my best friend.
We've been through
a lot together.
Come on, we're in this
together, we're a team.
Team? Sometimes I feel
like I'm just your bitch!
Assistant, Eugene,
you're my assistant,
- and we're here to get a job done!
- But you treat me like I'm your bitch!
Fine, if you want to consider
yourself my bitch, then do so.
I wish Neil would get here
so we could get started.
My uncle showed us what
to do and how to do it,
and if we need to do it in
every building in Denver,
we'll do it in every
building in Denver.
Queers.
Hey back off man.
He's a scientist!
What? Oh, there's
a misunderstanding,
we're not like that, you see
we're here in search
of ectoplasmic energy
ghosts in hopes
that we can prevent
any paranormal outbreak
of malevolent inhuman spirits.
We're affiliated
with the Ghostbusters,
out of New York,
ever heard of us?
Neil Anderson!
Long time no see.
If you happen to see
anything, well, um... spooky--
Let's go, Ed!
We're wasting
valuable drinking time!
...give us a call!
Queers.
So, Neil...
tell me about these dreams...
I'd rather not talk about it.
I get crap from Chuck
about it all the time.
Chuck?
Is he still dating Nancy?
- Yeah, yeah.
- Nancy Ashton?
Isn't that the girl you had
a crush on? She's hot.
- Why is she dating your roommate?
- I don't know.
It doesn't make any sense,
he's a complete slob...
he doesn't have a job--
I'm sure she'll realize her
mistake soon enough.
Yeah, I guess.
What kind of experiments
are you here for anyway?
"Paranormal investigations"
he thinks he's Fox Mulder
or something.
Oh, for God's sake, Ed!
You're not following in
the footsteps of
your crazy uncle
with all that ghost
busting crap are you?
- Maybe I am.
- Well, I know one thing...
those proton packs
are cool as hell!
So tell me about
your nightmares, Neil.
Y'know, I read that bad
dreams are caused by stress.
Yeah, I've heard. I really jus--
What's going on?
Some kind of poltergeist...
been scarin' away my customers.
Really?
- You can't be serious.
- I'm always serious.
This is heavy, doc!
- Why do I get the messed up uniform?
- They're hand me downs.
So why do I get
the hand me down
that looks like a ghost
whipped his ass with it?
It's ectoplasm. Slime...
and probably a bit of marshmallow
now that you mention it.
Marshmallow?
Maybe it's gone.
I don't think so.
- Are you okay?
- Yeah, I'm just--
- Neil, throw the trap down!
- What?
The trap! You'll have to
throw it! It's on my belt!
On 3, take your foot
off the pedal!
Everyone remember to
look away from the trap!
One... two... three! Now!
Wow, I guess you were right, Ed!
Oh my god that was... awesome!
You boys just saved my
business! What do I owe you?
- Uh...
- Two grand!
Good morning, I'm Ed Rooney.
This morning the
Mile High city is alive
with talk of
supernatural activity,
ghosts and hauntings pouring
in from all over the front range.
Hey babe, why don't
you come over here
- I just got a dimer from--
- That's all you do with your life!
- Yeah...
- I don't know how Neil puts up with it!
Neil? Yeah, he's a winner.
He's been staying with
his Ghostbuster friends
at their little
headquarters downtown
hasn't been home in a week.
Well, he's been a
busy man these days...
what with a job and all.
Oh geez, who cares what
that guy does, anyway?
- Maybe I do.
- What's that supposed to mean?
Nothing, look, I've got to go...
maybe I'll talk to you tomorrow.
You know what? Whatever!
Man, I'm dead. What a week.
I'm not chasing one
more ghost until
I get at least 8 hours
of uninterrupted sleep.
Speaking of which,
you don't seem
to be suffering from
any bad dreams lately.
Nope...
ever since I stopped
sleeping at my apartment.
That's unusual.
Yeah, I think it was that
crappy mattress I bought...
Mattress?
Did you start having bad
dreams as soon as you got it?
Pew!
It is entirely possible you have
a poltergeist in
the mattress itself.
Why not... he's not using it.
Whoa, a haunted bed?
Why not? What happens
in these dreams, Neil?
It's really bizarre.
In the dream,
I'm always in this... place.
I'm all alone, but suddenly
in the distance,
there's this guy...
his face is horribly burned,
and he's got these...
knives on his fingers...
like claws...
he calls himself Freddy...
Freddy Krueger.
You're all alone, now Neil!
Neil? What? No, I'm Chuck.
How Sweet! Fresh Meat!
Dude, are you gay?
Hey Chuck, let's toke up!
Hey man, you're all right!
- Hello?
- I'm your boyfriend now, Nancy!
- I'm sorry, who is this?
- Oh... uh... is Nancy there?
Nancy, it's for you!
Hmm... a dream demon.
It's not unheard of.
Yeah, so how do we stop
him if he's not a ghost?
I think we should check out
that mattress as soon as possible.
Right... like in the morning.
Actually, I was thinking right now.
Well, have fun.
I'm gonna get some rest.
I have a feeling
that Freddy could be
the entire reason
the PKE levels in
- Denver have surged recently.
- No way...
there have been so
many other ghosts in...
Well, all my recent data
points to something else.
I think Freddy may
have somehow opened
a rift to another dimension.
I wouldn't rule out
Freddy actually controlling
the ghosts himself.
- I have to see that mattress.
- Okay...
as long as we're not
there all damn night.
I just need to get some readings.
Neil, you better come here.
Look at those claw marks!
Just like my dream!
Its almost as if by
sleeping in your bed,
Chuck encountered
your dream demon!
- Freddy.
- A man is dead in your bed!
What should we do?
I have an idea.
Strange, I halfway expected
Freddy to emerge
from the mattress.
Hey, if we killed him
just by burning
his haunted mattress,
I'm fine with that.
I just didn't think it
would be that easy.
That's the third
teenager murdered
in their sleep in
the last week.
I think we both know
what this points to.
Agreed. I was going
over the possibilities
of how this may have happened.
We probably set Freddy free
when we burned the mattress.
Likely... but it also
may have occurred
when he made his
first kill in a new city.
That's why he didn't
emerge from the mattress.
Ghostbusters.
What do you mean
Nancy won't wake up -
is she having a nightmare?
Okay, we're on the way!
Surprise, it's the Ghostbusters!
Go, get them!
Ghostbusters!
Hello?
We found her like this.
She appears to be
trapped in a dream state.
Well, at least she's not dead!
It's Freddy... he's got her...
The readings I'm getting on
this are off the charts!
If the neural psycho
kinetic energy is constant,
this demon of yours
may be invincible!
No, there has to be
a way to stop him.
Maybe we could just
shoot him in the face?
- Well, that would kill me!
- Hey, what would Jared do?
Yeah, what would Jared do?
I would go into the
dream-dimension
where Freddy lives
and pull him into reality.
Once he is real,
you should be able to
contain him with your equipment.
Then I'd go to Subway
for a Roasted Chicken
sandwich on parmesan
oregano bread.
Of course, it's so simple!
Thanks, Jared!
Look, if there aren't any
more of these damn questions
for a while,
I'm gonna have a nap!
- No, please!
- It's okay.
I had Subway for lunch!
This is all makeshift, but
theoretically, it should work.
Once you two have
a hold on Freddy,
I'll pull you from the dream
and we can trap him, got it?
- Let's do this like Falco!
- Like Falco?
Rock me Amadeus!
- Where are we?
- Oh man,
this is it, this is my dream.
Right.
Let's find Freddy.
Who ya gonna kill?
Ghostbusters!
Haaahahahaha!
Alright, let's bag this
sucker and go home.
Mr. Anderson, welcome back.
My name... is Neil!
They don't hurt him at all!
- Run?
- Yes.
What are they doing?!
All you have to do
is grab a hold of him!
Nancy!
Neil! I knew you'd come!
Wake up, Nancy!
What happened?
Got him! Now Ed, now!
I had him!
No, he's definitely here...
somewhere.
He just disappeared!
I thought he could be
harmed in the real world!
Theoretically, he can...
but he seems to
have maintained some of
his dreamworld powers.
- I'll swallow your soul!
- Oh crap, guys!
Get me out of here! Now!
This equipment to bring
Neil back is fried.
There's only one
way to get him out.
- What about Freddy?
- Eugene, keep me covered.
What are we gonna do?
I've got a plan.
We'll cross the streams.
Wait, wait...
that just sounds like a bad idea.
I mean I'm no scientist,
but I swear crossing
streams sounds.
It may just create
enough energy
to knock us back
into the waking world!
Three... four...
better lock your door!
But what if crossing the
streams doesn't work,
and we end up blowing
up the universe?!
Well, we could either try it,
or stay here
while these phantoms
feast upon our souls!
Five... six...
It's time to kick ass
and chew bubble gum
and I'm all outta gum!
You're not gonna cram
me into that toaster!
Thisssssssssssssssucks!!
- Wow, it worked!
- Of course it worked,
that's because
I know what I'm doing!
We better get this thing
to the containment unit.
- Who are you guys?
- We're the Ghostbusters.
Captioned by Grantman Brown