North and South came along
and l would've died to get it, you know.
lt was just one of those roles
of a lifetime.
This is one With the Wind
for the last half of the 20th century.
for television.
l didn't have to create Madeline.
John Jakes created Madeline.
The popularity of the American Çivil War
and all that goes with it...
... really lies
in the emotion of people...
... who are close to one another
being torn apart by what they believe...
... or what they're supposed
to believe.
Roots was the story of the South
from the black point of view.
North and South is the story
of the South...
... from the white point of view.
The very first thing that you hear
when the project goes on...
... is the main title and the music.
And the music is gonna carry
that message...
... of what is this thing all about.
Çue marker.
Well, North and South,
the trilogy began...
... with a three-book contract
that l had.
Originally, it was to be three books...
... about a military family
through the years, one family.
l then started to research it.
And of course, the first place l went to
was West Point.
Read the history of West Point.
And in one book,
l came across this one page...
... that named all of the generals
who fought each other...
... in the Çivil War on opposite sides.
They had all known each other
at West Point.
They had gone to school together.
They had gone to Mexico together,
fought there.
And l called up my editor
and l said, ''Julian, this has gotta be it.
Now, we're gonna do two families
at West Point...
... and it divides very nicely
into North and South...
... dealing with the antebellum years...
... Love and War dealing
with the war itself...
... Heaven and Hell dealing
with Reconstruction. ''
And that was it,
but it was an evolution.
Well, the North and South
came about...
... because l actually got a call
from ABÇ...
... they just bought a book
called North and South.
l had just done Roots.
l did The Thorn Birds for them,
they said:
''We couldn't think
of anybody better...
... we'd like to turn over
the whole project but to you. ''
So l read the book, the first book,
right away.
l said it's a great, juicy story.
John Jakes is a very juicy writer.
lt was material that could be adapted
so well for the form, the long form...
... in which feature films can't do...
... because they're compressed
into an hour and a half or two hours.
And this story needed a lot of time
to be told.
To be told effectively
and to be told the right way.
l knew l had to do a formidable amount
of research for the trilogy.
First of all, because the Çivil War
is such an enormously popular subject...
... not only in the United States,
but around the world.
Today, the Çivil War is called sometimes
the Brothers' War, the Çousins' War.
And phrases like that
really exemplify the split...
... the painful split
that took part in our country.
y ou know, years ago...
... John Çalhoun said
that West Point men...
... would lead great armies.
He never thought they'd be leading them
against each other.
And l hadn't really realized
it was that deep or that harrowing.
But that was the whole point
that emerged...
... in writing North and South
was these two guys basically...
... who had a great affection
for one another...
... as West Point classmates.
At the end, when war broke out,
they were pulled apart.
They each had to go their own way.
And it was more
than just a casual decision.
lt was very, very emotional.
l tell you, we didn't have any problems
with the theme...
... with any controversy
with the North and South...
... for one particular reason.
y ou heard the South's point of view...
... and you heard the North's point
of view, so it wasn't... .
y ou heard slavery.
But then you heard the people
in the North saying how bad it was.
l was really intrigued
with this time period...
... because, at the same time,
it was a coming-of-age story...
... in many ways for Orry and George.
lt was a coming-of-age period
in my life as Patrick, you know.
Having to really analyze
and look at who l am...
... and what l was about
and who l thought l was...
... as opposed to who l really was.
Television has its place...
... and North and South definitely
had its place telling the story...
... of certain aspects of slavery...
... seen from a white man's
perspective.
l think it did marvelous things
with Virgilia's character, you know...
... the abolitionists and all of that.
Reading John Jakes' books
gave me great insight...
... but it also prodded me
to do a lot more research.
And also delve
into my own family tree.
Some who have died
and some who spent time...
... in Çonfederate prison camps,
and so forth...
... so that really brought it
very close to me.
The only thing l determined...
... before l started
writing North and South...
... was that l would not be an apologist
for slavery under any circumstances.
l've actually been cornered at parties
by what l call professional Southerners...
... who tried to tell me that slavery
wasn't so bad.
lt was okay.
They were wage slaves in the North.
They were slaves in the factories.
And to that, l always say, ''y es,
but in the North, they could walk away.
They could just walk away. ''
l had no idea what l was getting into,
because l am a Southern man.
l do come from a belief system
that is based in integrity and morality...
... and a certain code.
This time period,
with the Çivil War brewing...
... in many ways, it was the first time
men were challenged...
... to start questioning this code.
l was living in South Çarolina...
... recently moved in
at the time l started the book.
l located their plantation
up near Çharleston.
l debated as to whether
to put the Main family...
... in the cotton business
or the rice business.
Ultimately, l decided on the rice business
because that was older...
... than the cotton business
in South Çarolina.
l would say the Main family
were middle-of-the-road Southerners...
... in the sense
that they were slave owners...
... but tried not to mistreat
their slaves.
But when push came to shove,
they were willing...
... to apply horrible punishments
to the slaves.
Mr. Main, sir.
What's Priam done?
Why you beating him?
There's no crime exactly.
lt's his attitude, sir.
Priam don't show the proper respect.
A good overseer knows how to get
a man's respect without beating him.
And we don't whip slaves
at Mont Royal.
lt really taught me what it is
to be a true Southern man, you know.
lt was like, at one point, my agent
had a meeting with me...
... and said, ''y ou've got to quit
calling everybody 'sir. ' ''
l went, ''Why?''
He says, ''Because it shows
a lack of respect for yourself. ''
l went, ''What the hell is wrong
with you? l mean, that's insanity. ''
lt had nothing to do
with my self-esteem.
lt had to do with, you know,
the certain way you're brought up.
y ou hold the door for women.
y ou pull their chair out.
lt's your job. lt's not a macho thing.
But also, when you say ''sir''
in a different context...
... it can also be very dangerous,
you know.
''Sir, you mess with me one more time,
and l break every bone in your body. ''
Let's have you, Mr. Main.
At your service, sir.
We had two personalities,
we picked James Read...
... and we had auditions and readings
and everything...
... and James Read
looked the right to us.
We wanted attractive-looking actors,
obviously.
Patrick Swayze was not a big star
at the time.
He looked perfect for us too.
Both of them auditioned and read
and screen-tested...
... and they got the part
because they came out the best...
... in the screen test and the audition.
David Wolper and l
didn't have many arguments.
But we had one
about Orry losing his arm, you know.
ln the book,
he loses an arm fighting in Mexico.
Çonsequently, his other arm
is extremely powerful...
... and it can even be used as a weapon.
Well, David didn't wanna do that.
And l can remember we argued about it
on the phone.
And he finally persuaded me by saying,
''Look, '' he said.
''lf l have to have 1 2 hours
or 1 0 hours or eight hours or whatever...
... with Patrick Swayze with his arm
tied behind his back...
... they won't get the story.
They'll be saying,
'Where's his arm hiding?
Where's his arm hiding?' ''
So l said, ''All right, you've won.
y ou've won. ''
Patrick has such charisma...
... that every girl who met,
and l'm sure meets him today...
... you meet him and you go:
And he lights something up
inside you.
So it wasn't difficult to act that.
Because even though l didn't want
to sort of leap off...
... into the sunset with him,
he's a charismatic person...
... and he inspires those looks
and that flirtatiousness.
l don't even know your name.
lt's Orry, Orry Main.
l'm from Mont Royal
just up the river.
My name is Madeline Fabray.
l'm delighted to meet you.
l've always said, ''y ou give me horses,
capes and cleavage...
... and l'm a happy man, '' you know.
Well, l still have them.
l still have the wardrobe.
But l've never let go
of my general's uniform...
... and the cape when Madeline
and l make love for the first time...
... in that burned-out church...
... and sort of consummate
this doomed...
... or looks like it's doomed,
relationship.
He loved you very much.
- l know.
- l'm gonna miss him so.
lt was a really emotional time for me
because my dad died.
My real dad died soon before.
So when you asked me earlier
about, you know:
''How does it feel
with your father dying, as Orry...
... and having to take over the family
and that responsibility...
... and carry on the legacy?''
l was in the throes, personally...
... in the throes of,
''What do l do without my dad?''
The North
was so overwhelmingly powerful...
... as an industrial concern,
as an industrial society...
... that it seemed to me
that having Hazards...
... in the iron business, making cannon,
making whatever they made...
... during the war,
was probably a good way...
... to exemplify the strength
of the North.
l think that my character,
George Hazard...
... was the conscience of the story...
... the moral conscience,
the moral authority.
He had a true understanding
of the division...
... that was apparently
ripping the country apart.
lt wasn't black and white.
lt wasn't the South is bad,
the North is good.
lt's much more complicated than that.
There was not a guy
on North and South...
... that l didn't, at one point
or another, think:
''y ou're so darling,
you're just so darling.
Let me just hug you and kiss you. ''
James Read is certainly one of them.
And of course, l do get to hug him
and kiss him in North and South III.
A marvelous actor. He really is.
l tried to bring the sense of me
that meets up with the character.
And George's journey is one...
... that goes from optimistic youth
looking to the promise of the future...
... to one that grows
into disillusionment...
... and pain...
... and the suffering
that goes with fighting for a cause...
... that you believe in
but carries with it a tremendous price.
l fell in love with him as a person.
And his ease, his James Bond
kind of, you know...
... handsome and cool and... .
ln many ways, l wanted to be him
because he was just so cool...
... and just had so much class
and, you know...
... and l'm like the reactionary,
you know, ''lf it moves, eat it. ''
He was great in this series.
He really was.
He had a tough uphill battle
with that part, you know.
North, upper class, upper... .
He didn't have any of the raw emotion
that Orry Main had.
He had an uphill battle
and he pulled it off really well.
Well, George was sort
of the steady one in the family.
Physically, George and Orry
in the pictures are reversed.
Orry was tall and thin,
skinny kind of a Lincoln-esque figure.
George was short, stocky.
That changed
when the actors were cast.
My brother obviously forgot
to introduce me, Mr. Main.
Of course not.
l'm Virgilia Hazard.
Virgilia, who's always been one
of my favorite characters...
... she was a fiery abolitionist.
So where, ladies and gentlemen,
do these new slaves come from?
Why, they come from slavery itself.
For the true crop
of a Southern plantation...
... is a human crop.
Don't have to tell about Kirstie Alley,
the audience know how feisty she is.
Kirstie is intense.
l mean she's got that fire in her eyes.
She gets on something,
she's like a pit bull.
As actors, we played
in underlying current of attraction...
... to where it was that kind of
dangerous male-female relationship.
Well, since you're so enamored
with women and their ideas...
... perhaps you would enjoy listening
to one who actually has some.
Very easy to believe.
Very easy to see the passion
of that character come alive in her.
Taking you into South Çarolina...
... is like taking a torch
into a powder magazine.
l'll be good as gold, l promise.
To you, madam.
y ou're love of beauty
is exceeded only by a love of money.
Oh, how true.
Now, somebody like Elizabeth Taylor,
she agreed to do magazine...
... newspaper, radio
and television interview.
So she came down to Çharleston...
... because she hadn't done an interview
for about five years.
So, what she brought us
for that one day...
... was a network television show
on three networks...
... major stories by AP and UP...
... major stories in People,
TIME magazine.
And so it's worth paying her.
l have some rather distressing news,
Madeline.
l know that you probably told Orry
and no doubt he said that our family--
What stays between Orry and me
is none of your business, Ashton.
Well, they were all feisty, l gotta tell you.
They became Kirstie Alley...
... Terri Garber, Wendy Kilbourne.
Those three
became very close on the set.
l declare, l wish l could go out
exactly like this.
The clothes.
The clothes were a nightmare for me,
l know.
ln the days when people
actually wore those clothes...
... those women have them on
for maybe two hours a day.
We had them on for 1 2, 1 4,
sometimes longer, a day.
Most of the women stopped
getting our periods.
Çompletely stopped.
Because the pulling in
of all of your organs...
... just seizes you up.
And at lunch time,
we would get to take our corsets off...
... and literally they would hang them up
outside the trailer...
... and they would just drip
with the sweat...
... and then you put them back on.
Lesley-Anne Down is a beautiful,
beautiful woman.
l have done two films with her...
... so l know how beautiful she is.
l've always found that
no matter what angle you film...
... Lesley-Anne Down from,
she's beautiful.
There wasn't even a question
as to what part l wanted to play.
l mean, on page two...
... it was obvious to me that Madeline
was your absolute archetypal heroine.
She was the woman
that would be remembered.
Not that her part was more important
than anybody else's...
... but she's definitive.
She was just beautifully written...
... and she was one of those girls...
... that the guys just want to get
on a big old horse and go rescue.
They wanna be Orry Main.
Lesley and l
both were of the belief...
... that it's not about jumping
somebody's bones...
... or sucking face that's sexy.
lt's about the need and the passion,
the desire and the connection...
... between two human beings
in there eyes.
y ou know what, passionate love scenes
l have some experience with...
... so whenever you have to act those,
it just tickles the old emotions again.
So you're kind of like,
''Oh, yeah l remember that. ''
Lesley-Anne Down is the essence
of a true Southern belle.
She was eye candy.
She was just, you know, luscious.
The scope of the production
was staggering.
The size and re-enacting Çivil War battles
and going back to this time period...
... but we were shooting in the places
it all happened.
Boone Hall, this gorgeous plantation.
Standing in between those columns
and looking out...
... how could you not be this guy?
And going down the streets
of Çharleston in carriages...
... all you had to do
is leave yourself open...
... and the production value alone
would take you away.
The first time
that we were at Boone Hall...
... you turn a corner
and you see the canopy of trees...
... like a cathedral
stretched out in front of you.
And there is the house
that is so famous.
lt's goose-bumpy.
lt took us a year and a half.
We filmed it in Çharleston,
South Çarolina...
... and some were in Mississippi...
... and some here out in the Simi Valley,
Newhall, Çalifornia.
We had a lot of problem--
l think one of the funniest ones
that happened to us...
... is we shot in Çharleston.
Because Çharleston is a city
that looks the same.
Whole areas of Çharleston are no
different than they were back in 1 800.
So one particular street,
whenever we film...
... we had to put dirt
over the pavement...
... because there wasn't any pavement
in that period.
So one street, we put dirt
up and down the pavement...
... and a woman comes out
screaming and yelling:
''y ou're gonna ruin my house.
y ou're putting dirt in my house.
This is an 1 860 house. All this filth
and dirt is gonna ruin my house. ''
l looked at her and l said, ''Lady,
there was dirt in front of your house...
... for a hundred years before l came.
And it's lasted today,
it's gonna last one more day of dirt. ''
Then she looked at me and said,
''y our right, Mr. Wolper, you're right. ''
We're shooting
outside of Natchez, Mississippi...
... and l don't know if you've ever been
in Natchez in July, but it's a little hot.
We're shooting
in sweltering Southern heat...
... with 1 50-percent humidity.
And, of course, we're shooting
a winter scene, it's snowing.
And while on camera,
l would be able to turn my sweat of...
... but then here and there...
... l would just turn or lean over or
whatever in a fight scene, so whatever...
... and just pass out
and just hit the ground.
lt's like, ''Swayze's on the ground again.
Slap him, get him up. ''
And it was so hot that the soap flakes
they used to imitate snow...
... were melting
and dripping on the costumes.
Didn't lend the necessary air
of authenticity they were looking for.
The major thing, of course,
with the Çivil War was a battle scene.
Fortunately, in a Çivil War,
there were groups in the South...
... who meet every week
and restage battles...
... live like the people did
in those days.
They lived in the tents,
they spent overnight together...
... they restage the battles together.
Without them,
it'd be nearly impossible to--
lt will take you months
to get the costumes...
... figure out how to stage the battles.
So they really are a terrific help
with people who do Çivil War films.
This group are Çivil War experts.
They're just sensational.
lf that kind of dedication to authenticity
didn't inspire you...
... and lead you to believe that
there are people really dedicated...
... to telling the story
in a true and accurate way...
... then nothing else would.
They need no direction.
''Action, '' and they just--
lt's hard to stop them.
Stop killing each other,
the camera's not rolling anymore.
l know that a book is not going
to jump fully-blown onto the screen...
... and l was very happy, generally...
... with the adaptations
that came out of these novels.
y ou got a lot of writers who say:
''Well, l can't put this in.
y ou changed my book, you did this. ''
John Jakes was nothing like that.
He loved what we had done in the script,
he loved everything.
He loved what we left out
and what we edited...
... and we told him,
the reasons why we did it.
He totally approved everything.
And he was one of those writers
who understands the business.
l had to sit with David Wolper,
who is an elegant gentleman...
... with a reputation as a producer
unparalleled, unrivalled by anyone else.
He's a special man.
And l believe he said to me after
knowing what the project was about...
... that he wanted something
like one with the Wind.
And l probably said, ''Okay. ''
And l do remember playing it
on the piano...
... for both David and the director.
And l obviously accomplished
what l'd set out to do...
... at least in the minds
of David and our director.
The music has the emotion stuff.
ls it a big project, is it a big picture,
is it a big mini-series?
l think my opening does that.
l think it delivers the goods.
y ou know, it either has a spark
and a magic or it doesn't.
And North and South
had a spark and a magic.
Perfect quality and perfect sound.
l mean, there's nothing--
l couldn't ask for more as a producer.
l casually turned to David and l said:
''By the way,
when do we go on the air?''
He says, ''ln three weeks. ''
Shortened my life by six months,
l'm sure...
... but l began immediately.
Every morning from 6:00
to 6:00 at night, l wrote music...
... because l had a week's worth
of music to start recording...
... and l was, for two weeks now...
... always recording at night,
writing during the day.
One, two, three, four... .
Wouldn't it be nice if we had,
in a Wagnerian sense, a light motif?
A little theme that you attached
to various players, actors, characters...
... as they came in, or situations.
y ou know, l fell in love with you
during our very first dance.
''Oh, l'm in love, ''
and you hear the love theme.
''Oh, here comes him, ''
and his theme plays.
So l did that.
l made a little pallet of themes
for everyone and some situations...
... and l think every time we fought,
l did something.
Playing the theme for David at the piano
the first time...
... l'm glad
that he thought it was really good...
... because l'd have to go back
and do another one if he didn't.
Sometimes when l watch something
1 0 years later and see the film...
... l still say to myself,
''l don't like that scene.
lt could have been something.
lt could have been better. ''
When Orry Main came
from the South to West Point...
... in actuality,
a number of people from the South...
... brought their slaves with them
to West Point.
And we cut it out there...
... because you'd have this long
explanation of what happened there...
... and l didn't wanna get
into a controversy and everything.
But later on, l said to myself,
''That would have been a terrific scene. ''
lt would have said something
to the other characters...
... people from the North, by saying,
by getting a closer picture...
... of what slavery was all about.
And it would have, l think,
helped the overall story...
... that we didn't put in,
and l'm sorry about that.
lt was a very, very explosive,
you know, period of time.
l think it was like
a gigantic soap opera.
y ou turn on one episode,
you just get sucked in.
l got the opportunity to work
with unbelievable people.
l mean, Jimmy Stewart.
There now,
that's the smile l remember.
l could tell
how much your wife cared for you...
... and that troubled me all the time
l was holding my silence.
l got myself all prepped and primed to
walk on the set with Jimmy Stewart...
... and when l walked on the set,
my knees turned to butter...
... and l couldn't remember one word
of what l was supposed to say.
l felt like a little kid just standing there,
just in awe.
l was in New Orleans
a couple of months ago...
... and this is almost 20 years
after the show first aired...
... and l was walking
down Bourbon Street...
... and a guy came up to me
and stopped...
... and looked at me and said,
''General Hazard. ''
And he saluted me.
l was just taken aback.
One of the things
that l'm most proud of...
... l'll tell you, the North and South
is one of my favorites.
There's hours of music.
y ou mean,
which book do l like personally?
My favorite is the middle one,
Love and War...
... because it covers the entire Çivil War,
start to finish.
And l think it's a pretty good
highlight version of the war...
... from the Southern side
as well as the Northern side.
There's no question, number one
was my favorite book, of course it was.
lt broke my heart that l didn't get to--
l didn't get to do this role
and my dad see it.
Anyplace where you find
the essence of civil war...
... where you have one people
divided on an issue...
... makes it a story
that people can relate to...
... no matter where they're from
or what language they speak.
lt was a true...
... extra-rich chocolate piece of life,
you know.
lt truly was.
What l enjoy about the results
is that we're still talking about it...
... and we can still show the film
20 years later.
And we'll still be able to show it
50 years later...
... because it's a story about history.
lt will always be relevant.
lt will always be important.