[ Man ]
Last time, on Hercules.
Hercules!
- [ Both ] Hercules?
-[ Colchis ] Why would I
wanna kill a pig?
Because this pig...
is Hercules.
Hi there.
Nice day for a ride,
don't you think?
- I'm Katherine.
- [ Hercules ]
Are you talking to me?
If we had Hermes' sandals,
we could cover this entire
province in no time.
I'll help you steal those
sandals, but we do it
my way,capisce?
We're in a slaughterhouse,
and the man who brought us here
is a butcher.
- Okay, think, Herc.
- [ Laughs ]
Stop this crazy thing!
Whoa!
You idiot!
This isn't Hercules!
What?
That pig's a girl!
Whoa!
Way to go, Flavio.
What's the matter, Discord?
Chicken?
- You are on my list!
- Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
You know, it's not
too late to go back.
Will you come with me?
It would be my pleasure
to take you home.
See, if I could,
I'd tell you that
everything is gonna be okay.
You know, that your family's
not gonna be upset that you
ran away...
and that, well, they're gonna
be glad that you came home.
That's all well and good
as far as it goes,
but there was more
to my running away
than I told you.
Katherine, I--
I can still understand you.
Well, it'd be sad
if you forgot everything
you learned as a pig.
Yeah, but you just
let me go on and on,
ever since we left
my mother's house
without so much as an oink.
Why didn't you tell me we could
still talk to each other?
I wasn't sure you'd want to,
since you're human again.
Humans are sort of
above the rest of us.
That's what most of 'em
seem to believe anyway--
that they're superior.
I've been both. I, uh--
I know better.
[ Chicken Clucking ]
[ Discord ]
Enough, okay? Fix this!
Lean on Artemis!
Get her to change me back!
Not to hurry, Discord.
The possibilities here
are... interesting.
Not a chance! Pull it on
some other pullet.
[ Clucks ]
Just give me back my body!
All in good time.
You were close to greatness.
Turning Hercules into a porker,
it was, well, genius.
But you blew it.
You just had to be the porkee.
You've got
a one-track mind.
What do you want from me,
beside the obvious?
What can a chicken
do to Hercules?
My mind isn't on my brother
right now.
It's on that piddling mortal
who did this to you--
Iolaus.
[ Clucks ]
I'm offended he thought
he could get away with it.
You're offended?
How do you think I feel?
My giblets
are in a stew!
Your giblets got you into this
in the first place.
Perhaps this will teach you
to keep your tail feathers
together.
[ Squawks ]
What?
Oh.
You are really twisted,
you know that?
I think I'll leave you
the way you are for now,
give you time to think
about how you screwed up
the perfect opportunity.
Don't push it.
Next time, it won't be an egg.
[ Clucks ]
Ha! What kind of gratitude
was that?
Let me tell you something.
Hermes without his little
sandals is a nobody.
You think he'd be glad
to get 'em back.
Considering we stole them
in the first place, I can
understand his attitude.
Well, I still think
it's a bad idea.
Eventually, I would've
gotten the hang of flying
those little puppies,
and it would've been
very handy.
Oh, yeah.
Handy for quick getaways,
leaving no trace.
No, no.
You misunderstood me.
I meant handy
in a good way.
You mean like you could
steal everything and anything?
That's your idea of a good way.
I prefer to think of it
as honing my craft.
Oh, please!
[ Thunder Crashing ]
-Ares.
- Oh, I got a bad feeling.
Oh, it's gonna be so much
more than a bad feeling.
Does this look familiar?
[ Clucking ]
Let me at 'em!
Ah, well, the--
The beak looks familiar, but--
You know, to tell you the truth,
all chickens pretty much
look the same to me.
[ Iolaus ]
So what do you think?
Original recipe
or spartacue sauce?
[ Laughing ]
Impudent toad!
Before this day is out,
you'll be groveling for mercy.
Get ready for the worst day
of your miserable lives!
[ Chuckles ]
Doesn't he know
I'm the King of Thieves?
I'll shuck these toys
like a bad habit.
Those chains were
forged by Hephaestus.
No lock to pick.
No way to get out.
You two are stuck
with each other.
By the end of the day,
you will despise each other.
That'll be
an improvement.
[ Clucks ]
Yeah, okay.
She doesn't think the chains
are enough and, you know,
I think I agree.
[ Chuckling ]
[ Laughing ]
I'll be back.
Got a big surprise
in store for you, Iolaus.
[ Laughing ]
[ Clucking ]
[ Man Narrating ]
This is the story
of a time long ago,
a time of myth and legend,
when the ancient gods
were petty and cruel,
and they plagued mankind
with suffering.
Only one man dared
to challenge their power--
Hercules.
Hercules possessed a strength
the world had never seen,
a strength surpassed
only by the power of his heart.
He journeyed the earth,
battling the minions
of his wicked stepmother, Hera,
the all-powerful
queen of the gods.
But wherever
there was evil,
wherever an innocent
would suffer,
there would be... Hercules.
- [ Screeching ]
- [ Roaring ]
Hail!
Oh, I don't know
why Ares included me
in his little game.
You're the one that turned
Discord into a chicken!
Yeah, but only so
she wouldn't turn you
into a rat,
which, now that I think
about it, you already are.
[ Yelps ]
Will you watch
where I'm going!
Oh, look!
My arrangement!
You rearranged
my arrangement!
Oh, what if I did?
There's plenty of
small leaves around.
We gotta find
some clothes.
[ Laughs ]
Okay. Say we did.
How would we get 'em on
with these?
Hercules! He's the one
that can break us free...
before Ares comes back
with his big surprise,
whatever that is.
Okay, and where do you
suppose we find Hercules?
He could be anywhere!
What is this,
20 questions?
Katherine!
Hercules has gone
to take her home.
We'll go there first.
Well, let's get going.
I'm flapping in the breeze here.
Okay!
Yeah, okay!
[ Katherine ]
I've been thinking about
something, Hercules.
Would you help me
become human?
But you don't like humans.
Why would you wanna be one?
Some of them are pretty nice.
Humans can do as they please.
Pigs can't.
Look, everyone lives
with some limitations.
But you're smart and
brave and generous.
I've seen that.
That's well and good
as far as it goes,
but I'm still a pig.
The King of Thieves in a sack.
My image is ruined.
Listen, you,
why don't you just
pick up the pace?
Because the sooner
we get there, the sooner
Hercules can free us...
and the sooner
I'll be rid of you.
[ Yelps ]
You know, two can play
the yank game.
Oh, yeah?
Yeah!
Do you like hospital food?
You wanna wake up
with a crowd around ya?
- You and whose army?
- You're lookin' at him.
Yeah?
Yeah.
[ Grunting ]
You'll never--
I told ya--
Get up!
It ain't gonna happen!
[ Screaming ]
It just keeps gettin'
better and better.
[ Iolaus ]
Listen, I told you.
I'm a hunter.
I've got an excellent
sense of direction,
and the village is this way.
Yeah, well, I'm a thief,
and I robbed that town,
and I'm telling you
it's back that way.
You couldn't find your way
out of a sock!
dddd [ Humming ]
Hey, let's ask
the little girl.
[ Ares And Discord Laughing ]
Oh, this is
just too good.
[ Autolycus ] Little girl--
[ Discord ]
You said it, Baby.
Wait till they try
and explain themselves.
No one will understand a word
they're trying to say.
[ Laughing ]
Hi, honey, it's okay--
[ Growling ]
[ Growling, Barking ]
- [ Growling ]
- [ Screaming ]
[ Screaming Continues ]
What is her problem?
I don't know.
Kids these days.
[ Man ]
What is it?
What's wrong?
It was a monster!
It looked like
it was coming apart.
It tried to get me.
[ Whimpering ]
Come, dear.
Let's get it!
[ Crowd Yelling ]
Believe me, you don't even
wanna be half-human.
If the Fates had cast
your destiny to be a human,
you would've been born that way.
You're meant to be a pig.
I mean, that's who you are.
I know you're right, but if
I have a chance to change
that destiny...
and want to,
shouldn't I take it?
- And shouldn't you help me?
- Look, Katherine, I wish I--
[ Hercules ]
Hello, Aphrodite.
Who's that?
[ Squealing ]
Uh, don't ask.
Don't tell.
I'd expect this
sort of thing from Ares,
but for you, Herc,
it's a little kinky.
Oh, you wish.
[ Giggles ]
I'm here as a favor
to Artemis.
Oh! Yeah. I figured
someone would be along.
She's very grateful
to you, Hercola.
And she wants to know
if there's anything
she can do in return,
-or that I can do for her.
- No, just tell her thanks.
I was glad to help.
Hercules, once the bow is gone,
so is my hope.
It's my one wish in life.
Please?
I'm not up on my pig latin,
but this sounds serious.
It'll break my heart
if I stay a pig.
- She wants to be human.
- Honey, you can wait until
you're old and cold...
for a man to get a clue.
But broken hearts
are my department.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Aphrodite, what-- D-Don't!
[ Squealing ]
- [ Katherine ] Yeah!
- There you go, Hamlet.
If you're gonna be one,
you might as well
look your best.
- Thanks, sis.
- You're welcome, bro.
Toodles.
Yippee!
[ Laughs ]
Great.
Yippee!
Thank you, Hercules!
Thank you!
This is the happiest day
of my life!
You're welcome.
But I never thought clothes
would be so uncomfortable.
Well, they're
kind of necessary.
I don't see why.
Not on a beautiful,
sunny day like today.
[ Gasps ]
Look at that!
What?
[ Laughs ]
Oh, uh, Katherine,
I don't think--
No. No, no, it--
Ahh!
[ Hercules ]
Katherine, you really
shouldn't be--
-[ Girl ]
Mama, look at the funny lady.
- Whee!
Uh, Katherine, please.
There's-- There's people.
[ Katherine ]
Oh, boy!
Oh, yeah.
Take it off!
Take it all off!
Katherine, really,
this isn't a good idea.
There's people here,
and it's just--
Katherine, see,
humans don't do this.
- [ Moans ]
- Come with me!
Whee!
She, uh, says it's good
for her complexion.
This is my favorite thing
in the world.
All right,
Mr. I-know-where-we-are,
where are we?
We're lost.
That's where we are.
We're headed north!
I know where we are.
Yeah, so do I.
We're in a swamp
being eaten by bugs.
Shush!
Ah!
Look.
A crowd of people
came through here.
[ Sniffs ]
Not long ago. See?
The guy in the front was
shorter than all the others.
That's good, right?
Yeah.
Well, then let's find them.
Surely they know the way
to civilization.
Wait. Shh. Listen.
We're lost again,
ain't we?
There's no monster here!
Yes, there is.
You heard the girl.
And this is the place he'd be.
Nothing gives me
a warm, fuzzy feeling
like a mob of armed villagers.
Let's get out of here.
Probably no monster anyway.
Come on.
[ Laughs ]
Wow. Are we glad to see you.
Yeah. Somebody lose a cow
or... something?
[ Growling ]
[ Grunting, Growling ]
You idiots!
They can't understand
a word you're saying!
I don't think
they can understand
a word we're saying.
[ Discord ]
You got it, Mud-boy.
- It's the monster!
- Where?
- Get him!
- [ Growling ]
- Don't let it escape!
- Burn it alive!
No! Skin it alive!
Maybe over there.
Where'd he go?
[ Men Chattering ]
Who are those guys?
Beats me.
Do I look as bad as you?
Yeah.
You know, the one drawback
of life on the run is
missing regular meals.
I am starved.
Wait. Don't eat those.
It's a goosenberry.
They're supposed
to be fermented.
[ Laughs ]
A common mistake
to the untrained eye.
See, this, my friend,
is a farkenberry.
It's a cousin
to the goosenberry, but
with one important difference.
See, your farken doesn't put you
to sleep like your goosen.
If this was a goosenberry,
I'd be sound asleep by now.
Hmm.
Wait a sec.
[ Snores ]
Farkenberries.
Oh, great.
Oh, boy. I could do
with some real boots.
You want boots?
How about big boots?
And the feet to go with 'em.
[ Laughing ]
What the--
- Ares!
- [ Clucking ]
- [ Yawning ]
- Whoa! Hey, don't do that.
[ Autolycus Laughs ]
Hey, you got quite a set
of waffle-stompers there.
Oh. You like 'em?
Hey, you got 'em.
Come on.
Zap 'em again.
What's happening?
What's happening to us?
I don't know!
This is so much fun.
Is that it?
Is that all you've got?
Oh, no.
Not at all.
]
dddd [ Harp
[ Gasps ]
This is beautiful.
Everyone's so pretty.
Well, so are you.
Um, I'll return your shirt
as soon as I find a dress
I like as much.
Looks better on you
than it does on me.
It's always an honor
to have you here,
Hercules.
[ Snaps Fingers ]
We'll give you
our best table.
Thank you, Wolfgang.
It's okay.
Right there.
Sit.
I'm so hungry, I could eat
an entire bucket of slop.
What's this for?
Oh, uh, that goes...
on your lap.
Like this. Yeah.
Here you are.
After this, I'd like to take
a look around by myself,
feel what it's like
to be one of you.
That's a good idea.
I'll be around
if you need me.
This is so exciting.
[ Slurping ]
[ Woman ]
Oh!
Katherine?
This is delicious.
Mmm!
[ Woman ]
That is disgusting.
Eats like an animal,
like a pig!
Hercules, I'm sorry,
but this won't do.
Oh, um--
Of course it will!
[ Slurping ]
[ Gasps ]
It's very good soup.
It's a little salty for my
taste, but it's very good.
Thank you.
Thank you,
I-I suppose.
Mmm!
[ Gasps ]
Oh, boy.
That was close.
Well, the good news is
it can't get any worse.
[ Laughing ]
Gotcha!
It's an abomination.
The only good monster
is a dead monster.
This is not good.
Uh, fellas, can we talk?
Let's kill it
before it destroys our minds!
-[ Man ]
Hold on here!
- Huh?
I am P.T. Barnabus,
founder of the Greatest Show
in Greece.
And I can use this
freak of nature
in my circus.
Follow me, one and all.
A new freak
for the new freak show.
Who you callin' a freak,
you geek?
Actually,
I hate to say this,
but to him, we're the geeks.
Oh, be careful!
Not too close!
Stories of the big-footed,
two-headed forest monster...
has frightened our children
for generations.
Yes. That's why it belongs
in a freak show.
[ Laughs ]
Hideous!
Anybody got a chicken?
Let's see if it bites
the head off.
[ Crowd Laughs ]
Quick.
We better act crazy.
I'd rather go home
with Uncle Carny here
than end up a human pincushion.
Okay.
[ Both Babbling ]
Marvelous!
Spectacular!
I'll pay top dinar.
We gotta get out of here.
What do you suggest?
Run!
[ All Yelling ]
Are we talking
cash on the barrelhead?
[ Babbling ]
They're gaining!
[ Mob Yelling ]
All right!
Hello.
This is another fine mess
you got us into.
I got two words for you:
Discord, Artemis's bow.
That's three words.
Well, whatever.
You know, I can pick
that puny lock in my sleep,
but I actually
think we're safer in here.
Say, underneath these sacks,
we're naked.
Where you been
hiding the pick?
- Don't ask.
- Okay.
[ Children Laughing ]
[ Hisses ]
Freaks. Outcasts.
Dregs of society.
Well, that's life
under the big top.
I was talking about us.
[ Elephant Trumpets ]
Don't antagonize 'em.
For once in your life,
keep your trap shut,
if that's possible.
What, and miss out on all your
insults and witty repartee?
With pleasure!
Oh, go boil your head.
Hey!
No sleeping on the job!
You give me that stick!
I'll ram it down
your fat neck!
Yeah, you bloodsucking
son of a Xiphopagus.
[ Growling ]
[ Babbling ]
See this ferocious
man-eater...
in a fight to the death
with Hippochimora,
the muscle man.
Come to the show!
Come to the circus!
Come to the circus?
Come over here,
and I'll do a high-wire act
on that pasty face of yours!
[ Screaming And Babbling ]
You call that
keeping your cool?
Next thing, they're gonna
wanna throw us to the lions.
Stop it! This is all your fault!
Now go to your corner
and get out of my hair!
Okay, I will!
That's amazing.
It's mating with itself.
Mmm! Goosenberries.
Come one, come all!
Two nights only!
Come to the circus!
Kids get in
for a half a dinar.
A circus?
Sounds like fun.
More fun than
a human sacrifice.
Bloodier too!
Be there.
[ Laughs ]
[ Horse Whinnies ]
Sadie!
Do I know you?
It's me-- Katherine!
Katherine!
I didn't recognize you.
I'm a woman now.
I'm my own master.
Good for you.
I'm proud of you.
You look a little thirsty.
Here, let me give you
a hand.
I've got two now.
[ Giggles ]
Thanks. That hits the spot.
You know how you used
to dream about breaking
out of these traces...
and riding off
into the sunset?
Well, that's what I've done,
and it's wonderful.
I'm so happy for you.
Still, the farm hasn't
been the same without you.
You really lit the place up.
We did have fun,
didn't we?
I just felt like it was
time to move on.
Meet new friends.
And I have.
He's wonderful.
But, Katherine,
your family,
they miss you terribly.
Your parents have been
worried sick about you.
I've been thinking
about them too.
I never meant
to hurt them.
Hey, Herc!
Hey, how are you?
How's the weather
down there? See ya.
[ Man ]
Okay, ready.
[ Girl ]
dd Nana-nana na na
Nana-nana na na dd
dd Nana nana dddd
Don't make faces
at the monster, honey.
But for the grace of the gods,
it could be you in that cage.
[ Mother ]
Now run along.
Ha ha!
[ Blows Raspberry ]
Iolaus? Autolycus?
Oh! Oh!
Boy, am I glad
to see you!
I wish I could say the same,
but you guys are
makin' me kind of queasy.
- What are you doing in there?
- Six shows a night,
that's what.
Yeah.
Hey, now that the big guy's
here, this gig is over.
Yeah, I'm with you, buddy.
Come on.
[ Babbling ]
Here we go.
-Let's get out of here.
Come on.
- Will you quit pushing me?
I'm trying to get down
the stairs.
You're steppin' on my feet!
Come on.
What are you doing?
Hey, those are... big feet.
Well, you know what they say
about big feet, don't you?
- Big boots?
- Will you guys quit it?
Chains of Hephaestus.
Ares. Discord.
Chicken.
Yeah. 'Nough said?
Uh, yeah, I get the picture.
Here. Let me help.
Hold still.
One minute.
Wha-- Oh!
It's better over here.
[ Laughs ]
Very funny. Come on.
Get us out of these.
Um, sorry.
Come on.
Yeah.
Ready?
[ Laughing ]
Thanks, Herc.
What's the matter?
You lose your shirt?
Oh, uh, it's my new look.
I'll catch up with you later.
I've gotta go see a goddess
about a pig.
Well, I wish I could say
it's been fun, but it hasn't.
Yeah.
Good riddance.
You say anything about this,
and I'll deny everything.
No problem.
[ Brush Rustling ]
Okay, whoever you are,
you think you can sneak up
on the King of Thieves,
you have got another think--
Sweet Mother of Zeus.
[ Screams ]
Callipus! Callipus!
Don't go.
I won't hurt you.
It's me-- Katherine.
[ Hercules ]
They don't know you.
We grew up together.
But you're different now.
It won't be so easy fitting in.
Believe me, I, uh-- I know.
I'm not ever gonna fit in
this world with you, am I?
[ Squealing ]
Hercules, will you
please take me home,
where I belong?
[ Grunting ]
It's a mon-- It's a mon--
M-M-Monster!
C-C-Coming for us!
Okay, wait.
You mean a real monster
did this to you?
What kind of monster?
It's a--
It's... b-b-big!
Big?
Ares said there'd be
a big surprise waiting for us.
Okay, come on.
Spit it out.
Okay.
[ Growls ]
[ Clucking, Screaming ]
[ Growls, Screams ]
Okay, it's big.
Now, uh-- Sounds like?
[ Babbling ]
[ Laughing ]
Hey, wait, wait!
This is getting us nowhere.
Okay, where was this monster?
[ Mumbles ]
Okay, let's go.
Ah-ah-ah!
Wrong direction.
See, if Ares is behind this,
there's no escaping it.
Might as well suck it up
and face it.
Come on. Come on.
Whatever it is,
it belongs in my circus.
[ Woman ]
This is exciting!
[ Screams ]
It's all right. It's okay.
Calm down. It's okay.
And they callus
weirdos.
Is this the spot?
Baba!
Wait a minute.
What kind of monster
could've made these tracks?
They look kind of familiar.
A chi-chi--
A chi-chi-chi--
Hey! Act it out again.
That's funny.
[ Crowd Gasping ]
This feels big.
[ Babbles ]
[ Heavy Footstep ]
Look! It's the monster!
Th-Th-That's it!
It's gigantic!
It's colossal.
[ Clucking ]
It's a chicken.
It's-- It's Discord.
Why did the chicken
cross the road?
To kill us all!
- [ Screams ]
- [ Squawks ]
Run!
Oh, where's Hercules?
He's snoozin' when he
should be bruisin'.
[ Iolaus ]
As soon as Hercules is around,
he'll be here.
She's pretty hard to miss.
Meantime, we're on our own.
What do you mean, we, sidekick?
You're the one that turned her
into a chicken.
She's lookin' at you
like you're a drumstick.
Knock it off!
-[ Squawking ]
-I'll try and distract her.
You come up with a plan.
Yeah, easy for you.
Hey! Hey, chicken!
Come on!
[ Screams ]
[ Barnabus ]
Come on! Don't waste time.
Get in the tent.
Come on!
Hurry, hurry, hurry, hurry!
Hey, what're you doing?
We gotta get everybody
in the tent to safety.
Come on!
Are you crazy? This tent
won't stop that bird.
I gotta get outta here.
[ Woman Screams ]
Iolaus, I hope you know
what you're doing.
[ Screaming ]
All right, everybody listen up.
Step away from the sides
of the tent.
Remain calm.
Everything is under control.
Oww!
You? What happened
to our distraction?
[ Babbling ]
Yeah, I know how you feel.
Come on.
We gotta get these people
out of this tent.
All right, everyone,
out you go. Nice and easy.
Single file now.
No pushing.
There is no reason to worry.
Hey, hey, hey.
Not a good place to be. Go.
There's a big--
Gotta go. Safety, safety.
Come on. Everybody.
- Iolaus, let's get out of here.
- Okay.
[ Screams ]
[ Screaming ]
So much for
your plan beta.
Don't look at me.
I'm usually causing trouble.
[ Screaming ]
[ Cloth Tearing ]
- [ Growls ]
- [ Stuttering ] Chi-chi-chi--
Go! Go, go!
Everybody run! Run!
Get out of here! Come on!
[ Discord Growls ]
- Time for a new plan.
- What do you got?
[ Squawking ]
I got a good one.
What?
- Run like Tartarus.
-[ Roaring ]
My baby! My baby!
- There!
- [ Crying ]
Uh, I'll get the baby.
You come up with
plan... gamma.
I got you, buddy.
Here's your baby, ma'am.
Oh, thank you.
I'll collect later.
Plan gamma. Plan gamma.
Plan--
Come on, let's go.
No, wait.
- What are you doing?
- Plan gamma.
- Goosenberries?
- Yeah.
[ Screaming ]
[ Crunching ]
Oh!
[ Screaming ]
Okay, genius,
how do we get her
to take her medicine?
I'll distract her.
You do the rest.
Hey, you, ya big chicken!
Come on! Come on!
Is that all ya got?
Give it to me. Come on.
I can take anything
you got to give.
What do you got
under those feathers?
[ Laughs ]
For once,
you're thinkin'.
Okay, say the word.
[ Blows Raspberry ]
Come on! Give me that!
[ Roars ]
Come on!
- Now!
- [ Yodels ]
[ Laughs ]
Say good night, Big Bird.
Yeah!
[ Roaring ]
[ Autolycus ]
Come on, goosenberries,
do your stuff.
[ Screaming ]
[ Laughing ]
You know, I haven't
laughed so hard...
since the entire Mycenaean army
drank rancid water
and got the runs.
[ Continues Laughing ]
Let's go,
my little chickadee.
[ Chuckling ]
Iolaus, wait till
Hercules hears...
that we took on a monster
all by ourselves.
Yeah.
You gonna tell him
it was a chicken?
[ Chuckles ]
That'll be our secret.
[ Laughing ]
[ Yawning ]
- You know, Iolaus?
- Yeah?
You're not half bad.
If I ever need a partner,
you might just be
the lucky one.
Thanks, Autolycus.
I appreciate that,
but, uh,
I've already got a pa--
I love being human, Hercules.
It's just not me.
I guess you were right
all along.
Now who know
who you really are.
I also know
I'm gonna miss you.
I'll miss you too.
We're ready, Aphrodite.
I had a feeling
this would come in handy,
although why anyone would wanna
trade in a beautiful bod
like that is beyond me.
I just love
the way that works.
[ Grunting ]
They know me now, Hercules.
I'm home.
One of these days,
we're gonna have a long talk,
and I wanna hear
all about it.
[ Squealing, Grunting ]
Good-bye, Katherine.
[ Katherine ]
It's so great
to see you guys.
I missed you so much.
You won't believe
what happened to me.
I met the greatest human.