BOOGEYMEN
The Killer Compilation
Which're the most inhuman,
grotesque, demonic,
psychotic monsters
ever to appear on film...
...all in one
in same collection:
"BOOGEYMEN"
You can't kill the boogeyman.
This subtitle was formed
by 'cobra35' (from Turkiye)
"Have fun!!!"
He is here...
PINHEAD
from Clive Barker's "HELLRAISER"
Demon guardian of Hell
Called to Earth to
punish human sinners
Devoted to the art
of torture
We'll tear your soul apart.
What the hell is that?
Frank.
No!
We have to hear it
from your own lips.
This isn't for your eyes.
You set me up, bitch!
Jesus wept.
FREDDY KRUEGER
from "A NIGHTMARE ON ELM STREET"
Bastard son of
100 maniacs
Burned alive by his
Elm Street neighbors
Stalks you in
your dreams
Whatever you do,
don't fall asleep.
Somebody there?
Tina!
Who the hell is that?
Now...
Shit.
Please, God...
This...
...is God.
Tina!
Watch this.
Nancy! Open the door!
Nancy!
Rod, help me!
Help me!
WISHMASTER
Ancient evil ghoul
Grants the wishes of mortals
but steals their souls.
Takes on human appearances
As you wish..
Geez!
Asshole.
Catch you.
ANATOMY LAB
Hey, who is the teachers' pet, huh?
Why the hell are working
in the dark, man?
Wait a minute...
Who are you?
What the fuck?
Oh my God!
Might understand!
This is not something you wish to see.
Very well.
My eyes! My eyes!
Oh my God!
I can't see!
You bastard!
My eyes!
LEATHERFACE
from "The Texas Chain Saw Massacre"
Cross-dressing
chainsaw killer
Base on the real-life
mass murderer Ed Gein
Makes his masks from
the human skin of his victims
GHOSTFACE
from "SCREAM"
Disturbed high school student
Stalks beautiful teenage girls
Inspired by Florida's
"Gainesville Ripper"
Tatum, just get in the car--
Hello, Sidney.
Uh, hi, who is this?
You tell me.
Well, I-I have no idea.
Scary night, isn't it?
With the murders and all,
it's like right out of a
horror movie or something.
Randy, you gave yourself away.
Are you calling from work,
'cause Tatum's on her way over.
Do you like scary movies,
Sidney?
I like that thing you're doing
with your voice, Randy. It's sexy.
What's your favourite
scary movie?
Oh, come on. You know
I don't watch that shit.
Why not? Too scared?
No, no. It's just, what's
the point? They're all the same.
Some stupid killer stalking some
big-breasted girl who can't act...
...who's always
running up the stairs...
...when she should be going out
the front door. It's insulting.
Are you alone in the house?
Randy, that's so unoriginal.
I'm disappointed in you.
Maybe that's because I'm not Randy.
So, who are you?
The question isn't
"Who am I?"
The question is
"Where am I?"
S- S-So, where are you?
Your front porch.
Why would you be calling
from my front porch?
That's the original part.
Oh, yeah?
Well, I call your bluff.
So, where are you?
Right here.
Can you see me right now?
Uh-huh.
Uh-huh. Okay.
What am I doin'? Huh?
Huh? What am I doin'?
Hello!
Nice try, Randy. Tell Tatum
to hurry up, okay? Bye now.
If you hang up on me,
you'll die just like your mother!
Do you wanna die, Sidney?
Your mother sure didn't.
Fuck you, you cretin!
No!
Shit!
Home or Phone number to call:
Calling 911... Ringing...
Connected to 911.
911 Operator:
- What is your emergency?
LEPRECHAUN
2,000 year old demonic elf
with evil magic powers
Razor-sharp teeth
and claws
Viciously kills to
protect his pot of gold
Three to left...
To right...
There you go.
I want ME gold coin!
Me coin.
It's not nice to steal gold coins
from a Leprechaun.
Bad, so boner...
bad, so boner...
I'll be back.
Now, we're going to play.
Do you want to play with me?
Oh, no, no...
# This old Lep, he played one. #
# He played pogo on his lung. #
Teach you to steal ME gold?
Can't let dirty shoes now, can we?
There.
Nice and shiny.
He'll bounce back it no time.
CHUCKY
from the "CHILD'S PLAY" series
Demonic killer doll
Possessed by the
soul of a serial killer
Needs a boy's body to
become human again
Sorry Jack,
Chucky is back...
Peekaboo!
Please, let me
out of here, Andy.
It's dark in here.
I promise I won't
kill anyone else. Okay?
Now open the goddamn door!
Let me out, you little dick!
Let me the fuck out!
Andy, I told you
to stay in your seat.
Come out of there!
Open this door right now.
Andy, come out
this very second.
Andy! Andy!
Andy?
Andy, this isn't funny.
You've been very naughty,
Miss Kettlewell.
CANDYMAN
Sinister hook-wielding
ghost
Appears when his name
is said five times in a mirror
Seeks a female
companion to take to Hell
Candyman...
Helen...
Yes?
Who is that?
Helen...
I came for you.
Do I know you?
No... no...
...but you doubted me.
I'm sorry. I have to go.
No need to leave yet.
But I'm late.
You were not content
with the stories,
so I was obliged to come.
Be my victim.
I am the writing on the wall,
the whisper in the classroom.
Without these things
I am nothing,
so now I must shed
innocent blood.
Come with me.
SIMON
from "THE UGLY"
Scar-faced serial killer
with telekinetic powers
Possessed by the Uglies,
demons who induce his murderous rages
Insatiable need to kill
How did you feel when you killed them?
I felt free.
I was happy for the briefest moment.
Simon...
Where are they now?
You still see?
You have no idea what it is like for me.
Why don't you tell me?
You couldn't possible know
what I got it through.
Come back to bed.
I want to know what you go through.
Simon.
What do you want to do?
Kill the bitch...
Kill the bitch!
What?
What is it Simon?
They won't leave me alone
until I've done it.
Each time, they make it harder
and harder and harder not to...
...until I have it done.
What do you have to do?
Kill the bitch...
What?
You look out so vain!
Look!
FISHERMAN
from "I KNOW WHAT YOU DID LAST SUMMER"
Mysterious killer in
black fishing gear
Wields a deadly metal hook
Stalks the teens who left him
for dead after a horrible car accident
Elsa, open the door now!
Please, Jesus Christ, hurry!
- Please, please...
- I'm coming. - Come on!
- Please!
- The Broad Street entrance is open.
I'm being attacked.
You're what?
Lock the other door,
I'll call the police.
- What is going on?
- Just do what I say, god damn it!
Come on, come on...
Elsa...
Elsa?
Elsa, where are you?
No!
CAMILLA
from "THE GUARDIAN"
Occupation: Nanny
Possessed by the spirit
of an ancient tree...
...that feeds off the blood
of your newborn baby
What is its story without woman?
I mean, sho cooks,
she cleans,
she takes care
of the baby...
What else she do?
- I need the child.
- No!
Before the blood changes.
THE DENTIST
Doctor Alan Feinstone, D.D.S.
Sadistically tortures his patients
Snaps in reaction to plaque,
cavities...
...and his wife's adultery
Open wide...
Do you hear how she--
she hits the highnote...
so-- so perfectly...
...from the depths of her soul?
She sings of love.
All love.
We're gonna lose our table.
Brook.
Please humour me.
Alan, I mean, this really
doesn't seem like a good time.
Brook, it's our anniversary.
Pretty, please?
Just enough.
We wouldn't wanna lose you.
You thought to fool me, huh?
Only I've been watching you.
I've been watching
what you've become...
...filthy...
...just like the rest of them.
You, Paula Roberts...
Matt...
You wouldn't want me to cut out
your tongue, would you?
What would Matt think?
You wouldn't be much used to him.
Then...
Now, you'll pay...
...all that you've done to me.
the TALL MAN
from "PHANTASM"
Occupation: Mortician
Transforms human corpses
into zombie dwarves
Impales his enemies with
killer flying spheres
You play
a good game, boy...
Now you die!
Oh shit!
BLADE
from "THE PUPPETMASTER"
Leader of a gang
of killer puppets
Obeys the sadistic will
of the Puppetmaster
One hand is a hook,
the other a knife
Let me go!
Neil...
No...
no, stop.
No... Stop.
I'm a different...
Get away!
No! Stop!
Stop!
NORMAN BATES
from "PSYCHO"
Caretaker of the
Bates Motel
Likes to watch
young blondes in the shower
Kills anyone that gets
between him and his mother
Well, a boy's best friend
is his mother.
You look frightened. Have I been
saying something frightening?
I don't know
what you've been saying.
I've been talking about your mother,
about your motel.
- How you gonna do it?
- Do what?
Buy a new one
in a new town...
...where you won't have
to hide your mother.
Why don't you just get in
your car and drive away, ok?
Where will you get
the money to do that?
- Or do you already have it
socked away? - Shut up!
A lot of it.
Forty thousand dollars.
I bet your mother knows
where the money is...
...and what you did to get it.
I think she'll tell us.
Where's that girl
you came here with?
Where is she?
Mrs. Bates, it's...
Norman Bates!
JASON VOORHEES
from "JASON GOES TO HELL: THE FINAL FRIDAY"
Original campground killer
Drowned as a child at
Camp Crystal Lake
Returnes from the dead
to avenge his mother's death
MICHAEL MYERS
from "HALLOWEEN"
Committed at age six
to a mental asylum...
...after killing his sister
Escaped 15 years later
What was living behind
that boy's eyes...
...was purely and simply evil.
I think he'll come back.
Babies...
We're gonna take a little walk.
Was it the boogeyman?
- I'm scared.
- There's nothing to be scared of.
Are you sure?
How?
I killed him.
You can't kill the boogeyman.
Get in there!
Come on, Tommy!
Now, lock the door!
Tommy...
Unlock the door.
Come here.
Now just listen to me...
I want you to go down the
stairs and out the front door.
And I want you to go down the
street to the Mackenzies' house...
I want you to tell them to call the police.
And tell them to send them over here.
- Laurie...
- Now, do you understand me?
- Yes.
- Go. Do as I say.
Get help! Get help!
Come on!
Was that the boogeyman?
As a matter of fact, it was.
the 5 SCARIEST MOVIES of all time
1. THE EXORCIST
2. HALLOWEEN
3. THE SHINING
4. A NIGHTMARE ON ELM STREET
5. SCREAM
SOURCE: TOTAL MAGAZINE
the SCARIEST BOOGEYMEN on film
SOURCE: misterpoll.com
BOOGEYMAN BODY COUNT
SOURCE: HORROR MOVIE SURVIVAL GUIDE
THE TALL MAN:
79+ and 1 dog
MICHAEL MYERS:
75 and 4 dogs
83% OF CHILDREN
ARE SCARED OF THE BOOGEYMAN!
SOURCE:
"WHEN YOUR CHILD IS AFRAID"
Not scared, are you?
This subtitle was formed
by 'cobra35' (from Turkiye)
"I hope, you had fun!!!"