Come quickly.
Careful.
San Ms. Dena!
San Ms. Dena?
- Yes.
Please, help my son.
He has in recent days
more voices.
He thinks that something would do him harm.
Tell her.
- I hear his voice.
It is increasingly stronger.
What did he say?
- Nothing.
Tell me what he said!
He has a silver chain from a
car stolen from gypsies.
We have tried to chain
return.
But they did not accept him.
Where is he?
- Here.
Bring him inside.
Holy Father, we ask you, is to
mercy on this sick boy.
No ... my son!
Calm, quiet, we come down.
Watch out, away from there, fast!
Help me!
We will meet again ...
Here!
DRAG ME TO HELL
Repeat the following sentences, literally,
as they are pronounced.
There is no error possible, as the
properly quoted.
You get a good sound when the mouth is round.
A good sound when the mouth is round.
Round, round.
I think this is going to work.
I call this afternoon and let you know.
Thank you very much.
- Sure.
Thank you
- Have a nice day.
You also, a pleasant goodbye.
Mr. Jack ...
Have you already taken a decision on
who the new assistant manager?
I'm still not, but the
date it between you and Stu.
Stu, who new?
- I know he is new,
but he is very enthusiastic and
because we love.
Stu is someone who goes on and
dare to take tough decisions.
I am also able to make difficult
decisions.
I'll let you know, once I
have decided, right?
In the meantime, please me by not
qualified procedures leading, right?
Well.
And ... do you mind now
lunch break to take?
No problem.
- And maybe on your way back,
a turkey sandwich for me take.
A turkey sandwich, a good choice.
- That you can do for me, thanks.
With sharp mustard.
You must still sign.
Beloney and Johnson.
- Oh yes, of course.
Professor Well, congratulations, with which you
has been very interesting.
Thank you.
I thought you would have a beer lust.
I am also a bit disappointing.
Oh, this thing, it does not stop me.
Christine, you do it but.
I get a new one.
- I tell you that you are crazy.
Piece.
What's broken?
You're smart and sexy and amazing.
Oh, I almost forgot.
- I found this at the bank.
What is this?
My God, it is a standing Liberty 1929
and it is almost cool.
Was this just at the bank?
- Yes, really.
That is in my nurd 'like
coin collection.
Thanks honey, I think
him very much.
Well then.
- Day, until later.
Until later, okay?
Roger Dalton.
- Hello, darling.
Hi, Mom.
- What are you doing?
Christine was just before lunch and
We have a few things through.
O, from the farm?
- Yes, I already have one years courting her.
She was eating ... we were eating.
I know, she is very nice.
- Yes, that's it, I can not wait for you ...
You know your father and I ...
- I told her ...
have certain expectations for you.
- I do not get ...
Like that handsome girl
I played with tennis.
You know she graduated cum laude at Yale.
And she is now a successful lawyer.
- Yes, you told me.
That's the kind of girl, where I
would like to see them.
Mom ...
- It's the kind of woman,
you really could help, social and
hence your career.
and there would now have to think.
- Mom, I ...
You can not play with little girls
of the farm.
It is now time to find a true partner.
Christine, you have my work,
confused.
I did not.
- Yes, I said I did not post.
You did not say.
It does not matter, it is okay.
Mr. Jacks.
- What Winny?
Do you drink?
- Yes, I love drink.
What do I need this, Sunday,
I can not use.
This cerises?
- Yes.
These are great seats.
Here you warm.
Yes, hot.
- Are you sure it is good?
Thank you then.
Can you help me?
Of course, what can I do for you?
This paper, my house and all
my other possessions, personals.
Please let them stop.
Mrs. ...
- Ganush.
Mrs. Ganush, the bank lets you know they your
property on the 325 Brandon Street,
Today, confiscate.
But that is my house, all 30 years.
And I've always paid me to my eye
lost by that disease.
I hope soon to have money, I have
just a little more time.
I do not think my manager you
gives more credit.
Please, do not you try?
Well.
- God bless u.
God bless u.
I have an older woman, who for delay
of a mortgage term calls.
She has a fixed income and at the moment
some medical problems.
Can we do something to help her?
It seems, she has already
twice been postponed.
In these cases we put
attachment of the collateral.
And the bank earns a substantial amount
to costs.
But then we put her out of her house.
Yes, that's a difficult decision.
You must decide.
I rule it.
Mrs Ganush ... sorry, mrs Ganush,
but a delay is not possible.
What?
- I would like to help,
but it is not ...
- No ... Please, it's my house.
Where should I live?
You gave your granddaughter as reference,
maybe you can stay with her.
Since I do not want to burden her.
And there are fine and residential care
facilities ...
I want in my house.
I would never want to live in such homes.
I really, really sorry.
I am a proud woman and
difficulties have now.
And ... I've never come to have questions.
But now, I pray thee
I will do everything for you.
- Mrs. Ganush, please scroll down.
I pray you, on my mother's grave ...
I pray you
- Please, let loose, let loose!
Security!
Stop!
Here Billy, here it is.
- I'm coming.
You ... you move me crazy ..
I pray for you and you put me crazy.
I think you are nothing
to do, ma'am.
Come along.
Mrs Ganush ...
Help me here.
Come on!
Something I had never seen.
You okay?
You did very well, you know?
Good night, until tomorrow.
I've just seen that McPherson loan.
This is an impressive piece of work.
Thank you.
Would you like to take this home to
complete it,
because I would like to regional
Deputy Director show tomorrow morning.
Of course, I do like.
- Really?
Thank you.
Oh, and the position of assistant manager
concerned, are you on top.
You've put me crazy.
You get what you deserve.
I beat you, you witch!
Now will you come to me have to beg.
They send someone to talk to her,
she will not bother you.
Then you do not need to think of her.
I call Mr. Jacks
and ask him if he 's night with you to
The car will run, right?
All right.
You say it is good.
But it's still okay with you, right?
Yeah, it goes well.
What, what is going on?
It's just ... perhaps, I had her do
delay should give.
Chris, no, you do not.
The bank gave her 2 times already postponed it?
If you do not pay your mortgage
you lose your house,
what is expected then that woman?
This is not your fault, do not worry.
What is, is there something wrong?
Did you know?
- What?
Really?
No, what do you mean?
I know this sounds weird, but I
want to go to a soothsayer.
Now, you kidding?
Come on Chris, I will predict your future.
Eh ... in the near future, we get into the
car and go home to relax.
Do not!
Why, by what happened
to that old woman?
Chris, I really think that we should go home now.
Would you do it for me?
If my students could see me now ...
is the only lesson I can teach them,
hypocritical, one on one.
So many things to choose from, but
not what I seek.
And that's a weird dried head of a monkey.
Oh, wait, never mind, he is al
I'm Rham Jas.
Nice that you are there.
I'm Christine, and it is Clay.
But did you know not?
I'm just kidding.
What can I do for you?
- I want you predict my future.
Can you?
- I can see some energy.
Sometimes that energy says something about
the things to come.
That is $ 60, please.
- Are you serious?
Yes.
- 60 ...
Is not that a bit expensive, do?
- You're not serious.
Please, do it.
- Well, come on, Chris.
Wait, wait, I pay.
Oh, you know what, here it is.
Please.
A platinum card, very well.
Thank you.
Here, here.
- Thanks.
No, please.
So you want to know something about your fate?
- Yes.
Very well, let what the future
has in store for you.
Freud said that nothing in the future
you lot had to do,
but rather something that the subconscious,
created to make choices.
True, but you can not the world
all contain
only with the mind.
Oh, Karl Jung.
- Yes.
From his writings.
Psychological characterisations.
- Favorite psychologist of our time.
He was at least not afraid to God in his
considerations, to take.
Well, he was not afraid of God ...
Clay, please.
- Well let's start, come on.
Shall we?
I'm ready.
Give me your hand, please.
- Okay.
You work with money.
That's right.
And you've recently lost something.
No, no, I do not.
- No, you do not lose anything ...
but there is something taken away from you.
No.
A knot.
- Oh my God.
Yes.
What does it matter if it's a
node is lost ...
Clay, which was very strange, the old woman
pulled a button from my sleeve.
Why would she do that?
- Do you sometimes just silent?
I think this is enough for tonight.
What's wrong?
I'm tired and I see it
late become.
I will of course refund your money.
- Wait, wait ...
Have you seen something?
You will be followed by a bad spirit.
- What do you mean?
No ...
- Have you disturbed the dead in the cemetery?
No.
- Something with a Ouija board or black magic?
Okay, calm down, man, come on.
Wait, wait, no, no.
Perhaps, someone has cursed you.
But how he knew all that.
Did some ... that you had lost a button?
He knew little, he gambled well
on a few things ...
He makes you upset and leave you with
all these questions.
And of course with his business card.
Come on Chris, he is a crook.
But he wanted the money, he wanted
rendering, remember?
Well, he did have one attempt, but he has
ultimately, is not accepted?
Yeah, I guess.
I need to go check on the
repair of your car goes, manage that?
Yes.
- Okay.
Kitty, care for her.
- I'm back in an hour.
Here, hold it against your lip.
- Thank you.
I can not believe they came here
is, this is really ridiculous.
It was not.
Who was it?
I do not know, I could not see.
- Of course it was, that could not otherwise.
No, Clay, there was none.
- It was a man, Chris, it was someone.
The light was out and I saw who it was ...
- Clay, there was nobody here!
But who did this?
Who has beaten you in your face?
I think the reaction on the fact
she was attacked, earlier today.
A classic case of post traumatic stress.
Yes, she shows signs of panic,
is a bit paranoid, so ...
Wait, I will just exhaust you.
- No, no, it succeeds.
How are you?
- It's better.
Especially after the doctor has explained to me.
He said that victims of violence,
relive the trauma.
I did not ... did not know what it was.
That happens sometimes.
I ... I feel ...
a little embarrassed.
- That you kidding, no ...
You do for me never be ashamed.
Listen, I thought we maybe small trip
could make.
We deal Saturday and then the train
to Santa Barbara ...
The cabin of your parents?
Yes, if you like.
- Oh, my God, how nice.
Yeah, okay.
- That seems so exciting.
Honey, you'll be great.
There is much to see.
There are trees and it is very private ...
It is amazing, really good.
I think we need ...
and then we ...
we can just talk.
What?
What's on?
I could ... I could not wake up.
It's okay.
It is good.
Come on, it was only a dream.
That is the rental car they
have delivered this morning.
That is fine.
- Certainly.
I love you.
- I love you.
Hey baby ... try today, no old
ladies angry, okay?
Hey, Christine ... are you just here?
- You thought I would come later?
Haha, very funny, Christine.
What is this?
What do you want?
I want you to teach me the right procedures.
I'm busy, can we do tomorrow?
Well.
- Okay.
I would say you now Mr. Jacks
not have time, maybe ...
No, no ... Okay, I'll do it.
Well, we talked about the guidelines for
the collateral of the loans.
Okay, Latsia Client is a company that no
traditional bank financing can do.
And ...
Get your dirty hands off my desk!
Christine blood ... Brown.
Christine ... your nose.
Of course, you have a minute?
Here, let me help.
- No, no, I got this under control.
What is wrong with you?
Mr. Jack ...
- Have what I got in my mouth?
Oh my God!
- Got it in my mouth?
Come along, here.
I am so sorry!
Oh my God!
Have I got something in my mouth?
What is it?
Hi, I come to Sylvia Ganush, is she here?
Who are you?
I am ... a friend of hers.
A white ...
I know who you are, my grandmother said
all that you would come.
You're the woman from the bank.
Those who are taking away her house.
It was actually the bank that taking away the house.
I only work there.
I even tried the house of
your grandmother, to get back.
But that was not my boss.
And now you stand here in my portal
and lying to me.
No.
You were once a fat, is not it?
Yes.
- I can see.
You're not welcome here.
Wait ... I must see her, she must forgive me.
And I give her the house back.
- You're everything to make is that it?
Yes.
Come on.
Where is she?
Get off me!
Will you still make it up to her?
You deserve everything that happens to you now.
I think you will be haunted by Alamia.
That is the word that the old woman used.
The black goat, only called by the
Gypsies, for their worst curses.
The first 3 days will appear as a Alamia
bad spirit,
who torments his victim.
Then he reveals himself,
as a collector of souls and pursue
owner of the cursed object.
A cursed object, what object?
Something of the victim is taken,
cursed and then returned.
This?
What if I just burned?
The condition of the node does not matter,
You're still the owner.
Alamia will still take you.
- Taking over where?
How to get here from?
You can try to deceive the mind.
The simplest way would be a blood sacrifice
and a small animal would be sacrificed.
Maybe a chicken.
No, not really. I'm vegetarian and I
worked in the puppy heart, for God's sake.
I no dead animals.
You'll be surprised what you would do if
Alamia, you will get.
This is how it should happen.
Come here, Kitty.
Here, Kitty, Kitty.
Chris.
Oh, there you are.
what are you doing?
At the bank they said that once you left
and you had answered the phone.
Is that blood?
No, why would it be blood?
Honey, there's blood on your sleeve.
Blood you?
- No, it's just tomato juice.
I cut a tomato in the kitchen and
it should come on my sleeve.
Hey, Chris, why do we dinner
not another time?
You've had a few difficult days.
Maybe better.
No, I want to go to that dinner.
- I know, but ...
are you sure you feel good?
Honestly ... was not.
But I think everything is okay.
I really believe that.
What do you think?
You look beautiful.
Gosh, what a beautiful day.
- Yes, that is.
Within it will be nice.
They'll like it.
Clay.
- Mom, good to see you.
This is Christine, this is my mom, Trudy.
Hi, Christine.
- Hello, nice to meet you.
Please, come in, this way.
Dad, how is it?
Good to see you.
Eh ... This is Christine, Christine,
This is my father, Larry.
You have a beautiful house.
- Oh, thank you.
Can I pour?
- A wine?
Yes, please.
Okay, Cannula.
- I'll be back.
For me a Chardonnay.
- Yeah, baby.
I hope you do not mind.
- Oh, what fun.
Self made?
- Yes.
And how do you call that pie?
- It is ... a harvest pie.
Is that something you created on the farm?
- No ...
I mean not.
We did that once, when we ...
geese have had ...
Around the harvest, that is when the
a thick layer of goose fat to make.
And that makes for a rich cake.
Well, then ... Thank you.
Look, please.
- Come along to the dining room.
Yes, that's good.
- Good.
Oh, Jesus.
- Hey, you, stop.
I understand that no beast.
I hate cats.
What weird saying, he is normally so sweet.
That's okay.
I also had a cat, I understand.
You have a cat.
Whether he should have walked away.
How would I know?
You know how cats are, they come and go.
That is true.
Well, let's sit down.
- Yes, yes, please.
How are you collecting coins, son?
That's my father's favorite topic.
Christine, just got a standing "Liberty"
penny found me at the bank.
Oh, really?
- Apart not?
Yes, it is a rare coin.
That job at the counter of the bank,
is so difficult for you.
With all that counting and repeating ...
it'll be boring.
Yes, you're right, but I
'm not a desk assistant.
O?
- Mom, Christine handles loans.
It makes loans to small businesses and
private houses at the bank.
And they will probably get a promotion, so ...
Is not it, Chris?
If successful, the account which I
am doing, that would certainly help.
This is an important loan.
It is the biggest of my branch,
has ever issued.
And that is how you ended up?
Well ... I read the "Wall Street Journal '
and was a medical products company
against, who wanted to expand out.
But who have not had the liquidity.
So I presented the director a formula,
their long-term loans to restructure.
It sounds like it goes very well
with you, Christine.
Your mother must be very proud of you.
I think so.
I have my mother, not recently seen.
- Why is that?
It is ... it is a private matter.
I talk with Christine.
Since my father is deceased,
they do not talk much.
She resides on the farm and
is much like himself, because ...
Want?
Because her husband is deceased,
she wants her own.
Why ...
- Because my mother is an alcoholic.
I'm sorry.
That is really not something to be ashamed.
I must tell you honestly that I really
find refreshing.
My father had a drinking problem and
I was ashamed to admit it.
You have backbone.
I thought that last girl like that you
brought, what was her name?
Alice.
We do not ...
- Alicia.
Alicia.
- That was very bad.
Bad mannered and absolutely no ambition.
He met her through the internet.
That is the reason.
On the Internet ... Who says that?
Did you expect of him?
- No, not really.
Shall we take some of your pie?
- He looks very hot.
You'll not only enjoy it,
if you hate delicious things.
Harvest pie huh?
- That's right.
I want the recipe.
- It tastes very full, right?
Did you hear anything?
No, are you okay?
How do you know?
- Yes very nice.
Mom, I met her via the internet.
That is a bit misleading ...
You must not do so
find no partner.
You can change the things you hear or things,
they write, no trust.
And the pictures are often not real.
Is not that so?
Yes, that's true.
- It's not that you must think,
that people of good birth and successfully,
flirts off potential, could be.
You're talking about bars.
- That is such a strange situation, it is ...
... do not you, Christine?
No, no, course not.
What we have done, we are together
met in a bar, right Chris?
Oh my God, yes, that is.
- Shit.
You must set priorities.
The agency relationship was not Mom,
it was a bar.
So, we met in a bar.
And we agreed via the Internet.
You okay?
Okay?
Here, have some ...
It was something from her plate.
Oh my God!
Sorry, I do not know ...
Okay, I hear you, leave me alone,
leave me the hell alone!
Please, there is none.
I think I should go.
- Yeah, I think that is the best.
Hey Chris ...
- Do not go after her, she is sick.
No, she does my help.
- Let her go.
Chris!
What's on?
Well, I did what you said!
I've killed that pussy.
You're a jerk!
These are illustrious and powerful forces, we
face. There are no guarantees!
You should talk directly with the black spirit.
You should avoid it steals your soul.
And fast.
I know someone who can help us.
And I should trust you?
Tomorrow is the third day.
Alamia then come after you.
We must not let this happen!
But you must understand ...
that the woman who can help us,
themselves in serious danger.
And she will not do for free.
What you need from me?
$ 10,000 ... cash.
Tomorrow.
Mr. Jacks.
- Yes.
This is a bit strange for me
and I know that it is not official.
But I was wondering if I advance
could get.
With regard to promotion to
assistant manager?
Yes. One of my family is seriously ill.
Not fatal, but it is possible.
- Christine ...
There is a problem.
The McPherson contract
canceled last night.
What?
- Yes.
Just when I had said that the regional manager
This is great loan was coming ...
I heard they had closed a deal
with "First National".
I still have a call to what whores
exactly happened, but ...
Now does not this look so good
for you and me.
So the promotion to assistant manager,
is postponed.
I even think that anything that happened,
this job I will have to give Stu.
Stu ... I understand.
Sorry, look, if you
family problems,
you might have to take time off today.
These things happen.
What is that?
3800 for everything.
- Includes my jewelry?
Included.
- But this is much more valuable.
Please?
This is everything I have, I pray you
It is a choice of parts.
Chris ... Chris.
Honey?
I thought you would not eat.
I thought ... I'm late but,
I even eat ice cream.
I've paid Rham Jas.
What ... you love me for a fool.
I paid him.
- What, I thought you did not believe me.
I do not know, I still believe.
I really do not know, but I do know,
that you believe in here.
I know how important it is for you and
how much pain you do it.
And uh ...
and I also remember, I remember one
promise, which I did and was in love with you.
I told myself that I ...
I would always watch over you.
And you should care.
So I let him pay.
Remember the day you
was in love with me?
To the second even.
Oh my God.
Are you sure I would go with
to within?
He said I just had to come.
- Yes, he told me.
Christine, I can imagine ...
Shaun San Dena.
Welcome.
- Pleasant.
Shaun San Dena is an experienced medium.
Furthermore, she has had contact with Alamia.
I am the spirit come first,
many years ago,
in this house.
And ... what happened?
I lost ... the soul of a boy ...
the beast.
I have waited many years for me
to take revenge.
And bad thing to destroy.
Can I be on?
Please?
tonight ...
Will I have the chance.
But for him to call,
I need your help.
Can you strong enough?
I will try.
My deceased husband, Sandok,
was also a medium.
He has chosen this house because he felt
that certain forces are present.
In this house there are some ...
conditions exist.
You can find some open ports, so
we can see what happens.
Certain actions can
a kind of door opening,
where we can go through.
But also, so we can feel things ...
what to do in this world.
And in her world so others can come.
Please, sit down.
What happens?
Everything we do is to help you.
- Please!
Christine ... please.
Thank you.
Holy Spirit ... To us
work, bless ...
If the spirit in me, put my hand
than the beast.
Do you understand?
- Yes.
I force the spirit of the Alamia,
the goat to go.
Milos, then save.
- Yes, I'll do that.
Here!
And hard, you hear?
I understand.
We should be open.
What should I do?
You must let the darkness.
You should invite your dead spirit.
I'm afraid.
- Yes ...
Repeat these words ...
I welcome the dead ...
in my soul.
I welcome the dead in my soul.
- You gotta believe!
We wait holy spirits,
are you with us?
Something else is here with us.
Yes.
This is not Alamia.
It is ...
the spirit of a lost soul.
From years ago.
Sometimes hanging with you for the Perplexed
around the door.
There are more, here.
Say what spirit.
Mind, say what!
He is coming.
He has the body of Shaun San Dena,
taken possession.
Alamia ...
Alamia, what you want?
I want the soul of Christine Brown!
We will take possession of her body,
to celebrate the brave.
No, it was my manager, Jim jackets.
He was the ...
Stil ... Alamia, I ask you this meaningless
women, not to take.
She is certainly not worthy of your greatness.
No!
I come to you, Christine.
You are mine!
No ... You tricked me there!
You whore with a black heart!
Milos now ... now!
- You whore!
Go away, you evil spirit!
Alamia!
I'm the one who has called you,
in this circle.
I recommend you leave this house now!
She has nice breasts!
Christine ...
I do not want your cat, but you!
Little whores queen!
Shaun San Dena!
You must exorcise the spirit!
Yes.
Milos!
I'm fine.
- My God!
- Oh my God.
You did it.
- Thank God.
I've tried ...
- You okay?
Oh my God ... help me!
Internal bleeding.
She still breathes?
No.
Oh God.
It is sad.
- Yes.
Strange how things work.
She had waited 40 years, the probability
Alamia to overcome.
And on the last night of her
life, is successful.
I think you've misunderstood.
Alamia can not be averted
through a medium.
That was the lesson of last night.
Sorry.
But I saw that she overcame.
- No, she drove him from the seance.
He comes back.
The goat was not slain.
And when it gets dark ...
Alamia is the owner of
the cursed object.
Of course you would, now not
the owner must be more.
Got the knot?
Give it away, then
you have given away the curse.
Why did not you do this before?
Because the Alamia will take the soul of
person to whom you give the knot.
And forever will burn in hell.
And that would be my fault.
- And I am guilty.
Whatever you decide.
- He has left a warning.
Is it over?
It is over.
You'll burn in hell!
- You whore, you will burn in hell!
Your time is coming!
You'll burn in ...
Okay?
Jesus say.
Do you still feel like our trip,
to Santa Barbara? - Yes.
Yes, that's good.
- Okay, what time will you pick me?
It's better when I come to the station.
I must go do something.
I can do.
I will on the way to ...
No, no, I have it all under control.
See you then at 07.30 hours.
- Where is my envelope?
What envelope?
- He sat in my bag, I had him just yet.
It's just one envelope.
- No, he should be here.
He is here, so we will also
eventually found.
My God, I thought I had lost him.
Ok.
07.30, on time!
Are you sure that you do not want anything?
No, so you'll just sit still
which is it?
Yes, perhaps, what of that?
Honey, I earn through tips and
Coffee drinkers do not match.
Bljf with the coffee, then I give you
a tip that you'll never forget.
What looks good out there, say.
You are the sweetest in the world.
It does not in question, Stu.
You will ensure that you are over 10 minutes
I tell Mr. Jacks or something you do not
I want to tell him.
Oh yes, what then?
- First you that the McPherson case,
stolen from my desk and have to
"First National" have given.
And now you have 9 minutes.
Enter only one.
- Really?
Please, Christine, betrayed me.
It was not intentional.
- What do you want?
I have something to give a small gift.
A gift, I do not understand, I thought
you called me here to ...
that case the 'First National'.
Listen, you do not understand.
Just shut up!
That gift, which I will give you, is your
possession, you own it, okay?
Well.
What?
Forget it.
- I thought of punishment for that loan.
Go.
Okay, thank you, Christine.
But you betray me, huh?
- Go away!
Who can I give?
GANUSH SYLVIA
Well ... is that possible?
There are blessings gypsy
also working with the dead.
They give gifts to the deceased who
appropriate to their souls.
But in reality,
the soul never dies.
Yeah, I think you have to curse someone
can give, who is deceased.
But you must have a formal gift,
to make of the deceased.
I know something better than that, I push
by her throat.
GANUSH
I give it back to you!
And you take him from me.
You want him back?
Take it!
Whatever you do, you'll get him.
I ... Christine Brown, give this knot,
officially yours ... Sylvia Ganush!
Stitch in, bitch!
Goodbye!
Hi, Christine, leave a message ...
Christine, it was Jim, Jim Jacks.
Sorry to call so early,
but last night, I found annoying
Information about Stu Rubin.
It appears your records on the loan McPherson
and tried it a deal
to do with "First National".
I think he thought that we
would not come back.
And that would be so, if he is not one hours
ago and you came along and blamed.
When I confronted him with some errors in
the story, he began to cry and ...
Well ... that we no longer.
So I wanted to let you know that Monday morning,
the job of assistant manager,
is waiting on you.
Everything is okay.
Good morning.
Sorry we are not ...
- Oh, I ... I just want this coat.
We are still not open.
- My friend and I go on a trip.
There he is.
Hi.
Hey. there you are.
- Good to see you.
There are so many things I have
to tell.
Yeah, I know, but I've
all been in a row.
Okay, go ahead.
You always keep watch over me.
And I thank you for it.
And there is something ... something that
I previously could not confess.
I had mrs Ganush a delay
give her loan.
But I did not.
It was my decision ...
and it was wrong of me.
You're so, n goeierd.
You are so beautiful now.
Do you like my new coat?
Yeah, well, really, what have you done with that old?
I've discarded him and I want him
never seen.
Oh no, get it back, see what
I've found.
I found this in the car, eh ...
I thought maybe you could ...
I thought maybe ... Now he is back ...
He still very much like my
"Liberty" quarter appears.
The envelope ... Go, Go ...
Chris ... Chris ...
Oh my God!
- Hey, hey, hey!
Hey, hey, hey ... stop!
Chris, O God ...
Hey, hey ... Hey, hey, you ...
Oh, God, no ...
Help me!
Help me please!