Someone once told me
we always are where we're supposed to be.
Now I believe it.
Life is a journey. You know where it begins,
you never know where it ends...
Or how...
It's not easy finding one's path.
Sometimes we get lost.
Sometimes we stumble and fall.
And if we are not in control
of our own destiny then what is?
Is it fate or Lady Luck?
Random chaos or God?
And if it is God and you were given the chance
to become the instrument of providence...
Would you do it?
TEXAS SIX MONTHS EARLIER
- Excuse me, I'm sorry to bother you, Ma'am.
- Yeah, can I help you?
I'm Iost and I ran out of gas
a Iittle ways down the road from you.
- I was using my cell phone to navigate...
- Oh we don't have cell phone
reception out here.
Yeah, no kidding. I got to a fork,
I had no idea which way to tum.
Honestly I can't even find your road
on the map. I have no idea where I am.
I don't think I'm where
I'm supposed to be though.
We always are
where we're supposed to be...
But you know you're right
about the gas station.
Ain't none up this road
that's for sure!
Oh honey, don't fee I bad,
everybody gets Iost around here.
Heck, I've been trying to get out of
this place myself for fifty years!
I wanted us to move to Florida
to be closer to my sister
but my husband, God rest his sou I,
just didn't want to hear about it.
On account of all of his old cars.
Just look at this! What a mess!
They're everywhere!
You know, he nevercould see an old clunker
without ending up buying it.
And when he'd come home from a business trip,
he was a salesman you know,
he'd be towing some
piece of old junk behind him.
I sold the property last week
and howin heaven am I supposed
to have all this junk moved out
by the end ofthe month?
Well I sure hope the Japanese people
buy them all tomorrow!
I need to get all this junk out of here!
Oh there you are!
I found the gas.
- Joann, are you selling all your cars?
- Oh you bet!
- Even this one?
- Yeah all of them.
- Would you consider selling it to me?
- You're not one ofthose
crazy car people are you?
- I'm a hot roadder, Joann.
- Oh for heaven sakes...
Look, I don't have a Iot of money
and I'm sure your buyers tomorrow
can offer you a Iot more than I can.
But this here, this is my dream.
My husband always did Iove this one,
not really sure why...
You should have seen it
when he brought it home.
It was a mess!
He worked on it fourteen years,
fixed it up Iike new.
You think he ever drove it once? No...
It's just been sitting here, gathering dust,
just Iike the rest of'em.
Well, you know I'm sure your husband
would prefer to see it stay closerto home...
You reached Monk.
I'm busy doing burnouts right now,
so leave a message.
Hey Monk, it's Faith. Call me as soon as
you get this message, okay, it's super urgent.
You'll never bell eve what I found here.
Um, no I'm not coming back with a script,
but I'm coming back with inspiration.
I'll give you a hint:It's a car.
The lady is super nice,
she's even throwing in an old trailer
in the deal, so I'm going to be able to
tow it back, the car is not running.
Anyways I need your help okay?
I'm short two grand to close this deal and
I'm heading back to Tyler right now,
there's a Western Union up there.And...
shit I sure hope you get this message.
I'm running out of time.
Okay call me okay? Bye.
Joann, thank you so much for everything.
Oh you're welcome honey
and I hope you enjoy it.
Hey if that pink slip shows up
while you're packing, will you mail it to me?
Oh sure will Honey, sure will!
And you have a safe trip back to LA!
- I will.
- O.K
- Thankyou!
- Bye bye!
What year is it?
32!
Wow, right on!
Rex, Rex. Checkthis out:
Filthy, this is so him!
This is you man, I'm buying this!
Oh shit, I forgot my purse in my roadster.
I'll be back.
Is this your car?
- Yes!
- Really? It's yours?
- I mean, not your husband's?
- I don't have one ofthose.
- Boyfriend?
Don't have one ofthose either.
No, this is my Deuce.
- Well you got a very nice roadster.
- Thankyou.
I Iike your steering wheel.
53 Chevy, right?
My dad was a hardcore
hot rodderfrom the fifties...
Had a sweet 34 roadster
with a Hemi engine in it...
When I saw that spade on
your steering wheel
reminded me of a story he to Id me
about him and his buddies, back in the days.
Come on! Can't this piece of crap
go any faster?
Howlong do you thinkit's gonna
take him to test drive the coup e?
- Oh the way he drives?
Probably not verylong!
- Art's not going to do it anyway, Bob...
- He'll do it! OKTrust me!
- We'll see.
He's gonna marry my sister. Trust...
Hang a right, there.
Damn!
Hey Daddy-o!
Huh! What's up Bob?
What's up guys?
- Hey is the Chief around?
- No, he went into town to pick up some parts.
- Oh yeah? So he'll be gone fora while then?
- At Ieast an hour.
Why?
Hey, can I talkto you fora second?
You see, we came to see
the Deuce of Spades and...
I to Id the boys that
you'd pop the hoodforus.
You know I can't do that,
I'll be in deep shit if I show you.
So, you want me to tell pop
about yourplans to marry Sandy then?
Ornot?
Bob! Why do you always got to be
such an asshole?
Whateverit takes man.
I want to gander
at what's under that hood.
OK... But make it quick.
- Wow!
- Give me that.
He's gonna kick my ass
if he finds out...
- No one's gonna to tell him, right boys?
- No! No way!
Holy shit!
Hot Damn! Look at that thing!
Look at the powerplant!
No wonder no one can take him!
- What is it?
- It's a TURBO-FIRE V8...
- It's got a 162 horsepower
right out ofthe box.
- Oh man!
- How did he fit three carbs on there?
- He built that himself. He's got to
have at Ieast 250 horsepower.
- Good Christ!
- Those are some strange Iooking drums...
- These are prototypes. Something he's been
working on with a buddy over at GM.
- He's working with GM?
This Iad is only a yearolderthan me
and he knows 10 times more about
hotrods than any of us...
Nothing is as fast as
the Deuce of Spades, man!
Well why do they call it
the Deuce of Spades anyway?
Come on! Who brought this kid?
There's a spade smack dab center
in the steeringwheel.
Ain't you seen it yet dummy?
No!
Ah, well, Iet's show it to you!
Come here.
You see, it's his trademark.
He puts it on every one of his cars.
You see it now?
My dad said that the guy was running
the first overhead valve Chevy V8 everbuilt.
He was running it Iong before
the fifty fives came out ...
- Really?
- Yeah, when I saw that spade on your car...
It made me wonder...
Could this is be
the Deuce of Spades?
I don't think so.
This car's from Minnesota.
The woman who so Id it to me
was pretty sure about it...
I'm sorry...
Well, you know, my dad,
he was quite a talker.
Had a Iot of stories from the old days.
It's hard to tell how many ofthose
were actually true.
- I hear you.
- It was nice meeting you.
Likewise! Thanks for sharing the story,
I enjoyed it.
- Have a good day. Bye bye.
- Bye bye.
DOES TRUE LOVE REALLY EXIST?
YOU WILL COME TO THE HELP
OF A STRANGER IN NEED
Yeah yeah there's room...
Monk said to put a remote booster
between the seat and the trunk pane I...
I've neverlooked,
but I will today how's that?
OK Rex, I'll talk to you Iater.. Bye...
Sunday, September 4th, 1955...
My darling Bettle.
I know you're really mad at me right now
but please hear me out.
I know what I did was wrong
and I'm sorry.
I should have stopped you that night,
told you that I love you
when I had the chance.
Now I fear it's too late.
I've lost you and it hurts.
I can't sleep, I can't eat...
I can't think straight...
What have you done to me?
Tommy keeps saying I'll get over it
but he's wrong.
He's been going tothe Circus
setting up races for me
but my heart's not into it.
I don't want to do this any more.
You asked me how long I needed
and I told you I didn't know.
Well I know now. I'm ready.
They took my license but I don't care
tomorrow I'm driving the Deuce
all the way to New York.
I'll drive day and night if I haveto.
I'm coming to you Bettie
and I'm gonna marry you.
So please forgive me
and take back my ring.
Keep it close to your heart
until I can hold you in my arms again.
Your Johnny.
The number you have reached
has been disconnected.
Oh here you are!
- Is that a cigarette I'm smelling?
- Yes. Why?
- You know what the doctors said, come on!
- Oh Doctors...
What do they know?
They're all floosies.
I'm 82 and I can still do bum outs!
Hey Monk
- I wanted to pick
your brains about something...
- Shoot!
Everheard of a fifties joint calledthe Circus?
I'm thinking maybe in Minnesota...
Minnesota? Hell no!
Piccadilly Circus was right here
in Southem California, the cradle of hot rod ding!
I used to go there all the time.
Set up street races.
- In Southern California?
- That's what Ijust said!
You want my hearing aid?
Just a couple ofblocks up the street.
I'm gonna go check it out...
It's all gone.
Bulldozed over a couple years back.
They built a shopping mall on it.
There's no thing's Ieft Faith...
Nothing.
Dear Faith
I found this box
when I was cleaning up the barn.
The Bill of Salewas in it
along with a few other items
my husband found in the trunk
of the car when he bought it.
I hope you're enjoying the car.
Joann
When I saw that spade
on your car, made me wonder.
could this bethe Deuce Of Spades?
There's a spade smack dab center
in the steering wheel.
It's his trademark,
he puts it on everyone of his cars.
Nothing is as fast as
the Deuce of Spades man!
MAKING ROADSTER HISTORY
Johnny Callaway and his record
breaking street roadster
FAITH: BILL OF SALE
SAUGUS SALVAGE
SEPTEMBER 5TH, 1955
SOLD WRECKED 32 FORD ROADSTER
AS IS - $50 - PAID
September 5
Oh my God...
September4rt h
NEWS ARCHIVE SEARCH
JOHNNYCALLAWAYCRASH
ZERO MATCHING RESULTS FOUND!
SEPTEMBER 5TH, 1955
ONE MATCHING RESULT FOUND!
LOS ANGELES PRESS - SEPTEMBER 5TH, 1955
Shit.
HOT ROD STREET RACE ENDS IN TRAGEDY:
TWO DEAD!
LOCAL RESIDENT TOM MILLER WITNESSES
FATAL CRASH AND ALERTS AUTHORITIES.
Come in please
Dad, this is the lady
that called yesterday.
She's here to see you.
She has some questions to ask you.
Mr. Miller?
Yes...
Sir, I wanted to ask you about a crash
you witnessed 50 years ago
involving a man by the name
of Johnny Callaway...
Yes... Johnny... Callaway...
Sir, can you tell me
about the crash please?
What happened that night?
The Deuce of Spades...
They took it from Johnny...
Theytook everything...
You knew Johnny didn't you?
Two quarts to go...
Every Saturday...
Sir, the Deuce of Spades crash...
The papersaid you witnessed it.
What crash?
Johnny's crash...
Who?
Do you know anything about the crash?
No. He's never mentioned it to me...
Johnny!
God damn it Johnny
don't you d le on me.
I need a sign.
You the girl asking about Johnny Callaway?
Yes...
This is for you.
SEEK AND YOU SHALL FIND
1406 ELLIS STREET
GLENDALE, CA91203
SUNDAY4 p.m.
Come in...
You have been asking yourself
Iots of questions...
Wondering what happened to Johnny.
I'm Sandy.
How do you know I have been Iooking
for Johnny Callaway?
My son sometimes goes
to Bob's Big Boy.
- People talk.
- Did you know him?
Oh yes. I knew Johnny Callaway.
I knew him real well...
Full throttle Johnny.
That's what they called him.
The fastest guy around.
A II the girls wanted to be with him
and all the boys wanted to be him...
He was a Iegend!
The weather is great,
it's great roadster weather...
So how's the weather in Ohio?
Yeah the roadster ran great
the whole way out.
No but that's not why I called.
I'm stopped at a gas station
you're nevergonna believe
who the attendant knows.
Johnny Callaway.
Hey Johnny, what did you do
to my brother Eddie?
He came home Iast night and started
kicking the heck out of his coup e.
- Put a big dent in the door!
- Yeah and then he tore
his entire engine apart.
- He was at it all night!
- Hey, Johnnywe're going to the bowling alley...
- You wanna come with us?
- No I can't. I got something I got to do.
Well all right Johnny...
Maybe some other time then... Soon?
What did I tell ya?
Like clockwork!
Talk about the devil!
Hey Johnny, 'two quarts to go'?
Yeah.Two quarts to go!
This fellah just moved here from Ohio.
Said everybody back there's been talking
about you and your Deuce.
Is that right?
So you're the famous Johnny Callaway?
It's an ho nor!
Myname is Gary,
but everybody calls me ZIP.
I'm a CAM JAMMER.
A II right! A II right!
Hey Zip, that is a nice beater
you got there.
But what do you got under the hood?
- Enough to keep me away from trouble.
- Why don't we head out to Paradise road
and have a Iittle competition?
- Really?
- Yeah... Let's do it!
- Hell yeah!
AI right!
So Johnny, 'put it on your books'?
Heymac!
Can I get some service over here?
A II right!
Yeah, put in on my books.
Are you sure you should be
doing this while smoking?
You want gas or don't you?
A II right Zip, this is it.
I'm gonna give you three carlengths.
Three carlengths? Are you sure?
- Yeah, I'm sure...
- Ok...
Damn he's fast!
There's Johnny and his roadster in 1954...
And this here is mylate husband Art.
Him and Johnny were Iike brothers.
This here is the Callaway Speed Shop.
I have so many fond memories
in that shop...
That's where Art kissed me
forthe first time!
- Who's this?
- Ah! That's Bettie Thompson, Johnny's girl.
Look at them,
they were so happybackthen...
It was so Iong ago,
but I remember it Iike it was yesterday...
The night they met
August 20th 1953...
- This place's an armpit.
- Yeah Johnnylet's shove off.
Come on you guys,
I want you guys to meet my girl, Sandy...
I'm gonna marry this girl,
to hell with it! Oooh she's a dish!
She's a dish alright!
Adish with no meat on it!
Hey Sandy!
I want you to meet
my best bud Johnny Callaway.
Johnny...
I've heard so much about you...
- Oh Is that right?
- Yeah! We were just Iooking
at your Deuce here
- Art says it's the fastest rod in town?
- You'd betterbelieve it!
Hi! I'm Peggie...
It's a nice roadster you got here.
You think you could
give me a ride home Iater?
I can't. I'm going out to the desert.
He's gonna spend all night sleeping
under his car just so he's first in Iine
tomorrowmoming.
He's crazy!
Well, I'm gonna cut out.
It was nice meeting you all...
Excuse me...
A II right, well...
Guess we'll see you guys
tomorrowmoming at EI Mirage.
Don't even think about it.
What?
He'd breakyourheart...
A II right!
You broke your own record man!
Fast as shit!
Good day racing today, guys!
Good day racing...
- Johnny you were flying!
- That was incredible Johnny!
- Man you were fast!
- Cheers!
- Here's to Johnny!
- To Johnny Callaway, the fastest guy!
Overthe next two weeks, life resumed as usual.
Johnnywas busy being... Johnny.
You guys OK?
Go ahead and give it a crank now.
Wow!
I don't knowhowyou did that,
but thanks!
- Jeff Granger
- Johnny Callaway
Tommy Miller
Vic Wayne, nice to meet you.
- Well, I guess we're off.
- What do you say we run them?
- What on that road?
- That road is good as any.
A II right! Let's do it!
I'm gonna hop in here
to even out the odds
Good Iuck fellahs!
Let's go Ladies!
Come on Ladies!
Oh! Oh! His hood just popped open!
He's out! He's out Johnny!
One down, one to go!
Damn it!
God damn it!
Oh shit Johnny we got
a black and white on ourtail!
Is there a problem Offcer?
Johnny lived for speed.
Street racing, drag racing, Time Trials.
You name it, he did it.
And there was really no room
in his life for anything else.
Til Bettle came along...
Hey Art!
Yah!
That girl the other day,
Sandy's friend...
- Who? Peggie?
- No, not Peggie. The brunette...
What 'bout her?
- What's her name?
- Bettie. Why?
ONE MAN WOMAN.
BUD DIDN'T STAND A CHANCE WITH HER,
BUT HE COULDN'T STOP TRYING
- So? What did you find out?
- He's hot for you.
Really? Is that what Art said?
Heck no! But Johnny's
definitely interested.
Art started asking me questions about you
and why do youthink that is?
- You really think so?
- I know so.
- So, what did you tell him?
- Well, I to Id him that you're one smart girl
and that you're not like some
ofthoseeasy girls that the hotrodders go for.
Really? You said that?
Well, yeah, it's the truth!
Hey Art?
Yep?
That girl Bettie, what's she Iike?
Don't waste your time on her Johnny
that girl doesn't put out.
She's tight.
She's tight?
Yeah! Rea I tight.
Really...
Great. He's not gonna want
to go out with me now...
Well, I wouldn't be too sure if I were you...
Today, Art asked me where you Iive.
I'm pretty sure Johnny's gonna offer
you a ride in his Deuce!
Oh my God...
What am I going to do Sandy?
I'm afraid of speed...
Listen honey, you're gonna need
a really strong stomach
if you want to go out with Johnny Callaway...
AI right, I'll mention it to Art.
- So: Do you Iike the boy?
- Like him?
I think I Iove him...
Look Bettie, I have to warn you
all the girls in town are chasing after Johnny...
And all he has to do is just snap his fingers
and they'll fall right into his Iap.
Do you know what I mean?
I know...
AI right, Well then if you're really
serious about him
this is what you're gonna do...
Have a good day, be a good girl.
OK sweetie? I Iove you!
Love you too, mom!
Hi there!
Hi!
Do I know you?
We met a couple weeks ago...
Remember?
- I'm Art's friend.
- Oh... That's right...
What's your name again?
I'm Johnny... Johnny Callaway.
So... What are you doing
out here Johnny Callaway?
Well, Art mentioned
you've been walking to school
I thought I might come out
and offer you a ride.
That's really nice of you but
I enjoy the walk...
Take care...
AI right, see you tomorrow.
Hey that blistersure Iooks painful.
It Iooks worse than it is.
Heywhy don't you hop in the Deuce,
I'll give you a ride to school.
I'll drive slow, I promise.
No thank you...
It's a nice day fora ride in the Deuce.
No thank you.
Hey, we're a Iittle bit Iate today,
aren't we?
Hop in, I'll get you there right on time...
Thank you! I can make it!
You want to get a ride with me today Bettie?
Or do you still preferwalking?
Walking is good for you!
Aren't you tired of coming here every day?
No. I reallylike the view.
You'll get tired ofthe view soon enough.
Come on Sandy! It's been four weeks.
He's gonna get tired ofthis and give up...
When Johnnywants something, he never gives up.
Are you gonna followme
all the way to school?
Yep!
Not any more!
Johnny you never give up do you?
Check out the gait on that rig!
Heybaby! What you doing
out here all alone?
I'll take her home
and showherto my mother!
Come on baby don't be scared!
Well hello there!
- Now, what's a pretty girl Iike you
doing out here all alone?
- Leave me alone!
- Don't play so hard to get!
- Let go of me!
God Damn it!
Hey! Knockit off, she's with me.
Oh yeah? It doesn't Iooklike it to me!
Shit man, it's Callaway...
Hey Johnny we were just having a Iittle fun.
We don't want any trouble.
- Take it easy Johnny we don't want any trouble.
- We didn't know she was your girl.
Get the hell out of here, assholes.
These God Damn jocks
think they can run this town
cause they go to that God damn
uppity college!
I'm sorry...
So why don't you go to school Johnny?
I used to.
I have to run my dad's shop now.
Where is your dad?
He's dead.
I'm sorry...
What about you?
What do you go to school for?
To become smart.
Why you not smart already?
- I want to be a famous writer some day.
- Awritereh?
You gonna write a book about me?
Maybe...
- So how did your race...
- Look I don't know
You go.
I was just asking
howyourrace went yesterday?
I dusted every Iast one ofthem...
You're used to always winning, aren't you?
I was til I met you...
So what do you do
when you don't get your way?
Bettie, I don't know what people
have toldyou about me,
but I'm not how you think.
Just give me a chance to prove it...
Please.
AI right Johnny.
I'll Iet you drive me to school today.
AI right!
Thank you...
From that day on Johnnywould drive
Bettle to school every moming
and take her home
every afternoon.
Hewas always careful to stay clear
of Bettle's house and her parents
Hotrodders were considered hoodlums
in those days you see...
Oh! I'm Johnny Callaway!
Every moment together
was a moment they stole...
And every day they lookedforwardto that
little bit of time they got to spend together.
Let's go somewhere today, just you and me.
- I have to go to school Johnny!
- Ah!
School is always gonna be there.
I might not be, you know?
I could crash and die
and be gone in an instant!
That's a horrible thing to say!
Don't say things Iike that!
So you do care...
Some might say Johnny
was a bad influence on Bettle
but I think he was the best thing
that could have happened to her...
What are you doing here? Are you crazy?
My mother's home, she'll see us! Go!
Ear I? I think we have a problem!
Damn Hotrodders!
Johnny...
Johnny stop...
Johnny Stop!
I'm sorry...
I'll be more gentle.
It's just... I never...
No, it's ok, you don't need to exp Iain.
I don't want to make you do
anything you don't want to.
I'll wait for you...
Johnny please, you should go...
My parents will be home any second.
Ifmy mom sees you, she'll have a cow...
Oh my Godthey're here! Go!
Go!
Don't try to deny it young Iady,
you have a hickey on your neck!
- I forbid you to see him you hear me?
- No ma! I Iove him!
- I forbid you to see that hoodlum!
- I Iove him!
Earl, do something!
Listen to your mother, Bettie.
You will not see that boy again,
you understand me young Iady? Ever!
Now go to your room!
Johnny heard everything
and from that moment he knew that
Bettie's mother would never approve of him.
Do you believe in True Love?
I used to...
I waited for it fora Iong Iongtime.
Finally, one day, I stopped waiting.
It's easier that way you see?
No more disappointments.
Don't give up on True Love Faith.
It does exist.
But it's rare.And precious.
And only happens once in a Iifetime...
Ifyou're Iucky.
- Seems to me all that Johnny and Bettie
found was heartache.
- Well...
Sometimes true Love and heartache
go hand in hand.
True Iove can be a great blessing,
and a great curse.
Well if it was true Iove forthem,
why did it end?
Who says it did?
Theybroke up. Why?
When I think back, I think it probably all started
with the Passion Pit, Iate spring of 1955...
Hey Art?
- Wasn't Johnny working on a red chevy today?
- Uh huh...
- That snake! He'd better not.
- What?
It's Johnny!
- Where?
- There!
- What's he doing here?
- What do you think he's doing here?
Who is he doing it with?
I don't know... Bettie?
Bettie? No way!
Bettie's not the Passion Pit type.
Ifthat son of a gun is cheating on her
I swear to God I will kill him...
Sandy! Get back here!
Johnny I Iove you...
Wait.
- What?
- I heard something...
It's OK...
You are a psycho Sandy!
He was with Bettie!
Didyou know that they were going
all the way?
I mean I had no idea...
She's been hiding it from me...
Didyou know?
Get in the car!
Johnny gave Bettie his ring.
They had been going steadyfortwo years now
but he never told her once that he loved her.
And he would not pop the question...
Now that she had slept with him,
Bettle started worrying that he never would.
[FAITH]-But he loved her...
[SANDY] - Oh yes, he loved her.
But the wheels offate were already in motion.
If you are not going to do
something about it, I will.
She's having sex with that hoodlum,
you know that, don't you?
- Well... How can you be so sure...
- I know she is! I can telljust by Iooking at her.
This has got to stop.
What do you want me to do?
She's not a chi Id any more, Helen.
She's not even 18!
She doesn't know what she's doing!
And I will not Iet her make a mistake
she'll regret forthe rest of herlife.
I'm sending her to College in Attica.
- Attica? Where in the hell is Attica?
- New York, Ear I, Attica's in New York.
That's all the way on the
other side ofthe country!
Exactly.
Johnny! Comedown here!
Could you hand me that wrench?
AI right. Now, the engine is running kinda rough.
So what do you think we should do?
Check ignition system,
fuel Iines and carburetor.
That's good Johnny!
That's really good.
- Sir?
- Yes son.
Is it true that you are
going away tomorrow?
Yes.
But you'll be back sir, right?
Yes, Johnny, I'll be back.
Promise?
Yeah... I Promise.
Hey and when I get back,
you and I we're gonna put the 32 body on
and then one day soon,
she'll be all yours...
You take good care ofyourmother
while I'm away, you hear?
I will sir.
Rememberto start the roadster everyday.
Keep this forme,
til I get back Johnny...
OK.
Johnny! Come back!
Don't go.
What?
Tomorrow... Don't go.
- Johnny, I have to...
- Why do you have to go to college
all the way in New York?
Tell your parents you're not going.
It's not that simple...
You think I don't know what you want?
I know what you want...
What are you saying?
I don't know...
Just be patient with me...
Ijust need more time...
Bettie...
- Tommy sent us.
- What's up?
He wanted to warn you.
There's a new cat with a mean heap at Saugus.
He's Iooking for you.
- He's been Iaying rubberall overtown,
telling everybody he's gonna cream you.
- Oh yeah?
He's got the fastest hotrod in Fresno.
Oh yeah. Tommy said
you got triple trouble heading your way.
He's real fast Johnny.
You'd better get your ass down there quick.
What's he running?
Dunno, but it sounds nasty!
He means business.
Oh, one more thing.
Watch out for John Law.
There's a black and white on White Oaks,
parked behind the hedge, waitingforyou.
- Yeah thanks.
- You got it
You're not thinking about going down
to Saugus ourlast night together are you?
Johnny please don't do this.
I have a reallybadfeeling about this...
You don't understand!
Everybody in town knows
that he's Iooking forme.
I have to go.
Hey what's cooking? What did I miss?
This Fresno guy, man he's a turkey,
he just jumped the gun.
Thinks he's a real bad ass
but he's a rookie.
- So... What do you guys think?
- I think Johnny's gonna whip his ass!
Ehhh... I don't know guys I mean
this guy's green, but he tears ass.
- I think Johnny's could be up shit creek this time.
- Hey guys shut up, shut up! Tommy is about to flag.
- You're out.
- What do you mean I'm out?
- You're out!
- This is bullshit!
This is bullshit! You tipped him off.
I saw you move your foot asshole!
Watch your God Damn mouth
you dumb wop!
- Who are you calling a wop, asshole?
- Hey what's going on here?
Oh this God damn wop thinks
he can run ourdragstrip.
Hey Buddy! If Tommy said you're out, you're out!
So take your piece of shit and get it out of here?
This ain't Raisin City!
No! I'm not going anywhere
until I get a fair chance to race this guy!
You had three chances already asshole!
Move yourcaroffmytrack now!
What, is this a set-up? Huh?
You guys asshole buddies?
This ain't over you son of a bitch!
I'm not done with you either!
- Name your time and place asshole!
- Hey!
Look out Johnny he's got a knife!
Son of a bitch!
Fight! Fight!
Knock it off. Knockit off!
Go back to Fresno, Ioser!
Hey meet me at Sepulveda blvd
tonight, Culver City.
We're gonna settle this
once and for all damn it!
- I'll be there!
- You'd better be there, asshole!
Ifracing this kid is so important to you
if it's more important than us,
then go ahead, go race him!
But don't expect me to be here
when you come back.
Ifyou come back.
And so Johnny drove out to Culver City
that night to race Fresno.
Dozens of Police cars raided the place.
They arrested everybody!
Johnnywas detained overnight...
It's 6AM Bettie, he's not coming.
You're gonna miss your train...
But Bettle didn't know.
She was hoping until the last minute
that he was going to show up at
the train station to stop her and make up.
Give this to Johnny. He'll understand.
Tell him if he wants to work this out,
to call me Sundaynight 8 p.m. New York time.
If...
If I don't hear from him,
I'll assume it's over.
Here's the number he can reach me at.
Sweetie I to Id he would break your heart...
But you didn't Iisten...
Look, you're betteroffwithout him.
He wasn't good enough for you anyway.
You kids stay out oftrouble, you hear?
Yes Officer! Sure...
God damn fuzz!
- Oh man...
- Yep...
Johnny's definitely gonna
Iose his Iicense overthis!
- Yeah, I heard they impounded his car!
- Shit!
Hey Johnny! Where you go in'?
God damn it! Shit!
She doesn't want to see you again
for as Iong as she Iives. Get it?
Is something wrong
with the food Johnny?
You haven't touched your food.
I have a message from Bettie.
She said to give you this,
that you would understand.
Did she say anything else?
No...
I'm so sorry Johnny...
Johnny spent the next two weeks
in his shop, working night and day.
It was Iike he was using work
as a pain killer.
He always said his brains worked best
when he was wrenching...
Well, he must have been doing
a Iot of thinking.
Hi Johnny!
You hurt yourselfJohnny.
It's nothing.
I think you should go.
What?
You heard me!
You should go.
Can't wait to see the Iook on Fresno's face
when Johnny whips his ass!
I should have backed right up
in his piece of shit you know that?
- Yeah!
- I can't stand that son of a bitch!
- So I can pick it up in a couple hours then?
- Yeah it'd be just fine.
Great.Thanks so much for doing this
on Labor Day I really appreciate it.
Hey you're welcome Mr. Wilson!
[TOMMY]- What kind of name is Crosciato?
[ART]- I think it's Italian for"slow".
[ART] Hey Mr. Wilson!
Ah, don't worry, Johnny's gonna show him.
Right Johnny?
- What you guys up to?
- Fresno.
Can you believe
that asshole's still in town?
He pulls in at Tips, blocks me off...
Me and Art we're ready to bust out so now
we're stuck with this wop getting in our face.
He's wound tight, man!
He's going on and on
how he's not going back to Fresno
until he has a chance
to stomp your ass.
Stomp my ass, eh?
- That's what he said.
- I set a race up for you man.
Saugus tonight, midnight.
- So Iet's give him a real good
ass whipping Johnny, what do you say?
- I gotta get this done.
- Finish it tomorrow!
I can't. I'm Ieaving tomorrow
and I'll be back in a couple weeks.
What about the race?
You can do both Johnny!
You can do the race and then come back
and finish the car. What's the big deal?
You know Tommy you just don't get it!
I'm done with this racing shit
It's been nothing but trouble.
You what?
You heard me, I'm done.
- You can't hang it up Johnny! Not now!
- Yeah Johnny... Just do this Iast race!
Listen you guys! There's always going
to be the next race!
There's always gonna be the next asshole
coming into town
just wanting to prove something.
- Yeah Johnny this is our town
we should do something about it!
It's nevergonna end!
I don't want to do this any more.
What the hell man?
- You know ever since that broad Ieft you...
- Heywatch it Tommy! Just watch it!
Wow oh! Come on Johnny!
Stop being such a jerk!
Just do the race!
- I already set up the race for you.
You can't make me Iookbad Johnny!
It's a matterofhonor.
What do you say?
I'll think about it...
OK, Johnny you think about it
and we'll see you at Saugus at midnight.
See you there buddy.
He's Iate.
I don't think he's gonna show.
He'll show.
- Yourbuddy's a chicken!
He's gonna be a no show.
- Shut up you dumb wop!
Johnnywill show.
Johnny always shows.
Oh yeah well maybe he realizes
he's not the hot shit around here any more.
Yeah, yeah... We're gonna find out soon
aren't we, asshole!
Jerk!
He'd bettershow...
There he is!
I toldyou he'd show.
Get ready to get your ass whipped,
shit head!
Johnny's here.
Let's just get this over with, OK?
- AI right! Line 'em up!
- Do I Iooklike a stupid ass?
- We'll do a toss. Fairand square.
- Fine!
I got a wrench.
- Hell no!
- Nowwhat?
- Have him do it!
Will you just Iet him do it?
- I'll do it.
- Asshole!
Line them up!
Bring it forward... Come on...
Stop!
Johnny, bring it forward... Stop!
AI right! Are you ready?
Are you ready?
On three...
One!
Two!
Three!
Johnny...
Johnny!
Hop on!
Art! Overhere!
Careful!
Oh shit!
Is he alive?
- Is.. Is he.. Is he breathing?
- I don't know...
Johnny can you hear me?
Go get help!
Now God damn it!
Damn it Johnny don't you die on me...
Hang in there OK buddy...
Help is on the way alright?
It'll be here soon...
You knowhowthis accident happened, son?
No sir, we were driving down Soledad
and we saw a fire...
So we stopped to check out
what was going on...
So what do we have here Detective?
Two dead and the third kid
isn't Iikely to make it.
Step over here fora moment please.
Hello?
- Mrs. Callaway?
- Yes!
Yourson survived the surgery.
But he's in a deep coma...
Will Johnny Iive?
He was hurt bad.
We are doing everything
that we can for him.
I...
I don't want to give you anyfalse hope.
Doctor, there is a Detective
here to see you...
- Tell him I'll be with him
in just a few minutes.
- AI right.
I got to go.
Tommy deserted Johnny and Art.
Went down to Mexico and laid low
there forthe next few years
waiting forthis whole mess
to blow over.
He was scared.
- Howfast was he going?
- Probably as fast as he could go!
- I want you all out ofthe hallway!
- Tell us what's going on!
God Damn it he's seizing!
Ho Id him! Doctorcheck his vita Is!
Restrain him! Ho Id him!
Administering one milligram Epinephrine.
Nurse! Get the door!
Get that door!
Bettiecame back to town
to visit her family during Spring Break.
She was still in love with Johnny.
Are you sure you want to do this Bettie?
Yes.
It's gonna be real hard on you Bettie...
I have to see him...
- But he won't know you're there...
- Hasn't there been any improvement?
It's been six months...
I'm so sorry sweetie...
It's time you move on with your Iife.
Sandy said you met a nice boy in college?
Yeah, maybe... But he's not Johnny.
Well I've got to warn you
Johnny's not Iike you remember him...
You'll see what I mean when you see him.
Young Iady get off of him!
You could seriously injure him,
he has a feeding tube in his abdomen!
Is she OK?
Here why don't you sit down?
Are you injured miss?
You have blood on your arm!
It's not herblood...
Bettie please don't cry...
Look, I didn't want to tell you this
because I knew it would hurt you
but I think you should know.
Johnny had already moved on.
I saw him having sex
on the back of his roadster
just a couple days after you Ieft.
What?
I swear to God Bettie...
You should move on...
Give that Boston boy a chance.
Give him a chance.
A long year in the coma.
The Doctors wanted to pull the plug
but Jeannewouldn't let them.
She just wouldn't give up on him.
All her savings were gone
so she had to sell the shop and her house
just to keep Johnny alive.
On the outside, life went on.
Anotherfast guy came along
and became the new hero.
Everyone forgot about Johnny Callaway
and the Deuce of Spades.
Everyone, but Art.
I'm done with this racing shit,
it's been nothing but trouble.
You can't hang it up Johnny! Not now!
Yeah Johnny just do this last race...
Come on man
it's a matter of ho nor...
What do you say?
Nurse! Nurse!
Oh my Good Lord in Heaven!
Doctor!
Well Mrs. Callaway,
he sure surprised all of us.
His coming out ofthe coma
is nothing short of a miracle.
But we ran some tests on him and...
yourson has some brain damage.
Right now he is unable to talk
and his right side is non responsive.
Now some of it may come back
with time... But...
It's not very Iikely.
Three months went by
with little to no improvement.
He was now coherent and able to talk
and starting to understand
what had happened to him.
How are you doing darling?
I'm OK...
Why don't you write to her?
I can write it for you...
Take a Iook at me Ma'...
Take a really good Iook at me...
Johnnywas a strong kid
but no matter how strong something is
there's always a breaking point...
Johnny, you didn't eat anything...
I'm not hungry.
I know you're not hungry,
but you have to eat something.
You have to get your strength back...
Leave me alone.
Please eat this.
What do you want from me Peggie?
Huh? What do you want from me?
You're not her...
You're nevergonna be her!
- Now, get out of my room!
- Why are you doing this?
Get out ofmyroom!
Get out!
- Why are you doing this?
- Get the hell out of my room!
Goodluck to you, Johnny!
I got to give it to him:
He had a lot of will power.
He couldn't stand being on a wheelchair
so he got rid of it.
Had Art toss it down a ravine
if you can imagine that!
He was such a stubborn,
unreasonable boy.
Struggled for months
trying to walk on crutches.
Droveeverybody crazy!
But in the end, he did it.
Here.
Put it back.
Put it back!
You know what Johnny?
You need to stop being
so God Damn hard headed!
I don't needyourhelp.
I can do this myself.
It's getting Iate... I gotta cut out.
Sandy's waiting for me...
Oh Sandy's waiting for you eh?
Oh then betterhaul ass!
You've been at it for hours!
Let me just help you get it done.
Just Ieave my sticks by the car
- OK?
- Come on!
- I'll be just fine!
You're nevergonna be able
to get up without myhelp.
You know that, right?
Just get out of here.
Just get!
Fine!
Nowthat Johnny was wrenching again,
they were able to make rent.
And fora brief moment, it seemed
that maybe he was going to be able
to bounce back from all this...
But Johnny's ordeal was far from over.
He was summoned to appear in court,
now on trial forinvoluntary man slaughter.
- Are you serious?
- Oh yeah!
Two people
were dead because of him,
including an innocent farmer
who Ieft a wife and kids behind him.
Oh, the authorities wanted
to make an example of Johnny.
Theythrewthe book at him.
They gave him everything he deserved...
And then some.
What about Art and Tommy?
Tommy was gone and Art was
too scared to step forward and confess.
So he Iied
and Johnnytookthe fall.
The Court hereby sentences the Defendant
Johnny Michael Callaway
to three years in the State Penitentiary.
We all thought they would go easy on Johnny
because he was crippled.
But we were wrong...
When Art heard the verdict,
he could not handle the guilt.
Art?
It's me, Sandy...
It's me baby, come on, open the door...
Don't do that to yourselfArt,
it wasn't yourfault!
Yes it was!
Please just open the door?
We're all worried sick about you ...
This is all myfault...
I'm so sorry baby...
He was my best friend...
My best friend...
And I betrayed him.
But baby, you can't tum
your back on him now, OK?
You have got to go visit him!
I'll never be able to face him...
I'll never be able to tell him
how sorry I am...
Johnny was a great frlendto all of us
but in the end, we all turned
our backs on him in his time of need.
And so when he came out of jail
in the spring of 1959
he left everything behind.
Johnny walked away and
none of us ever saw him again.
What about Bettie?
Bettie married that nice boy from Boston
and became a novelist.
Look up her book
"Deuce of Hearts".
She wrote it in the Seventies,
afterherdivorce...
She changed the names
and some ofthe details
but basically it was
herstorywith Johnny...
She was still in Iove with him.
Did you ever try
to get in touch with her?
My dearchild,
afterall these years
I would not know what to say
or where to begin...
Sandy, do you think Johnny
is still alive
out there, somewhere?
I don't know...
I am afraid no one can
answer that question.
There was a rumorin the Iate sixties...
But it was just a rum or.
There was this well known movie actor
who bought a fast car from a customizer
and guess what was painted on the firewall?
Aspade?
Yeah.
There's a Iady here
to talk to you about Johnny.
Yes, Johnny did a carforme.
I don't know where he is though,
I haven't seen him since.
Didn't Johnny do a carforwhat's her name?
No, no... Johnny turned
that job down, remember?
Johnny didn't want to do the car,
because of me and my big mouth.
I happened to mention that
the ownerwantedto street race it.
That was it.
Johnny wanted nothing to do with it.
He wouldn't budge on that either!
He was a v er
y stubborn man.
Diffcult to deal with.
- Yeah.. That's what I hear...
- I ended up traileringthat car
all the way up there and backfornothing.
It was a good three hour
drive one way!
Do you happen to remember
where the shop was Iocated?
No, not exactly...
I was onlythere that one time
and that was over 15 years ago.
But do I remember it was in the desert,
next to a dry Iake
and that Johnny guy,
he had over a hundred old cars
sitting in the back on his property!
That was a pretty awesome sight to see!
I think Johnny knew Winfield so
why don't you check with Winfield
- maybe he knows...
- Yeah, he's right!
Winfield might be able to help you.
He's been racing on the Iakes
since the Forties.
If you go to the SC TA Meet tomorrow,
you'll probably catch him there.
He's still racing.
Damn it!
I don't have time forthis shit!
Yep... Fuel pump!
Great...
Out on the rook le line folks
you haveto stay under 150 mph
and if you're driving a roadster,
you have to stay under 150 mph and spin...
Ok I'm gonna call this
a good record.
You guys are all set to go,
congratulations.
Excuse me! I'm IookingforGene Winfield...
You'll find him in his pits,
a blue roadster, a couple of bellytanks.
Thankyou!
Excuse me.
Hi there.Are you Gene Winfield?
Yes I am... Is this?
I'll be damned...
Ijust can't believe it! The Iast time
I saw this car was July of55!
Howthe hell did you end up
with Callaway's car?
It's a Iong story...
Didyou know Johnny?
Yes, everybody knew Johnny.
Do you happen to know where he is?
Ifhe's still alive?
No... Nobody's seen Johnny
since he crashed in 55.
I was to Id he Iives on a drylake...
Somewhere around here...
- I was thinking maybe here, at EI Mirage?
- No...
I've been here for25 years and if Johnny
was around here, I would know it.
Well how many other dry Iakes
are there around here?
Oh many many!
This is a big desert!
He's got Iike a hundred jalopies
sitting in his backyard.
- You'dthink somebody
would know about it.
- Well...
I have to find him.
OK.There's a hangar overthere,
the guy's name is Pete.
He flies all around this area
and if anyone can see a hundred jalopies in
a back yard, he would see it from up there.
You go see Pete and tell him I sent you,
he owes me.
Thankyou.
You're welcome.
MEET BET TIE THOMPSON
BOOK SIGNING TODAY2 p.m. TO 4 p.m.
"WITHOUT LOVE"
- Thankyou so much and it was
a pleasure to meet you.
- Thank you for coming.
Hello, couldyou make this out to Selma?
- Sure.
- Thankyou very much.
- You're welcome.
Couldyou address this to Gloria please?
- Thankyou it was a pleasure to meet you.
- Thankyou.
Does she still Iove him?
Yes...
More than anything...
Excuse me.
Sorryto interrupt Mrs Thompson.
Could you please come
by my office before you Ieave?
I have some papers
that I need you to sign.
Oh... Well, could you give me
a moment please?
Oh sure, sure take your time...
BET TIE: YOU NEED TO KNOWTHETRUTH
PEGGIE LIED TO YOU.
Oh... I'm Johnny Callaway
I'll wait for you...
Oh God....
Oh God...
Just be patient with me please...
Why?
Why didn't you tell me?
HARPER LAKE- JALOPIES
Anybody home?
Hello?
I have decided to write
so maybe I won't lose my sanity.
What's left of it.
If hell exists it's here and I'm in it.
Theywould not let me keep my crutches so
I'm back to being bedridden pretty much.
I'm in isolation
somewhere on the third floor
in Block D.
August 20th, 1957.
An inmate was stabbed to death yesterday.
They found him in a 10 foot pool of blood.
If I am to survive in here
that damn leg of mine better heal fast.
I don't care what the doctors said.
I swear when I come out of here
I'll be walking.
August 25th, 1957.
I know I died that night.
I remember hovering above the tree...
I keep thinking about that kid.
He's been haunting me in my dreams...
I never saw the tractor
his roadster was in the way.
Why didn't we give up and slow down
whenwecame to the end?
Why couldn't we?
I got to watch out for Yates.
He's been looking for a reason toget me.
He's a mean son of a gun
and from what I hear
there isn't an inmate in here who hasn't
been tore-up by his club at least once.
I have yet to have anyone come visit me.
Every Sunday, I hope...
But no one.
October 10th - The horrible seizures
and headaches are back.
Sometimes, I just want to slam my head
against the walls just to make them stop.
Thedrugs they're giving me
aren't working.
I feel and look like shit.
November 27th 1957.
I'm worried about my mother.
How will she manage without my help?
How will she be able to pay the hospital?
Another year and a half ofthis.
I don't know if I have it in me.
I think about Art,
hewas like a brother to me.
I would have laid down
my life for him.
And I watched him
standing thereat my trial
lying tothem...
I should have hit the brakes
when I crossed the finish line.
Why didn't I?
Dear Johnny
I finally heard from Bettie.
She called me yesterday
and we talked fora Iong time.
I am sorry to tell you this but she got...
...married Iast month.
Ijust thought you should know.
Two people are dead because of me.
I haveto live with that guilt
forthe rest of my life.
Lordforgive me for what I've done.
Have mercy on my soul.
I saw how the farmer's family looked at me
how they hated me.
Andthe face of his kids
I'll never forget their faces.
I still love her.
Why?
Why can't I just stop?
Callaway! You have a Ietter.
Callawayknockit off!
I said knock it off!
January 13th, 1959
My mother d led.
I can't even describe the pain
or put it into words...
Theangerthat consumes me
I couldn't keep it in any longer.
They beat me really hard.
Maybe I deserve it
for what I've done to her.
The hole was cold and dark.
Part of me d led in there.
Mywhole life feels like
a bottomless hole right now
and I keep falling
deeper and deeper in it.
I don't think I'll ever be able
to come out ofthis.
Johnny!
DO
YOU
BELIEVE
IN
SECOND
CHANCES?
JOHNNY
And when I get back you and I
aregonna put the32 body on
and then one day soon,
she'll be all yours!
Man you were fast!
- Cheers!
- Here's to Johnny!
To Johnny Callawaythe fastest guy!
- Hi Johnny, two quarts to go?
- Yeah two quarts to go.
Said everybody back there's
been talking about you and your Deuce.
So you're the famous Johnny Callaway?
It's an honorl.
Johnny... I love you...
Theytook my license but I don't care.
Tomorrow I'm driving the Deuce
all the way to New York.
I'll drive day and night if I haveto.
I'm coming to you Bettie
and I'm gonna marry you.
BET TIE STILL LOVES YOU