You tell me what that is.
You stay right there. I'll be back.
- Hi, Bernice.
- Miss Olivia.
Hey, you be a good girl.
I'll see you after work.
- Okay.
- Bye-bye.
Bye.
Bobby, get up.
Eight-thirty?
Get out of here. Go on.
Go on. Get.
Look at you.
Hey, look at your friend there.
Ma, why didn't you even
wake me up?
I should body-slam him.
Hey, man, can...?
- Good morning, Donna.
- Good morning, Mr. Tinsdale.
- These are for you.
- Thank you.
- Have a nice day.
Waymon.
- David.
- Donna.
Drake, Gearson & Burke,
may I help you?
- What was that all about?
- No big deal.
- I thought you two were an item.
- She just couldn't cut it, that's all.
Yeah, right.
Sheila, good morning.
Have my presentation materials
come up from the mailroom?
- Not yet.
- Not yet? Call the mailroom.
How about the conference room?
Have they got chairs?
The audio-visual.
Have they set up the projector?
Waymon, will you relax?
I've taken care of everything.
This is the biggest deal
of my career.
I'm aware of that. Why do you think
I've been here since 6:30 this morning?
- Get going. Atwell is waiting.
- Thank you.
- Good luck.
- Won't need it.
Oh, are you okay?
Can I help you with something?
I fell for you, babe.
How about lunch this afternoon?
You've got to be kidding.
How about dinner tonight?
Okay, lunch tomorrow?
How about a frank right now?
Slice of pizza?
Well, well, well.
Hey, hey.
- What happened last night?
- Don't know about you...
...brothers like me
gotta work in the morning.
- You see I'm in the house.
- Yeah, but you late in the house.
- Hey, but I'm in here.
- I don't see how you do it, man.
Stay out all night long
and come in here and be up all day.
Me, I gotta be home by 12 midnight
if I gotta face Monroe in the morning.
Hey, as far as I'm concerned...
...Monroe can get the bozac,
you know what I'm saying?
Johnson, you wouldn't happen to be
just getting here at 9:15?
No, homey, I was on time.
You didn't see me.
I was back there getting busy.
What kind of fool
do you take me for?
- Well...
- Watch it.
I am not one of your tack-head cronies.
I'm the boss.
The head nigga in charge.
Now, you get
your late ass to work, pronto.
Don't forget that package
for Mr. Tinsdale.
It was supposed to be on his desk
first thing.
Guess who had to take the heat
over that?
But no more, Johnson.
No more.
- Homey don't play that.
- You watch too much TV, man.
No, I'm serious, man.
Monroe don't play no games.
Yeah, well, neither do I.
I'm tired of this punk shit, man.
I came here to be a real-estate broker,
not no damn mail boy.
- I'm moving up.
- Up where?
Upstairs. Land of suit and ties.
Power lunches,
more girls than you can stand.
I'm getting paid in full.
Waymon Tinsdale's supposed
to help you get there?
- That's right. Because that's my boy.
- Your boy? Man, don't make me laugh.
Your boy
was supposed to help you...
...get in that training program
two years ago.
You ain't
but a late-in-the-house dreamer.
- You ain't going nowhere.
- Yeah, that's what you think.
Boy just don't know
when he got it good, do he?
Gentlemen, real estate
in New York City is at an all-time low.
Overbuilding and the soft economy...
...have caused a record number
of foreclosures...
...in New York in the last year.
Now, the good news
is that the opportunities for cash buyers...
...with the ability to wait out
this temporary market correction...
...never been better.
Gentlemen, if you please.
We believe the Savoy Tower property...
...is the most spectacular opportunity
of its kind in New York today.
There isn't a foreclosure property
of this size in the city...
...with a better return on investment.
And Mr. Atwell and the First Manhattan Bank
are prepared to negotiate...
...around-the-clock to close the deal
this week.
That is, if you're prepared
to make an offer now.
We've reviewed
your proposal carefully...
...and we're extremely interested.
However, before we can make
a formal offer...
...we need detailed
15-year financial projections.
Fifteen years?
Yes. If the figures
meet our requirement...
...we're prepared
to close the deal immediately.
I understand.
You'll have the projections
by Wednesday.
If you have a minute, I'd like you
to meet our president, Mr. Drake.
Excuse me.
One of the unique features
of this property...
Terrific, Waymon.
Don't let them move.
I'm on my way.
As I was saying...
- Excuse me, David.
We'll have to continue this later.
Something important has come up.
Listen, why don't you
reschedule with Peg, huh?
Sure.
Okay, I...
- Hey, Bobby.
- Gary.
Doing up here
fronting in that weak-ass suit?
Better get your Dr. Doolittle ass
upstairs before Monroe busts you.
What are you talking about?
I'm out of the mailroom.
I'm in the training program now.
You?
Training program?
What is this, the Twilight Zone?
I've been trying to get in that program
since I started this gig.
- How you get in?
- David Barnes.
He liked my initiative.
Initiative? What initiative?
Hey, why you jumping
all over me, man?
It's not my fault that I'm in
and you're not.
Yeah, you're right.
Hey, man, congrats.
Like I always said:
"If you wanna make a power move,
you gotta have a hook-up. "
You go for yours.
I'll damn sure go for mine.
Wednesday. Wednesday.
- Perfect.
- I had a good teacher.
The presentation was excellent.
But I'm concerned
about those projections.
Don't be. The guy was taking advantage
of the soft market.
He closed two foreclosure deals
in Los Angeles last month.
This property is a steal.
And he knows it. Trust me.
Cafe 43.
Yeah. Yes, he is.
Sure. No problem.
Listen, Mr. Atwell needs
to call his office.
- He's at Table 6.
- Okay.
Closing this deal is important
to the bank and to you.
Yes, I know.
Excuse me.
Mr. Atwell, there's a call for you.
I think you owe me
an explanation, missy.
Coming half an hour late
in the middle of the lunch rush.
There must have been 100 people
at that audition.
- Audition?
- Yes.
If you had your priorities straight
you would have been here on time.
I tried to get here on time.
Really, I did.
I don't care.
if you would have left earlier...
...then I wouldn't be here
trying to be manager and hostess.
Okay, you're right. I'm sorry.
It'll never, ever happen again.
Oh, I know it won't happen again
since I will have to fire you, missy.
Oh, come on, Russ.
You know how much I need this job.
It's too late for begging, missy.
You're over.
Missy? I have a name.
- Use it.
- Lower your voice.
I will do whatever the hell
I wanna do...
...because I've had it with you
and this trifling job.
I don't need this shit.
It's not my career, unlike yourself,
Mr. Professional-Ass-Kisser.
You're fired!
Get out.
With pleasure.
Thanks.
Miss.
Is something wrong, sir?
Hm? Uh...
No. We're ready to order. Thank you.
I don't look like a broker to you?
That goes to show
how much you know...
...about the world
of real estate, baby.
A lot of us wear sneakers.
It's a fast-moving game,
you just got to be able to keep up.
Well, look, if you can't keep up,
I'm gonna have to step off.
Step off now.
It's cool, homey.
Just a minute, all right?
Yeah, so, if...
Hello? Hello, Tonya?
Man, what's up with that shit, man?
- I was almost in there.
In where?
In there, man.
You wouldn't know nothing about that,
so squash it.
You know...
...I am getting real tired of you
constantly abusing my friendship.
I try to do things for you
whenever I can.
And still, you pull stunts like this.
Like what?
Like what? Like using my office
as your own personal cafeteria.
- Suppose I had been with a client.
- But you weren't.
But suppose I was.
This place smells
like a fast-food explosion.
So open up a window
or something, man.
I came here to talk to you for a reason.
What now?
Training program, man.
- You was gonna hook me up.
- I did nothing of the sort.
You asked me about it,
I told you. Simple.
You said you was gonna help me.
Don't front on me like that.
Even if that was true, which it's not...
...they aren't accepting
any new trainees now.
That's bullshit. My boy Gary O'Hara
just made the cut.
Well, Gary went to St. John's University.
I went to school too.
Community college.
Not exactly the same thing.
This is bogus.
Why you illing like that?
Now, see? That is what
I am talking about.
"llling"?
What kind of word is that?
Look at the way you're dressed.
I work in the mailroom. What am I
supposed to wear, Armani suit?
No.
But you don't have to speak
and dress so...
So... How do I put this?
- Black?
- Well, yes, black.
You know what, G?
You are straight-up
whiter than the whitest white man.
I thought there was a bit of black
under that tired blue suit you got on.
I see what time it is with you now.
Thanks for nothing, Mr. Tinsdale.
Diedre on line one.
Hi.
Waymon, how could you
cancel lunch today?
I had something very important
to talk to you about.
Don't you love me?
Diedre, please. Of course I do.
I don't wanna fight with you now.
I had to take a very important client
to lunch.
More important than me, I suppose?
Well, yes. Today, I suppose he was.
All right.
I'll just forget you ever said that.
It's not important.
I know how obsessive you can be
about work.
All is forgiven.
We'll talk about it tomorrow
on the squash court.
Don't be late. Ciao, sweetie.
- Good night, Mr. Tinsdale.
- Oh, good night, Donna.
I don't know
where you know Natalie from...
...but you might as well keep
your miniature-ass dick in your pants...
...because the girl's too fly for you.
Wait. You know this girl? Bobby.
Pfft. Pencil dick.
Weenie roast.
Pig in a blanket. Mini-squirt.
Hey, look at Mitchell over there.
- Yeah.
- I hear he lost his job. His firm folded.
Oh, man. Another real-estate broker
bites the dust.
- That could be one of us.
- Not me.
I have Porsche payments to make.
- I told you not to buy that car now.
- I already have a mother.
Anyway, as soon as Drake hands me
that partnership, I'm set.
- You?
- Mm-hm.
Be serious. Tinsdale is the man.
Everybody knows that.
Yeah, everybody is wrong.
Our token black is not gonna use...
...affirmative action to get my job.
Whoa. I thought you and Waymon
were buddies.
What does that have to do
with anything?
I would just think
you'd be happy for him.
Not as happy as I'd be for me.
- Hey, guys.
- Waymon.
- We were just talking about you.
- How you doing?
- What took so long? You're late.
- Work. What else? I'm still not done.
I'm just here taking a quick break.
Uh, club soda with lime, please.
You shouldn't work so hard, Waymon.
You should find a nice little honey,
have some fun.
- I have one.
- Who, Diedre? I thought that was over.
Yeah, well...
...we decided to give it another try.
She must be a champ
between the sheets.
Hang tough, Mitch. Wow.
You know, his mistake was buying
all of that property up in Harlem.
I tried to tell him that
gentrification shit was just a pipe dream.
I mean, even Waymon wouldn't
be caught dead in that wasteland.
Isn't that right, Waymon?
Hey, don't be stupid.
Waymon probably grew up there, right?
I don't think Waymon's
ever even been to Harlem.
You ever been to Harlem, Waymon?
You...
I gotta get back to work.
You guys take it easy.
See you.
What the hell are you doing here?
- Me?
- You.
I don't see
anyone else here stealing.
- What you talking about, stealing?
- I'm talking about these.
Don't you know I have to account
for every piece of paper...
...every envelope,
every damn paper clip in here?
It's my responsibility
to see that thieves like you...
...don't nickel-and-dime this place
out of business.
I wouldn't be bragging on no shit
if I were you.
Mother... What? That's it. You're fired.
You're finished. Get out.
What's going on in here?
Uh, nothing for you to concern
yourself with, Mr. Tinsdale.
Well, I am concerned.
I caught him red-handed,
stealing company property.
What property?
These.
- These are mine.
- Yours?
- What?
- They're mine.
Well, actually,
a client of mine's.
Bobby was doing me a favor,
weren't you?
Yeah, yeah. I thought you had
cleared that with Mr. Taylor.
Yeah, I don't appreciate that, man.
You almost got me fired.
I'm down here trying to do business for you.
You know what I'm saying?
You got me in a limbo.
You put my shit in jeopardy.
I said, I was sorry. Drop it.
I apologize, Monroe.
This won't happen again.
I am not taking the fall
for any shady goings-on.
Good night.
So, what brings you down here?
Slumming or what?
Bobby, this girl on the flyer,
you know her?
Yeah, I know her. So, what about it?
Well, she was in this restaurant,
I was having lunch...
...and she dropped this photograph.
And I'd like to return it.
This about Natalie?
This should be about the way
you dissed me.
Come on, Bobby,
I made a mistake in judgment, okay?
I'm sorry.
I was wrong not to at least listen.
Yeah, okay. But I'm gonna tell you now.
She ain't gonna be interested
in no square, blockheaded nigga like you.
Later.
Bobby.
Just tell me where to find her.
Yeah, keep dreaming.
Besides, what's in it for me?
- A promotion.
- I heard that before.
Not from a partner, you haven't.
Partner?
You introduce me to Natalie...
...and start dressing like
you're going to work and not to a party...
...and I'll put you
into the training program.
Deal?
Yeah, deal.
Yeah.
Shit. I'm late.
Concentrate.
I'm not playing anymore.
Not until I find out
what is going on here.
I'll tell you what's going on here.
Nothing. Absolutely nothing.
Waymon, you're throwing us
completely off schedule.
I was half an hour late. Shoot me.
Don't tempt me.
I'm not talking about today, stupid.
I'm talking about every day.
Stupid?
Waymon, if we don't start investing
some quality time into this relationship...
...I'm afraid everything's gonna go
out of whack.
What are you talking about?
Well.
Way...
...I was figuring
that if we're engaged by Christmas...
...then we can find the most perfect
condo in the winter...
...which is the best time to shop.
And then be married by summer.
Married by summer?
Oh, honey, it's the only possible time
for me to vacation.
Look, we've only been back together
for two weeks.
I mean, don't you think
that this is just a little premature?
I think you better
get with the program, mister...
...or lose the best woman you ever had.
Diedre, wait.
Diedre.
Well, Millicent, you go to bed
with dogs, you wake up with fleas.
And believe me, I am scratching.
Well, you cannot say
I didn't tell you so.
No, I guess I can't, Diedre.
I knew he was wrong for you
the first time I met him.
Oh, God. Sometimes I think
I'm just better off alone.
Karen, how can you say that?
Look at Waymon and me.
Our relationship is great.
When you choose a man
with your head...
...and not your heart,
you make a smarter choice.
So I may not be in love
with Waymon...
...but I know we make
a damn good team.
What about romance, passion,
sex till you can't stand up straight.
I need that.
You got that and where'd that get you?
A broken heart, a sore back,
a yeast infection.
And a stack of bills.
Speaking of sore backs.
I sure hope there's gonna be men
at this party.
Don't worry. Diedre has it covered.
Waymon is inviting some eligibles
from work.
Oh, God. I can imagine.
Excuse me?
Beggars can't be choosers.
Check, please.
Darryl, did Johnson get back
from lunch yet?
You hear me talking to you, boy?
I'm working through lunch
if you don't mind.
Working through lunch?
Man, what you looking at?
You must be on something.
Or coming off it.
I ain't on nothing and you know it.
Oh, you're on something all right.
Must be some powerful shit too.
- What I tell you?
- You got it, man.
Yo, yo.
- Hey.
- Well?
- Well, what?
- Well, what? Natalie.
- Don't worry about it.
- You in there.
- In where?
Forget about it. Meet me at
the Kilimanjaro tonight, midnight.
Midnight? Are you crazy?
I can't meet you at midnight.
I've gotta work tomorrow.
And so do you.
If you stay up past 9:00 one night,
it's not gonna kill you.
That may be true,
but I can't meet you tonight anyway.
- I've gotta meet Diedre.
- Man, you going out like that?
No, as a matter of fact,
we're staying in.
That's not what I meant, man.
Look, if you're there, you're there.
If you're not,
hey, I did my part, right?
Okay. Now, look...
Hey, Bobby. What's up?
- What's up, G-Man?
Gary...
...let's go.
What'd you wanna speak to me about?
I wanted to let you know
I think you're doing an excellent job.
Better than I could've hoped for.
Thanks. Thanks, Mr. Barnes.
But I wanna make sure
you go the distance.
The distance?
Let me be more specific.
Gary, my future is your future.
Where I go, you go.
When I am a partner in the most
powerful real-estate firm in New York...
...we're gonna own this town.
That is, if you're willing to do
what it takes.
Yeah. Yeah, I'm willing to do anything.
- I'm a team player.
- Good. Good.
I'm glad to hear that, Gary.
Driver, stop the car.
Gary.
Gary, get home safe, okay?
All right. Okay, a little to the left.
- A little to the left.
Sorry.
Oh, good. All right. Now, grab it.
Grab it. Harder.
Oh, good.
All right. Don't stop.
I said, don't stop.
Good. All right. I'm there. I'm there.
I'm there.
Oh! Yes!
Ahh. Ah.
Could you get off me, please?
- Ow. Careful.
- Sorry.
For the thing.
Excuse me.
Excuse me, please.
Excuse me. Excuse me, please.
Excuse me. Good evening.
Good evening.
Hi, ladies. How are you?
Come on in.
Have a good time tonight.
How are you doing, man?
You can forget it.
- Bobby.
- Hey, hey. What's up?
- All right.
- How are you doing, big man?
- What's up? You ready for this?
- Come on in.
- I'm with him.
- Sure.
- Hey, Bobby?
- Oh, he's with me.
Sorry, man. Come on in.
Hey. Hey.
What was that guy's problem?
Hey, man, if you're in, you're in.
If you're not, you're not. Simple as that.
You're saying I'm not in?
Look, don't you own
any fly gear at all, man?
If you mean trendy clothes, no.
They're a waste of money.
Look, if you wanna get next to Natalie,
who is definitely high-level...
...you're gonna have to spend
some big bucks, man.
This happens to be
a Brooks Brothers suit.
Yeah. I suggest
you write that shit on the front.
Because it looks like
any old tired-ass gray suit to me.
What's up
with the Frankenstein shoes?
- That shows how much you know.
- Hey, hey.
That's all I'm trying to say.
- Look, where is she?
- Look, man, she's here, all right?
Try to have a little fun.
If you know how.
Well, maybe she's not here tonight.
I should go home
and get some work done.
Look, the girl gives the parties here,
all right?
Her job is to be here.
She's gonna be here.
Why don't you just give that work shit
a rest, all right? And just chill.
Yo, what you need?
Yeah, yeah, give me
a Hennessey and Coke.
And for my boy...
Waymon, what you want?
Club soda, please, with lime.
Man, what's up
with the club soda?
It's late. I don't handle
hard liquor too well late at night.
That sounds like some shit
you need to keep to yourself.
You don't want people thinking
you're soft.
Yo. I see skin. I'll be back.
What? You see what?
- So, what's your name, baby?
- Davika.
- That's not your club name, huh?
- No. Do you have a club name?
No, I ain't got no club name.
My name is straight-up Bobby.
Would you like to dance?
Excuse me.
I'm sorry.
Excuse me. Excuse me. Please.
Excuse me. Excuse me.
You with the corny suit on.
Yeah. You just knocked over my drinks.
You gotta pay for it.
Mr. Tinsdale knew
you were coming by this morning.
I can't imagine what happened to him.
Let me check his office
for the financial projections.
You can look them over while you wait.
He'll be in shortly.
I certainly hope so.
Waymon?
Mr. Tinsdale.
- What time is it?
- Ten-fifteen.
You had at 10 a. m. with Mr. Atwell.
Oh, damn.
You what?
I called Mr. Kagawa and let them know
that they'll have it by Friday.
We should have discussed this.
I apologize. It just turned out to be
more work than I anticipated.
You do realize how important
this deal is to both of us?
- Yes, sir, I'm aware of that.
- You better be.
Uh, Mr. Atwell, sir? Mr. Atwell.
Mr. Atwell, please.
This is not a problem. Believe me
when I tell you that I am on top of this...
- I hope you haven't blown it.
- We'll speak later.
Damn.
Excuse me one second.
Hey, Waymon, wait up.
Waymon. Waymon, what's wrong?
You look awful.
I'm fine.
Come on, this is me you're talking to.
I know there's something wrong.
The Savoy Tower projections.
I just never thought it would be
this much work.
Well, why don't you let me help?
That's okay. I got it covered.
Hey, what are friends for?
Friends?
I gotta get back to work.
We'll talk about this later in private.
Yeah. Yeah.
Excuse me.
What's with you and him?
He's a racist bastard.
Is that what you came in here
to tell me?
If it is, I don't have time
to listen to your militant ravings right now.
Just chill, brother. And picture this:
Champagne, mellow music, you...
...and Natalie
making that love connection.
Oh, I can picture it.
When is it going to happen?
- Tonight.
- Tonight?
No, I can't make it tonight.
I gotta get some sleep.
I've got a deadline to meet.
I can't blow it. What about tomorrow?
Tomorrow works for me.
Man, this ain't no damn power lunch, man.
This is love.
You can't be
penciling that shit in, man.
Let me tell you something.
That ham is cooked, glazed
and ready to be sliced.
You just gotta go for it.
Okay. Okay.
I just can't stay out late.
Bet. But you can't go with me
looking like that tonight.
What is wrong with the way I dress?
Don't make me answer that.
But I tell you what,
meet me after work...
...I'll take you to the place.
I'll hook you up.
Yeah.
Bet.
No, no, no.
Forget it.
All right.
- You got it.
- I got it?
- I got it.
Yo, I got it going on.
You know
what I'm saying to you, baby?
I'm kicking it a lot.
Oh, shit.
I called you a hundred times.
You didn't return any of my calls.
That's very unprofessional
of you, Waymon.
Look, honey, you've come
at a really bad time.
I was on my way out the door.
What is going on with you?
And I know
you are not seeing someone else.
What? No, no.
Of course not. Come on.
Now, look, I have a very important
meeting with my Japanese buyers.
- Dressed like that?
- What do you mean?
- Honey, I swear, you look like a jerk.
- Gee, thanks, hon.
I didn't mean that.
- So why don't I come with?
- You can't.
I mean, you know how these Japanese
are about women seen and not heard.
- Yes.
- Diedre, please. I'm running late.
You're always
talking about staying focused.
Making that almighty dollar
always comes first.
- Right.
- A condo...
...Benz, exotic vacations.
Now, how am I supposed to get
all of that for you?
I'll tell you how,
by working my tail off night and day.
That's how, right?
I guess you're right.
I knew you'd understand.
Hey, where are we going, anyway?
You the one who said
you wanted to chase the girl down, right?
So chill out and drive, man.
Are we in Harlem?
Yeah. So?
Nothing.
Don't tell me
you never been to Harlem before.
That's crazy retarded.
- You never been to Harlem before.
- Of course I've been uptown before.
I just didn't know we were
coming up here tonight, that's all.
What is this, one of those crack alleys?
Crack alleys? Man, you tripping.
This doesn't look safe to me, Bobby.
Why don't you stop squawking
like a sucker?
Don't nobody want what you got.
Ow.
She came here
to meet some of her people.
There she is.
- Who are those guys?
- Those guys are large and in charge.
That's all you need to know.
Like I was saying,
we should make a move on 2-5 Street.
You're right.
People don't appreciate the value
of that location.
Yeah, brother. If we could
just bum-rush that entire situation.
Hey, fellas, how's it going?
- Hey, Johnson.
This is Waymon Tinsdale.
Hey, home dudes. What is going on?
Excuse us. We're busy.
Hey, hey, no problem.
Girl, he may be cute,
but he got too many ain't-gots.
- So, what you saying?
- I'm saying he ain't got no A-P-T.
Uh-huh.
- He ain't got no J-O-B.
- I heard that.
And he ain't got no C-A-R.
You know, you can ride a dream
by yourself, girlfriend.
- Thank you.
- There it is.
Hi.
It's on the house.
Uh...
Thanks.
You all right?
You seem a little nervous.
Me, nervous?
Hey, no. I'm just chilling.
Is love this place. It's really, uh, def.
Right.
Well, enjoy yourself.
What's happening, troop?
What you drinking?
- Uh, club soda with lime.
- Club soda with lime, yeah.
Hey, bartender,
give us two shots of Black Label.
No, I...
Listen, Sherm, let me explain
something to you about women.
These young ladies in here...
...any man, even you,
can pull a serious fine honey out of here.
All you gotta do is remember
one golden rule, which is...
...the man with the gold, rules.
Hey, I'd love to,
but my jeep is in the shop.
Jeep? I thought you said
you had a Benz.
I said that?
- Yeah.
- I mean, my Benz, uh...
Hey, Bobby, man.
I've been looking all over for you.
- Johnnie Walker, Black.
- Man, what you been doing?
Hey, man. Hey, sharp as a tack.
Your ass is leery, man.
- You've been over there...
- Maybe you two could use a little drink.
Thanks, Nat.
You know, you're kind of cute.
You're in there.
- I'm in there.
- In there.
- Hey, I'm the man.
- You're the man.
Hey, man, I'm jamming on the...
Oh, shit.
How about a BMW, baby?
Know when to say when, boyfriend.
You're a valued member
of this firm, David.
Thank you.
- A real team player.
I try, sir.
You and Waymon Tinsdale are friends,
aren't you?
Yes. Why?
Is he in some sort of trouble?
Oh, no, no. Nothing like that.
It's just that he is focusing
on a very important deal these days...
...and hasn't much time
for anything else.
I've tried to warn him
not to put all his eggs in one basket.
What I wanna know is...
...can you take on
some of his smaller deals?
I want him to stay concentrated
on the Savoy Tower deal.
When he closes that one...
...it'll be a victory for the whole team.
- Of course.
- Ah!
- I knew I could count on you.
- Thank you.
To hell with that deal
and the damn team.
- Need some help?
- No.
Listen. I've been meaning to talk to you
about my status here at the club.
Since I took over promotions,
business has tripled.
I should be a partner.
- Jake.
- What?
You and I both know
I made this club hot.
Look. I don't have time for this
right now, okay?
Hopefully we can talk about it later on.
Natalie...
...these just came for you.
Oh, thank you.
Finally.
- Congratulations.
Have you arranged for the messenger
for tomorrow morning?
Absolutely.
Don't forget to toss
these earlier projections.
The numbers are all wrong.
No problem. I'll take them down
to recycling right now.
You've done enough for one day.
Take care of it tomorrow.
- Good night.
- Hi, Bobby.
- How're you doing?
- How's the head?
- Uh.
Terrible. But I haven't had time
to think about it.
I've been working
on the Savoy Tower deal.
The deal I almost blew
hanging out with you.
Tomorrow morning, the projections
will be delivered by messenger...
...at 7 a. m.
- Messenger?
Are you crazy? Those brothers are ill.
Give it to me, I'll take it.
They're not in right now, anyway.
And I don't wanna take the chance
that the hotel will lose it.
Besides, I feel more comfortable
with a professional messenger.
Man, now I'm insulted.
Tomorrow morning, the deal will be done.
You'll be my trainee.
Not because you helped me
meet Natalie...
...but because
you deserve the chance.
The least you could do is trust me
to make a run across town.
With this in the hands
of a stranger...
...you won't be able to concentrate on
the real deal: getting busy with Natalie.
Okay. I get your point.
- Seven a. m.
- I'll be there at 6:30.
Great. Now, where's my car?
- I left it at home.
- What?
Don't worry. It's safe, all right?
All right.
Look.
Meet me at this address
at 10:00.
Don't be late.
Tonight's the night.
Bet.
You know, we have sort of this open thing
happening now, you know?
And I really believe in giving a man
his space.
It can benefit everyone
in the relationship.
Now, don't you agree?
Well, I don't know.
I'm married, faithful and very happy.
Oh, congratulations. Excuse me.
Waymon. Waymon.
Hi, Waymon? Hey.
You remember...
You remember, uh, Susan. Susan.
Nice to meet you.
So how's the Atwell deal coming?
Great. Great.
What? What, it's done?
No. It will be tomorrow
when they receive the new projections.
Oh, I see. Oh, well, that's great.
That's great. Good luck, Waymon.
Thank you. Thank you.
Waymon. Honey.
Excuse me.
Hey, turn that down
or I'm calling the police.
- You talking to me?
- I don't see any other idiots out here.
Crazy bitch.
- Low-life.
- Baby, your weave's too tight.
Oh, shit.
With this recession and unemployment
reaching an all-time high...
...the job market is a merciless place.
- Isn't that right?
- Hm?
Uh, yes, absolutely.
The black youth have it the worst.
And it's a shame
that they just aren't prepared.
I honestly think they don't know
what it takes to get ahead.
What exactly are you saying?
I'm saying that...
...carving your name
on the back of your head...
...is not exactly a career move.
Diedre, that's ridiculous.
I mean, one thing
has absolutely nothing to do with the other.
- Would you excuse us, please?
- Certainly.
How dare you contradict me
in front of people.
I don't know what's going on with you,
but I don't like it.
You know what's going on me?
I'm finally seeing the light.
Who do you think you are
that you can tell me what to think?
Or what to wear, what to do?
I need a companion. I need a friend.
Not an overseer.
I will not have this discussion here.
I'll call the police.
- You better stop fronting.
- I ain't after your fake-ass gold.
- Excuse me.
I'm here to see Waymon.
- Waymon?
Hey.
- What's up?
- What is this person doing here?
Person? You fake Whitney Houston-ass...
- You nappy-headed thing...
- All right. Hold it.
This person happens to be
a friend of mine.
- His name is Bobby Johnson.
A friend of yours?
I'm not gonna take much more of this.
This shit is whack. I'm out of here.
- Bobby, wait.
- Wait.
Hey, you coming?
Coming where?
If you leave this party with that thug...
...it's over.
I never wanna see you again.
Okay.
Fine.
You son of a bitch!
You better get your black ass
out here.
I'm counting to one, two...
Man, don't even sweat that, man.
She ain't all that.
She needs to take
some of that attorney money...
...and purchase some more ass.
That what she need to do.
Come on. You know the girl look like
a well-dressed number-two pencil, man.
Sex was probably weak too.
She's like one of them
military-type bitches.
Military?
You know, military. You know:
Left, right, left
In, out, in
Hump, half, hump, right
Hump, full, hump
I'm right, right?
Just be there in half an hour.
Gary, I really don't care.
Just be there.
I'm sorry, everybody,
but the club's been closed.
- What?
- I'm as surprised as all of you are.
But you'll all get invitations
to my next event.
I'm really sorry.
What's going on?
The club has been padlocked
by the damn IRS.
And that asshole Jake
didn't even tell me what was up.
I invited all these people down here.
And now I look like a fool.
No, you don't.
More than that,
I don't even get paid for tonight.
I can just forget about my partnership.
I gotta get out of here.
Can you give me a ride?
Oh, yeah. Right. Right.
No problem.
Why don't you go ahead?
I got some important things
to take care of tomorrow.
Yeah, we'll see you later.
See you.
My boy's in there.
Watch your legs.
Come on. Come on.
You're late.
- Are you serious?
- Yes, I am.
Now, come on.
I'm so tired of everything always
blowing up in my face.
Nothing I do ever turns out
the way I plan it.
What is it exactly that you wanna do?
Well, for a long time, it was dancing.
But the auditions are murder.
And then when I finally do get a job,
the money barely pays the rent.
I just don't know anymore.
You know what
I've always dreamed of doing?
- Owning my own nightclub.
- Yeah?
- Mm-hm.
- Well, don't give up on that one.
When I was in junior high school,
I wanted to join a band.
You know, be a rock star.
So I asked my parents
if I could take guitar lessons.
They said, "Absolutely not.
We're not going to spend
our hard-earned money...
...on some guitar lessons. "
So I tried to teach myself...
...and after a while,
I got discouraged and I stopped.
Now, if I'd continued, who knows?
Might have been
Michael Jackson, Prince...
...Waymon Tinsdale III.
There's not a more beautiful view
in all the world.
You are so beautiful.
Thank you.
Are we gonna get busted
for this?
Not if you keep your mouth shut.
Bingo. Okay.
We're just gonna make a few changes
in these projections, okay?
Come on.
Do your thing.
- Come on.
- All right. All right. All right.
- We're in.
- Yeah.
What's up, Pep?
Mr. Kagawa on line one.
Good morning.
I trusted you and you blew it.
How could you have messed this up?
How? How?
- Get off me, man. You tripping.
- Yeah, I'm tripping.
What the hell's going on here?
The Savoy Tower deal. Bobby blew it.
I showed him the package...
...but somehow he managed to get an
earlier draft with all the wrong numbers.
All I did is what you asked me to do.
That's all I did.
The Japanese took one look
at those figures, made a phone call...
...and closed a deal
with somebody else.
They're on a plane to Los Angeles.
I'm finished. And so are you.
Well, you heard the man. You're fired.
Get your stuff and go.
I'm very sorry, sir.
I don't know how this happened.
What do you mean?
You put a multimillion-dollar deal
in the hands of a mail boy.
That's how it happened. Waymon...
...this isn't the kind of error
a partner would make.
Wait a minute. Sir, I can fix this.
- I just have to find a new buyer.
- We've lost the listing.
Atwell intends
to take the bank's business...
...to another firm on Monday.
Mr. Drake, I can do this.
I doubt it.
Well, what about Sunday?
We can do brunch.
Yeah, I see. Well, this deal is ready to go.
Sure. Sure.
Well, some of the best deals are done
on short notice.
Mr. Vance, excuse me. I'm sorry.
One second.
- Yeah, Sheila, what is it?
There's a Natalie here to see you.
Send her in.
Sorry about that, Mr. Vance.
As I was saying, the... Hello?
- Hello, Mr. Vance?
Hi.
Mr. Vance. Damn.
Would you get me Vance
on the line again, please?
- Now.
- Yes, sir.
- Hi.
What is it?
You invited me to lunch, remember?
Damn. I've been so busy,
I totally forgot.
I'm sorry, I can't go now.
No problem. You wanna meet later?
I don't think so.
What's the matter with you?
This happens to be the worst day
of my life. That's the matter.
There's a whole lot of that going around.
Darryl just told me Bobby got fired.
Yeah, well, he's a big boy.
I'm sure he'll get over it.
I thought you two were friends.
Hardly. If it hadn't been for him dragging
me all over the city chasing after you...
...none of this would have happened.
What's that supposed to mean?
Nothing. Nothing.
I have Mr. Vance on the line.
Uh, excuse me. I have to take this.
Take it and shove it.
I don't know what made me think
you were so different.
Natalie.
Natalie. Natalie, wait. Natalie, please.
Drop dead.
Natalie. Natalie.
- Waymon?
- What?
Don't snap at me.
Just calm down for a minute.
I printed a copy of the final report.
This is completely different
than any of our drafts.
This wasn't a mix-up.
Someone or something
must have changed the projections.
But whoever it was,
it wasn't Bobby.
Hi.
Hey.
Listen, I, uh...
I just wanted to say job well done.
Oh, thanks.
You know, Bobby got fired.
He was on his way out anyway.
Look, business is business.
Remember that.
Take this to Processing.
Hey, the girl was dope.
You know what I'm saying?
Ten-high. It's Sydney Poitier.
Guess who's coming to get high?
Hey, Bobby, can I talk to you?
I can't hear you.
Ain't you heard?
He ain't got the booters no more.
- Please?
- We ain't got no crack neither, Sydney.
You're in the wrong spot for that.
Hey, look,
why don't you just back off, okay?
You want a piece of me?
- Come on.
- Better do something about that.
- Let's do this.
- Man. Man, time-out.
Let's take a walk.
All right. So you came here to talk.
So talk.
I wanted to apologize
for what happened today.
I accused you of doing something
that you didn't do.
That you couldn't have done.
I'm sorry.
That's black folks' problem, man.
Always passing judgment
on each other.
Putting our own brothers down,
and for what?
You're right.
We're friends.
Bobby, I should have trusted you.
People need to give each other
more credit, man.
Take a little more time
to understand each other.
Look, Bobby, I'm probably gonna
offer the firm my resignation.
But I want you to know that before I go,
I'm gonna try to get your job back.
Quit?
No, man, you can't go out like that.
We need you in there,
help put some brothers down.
Bobby, I've gotta find a buyer
willing to invest $ 75 million by Monday.
- It's impossible.
- Nothing's impossible.
You deserve that partnership, man.
Look, I got an idea.
Am I still your trainee?
Hey, you know it.
It's, "You know that.
You know that. "
Whatever. What are you gonna do?
Get your high-powered
presentation together.
I'll check you on Monday.
I got some people I gotta see.
What are you gonna do?
Just get out of Harlem
before you get your ass whipped.
Here you are.
Been looking all over for you.
Now you know where to find me.
The late Frank Burke's office.
- Did you have a good weekend?
- Pretty good.
You wanna get some lunch? My treat.
Why not? You can take me to
the Ferry Bank Caf. I love that place.
Are you crazy?
It's all the way in Brooklyn.
Hey, you're going out
with the boss.
Lunch is over when I say
that lunch is over.
Now you're talking.
All right.
He's having trouble with the financing
on this gold-company deal.
It's not penciling out right.
I could get a better loan
from a guy named Vinny.
It's the Halloran brothers
to see Waymon Tinsdale.
Sheila, the Halloran brothers
to see Mr. Tinsdale.
Well, Bobby, here's your boy.
- Hey, what's up?
- Hey. All right.
Y'all remember my homeboy,
Waymon Tinsdale?
How could I forget?
It's nice to see you again.
Leroy Halloran. These are my brothers
Roland and Theodore.
The Halloran brothers?
The ones that own
the Harlem National Bank?
In the flesh.
Oh, I didn't know.
Man, you must have really thought
I was a jerk the first time we met.
You could say that.
But thanks to Bobby,
we came anyway.
- Hey, just doing my job.
- And a good job it is.
Would you escort these gentlemen
to conference room B, please?
Hey, no problem. Fellas?
Get Atwell on the phone.
No, send a limousine for him.
Tell him I'm meeting with the Halloran
brothers of the Harlem National Bank.
I present to you the Savoy Tower.
Downtown Manhattan,
prime real estate.
One, we'll begin...
And one of the most exciting features
is the pedestrian mall.
it has 84 stories.
Six million dollars.
Four-four-seven-zero
two-nine-four-seven-zero-three...
- two thousand dollars per square foot,
offers a projected income...
...of a quarter of a billion dollars.
All right.
We're only a little apart on pricing.
You sweeten your deal by $2 million,
you got a deal.
- Deal.
- Yeah.
Hey, yeah.
Waymon, what the hell
is going on here?
Mr. Drake.
We were getting ready to call you
and invite you down to the celebration.
Celebration?
Yes. With the assistance
of Mr. Bobby Johnson...
...the Savoy Tower has a buyer.
Oh?
Mr. Drake, I'd like to introduce you
to the Halloran brothers...
...of Harlem National Bank.
- What's up, homes?
- What's happening, Jack?
They've agreed to our terms.
I see.
Well, Mr. Johnson...
...where's my glass?
- Thank you very much, sir.
It feels good, doesn't it?
- Roland, thank you for coming by.
- Yes.
We look forward to seeing you.
Anything I can do.
Boy, that's the life, huh?
Are you just coming back
from lunch?
- Yes, sir.
- I'll speak with you later.
Hey, what's going on here?
Only closing the Savoy Towers deal.
What? Wait, what are you doing here?
You were fired.
Well, he's rehired.
I'm taking this up with the board, sir.
And tell them what?
All right, shut up and get out.
You're fired.
You can't fire me, because I quit.
This is getting good.
Mr. Tinsdale, I changed the figures
on your report Thursday night.
- You did what?
- What?
I know...
David told me to do it.
You damn liar.
You watch yourself, Mr. Barnes.
I shouldn't have done it.
I'm sorry.
I don't have to stay here
and listen to this.
It says here,
"David Barnes, in, 12:30 a. m., out... "
Give me that, you stupid nig...
God, dog.
Way to go, Waymon.
Mr. Tinsdale, I'll see you
in the office, partner.
Yes, sir.
- Thank you.
I didn't know he had it in him.
Uh... Uh...
...Mr. Drake, if I could just...
- Partner. I'm a partner.
- Partner. You did it.
- All this time, man.
- That's what he said, man.
- Tyson. You see that jab?
- Whoo!
Who is it?
- Waymon.
What do you want?
Uh... Well...
...I came by because
I wanted to apologize for what happened.
I'm really sorry.
You should be.
I never ever wanted to hurt you.
Natalie, I just want another chance.
I need you.
I hope he brought his kneepads.
I'm on my knees. I'm begging.
Get up. Somebody might see you.
I don't care who sees me.
Come on, get up.
Not until you say yes.
Yes. Get up.
What's up, man?
I thought we was going for a ride.
Hey, I got something I want you to see.
Come on.
It's great. It's great.
You're gonna love it.
Yo, Bobby.
- Hey, Nat.
Man, you went out, man.
I can't believe my boy went out
like that.
Oh, hardwood floors.
Yes.
But it's bigger than hardwood floors.
This is really big.
You gotta get ready.
It's bigger than gigantic.
Gigantic.
- This is the biggest thing. It is so big.
- One, two, three, surprise!
What do you think?
Well...
...I think it's great.
- But what is it?
- What is it?
It's what you've always wanted.
It's your own club.
The Halloran brothers agreed to put up
all the money.
If you do the work,
they split the profits with you fifty-fifty.
What do you say?
I say yes.
It's all in a day's work, babydoll.
Me and Waymon hooked it up.
It's a business-type thing,
you know?
Start getting busy on the business side,
ain't nothing we can't do.
Start getting busy.
Excuse...
Yo, I did some shit too.
There you go. Okay.
That's what I'm talking about.
- Hey.
- Man, come on.
Good night, Mr. Tinsdale.
Hey, man. You still working?
We're going to be late.
Hey, business first, right?
I like the way you think.
- You ready for this?
- Hey, I was born ready.
You were born ready. Is that right?
- Yeah.
Speaking of ready,
you seen Drake's new secretary?
I already closed that deal.
- Yeah, well, she told me.
- I think it's the suit.
- No, I think it's the paycheck.
- Good night, Donna.
- Good night, Mr. Tinsdale. Mr. Johnson.
See you.
Whoa! Are you ready for this?
Ain't nothing to it,
but to do it, brother.
- Let's go.
- Time to party.
Hey, hey, what's happening, man?
Okay.
- What's up, chill?
- My man.
Hey, how you living?
All right. All right.
I see you.
Looking good.
Now, don't forget. Don't forget.
Hey, my man. My man, my man.
You know, we gotta talk.
I'll be back.
- Hi, baby.
- Hey.
- I'm glad you came.
- All right.
- You're gorgeous.
- Thank you.
You don't look too bad yourself.
Excuse me.
- Excuse me.
- Pardon, please.
- Pardon me.
- Excuse me.
And what is so damn funny?
Let us in.
- This ain't for you, all right?
- The nerve.
I demand to see somebody in charge.
Oh, man, perfect timing.
These ladies wanna talk to you.
Aha. Ah!
If it isn't
Teenage Mutant Negro Chicken Legs.
- Taxi. Oh, excuse us.
- Excuse us.
Damn, she could Hula-Hoop
with a damn Cheerio, couldn't she?
That's right, get out of here. See you.