I may be on the verge
of discovering the true nature
of Destiny's mission.
You've had
control of this ship
the whole time!
Why wouldn't you tell anyone?
The Lucian
alliance is planning
an attack on Earth.
I killed Riley.
I suffocated him
with my own hands.
You are a good commander.
There is no mission
other than getting
these people home.
It was never about
going home.
It's about getting us
to where we're going.
That is the mission.
I've just been going over
the shuttle's navigational data
trying to figure out
The path you took
back to Destiny.
It seems you were there,
and then you were here.
Nothing in between.
Every square inch of this thing
is in perfect factory condition.
:There's hundreds
of these things!
There's no way we're going to
be able to shoot them all down!
How's that
damage report coming?
I'll arrange
a briefing when we're ready,
but it's not going to be pretty.
I'm
supposed to be back to normal.
You managed to retain
some of the knowledge
you gained.
I should think
that's a good thing.
Because I can still be useful.
Everyone on this ship
is useful.
We all belong here.
All right,
somebody say something.
How bad is it?
It isn't any one thing,
it's the accumulation.
This ship just wasn't up
to fighting a battle like that.
A big chunk of the life support
is still down, too.
Well, you can repair it, right?
With what?
Even if we knew how,
we don't have the spare parts.
I mean, I'm talking
about things
that are broken
and burnt out that...
That I don't even know
what they do.
Now, if life support
was our only problem,
we might be able to
figure something out.
But there are dozens of systems
on the brink of failure.
Weapons, shields...
Well, they're operating.
And at mission critical levels?
We are down
to one last everything.
There's practically
no redundancy.
"Practically no redundancy..."
Wasn't funny
the first three times!
Well, I'm very tired.
Okay, we know
what the problems are.
What are the solutions?
Well, what I think
we're trying to say...
We make do as best we can
and carry on with the mission.
Well, it doesn't sound like
that's what they were
trying to say.
You're talking like
we have a choice here.
Actually...
Eli, please...
Ginn and I figured out
how to dial
the ninth chevron back to Earth
while Destiny recharges
in a star.
Without blowing up
the ship, you mean?
Yeah.
No.
Here we go.
Look, Eli's solution,
however brilliant,
fails to consider
the thousand things
that could go wrong
when attempting to open
a wormhole in a star.
I can show you the simulation.
More to the point,
it could cause
the same kind of overload
that happened on Icarus.
Well, who cares
if we're not even
going to be here?
Well, I do, lieutenant.
Along with anyone else
who cares to remain
aboard this ship.
Rush, come on, man.
Nobody in their right mind
would stay.
You said you understood
how important this mission was.
I did.
So, what's changed?
Nicholas,
you know what's changed.
Look I was all aboard
with this, you know that,
but if the ship can't fly,
there is no mission.
It's not like we're
just giving up here.
Well, that's exactly
what we're doing.
Well, fortunately for
the people on this ship,
the decision
is not yours to make.
Well, thankfully it's not
your bloody decision either...
Rush!
We can get through this!
They are just being defeatist!
My first responsibility
is the safety of these people.
I'm sorry.
Yeah, right.
sync and corrected by dr.jackson
for www.addic7ed.com
Oh, whoa.
Stand aside, sergeant.
Hey...
I can't do that.
Colonel's orders.
Since when?
Just now.
Did he say why?
I didn't ask.
Okay, could you tell me
where else
I've been banned from?
Save me wasting my time.
Pretty much any place
that you can push buttons.
Ah.
And I've got people
where all the buttons are.
Destiny's course
is taking us toward a star
roughly 18 hours ahead,
We assume to recharge.
We...
We should be ready.
Oh, we've been ready
for a long time.
I'm ready, and I just got here.
I can only imagine
what it's like for you.
Hi.
We've been expecting you.
Well, it seems you can predict
my every move.
Well, I had to make sure
you didn't lock us out of
the dialing programs.
The thought
never crossed my mind.
I see the elders have gathered.
You should know Eli is using
the stones right now
to run his calculations
by the best people on Earth.
They'll tell him
what I told him.
The work is brilliant,
but what works on paper
does not necessarily
work within a star.
Well, Eli said
that he's taken that
into consideration.
Eli is not an astrophysicist.
Inside a star
there are magnetic fields,
enormous pressures,
solar flares,
conditions that make events
unpredictable
by any mathematics.
Now, will Eli's
connection to Earth work?
Possibly,
But what happens
the moment that wormhole
has been established
is anybody's guess.
It could blow a hole
in the fabric of space-time.
He's out of his freaking mind,
you know that.
All right.
So, what are you
asking us to do?
Let me talk to the crew.
At least some
of them understand
how important it is
to remain on this ship...
Nobody is going to
agree to that!
You say
you have no choice
but to leave.
I have no choice but to stay.
We're going to brief everyone
in the gate-room
the minute we come out of FTL.
You can address them then.
It would carry far more weight
if you were standing
alongside me.
I can do that.
Thank you.
You're not serious.
Oh, I think he is.
We've run the simulation
a dozen times.
It works.
So, the gamer came up with
power flow algorithm?
Eli, yeah.
I gotta say, you know,
when we tried to solve
this back on Earth,
There we a lot of
smart people in that room.
Yeah, well, don't
tell him I said this,
but he's arguably
the smartest person
I've ever met...
You all right?
I'm fine. I'm back.
What did they say?
The math works, so we're on.
Who was the smartest person
you were just talking about?
Einstein?
Einstein.
Yeah, he was-
he was pretty smart.
But don't ever tell him
you said that?
All right, come on,
Let's go tell
the colonel the news.
Hey, T.J., can you
give us a minute?
Yeah.
Can you keep this ship flying?
Yeah, with help.
Then I need to know
an absolute minimum
number of personnel
You need to do it.
Well, as many as possible,
obviously.
I need a number.
I'll say a dozen.
Plus you and me?
No, including us.
So 10.
Yeah, look,
I-I've written down
most of what I intend to say.
If you've got anything
you might want to add...
Everett, is Rush
in the gate-room with you?
Yeah, what is it?
I need both of you
on the bridge.
We don't have time
for this just now.
David, we were just going
to talk to the crew.
Can it wait?
Negative!
Get up here.
Trust me.
We have time.
Yeah.
Time they might need to decide.
Just keep everyone here,
we'll be right back.
Uh, sure.
What is it?
It was in orbit
around the star.
Destiny picked it up
when it turned towards us,
and then we got
the radio broadcast.
From who?
You.
I don't understand.
Neither do we.
Wait for it...
Wait for what?
I repeat, this is
Dr. Nicholas Rush
Calling the Destiny.
I'm aboard the shuttle
headed your way.
Please respond.
Well, isn't this
an interesting turn of events?
What is this?
Well, I wouldn't know, colonel.
How about you tell me?
Well, it's not a recording,
if that's what you're thinking.
It's a subspace broadcast,
and beyond the fact
that it sounds
exactly like Rush,
I can tell that
that's our shuttle,
and it's on
an intercept course.
Even though according to this,
the shuttle is still docked
with Destiny.
Again, this is Dr. Rush.
I need assistance with
the docking procedure.
I know you can hear me.
Have we responded yet?
No, not yet.
Well, best not
to keep me waiting.
Hello, this is also
Dr. Nicholas Rush.
How can we be of assistance?
Tell them not to try
and dial Earth.
It won't work.
If they go through with it,
they're all going to die.
This is colonel Young.
Doctor Rush is sitting
right next to me.
Yes, obviously.
We've just spoken.
The only reasonable explanation
is that somehow
I've come back through time.
Reasonable explanation?
I couldn't be sure
until I seen you
dropping out of FTL,
Which happened
roughly 12 hours ago
in my time-line.
And we're supposed to just
take your word for this?
Shortly after
we dropped out of FTL, colonel,
you asked me for a number.
I told you ten, plus two.
12?
That's well calculated,
Mr. Volker,
But I think you're
missing the point here.
Is that true?
Did you just have
that conversation?
Yeah. Yeah, we did.
It's weird.
I was completely stoked
about this mission.
Yeah, we all were.
All of a sudden
I can't wait to see my kid.
Wow.
Gosh, and I thought
the hardest thing
was going to be
introducing you to my mom.
Okay, that makes me
more nervous
than goin' through
the dang gate.
:Hey, when we get back,
we-we're all still
gonna hang out,
right?
Yeah, of course we will.
We will have
a reunion every year.
I was thinking more along
the lines of Fridays.
Depends on whether you're
stationed Earth-side.
I can guarantee you
that Earth will be my station.
But you're joining
Stargate command.
like they're gonna ask me.
They'll ask you, Eli.
You'll be right up there
with the other SGC brainiacs,
Like Dr. Jackson
and colonel Carter, and, uh...
What was that guy's name
who kept staring at your...
Ugh, McKay.
Yeah, McKay.
They'll ask you right
when we get back.
Lieutenant Scott, come in.
Yes, sir, is there-
is there a problem?
Yeah. Join up with Greer,
head to shuttle bay 2.
Open it.
Don't listen to him!
He's going to try
and kill you all!
What in the hell?
T.J., this is Young.
Yes, sir, the gang's all here.
Yeah, they're going to
have to wait.
We need you in the infirmary.
How did you get the burn?
There was an overload.
I couldn't stop it.
Explosions all over the ship
one after another.
The air became so toxic,
I had no choice but to abandon.
At which point,
you somehow went back
12 hours in time?
No, no, no, that would have
to happen inside the star.
The ship itself must have passed
very near a solar flare
in the exact moment
we locked the ninth
chevron address.
A temporal event,
Like we've seen cause
time travel through wormholes.
It somehow affected
the entire ship.
One of those
unpredictable things
I remember warning you about.
What are you smiling at?
Well, you should know.
What, fascinating, is it?
Well, you wouldn't think so
if you'd been through
what I've been through.
Well, I won't have to now,
will I?
Look, we can still do this
if we could just learn
from your mistakes.
My mistakes?
The only mistake was trying it
in the first place!
No, no, wait a second,
she's right.
Just because it went wrong
the first time round...
Wait, isn't it the same time
again?
No, not entirely.
We'd end up with two of us
staying behind next time.
If we kept going long enough,
we'd soon have an entire crew.
We still have an hour
before we run Eli's program.
Tell us what happened.
Up to the point
you received my radio signal,
you know what happened...
I need a number.
I'll say a dozen.
Plus you and me?
No, including us.
So 10.
Yeah, look, I've written down
Most of what I intend to say.
If you've got anything
you might want to add...
So, I'll speak
when you're done,
But just so we're clear,
if we don't get
the 10 volunteers...
We will.
Okay.
You were true
to your word, colonel.
You stood alongside me.
Ladies and gentlemen,
if I could have
your attention, please?
Dr. Rush would like to say
a few words.
My friends...
Well, yes, perhaps that's...
an overstatement,
but we are at least shipmates,
who have, up until now,
shared great adversity.
I know a lot of you,
probably most of you,
also share the hope
of going home.
It is a fact
that the conditions
inside a star
bode very poorly
for the sustained viability
of a wormhole,
and I owe it to you all
to tell you that.
Stop trying to scare people
and get on with this.
The ancients did not devote
the efforts of
an entire generation
to build this ship
on a whim.
Neither was Destiny
named on a whim.
Over a million years ago,
the ancients discovered
a complex structure
buried deep within
the background radiation,
the fingerprints
of an intelligence
that existed very near
the beginning of time itself.
Destiny was launched
in search of that intelligence.
Who knows how close we are
to finding it?
How close we are to learning,
in the ancients' words,
"the Destiny of all things."
I don't pretend to know
when that's going to be,
in which stars it will happen,
or even how that
will change our view
of the universe.
I only know
that Destiny has come this far,
and if we abandon her now...
there'll be no coming back.
All of that knowledge
will be lost forever.
I believe this journey
is the reason I'm here,
but I can't hope
to do it alone.
I ask you to come with me.
Now, I, uh,
I believe that those of you
who want to go home
deserve that chance,
but I joined Stargate command
for a reason,
so I too
am willing to stay aboard.
What we are looking for
are 10 volunteers,
so I am asking those of you
who want to be here,
please step forward.
All right, listen to me!
You've already accomplished
the damn mission!
Our goal was to investigate
the ninth chevron address,
and you've done that.
Now, I do not deny
that there once was a mission,
but if it was as important
as Rush claims it to be,
they sure as hell couldn't
expect us to do it.
There is no noble voyage
to save the universe
or to meet God,
or whatever it is
that Rush has sold you on!
there is only the day
that this ship dies!
David, we don't know that.
I've got a good mind
to try to take you all back
by force.
Good luck with that.
Those of you still
taking part in the evacuation
are going to form two lines.
Everything we carry with us
becomes a projectile
in a nine-chevron transit,
so we are going home
with the clothes on our backs,
nothing more.
Eli has warned them
to expect us,
but it seems that
a radio signal does not reach
across a nine chevron
connection,
So I'll go first
to warn them
that we're on our way.
You will follow
in three-second intervals
two at a time.
Eli, are we ready?
Yeah, the program’s all set.
You're good to go.
15 minutes, people...
And we go home!
And 15 minutes after that,
you were dead.
If all those people
stayed aboard,
why were you the only survivor?
I told you,
there was an overload.
It doesn't matter.
We have a second chance now.
You just need to tell us
what went wrong,
what can we do differently.
Eli's program
is based on precise timing
in the recharging process.
A time which is
fast approaching.
All right, so you dialed
the ninth chevron...
And?
And it worked.
We made the connection.
Chevron nine is locked!
Wait three seconds,
then follow me!
No, no, wait, wait!
Stop!
What is it?
The wormhole is unstable.
See for yourself.
Well, shut it down.
I can't.
One of the mains blew out.
My program can't compensate.
We'll have to configure
the power levels on the fly.
Yes, Eli,
that's what I'm doing.
I've almost got it.
Everybody, stand by!
That's as stable
as we're gonna get.
Okay, go, go, go!
It's beginning to overload!
Well, we were supposed to be
gone by now!
We can't stay ahead of this!
We're losing her!
That's it, everyone,
we're going through!
Let's go!
All right, you heard him,
let's go!
Come on!
Eli, there's
nothing more you can do.
Eli, get the hell out of here!
Rush...
I can't maintain
a stable connection
and argue with you
at the same time.
Now, please go.
Go!
I don't really know
how long I stayed there.
It felt like hours.
I kept waiting for
the end to come,
but Destiny fought
to stay alive.
How are you sure that we...
They...
All didn't make it?
I didn't say
they all didn't make it.
I'm dr Rush.
How many of them
made it through?
I'm sorry, sir.
Only one, hours ago.
He's been waiting
to switch with someone
to see why the others
didn't follow.
The connection was made...
but you were the only one
who made it through to Earth.
We were told we'd be leaving
for Earth by now.
What's happening?
Some funky, funky stuff, man.
Lieutenant Scott, come in.
Sir, you are cutting it
awful close here.
Stand down, lieutenant,
we've decided not to go ahead.
You've got to be kidding me.
Sir?
We have reason to believe
The evacuees will not
make it through alive.
Send everyone
to their quarters.
Understood.
You made the right decision.
Yeah, about bloody time.
I want to use the stones
to confirm his story.
Well, we've never
used the stones inside a star,
and I don't think now
is the time to start it,
but I'll tell you what,
you can go talk to yourself
once we're on safely
on the other side.
Safely.
I think now we all need
to be on the bridge.
Oh, well,
at least I'll have someone
To engage in
a decent conversation.
There it is.
Well, I think that's
confirmation, don't you?
We're altering course
and accelerating.
But we're close enough
to get a decent look at her.
There but for
the grace of God, huh?
It's my fault.
Everybody on that ship
died because of me.
Yeah, well, the only reason
we're even in this situation
Is because you were all
trying to save me.
Do you guys see what I see?
What?
The damage is confined mostly
to the engineering spaces.
The main living compartments
look intact.
So?
I've got an idea.
Out of the way, out of the way!
Move, move, move!
You just said it was
falling back toward the star.
That was me, actually.
O-okay.
I'm telling you, we need
to get over to that ship.
It might be worth the risk
if we can salvage ammunition,
food, supplies...
No, no, that's not
what he's talking about...
Well, what is it, then?
Spare parts.
I had the same idea.
I ran the whole way, too, so...
Hmm.
How much time do we have
before we're out of range?
Well, we can't take a shuttle,
the other ship is too close
to the star,
and Destiny is
accelerating away.
We can arrange
a short FTL jump,
use the Stargate.
It's the same gate.
Can it dial itself?
I don't see why not.
Destiny's address
isn't based on
a fixed point in space.
We'll have to input
the distance calculation,
but you...
Guys should be able
to work that out, right?
Yeah, between me,
Eli, and me...
All right, well, let's, uh,
Let's start
putting together a list.
Yeah.
I'd like to lead
the team over there.
I should go as well.
I'm the only one who knows
which systems were affected
by the overload.
Listen, Rush,
I don't even know if that's
what I should call you.
Well, it is my name.
Fine.
What I'm trying to say
is that you've been
through hell and back.
You don't got to do this.
The man wants to help,
Everett, let him help.
We're gonna need
all hands for this.
Okay.
These are priority number one!
We want as many as we can
get our hands on.
This one's burned out.
This one is good.
Now, they're in every console,
Power relay,
and pretty much every
piece of equipment
aboard the ship.
Open 'em up,
pull 'em out and move on.
What do you call those things?
I don't know,
things that make it go.
We should find
concentrations of working parts
in the bridge,
control interface
and neural interface rooms.
Number two, these things,
and don't ask me
what they're called.
I'm not even sure
how they work.
We also have to
get our hands on
the other repair robot,
and shield emitter relays.
We'll get
everything on the list.
If there's still time,
we'll move on to our
secondary objectives.
How much time do we have?
We'll assess that
once we're aboard.
Conditions will be difficult
and they will be dangerous,
but make no mistake,
We need to salvage these things
if we are going to survive.
Dial the gate.
Everyone step back.
Send the kino.
It's getting hot already,
but the air...
Is still breathable.
I'd call it a green light.
Let's move.
Okay, let's go.
Let's move it.
Form into your teams
and stand by.
Okay, I'm reading
power and life support
In both the bridge
and control interface room.
40 minutes
till the shield fails.
Then that's the time we have.
Lieutenant,
that means your team
heads straight to the armory.
Got it.
You know your assignments, let's
go!
This is Telford.
We are proceeding.
40 minutes on the clock.
Okay, let's go.
David, be careful.
Will do.
Someone should report
to home-world command,
explain what's been going on.
Well, you go ahead,
and when you're back,
you can explain it to me.
They must think we're all dead.
It didn't happen.
Yeah, it did.
Not to us, Eli...
You can say anything you like.
Tell me to take
one time-line at a time,
but if Rush wasn't sent back
by a freak of physics,
we'd all be dead by now.
Move it, come on!
We'll start here.
Let's make this quick.
Spread out.
Over here, guys.
Want to try to get
that alarm off?
Start at the back!
Guess we're not going in there.
So, this must be
pretty weird for you two, huh?
Yes.
Half the ones I'm pulling
are burned out
from the overload.
I'll take what we can get.
Go get your c02 nodes.
We need to breathe, too.
Penhall, you're with me.
That's half time,
start packing it up!
Get back to the Stargate,
quickly as you can.
Go!
Gettin' hot, huh?
Yeah, but it's a dry heat.
All right, that's it,
we're out of here.
Move.
Get back to the gate-room. Double
time!
How we doing?
We eat tonight.
Excellent.
Get out of here.
Pack it up.
Let's go.
All right, that's it, let's go!
What do you think?
I think it's not on our list.
It could double
the amount of weapons
we could bring online.
Do we even have time for this?
Colonel, we've come across
a piece of equipment
that could
significantly increase
Our weapons capability,
but we're up against the clock.
For that, we should risk it!
For once, he agrees with me.
Okay, I'll go
and I'll bring back
the proper tools.
Be careful not to touch
the damaged one.
About a thousand volts
running through that.
Do you think I might know that?
Didn't mean to sneak up on you.
This is it?
Yeah.
The others took the parts we had
back to the gate-room.
My younger self
is coming back to help,
but I don't want to
wait for him.
You don't trust
him either, huh?
So, what went wrong?
What are you talking about?
Not that I think you would
kill them all deliberately.
I tried to save them!
You don't think
I buy that story?
Rush valiantly keeping
the gate open
while the ship explodes
all around him?
I don't care what you think.
It wouldn't be the first time
you sabotaged the ship
to make an ass out of me,
would it?
The last time
we tried to dial Earth
from inside a star
comes to mind,
among others.
So, what went wrong?
The wormhole was unstable!
I'm talking about
what really happened.
Their blood is on your hands,
not mine.
They would all
have made it home,
but you did something!
I was trying
to buy them some time!
Oh, and there's not
a single person left alive
to confirm...
Get your hands off of me!
You're the coward!
You're the one who didn't
believe in the mission!
You're the one
that killed them!
Oh no...
All right, right over here!
Hey, Rush, where's
your other, uh...
He's found something
for the weapons systems.
There's no time!
We still have time.
I'm just going back to help.
I'll go with you!
Dial the gate
and keep it open for us.
T.J. Get these people
outta here.
Don't stay too long!
All right, everybody, move out,
We're going to dial the gate!
They're dialing back.
Good.
That was fast.
I wasn't finished reporting,
but when colonel Telford
found out
that we were still here,
he insisted
that he be allowed
to use the stones
to switch with someone,
preferably himself.
That's weird.
Yeah, well, that can wait.
At least they know we're alive.
Oh no...
Lieutenant Scott,
where the hell are you?
Goin' after something
that's supposed to double
the weapons capability, sir.
Negative. You don't
have time for that.
I need you to locate
colonel Telford.
He's not answering his radio.
Roger that, sir,
we're comin' right around...
Scott, say again?
You were cut off.
We found the colonel, sir.
He's dead.
Where's Rush?
He's right beside me.
I don't know where
the other one is.
I do.
Hey, hey, Rush!
Sir, Rush just ran off on me.
Let him go.
Sir!
You only have a few minutes
before the shield fails.
Let him go,
that is an order, lieutenant.
It was an accident.
I believe you,
but they won't.
No.
Tell me, when you, uh,
dialed Earth...
what really happened?
I told you what happened.
And so now you're...
trying to decide
whether or not
to sit in that chair.
Well, wouldn't you in my place?
I'm not sure if even
the knowledge of the ancients
can help you now.
Well, I really don't have
anything to lose
at this point.
Imagine what I could learn.
Well, you won't have much time.
Well, time's relative.
We've just proved
that, haven't we?
So, what are you waiting for?
I need your help.
Thank you.
Good bye.
Come on, come on, come on!
You're welcome.
I'm okay, I'm okay.
Nicholas...
Yeah?
Where's the other Rush?
I don't know.
You told Scott
you knew where he went.
I was wrong.
I went looking for him,
couldn't find him.
Maybe he decided
to go down with his ship.
That doesn't sound like me.
Still, you must, uh,
you must be pleased
about one thing.
What's that?
Well, we can fix the ship,
get on with the mission.
Yeah, of course.
Get on with the mission.
sync and corrected by dr.jackson
for www.addic7ed.com
www.tvsubtitles.net