Man: Scotland
didn't invent football,
but we'll take
a back seat to no one
in our passion
for the game.
With 40 professional teams
in a country of five million,
football is as much a part
of the national fabric
as single malt
and bad weather.
Some say it's a religion.
If so, there are two denominations
in this church--
Celtic and Rangers.
One Catholic,
one Protestant--
us and them.
The forces of evil
and darkness
known collectively
as ''The Old Firm.''
There maybe no rivalry
in all of football
to match theirs,
maybe not in all
of sports.
For over a century, the players
have bashed heads on the field,
their supporters off it.
Together,
they've dominated the game
and won
the Scottish Cup more
than all the other teams
put together.
But this is not a story
about Celtic and Rangers.
There's not enough lager
in all the pubs in Glasgow
to do it justice
in a single sitting.
Besides, only a fool
would try to get it right.
But any story about football
in this land
is colored by their rivalry.
Whatever your team,
big or small,
football in Scotland isn't
a matter of life or death--
it's more important.
( bagpipe music plays )
Minister: Dear Lord,
our Father and our Savior...
please welcome one of our own
to Your flock.
Alex Wilson
loved Kilnockie football
almost as much as he loved
his wife, Annie,
and his three sons.
For 47 years, he never missed
a home match.
So it is fitting
that we send him off today
in the place he liked
to call home.
A family man,
and a football man,
Alex Wilson
played the game of life
with loyalty
to those he loved,
with kindness to all he met.
He was a generous man
who never stopped trying
to help others--
right up to the final whistle.
May you rest in peace,
Alexander Wilson,
and may you always run
with the lads.
He's a fucking headcase,
Peter, a waster, eh?
What are you trying
to build,
a football team
or a distillery?
- He scores goals.
- Oh, aye, he could.
Couldn't score
in a brothel now.
Why do you think
he was available?
You know, Gordon,
I know this is a family affair.
I respect that.
It's none of my business, by the way,
but I want to make sure
you don't put
your personal feelings ahead
of whatever's good
for the team.
Buying a team is different
than running a team.
How do you think the lads
are gonna feel
bringing in a player
who makes more
- than all of them combined?
- You know what?
If they really wanna win,
it's not an issue.
- Oh.
- He puts fans in the stands.
You know why?
Simple.
He's really good.
He can score,
he plays defense,
he anticipates,
he can see the field.
He's won two Golden Boots.
This guy's gonna give us
the punch we need, Gordon,
to make a run at the Cup.
Don't you wanna win a Cup?
We've won the first
three matches without him.
I know, but now
the big boys are here.
Teams win the Cup, Peter,
not prima donnas reminiscing
over their past glories.
I used to have hair...
once upon a time.
Eh?
( screeching )
Bloody menace !
Where the hell
do you think you are?
Fucking nutter.
Peter: There's never
a League Champion year.
Not even a semifinal
appearance in a Cup.
Nothing.
1899 to 1999, nothing.
- The wilderness years.
- Gordon: Yeah.
Peter, is the meeting over?
No.
Gordon, I'm thinking about
moving this team to Dublin.
A Scottish football team
in Ireland?
Next you'll be wanting us
to play Gaelic football
and use our fucking hands.
You should be locked up.
You're kidding.
They're so hungry
for professional football.
Really hungry.
And they've got
a brand new stadium.
Don't you want more
than this?
I do.
After a hundred years,
you want to move
the Kilnockie team to Ireland?
You're talking about
the heartbeat of this town.
10 decades of tradition.
I mean, you're talking about--
you're talking about my job.
You're not going anywhere.
I'll tell you another thing,
Jackie McQuillan's
gonna make a difference too.
I want to be there
when you tell 'em
you're moving the team
to Ireland.
Minister:
Earth to earth,
ashes to ashes,
dust to dust,
in the sure
and certain hope
of resurrection
to eternal life,
through our Lord
Jesus Christ
Amen.
Boylie.
Come on, son, pass back!
Go on, Boylie, bury it.
Well done.
Good save, Brian.
Go on, Kirky.
Yes, good save.
Get in there, Silky.
Come on, Silky.
Jesus Andy, you can't score
if the ball's not in the net.
Look, lads,
it's where you put it,
not where you point it
that counts.
Aye, goes for your women
as well, right?
Okay, Romeo,
you show 'em how it's done.
( speaking foreign language )
There's three points
in American football, cap.
Okay, smart-mouth,
let's see how well you do.
- Let's put the Yank in the net.
- Give 'em hell, Kelsey.
Well done, Kelsey.
Not bad for a pizza boy
from the States.
Well done, Kelsey.
Go on, go on.
Where, where's he going?
Hey!
Where's he going?
Hey, Diego! Hey!
- Where's he going?
- Home?
I don't think he likes
the weather.
Hey, come here.
Diego, come here.
Come back here !
Hey!
Training begins at 10:00 sharp.
You better
tell the sheeps, Gordon.
They seem to like the roads better
than they like the fields.
I didn't want this.
Nor did I.
But I'm here to play football.
You were always a fuck-up,
McQuillan.
Always will be.
Nice to see you too,
Gordon.
Aye.
Fucking hell.
Alan Barnes, Jackie.
- Pleasure to meet you.
- How are you doing, Alan?
We're probably happier to have you
than you are to be here,
but you know, just--
just think of it as Parkhead.
A wee bit different.
What do you think?
- Okay then.
- I'll show you the guys.
Woman:
I wonder how it went today--
Jackie and Dad together again.
If Jackie showed up.
Yeah, well, he told me
he was going to.
He told you a lot of things
he was going to do.
We've started
seeing each other again.
Landing in the Second Division
hit him hard, Mom.
- Let alone here.
- He's lucky to be here.
He's brought enough pain
to your life, Kate.
He's little Jackie's father.
You can't undo
what's been done.
Loving them is never
the problem, is it, Mom?
It's everything else,
when you share your husband
with this game.
Your father and I have been
married for 40 years.
It's not the amount
of time, Mom.
When you marry a football man,
you become a football wife.
Talent, temperament--
the church they believe in.
Inside, I swear to God,
they are all driven,
stubborn, selfish,
and as competitive as a pack
of street dogs.
And those are probably just
the best traits.
The truth is that...
Jackie and Dad are actually more
alike than they are different.
( door opens )
Hi, Dad.
Hi, I'm Andy Gray.
Welcome to ''Sky Sports,''
here to talk about
the headline
that's dominated
Scottish football.
It is, of course,
the recent signing
by Kilnockie
of Jackie McQuillan,
twice a Golden Boot winner.
No doubt the supporters
will be looking forward
to some great
goal scoring magic.
So, let's take a look back
at the career
of this legendary
Celtic striker.
Jackie !
Gray:
The question now is...
he may be down,
but is he out?
Will the gamble pay off
for Kilnockie's
American owner,
Peter Cameron,
and manager, Gordon McCleod?
All of Scotland
will be watching.
Hey, Jackie.
How are you doing?
I just wanted to say
what an honor it was
to be playing on
the same field with you today.
When I was in college
I used to watch
the satellite feed
of your matches.
And I remember the time
where you beat
three Rangers defenders,
and dinked the ball
over the keeper's head
to get the winner--
in injury time.
Man, that was--
that was some goal.
I'm sorry,
I forgot your name.
Kelsey.
Kelsey, let me give you
a piece of advice.
You don't live
in the past, son.
- Announcer: St. Mirren...
- Man: Shh.
Announcer:
...will play Kilmarnock.
Dundee will play
Queen of the South.
Kilnockie...
will play Dumbarton.
( cheering )
( phone rings )
- Hello?
- Hello, Irene.
- Is Gordon there?
- Uh-huh, Ian, he is.
- Great news.
- He's just coming.
- Ian.
- Hey, gaffer.
- Aye.
- Have you heard the draw?
Dumbarton, at home.
Gives us a right chance
to get through, eh?
Only if we score
more goals than they do.
- Oh, I'm sure we will.
- Aye, it's great.
- Okay then, bye.
- Talk to you later.
Dumbarton, eh?
Maybe we'll go one more.
Oh, aye, maybe.
Was Jackie
at training today?
Jackie?
Late.
Sheep on the road.
If it's not one thing
it's another.
Mmm.
I thought he was out
of my life forever.
Are we planning on having
another child, Gordon?
Eh?
( scoffs )
Then you might try saying hello
to the one you do have.
The only one.
Right here.
Hey, hold.
- Cheers.
- Hi.
Hello.
Hey, hi, son.
- What's your name?
- Martin Christie, sir.
- What position you play?
- Sweeper, sir.
Sweeper. Too bad.
You'll go against Jackie McQuillan.
If he gets half a step on you,
the ball's in the net.
Hello, gaffer.
Go shit a brick
somewhere, eh?
Good to see you.
Cheers.
Hello, Rob MacLean
and Andy Gray here
on the Cup trail
at Kilnockie
against Dumbarton.
It's the fourth round
of the Cup,
we're down to the last 16
and little Kilnockie hopes
the road to glory
starts here for them
against Dumbarton.
And, Andy, Jackie's back.
No doubt about that.
That's who we're all here to see.
He may have been in London
with Arsenal for two years,
but the fans certainly
haven't forgotten the boy.
Hey, hey, Colin. Colin !
Tell your wife I'll be around
Tuesday morning as usual.
Some girl that, Colin, eh?
You big fucking Nancy boy!
I hear your wife's a bit
of a goalkeeper, too, eh?
She lets everything in
but the balls !
# When I'm calling you #
# We've all shagged her too. #
On the bench is the Kilnockie
manager, Gordon McCleod.
There must be mixed feelings
for him at the moment
as his long-removed son-in-law
returns to Scottish football.
And, Andy,
I wonder what sort
of physical shape
Jackie's in.
Physically he looks
a little heavy,
but he'll lose those pounds
in the next month or so.
It's mentally
where I've got a worry.
This is a young lad
who's played
at the top level all
of his life.
He's won the Golden Boot
twice as well.
He doesn't know
what life's like at this level.
Here he is today playing for
a Second Division and the Cup,
and not only that,
playing for his father-in-law.
Come on !
The first real attack
on goal.
And the first real test
of Brian Burns
in the Kilnockie goal
but the shot flies wide.
Get it out.
We're on the attack.
That's Peter Cameron,
the American owner
of Kilnockie,
looking on nervously.
First 40 minutes
of this match or so,
I'm looking
at Jackie's performance.
he looks a little
heavy legged to me.
He looks a little off the pace,
but his touch is good.
But if you give this guy
half a chance, he'll take it.
So Kilnockie continuing
to press forward,
but still no break through.
Corner kick.
And Owen Coyle
will take this one.
Left footed, curling it in.
He's aimed it
towards McQuillan.
Up goes Jackie McQuillan !
His header--
And the opening goal !
Kilnockie are ahead !
Daddy scored !
Yeah !
You talk about fitness,
you don't need it.
He needs half a yard.
We said the boy was
a finisher.
He's just shown the whole
of Kilnockie
he hasn't lost the magic art.
A minute before half time.
What a great boost that is
for Kilnockie.
What happened?
What happened?!
Well what the fuck
do you think happened?!
Yes ! Yes !
Yes !
That was pure instinct.
The timing of the run.
And it's one-nil.
( chattering )
Malkie.
Fucking Malkie.
The most recognizable striker
in all of Scotland,
and not one
of you fuckwits mark him.
Is he talking about you?
I don't think it's you,
that's for sure.
Malcolm, you're hanging around
like a fart in a trance.
Can you not see McQuillan?
Well, if he's not Casper
the fucking ghost, mark him !
'Cause if you don't,
you'll be beside me
on the bench for the rest
of the fucking season
getting skelfs in your arse !
Fucking do it!
Do it!
Just because you don't like
my biscuits,
doesn't mean you can break
my crockery!
Not in this place you don't.
( whistle sounds )
Announcer:
Well, it's been all Dumbarton
for the last 20 minutes,
but I do feel that Kilnockie
have defended comfortably.
No real dramas.
I just think that
they're gonna see it through.
I think they're in
the next round.
And there goes
the final whistle.
Mike McCurry, the referee,
brings the match to an end.
And the celebrations are
with the Kilnockie supporters.
They are through to the last
eight of the Cup.
And the match winner
is Jackie McQuillan.
The only goal of the game.
The header
from Owen Coyle's corner.
Kilnockie march on.
Well, the chairman'll be
a pretty pleased man
because he said that
Jackie McQuillan
would put bumps on seats,
would score goals,
and he's done both
of those today.
This'll be interesting.
The manager hugging
every player as they come off.
What about the son-in-law?
What about the goal scorer?
What does he get?
A good firm hand shake.
I thought you might like
some tea, boss.
I won't be late,
I'm having dinner with your dad.
Why can't I come?
Well, because then Maggie
would have no one
to keep her company.
I'm not that much fun.
Oh yes, you are.
( moaning )
Yes !
Oh, Jackie !
( phone ringing )
( ringing continues )
Oh, shit.
Katie, what was
I supposed to do?
It was the first match.
It was our first win.
How could I not go out
with them?
And you couldn't
have called?
Couldn't have torn yourself
away from the lads,
for what, 30 seconds?
- I should've.
- I thought you'd stopped drinking.
Drinking-drinking, I have.
I haven't touched
the hard stuff.
But I just figured,
after the match
a couple of beers
with the boys--
Jackie,
what will you ever do
the day you run out
of excuses?
'Cause God knows, Jackie,
it is a thick book.
But somehow,
I just--
I keep thinking
you must be near the end.
You must be.
So are you,
Jackie?
'Cause, my book of patience
is just almost as thick.
But I know
I'm at the end.
Katie.
Great goal,
Jackie.
Yeah, I want 50 quid
on Hearts.
I want 50 quid
on Trap Five.
Yeah, and give me
200 quid on the Rangers.
Okay?
You should try this new
invention, Gordon.
Called a car.
I prefer this thing
they call exercise.
It's a little
old-fashioned, Jackie,
but you might want
to try it.
It doesn't
run out of gas--
at the end
of the game.
Okay...
after the draw,
we'll know who's up next.
But it won't matter if we play
like we played on Saturday.
That'll be out last
go in the Cup,
and our last chance
to make up any ground.
'Cause we're not the most
talented team in Scotland.
So we'll go only as far--
as our hearts
and our lungs
will carry us.
Now, the heart is
up to you.
The lungs I can help you with
and will.
That's my job.
And maybe get
using this.
Or some wee part of it.
You give me the heart,
I'll give you the lungs.
And together we'll
work on the head.
Eh, go on,
Jackie.
One more time.
Eh, one more time, eh.
That's good.
Go on, Andy.
Good.
Oh, brilliant.
Well done.
Perfect, perfect.
- Brilliant, brilliant.
- Hey, hey, hey.
Kelsey, Kelsey,
more rhythm.
Bop-bop-bop-bop.
( whistles )
Great training, lads.
That's great.
If the other team looks like this
at the end of the match,
- hey, we've got a chance.
- ( cell phone rings )
( cell phone rings )
Oh.
Am I interrupting
somebody's wee plans here?
( cell phone ringing )
Ian,
drive Jackie's car back
to the grounds.
Lads, have a run home,
compliments
of Mr. McQuillan.
- ( angry chatter )
- Hey, just fucking shut it.
Listen to the gaffer
and get on with it. Move it.
( whistles )
Go. Out of here.
Out. Go.
Fucking tosser.
Tell Ronaldo our offer
is final.
And get me Zidane.
See ya.
One fucking dent and you'll need
an ice-pack for your bollocks !
( whistles )
( laughs )
It's a good thing,
this invention, eh?
You know, once I get
the lungs in shape
we can move onto
the head.
And work on
that together, eh, boss?
You know,
I've been thinking,
when it comes to Katie,
we're exactly where we were,
aren't we?
Celtic, Ranger--
the forces of darkness
and evil, eh, gaffer?
Give me some, Brenda.
I'm fucking starving.
You've got fuck all,
big man.
Martin Smith,
the devil himself.
Don't let the boss see you
reading about him.
- How come?
- Because you're in Scotland.
There's two camps
in Scotland.
There's the Smith camp
and the McCleod camp.
And seeing as you're playing
for the McCleods,
I suggest keeping your ass
in this one, you know?
- Yeah, thanks, Al.
- Hey, man, no problem.
Anytime.
And so that's when
the boss ended up in Dundee.
- Smith was the manager,
- Right.
Gordon was his assistant.
Along comes a new chairman.
Not unlike, you know,
you-know-who.
Thinks he can run
the team better than the guys
actually running
the fucking team.
So Gordon and Smithy,
they agreed to quit.
Two friends, one plan.
It's done.
It's done and concrete.
The boss goes in first,
hands his resignation.
Smithy goes in last.
The rest is history.
Man:
Shhh, hey, hey.
Announcer:
Hibernian...
will play
Dunfermline Athletic.
Kilnockie...
will play
Queen of the South.
Hey, that could
have been worse, lads.
That could've been
a lot fucking worse.
- Rangers...
- Shhh.
will play Celtic.
( crowd cheers )
Kelsey!
I'm joined now by former Ranger,
Andy Gray.
Celtic and Rangers going
head-to-head in the quarter-finals.
Unless you're a Celtic
or a Rangers fan,
you've got to be happy about
your team's chances
- of getting into the next round.
- The truth is, Rob,
if you're gonna win the Cup,
you'll have to beat
one of these teams
along the way.
But beating one of them is a lot
easier than beating both.
Now, you've seen your share
of Cup competition,
besides a favorable draw,
what else has to happen
for a lower division team
to have a shot at glory?
Well, scoring more goals
than your opponents helps.
I think big decisions have
to go your way.
You do need to get lucky.
Of course, if your name's
on the Cup, that helps.
Thank you, sir.
Peter:
Hey, Gordon.
I'll be right down.
- How are you doing?
- Good.
- Okay.
Good.
You want a Coke or something?
Or a juice?
- No, no, I'm fine.
- Tea?
Okay.
I'm sorry I was late,
I was out working in the yard.
Come here,
I wanna show you something.
You wanna see something cool?
Check this out, man.
- Oh.
- Yeah.
- Brilliant.
You see?
You can check our scores.
- Uh-huh, I see.
- Look at that. See?
Man U .
They lost.
Queen of the South.
Heard they played
like shite.
Good enough to win.
Yeah, I guess so.
You're sure you don't want
a tea or something?
- No, no, I'm fine, fine.
- You want a grape?
Let me ask you something.
What's your opinion on
where we play these guys?
Well, we drew them at home
with hometown fans.
Scottish fans.
- It's what you fight for.
- Yeah, I know.
It's kinda what
I'm afraid of, you know?
They brought, like,
8,000 maniac fans
a couple of years ago
to the Coke Cup.
You know, in our stadium,
I'm not sure,
that'd be so safe.
Could get crazy.
They can buy their tickets
like everyone else.
How important do you think
home field advantage is?
( laughs )
I mean, let me ask you,
you think we can beat
a First Division team?
At my age, you take
any chance you get.
If you're lucky enough
to even get one,
you sure don't piss away
the one edge you have.
- Correct?
- Yeah.
You know,
I'm gonna tell you something.
If we had a bigger stadium,
we'd make a whole lot
more money on one match
than we make in any four,
all year.
Do you want to make more money
or do you want us to do better?
I wanna do both.
You've already talked
to the constable, haven't you?
Yeah.
And he agrees with me.
There's no way he can guarantee
our safety.
That's a lot of crap
and you know it.
The safety of your wallet's
more like it. Right?
You know...
you know, I'm going
to tell you something.
I really respect you
and I know we both love soccer.
And I know those guys
would lay down their lives for you.
And I know something else,
you and me we're like twins.
Thing is, Gordon,
I'm asking you to work with me.
'Cause if our name's
on the Cup,
it doesn't matter
where we play.
- You know what I mean?
- Cheers.
Whew. Boy.
Announcer:
It was the name of Kilnockie
which came out of the hat first,
but it's turned into
a home game
for Queen of the South.
They've given away
home advantage, have Kilnockie.
Will the gamble pay off?
Well, the next 90 minutes
will tell us that,
but I know Gordon McCleod
was furious
and didn't agree
with his chairman, Peter Cameron.
It's a fantastic atmosphere.
Queen of the South going into
this one, obviously, as the favorites.
They're in the First Division,
Kilnockie from the Second.
But with Jackie McQuillan
up front, anything's possible.
Gordon:
How you doing? See you.
Go easy on the lads today.
Not used to playing
you big boys.
Graham, what are you looking
so serious for?
It's only us.
He-man, eh?
All right?
Announcer:
There's not much doubt
about the match
in the quarter-finals.
It's the meeting
of The Old Firm at Ibrox.
But try telling that
to the people packed inside
Palmerston for this one.
And, of course, Andy,
one of The Old Firms today
will perish.
Hey, deefie !
Is that your wife cleaning
the bogs up behind the terraces?
'Cause there's a big queue
of guys up there
and they're all smiling
like fucking Coco the Clown !
( sings circus melody )
- Hello.
- Hi.
I though you had
too much class work.
Always, but a girl's got
to have some fun.
Announcer:
It's a ridiculous decision
for the chairman to force
this team to go away from home
and give up home advantage,
especially when the team
you're playing
is a division above.
He's only chasing the fast buck.
That's wrong.
We've had a good run
in the Cup, lads,
and I'm proud of you.
I'm proud.
But now we're in against
the bigger teams.
Now, you know,
what they're thinking about
right now in there, eh?
Their next match.
They've already beaten you.
I've seen their eyes.
You're nothing but a 90-minute
pass to the semi-finals.
So, let them play
their next match up here,
we'll play this one out there.
Get the result
and tell them they missed
a hell of a game, okay?
Everybody up and let's go.
- ( cheering )
- Let's go.
Announcer: A chance
to make progress to the semi-finals
as this match gets under way.
( whistle )
Looking early on at McQuillan,
I think he might
find himself very,
very tightly marked
this afternoon.
That little burst of pace
wasn't there a month ago.
It's there now.
And he sparks
the first attack on Coyle
at the back post
and Andy Smith'seffort
spins up into the arms
of the goalkeeper.
They're under pressure here
as an attack is sparked
by Queen of the South.
And that's a good solid save.
Well behind it was Brian Burns.
They've given away
home advantage,
they don't wanna give away
the first goal.
That's a very important save.
Coylie, Coylie !
- For fuck's sake !
- And that's a heavy tackle.
That's a bad tackle.
You won't get
a fucking sniff today.
You're fucking mine
all fucking day.
Announcer: We wondered
who would be the man marker,
- and it's Derek McCall.
- ( crowd chants ''Off! '' )
That's a cynical,
crude tackle from behind.
A little message from McCall--
'' Hey, McQuillan,
there's more to come.''
A minute to go
in the first half.
It's Queens on the attack.
It's Angus Doyle
with the shot.
And he scores !
Through the legs of Burns.
A blunder by the keeper.
That won't endear him
to the manager.
And Queens have the lead.
What a blow for Kilnockie.
44 minutes of great defending
spoiled by one mistake.
You mentioned the manager.
He won't be happy.
He's an ex-goalkeeper.
Fucking !
- Boss...
- Hey!
I'm sorry. I should have shut
my fucking legs.
No, son, no. Your mother
should have shut hers.
Okay.
They're marking close, lads.
You've got to move without the ball
to lose your marker.
Try and work off your man.
Stretch them a bit
at the back, okay?
And make 'em work.
Alan, your first touch
is taking it farther than
I could kick it. Relax on the ball.
Son, their striker
always fakes to one side
and pushes it onto
his right foot every time.
- Right, okay, yeah.
- Jim, keep going, wee man.
Superb.
Aye, aye.
Brian, you've got 45 minutes
to make amends.
Get yourself an early touch,
and command the area, right?
Okay, boss.
( stuttering )
Is there anything else?
Don't give away
any more
f-f-fucking goals.
( laughter )
How will Kilnockie respond
in the second half?
What a psychological blow
it was to concede that goal
in the final minute
of the first half.
And they need to give
themselves some belief--
And it's McQuillan.
Oh, unbelievable !
What a start
to the second half!
The question is answered.
- It's one-one.
- Oh, what a response.
You know,
people often ask me
when managers earn
their money.
Half time it's one
of those times.
And the manager's earned
his dough there.
He sent his team out
absolutely flying.
We talked about man marking.
You can get as tight
as you like against this boy.
McCall was, but McQuillan's
ability was too good.
What a finish from the kid.
Here come Kilnockie again.
And Owen Coyle.
He's aimed it toward
McQuillan.
Onto his right foot,
the shot and the goal !
It's another one
for Kilnockie.
On me, lads.
Someone up there loves us today.
There's time
to lose it yet.
Queen of the South
now trying to battle
their way back
into the Cup tie.
And that's a bad foul by
McQuillan this time on McCall.
He's hitting back after
a fair bit of provocation
- and that's not clever.
- It's not the way you do it.
Scoring goals is the way
you do it for him.
But that's just a little bit
of revenge.
He has been kicked
from pillar to post, though,
for most of this game
by McCall,
so I suppose
we could see it coming.
That deflected shot
was well held by Brian Burns.
Kilnockie have defended well.
That was a good confident,
solid stop
and that gives confidence
to his defense.
And Jimmy Boyle flights it
across towards McQuillan.
His overhead kick!
Oh, that's brilliant!
( crowd cheers )
And that is surely the goal
which takes Kilnockie through
to the semis.
It's also the goal
of the competition.
If he was Brazilian,
we would be talking about
this goal for the rest
of the season.
There's talkers
and there's fucking doers.
Just like I'm doing
your fucking missus.
- You shouldn't let her go.
- What did you say?
That's a sweet fucking shag,
your wife Jackie.
But wait a minute,
what's happening here?
He's lost the plot!
He's lashed out,
it's McQuillan at McCall.
- Words were said.
- See you later, asshole.
McQuillan lashed out
and there's only one outcome.
Referee Willie Young
holds up the red card.
McQuillan off.
Kilnockie down to 10 men.
- I give up.
- What is he doing?
He's absolutely mad.
In those 15 seconds,
we've just seen a cameo of this man.
From the sheer brilliance
of a hat trick,
to the sheer stupidity
of his actions.
- Unbelievable.
- Fuck's sake !
Get your fucking sellin' out
on the road.
What are you fucking
on about?!
He might need that
medical bag if the manager,
Gordon McCleod, gets to him.
Reporter:
What prompted the fight, Gordon?
You know Jackie, he could start
a fight in an empty house.
What did you tell him?
I told him you cannot score
from the stands.
A wee bit of the old Jackie
out there today, aye, Gordon?
Aye, aye.
But old or new, eh,
old or new,
it's the team that win
or loses.
I like the way
my lads hung on at the end.
There have been some rumors
about your team going to Dublin.
Can you comment on that?
I think the Irish
have enough troubles
without sending them
this team.
- Thanks, Jackie.
- No problem.
Maybe someday my own kid
will get to see me play, eh?
Oh, play.
Is that what you call
your performance today?
Why do you think
I stopped bringing him?
- That guy was a wanker.
- And you had absolutely
no trouble sinking
to his level, did you?
Dad's dream is winning
that Cup.
Now you're defending him.
It'd be a bad living defending
the likes of you two.
I'm driving.
How come everybody's driving
my fucking car but me?
Drinking beer out
of a whiskey bottle?
What are we doing here?
How can you know
where you're going, Jackie,
if you can't remember
where you're from?
The Gorbals.
The birthplace of the great
Jackie McQuillan.
You say you want
to get back together.
You can't even pull
yourself together.
You're sill drinking.
Still getting tossed out
of games.
So what's changed, huh?
What is different
since I left?
What's in it for me
and little Jackie,
except more of the same?
Katie, where are you going?
Home.
At least I know where it is.
There's no danger
of her being here, eh?
Honest to God, Gordon,
you'd think it was a virus
you were discussing
and not your own flesh
and blood.
( bell rings )
Granny!
Grandpa !
Oh, my wee man,
how are you doing?
Maggie?
Maggie, it's us.
Striker, eh?
Rangers' quarter-final
victory today
was overshadowed
by violence which broke out
inside Ibrox with little more
than a minute to play
and spilled
onto the streets.
Police were able
to restore order,
but not before
three supporters
were taken
to the hospital.
Another dozen were arrested
- and flare-ups were reported...
- Hurry up, Campbell.
Rangers go through with
a four-two victory at home.
But the score is still being settled
in some parts of Glasgow.
In other Cup
quarter-final action,
Dunfermline
were victors today
along with Kilmarnock
and little Kilnockie.
Come on !
Quick, get in the car!
Move quick.
I'm Jackie McQuillan.
Now move.
Quick.
What are you doing?
Are you stupid?
You should know better
than that.
You're lucky I was the one
that picked you up.
- Make sure he gets home, boss.
- No problem.
Cheers.
By the way, if I had a real top,
I'd give you one.
Okay?
Vendor: Evening Times !
Times !
Evening Times !
Gordon: The problem is,
people don't change.
No, not in the basic way.
No matter what happens,
what they go through,
what they stand to lose.
You are what you are.
Aye.
Just be as hard on yourself
as you are on others.
You too, eh?
- ( laughs )
- Gordon.
That's fine, Irene.
No, no, that's fine.
I'm not saying there haven't
been disappointments.
Disappointments?
What are you talking about?
Jackie getting red-carded
isn't a disappointment,
just an accident waiting
to happen.
I'm surprised it took so long.
What I don't need is you
or anyone else telling me
how I'm supposed to feel
when people knife me
in the back or take something
precious from me.
I just think it's time
you let something precious
back into your life.
It'll be time
when it's time, okay?
But seeing
those pictures today...
of wee Jackie,
it was like viewing something
beautiful while walking on glass.
'Cause here
there was only joy.
But in my guts,
deep down,
it's a terrible gnawing.
'Cause, Irene,
there's not a day that passes
( sobbing )
I don't think about Katie.
My sweet, sweet Katie.
Not a minute I don't hurt.
But it wasn't me who married outside
the church she was brought up in,
just like it wasn't me who hung
his best friend out to dry.
Nor is it me who pissed
away more talent
than God gave any other
10 players put together.
But it was me...
who had his daughter stolen
from him.
- Jackie never stole Kate--
- She was engaged to be married
to another man when Jackie McQuillan
stepped into her life.
- What do you call that?
- They fell in love, Gordon.
You can't change some things.
You just said it.
But you can change the way
you look at things
and think about them.
So tell me,
just how are you looking
at the prospect
of me looking for a job
when the team moves
to Dublin?
You only betray yourself,
Gordon,
if you can't let go
of the things
that cause you pain.
I don't care if you ever talk
to Martin Smith again.
But it's not the same
with Kate.
She loves you
with all her heart.
And you know why?
Because some things
never change.
( crowd cheering )
( yelling )
Yes !
Promoted
to the First Division, man.
Congratulations.
Listen to these guys.
Is that good enough
to keep us here?
You're the talk of all Scotland.
Everybody's digging you.
Let's just keep everybody talking
till you and me
are drinking
from the Cup, huh?
- Towels, boys.
- ( yelling )
( laughs )
That's outrageous, eh?
Right. Okay.
Let's see if you can beat
your old man with a spot kick.
Don't fancy.
Give it your best.
Come on.
Yeah !
You know your trouble?
You've been watching too much
Italian football.
- I haven't.
- You have. Now come here.
The whole object
is to be cool.
Scoring a goal should be
as natural
as having your breakfast.
Usually one fist gets
the job done.
The attitude should be
plenty more
where that came from.
Now, let's talk about
the goal.
The spectacular goal.
The goal that wins
the Cup Final.
What you've got to do is freeze
and capture the moment.
Both hands in the air,
fists raised.
You don't move,
and you remember...
all these people in the stadium
are here because of you.
How's this?
Perfect.
Now, here's the set-up.
Cup Final.
Hampden Park.
50,000 fans.
It's a penalty shoot out.
Everybody's scored.
And you have got
the last kick.
You know something?
You're shitting your pants.
You've got to beat me.
Right, come on.
Oh ! Now remember...
50,000 fans.
Can you hear them?
Give me your best.
Come on then, give us it.
Yeah !
Are you all right?
I just keep thinking
about that boy.
It could just as easily
have been wee Jackie, you know?
Wearing his Celtic top
in the wrong part of town.
About to get hurt because
of that.
Yeah, well,
you saved him, babe.
You should be
happy about that.
You know the press, they blew
everything out of proportion.
Those kids never even
saw him.
It's still us versus them.
I mean, look at your father.
He hasn't been to church
in 40 years.
40 years.
And he won't talk
to his daughter
because she married someone
who hadn't been
to his church in 20.
How do we undo that?
What about us?
Start over.
Remember what it was that got you
started in the first place?
Build on that.
- Redis cover where--
- Sshhh.
Announcer: It's semi-final time.
Kilnockie nearly promoted
but still in
the Second Division
against Kilmarnock
from the Premier League.
And no chance of Kilnockie
relinquishing home advantage,
because we're on neutral ground
at Premier Park,
where not only are they facing
a Premiership side, Rob,
they've got to beat them
without Jackie McQuillan.
After his recent sending off
against Queen of the South,
he's sitting in the stands.
- Hey, man.
- Hi, chairman.
Jackie, Mr. O'Shea
and Mr. Clancy.
Jackie McQuillan.
Great player this guy.
Could get used to this gaffer.
Let's make it a habit.
Aye, aye.
And that's the experienced
Hugh Dallas as the referee.
Watch this.
Here we go.
- Oh, right.
- ( whistle sounds )
And the semi-final
gets under way.
The striking on us
for Kilnockie falls
on Andy Smith
and Owen Coyle.
The side, of course,
minus McQuillan.
The supply, it's hoped,
will come from Alan Lawrence.
And immediately
it's Lawrence in possession.
A curling cross into the area
but too close to the keeper
and plucked out of the air
by Meldrum.
Well, I've been very impressed
with this start, Rob.
I thought they might defend
in the early stages of this game,
but they've actually looked to try
to score an early goal, Kilnockie.
Very ambitious.
There'll be pressure from Kilmarnock,
of course, the favorites.
And it's them on the attack
with that shot directly
at Brian Burns.
A comfortable save but that
will give him some confidence.
He's certainly a key man.
Well, if you don't have
your top goal scorer,
and you don't have
your best player,
you might have to rely
on your goalkeeper today.
That's a confidence
boosting save.
Here come Kilnockie again.
Again it's Lawrence.
He's made a good start.
He cuts in.
This is a real chance
for Kilnockie.
A brave save by Meldrum
at his feet.
But he overran it, surely.
Yes, he definitely did.
It was a brave save.
But he's a postman,
young Lawrence,
and he should have delivered
a better finish than he did.
That was an absolutely
glorious opportunity.
Here comes
another opportunity.
It's Owen Coyle.
Cuts in from
the right hand side
onto his favorite
left peg.
The cross aimed
at Andy Smith.
Smith's header...
and it's a goal !
A crushing header
from Smith.
And Kilnockie leads Kilmarnock
by a goal to nil.
Well, it can't get much better
than this for this side.
Second Division
against Premier.
They've really held their own
in the opening half hour.
And what a sucker punch.
Beautifully flighted ball,
and I have to say
a towering, accurate,
almost unstoppable header
from big Andy Smith.
We got the goal we weren't sure
we could get, lads, hey?
Now we have
to make it stand up.
Don't get caught
ball watching.
See the ball through
your man.
That's the way
you shut them down.
You cut off their movement.
And remember, you only get
one chance at a Premier team.
This is our shot at glory,
lads, all right?
All right,
go and give it to them !
( together )
Come on, let's go!
Announcer: Kilmarnock giving it
everything in this second half
as they try to battle
their way back into the Cup tie.
They badly want to be
in the final.
But they are one down, Andy.
Yes, but they've been camped
in Kilnockie's half
for the opening half hour
of this second half.
And their goalkeeper,
Brian Burns,
has been absolutely
sensational.
They're looking
a little tired as we get
to the last quarter
of an hour.
I am a touch concerned
for them.
Burns has been a hero so far.
- Who's got 11 ?
- He's been brave and decisive
- and he has to continue to be so.
- Who's got 11 ?
- 11 !
- Curled in toward the near post.
- Burns has to come for it,
and he makes a good solid
confident punch.
Oh, but he's fallen
awkwardly.
And he's not getting up.
Burns is in trouble.
This could be
a bad injury blow.
Almost symbolically, the rain's
come down on Premier Park.
Black clouds overhead
for the Kilnockie supporters.
Kelsey, get warmed up.
Come on, quickly.
Hurry up.
Hey, Kelsey, get warmed up!
Come on, get warmed up.
Hurry up.
Announcer: He landed
really awkwardly, Rob.
As he got into the net,
I think his arm tangled there.
It went underneath him.
All his weight landed on his shoulder.
I think he's got
serious problems.
I think we're about to see
a substitution made.
Come on, Kelsey,
pay attention.
- Get your mind on it.
- Kelsey O'Brian
is the reserve keeper
on the bench. He's 23.
And he's played soccer
at Dartmouth College
in the U .S., but he's never
experienced anything like this.
Well, what a test
for the young man.
Goodness knows
how he's feeling.
He knows he's coming on.
God, what nerves.
What nerves he must have.
Here's your chance, son.
No more small print.
Just big fucking headlines
up for grabs.
So, go and grab 'em.
I was just thinking, Rob,
we're about to witness probably
the biggest 10 minutes
in the history
of Kilnockie Football Club.
And what do they have to do?
Put a rookie American
with no experience
and no one's ever heard of,
into the goal.
The crowd knows he's American.
Listen to them.
Is that,
''Yank, Yank, Yank,''
or is it something even
more offensive, I wonder?
( crowd chanting ''Yank'' )
But he's got lucky,
I tell ya,
I thought
that was a corner.
I thought Burns punched it
straight out.
The referee has given a goal kick
in all the confusion.
Gives the goalkeeper
a chance to settle.
Good clearance up field.
Get settled.
Dear, oh dear.
Well, that's ominous.
His first touch of the ball,
a real sclaff.
He took a chunk of turf.
And let's hope
his shot stopping
is better than
his goal kicking.
Here comes
the Kilmarnock pressure.
Dealt with quite
comfortably there.
- Hetherston thumped it clear.
- Fuck, four minutes.
- Where's he get that from?
- The signal from the touch-line
is that four minutes
will be added.
Oh, Christ.
How much time?
I don't know.
I can't look.
Agony written
all over the faces
of the Kilnockie supporters.
Can they hold on?
How much time
are you giving them?
Why don't you stick on
a green jersey
- and make it legal, eh?!
- Calm down, okay?
You either behave
yourself...
Who said there's no pressure
in this game?
Hugh Dallas telling him
in no uncertain terms,
''Sit down, son.''
You can blow the whistle
any old time,
says Gordon McCleod.
That one last chance possibly
for Kilmarnock.
Kilmarnock pressing.
That's a good effort.
And touched over the top
by Kelsey O'Brian.
That's a corner kick.
They're almost there, Rob.
10 seconds to go.
This could be the last chance
for Kilmarnock.
And that's a good punch
by O'Brian.
It's out
of the danger area.
As the full time
whistle goes.
It's unbelievable !
Kilnockie are through
to the final
of the Scottish Cup
and they'll play,
believe it or not,
Rangers.
Well, I can't believe
what I've witnessed this afternoon.
A Second Division side
arrived here against
a Premier League side.
They arrive here
without the top man.
Without their main striker.
Their goalkeeper gets carried
off 10 minutes from the end.
They stick in
a rookie American
no-one's ever hear of.
Hold out.
It's unbelievable.
And victorious scenes
there'll be
in Kilnockie tonight
as the reality
of what they've achieved today
begins to sink in.
And it will take some
sinking in
for Kelsey O'Brian.
He's joined the little team
with the big heart
and he's come up
with the goods.
Kelsey.
Here's to your future.
Well done.
Gordon: So, Kelsey,
you feeling all right?
Kelsey: I feel a bit,
you know, sick.
You know...
before the semi-final,
the most people I ever played
in front of was maybe 2,200.
Uh-huh.
- You ever fish?
- Yeah, with my grandpa as a kid.
Well, when you're standing
in that river, son,
there's only one thing
you're concentrating on.
That wee fly floating
with the current 30, 40 feet away.
So you mend your line
once or twice,
but you never take your eye
off the wee fly.
It's the same thing
with goalkeeping.
You get the angle you want,
make sure of your footing,
keep your line,
then you concentrate
on nothing
but that wee bouncing ball
out there.
Everything else goes.
The fans, the noise,
the colors,
all the jumping around.
Now, that's what I want you
to do against the Rangers, eh?
Go fishing.
( singing Scottish music )
( applauding )
# Oh, the summertime
has come #
# And the trees
are sweetly blooming #
# And the wild
mountain thyme #
# Grows around
the purple heather #
# Will you go, lassie, go?
- Are you dancing?
- Are you asking?
Aye.
# And we'll all go together #
# To pull wild mountain thyme #
# All around
the blooming heather #
# Will you go, #
# Lassie, go? #
- ( music ends )
- Well played, lads.
Ladies and gentlemen,
Gordon McCleod.
( applause )
It's a great night--
for this team
and this town.
But I cannot help wondering
where home is
if we win the Cup.
Maybe the owner of the team
could clear this up for us tonight.
Four months ago you told me
we had to do better.
We're a First Division
team now.
Is that good enough?
Good enough to call
Kilnockie home?
Well, I'll tell you what,
Gordon,
I'll make you
the same promise
I made you
four months ago.
I promise you the team
stays here...
( applause )
if, and this is
what I told him,
you beat Rangers.
Oh.
Eh, now we know
what we're playing for.
Many of you also know
that home means
a lot to me.
I was born in a wee mining town
southwest of Glasgow.
And miners never forget
where they're from.
And fishermen remember,
too,
which is why I've always felt
at home in this town,
amongst all of you.
When it's life and death,
you learn quickly who you can trust,
be it in a mineshaft
or on a fishing boat.
I approach football
the same way.
I don't care if you're a good
player or a bad player.
If you're a good person
I'll work with you.
But I'd prefer you were a good player
as well as a good person.
( laughter )
Now...
there's a lot of good people
on this team
and a lot of good people who've been
rooting for them for a lot of years.
None of our success
could've happened
without your support.
Just like none of my success
would have been possible
without the support of my wife,
Irene.
- Aye.
- Aye, good on ya.
( applause )
There's a lot
of young players
who think they can be involved
in semis and finals every year.
But I never played
in a Cup Final
and I know a lot
of very good players who didn't.
So cherish this opportunity.
Now I won't make
any daft promises,
but we'll go and give
our all on Saturday
and we'll enjoy it.
But remember...
enjoyment to me
is winning.
All right?
Eh? Eh?
There's one last
official duty
to perform tonight.
Not five hours after
our Kilmarnock win
two of this team's
greatest supporters
rolled up their sleeves
and went to work.
( applause )
The result of their efforts
should make us all
feel proud.
( whistles )
If the coaches and the team
would please make their way up
to the stage.
- Go on. Jackie, go on.
- No way.
There is no way I am putting
one of those jackets on.
Hi, Jackie, glad to see
you could join us today.
So this is how
you boys travel?
( chatter )
You run out of gas, eh?
Aye, in a manner of speaking,
gaffer, aye.
Andy, you made
the squad, son.
- That's a boost to Rangers.
- As long as we're all here,
I wanna tell you to keep
your underpants on tonight.
No sex before the match.
I don't want you excited
except on the pitch tomorrow.
( horns honking )
David versus Goliath only
scratches the sur--
Shut up.
We're joined now,
in the Rangers trophy room,
by Rangers manager,
Martin Smith.
Martin, here you are again
in a familiar position--
the night before another Cup Final
involving the Rangers.
If you beat Kilnockie tomorrow,
you'll make it a clean sweep.
The Treble.
No one's done it in 30 years.
It'd be a lot better if we could keep
Jackie McQuillan out.
- You bastard.
- Is there anything you'd like to say
to Gordon tonight?
We did invite him on
- but he declined.
- Well, you know...
Gordon's awfully shy.
Hides his light under a bushel.
Come on back, Gordon.
All is forgiven.
This is nothing to do
between me and Gordon
or Jackie and the Rangers.
It's between the two teams.
Jackie's certainly been
a Rangers killer.
Have you any plan for him?
( knocking )
Well, I understand some
of the supporters
are gonna go over
to his hotel tonight.
If we can't keep him awake,
we'll have--
- Gaffer, hey.
- Hey.
- You doing all right?
- Aye, good. You?
- Yeah, okay.
- Good.
Er...
I-- I don't wanna lose this game
before it starts.
Stay in your room.
Don't go out.
Don't drink.
Don't do what you did
on too many nights.
- All right?
- Mmm-hmm, mmm-hmm.
Yup.
That must give you
the boke, that.
Seeing that prick sitting there
like that.
It's water under the bridge.
Aye, but it could have
been you, gaffer.
If that bastard had left
his resignation
in that room in Dundee
instead of leaving with a raise.
Aye, that gave me the boke.
- So he'll be a marked man?
- Closely marked man.
But it's not just him.
It's not even
keeping the team in Kilnockie,
though I want it
with all my heart.
( laughs )
Come here.
I was a run-of-the-mill
squad player
wherever I played.
Even the Teddy Bears weren't
any good when I made it to Ibrox.
So I never won anything,
let alone a championship.
So tomorrow,
for once in my life,
I want to win something.
( laughs )
I want to win the Cup.
Okay?
Stay here.
Stay here, eh?
- Cheers.
- Okay.
Oh, what you did
for that Protestant boy
- was a good thing.
- Protestant boy?
It had nothing to do
with any church for me, gaffer.
You know, maybe someday
you'll understand.
And think the same way
about Kate.
Hasn't been about that
for a long time.
Maybe it never was.
Maybe.
Eh?
( screaming )
It's a nice crowd
you've got here.
Hi there.
Um, can you give me
- Jackie McQuillan's room number?
- I'm sorry, ma'am,
- but I don't know who you--
- I'm Mrs. McQuillan.
Oh. Of course.
We're just trying to protect
our players' privacy--
I can see you're doing
a really nice job
with the traffic control.
( knocking )
Hiya, Jackie.
Remember me?
- Annie.
Who could forget?
Just like old times, eh?
Being in the Cup Final.
- Scoring.
- Look, I mean, I'm suppos--
- I can't go out, you know.
- Who said anything about going out?
Aren't you wearing
the wrong colors, darling?
Yeah, well, I never really
thought blue
was ever a match
for my personality.
That's her.
I'm telling ya, that's her.
That's McQuillan's wife.
( knocking )
( water running )
The nutters are on the loose.
And that's just my team-mates.
Mum told me that...
somebody took
the team bus today.
Well, I'm proud of you.
So, how do you feel?
Like I might never
feel this way again.
I don't know what the hell
I'm gonna do when it's all over.
I am gonna take care of you
for the rest of your life.
You just worry about tomorrow.
Flooding the bathroom however,
is not really the best way
to start.
( draining )
I should have known.
You're never gonna get any peace
with this racket going on.
- Come on.
- What are you doing?
Just go out.
I promised Gordon
I'd stay in.
I'm just talking about a drive
or a cup of coffee.
Could be the only peace
you'll get.
I promise I will have you back
before curfew.
- Ah, there you are.
- Hey! Come on, Jackie.
- Where are you going?
- Whoa ! Come here !
Hey!
Hey, Jackie
have a drink on me.
- ( glass shatters )
- ( laughing )
- Are you fucking mental?
- As mental as a Celtic like you !
People get killed
because of assholes like you !
- It's a game !
- Jackie, just leave it.
It's just a fucking game !
( screaming )
McQuillan at the gate.
( siren blares )
( crowd screams,
bagpipes play )
Rob: Glasgow woke up this morning
to find Kilnockie striker,
Jackie McQuillan,
had been released from jail
following a brawl with Rangers
supporters at a Glasgow hotel.
Two men were taken
to hospital for treatment.
Jackie McQuillan was
apparently unhurt.
Police don't expect
to make a full report
until sometime
later today or tomorrow
when it's decided what,
if any charges, will be filed.
Rob's with me now.
Rob, what's the latest?
Rob: Andy, I spoke to Nockie
assistant coach, Ian Mc Veigh,
a few minutes ago.
Jackie is fit to play.
Whether he does or not
will depend on his manager
and his father-in-law,
Gordon McCleod.
And we know all about their
rocky relationship.
Dad.
Dad !
Rob: Realistically,
what are their chances?
A Second Division team
taking on The Old Firm,
a team that's never been
to a final
against a team
that's been 35 times
and won 27.
A team with a total payroll
of some quarter of a million pounds
going up against a team
with seven players alone
who make more than that.
A team of Scots
with a rookie American in goal
taking on a club with players
from nine different countries.
On paper Kilnockie
haven't a chance.
I've been reading a lot of
David and Goliath stories
in the papers this week.
If I was a reporter,
it'd be my angle too.
It has a nice ring about it,
except the ring of truth.
In that match up,
one side had a sword,
the other a stone.
In this version,
we both use
the same weapon.
This is what we play with,
lads.
And whoever wants it the more...
will win.
We can beat this team.
I want you to be
street fighters.
Fight for every loose ball,
every header.
When they've got the ball,
be where they are.
And when we've got it
I want you to be
where they aren't.
Personal performance
and high individual standards
count here.
So, with that in mind...
everybody up.
I want a wee fucking bounce here.
Let's go on the spot.
Make sure we keep
with the ball early.
Jump early.
Make them tight.
And we're in.
And we're out.
Boylie, Lumber,
keep your eye on the ball.
Make sure we're setting up
tackles.
And we're in.
And we're out.
Don't let them play.
They get the ball,
we get them tackled.
Don't fucking allow them
to dictate the game.
You get in there and seize it.
And we're in.
And we're out.
Whoa, whoa,
whatever you do,
don't score early
and piss 'em off.
Out come the teams,
and what does it feel like
for these players?
Andy Gray can certainly
answer that question.
Andy, you've played
in seven.
Andy: It's a brilliant time.
Between now
and the end,
they're not gonna enjoy it.
None of those players.
But you get the chance.
You come out, stand and line up.
It gives you a chance to look
for your family and friends,
give 'em a little wave.
It's the only time you get
to relax before
this match starts.
Rob: And it's a huge day
for the man in the cloth cap.
Gordon McCleod up against
Martin Smith,
the opposition manager.
They haven't spoken
for more than 20 years.
This is a real grudge match.
And Kilnockie playing
for their future in Scotland.
Rob: Playing for their very
future
without their top striker.
Rob:
Gordon McCleod felt
it was a decision
that had to be taken.
It was a matter of discipline.
A gamble that will pay off
or a gamble that won't.
McQuillan on the bench
as Kilnockie kick-off
in the Scottish Cup Final.
And the challenge doesn't come
much bigger
than tackling Rangers.
And immediately...
it's the big favorites
on the attack.
How come Dad's not playing?
I don't know, honey.
And there'll be a lot of defending
to do for Kilnockie.
Andy: Well, if I was Martin Smith
I'd be saying,
''Get shots on goal
as early and as many as you can.
Test this American goalkeeper.
See what he's really like.''
For Kilnockie it'll be:
defend as well as you can;
hopefully get a little
breakaway and a little luck.
Rob:
What an emotional day this is.
Kilnockie,
a big-hearted team,
there's not much doubt
about that,
but they'll need more
than just big hearts today.
- Owen, go on.
- They'll need
to show the sort of ability
they've shown to get here
if they're going to take this
one step further.
And it's almost unbelievable.
Here come Rangers.
Derek Ferguson is pulling
the strings in the midfield.
Robertson has the chance.
It's touched back,
and it's Ferguson's shot.
And it's fumbled
by Kelsey O'Brian.
He gathers it
at the second attempt.
That's the first real
threat to Kilnockie.
Rob: He did well in the end
but he got lucky.
- He's bound to be nervous.
- Andy: 25 minutes in.
He's not had a lot of the ball,
the goalkeeper,
and I still think
he'll be a touch nervy.
Rob: That scoreboard
make sencouraging viewing
for Gordon McCleod
and the Kilnockie supporters.
Here's yet more pressure
from Rangers.
In comes the cross...
out comes Kelsey O'Brian,
that's a poor punch.
And it's Ferguson !
And that's one-nil.
- Rangers have the lead...
- Jesus !
- Ah, fuck it!
- after O'Brian's mistake.
And this time he's
punished by Ferguson.
- One-nil.
- Andy: He'd done well up till then.
But you always wondered, could he
keep it going for 90 minutes?
The answer was,
unfortunately for Kilnockie, no.
A really poor punch
from the American.
Ferguson pounces.
It was a mountain to climb.
It's even bigger than that
now for Kilnockie.
One-fucking-nothing,
you think that's funny?
One-nothing against
a bunch of rubbish,
you're all smiles?
Marking, horrible.
Finishing, deplorable.
A bunch of fucking
potato-pickers
is holding the mighty
Glasgow Rangers to one goal
and you're happy?!
Your daughter's wanting to see you.
She's in the boardroom.
You better go.
Okay, lads, settle down.
One mistake
can make it difficult.
You don't have
to make it difficult!
Shut the door, Dad.
You're good at that.
Jackie didn't get into a fight
last night
because he was drunk
or arrogant
or just being Jackie.
He got into a fight
because he was defending me
and you
and anyone else
who loves this game
and believes that it should
heal rifts not cement them.
Oh no,
you're gonna hear me.
See, I know that you love
to brood on your betrayals.
You tie them all up
into little bundles,
like...
firewood,
and then warm
your Gaelic blood
when you think about them.
It's not Jackie's fault
that he was born with talent.
So stop blaming him
for your own failings.
It's you
and your jealousy
and your anger
that God had the nerve
to give someone else
so much more
than he gave you.
I don't suppose there's much
you can do about being stubborn.
And there's definitely nothing
even you can do
about getting old.
But for God's sake,
Dad,
you don't
have to be stupid.
I want this game, boys.
I want the Treble.
Do you hear me?
Right?!
Fucking do it!
Rob: We've just
been asking the question
during the half time interval
and it's answered
at the start of the second half.
McQuillan's on
for the second half.
- Yes !
- Jackie McQuillan is on.
He's scored nine goals
in seven Cup Finals, Andy.
Rob: And four of them
against Rangers.
He had to come on, it's as
simple as that, Rob.
One down against
the team chasing Treble.
McQuillan on the bench?
Not for long.
He had to come on.
And I have to say,
what a start he's made
to the second half.
He looks fit.
He looks fresh.
Rob: I think he sent on an angry
young man, Gordon McCleod.
He's gonna prove to one or two
people that he isn't finished.
I know he's playing. I can see
he's playing. I've got eyes.
He's the only player they've got.
I'm coming down.
The personal feud between McQuillan
and McCleod is no secret.
But could this be
a managerial masterstroke?
Andy: He's flying.
Rob: Rangers in control
and dominating the game.
Second half.
It's been all Kilnockie.
Rob: So much so,
at times you'd think
they're the Premiere side.
It's been an immense performance.
If it isn't St. Martin come down
to mingle with the less fortunate.
You've been missing
a good game.
The little guys are down.
But they're about to rise up
and bite the big boys
in the ass.
Gazzer,
pick up McQuillan.
I don't wanna see his name,
understand?
Put him in your pocket.
He's down on the touchline,
is Martin Smith.
He could stay up in the
director's box no longer.
Gazzer, wake up!
It's no big secret he's in the game.
What a good save that was
from Ally Maxwell.
- ( grunts )
- That's a bad tackle on McQuillan.
They see him as the big threat
to their Cup Final chances.
Crowd:
Off, off, off!
( screaming )
A yellow card.
That's bullshit.
He should have been booted !
Performance artist.
Still taking the low road,
eh, Martin?
It's a goddamn mugging
and you know it.
Turning your back again.
You're good at that, eh?
Always was your best side.
That's enough. Sit down.
Down. Okay?
Andy: The message came on
from the touchline,
''Sort out McQuillan.''
There's absolutely no doubt.
- And sort them out they have.
- ( whistle )
Andy: I know I might be
upsetting a few people,
but I'd love to see them get
an equalizer.
They're running out of time...
,
you're backing Kilnockie?
Never.
( cheering )
Hey, Kelsey!
Supporter: What?
Did they score? What?
Fucking what?
Tell me.
Gonna shut up?
Rob: The agitation is
on the Rangers bench.
How much time
are we playing here?
John Rowbotham's had
a look at his watch.
And it's almost all over.
Rangers within seconds,
surely, of holding aloft
the Scottish Cup.
Jimmy Boyle might have
other ideas.
His cross !
Up goes McQuillan !
What a header!
And what a goal !
- Oh, yes !
- Andy: I don't believe that.
- Oh my God.
- Rob: That is incredible.
How do you script things
like this?
It would have to be him.
It would have to be
the last minute.
The color has drained
from the face of Martin Smith.
Jackie McQuillan
has come back
to Scottish football
to haunt him.
Kelsey O'Brian has run
the full length of the field
to join in the celebrations,
which will be echoing
around the northeast coastline,
no doubt about that.
All those who couldn't travel
to Hampden today...
will be enjoying this moment.
- Oh, no.
- No.
Five million fucking quid
for a blind man
with two left fucking feet
who doesn't
even speak English.
I wanna go first.
- Jackie, the nail in the coffin.
- Aye, gov.
- Alan, you start us off.
- Done.
Blackie,
I want you in on this.
No problem.
Silky, you go third.
Any other Bravehearts?
Rob: This is a cruel way
to settle a football match,
especially a Cup Final.
It's all about
winners and losers,
the joy,
the heartbreak.
And it's Eddie May
up first for Rangers, Andy.
Andy: What a day it's been,
Rob.
One-one after 90 minutes.
Extra time couldn't
give us a winner,
so now we're
down to penalties.
The one thing I'll tell you,
in the next few minutes,
we'll have a hero
and a villain.
It's May versus O'Brian.
And Eddie May scores.
Strike one to Rangers.
That gets them off
to the best possible start.
Andy: Yeah, they obviously
won the toss, Rob,
because they went in first.
That's important.
Now Kilnockie are
playing catch-up.
Rob: Next up is Captain Courageous
for Kilnockie--
Alan Barnes, the skipper.
He wanted to take
the first one.
the responsibility.
Barnes versus Maxwell.
And he sends him
the wrong way.
Kilnockie are one-one
in the penalty shoot out.
They'll feel
a bit better now,
with that one going in.
The pressure unloaded
for Barnes.
And the pressure now on,
for young Robertson.
He blasted it,
Robertson.
And scored.
Two-one in the shoot out.
That's your type
of penalty, isn't it?
Low on finesse,
high on velocity.
Andy: My type of penalty
finds the net.
( laughs )
This man knows
all about penalties--
Kenny Black.
You don't get much better
than that.
Left foot ferocious.
Top corner.
Andy: A little bit
of emotion as well.
( laughing )
But all wrapped up.
A little apology.
Now it's--
John Stone !
And that's three-two
to Rangers.
O'Brian went left,
the ball went the other way.
And Rangers again
have the edge.
Andy: Five pretty good penalties
I have to say.
That's cool.
A little wink to Ally Maxwell.
- He fancies this, doesn't he?
- They call him Silky.
He just passed
that into the net,
picked his spot.
Again,
Maxwell chose wrong.
And it's three each.
Andy: At the moment neither
goalkeeper's getting
anywhere near a penalty.
Now Harris for Rangers.
It's gone through.
O'Brian gave it his best shot
but he couldn't keep it out.
Rangers piling on
the pressure.
Sandy Stewart.
- ( grunts )
- A save by Maxwell !
The first save
of the shoot out
denies the former
Airdrie player.
He can't believe it.
What's going on?
Is it bad?
We're dead,
unless Kelsey makes this save.
Gordon: When you're standing
in that river, son,
there's only one thing
you're concentrating on,
the wee fly floating
with the current.
It's the same thing
between the sticks, Kelsey.
You get the angle you want,
you concentrate on nothing
but that wee ball out there.
Everything else goes,
the fans, the noise,
the colors.
That's what
I want you to do.
Go fishing.
- ( groans )
- What a fine save !
The fairy tale continues !
Yes ! Yes !
Yes !
Yeah !
The emotional roller-coaster
rolls on.
And cometh the hour.
Cometh the man.
Who would Kilnockie want
at this stage...
to step up,
to strike the penalty
which can keep them
in the Cup Final?
You would have to answer it
with two words:
Jackie McQuillan.
Andy: In normal circumstances, Rob,
I would agree,
but let me
tell you something,
these are not
normal circumstances.
This is pressure
the likes of even Jackie McQuillan
- hasn't faced before.
- ( crowd taunting )
McQuillan, you fucking drunk,
you couldn't kick your own ass !
Can he keep Kilnockie
in the match?
Rob: Oh, what a save
by Ally Maxwell !
Rangers have won the Cup!
It's heartbreak for McQuillan.
It's heartbreak for Kilnockie.
The fairy tale is over.
If you're gonna be a McCleod,
son,
you're gonna have to learn
to stand on your own two feet.
Sorry, gaffer.
That's football, son.
McCleod and McQuillan walk off
side-by-side...
leaving the Hampden stage.
And could this be
the curtain-call for Kilnockie?
The road to glory
has ended here.
And if they move to Ireland,
they've left their supporters
with a performance to remember.
Kilnockie may have
lost today,
but they did not fail.
How does it feel to have
come so close?
What can I say, lads?
What can I say?
Just, you know--
cheers.
Cheers, all right?
Better luck in Dublin.
I don't think so,
fellas.
Look at these people.
You can't buy
this kind of loyalty.
I think we're gonna stay
right here.
Next year we're gonna
win this thing.
I can't do anything
about getting old...
my-- my wee lamb.
- It's all right.
- I missed you.
It's a good feeling.
A good feeling.
A feeling of relief.
Brian, hold this.
Gordon.
Winning by penalty kicks
isn't winning.
Maybe not...
but, I'd rather see my name
on the Cup than yours.
Cheers.
Here.
You hold it, yeah?
Left hand.
Pound says wee Jackie
gets the first fish.
If he catches one before me,
he's walking home.
( reel spinning )
Kate:
Fish in !
- Eh?
- Fish in !
Go on, Katie !
Whew!
At least we're not
walking home, eh?