[###]
MAN:
Mrs. McIntosh.
[REPORTERS CLAMORING]
MAN:
Don't you care
what you're doing to him?
You couId ruin his Iife.
WOMAN: You leave our kids aIone.
You hang in there, bro, all right?
MAN:
Keith, the whoIe town is behind you.
WOMAN:
We're with you.
[REPORTERS SHOUTING]
[###]
[PEOPLE CHATTERING]
WOMAN:
Okay, there you go.
Bob, hang on.
The kids don't want you to leave
without saying goodbye.
I would never forget something
that important.
Come here, you guys.
Pink? Whatever that coIor was
looked good.
There he is.
What? Who?
Don't look at him.
TABITHA: Oh, Aaron.
Can you, like, smell him
from 100 yards now or what?
Bet he's going to Shane's
party tonight.
Yeah, so?
Well, we have to get into that party.
Who do you know
who can get us into it?
I know.
[CELL PHONE BEEPING]
Tabitha Lienart wants to know
if she can come to Shane's party
and bring Daisy.
Ew. They're sophomores.
It's New Year's Eve for everyone,
sophomores too.
Whatever. It's Shane's house.
You should ask him.
I'll ask Ryan.
[CELL PHONE RINGS]
[ROCK MUSIC
BLARING OVER STEREO]
Hey, sweetie. You hungry?
I can whip you up some French toast.
No, thanks. I had some cereal, so...
Wow, that is really good.
Yeah?
[CHUCKLES]
Didn't you have a history paper
due before Christmas?
I'll get to it. Jordan's coming over
to help me with it.
I think getting good grades
sounds like a heck
of a New Year's resoIution.
[CELL PHONE RINGS]
Ryan, what's up, man?
[RYAN SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY
OVER PHONE]
Yeah, dude, that's totally cooI.
Yeah. Oh, I think Grace
already put it on Facebook.
RYAN: It's gonna rock tonight.
It's gonna be so awesome, right?
Later, man.
All right, catch you Iater.
You wouldn't be getting rid of us?
Damn it, you figured me out.
Okay, ready. I'm ready.
Bob, good Iuck in the big race. I was
looking forward to kicking your ass.
Hey, have a margarita for me
down in Cabo.
KATY: Bye, Trudy. Have fun.
Bye, Katy. Happy New Year.
You coming to Daddy's race?
BOTH: Yeah.
Good.
Go strike fear in your competition.
I would, if I had any competition.
Smart-ass. Go.
Bye. All right,
we'll see you at the finish Iine.
[JOSHUA RADIN'S
"ROAD TO RIDE ON" PLAYING]
MAN: All right! Go!
Oh.
There.
A friend indeed. I smelled coffee,
but I didn't dare miss the finish.
At least we know he'll finish.
Excuse me, miss.
Yes, sir, can I help you?
I wanted you to know
those are real nice buns.
Oh, really? Well, you can look,
but you can't touch.
[CLEARS THROAT]
Hey.
Angie. What's happening?
Aaron. No.
What you got here?
What? Come on.
Go get your own.
Yo, yo, yo, the great Keith Moore,
gracing us with his presence.
Can I have your autograph?
No.
Did you know our buddy Keith broke
the CaIifornia high schooI record
for most touchdowns
in a singIe game?
Attaboy.
Thank you very much.
[ALL CHEERING]
Go, Daddy! Daddy!
What a ride. Best race time ever.
Rees Harbor's own
former triathIon champion,
and by the way,
one hell of a good Iawyer,
Mr. Robert McIntosh.
[ALL CHEERING]
Hey, buddy.
Yeah, buddy! Yeah!
Hey, I'll meet you outside.
Okay.
[###]
Boo!
Oh, my God. Hi.
Is this how you see me?
Yeah.
[LAUGHS]
Ew. I don't need to see tongue.
Keith wants me to go to Shane's
to make Jell-O shots.
Give me a ride?
Yeah, sure.
Yeah.
Oh, my God, Ryan. Tell your mom
you need a new ride for graduation.
No, I like the way it rumbIes.
SeriousIy? You wanna be seen
in a hunk of junk?
Hey, Iadies. You need a Iift?
ANGIE:
Not from you.
Oh, come on. Come give us a kiss.
ANGIE: Ew.
Get Iost, dude.
[ENGINE REVVING]
What the hell is your probIem?
What are you gonna do about it?
JORDAN: Ryan.
ANGIE: If you don't knock it off,
I'm gonna tell my friend
to kick your ass. He's Keith Moore.
Man, this is a waste of time. Let's go.
You gonna hide
behind your girIfriend, man?
I was taking care of it.
Whatever.
They're gone. Who cares?
Hey.
What?
It's no big deal, okay?
Okay.
Ryan.
[HIP-HOP MUSIC
PLAYING OVER SPEAKERS]
Oh, nice.
[BLOWS NOISEMAKER]
Jordan, can you grab the fridge?
Yeah.
SHANE: Hey, Keith, Aaron.
Thank you.
Yo, Shane, where's the tub at?
Right over there, dumb-ass.
Dumb-ass?
Dumb-ass.
What took you guys so Iong?
We were looking for those morons
you said hassIed you.
What? Why didn't you call me, man?
AARON: You had your chance.
Like your scrawny ass
would be much help
in a fight anyway.
Shut up. I'll fight you.
He's cute when he looks all feisty--
I'm messing with you.
You can be the one to tap the keg.
No, he's gotta take me home first.
What?
We'll be back in a whiIe.
You're Iucky.
I was about to pull
my kung fu moves on you guys.
Kung fu.
See you guys in a bit.
Bye.
SHANE:
See you, Ryan. See you, Jordan.
KEITH:
See you, Ryan.
[###]
You look sexy
when you get out of the shower.
Smells good.
Me or the soup?
[CHUCKLES]
Needs a little--
[LAUGHS]
A little cayenne.
Well, the kids are completeIy
sucked into that movie.
Oh, really?
I think that we should
take advantage of this window.
I don't think we have a lot of time.
I think we should make time.
You think?
Okay, let's go.
SARA: Mom?
Ugh.
JOSH: Where's Dad?
SARA: Mommy?
You or me?
Ha-ha-ha.
Okay, fine, I'll go.
I love you.
I love you too.
I'm gonna go get changed.
[HIP-HOP MUSIC
BLARING OVER SPEAKERS]
Oh.
TABITHA: Hey, there's Aaron.
I got suspended for four days.
You guys. This.
KEITH: I know.
ANGIE:
By the way, you're welcome.
Down the hatch.
Thank you.
Oh, yeah.
That's pretty good.
Nice.
ANGIE:
Yeah, how can we help you?
Shane invited us.
Really?
Yeah.
KEITH: Okay.
Jell-O shots?
AARON: Shoot it.
RYAN: Yo, Keith.
Hey.
Yes. Bring it on.
ANGIE: WeIcome back.
Whoo!
KEITH: Happy New Year.
Happy New Year.
Hi.
Sorry we're Iate.
I couIdn't find a spot there.
Don't worry.
It looks like Shane's
having himseIf a little party, eh?
Heh. A little party?
For me?
Yes.
Nice ride today, buddy.
Thanks.
[KIDS SHOUTING]
Yay! Come on in.
Katy, you look gorgeous.
You too, honey. BeautifuI.
Hello.
She aIways does.
Sandra, I love that dress.
Thanks. It's a new Iine
I'm carrying at the shop.
You should check it out.
Uh-huh.
[HIP-HOP MUSIC
BLARING OVER SPEAKERS]
All right, everybody in here.
All right, to a kick-ass New Year.
Senior year.
Yeah.
And great friends.
[ALL CHEERING]
Yes.
This is so typicaI of Larry, right?
[LAUGHING]
KATY: Sex, Lies, and--
BOB: Revenge of the Nerds.
[MUMBLING]
And Videotape.
Okay, no. Okay.
Rat. Rat. Ratatouille.
Shrek. Shrek!
Shrek!
We're so Iosing. Come on,
give me some more.
Okay, me, wife, woman. Woman.
[ALL LAUGHING]
Uh-- Moby Dick? I know, I know.
My Best Friend's Wedding!
[LAUGHING AND CHEERING]
LARRY:
You're a genius.
What? What were you thinking?
We're so good.
[ENGINE REVVING]
You guys are terribIe.
It's a New Year's Eve party.
PAT: What were they doing?
There are a lot of cars
out there.
Well, when the cat's away...
[CHATTERING]
Yo, yo, hey, where are you going?
Going to pick up some booze.
Yeah.
You're the man.
I know, right?
Get in here. Those jerks
from the parking lot are here
and now Ryan's
trying to fight them.
What, you think you can take me?
Stop. Aren't you gonna do
something about this?
No, this is Ryan's deal.
He told me to stay out of it.
Ooh.
KEITH:
Okay, okay, all right.
Now you either get out of here
or you deal with me.
We're gonna go. Let's go.
Yeah, get out of here.
Come on, bro.
Get up. Let's get up.
Let's go upstairs. Come on.
Go smoke some weed and chill out.
It's all right. It's all right, come on.
[BLOWS NOISEMAKER]
[CAR ALARM BLARING]
[BOTH LAUGH]
Did you see Eddie's face
after the race? It was gIowing.
LARRY:
I thought your head
was gonna pop off, buddy.
Oh, no.
KATY:
Oh, Sara-bear. Come here, honey.
What's wrong?
It's so noisy outside.
Oh, I know. Come here.
ShouId we call the cops?
No, maybe I'll just go over there
and talk to Shane.
Come on, piIgrims.
Let's go over there
and scare those kids straight.
I love you, Daddy.
Oh, my baby, come here. I love you.
Go upstairs.
Don't wake your brother up.
Hurry back. I'll put her to bed.
Good night, Sara.
[HIP-HOP MUSIC
BLARING OVER SPEAKERS]
[PEOPLE CHATTERING]
Let's split up, ask for Shane.
You got it, cowboy.
Have you seen Shane Batesman?
Uh-uh. I-- I don't know.
ED:
Hello, Iadies.
You know where Shane is?
Yo, go Iong.
He's a future Heisman winner, baby.
[ALL LAUGHING]
Nice catch.
I can't take you anywhere.
I know, right? Here.
You're unreal.
Oh, man.
How's that going?
AARON: Not bad.
Oh, hey. Come here,
come here. Heh-heh. Oh.
You are so wasted.
What? Lighten up.
You're such a drunk.
MAN [ON TV]:
New Year's Eve celebration
from Times Square...
They are asleep.
PAT: Come on.
Where's my drink?
Hey. Hi, honey.
[LAUGHS]
Well, where's your posse?
I don't know. I Iost them.
Lost them?
Three Stooges.
You left them there?
Oh, that place is a mob scene.
Can I come in?
Just shut the door.
KEITH: All right.
ANGIE: You're an all-star?
KEITH: A real all-star.
AARON: You gotta hoId it.
KEITH:
Yeah, good one.
BOTH:
Busted.
Hey, what's going on in here?
Who are you?
Where's Shane?
He's not here right now.
This is my friend's house and you're
gonna have to take it downstairs.
This room is off-Iimits.
PAT: It's aImost midnight.
Oh, guys, we gotta-- We need refills.
[MAN SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY
OVER TV]
[HIP-HOP MUSIC
BLARING OVER SPEAKERS]
I hate it when Ryan is drunk.
WOMAN:
Everybody, get downstairs!
MAN [ON TV]:
First kiss and hug of the New Year.
I like the odds. Get ready, Iadies.
You're a deviI.
Jordan?
I think I'm gonna throw up.
[RYAN VOMITING]
I'm gonna take him home.
I'm gonna call Bob.
He's missing everything.
SANDRA:
Okay, honey, it's yours, it's you.
It's you, baby, it's you.
I'm sorry.
GROUP: Sixteen, 15,
14, 13, 12, 11,
10, nine--
ALL EXCEPT KATY:
Eight, seven, six--
GROUP: Five, four, three, two--
ALL: One.
ALL:
Happy New Year!
[###]
[BLOWING NOISEMAKERS]
B-- Bob?
ALL:
Cheers.
Hey, hey. Hey.
It's New Year.
Aren't you gonna give me a kiss?
[ALL CHEERING]
I kissed him and he just
pushed me away like I was gross.
It's gonna be a wonderfuI year.
Yeah.
Happy New Year, sweetie.
Get in the car.
Why don't you give him another call
on his cell?
It's good. I need more.
ED: This is good.
PAT: I know.
BOB [ON RECORDING]:
Hi. This is Bob McIntosh.
Leave a message.
[SIREN WAILING]
Larry, what's going on?
It's-- It's Bob. He's unconscious.
What? What happened?
What do we have?
AduIt maIe, full cardiac arrest.
Start externaI compressions now.
It's Bob McIntosh.
KATY:
Steve?
Steve, is Bob gonna be okay?
I'll take good care of him.
Let me do my job.
Mrs. McIntosh, I'm sorry,
but you're not allowed in here.
[INDISTINCT CHATTER
OVER RADIO]
What the hell's going on?
Nothing.
Well, obviousIy something.
What about you all?
Can you tell me
what happened here?
Some guy got hurt.
They took him away
in an ambuIance.
Somebody got hurt? Who was it?
How should I know?
COP:
Did any of you see what happened?
No.
No, officer.
I mean, I just got here, so...
You're Shane Batesman, right?
Yeah.
I know your dad. You think
he's gonna be happy with this?
No, I think he's gonna be
pretty pissed off.
[###]
I'll drop your truck
off tomorrow.
You're mad at me.
[SOFTLY]
Yeah.
Ryan.
[LAUGHS]
I love you like crazy. Heh.
I love you too.
Thanks.
[SIGHS]
So you don't know who this guy was?
Other than he was an ass, no.
He said he was your dad's friend
or something.
Wait, so you talked to him?
We onIy talked to him
for, like, a second.
Yeah.
He told us to leave so we went out.
It's not a big deal.
But what happened to the guy then?
Who called the ambuIance?
I don't know.
I was down here partying
when it all went down.
[KEITH CLEARS THROAT]
My parents are gonna freak.
PAT:
The waiting is the hardest part.
Remember when you were
in that car accident?
What? I never heard about that.
PAT:
It's back when we were dating.
He broke his arm,
a coupIe of his ribs, his nose.
[PAT CHUCKLES]
And look at him now.
[###]
Steve.
I tried to resuscitate him.
No, don't--
I-- I did everything I couId.
But Bob died.
Steve, no.
Katy, I'm very sorry.
Oh, my God.
Okay.
[###]
ED:
Katy, I'm so sorry.
They think maybe
it was a heart attack.
They're not sure.
They're gonna do an autopsy.
MAN [ON TV]:
The stock market closed
with a solid...
Hey, happy New Year, Jordy.
Happy New Year, Daddy.
How was the party?
It was okay. Mm-hm.
Just okay?
We're gonna check out a matinee,
if you'd like to come.
Mm. Thanks,
but I have to take Ryan's truck back.
Okay.
[NEWS THEME PLAYS OVER TV]
A Rees Harbor man has died after
being rushed to Rockport General
from a New Year's Eve party
on King James Road.
[###]
What's going on in here?
Where's Shane?
He's not here right now.
--At the home of a neighbor where
200 teenagers were gathered.
I have to find my phone.
REPORTER:
Attempts to revive
were unsuccessful.
Jordan?
[SIGHS]
What's this big emergency,
you had to get me up so earIy?
You know that guy from the party
last night? He died.
What guy?
What are you talking about?
The guy who came into the bedroom
and told us to get out.
[SIGHS]
You really don't remember.
No.
I'm calling Angie.
Angie, did you hear about the guy,
the one from the party?
ANGIE:
I know, he died.
I'll get Keith and Aaron to meet us.
You call Ryan.
I got Ryan already.
He doesn't remember anything.
He got way too drunk.
Shh. Calm. Quiet.
What are we gonna do?
Don't say anything.
Just get over to Rees Point and
we'll figure it out when we get there.
[###]
PAT: Katy, can I get you some tea?
KATY: Sure, thanks.
KATY:
Hey, Sara-bear, come here.
Come here. Hey.
Hey. Where's your brother?
Where's Daddy? I can't find him.
I know, baby. Come here.
I gotta talk to both of you. Come here.
I have something sad
to tell you about Daddy.
KEITH [ON RECORDING]:
Hey, this is Keith.
Leave a message after the tone.
[BOAT HORN BLOWS]
ANGIE:
Did you guys get Keith?
No, he's not answering his phone.
[RYAN SIGHS]
RYAN:
So this guy really died, huh?
Man, that sucks.
Yeah. Yeah, it sucks.
This cop was asking us
all these questions.
What did you tell him?
Nothing.
I mean, there's nothing to tell, really.
Right?
How can you say that?
What do you mean?
You were there. It was no big thing.
Come on, let's just go.
The rest of you too. Let's go.
Yeah, we heard you.
We're on our way out, all right?
[PUNCH LANDS]
We should say
we never saw the guy.
There were other people up there
when he came in.
We should tell the cops
what we told Shane,
that the guy came into the bedroom,
he told us to get out and we left.
And the last time we saw him,
he was alive and well, which is true.
Is it?
Yes. You were there.
I went out before you guys.
You were in there when I left.
Yeah, we were right behind you.
WouId you please tell her?
Man, I don't remember any of this.
[SIGHS]
I have a snowboard
competition coming up.
I want that endorsement deal.
My dad got me that internship
at the paper this summer.
Yeah, so if we open our mouths,
we're all screwed.
She's not gonna say anything.
She's cooI. Right, Jordan?
[###]
Fine.
I won't say anything.
Good.
Now, what about that sophomore
that was there?
Aaron.
Hey.
I thought maybe you and I
couId go take a little ride.
Mom, I'll be right back.
[###]
[SOBBING]
[KNOCK ON DOOR]
[CLEARS THROAT]
Yeah?
SANDRA: It's Sandy.
Come on in.
A Detective Jackson is here
to see you.
Okay.
I'll be right down.
[DOOR CLOSES]
The full autopsy report
won't be avaiIabIe until next week.
I got a call from
the coroner's office this morning
with a preIiminary report.
Yeah, it was a heart attack.
No. Your husband died
of a brain hemorrhage.
You mean like a--? Like a stroke?
Not exactIy, no.
The probIem was a Iack of bIood
to the brain due to a severed artery.
What are you saying?
I'm saying that your husband
suffered a bIunt force trauma
consistent with a beating.
That's impossibIe.
I'm sorry.
[###]
Mrs. McIntosh, the coroner
beIieves that your husband
was kicked to death.
He was murdered.
[###]
These are from Bob's office.
Mommy, where's my cereal?
SANDRA:
It's right here. I've got it. Okay.
I don't want milk on my cereal.
What?
That's okay,
I'll get you another bowI, honey.
KATY:
It's fine, it's fine.
I'll run to the store.
KATY: It's fine.
Sorry. I didn't know
she liked them dry.
It's okay, really.
[DOORBELL RINGS]
You know what,
can you get the door?
Yeah.
Thank you.
I'm just gonna pour the milk out.
Here, just eat it like that.
Those are all wet.
Okay. I'll-- I'll fix it.
Mommy, I'm hungry.
Sara, I am doing
the best I can, okay?
[KATY SIGHS]
I'm sorry. Here.
Just start on those, okay? There.
Can you start on those, babe?
I'll make you some toast.
Katy, you're exhausted.
Why don't you go and Iie down?
I can watch the kids.
I'm good. I need to keep moving.
Otherwise I'll start crying
and I might not be abIe to stop.
[SNIFFS THEN CLEARS THROAT]
They just Iost their dad. I can't let
them think they've Iost their mom too.
[###]
PauI, you wanted to see me?
Yeah. Okay, so you were the first unit
on scene last night, right?
Yes, sir.
Okay.
You secured the area,
identified all witnesses.
Paramedics told me
they thought it was a heart attack.
There were 200 kids here last night.
You must have got
a lot of information.
If I had any indication
this was a crime scene,
I would've been more thorough.
I've got maybe a dozen names.
Okay, well, we have to contact
each and every one
of those kids that were
here at the party,
so I hope you're up
for some serious overtime.
[BUZZING]
Yeah?
Finally someone picks up their phone.
What the hell happened last night?
What are you talking about?
There's cops all over my house.
My dad's friend
from across the street
was killed here.
What?
Wasn't just dead, he was murdered.
In my parents' bedroom.
Murdered? You're kidding.
What? What's wrong?
My parents are gonna be home
in an hour.
What the hell am I supposed
to tell them? What?
Uh--
I'll call you back.
Look, this doesn't change anything.
No reason we should spill our guts
about what happened.
Don't see how an investigation
changes anything?
WouId you keep your voice down?
Not for us.
Okay, we didn't kill the guy.
How do you know?
He was on the fIoor
when Keith and I left that room.
Yes, yes, he was on the fIoor,
but he was still bitching at us.
[PUNCH LANDS]
Dude, that was harsh, man.
Ha-ha-ha.
BOB:
What the hell's wrong
with you people?
KEITH: Let's go party.
AARON: That was sick.
AARON:
WouId you please tell them, Daisy?
Yeah. There was a lot of other people
upstairs when we went out.
ExactIy. So if the guy got whacked,
then someone eIse did the whacking.
And I don't want that pinned on us,
do you?
Where's Keith?
I don't know.
His dad took his phone away.
Hi, Jordan.
Hi.
These are the memoriaI ribbons
for Bob McIntosh.
JORDAN: Okay.
MAN: They expect so many people,
they'll hoId it
at the community center.
Anyway, hand them out.
That'd be great.
Yeah.
[###]
Bob McIntosh was many things:
Father, husband, friend.
But he was aIso a Iawyer,
committed to justice.
A commitment for Bob meant action.
And his death
was tragic,
untimely,
and so unnecessary.
Okay. It's okay.
[MOUTHING]
BOB: Let's go. Get up.
RYAN: All right, I'm fine, you guys.
BOB: You too, buddy. Let's go.
KEITH: We heard you, okay?
RYAN:
Something happened
at the funeraI yesterday.
I... I think I remember.
What do you remember?
MostIy acting like a jerk.
I acted like a jerk that whoIe night,
didn't I?
Yeah, pretty much.
I don't know why
you haven't dumped me already.
[LAUGHS]
I don't know either.
When you're not with your friends,
you are the sweetest person
I've ever met.
Why are you ragging on them?
They've been good to you.
When you hang out with them,
you get stupid.
You get into fights,
and now this guy got killed.
You're saying my friends killed him?
No, that's not what I'm saying.
You know what? Forget it.
[SIGHS]
Jordan, I don't wanna fight.
Me either.
RYAN:
I can just keep driving, you know?
You can come stay at my place
for a little.
No, they'll just be back.
I might as well get this over with.
[###]
JORDAN:
So we werejjust hanging out
in the room.
And then the guy, Mr. McIntosh,
he came in,
and said that he wanted us
to get out.
Can you remember
his exact words?
I don't know, like:
"I'm gonna have to ask you to take
the party downstairs," or something.
And what did you do?
JORDAN:
I got up and said, "Let's go," and...
Was this the point when Keith Moore
called him a name?
I guess.
Come on.
[PUNCH LANDS]
Oh! Ha-ha. That was sick.
Oh, you little bitch.
Maybe Keith did call him a name.
Okay.
But then he came out
with me and Angie and...
Oh, yeah.
Come on, let's go party. Yee!
Then the other guys,
they came out right after us.
And the last time you saw
Bob McIntosh, he was...
What, he was just standing there?
Yeah.
He didn't seem like
he was distressed
in any way to you?
Is that true?
If she says it's true, it's true.
If she saw anything that might help,
she knows we'd expect her
to come forward.
Daisy isn't home right now.
Don't know when she'll be back.
Okay, what? What?
Keith called him a name?
Okay, I don't remember that,
but, I mean, I was pretty wasted.
Look, we know they're underage.
And we've had a Iong,
very serious talk about all that, right?
Yeah.
It's not gonna happen again.
Uh-huh. What happened
after Keith got into this
sparring match with Mr. McIntosh?
Nothing.
Nothing?
How many people would you say
were upstairs when you left?
Let me guess. Ten.
Ten.
[PEOPLE CHATTERING]
The kids are having so much fun.
I'm so gIad you didn't canceI.
Well, I can't canceI birthdays.
No.
Bob was so excited
to throw this party for the kids.
You know, he loved parties.
Yes, he did.
MAN:
Red Iight!
SANDRA:
You want me to help?
This pinhata was his idea, and now
I don't know how to hang it up.
[###]
You know,
I called that grief counseIor,
and he said to me,
that it would be three weeks
before I couId get an appointment.
He said, "I don't know if you're aware,
but there's been a crisis in this town."
[LAUGHS]
[SNIFFLING]
Katy, it's okay to grieve.
WOMAN:
Katy, there's someone at the door.
You know, I'll go get that.
No, I got it, I got it.
Here, you have a look at it.
Is this a bad time?
Um...
Dealing with teenagers
is tough with peer pressure
not to talk to cops.
But we have narrowed this down
to a small group of kids
that had some confrontation with
your husband that Ied to an attack.
UnfortunateIy,
they're all saying the same thing.
It was just a short exchange
and Bob was alive
when they left the room.
And do you beIieve them?
They're not telling the whoIe story.
What's that mean?
SeveraI said
there were others upstairs.
We're trying to figure out
who those others were.
Two hundred kids at that party,
no one saw what happened to Bob?
No, we will continue
to interview them,
and eventually--
Eventually? How am I supposed
to live with eventually?
How am I supposed to
take my kids to the market,
and not know if the boy bagging
killed their father?
Mrs. McIntosh, I completeIy under--
No, I'm sorry, but you don't.
Every time I walk out my front door,
and I see that house and I think:
"That's where Bob
was beaten to death
and, gee, I wonder who did it."
I'm sorry.
I know that you're working overtime.
Oh, no.
You have every right to be frustrated.
It's not just that. It's...
I hate feeling powerIess.
And some of those kids must know
what happened to Bob.
There's gotta be a way
that I can convince them to talk.
And there is, but that's not your job.
That's my job. Okay?
Okay.
[###]
MAN [ON TV]:
She has been posting dozens
of flyers throughout Rees Harbor
asking for help in the killing
that remains unsolved.
Dad, are we still going out to--?
Shh.
She hopes the $10,000 reward
will encourage
those with information about
her husband's death
to come forward.
KATY:
I don't know how anyone
who lives here can feel safe
when we have a bunch of drunk,
violent, irresponsible kids,
who are posing a threat
to the community.
The kids who know
what happened to Bob,
need to tell the police
what they know.
Their parents should be
encouraging them to do this.
Hey, Shane.
What's his probIem IateIy?
My dad put me through this
third-degree thing last night.
It sucked.
It totally sucked.
DAISY:
Have you guys seen this?
We know all about it.
Not our probIem. We're done.
Aren't you worried
someone's gonna tell?
No. Because everybody knows
that a rat is the scum of the earth.
Right. So don't even think about
trying to score some cash.
First of all, I think staying out of jail
is worth a hell of a lot more
than a Iousy 10 grand,
and second, I'm no rat.
Then we have nothing
to worry about, do we?
Oh, right. We onIy Iied to the cops
in a murder investigation.
This is our senior year.
Wasn't this supposed to be
the most fun time of our whoIe lives?
Not so much.
[DOOR OPENS]
You're not gonna talk to my daughter.
You've talked to her twice. I resent it.
Legally speaking, she's 18.
I don't need permission.
Yeah, Iegally speaking,
I can sue your ass for harassment.
Look, Angie needs to focus
on finishing schooI,
getting ready for college.
She can't do that
with you twisting her arm
to get her to admit
to something she didn't do.
Twisting her arm? I'm not.
I'm warning you,
stay away from these kids.
And I am telling you, these kids need
to come clean about what happened.
Right, right. Well, that's great. Okay,
well, thank you very much for calling.
I appreciate it, and we'll get back
to you if we need to. Thanks.
This is crazy.
I wish she'd talked to me first.
I can onIy follow up
on four or five an hour.
ShouId put another guy on this.
Concentrate on the witnesses
we know were there,
forget all these Iong shots.
[PHONE RINGS]
You telling the switchboard
to forward these calls to me?
Detective Jackson.
I can bareIy hear you.
You were at the party?
[HORN HONKS]
Wow.
Look at that car.
Nice.
How do you like
my new birthday present, huh?
My sisters were so freaking jealous,
man, they were, like, crying.
[LAUGHS]
So are you and Daisy,
like, together now?
We might be. She's all right.
Keith. Where you been?
Grounded. Is that your ride?
It is so sick, eh?
It's hot.
So sick.
Look at that thing. Come on, let's--
[SIREN WAILING]
Whoa, what's going on?
Keith Moore,
we have a warrant for your arrest.
Wait. Why?
You're charged with manslaughter
What?
In the death of Robert McIntosh.
I already told you, it was a tap.
I told you that.
PAUL:
You have the right to remain siIent.
Anything you say can
and will be used against you.
You have the right to an attorney.
If you cannot afford an attorney...
You ratted him out, didn't you?
No.
AARON:
This is so wrong.
[DOOR OPENS]
Hey, how are you?
Good morning.
Hi, guys. Oh, you're welcome.
Did you see all the letters
to the editor
defending Keith Moore
as if he's the victim in all this?
I know. My neighbor was saying
she's known Keith since he was 10,
and she said he's a real good kid.
Yeah, well,
maybe he is a really good kid,
but he still hit Bob at least once.
Thanks for looking after the kids.
It's important that
I'm there at the arraignment today.
He admitted from the beginning
that he punched Bob in the face?
And you never told me?
He called it a tap.
We had no confirmation
from witnesses
that it was anything but that
until an anonymous call said
a punch put him on the ground.
What eIse did they say? A punch
doesn't explain a severed artery.
He must have kicked him.
Well, that's all they're saying.
I thought you said you brought in
the person who's responsibIe.
No, I never said that.
But you're charging him
with manslaughter.
Keith Moore is gonna break
the siIence between these kids.
We're hoping he gives us the killer
if he thinks he's facing jail time.
Now, you brace yourseIf.
Moore's got a lot of support.
MAN 1:
Here he comes!
[###]
MAN 2: We're with you.
You hang in there, bro.
Don't worry. The town is behind you.
WOMAN: We're with you.
REPORTER:
Do you have a comment?
Look this way, Mrs. McIntosh, please.
You shouldn't be going after
my son.
He's cooperated with the poIice
from the beginning.
MAN 3:
He didn't have anything to do with it!
Don't you care?
You couId ruin his Iife.
You leave our kids aIone.
This isn't right.
I'm not backing down
till I find out who did it.
I have the right to know.
[DOOR OPENS]
[MUSIC PLAYING ON TV]
MARINA:
Hey, sweetie. Sorry I'm so Iate.
I picked up sandwiches at the deIi,
if you're hungry.
Uh-- No.
I'm not feeling too good.
Oh, no.
Are you feeling sick again?
Are you running a fever?
No, it's just my stomach.
Last week, it was your head,
and now your stomach.
[PHONE RINGS]
Jordan. That's weird.
Doesn't she usually call your cell?
Can you just tell her I'm asleep
or something?
Hi, Jordan.
No, I'm sorry. He can't come to
the phone. He's not feeling very well.
[BELL RINGS]
[CHATTERING]
You seen Ryan?
He hasn't been here in a week.
He's not answering his phone.
Do I look like his secretary to you?
Hey, guys, check this out.
[###]
[GASPS]
[STUDENTS LAUGHING
& CHATTERING]
[LAUGHS]
That's what you get, snitch.
I never said anything to anyone.
Yeah, right.
I hate you.
What is wrong with you?
Why do that?
The judge wouldn't let Keith
out of jail unIess he promised
not to talk to us.
Do you know how hard
I've been working to keep her quiet?
You just messed that all up.
NewsfIash, she didn't stay quiet.
Daisy, I'm sorry.
You guys have no reason
to be mean.
If I had called the cops,
they would know a lot more.
Just shut up, Daisy.
A lot of other stuff happened
that you guys don't even know--
Just shut your mouth!
[AARON AND KEITH CHUCKLE]
You wanna mess with us?
Stay down, punk.
Just don't say anything to Angie,
all right?
Just don't say anything to anybody.
[SOBBING]
I think there's more on me than Sara.
You're a mess.
You really should've let me buy.
Aw. Thank you.
But, uh, we're fine for the moment.
Hey, look, there's Sally. Hey, Sally.
[INAUDIBLE DIALOGUE]
What is that all about?
I got a nasty e-maiI from her the other
day. Her daughter was at the party.
She asked whether I was
gonna have her arrested too.
PAT:
Oh, of all the stupid things to say.
Well, if nothing eIse, I'm finding out
who my real friends are.
Yeah.
[KNOCK ON DOOR]
Ryan?
What?
Jordan's here to see you.
Don't let her in.
It's a little Iate for that.
Come on in, honey.
Oh, my God.
I had to come.
You don't answer your phone.
Are you mad at me?
No.
Then why won't you talk to me?
The detective was at schooI today,
and things are getting really crazy
between Angie and Daisy.
Angie thinks Daisy
is some kind of a snitch.
Daisy says--
I don't wanna know what Daisy says.
She says a lot more happened
that Angie and I don't know about.
This is why I don't wanna talk!
All you talk about is that night.
I don't wanna talk about it.
I don't wanna think about it!
Will you please get out
and leave me aIone?
Please! Just get--
Just get out. Get out.
[###]
What are you even doing here, huh?
Damn it!
PAUL:
Katy, you got a minute?
Yeah, I gotta pick up the twins.
What is it?
DA is dropping the mansIaughter
charge against Keith Moore.
What? Why?
We got Bob on the ground, but no
one's telling us what happened after.
So the whoIe thing was just a bIuff?
And Keith's attorney called us on it.
I'm sorry.
So basically, after three months,
you have nothing.
These kids are in this
group mentality, not talking.
The parents aren't helping.
Not that I blame them.
You don't blame them?
Think about it. What would you do?
If Josh and Sara were at that party,
would you turn them in?
I don't know. I'd like to think
that I would do the right thing.
I need you to know that
I'm not giving up on this case.
I'm not gonna stop
until I find the person who did this.
You know I can't just sit around
and do nothing, right? You know that.
[###]
You're sure about this?
Uh-- Why don't you read me
what you have?
[CLEARS THROAT]
I typed it up.
[KATY CLEARS THROAT]
"The months since my husband's
murder have been the most pa--"
I hate this. I'm--
I'm not good at pubIic speaking.
Yes, you are.
You can do this.
You're doing it for Josh and Sara.
[###]
Right. Okay.
[KATY SIGHS]
Again.
Okay.
"The months since
my husband's murder have been
the most painfuI
and difficuIt months of my Iife
and the lives of our two children."
Not onIy did we Iose Bob,
but knowing that he was
a victim of a vioIent crime
has threatened our sense of safety
in our community.
Today, my attorney
will be fiIing a civiI suit
against the known witnesses
who last saw my husband alive.
There is something very wrong
in Rees Harbor
if our children can witness
a fatal beating and not come clean.
We all need to address that.
The news of
the wrongful death suit
brought by the victim's widow,
Katy McIntosh,
against several
high school students,
exploded through the town
of Rees Harbor today.
We found sentiment both
for and against the action,
revealing a town
that has become bitterly divided
since the murder in question.
I didn't know Bob McIntosh,
but I don't blame his wife at all.
I don't think it's right
what's going on.
People aren't coming out
because they think it's not safe.
It's hurting my business.
MAN:
People are like,
"Those kids should talk."
That's not right. I'd never rat out
my friends, no matter what.
She deserves to know
who killed her husband.
You give me 10 minutes
alone with those kids,
I'll find out who did it.
We also spoke
with Detective Paul Jackson,
who is in charge of the case.
I'm not gonna comment
on this lawsuit,
but we are aware
that information is being withheld.
And if anybody wants to come in
and clarify their previous statements,
they can do so
without fear of repercussions.
[TV CLICKS OFF]
I don't know what to do.
I don't have money to hire a Iawyer.
We can hire one
to represent all of us.
Doesn't change the fact
that I can't afford it.
Don't worry about that, Leo.
We'll make sure it's covered.
I wanna know if we can countersue
for sIander or defamation or--
That's what I'm thinking.
We shouldn't take
this pubIic harassment Iying down.
[KNOCK ON DOOR]
It's a terribIe tragedy
that her husband was killed,
but that doesn't give her the right
to make scapegoats of our children.
[DOOR OPENS]
Hey, is Ryan here?
No.
Hasn't been home
for a coupIe nights.
I'll call the poIice.
Come in. We'll ask the kids.
They're in the back.
Hi.
Hey, have any of you kids
seen Ryan?
No.
ANGIE: Me neither.
I have an idea where he might be.
I can check.
Really?
AARON: Yeah.
Okay. I appreciate it.
I'm coming with you.
No, no, I got this.
He's my boyfriend.
I'm going with you.
[###]
All right.
Jordan, you call me.
I will.
[CAR DOORS CLOSING]
[MAN LAUGHS]
Who lives here?
I told you, no questions,
unIess you wanna wait in the car.
[ROCK MUSIC PLAYING
OVER SPEAKERS]
What do you dumb-asses want?
Chuck, we're looking for Ryan.
His truck's here.
Is he in there with you?
Don't know.
Ryan, you in here?
[MUSIC STOPS]
What are you doing here?
Wanna come out here
and talk to us?
Why did you bring her?
Ryan, don't.
What?
You're the one that doesn't like me
when I'm drunk.
Well, I'm drunk now, baby.
Heh-heh. I'm hammered.
Great. We're very happy for you.
But your mom is freaking out.
You haven't been home.
No. What? What?
What do you mean?
I left a note.
UnIess, uh-- UnIess I forgot.
Ha. Oops. Ha-ha.
We're gonna take you home,
tell your mom to chill out,
then we'll come back here and party.
No, man, I'm not going home.
I'm gonna crash here with Chuck
for a whiIe, so...
What about schooI?
We have a coupIe of months
until graduation.
You're not Iistening to me.
I don't give a crap about schooI.
I, uh... I'm done with schooI,
I'm done with home,
and I'm done with you, so...
[###]
[MAN COUGHING]
JORDAN:
But what about our pIans?
We were gonna get an apartment,
we were gonna go to college.
I don't wanna talk anymore.
AARON:
Dude, are you coming?
All right, forget this.
I'm out of here. Let's go.
I wish that you would
just tell me what's wrong.
[SIGHS]
[HORN BLOWS]
[PEOPLE CHATTERING]
Hey, Katy.
[DISHES CLATTERING]
Um... Excuse me. Uh...
You're Jordan, right?
Yeah.
You were in the room when
my husband was killed, weren't you?
I just--
MAN: Excuse me.
I'm gonna need you
to take your break now, okay?
I'll serve Mrs. McIntosh.
Okay.
I'll be right with you.
Yeah.
You see that girI I was talking to?
One of the witnesses.
You're kidding me.
Katy, leave the poor girI aIone.
Sandra.
No, Katy, I'm sorry, it's just--
It's a tourist town, okay?
This is making it difficuIt
for people to make a living.
I can't pretend nothing happened.
No one's saying that.
There are better ways to go about it.
Can't you let the poIice do their job?
They're not doing their job.
Then just leave those kids aIone.
Sandra, one of those kids
kicked Bob so hard
that it killed him.
SANDRA:
I know. It's just that--
[SIGHS]
I want them to find the guiIty person.
Do you?
Yes. But it's just--
If this is your strategy,
it's not working.
Yeah, well,
no one gave me a ruIe book.
I gotta go.
Katy, don't--
I can't beIieve you just said that.
Jordan, if you know what happened
to my husband,
and you're keeping quiet
to protect your friends--
Mrs. McIntosh.
Yeah, I'm leaving.
Please.
I'm leaving, I'm leaving.
Mrs. McIntosh, wait.
I didn't keep quiet.
I was the one who called the poIice.
[###]
I left the room after I saw Keith
punch your husband.
I don't know anything eIse.
If I did, I would tell you.
And the others,
do they know what happened?
I think so, some of them, but
they will never talk about it
around me.
Jordan, thank you. Thank you.
You were the snitch.
Hi, Katy. What can I do for you?
Jordan Mathers beIieves
that some of the kids
do know what happened.
Okay, that's heIpfuI. Of course,
we've known that all aIong.
No one's ever said those words.
Now you can bring them in
and interrogate them.
Again. Yeah, you know,
I can interrogate them 16 more times.
When you put this much pressure
on a group of kids,
they band together
and protect each other.
Are you talking about my lawsuit?
You're allowed to sue.
But it's hard to exploit cracks
in a group when they're
bonding together,
hiring attorneys to tell them
to shut their mouth.
I thought I was helping.
To help, trust us to do our jobs.
Trust isn't my strongest suit
right now.
There's stuff going on
I just can't discuss.
I know. I get it, PauI.
I am on your side.
I am not your enemy, Katy.
Yeah, well, sometimes
it doesn't feeI like that.
I'm-- I'm, uh--
I'm sorry.
I don't know if I can keep doing this.
Maybe I should just move back
to PortIand, be cIose to my famiIy.
[ROCK MUSIC
PLAYING OVER SPEAKERS]
I got uppers, downers.
Got weed, really good stuff.
Like really primo stuff.
CHRIS: We're talking at least three.
CHUCK: Three?
CHRIS: At least.
CHUCK:
Looks like I got a coupIe
new customers.
Go get us some beers.
All right. All right.
CHUCK:
Yeah, so, I mean, this stuff is...
[HORN HONKS]
You sure you don't want me
to go in with you?
We can talk to the principaI
and tell him what's going on.
No, then they'll just think
I ratted them out twice.
I know you feeI bad,
but you did the right thing.
When did I ever do the right thing?
I Iied to the poIice in the beginning,
I Iied to you, I Iied to my friends.
If you have to make yourseIf
an accompIice to murder
to prove your IoyaIty to friends,
it's time to get new friends.
You think?
[###]
Bye.
Hey.
I'm sorry. I'm so sorry.
I know.
I thought Pat was gonna smack me
after you left.
No, no--
She should've.
You heIped me see things differentIy.
I'm dropping the Iawsuit.
You're what?
Yeah, I thought that it would help
convince the kids to talk,
but I was wrong.
I've been wrong
about a lot of things IateIy.
No, I never should have said
what I said.
I was way out of Iine.
No, Sandy, I just...
I want you to understand
that this isn't about vengeance.
[SIGHS]
Wanna get some tea?
Yes.
[###]
I don't blame you guys
for being mad.
[BELL RINGS]
Oh, we are way beyond mad.
I know. You're scared too.
You should be scared.
I am. I've been freaked out
since New Year's Eve.
So you had Keith arrested?
I just wanted to tell what I saw.
We don't want the cops to know
what you saw.
Why not?
No one was trying to kill anyone
that night.
I'm not gonna rot in prison
and be somebody's bitch.
Do you understand that?
Why would you be going to prison?
UnIess you were the one who kicked
Bob McIntosh in the head.
Where'd you hear that? Huh?
Did Ryan tell you that?
No.
Is that why he's Iosing it right now?
Because he knows that you did it
and he's afraid to tell anyone?
[GUN FIRING]
CHRIS:
Look at him.
Guy thinks he's in "Call of Duty."
Whoa. Whoa.
Hey, man.
Hey, Ryan, come on, chill out.
Come smoke some of this joint,
soak in the beauty of nature.
He's a tortured souI.
Yeah? And why is that?
Sorry.
It's just a BB gun.
[CRYING]
I'm so sorry. I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
I didn't even know it was you.
I'm sorry. Shh.
No, it's okay, it's okay.
[SOBBING]
I shouldn't have done that.
We broke up.
Why? Why can't we be together?
Why can't we go back
to the way things were?
I miss you so much.
We just can't.
It's like you dropped out
of your whoIe Iife.
It's like you're another person.
Guess I am.
Ryan, please.
Just drop it, Jordan.
What did Aaron do?
I know you remember.
[###]
Is she tripping or what?
You were there?
Yeah.
So you know how that guy died?
KATY:
Give me a kiss night-night.
I love you.
I love you. Night-night.
Sweet dreams.
JOSH:
Mommy?
Yeah, honey?
Jeremy said that I should hurt
those guys that killed Daddy.
Oh, no, baby.
[###]
That's the last thing that we want.
We don't want any more people hurt.
Do I have to stop thinking
about Daddy?
No. We are never gonna
forget about Daddy.
Forgiving doesn't mean forgetting.
Your daddy is aIways gonna be
right here, right in our hearts.
Okay?
All right, you have Lion?
Mm-hm.
Okay, give me a kiss.
[PHONE RINGING]
Hello.
Katy. PauI Jackson.
I wanted you to know
we brought Ryan AIdridge in tonight.
You did?
Our undercover guys got him on tape
saying he knows
who killed your husband.
Finally.
KATY:
You've gotta be kidding me.
CouIdn't get Ryan to talk.
He's reIuctant to say anything
that might put a friend in prison.
You're not thinking of letting him go.
What choices do I have?
I couId book him on obstruction,
but he'll just get an attorney
to cry entrapment and get him off.
Look, Katy, um...
You think you're gonna find cIosure
in the justice system, and you won't.
Then let me talk to him.
No. No.
Why?
That's not the way things are done.
No, you couId jeopardize the case.
Ruin the case? What case?
You have nothing.
You just said
that he will probabIy walk.
Why do you think you can get
more out of him than we have?
Because I'm a mother,
and I know how to talk to kids.
[###]
He's probabIy scared.
I know I have been
since New Year's Eve.
PauI, please.
I should have every right
to look him in the eye,
and ask him what happened
if he knows anything.
I don't know.
PauI, this is your chance
to cIose the case.
You're a piece of work,
you know that?
All right.
I'll tell the DA you'll sue us
if we don't give you a shot.
[LAUGHS]
Thank you.
You ready?
I have no idea
what I'm gonna say to him.
Katy McIntosh at a Ioss for words?
Now, remember, the DA has put
a 30-minute time Iimit on this.
Okay.
Not much of a conversation
and this kid has perfected
the art of pIaying deaf.
So I got a guy right outside the room.
I'll be on the other side of the wall.
Come on.
You sure you wanna do this aIone?
You don't have to.
Yes, I do.
[###]
In my mind,
you looked so different.
I have a son,
and a daughter too.
They're twins.
Two for one. Heh.
I've got some pictures,
if you wanna see.
There, um...
That's Bob with the kids.
And, um...
I think they were around 4
when that picture was taken.
That's Josh and there's Sara.
I call her Sara-bear.
Sara's more like me. She...
She won't let anyone see her cry,
but I--
I keep finding a picture of Bob
hidden under her pillow.
And Josh, he's different.
He cries and he asks
all kinds of questions,
like, who's gonna take off
his training wheeIs?
And I hate those kinds of things,
I guess because
I'm not that good at them.
I'm trying to keep their lives normaI.
They keep asking me
what happened to their father,
and I don't know what to tell them,
because I don't know, but you do.
Ryan, look at me.
You know what happened to Bob
that night, don't you?
I know that you're not at peace.
They told me that
you dropped out of schooI and...
You must be carrying
a terribIe burden
and I know you're scared.
Ryan. Ryan, look at me.
You have to talk about it.
You have to talk about
what happened that night.
You have to tell the truth.
We are in this together.
Right? Whether we like it or not,
we are in this together.
You need to tell the poIice
what happened.
And I promise you, Ryan,
I promise you, I will stand by you.
I will be there for you 110 percent,
I promise.
[SIGHS]
[DOOR OPENS]
[###]
[DOOR CLOSES]
[SIGHS]
He's just a boy.
[DOOR OPENS THEN CLOSES]
[DOOR OPENS]
[SNIFFLES]
[DOOR CLOSES]
I'll tell you what happened,
but I want my mom here first.
[###]
Katy.
[DOOR OPENS]
[DOOR CLOSES]
It'll be okay.
Whatever you have to say,
I'm here for you.
PAUL:
Okay.
All right.
For the record, I'm talking with Ryan
AIdridge with his attorney present.
Okay, Ryan.
Why don't you tell us what
you know about New Year's Eve?
Well, uh,
first of all, I was kind of out of it,
so there are some parts
I don't remember.
But there were way more people
than we expected,
and there was a ton of aIcohoI.
I probabIy should have eaten first,
but...
[PEOPLE YELLING]
[LAUGHS THEN WHOOPS]
I got really drunk, really fast.
Um...
These guys showed up
who had given my girIfriend
a hard time earIier.
Get out!
Think you can take me?
You know, I was angry.
I just wanted to get back at them.
Before I got a chance to,
the one hit me,
and knocked me down
in front of all my friends.
Um, it was, um,
humiIiating.
[BOY LAUGHING]
[CROWD CHATTERING]
Um...
I guess
we must have gone upstairs.
He's a future Heisman winner, baby.
[BOTH LAUGHING]
I was still really pissed.
Oh.
You are so wasted.
What? Lighten up.
But I was trying to chill out,
and then Mr. McIntosh comes in.
AARON & KEITH:
Busted. Ha-ha-ha.
Hey, you guys,
what's going on in here?
What? Who are you?
BOB:
Where's Shane?
JORDAN:
He's not here right now.
Uh, this is my friend's house.
You have to take it downstairs.
This room is off-Iimits.
KEITH:
Ha-ha. Yeah.
Yeah, if you insist, buddy.
I think you're the one
who's off-Iimits, bro.
Narc.
Outnumbered.
We can pIay this one of two ways.
JORDAN: Guys, let's go. Come on.
Ryan?
Please? Let's go. Come on.
The rest of you too.
Come on, let's go. Get up, please.
All right, let's go.
He says we have to
take the party downstairs.
Thank you.
BOB: Come on.
We heard you. We're on our way out.
I don't really know what happened,
but Keith punched him.
Oh!
Whoa!
Come on. Let's go party. Ha-ha.
Bitch.
And Mr. McIntosh, you know,
he was on his hands and knees.
And it was like, "Okay. We've got
this guy who's giving us crap.
We got him down."
AARON:
That was harsh, man.
Are you gonna mess with us, huh?
So Aaron pushes him back down.
Stay down, punk. Ha.
I was just so
sick of people giving me crap,
you know?
[###]
Then, uh...
Then I kicked him.
I kicked him. I-- I--
[RYAN SIGHS]
I don't know why,
but I kicked him, like, maybe three
or maybe four times.
You know, I didn't--
I didn't realize how hard
I kicked him.
I killed him. It was me. I killed him.
I'm so sorry.
[SOBBING]
It's gonna be okay.
[###]
[SOBBING]
Yeah, that's really cooI.
[CELL PHONE RINGING]
Hello?
Wait. What?
Ryan just got arrested.
[STUDENTS CHATTERING]
Mommy!
Hi, you guys.