Hello?
I have a collect call
from Wayne Felde...
...a death-row inmate at
the correctional facility.
- Will you accept the charges?
- Hold on.
Why am I in your bed?
Go back to sleep. Go back to sleep.
Will you accept the charges?
- Hold on, just a second.
- Ma'am?
Ma'am, will you accept
the charges?
- Ma'am?
- Yes, I'll accept the charges.
Go ahead.
- You didn't wanna talk to me.
- No, it's not that.
I didn't get much sleep.
Yeah. I didn't get me much either.
Just had me a fine meal
of fried chicken and gravy.
That's what everybody wants
for their last meal.
Don't be sad, girl.
I'm getting what I want.
It's what I deserve.
I am glad
I had the chance to know you, Wayne.
Time's up.
Well...
...I better go now.
I got some place I gotta be.
You tak e care, darling.
- Graves Thomas.
- Good morning, Prissy.
- Why'd you do that?
- Do what?
Let me give my home number
to Wayne Felde.
- He called you?
- Yep.
- Are you all right?
Well, he was guilty anyway, darling.
He even admitted it himself.
And you was the only one
kept trying to help him.
Obviously didn't help him enough.
You don't know that.
What's this?
- Why is this case back on my desk?
- Do you know Calvin Willis?
I thought you said
he was a lost cause.
Was a lost cause.
Now, I got the detective coming in that
worked on the case for a little chat.
Well, I'm officially resigning
as a babysitter to the doomed.
Thing about old Calvin here, though,
he might actually be innocent.
- Right.
- No, I'm telling you, darling.
You don't need a law degree or cane
pole to smell something fishy here.
You remember
that detective I mentioned?
She was a metre maid about
the time the city council decided...
...that the old boys needed
more women on the force.
So they call in Miss Loretta Brooks,
give her a badge, give her a gun...
...and tell her to go to work
on this child-rape case...
...involving an 11 -year-old girl.
Her first case.
Right out of the chute,
no experience whatsoever.
Hey, I don't know how innocent he is,
but that man ain't guilty.
I don't wanna work on a rape case.
This one's with a child.
And a man that's wrongly accused...
...given a life sentence,
without a chance for parole.
Well, if he's innocent,
you'll get him out.
You do know
there are other paralegals in town...
...don't you, Miss Prissy?
None as smart and as cheap,
Mr. Graves.
Well, that's true.
Here's daddy.
- Daddy!
Give me some sugar.
Hey, darling.
Hey, baby.
- I love you, Mama.
- I love you.
Thanks for coming.
Hey, baby.
Baby.
I missed you so much.
I want that candy.
No, no, no. Share.
You got to share, now.
Why Papa didn't come?
He wasn't feeling up to it today.
He said I should give you a kiss
for him.
Just losing strength, Calvin.
Just losing strength.
Willis.
Move away from her.
That's my wife, man.
I don't care if it's your dying mama.
You keep your distance,
or the visit is over.
You can't tell me
I can't touch my own husband.
Visit's over.
Escort these folks out of here.
Come on, man.
What are you talking about?
I just got here.
You don't have the right to keep me
from seeing my own husband.
- Michelle.
- Get off of me.
It's all right, baby. They in a rush.
Hi, this us. Leave a message.
Prissy, please pick up. It's Margie.
Something happened
down at the lak e today.
Graves and I were on the boat.
I can't believe
y'all took the boat out anyway.
I thought Graves was like a cat,
didn't wanna get his hair wet.
He's dead. He's dead, Prissy.
Lightning, and he got struck down.
And he's dead.
Is this for real?
Yes.
- The storm. The storm...
- Oh, my God.
...and lightning struck him.
- Mama?
- Oh, that's awful.
I don't know what to do.
I don't know.
Hey, Prissy.
Hey, Reynolds.
I can't tell you how sorry I am
about Graves Thomas.
I don't know how many times
I heard the man say:
"If I am lying,
may I be struck by lightning...
...by the Lord Almighty."
Must have been one big-ass lie
he told on that boat.
Well, he sure thought the world
of you.
Always boasted you could out-brief
any attorney in town.
You know, Prissy...
...I could use a top-shelf paralegal
in my office.
The job's yours if you want it.
I might have to take you up on that.
You're?
You wanna come in with me?
No, this is as close as I wanna get
to another coffin.
When you get ready to go back
to work, you come by my office.
Thank you.
I might need a day or so.
Okay.
Look.
Hey, who are you?
What you doing here?
- Well...
- Keisha.
Child, haven't I told you
a thousand times...
...any talking to strangers need doing,
you come get Granny?
Are you Calvin Willis' grandmother?
Whatever you have to say
about my Calvin...
...I hope you don't say it
in front of his children.
I'm Prissy Gregory.
I'm from Graves Thomas' office.
Oh, you Mr. Thomas' girl.
He told us all about you.
Told us about
how you was playing with a gun...
...and shot yourself in the leg.
Boy, that story made
a great impression on my grand.
Now, y'all run on over there
to play now.
Your mama be on directly.
Come on in.
I can't say as I understand
why God take him that way.
Lord know more than me.
- Afternoon, Mama.
- Michelle.
- How you feeling, Papa?
- I'm okay.
This here is Prissy Gregory.
- She works with Mr. Thomas.
- Hi. Hi.
Michelle is Calvin's wife.
She's just like my own daughter.
Prissy just told us
that Mr. Thomas passed last week.
I brought Calvin's case file.
I know Mr. Thomas was only on this
a few months...
...but he'd gone through
your retainer.
Unfortunately, I don't know of a lawyer
who would do the case pro bono.
I'll take care of it.
Child, please,
how you gonna take care of it?
All right, now, Mama, you
got enough on your plate already.
Thank you for coming.
Hey. You shouldn't have come here.
You should've called me.
I thought it was Mr. And Ms. Newton
who hired Graves.
They was. They gave him
every cent they had.
Now all they got
is heartache and worries.
That woman in there raised Calvin.
More of a mother
than the one that left him.
His granddad,
you see him eaten away with cancer.
And you come here carrying this
burden they can't do nothing about?
Shame on you.
I was just doing my job,
and I didn't know.
No, I don't suppose you did.
Don't suppose you got any idea
what it's like...
...to have the one you love most
taken from you for no reason at all.
Keisha, Booji, come on,
it's time to go home.
Hey, listen, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
Why don't you give me the file back?
And I'll do what I can
to get you a good lawyer.
Fine. I won't hold my breath.
No, don't.
If I do find you one,
you need to be ready...
...to go through everything
about this case all over again.
Would you tell your boss...
...Graves Thomas
left him a little something in his will?
No, but if I tell him
it's a pro-bono case...
...he won't call me back, will he?
Okay.
- Hello?
- I'm here to see Graves Thomas.
Oh, I'm sorry.
I thought I'd cancelled all...
No, I told him not to write it down.
Look, if he's not here,
it's fine by me.
No, wait a minute. Who are you?
- Loretta Brooks.
- The detective on the Willis case?
You know, I am so tired of having to
defend that damn police photo line-up.
Just because I didn't know
to keep a record...
...of how it was assembled,
doesn't mean it wasn't legit.
It's not like I put pictures of white guys
in there. They were all black.
That girl pointed at Willis, all right?
I don't know
what you're talking about.
Graves won't be working
on the Willis case.
Then what the hell am I doing here?
Hi. Are you Jo Anne Johnson?
Reggie send you down here?
Lady, I ain't got his money.
No, no, no,
I'm not here about money.
I wanted to ask you
about your daughter Lucretia.
What business you got
asking about her?
- Can I come in?
- No, Lucretia don't live here no more.
- She lives with your sister in Ohio?
- How you know that? You police?
No, I'm a paralegal.
And I'm just helping out on the case.
I've been reading
the trial transcripts.
There are things
that I don't understand.
Like how come you identified
Calvin Willis...
...as your daughter's attacker...
...when you weren't actually home
that night?
- I ain't got time for this.
- No, please.
I just need to know, why did
you give the detective Calvin's name...
...before she started investigating?
Because Chante saw his car
parked outside my house.
Right, but did Lucretia
know Calvin too?
She picked his picture
out of a photo line-up.
But she couldn't identify him
in court, right?
Now, I understand that Lucretia
was a special-education child.
And that means
that she couldn't qualify as a witness...
...to give testimony in court.
When your baby girl look at you...
...her face swollen up, bleeding,
half her teeth gone...
...and point to a man...
...you believe her.
Hey. Listen,
I still haven't found you a lawyer yet.
I had hoped
that I could help you myself.
But this case, it's just like...
It's riddled with holes.
It's just that...
I'm just really not the right person.
What happened?
Papa died.
Calvin.
- Daddy, Daddy.
- Hi, Booji.
- Mama.
- Baby.
This is Miss Prissy.
She made it
so you could be here today.
Hey.
What you go and do that for?
Calvin.
Who are you to me or my papa?
This ain't the day
for you to forget your manners.
You thank this woman.
It's okay, it's okay. I did it for you.
And you've thanked me plenty.
I'm gonna leave you all
to your family and friends.
Okay?
Goodbye.
Look here, boy.
I will not allow your papa's body
to be laid to rest...
...till you show some respect
to Miss Prissy.
We'll be waiting right here on you.
Mama, you know Calvin.
Hey. Miss Prissy, hold up, now.
I'm...
I'm sorry for disrespecting you.
Mama said you used to be
Mr. Graves' secretary or something.
You helping out on my case now?
Maybe.
If I can convince a lawyer
that you're innocent.
What you mean, "if"?
Woman, I don't need your charity.
Why don't you take your white ass
back to where you came from?
I will.
Shut up.
What are you...?
What's this for?
"Sorry"?
You been acting mad at me
since Papa's funeral.
I ain't mad at you.
You need to talk to your mama.
Yeah, she mad at you because you
weren't nice to that white lady she like.
Your ears is way too big.
What I got to be nice to her for?
She the one acting high and mighty.
Ain't even a real lawyer.
Like you got lawyers
waiting in line to help you.
Granny said Miss Prissy
know the law real good.
That's right, she smart?
She got you out of here
for Papa's funeral, didn't she?
Send that card to her, then.
Tell her I had no call
treating her like that.
Tell her how
I ain't got no sense sometime.
Ryan?
What kind of soup you want
with your sandwich?
Tomato or chicken noodle?
Earth to Ryan.
You in a chicken noodle
kind of mood?
Mama, what does rape mean?
Does it mean all beat up?
I told you never to open
Mama's files.
I didn't. I found it on the ground.
I was trying to put it back.
What else did you see?
Nothing.
Is this the man that hurt that girl?
Mr. Graves was sure he didn't.
He got put in jail for it?
Why, if he didn't do it?
So you yourself tested
the boxer shorts found at the scene?
The boxer shorts
encrusted with semen.
- The size 44 boxer shorts.
- Yes.
Yes, I performed the test myself.
And did you know that Calvin Willis
at the time had a size 36-inch waist?
I believe they told me.
How'd you get downstairs here?
Told them I was hungry.
So you did know.
How could you testify
for the district attorney...
...that Willis was the guilty party?
Because the semen on the shorts
came from a type O secretor.
Calvin Willis is a type O secretor.
Silly me. Thanks.
What percentage of the black
population are type O secretors?
Basically 40 percent. Excuse me.
Well, that's a lot of black men.
Let me get this straight.
Forty percent of all black men
are type O secretors.
So you decided that Calvin Willis was
the only one who could've left semen...
...on a pair of boxers
that were 8 inches too big for him?
I don't know how you sleep at night.
You know, if I recall...
...there were witnesses
who placed him at the scene.
There was a witness.
She saw his car.
You know, I don't remember.
Go ask her.
- Go ask her.
- I will.
How could you be so sure...
...the car you saw the night Lucretia
was raped was Calvin's car?
You never did see a man
so vain about his car as Calvin Willis.
Always riding around
like he better than everybody else.
Hey, Calvin.
Check out Luther over there.
He the man.
Yo, Luther.
Luther.
Yeah.
You getting desperate
in your old age, man.
What you talking about, fool?
Running with a ho like Chante.
Look out.
Who you calling a ho?
You the biggest ho around here.
I can't even believe you fixed
your mouth to call me no ho.
You need... Get on out of here!
Get the hell off my property,
okay, creep!
Put me down, worthless!
Just standing there.
How you gonna let him
call me a ho?
You know what?
You can kiss my ass!
You sorry sucker!
Just gonna talk to me?
Hell, I'd have thrown
a rock at him too.
Fact is,
I wouldn't blame you if you set him up.
Told the police
you saw Calvin's car...
...at a time his wife swore
he was at home with her.
That skinny-ass wife of his...
...been putting up
with his tomcatting for years.
Wasn't no surprise to me
she made up that story.
Too bad for her it didn't work.
Calvin say they about to move him
down south to some max prison.
Say it like it ain't no big thing.
That's an 8-hour drive from here.
Michelle,
I need to ask you something.
Did you make up that alibi
for Calvin?
I'm not asking
if you think he did it or not.
I'm asking if you lied about him
being home by midnight.
Or maybe it's not even a case
of lying.
Just pretending you were sure
when you weren't.
I was not happy
with Calvin going out that night.
Calvin was always going out.
So I told him...
...you not home by 12:00,
I'm gonna lock your ass out.
So I was sitting...
...looking at that clock.
Calvin being Calvin...
...he got back here.
But not even five minutes to spare.
Judge Pifer,
I wanted to talk to you...
...about a client of Graves,
Calvin Willis.
Can't say that name rings a bell.
It was about five years ago,
1981, child rape.
The original defence attorney thought
that the evidence was so flimsy...
...he waived the right to a jury trial,
asked you to rule.
That's way too much water
under the bridge.
Let me get that for you.
Do you remember that you
allowed an evidence testimony...
...of a photo line-up
there was no real record of?
Or that the defendant had an alibi...
...or that the victim
couldn't identify him in court?
You're wasting my time.
Your Honour, I...
I know and understand
how this system works.
I know how an inexperienced detective
could botch an investigation.
I know how the DA has to prosecute
cases on low evidence...
...because basically
he's working an assembly line.
But what I don't know is what was it
that let you go along with it.
I am not God.
I don't pretend to be.
I do my job as I see fit.
You don't like the results,
you go complain to the appellate court.
Because I don't give a damn.
Excuse me.
There's a child rapist on the loose.
And this innocent man, Calvin Willis,
is doing life imprisonment.
Hey, don't let me persuade you
to give a damn.
Hope I didn't make you late
for your golf.
This is a post-conviction application.
I need your signature.
And I'll find a warm body
with a law degree.
He can sign it and I'll file it.
Why you doing this
if you don't like me?
- What I don't like is your attitude.
- I'm supposed to act different?
I'd be surprised
if you didn't behave badly.
It doesn't mean I have to like it.
I just wanna know why you doing it.
Because this case
reeks of injustice.
Maybe it's because I wanna show
my son that the truth matters.
My grandmother says you came
into our lives because of God's will.
Now, are you gonna disappoint
a faith like that?
I'll work on my attitude.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
I think.
Hey, look, you just handle it,
all right?
That's more like it. All right.
Looky, looky.
If it ain't the new brother.
You ain't too much for socializing,
is you?
You brain-dead or something, man?
That's why you don't talk?
I need to make my call.
It speaks.
So, what crime put you in here?
Brother, you writing a book?
Better watch
who you're getting big with, brother.
We'll rap later.
- Let him know who run things, Matthew.
- Yeah, Big M.
Move, guys. Back.
You know how to get off your head?
So, what's your next move?
You still filing that writ?
Yeah, just need to get it signed.
Got it right here in front of me.
It's a pretty little thing,
if I do say so myself.
Sounds good.
Hey, how you get him
to replace my ID that got stolen?
You talk ed to the warden?
No, not him. His right-hand man.
What'd you do?
Make promises you can't keep?
None of your damn business
what promises I make.
And how do you know
I can't keep them?
I ain't laughed in a long time.
It feels good.
Calvin Willis?
I told you I don't want you
working on this on my time.
Don't snap.
I worked on that writ at home.
All I want is your signature.
- I signed a post-conviction application.
- It was denied.
Your list of reversible errors was
compelling. On what grounds?
Judge denied it per curiam.
Because-l-said-so response, huh?
My favourite.
- You've put a lot of work in on this.
- Are you gonna sign it?
Or do I take the afternoon off
and harass some other attorney?
I'll sign it, you tell me
why you're devoting yourself to this...
...like a nun to the Church?
You're a defence attorney.
I don't know how you can ask.
You got a thing for this guy?
No, why?
You upset I don't have one for you?
I was just kidding.
Thank you.
That's a lovely wedding ring.
Was it expensive?
You know, Graves never told me
you were such a pain in the ass.
That's because Graves
was a true Southern gentleman.
Put some shoes on.
This is Louisiana State Prison
operator.
I have a collect call
from a Calvin Willis.
- Do you accept the charges?
- Yes, I'll accept.
- How's my baby doing?
- I don't know.
Tired, I guess.
I worked long hours this week.
Ain't nobody remember nothing.
So how's my kids doing?
They okay.
Act up sometimes.
You tell them their father said
they best mind their mama.
I been thinking about you
so much, baby.
Been thinking about them nights
after we put Keisha to bed.
We'd go into the living room.
I got turned down
for a house loan today.
A house loan?
What you doing trying to get a house?
We can't stay here no more, Calvin.
Everything's broke.
Just getting the kids
from the house to the car scares me.
We can't own no house.
Who you know own a house?
- I work.
- Name somebody you know...
...own their own house.
- I got good credit.
But today the bank said
they can't give that kind of money...
...to a woman
who has a husband in prison.
Because the husband is entitled
to half ownership.
And you...
Convicts is considered high risk.
Convict?
- That's how they see me?
- That is how everybody see you.
But you know what's true.
I don't see why you gotta yell.
This the first time I yelled at you.
Most wives get a chance
to yell at their husband.
I don't even get that.
I can't do this. I can't.
I can't do this no more.
I can't do this no more, Calvin.
I just can't.
I'm sorry.
Michelle.
That's enough.
Move it, all of you.
I think she trying to make herself
fall out of love with me.
I know she thinking about
every bad word I done called her.
Every time
I got with another woman.
Be better off for her if I was dead
and she'd just grieve and move on.
You're wrong.
I've buried two husbands.
You don't just get to move on.
Their ghosts follow you around.
She gonna leave me
to sit up in here alone...
...so she can buy a damn house.
Think you're the only one who got
a life sentence out of this relationship?
No, you're right.
Why would she want
a decent house?
Why can't she just spend
the rest of her life in that dump...
...she and your children are in?
You saying
I ain't got no right to be hurt?
Oh, of course you've got the right.
Now go on.
Moan and bitch all you want.
And I'll keep my smart-ass comments
to myself.
Go on, you must got more
to complain about.
Maybe I don't want to no more.
I see a man ain't got no business
coming to you for sympathy.
Nothing but a heart of stone.
Jeez.
If you're good, I'd like to talk business
before my eight-hour trip home.
Take a gander at this brief
that's headed to the state.
Last time you were bitching
and moaning about some little detail...
...that you wanted me to rewrite
the whole thing over...
...so I went home, did that.
Hey, shut your mouth, man.
I'm trying to sleep.
Yeah, wait till I see
you in the yard, boy.
- I'll knock you out.
- You got nothing.
Mama, go to bed.
It's late.
I'm just gonna...
Our house don't make no noise.
It's just silence.
The word says to let your light
shine within me...
...that they may see your good deeds
and praise your Father in heaven.
You gotta let your light shine.
Whereas nobody will know
who you are...
...and nobody will know
who you represent.
Our Lord Jesus says,
"I am the light of the world.
Whoever follows me
will never want to die...
...but will have the light of life."
Listen here.
What you doing?
Are you sad?
May I please spend the night
at Trevor's?
No. You're grounded.
Well, how about I file an appeal?
File your appeal.
I won't curse again...
...and I'll do an extra hour of yard work
next Saturday.
Make it two.
- Fine.
Appeal granted. Go to Trevor's.
Can you ask his mom
if you can stay tomorrow night as well?
I've gotta drive down to the prison.
I have a baseball game tomorrow.
I'm sorry, I'm gonna have to
miss this one.
It's not like you don't have
18 more coming up.
Not 18, three,
and the season's over.
Well, you're gonna have to
fire me as your mom.
Sounds good to me.
- I'm going to your game, all right?
- I don't care.
Well, I don't care if you care.
I'm going.
So, what you're saying is
federal court denied me again?
Oh, Calvin, I'm sorry.
It's been denied per curiam.
You know, I hear myself thinking...
...that I can't take
one more day in here.
Then I realise it's a whole year later
than what I thought it was.
You know Michelle
filed for div orce?
Oh, Calvin, I'm...
I gave it to her.
When I ask you to file a request
for initial police reports...
...I did not say,
"Oh, and add Calvin Willis to the list."
Is this the police report
for Lucretia's rape?
You know, you're not hearing me.
I'm tired of stumbling over
Calvin Willis every time I turn.
So no more phone calls
to that prison...
...and no more using this office
to further your little obsession.
Understood?
You can go in now.
He's back from lunch.
Come on in. Have a seat.
I'm sorry to keep you waiting.
Just running a little behind
here today.
You remember Lucretia
told the police...
...the man who raped her
was wearing a cowboy hat?
But Calvin told them at his trial,
he don't wear no cowboy hat.
He had had a haircut.
And he wasn't gonna cover up
that $65 haircut. No, no, no.
It says here one of Lucretia's
girlfriends said that a big guy, Harry...
...wearing a cowboy hat showed up
at Lucretia's house earlier that day.
Harry?
They didn't mention no Harry
at Calvin's trial.
I didn't hear nothing about no Harry.
Well, because Calvin's defence
never even knew about this.
Before this new law passed...
...the defence never even got to see
the initial police report.
But now we have this. This is proof that
the district attorney, Heinz Harris...
...withheld exculpatory evidence.
That's evidence
favourable to the defendant.
Which means we can ask
for a certificate of probable cause.
Probable cause, is that good?
We can appeal again.
Can I get a "hell, yeah"?
We'll be back!
Here's to the Fifth Circuit
Court of Appeals.
Okay.
Randy?
- Randy Arthur?
- Prissy Gregory.
Look at you. I haven't seen you
since you were in high school.
- Was that you?
- That was me, that was me.
You still got that
cute green cheerleader outfit?
What? You were not a cheerleader.
- Oh, yeah, she was a cheerleader.
- You are so dead.
So you still dating that guy
with the long blond hair?
What's his name? Svein?
His name wasn't Svein. It was Chris.
No, I'm not seeing him.
I haven't seen anyone in a long time.
How about you?
Me? I just got out of
a very intense relationship.
Anyone I know?
Sure, most people know her
as Southern Comfort...
...but I just call her Life-Ruining Bitch.
Sorry, I guess I'm in a bitter stage
of that breakup.
I guess this is the last sip
I'm having of this, then.
You know, that just makes me
wanna ask you out right now.
But I guess I'd better not.
I'm on a liver-transplant list.
You always were funny.
You don't look yellow.
Are you serious?
Oh, shoot. You don't know how much
that tempts a girl like me.
I have a special talent for tangling up
with men on the verge of dying.
I have no plans to die, girl.
- I got too many things I wanna do.
- Like?
Well, like write a hit album.
Maybe two.
Jumping out of an airplane.
Having sex in that airplane,
maybe with a cheerleader.
No, I wouldn't mind at all.
- I'll see you in court on Thursday.
- That sounds good.
All right.
You think I'm lick ed.
Well, I'm not lick ed.
And I'm gonna stay right here
and fight for this lost cause...
...even if this room gets filled
with lies lik e these.
Okay, Tina will be here by 5.
Come on, stand up. Give me a hug.
Hey.
Well, what, you don't wanna give
your mama a hug goodbye?
Just so you know,
this is my last trip down to the prison.
The only reason I'm driving there is...
...I need to tell Calvin
face-to-face that I'm quitting.
Because I can't do this anymore.
I can't.
Then you better hit the road.
We ain't got all day.
Get your shirt off.
Hey, bossman, you got any kids?
Like little girls?
Face front. Matthews, shut up.
Hey, I'm just asking, man...
...because I hear your boy Calvin here
likes them real young.
- That's a damn lie.
- Shut up.
Thank you.
I love you.
Don't spend all that money
on that candy machine.
Watch him, you hear?
And don't say nothing.
I appreciate
you taking my kids with you.
You're welcome.
I'd also appreciate it...
...if you didn't say anything to Calvin
about me being married right now.
Don't you think your kids will tell him?
They promised they wouldn't.
- Damn, they're big.
- Your face'll break out.
I want you to get either the Nabs
or get some peanuts. Now which one?
When I get out of here,
I'm gonna sit on their heads...
...make them stop growing.
Calvin.
You know, the certificate
of probable cause was our last hope.
People around here are talking about
this inmate in Michigan...
...who was set free
because of something called DNA.
- You heard of that?
- Yeah, yeah, I heard of it.
And I've also heard that
DNA testing is very expensive.
- You wait forever for the results.
- Don't think it's worth a shot?
We don't even know if the district
attorney has preserved the rape kit...
...or the boxer shorts.
I mean, Calvin,
it's been 11, 12 years.
And even if they did, they might not
agree to release it for testing.
- This is one long shot after another.
- Don't mean it ain't worth trying.
Do you even know
what DNA evidence is?
You understand that it's irrefutable?
- You know what that means?
- What are you saying?
Yes or no?
Well, I...
I can understand it. I understand if you
wanna go that route. It's just that...
It's just that I can't. I can't.
I'm sorry.
It's just that I need to
be done with this.
And I need you
to find someone else.
Calvin, my son
is hardly talking to me anymore...
...and my boss
is this close to firing me.
And I'm no use to you...
I'm no use to you
if my life is falling apart.
Please, Calvin, just tell me
that you understand.
Please just let me off the hook.
Wasn't never no hook.
Just me feeling lucky to have someone
willing to look me in the eye...
...willing to tell me what was what.
You best go on now.
Do what you got to do.
Ain't gonna give you no grief, not
after everything you've done for me.
Calvin, why'd you have to
make this so hard on me?
- I'm trying to make it easy.
- Well, you're not, neither of you.
I mean, we don't even know
if the district attorney still has any...
Anything that you can get
any evidence from.
- Maybe it wasn't such a good idea...
- No, it's okay.
It's all right, it's all right. I'll...
We just... I'm gonna...
I'll try and find you someone else
who can help you with this DNA idea...
...but I'm not promising anything.
Yes, ma'am.
Thank you.
Yeah.
We are adjourned.
- Good job.
- Thank you.
Mr. Harris. Heinz Harris.
I saw you look at me.
You're gonna make me chase you?
I received your letter.
I haven't made a decision.
I sent that letter two months ago.
How long does it take you
to release a kit for testing?
- I'm not even sure we retained that kit.
- You did, I checked.
Are you a glutton for punishment?
You've tried to appeal this case
how many times now?
You know exactly how many times.
Your office challenged it each time.
- That's because Mr. Willis is guilty.
- So prove it, release the kit.
- Lucretia's mother needs to know this.
- What do you mean?
I mean, if you can get her
to sign a statement...
...saying that I can release the kit,
I'll give it to you.
You have a good day.
I ain't signing it.
I know who raped Lucretia:
Calvin Willis.
It was his car. It was him.
This DNA test
will prove it conclusively.
Calvin Willis?
He drive that funky-ass Lincoln?
That was Adela's grandson, Ray.
- What kind of car he drive?
- Ragtop Caddy.
Chante saw it that night,
clear as day.
I got no use for someone trying to set
him free after what he did to my baby.
Why would I wanna set him free
for no reason?
This test will tell you 100 percent
for sure if he's the one.
- Police told me they got the right one.
- What, you always believe them?
Why you trying to take this away?
You heard the woman. Now go on.
Jo Anne, I have lived for eight years
now with Lucretia's photos.
Poor baby's face swollen,
her teeth...
- That's enough of that.
- Don't you touch me.
I know you wanna be completely sure
you get that monster who did it to her.
Look, lady, you can either walk out
or get tossed out.
It's all good to me.
All right, I'm sorry.
I'm gonna leave it here
and I just want you to think about it.
If for no other reason...
...your baby can know that her mama
put away the right man.
Wait.
That's the problem.
I can't get anyone to quote me
less than $6000 for a DNA test.
I thought you applied to that...
What do you call that?
That Barry Scheck deal.
The Innocence Project.
They get hundreds and hundreds
of applications...
...so the odds are really against us.
And even if they do take the case,
what they do is handle the legal work.
I still have to raise the money
for the test.
So raise the money.
Do I look like someone who can
make money rain from the sky?
I hear you've been working
with God.
No, God is working through me
according to the gospel of Ms. Newton.
Randy, I'm kind of tired.
I don't really...
Come on, I can sing if I want.
No, it's not about your singing.
I love your singing.
I just don't really...
- Baby?
- Oh, come on, baby.
Randy, stop.
I just don't wanna... l...
Randy.
Don't hold me! Don't pin me down!
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, I just...
I don't like being held down.
- Okay, I'm sorry.
- No, it's okay.
- You hungry?
- Yeah.
We got any of those
barbecue chips left?
You're getting fouled, man.
- Come on, man.
- Line up. Line up.
Good game, good game.
We'll go again? We gonna go again?
You all right? You all right?
All right, let's go.
Back up. Get off! Get off!
Get off him!
- Break it up.
- Get back. Get on back.
The guards can't protect you
if you don't name names.
The guards know
I'm accused of raping a child.
- They ain't gonna protect me.
- Those guys broke your ribs.
If you don't name names,
they could do it again.
- They will do it again.
- I wish you'd let me talk to somebody.
I've been trying to call
Michelle and the kids.
She won't take my calls no more.
- She got another man?
- I think you should ask her that.
You ain't got to pussyfoot like that.
I ain't no child.
- Tell me.
- Okay, yes, she's got a man.
That's good.
It's real good.
She got herself someone to love
just like you got yourself someone.
As long as you bitches is
getting some, that's all that matters.
That why you ain't got
my DNA test yet?
- Busy spreading your legs?
- That's enough.
Tell me you was in that mood,
I could've scratched that itch.
- What's wrong with you?
- Not a damn thing wrong.
If you let me get under this table...
...I guarantee you'd be wrapping your
legs around my neck like an octopus.
I'd tell you to go to hell...
...only, lucky for me,
you're already there.
It's gotta be Calvin.
Then don't answer it.
He's written you
a dozen letters of apology.
How long you gonna let him
twist in the wind?
I know he blew off a lot of steam
in the wrong way...
- Are you defending him, Randy?
- No, I'm with you on that.
But look what
he's been going through.
Are you saying I don't know
what he's been through?
So you want another number?
No.
Can you try that one again, please?
I'm not really mad at him anymore.
I just need a break from him.
I'm tired.
- And you're also an amazing woman.
- No.
Will you marry me?
- It's a simple yes-or-no question.
- There's nothing simple about that.
I love you, you love me.
I love Ryan, he loves me.
What's complicated?
You're still on the transplant list.
- I'm not gonna die on you, Prissy.
- Lf I marry you, you might.
I'm not gonna marry you, Randy.
Listen to me, darling.
I'm no angel.
I spent half my life drunk,
hurt all kinds of people.
If I do die, it's because
of my own curse, not yours.
So I'm gonna ask you again.
Oh, God.
Now, look at me.
Look at me, look at me.
- No, I don't wanna look.
- Look at me.
Look at me. Come on, come on.
Janet "Prissy" Gregory...
...will you marry me?
Oh, my God.
I do. I mean, yes, I will accept.
Hi, this is Vicki Tanner
with the Innocence Project.
I'm looking for Janet Gregory.
This is her. I'm sorry,
who did you say you're from?
The Innocence Project.
We've accepted your application
for Calvin Willis and l...
My God, they've just accepted
Calvin's application. I can't believe it.
- What a day.
- Oh, my God.
What's wrong?
Nothing, it's all great.
I just got a call from the l...
Hello? I'm so sorry, I'm so sorry.
Yeah, it's wonderful.
So how can I help?
The Innocence Project.
They said yes.
Reverend, thank you so much
for having folk stay after service.
Miss Prissy here been working
herself thin for two years...
...trying to raise enough money
to get my boy's DNA test.
They now need $12,000 because
the evidence is so old, it's hard to test.
I have literally tapped every person
I know, and I'm still short about 1500.
And she said to me,
"Don't worry none."
But I said, " It's my Calvin,
and I have to worry too."
Ms. Newton was saying that your
church might sponsor a fundraiser.
A rummage sale, a bake sale.
- That'd be good.
- Yeah.
It is such a shame about
your grandson, Sister Neralvil, but...
...well, I just don't see how
that's a concern for the church.
What?
I'm sorry,
wasn't Calvin baptised here?
Sure was. He was 11 years old.
Yes, yes.
Well, that was a long time ago.
The fact is, there aren't many here
who even remember Calvin.
Does anybody here
remember Calvin Willis?
As a boy,
he came to this church every Sunday.
He was taken from his home...
...and thrown in prison
for over 14 years now...
...for a crime he did not commit.
Are y'all saying
you don't remember Calvin Willis?
Ms. Newton,
is this the right church?
This is the right church.
Sorry. I think I'm gonna wait
for you in the car.
Lord, Neralvil, where did you find
that crazy white woman?
She ain't crazy.
If y'all knew what that woman
had done for me and mine...
She's standing here doing
the Lord's work on this holy day...
...calling on your conscience.
Now I wanna know,
did you hear or didn't you?
No, I suppose you didn't.
Black folk get deaf...
...when one of their own
get in trouble.
Lord, have mercy.
Ryan, I thought you said
you were gonna clean up.
Ryan. You said
Randy said
he wanted to show me something.
What you thinking? Your dad's
weaker than a 2-day-old kitten.
But not for long. You forget I'm now
number two on the transplant list.
Yeah.
You were number three
for about five months.
Come on, get your big yellow ass
back on that couch.
Dad.
What you got, man?
You gotta have something.
Hold on, let me holler at this
white lady real quick. Hold on.
Hey, Miss Lady.
Miss Woman-on-a-Mission.
I forgot your name.
That's okay. I forgot yours too.
Shelton.
But if it's all the same to you...
...l'd rather you forget it
after I tell you what I got to tell you.
Fine. Whatever floats your boat.
So about a week ago...
...I run into this brother just got back
in town named Luther.
So, you know, we chilling.
We drinking it up real good, smoking,
you know what I'm saying?
I say to him,
"Remember Calvin Willis?
The one that got popped
for raping that 11 -year-old girl?"
His drunk ass just start laughing...
...talking about, "Them fool police
ain't ever figure out he ain't do it."
I'm like,
"How you know he ain't do it?"
He just smile like Satan.
Start doing like this here:
But you ain't heard it from me.
So do you know this Luther guy?
Yeah, I know him.
Didn't hang with him, though.
Used to pay Chante for trim.
What'd he look like?
Big, ugly.
Hairy-ass beard.
- What did you just say?
- I said, he was big...
...he was ugly
and he had a hairy-ass beard.
When Lucretia's friend said "hairy,"
could she have meant "hairy face"?
He was a big talker. Said he robbed
liquor stores he ain't never set foot in.
I spoke to a couple of detectives
about Luther.
As far as they're concerned,
the case is closed.
But I was thinking,
if I can find him...
...maybe I can get some of his DNA
off a fork or something.
What is going on with you?
Are you pissed at me?
This cat came in here the other day
to visit another inmate.
Said he knew me back in the day,
and Michelle.
Said she not only got herself
a husband, but a baby girl.
If that were true,
somebody would've told me by now.
One of my kids, Mama,
certainly you.
You wouldn't lie to me
about something like that?
- Calvin, let's not go there again.
- No.
It is not my place to tell...
Wasn't your place?
What kind of answer is that?
Everybody got their place.
Mine's in here with nothing.
No, that's not true.
You've got your two kids.
- And when you get your freedom...
- My what? My freedom?
Does setting a coloured boy free...
...somehow make you feel
like a better person?
Don't matter if you've been lying
to him the whole damn time.
I don't wanna see you no more.
I don't need your help.
And I certainly don't trust you...
...bitch.
How could you do me like that?!
Play me for a damn fool.
You got them to lie to me,
Prissy, my kids, Mama?
- Calvin, l... I just...
- How could you do that?
It's because I still care about you.
What I mean, I just didn't
want you to hurt no more.
You don't know about hurt.
First you give a man my place
in your heart, my place in your bed.
Now you give him my place
as a father? They're my damn kids!
I did not cause you to go to prison.
This is not all my fault.
This part sure as hell is!
My life ain't worth a damn now
because of what you've done to me!
What's the matter, man?
Did your girlfriend lose
her Barbie doll at daycare?
Willis!
- Let go of me! Let go! Let go!
- Get off him, Willis.
- Get off him!
- Hold him down! Hold him down.
Willis!
- Goddamn. Hold him down!
- Stay down, Willis.
Stay down!
Stay down. Stay down, Willis.
You seriously still
going through with this?
Yeah.
I just talked with Tina at the diner...
...and she won't let anyone
bus the table...
...so I just have to get
the beer mug...
...or whatever else this Luther guy
puts his mouth on.
What are you doing?
I'm going. I'm gonna
get a table close by...
- No way.
...and watch you.
- Not happening.
- So he doesn't try anything.
I may not be able to do
a lot of things, darling...
...but I can still protect my wife.
I'm going.
Aren't you gonna drink your beer?
No, I was waiting on
some dead presidents.
And I thought you forgot.
So, what you wanna talk about?
Calvin Willis.
Poor Calvin.
The famous rapist
of Pan Street, huh?
Why him?
I'm trying to prove he's innocent.
So are you his lawyer or something?
No, Luther.
I just heard you were a friend of his.
Yeah. Yeah, I knew you was
too fine to be a lawyer.
- You fine as a...
- So you don't believe he's innocent?
Well, I mean, that all depends on what
you call innocent, now, doesn't it?
He don't deserve what he got,
that's for damn sure.
I mean, after all, God made women
to be good to their men.
It's biblical, as far as I'm concerned.
Ain't no such thing as rape.
What'd you say?
Oh, girl, come on now.
It's written right there in the Bible.
It says that God
put women on this earth...
...to be a vessel for their man.
And that's...
That's all women, baby...
...no matter their age or colour.
Take your hands off me,
you son of a bitch!
- Go on, get out or I'll rip off your head!
- You crazy...
Go on, get out of here!
I'll kill you! I'll see you again!
Get off me, Randy.
God. Well, I think
that went really well.
- What the hell was that?
- He was scum.
You didn't... You screwed up.
You didn't get his DNA.
Thank you.
You couldn't hear what he was saying.
You'll never have a chance
like this again, girl.
- Why didn't you tell me?
- Tell you what?
That you were raped.
You think because I overreacted
to that skanky-ass son of a b...
You more than overreacted.
You've been working on this for years.
You also overreacted
when I held you down that time.
Give me the keys, Randy.
I wanna go home.
Did you think I would judge you
or love you less?
I judged me. I thought I deserved it.
How old were you?
Old enough to know better
than to go off with some redneck...
...just because he's good-looking.
Nineteen.
He told me that he was gonna
take me to a concert and he didn't.
He took me off to his trailer
in the woods instead.
To be perfectly honest,
I didn't think about it.
I just went in.
And then he got me
liquored up real good...
...and before you know it,
he's holding me down and...
I had a choice: Get my head blown off
or go along with it.
- He had a gun?
- Yes, he had a gun.
After he'd done everything he could
to me, you know what he said?
"Well, Prissy,
you were asking for it...
...from the minute you came in,
weren't you?"
I thought, "Damn if he ain't right."
He wasn't right...
...and you know that.
You did not deserve
what he did to you.
Thank you for coming.
I sure do appreciate
you carrying me down here.
Oh, you're welcome.
I know you should be home
with your husband after his surgery.
Oh, him and his new liver
are getting on fine.
You know men. If I treat him
like an invalid, he'll sure act like one.
- He's fine.
- That's what I prayed for.
Because if God wanted him,
he sure would take him.
Like using his lightning on Graves?
Yes, ma'am. Now, that's right.
I wanna get out down there.
Can you drive down
just a little further?
Okay, sure.
Pull around over there.
Hey.
- Look over there.
- Oh, my God.
You see how the Lord do?
You did that?
I don't belie...
Everyone should have
a mother like that.
You know, she took me
to a surprise fundraiser.
She rallied the whole church
and she raised the rest of the money.
Well, high-five on that.
What's this?
Oh, it's a new tune
I've been working on.
Now, you're feeling better.
Take your pills?
Are you gonna be my mama...
...or are you gonna crawl under here
and be my wife?
You'll be popping your stitches.
Sorry.
It's feeling better?
You sure scared the crap out of me.
Oh, I know. But we got through it.
Now you gotta get on
with important things.
There's nothing
more important than you.
- And Ryan and Calvin.
- And Ryan.
- Are you playing with me?
- I'm fixing to.
I sure do love you, Miss Prissy.
Adela's "my sweet Lord" cookies.
I had them when I was knee-high.
Oh, she had a line at her table.
She said she's gonna make you
a batch for when you're out of there.
- She said that?
- Yeah, she did.
So I'm gonna get
a cashier's cheque tomorrow...
...and send it to the lab
for the rest of the test.
I also spok e with the woman
from the Innocence Project.
- Vicki?
- She's gonna follow up once a week.
Oh, praise God.
You said Reverend Hollis,
he remembered me?
A lot of people
remember you, Calvin.
A lot.
Sorry.
I hate waking you up too.
You want me to
make you breakfast before...?
Mama?
Mama, what's wrong?
Hey, sign here and here...
...and here.
What are you doing here?
My job.
You just buried your husband
two days ago.
I'm well aware of that, Calvin...
...but we still have to file
our notice of intent...
...with the DA
before the end of the month.
- Come on.
- It can wait.
- Randy would've wanted you to...
- Do me a favour.
Do not tell me what
a dead husband number three...
...would or wouldn't have wanted.
You need to take some time
grieving for yourself.
This is me grieving.
I just make it look easy
because I've had lots of practise.
I know how bad it got to hurt.
Let go of me, Calvin. Come on.
You feel hard...
...like you're made of stone.
Your whole body
must be sore from it.
Deep down inside,
you feel fiery hot.
Hot with all that injustice
burning inside you.
It's all right, let it burn on through.
I can't. Calvin, I can't.
- Yes, you can.
- No, I can't.
Come on, talk to me.
You taken my pain, Prissy. You've
been there for me a thousand times.
Go on and give me yours.
- Stop.
- Come on.
I don't get to fall apart.
I got a son and I've at least
gotta try and be there for him.
Sometimes I'm feeling nothing
and then I feel angry.
And I'm just... I'm just so angry.
I'm just angry.
- I'm just so angry.
- That's all right. That's all right.
I'm just mad.
I let him in and I let Ryan down.
- It's okay.
- I have Ryan...
And he's not here.
Oh, Calvin.
It's all right.
I'm back.
That's a very long half-hour.
You got a message on your desk.
Vicki Tanner
from the Innocence Project.
Something about
DNA results being in.
I'm leaving again.
Oh, come on.
What time is it now?
It's seven minutes later
than the last time.
Maybe there's a problem.
- We were getting worried.
- I'm sorry I'm late.
I got lost.
I was told to take Interstate 10
to the 55, and that put me back...
- Vicki, give him the letter.
- Right.
- Here are your results.
- You didn't open it?
No, I just stuffed them in my bag
and hopped in the car.
- No.
- We already know what it says, right?
You seem a mite nervous.
Well, aren't you?
You forget I know
what I was doing that night.
It says they tested the DNA...
...in the fingernail scrapings
and the boxer shorts...
...and compared it to Calvin's DNA,
and there was no match.
There's no match.
No match.
Praise God.
Thank you, Lord.
My boy walking free.
Walking free.
I got your room
already ready for you.
I just got to make the bed.
- Ms. Newton.
- Mama.
Well, I'm sorry, Ms. Newton,
but you can't take him home just yet.
We have to get a judge who'll agree
to even consider this new evidence.
You telling me
we got proof in our hand...
...and he got to go back to the cell?
I know. It ain't right.
No, it ain't right.
It sure ain't.
- You all right, baby?
- I'm good, Mama.
It's our position, Your Honour...
...that just because Mr. Willis' DNA
could not be identified...
...does not make him
innocent of this crime.
Now, remember, the victim
identified him from a photo...
...and there's eyewitness testimony
placing him at the scene.
Now, we see no reason
to overturn a decision...
...that stood for 20 years
and numerous appeals, Your Honour.
Your Honour, over 75 percent
of wrongful identifications of rape...
...are due to misidentifications
by eyewitnesses.
In my experience in these cases,
the district attorney's office...
...cares more about saving face
than it does finding justice.
Ms. Tanner...
...if I want your opinion
on investigative procedure...
...or Mr. Harris' motives, I'll ask.
I've heard your arguments.
I plan to go over your briefs
one more time...
...give you my ruling
this afternoon at 4.
- We are adjourned.
- All rise.
All right.
You heard the questions.
He may rule against us.
- Not if I have anything to do with it.
- Where are you going?
- I'm gonna have a chat with the judge.
- Do not go into his chambers.
Vicki, you heard the man.
- All of our work...
- He's gonna rule against us.
And I think I have the right,
after all these years...
...to end this on my terms,
or screw it up.
Your Honour...
If you want to speak with me,
make an appointment. I'm busy.
Busy with that load of bull crap
Heinz Harris just shovelled in your face.
Excuse me?
That man wouldn't recognise the truth
if it bit him in the ass twice.
Graves Thomas once told me
that you could be depended on...
...on Tuesdays and every other
Thursday to give a fair ruling.
Will you please listen to me?
I've spent nearly half my life
on this case.
I think the least you could do is
give me one minute of your attention.
It wouldn't matter.
I've already made my decision.
And even though
it's not a Tuesday...
...I just signed the order
releasing Calvin Willis from prison.
You mean, Calvin's getting out?
We don't wanna spoil the surprise...
...for old Heinz now, do we?
No, sir, we don't.
Thank you, Lord. Hallelujah.
Lord, you're just so good.
You're most kind, Lord. Lord Jesus.
You've just been so good.
Thank you, blessed Jesus.
- Thank you!
- Are you getting this?
Thank the Lord.
Thank you.
Oh, I wouldn't wanna step
without you, Lord.
Lord, I thank you. I thank you.
Thank you, Lord.
Your lady friend
brought these for you.
Get dressed.
Hey, Calvin.
Miss Prissy.
All right if I walk out with you?
I'd be honoured.
You ready?
There's a lot of people out there.
Thanks for these.
You know, these white folks' clothes.
Yeah. I thought you wouldn't mind.
I bought the shirt for Randy,
but it's never been worn.
You know...
...I never known nobody like you.
Well, that's because
you've been inside for 20 years.
I just wanna say thank you.
I don't wanna be crying.
I don't wanna cry.
You know, I see
why Randy never wore these.
- It's dry. Ready?
- Yes, ma'am.
Yes, Lord. Yes, Lord.
Thank you, Lord.
It just feels wonderful. Just wonderful.
I've waited a long time.