Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
Edit by Leonardo
Blood Night: The Legend Of Mary Hatchet
Hello darling.
Let me do it for you.
Your grandmother would have smiled at it.
She loved brushing my hair when I was your age '.
And 'You'd better go to sleep now, ok?
My God, Mary! Mary! What 'happened? And What' happened?
Oh God ..
Kings Park Psychiatric Center. Kings Park, NY 1989
Mary ...
Want to come and play?
Want the lollipop of popes cucu caca?
Mary ...
Mary ... want the lollipop of popes cucu caca ... small?
Mary!
I'll give you 'a quick lesson.
That 's what you need ...
The lollipop of popes ... and 'what you need, the lollipop of popes ...
Oh baby ... oh, baby
Oh, Mary do it, damn bitch ...
damn bitch ... damn bitch ...
Mary, you have to push!
You have to push!
Mary Push, push!
- Doctor?
- Sedatela! Sedatela!
I have it ... I keep it!
Presto! - Okay ... Calm down.
Okay, okay ...
You'll be fine Mary.
There were no complications during delivery.
Your child is not 'survived ...
She understands nothing of what is' success.
How did you leave your room, Mary?
Come on, now you reported to us ...
Hands up, now!
Hands up, come on!
Do not shoot us.
Those damn hands up, young lady!
- Hands up!
- Do it, lady.
Hands up, now!
NIGHT OF BLOOD The Legend of Mary Hatchet
Police arrested a 12 year old girl.
The Court considers "Mary Hatchet" unfit for trial.
Allegations of violent crime
The patient 'subject to violent attacks of rage ...
The symptoms of violence increase during menstruation ...
Diagnosis: menstrual dysphoric disorder
Your father and 'a genius. It'.
- Hey guys!
- What 's that?
We have some plans for this night of blood?
Well, we have a party ... and you stay home, right?
You hear these idiots who are wondering where it went Jen.
Dude, what the fuck? Come on guys.
Look, I'm just wondering where. Help.
Sorry brother, but the party and 'only for VIP, the kids are not allowed.
Without kids are peeing in diapers for fear of the festivities. We can not.
Come on guys, there will be at least a dozen parties tonight ...
... I'm sure you'll find something.
Yes, 'but those are not necessary for the balls.
Yes, 'your little balls and virgins.
Now take and get out of here. Strength.
- Nice to see together.
- True.
Your sister is tonight?
He said he would go first to where Daniel was. - Why '?
I do not know, man. Why 'do not you go and ask her?
'Cause you always get in the middle? I have an 'idea ...
'Cause you is not around here so some purposes' does not have to feel more' these things? What do you think?
Asshole.
I'm so 'happy not to hear more' talk. - My penis vegetarian not affect anyone.
Hey buddy, what happened?
Hey, how are you?
Hey, how are the ladies?
I am so 'excited for tonight.
What should I bring?
- Very alcohol.
We should arrive early this evening, I have special plans.
See you 'later we'll be busy.
- Oh my God
- Use protection!
Happy "Night of Blood"!
Night of blood!
Excuse me, kind sir. I think we took the wrong road.
Can 'show us the right way to Eisenhower Park?
- Sure. Keep up to here ...
Yes
- ... Turn left ...
- Left.
- And after two blocks on the right.
- Right. Ok!
- It 's all?
- That's it.
He unlaced his shoes.
- Do You Have?
Yes
Wait, wait ... expected.
Hey, remember this, I forgot the game.
What, man? ... the game?
- The game? What are you talking about?
- Let's play turn up the graves.
Girls like wrong, right?
You brought the game? And 'good?
- Walk ... - What? ...
- Wait.
- Do I look like Milton Bradley?
- Yes, you prick.
- Hello, Mary.
- It 's good to see you, sweet girl.
- Did you miss me, crazy bitch.
- Hell has treated you well?
Yes
- Hail to thee, Mary.
It 's the night of blood, baby ...
Oh my God ..
Dude, you're so 'gay.
No, say the truth, 'He fucks the Parker Brothers!
I do not play with that thing.
Me neither, the sister of a friend of my cousin has played with one of these things for years ...
... And strange things started happening. ... It was owned and you and 'never recovered.
Yes, 'and' losers by ...
- Anyone else?
- No, I do not believe in these things.
It will not happen 'anything, though.
- It 's crazy, will not do' anything.
Listen, I'll think 'me, come and put your lips on this ...
Damn fool!
Oh, a storm, I think.
Hey man, tell me ...
Please! Please ... bitch.
It 's your fifth beer in less than an hour.
Oh, sorry mom.
Good guys, and 'time to prepare for the test.
I have to pee.
But that pyramid!
You want it?
I have to do.
Well, put your finger on it.
No pushing or pressure, just keep it as a boy.
So, 'no pressure.
Start with a gentle circular motion.
Well, so '.
There 's some girl who wants cock?
Nobody 's been with none, right?
You make me sick.
Let's focus!
Sorry, man!
- Asshole!
- I told my cock.
I ... you play there?
- It ', of course ...
- Whatever.
You're completely fucked, but we have now.
Leave me a little 'space.
You are the spirit of Mary?
Want to talk to us?
Translation: ladyhawke17 [IScrew]
--== ==-- ItalianShare www.italianshare.net Section: ISubs Movies
Come and play, baby.
Guys, have you heard?
Do not take me for ass, not to get ass.
And if there is' anybody out there?
- Me too.
- I have not heard anything.
- Have you moved?
- I have not moved, and you?
- Yes, 'I have moved ...
- Guys, look.
Yes
Shit!
- My God ..
- See how I caught.
Do not hold anything better to do than get to play with a cursed Ouija board?
By Gus' s only a game, does not really work.
To hell, no!
Hungry souls, whose only purpose and 'escape from the torment of purgatory.
That's' cause they say that it rests on the weekends.
Come on, Gus. Tell us the beautiful story of Mary Hatchet.
I have some good stories about Vietnam.
That was a real horror.
It 's the "Night of Blood" Gus ... we all have seen "Platoon."
"Platoon" ... and 'just a bunch of actors.
Come on, no one tells the story well as you do. Come on, Gus.
All right.
Hey Gus, pass it, man.
Okay.
Shit, Gus ... this tastes like shit, man.
It 's not your grandmother, and' whiskey, boy.
This has the taste of urine from my grandmother.
It keeps me warm.
Many things can listen back to those days ...
Yes, 'we have heard, we have heard ...
Please do not make it too scary this time.
That 'something that I can not guarantee.
One night ...
... Long ago ...
in a cold and stormy night like this ...
there was this ...
... Couple with their baby, who was returning from a family reunion ...
his wife was sleeping in the front seat ...
... The child was doing the same in the back seat, a few hours before.
The husband was driving.
Suddenly ...
The man thinks he sees something ...
- She was good?
I don't know" responded Ligio, who then went on.
Looking better in the night, was able to see what ...
a naked girl walking on the roadside.
My God, we must do something.
Yes
Okay ... we'll help you, come on.
They decided that they could not let it roam.
Cosi 'made it up, and they put her in the back seat of the car.
They thought to take her to the police station more 'close ...
... And they would know what to do for her.
Her husband felt 'a strange noise from the back seat.
I watch 'in the rearview mirror ...
There was a woman ... this time with a bullet hole in his head ...
The wife cried, 'as crazy, the husband brake' and the woman was carrying the baby.
The couple look 'on the back of the car e. ..
and their son was safe and sound in the seat.
The woman ... gone.
The allocation husband 'again, when suddenly ...
Look in the back seat and there was a woman ...
But this time ... she cut 'head!
When the police came 'on the bloody crime scene, in the following days ...
they found the decapitated bodies of the two parents
but the baby was ... disappeared.
People think, 'that ...
Mary Hatchet ...
had brought the child to the grave with her.
'Cause before he died, the mother had separated from her daughter.
They never had to do it.
She was buried here in the shadow of King Park.
Each year in the "Night of Blood"
she comes back to claim some other head.
And he will 'until' not rediscover 'his own daughter.
Boys ... look up ...
not 'a plane flying low ... so be careful ...
because 'this is the "Night of Blood"
What a fool.
Damn!
Someone for this service?
I understand. Where is the fuse box?
In the basement.
Jen! Bring the ass here.
- Jen you've opened the door?
- No.
- You never open this door?
What the fuck?
But who cares, just close it!
Oh, it looks a bit 'creepy.
That this terrible thing.
Hey guys, look.
Oh, my God
Give me something.
- Chris, opened the door.
- No, you open it, the damn door.
I do not open anything.
- Open it yourself.
- Okay.
Good night, boys!
Vol .. shit!
Now if the people and 'made in his pants? Bitch!
I want to piss on the fucking face, bitch.
What ails them? Give it to me.
What the fuck is going on here?
There are two shits.
Have you lost all your friends we did scream like puppies.
What a good, little brother ...
What the fuck! We want to stay.
Come on, we took the liquor.
A whole box, man.
Hello Cas, how are you friend? I'm Gibs.
- At what time will be here '?
About ... never have imagined. I have a big event tonight.
-What? Where?
- I'm with Nicol.
What was it?
- Dude, I know.
Invite me ... invite me ... by ...
and more ', Jen and' completely mad at me, man.
I'm telling you, "Mom wants my sausage."
No, no, no friend I can, 'cause she wants to keep secret.
You know, only VIP friend.
And how did you do, man?
What can I say friend ... they respect me.
Hey ciucciacazzi, spring that phone and come and help me with this.
Okay friend, I arrive ... I'm coming.
Shit!
What was it?
I do not want to see these things, man.
This fucking DiToma Jones reminds me of my father's prick, man.
Friend ... You have inherited this house from your father?
Fantastic ... have earned a point for that. You know, right?
- A point?
- There is no point to enter.
- Great.
- Do not wear limits.
Well ... you guys have fun.
Hello,
- How are you doing, man?
- How are you, bastard?
How's this fresh meat?
- Be more 'kind, you idiot.
- What did you say?
I said you were a head of ...
Want a cold margarita?
Come on man, I need a cold drink. Look, look.
I was nine. I got up to go pee '.
I ... I heard this noise coming from the bedroom of my parents ...
looked like a pig screaming.
So 'I got out of bed, walked down the aisle ...
... I opened the door ...
... And I saw that my father fucked my ass ... my mother ...
and this damn album of Tom Jones, a friend ... very touching, my friend ...
It looks very sexy, man ... hot.
No, I hate ...
You and Mom 'hot ... I hate that.
That '... Tom Rey.
Hey man, it seems as if ... something you were breaking.
Calm down man, calm down.
There 's an icebreaker in the fridge ...
That does not make sense.
This is 'the most' surprising of all the blades of blenders.
No, no, my friend I think you're right.
- I tell you, is wrong.
- Small ...
You're wrong!
What the fuck is going on here, guys?
My love can not 'do a cold margarita.
The blender does not work ... It breaks the ice.
No, no, 'an old blender, there is' an icebreaker in the fridge, you idiot.
Just put it in the ice-breaker.
Your mom and hours' sleep with your father, as we speak ...
and your uncle is picking them to sell the video on the street.
Holy shit!
- Attack of the Killer Tomatoes, man.
- What 'this?
A horror movie old school, man.
We must see this.
No, I know ... I feel it 'better if I stay here and keep your ass ...
... To touch me everywhere all night.
However, men's shorts are much more 'comfortable ....
... And I take the piss easy.
This' baby, but you do not have the ass.
What? What 'this?
- Oh my God!
You're right ... to kill this cute little thing.
No, no, I think you're one of the hind most 'beautiful I have ever seen.
- With small ...
- It ', nothing.
What do you prefer? Do you prefer shorts or thongs?
That 's a good question ... depends on the ass honestly.
if the woman has a flat ass like an ant, there 'nothing that is fine ...
Wait, that means a flat ass like an ant?
And 'the butt plate ... and oval ... understood.
But if you want an opinion, I would say shorts for men ...
Specialemnte the Brazilian. They are made for the thong.
You got it right there, I'm dying to see one.
Leaving little to the imagination ...
Very nice boobs ...
I do not know, I still think that thongs are better ... I mean ...
You know I love to see this stretch out ...
something happens to me when I see shorts on the Brazilian.
Excuse me but what do you think?
- I should have thought ...
- Come on ...
I do not know ... to know what 's more, I touch with my hands.
I know that you like.
We are interrupting something?
What 'this?
It '... Attack of the Killer Tomatoes.
Attack of the Killer Tomatoes!
What the fuck ...
Oh, man, I'm sorry.
- Dude, what did you wrong?
- I can not believe you did.
Hey, stop.
Collaborate and listen ...
I was just trying to scare you, ok? "I think my shot was a bit 'wrong ...
Obviously, you broke my window, shit.
Look, Nicol, possiamoi adjust this window ...
before your parents come home.
Damn, you broke the damn window.
It 'seems that I have not had any luck, right?
Do you plan to sleep here tonight? Bring your ass into it.
- What is it?
- Nice shot friend.
I thought you were with Daniels.
There I was, but it smelled so I came here.
Alex it will be 'happy.
Hey guys, this is' Elisa.
Hello ... People call me Thurs ..
Thurs or gift ... Yes
- Hello, I'm Erick.
- Hello, nice to meet you.
- What 's your poison?
- I mean '?
What do you drink?
My sister says that the feast of Daniels stank.
Yes
Great ...
Here's what it '... done
Give me another drink ...
I think that is enough for me.
No, no, no ...
Let me help you, my lady ...
How did you meet you and Mary?
Oh, we have lived side by side.
And then I moved to Chicago because of my father's work.
So 'you came to see her?
It '. I have to go back in a couple of weeks.
Oh my God, this stinks ...
Well, Chicago would be nice but ...
I know ... I was born here and die 'here.
I absolutely love 's Arizona.
What was it?
- What does the Arizona?
I die, I say, new school, new way of living ...
Until 'I realized that the school where I was going was very popular ...
And I did not have to prove anything ... but I have always been very careful.
My God, how in prison.
- Well, you never know ...
What is it?
What do you mean?
Well, in reality '...
I have problems with the girls' large.
They call me ... rat, 'cause I'm young and stuff ...
were very possessive with the boys, as if I were to follow them and go with them ...
- What I've done ...
- What was that ...
what 'that counts, I say,' the guy broke up with his girlfriend three months later.
After we met at a party and behaved as if I had committed ...
a horrible crime, and really were afraid of me.
That and 'stupid, I mean, who cares ...
But then, on Monday '...
after the gym ... I was taking a shower e. ..
laughing all e. ..
I was on my own, and I found it odd, but I have not paid much attention ...
and the last thing I realized after ...
and 'I was with my face on the floor and the water on the head ...
I was kicking ass and taking.
You must not talk about these things ...
Do not worry, I have no problems.
It 'was an attack on a group ... and I almost died in the showers.
Shit!
And they have marked me ...
the old way ...
with a knife and a type ...
In short I tattooed a mouse
leg, 'cause that was my nickname ...
- Want to see it?
- Let me see ...
- Shit!
What was it?
- The mouse ...
I think my vagina if it is eaten ...
- Oh, my God ..
- Fantastic ...
I was too afraid ...
Where 'the bathroom?
In this direction ...
I think we have a winner ...
Guys, look for a room.
Do not use my bed ...
Surely we do in this room ...
Just li ...
The Killer Tomatoes!
WHAT 'murderess a tomato?
And 'better if you're good ... Alex.
Cheers!
Give me another ... oh, I'm fine.
- What the fuck-
- Oh my God ..
What '?
- Oh, shit!
Oh my God ..
Take it!
No, no, no!
Come on!
Dance, come on ...
Give it, give it to me baby ...
Shit!
It 's not right ...
- Friend ...
As we say fuck him?
Where the fuck that and go 'a blast!
Come here!
Dude, what the hell are you doing?
What do you think I'm doing?
- Hurry up and sgonfiala. Force.
What was it?
Do it all!
- Dude, man ... let's do it baby, come on.
- Oh my God
Fabulous ... too ill. I love my fucking life too.
I have something I want to talk ...
What is it?
You know what I'm saying?
Possibly.
What was it?
Probably the same thing I want to talk to me.
Dude, you have another beer?
Look in the fridge.
Stara 'well.
Translation: ladyhawke17 [IScrew]
COME AND VISIT
ITALIANSHARE ==-- --== www.italianshare.net
YOU WILL FIND MANY MORE MOVIES AND SUBS TORRENT EMULE HTTP LINK TO DOWNLOAD THE VIDEO
Who wants some 'very fluid? Take treasure.
- So ...
- It 's been fantastic ...
Yes, 'and' state ... a bit 'short.
Well ... We can do it again ...
Would you mind closing the window?
The window 'closed.
You can bring that fine ass here.
By Gibs.
Are you okay? At my first party I threw up all over the world.
God .. I remember it well.
We had a bottle from a dollar 51 and Alex and I, we sat in the cemetery.
It threw up in the cemetery ... I put his guts.
My God, it was not fun.
Go
I understand. It 's not even like me feel so'.
I'll give 'advice wait till' you salt and then throw up.
I'll take that as a yes'.
Come on, Gibs, come on!
be careful!
What are you guys doing?
Come, watch this.
Look at this.
Hey, look who's there '...
You did some shit?
Can I make you something? A "Bloody Mary"?
You look sexy when you look at me like shit.
- My God
- You do not understand.
What was it?
Did you hear?
What is it?
Can anyone tell me what is happening and do not tell me and 'the wind.
What? Do you think someone is making a joke?
Like who?
What 'that?
Let's get out of here!
What the fuck is going on?
I don't know" responded Ligio, who then went on.
The damn door and then it flies off the lights.
Probably 'the storm or wind, right?
It 's not the storm or wind, Jen.
Come on guys, and 'obvious that someone is trying to deceive us.
Like who?
Type the fucking "Mary Hatchet".
Oh, hush!
I was thinking the same thing.
Alex decided to go to the cemetery to lose time and he woke up.
And I tell you what 'happened to another girl, what did you think Alex?
Listen, you look like a moron.
Dude, even the ghost replied.
Now you say it was a ghost at the cemetery?
- What are you talking about?
- Of a fucking ghost, Leyna.
Dude, shut up ... there 'no ghost.
Yes it was, girl.
Erick, go up and called Jack and Taylor.
Fuck, man.
Has anyone seen Tim?
Corey, go check the fuse box ...
... And I'm going upstairs to look for those idiots.
Let's go ...
Alex.
Alex, come back here just a second.
What? Do not see what's going on?
- You found Taylor and Jessica?
- No.
Shit man, we do now?
- Wait a minute ... let me think.
Wait!
I can not leave here.
They died.
Wait, Alex!
Wait a minute, wait a moment ... here.
The damn tires are inflated ....
Corey listen to me, are you okay?
Alex, come on!
They died ... let's go.
Corey and Lindsay died.
I forgot the keys.
Come on.
- Are you crazy?
- Gus, we're in deep shit!
What are you talking about?
Mary Hatchet ...
Not uscirtene with this nonsense of "Night of Blood" ...
I'm serious, Gus.
Climb ...
Climb!
I will not go 'never in the car with the madman.
Are you kidding?
What do you know him you're at home?
By God, Jen ... and 'Clifford Gus.
Okay, stay here.
Jen, in your car, please!
Oh God, get in the van.
Come on!
Where are we going? We have to go to the police.
What the fuck do you want the police to a ghost?
They would have thought 20 years ago.
People think that the old Gus is just a drunk ...
But I've seen things you people would not believe ever ...
The things that he spent in Vietnam can not be compared to what I have seen
Mary Hatchet by my colleagues ...
Translation: ladyhawke17 [IScrew]
--== ==-- ITALIANSHARE www.italianshare.net Section ISubs Movies
Come and visit us on www.italianshare.net you will find links to download movies and many other subs in the ISubs Movies.
Gus, what are you friend?
Gus, that there 'friend? ... What are you doing?
My God, do not go.
Come on, come on friends ..
- Come on ...
No
I'm not going ... I do not come.
I'll stay with you ... I'll stay with her.
And 'this is the place, Gus?
It 'the only grave that I dug in Kings Park.
It is a bond between mother and daughter should not have been broken.
E 'to this evil that continues to live.
I told you so ...
She will continue 'until his research' will not find her child ...
Damn idiots ... I told you to bury them together.
What will we do now?
We begin to dig ...
E 'is empty.
Let's see if my key still works ..
Hey ... hey you.
Have you seen them?
See what?
And 'here.
Let's go ... come on ...
Do not tell ...
- What the fuck are we doing here?
- How the hell do I know?
This 'stupid, we had to go to the police, Gus will make them' kill everyone.
Shit, you're right. I'm going to find them.
No
You stay with me and I do not go there.
- But you said ...
- No
I only said to call the police, cursed the police.
Okay, okay ...
- I'm calling them '...
- Okay.
Shit!
Here, I found it!
Let me see.
Well, you think okay?
Of course it is.
These sons of bitches ... Damn!
It says here that Mary gave birth to a healthy baby girl.
Decided it was best to let them believe that the child was born dead ...
I do believe that someone 'that fucking bitch crazy about Mary Hatchet.
The know this thing ...
She was raped by a night watchman.
That was the straw that broke the camel's back.
'Cause they did not do an abortion?
I don't know" responded Ligio, who then went on.
Perhaps the decision was more 'easy to take.
But why 'to make her believe that her baby was dead?
What can I say?
It says here that the child was adopted by Michael and Leslie Jordano.
All this and '...
I hope that is not crazy like her mother
Go away please!
I understand, but I want to be alone at times like these.
Well ... ok.
Can not 'be ...
Do not you think I know my best friend?
You said you saw them both dead in the cellar, she and Corey.
Well, where is' the box?
Great, you ...
Excellent!
Alex?
I never saw the bodies ...
Only blood.
Mary and 'here.
There 'no ghost, Gus!
It 's the daughter of Mary ...
Hither, here ...
Are you okay?
Listen, you have to remain silent.
Listen to me ... listen ...
Come on out of here, ok.
Let's go ... from here.
Shit ...
- My God ..
- Sorry, sorry ...
We must stand united ...
Andra 'all right ...
Look, look ...
I will not let 'anything happen to you.
You know this.
Fuck!
- You have a phone?
- No. .. and 'in my purse at home.
It's all right ... well.
Help me ... please ...
Gibs? Jen?
Elisa, please do not do it ...
Just, please, stop.
Alex, stop!
It 's over ...
It 's over ... it' s over ...
Let's go ...
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org