HELSINKI-FILMI & ANAGRAM PRODUKTION
present
FORBIDDEN FRUIT
Laestadianism is a Lutheran revival
movement started in the mid-1800s.
They preach of repentance
and forgiveness.
Their summer services are
the largest summer event in Finland.
Finland has 110,000
Conservative Laestadians.
They take the Bible literally.
Contraceptives, alcohol, TV,
rhythm music, and premarital sex -
are forbidden.
Dear Lord, bless this day.
Protect my family
and give me strength.
Wake up.
Good morning.
Wake up, Martta.
Morning, Lars.
Were you playing with your toy car?
Shall we wake the others?
Take the car with you.
Wake up.
God's greetings.
Man's flesh is corrupt.
It was corrupted completely
when man fell from Paradise.
Even man's sense,
a gift to us from God -
was ruined by the Archfiend.
But God's grace...
-That curly-haired boy in the back.
He's too basic.
What about Paavo? He's really smart.
-Nah, he's so lame.
From that day on,
I have felt God's love in my heart.
Thus I beseech you, youngsters,
to keep your faith.
What the world has to offer
is deceitful -
and those who follow
the Archfiend's temptations -
will seldom get
what the world promises.
All your sins forgiven
in the name and blood of Christ.
Let us pray like our Lord,
Jesus Christ, has taught us.
Our Father, who art in Heaven
Hallowed be thy name
Thy Kingdom come
Thy will be done
On earth as it is in Heaven
I wish a long life
for the newlyweds!
If you've attended summer services
with Aaron, show your tongue, shout.
You shouldn't be here.
-Let me in.
Are you in faith?
-I came for my sister's wedding.
I hope you repent in God's name.
Could you please get her
so I can hug her and leave?
Eeva, do you promise
not to make a scene?
And could you wash your face?
Well.
And thank you. At least I've got
things to tell in group therapy.
Others have been fucked in the ass
and kept in dark cellars! Bye.
Eeva, you're always welcome...
-Thanks!
Let's race to the bend!
You're no match for me!
-I'll win!
No, you won't.
Oh no, were you hurt?
-No...
Don't. I'll check it.
Oh no...
I'm no doctor but...
Oh no.
I see no damage here.
Or here...
Maria, don't.
Oh no.
We were tempted by the Devil.
You experienced
a desire of the flesh.
Don't be embarrassed.
It's perfectly normal.
You know why? Luukas?
Raakel?
The Archfiend is testing us.
Exactly.
But sexuality belongs to marriage.
You must be patient.
What you felt
was the work of the Archfiend.
He tries to ruin your love.
All your sins forgiven
in the name and blood of Christ.
You're playing with fire, Maria.
I wanted a kiss. That's not a sin.
It leads to sin. -You really believe
that if I danced to rhythm music -
I'd fall from grace?
That is playing with fire.
I want to feel things.
And know things.
And see things.
Come and see the world with me.
One summer?
The world is a bad place.
Are you sure?
She's an adult
and can do what she wants.
Maria is dear to us all.
She's being tested more than us.
She is sensitive and impressionable.
You always have
the best sticky buns.
Everybody has to act with their
conscience and the word of God.
But now so many youngsters
give up their faith.
You, Raakel...
You could possibly help us.
Where is Maria?
It would be important
to get in touch with her.
You know that Maria's family
has suffered...
...losses.
Raakel, answer
your uncle's question.
I promised not to tell.
Maria will come back.
Fine. Let's say that
she probably will come back.
Let's say the probability
is nine out of ten.
Or let's say 95 out of a hundred.
-OK.
There is still a 5% chance
that we will lose her.
The world is a treacherous place.
It will condemn weak souls
to eternal damnation.
Want a lollipop?
It is that easy to give in
to temptation in the city.
One touch
and the Devil takes everything.
What can I do?
Force her to come back?
-Just hold her hand.
Be her guardian angel.
You'd lead the stray lamb
back to the flock.
That's the biggest favour
you can do for a friend.
You're a good girl.
You will manage.
But be careful.
Hi.
Did you come alone?
Yes.
Have you become paranoid?
-I feared it was a trap.
Stupid.
Good to see you.
This place belongs to an old lady.
I saw an ad in a newspaper.
Let's fix your bed here.
What? -I'm afraid.
Of what?
That you will stay here -
lose your faith and, think that -
nothing matters besides yourself -
money, things, and your looks.
I only want to see what it's like.
-You want to try it.
It's not that simple. Kissing
won't automatically lead to sex.
What if you lose faith
and are damned? -I won't.
Promise me you'll leave with me
if you become settled.
I won't settle here.
-What if you do and are damned?
You'll say the magic word
and I'll leave. -Shake hands on it.
Welcome to the job.
-Thank you.
Going to a club tonight?
-What happens there?
We get drunk,
mess around with boys -
dance, get pregnant and
have an abortion. The usual.
Oh fuck, what a question.
-You sound like a hillbilly.
Say ''fuck no'' and spit.
Fuck no.
-Something like that.
See ya. -See you.
Tuuli is really cool.
Cursing is a sin.
Technically, the Bible forbids
saying the Lord's name in vain.
And I didn't do that.
Come on.
You're so cool.
-Am I?
You want some make-up tips?
We have a new make-up line
for youngsters.
Come and sit down.
Come.
A little mascara makes
your look darker, right?
Like that.
Sun powder makes you sparkle
and you'll be noticed.
I'll go to the bathroom.
Order me some tea.
Hi. What would you like to have?
I want two of...
something alcoholic.
What kind of?
What would be good
for a first-timer?
You've never drank alcohol?
I think cider would be the best.
So, two?
That bathroom is unbelievable.
There was a chandelier.
I don't know if it is crystal...
-Here are the ciders.
I like these candles.
I'll take these back.
You should wash your face.
Here's yours.
There's Sunday service tomorrow.
Shall we go?
-I'll do that back home.
Shall we pray? -I'll ask for
forgiveness when I'm done.
You should pray every day.
Do I go to hell for not praying
if I die at night?
And for other reasons.
-You pray like some crackpot.
You pray if you accidentally
nudge some old lady.
What on earth are you praying now?
Some thoughts
and nudging an old lady.
That I don't say the magic word and
drag you home. -You don't have to.
If you're going to pray,
pray for my sister Eeva.
She's here somewhere.
She came to the wedding,
but didn't come to see me.
Dad said she is utterly lost.
LAESTADIAN CHAPEL
-The Archfiend tormented him.
''If you are the son of God,
turn this stone into bread.''
Jesus said that it's been written -
that man doesn't live
on bread alone...
I can take your coat.
-It's not necessary.
I was just tidying up,
putting everything in order.
You've grown.
Are you eighteen already?
-Yes.
Why are you here?
-I want to see the city.
You want a cider?
Sit down.
Oh, you haven't yet...
-No.
Try it. It tastes good.
It's made from apples.
I remember my first time.
There's a party tonight,
if you want to come.
How is everything at home?
-Fine, I guess.
Is Simeon in high school?
-In his second year.
Oh yeah.
Of course he is.
We'll do the eyes first.
Everybody will be wondering
who this beauty is.
These are not so good.
Look, this is beautiful.
-Give it to me.
Throw these away.
Do not covet the possessions
of others. Now it's yours.
Maria!
A good movie.
Have you seen other films
by this director?
No, I haven't seen other films
by this director.
Perhaps her finest film
will be shown here tomorrow.
It's great. I recommend it.
Hi.
How about a kiss?
What?
Right now? -Yeah.
Just you wait.
Want me to teach you how to kiss?
And where were you?
With the girl from the factory,
Tuuli.
What did you do?
-We talked and stuff.
I was worried about you.
You didn't answer your phone.
It switched off on its own.
-Sure...
Where were you?
Here. -Home by autumn,
get married as a virgin.
Good night.
Hi!
Hi.
I've seen that so many times
I didn't want to watch it again.
I just came from the shop...
What was I asking..? -You were
asking if I liked the film.
Well, did you like it?
-Yes, very much.
I'm going to the cafe
to escape from the rain...
Sure, let's go.
Here you are.
I managed to get these.
The waiter wants to go home.
I don't blame her.
Well, what shall we talk about?
Actually, I did have
some kind of a plan...
Let's get to know each other first,
then we can talk.
How about a staring contest?
-Sure.
You know it? -Yes.
We'll start on three, okay?
No looking before that.
-Or talking.
Or talking.
-But we can make faces.
OK. One, two, three.
You win.
This round.
-You were better.
Wasn't it kinda foolish
to wait in the rain?
No, I had a good reason.
My name is Toni.
Nice to have met you.
I have to go now.
-Huh? Why?
I have something to do.
-Wait!
You want to see Sixties' Japanese
short films tomorrow? -Maybe.
Please, they're interesting.
-I don't know.
Hi.
Have you been here
doing nothing?
Are you sleeping?
Yeah.
Bye. -Bye.
Shall we go?
God's greetings.
-God's greetings.
Hello.
God's greetings, Maria.
-God's greetings.
Want some?
Grandma Iita's bagels.
Thank you.
Well?
-Nothing much to tell.
How are things at home?
-We can't manage without you.
A joke.
-We should go to sleep.
Is everything okay?
-Yes.
Really? -Yes.
I can make coffee.
-We're out of coffee.
Do you want a lift home?
Maybe...
-Why don't you trust me?
It's not about trust.
It is dangerous to sit
at the blasphemers' table.
God's greetings, girls.
How are you, Maria?
-Fine, thanks.
You haven't been to service.
Have you enjoyed your trip?
-This place looks nice.
This is a... busy place.
Is everything OK?
Go to hell,
you hypocritical bastards!
Leave me alone! I'm fine.
Is everything really okay?
Yes.
They drove 700 kilometres
just for us.
They did it out of love.
Here nobody cares about anything.
What are you thinking?
I saw Eeva. We drank alcohol.
How did it feel?
Like jumping or being on a swing.
Everything feels more intense.
We went to a party too.
I kissed this dumb boy there.
Think what could have happened.
Nothing. It was nothing special.
Kissing? -Yeah. Like someone
stuck a fish in my mouth.
A fish? -Yeah.
You don't even like fish.
I'm sorry I lied to you.
All your sins forgiven in the name
and blood of Christ. -Amen.
I must also confess...
-Yes?
I met this boy. -What?
We went for a coffee.
But no fish or anything.
All your sins forgiven...
if you show him to me.
Never!
-You'd better show him.
No. -I want to see him.
You can stay.
I'm going somewhere else.
Is he either one of them?
Is he?
-Yes, but don't move.
Hey, over here!
Raakel is here!
Come here.
Hi. -Hello.
Maria. -Jussi. Hi.
Toni. Hello.
Great that you came. -Thanks
for the loud and clear invitation.
Do we really know each other or..?
Well, yeah. -Not exactly.
We don't know each other.
-But we've seen each other.
It is complicated.
-Well?
I asked Raakel to watch
Japanese short films.
Japanese short films?
Damn, you're a player!
What do you mean?
-Sorry, he's a freak. Avoid him.
That was a joke.
He's a good guy.
What are you doing?
-I don't know.
Going home, maybe eating.
-Sounds good. We'll come along.
Lets go. Come.
This is my place,
but Jussi sleeps here too.
I'm like an au pair.
Jussi has lived here
most of his life.
I brought my stuff here. It's
easier than going back and forth.
Where are your parents? -They
spend most of their time in Spain.
They abandoned you here?
A big house, electronics,
a car, and a swimming pool.
Toni's life is so hard.
Sometimes, life can be cruel.
-You guys are silly.
You know why?
Our noses are so big.
You know what that means?
Our big noses?
What does it mean, Toni?
-Well, that we have...
Yes?
-Big feet...
Toni is the freak
and I'm the funny one.
Who are you?
Nobody.
I'm a shadow. A three-dimensional
image from another world.
I'm not really here.
That's a pity.
This is my favourite music.
This song is about a blue unicorn -
who has escaped from his owner.
His task is to find songs
and give them to others.
Sorry.
I have other music too.
-No...
Come here.
Come closer.
But don't touch.
You can't touch me
because I don't exist.
I sleep here.
But are no games here.
You want to kiss me?
-Yes.
No. -Sorry.
Or yes. Do you want to?
-Yes.
Should I undress now?
-That is the standard procedure.
We could do it dressed, but it's
difficult. -Turn off the lights.
I... -What?
I'm a little nervous. -Why?
I haven't... done this before.
Is there something I can do?
-Just wait a minute.
For what?
-For me to loosen up.
Where is Maria?
-I don't know.
Is she alone with Jussi?
-Probably.
Maria! -Calm down,
he's not going to hurt her.
We have to go.
-There's no hurry!
A pretty good guitar,
but a little out of tune.
I had a guitar once,
but it got broken at a party.
How? -I was drunk and it was
out of tune so I smashed it.
Maria!
Open the door.
-Wait. I'll be there.
Should we exchange numbers?
We just switched operators,
we don't know our new numbers.
But that doesn't mean
that your number changes.
Well, we have this thing.
-This is my number.
Thanks.
Thanks for the food.
-Bye.
Kissing felt really nice. -Remember
that when you burn in hell.
What? -That's right.
Kissing, booze, and rhythm music
are not sins.
Do they really lead to sin?
Fuck no. I'm clean as a whistle
now and always.
Do you think you're stronger than
the rest? -Stronger than most!
You're carrying a burden of guilt!
You do what everybody else wants
and says. That's why you're weak!
I've dreamt about India
since I was a kid. Now I'm going.
Will you be there long?
-I don't know.
I'll come home when
I'm out of money or home sick.
I really don't know yet.
Isn't it scary, not knowing?
-No, it's not.
I'll know
after I've looked around first.
Come with me to India.
Wouldn't that be cool?
I don't know anything about you.
Where you come from.
What your dreams are.
I don't know anything.
I want someone
who's with me now.
You can't be a shadow.
You're nice.
-Why can't I touch you?
Do you have someone else?
-That's not the point.
But you have someone else.
What do you want from me?
Tell me honestly.
Answer me straight!
Do you have your
new phone numbers?
No.
That's odd.
God's greetings.
-God's greetings.
Is something the matter?
Tell me.
I'm evil. -No, you're not.
Yes, I am. -No.
I've used make-up.
I'm selfish -
and weak.
I still don't see a bad person.
Neither does God.
And He sees everything.
All your sins forgiven
in the name and blood of Christ.
God's greetings.
Did you go somewhere? -No.
You've just been here?
-Yes.
I was with Eeva,
we had some drinks.
Magic word. -What?
Let's go home. -Why?
You promised we'd go when I say it.
-If I was going out of control.
You drank again today.
-So?
You mean, I'm going to hell?
Yes, that's how it begins.
Where are you going?
To take heroin and sell my body.
By the way, nice mascara.
What are you afraid of?
Come, I'll show you.
Please, don't. -You were
assigned to protect me.
Here's the den of sin.
I wasn't told to take care of you.
I wanted to come.
And I'm Jesus Christ.
Look at me, it's still me.
Can we go now? -You have to taste
it. You have to understand all this.
Well, what is all this?
-Nothing. Ordinary life. Taste it.
We didn't order anything.
-A gift from those gentlemen.
You want Toni to screw you.
Don't... -You're a bad believer.
You're so fucking bad.
You know why?
You don't know where Satan lives.
Here. I've always known it.
I feel how he moves,
it feels wonderful!
But I won't give him anything!
You think Satan isn't in you.
That's why he can take you.
Why the look? Fucking bad believer!
You want Toni to screw you.
You'll burn in hell,
I'll go to Heaven!
Is everything alright?
-Yes. Throwing up helped.
Good. In Finland we have
these teen whores.
Will you abandon me
or do as you're told? Well?
An angel.
No.
I'll give you a hint.
He lives in the jungle.
No, you're a real angel.
Forgive me.
It was a monkey.
Monkey on your back.
Like a millstone around one's neck.
Good night.
-Good night.
I dropped my purse there.
Calm down. -Don't you understand,
they'll come here!
Don't exaggerate. -I dropped
my purse! They can find us!
We have to go!
Get dressed, we can't stay here.
You need a drink.
Have some.
-No, thanks.
Yes, you will.
My house, my rules.
We drink booze,
or you get the fuck out of here.
At least remove that crucifix.
We have a situation.
Can we stay the night?
You're always welcome
if you're drunk.
That was a joke.
Of course you can stay.
Jesus loves you. -You know
what kind of Christ I know?
You're a fucking coward.
You can't even look at me.
What the fuck are you afraid of?
Satan?
Or that you know
how screwed up that system is!
Laura, come here!
She's my lesbian lover.
Does it bother you?
Oh yeah, she's not even human,
because Jesus doesn't love her -
since she screws girls!
-I'll pray for you.
Don't you ever fucking pray for me!
You can stay.
Hi.
Can we stay the night?
-Is something the matter?
No. -Come inside.
You can use the sauna if you want.
Summer services start soon.
-Yeah.
I'm from Northern Ostrobothnia.
I'm 1 8 and the eldest sibling.
The others are Iida, Ariel,
Eleonoora, Helena -
Lars, Leevi, Tuomas, Ruut -
Martta, Jaacob, Esaias and Ellen.
-OK.
I believe in God.
I'm a Conservative Laestadian.
How does it feel?
Great.
Why couldn't you tell me?
Because you would've left.
I wouldn't have.
You could be from Southern
Ostrobothnia for all I care.
Who are you?
-I don't know.
At least not yet.
A human, a curious human.
How does it feel?
It feels really good.
What?
No.
No, no...
Raakel, I can't feel my faith.
I will go to hell!
What's the matter?
-I have to get out of here!
Let go! -Calm down!
Let go! -Calm down.
Calm down.
She's not here. Maria!
Here!
I'm filthy! I'm filthy!
I can't feel my faith!
Calm down.
You're suffering a minor shock,
you'll remain under observation.
A nurse will take care of
your scratch.
Say the magic word.
Say it.
You promised.
Raakel?
Say it.
Raakel...
Toni, no.
I don't want to take it off.
There's fire -
and water.
Together they make ash.
Fire is good, water is good.
Ash is nothing.
TO SUMMER SERVICES
People living in the Archfiend's
world don't want to believe -
that their sins are forgiven.
People are either for Christ
or against him.
Jesus means that...
We are all evil. The domain
of the Archfiend tempts us.
We God's children are tempted by all
the useless things we don't need.
We're all weak and sinners.
All of us think
that our sins are unique -
but they're not!
The gift of faith in our hearts
is based solely -
on the deeds of our Saviour,
Jesus Christ.
He gave his life
to redeem our sins.
To redeem our sins.
He is the refuge and sanctuary
who guides us.
You may believe.
Brothers, sisters, and friends,
your sins are forgiven.
All your sins forgiven
in the name and blood of Christ.
All your sins forgiven in the name
and blood of Christ, my dear child!
and expiatory blood of Christ.
All your sins forgiven in the name
and precious blood of Christ!
All your sins forgiven
in the name and blood of Christ!
All your sins forgiven in the name
and expiatory blood of Christ...
It'll rain soon.
Where are you going?
-Come.
Close your eyes.
Do it.
You smell nice.
Raakel, don't.
No one will see us.
God, please forgive Raakel
for her actions -
and forgive me for my weak flesh.
Please forgive Raakel
for her actions.
Jesus Christ!
Raakel, what did you do?
Go wash up at once!
You will not sit at my table
looking like that. Go!
Dear God, bless and protect us.
Bless and protect Raakel also,
and forgive her for being weak.
God's greetings.
God's greetings, Raakel.
So...
We wanted to see, Raakel -
if everything is alright.
Wait a moment.
I figured there would be
a lost lamb on the move.
I could make some porridge.
That's not necessary.
Remember to eat something
on the way.
You're so skinny.
You have to eat.
You hear me?
Bye bye.
It feels horrible
that my own child will burn in hell.
Bye bye.
XviD ~ DigieraMandela (DM'37')
Subs ~ DigieraMandela (DM'37') with SubRip