And now Sylvester the Skyman brings you
up-to-the-minute traffic
from our WST news chopper.
Thanks, Pat.
Well, folks, we've got a massive jam heading
into and out of Star City International.
Blame it on all the added security
put in place for the royal arrival.
Hey, it's not every day the crowned
Princess of Vlatava pays our city a visit.
- Cut her some--
- Cut me some.
Hi, this is Dinah.
I can't get to the phone right now.
But I'll call you back.
Uh, hey, it's me.
I know it seems like I'm late again.
But I'll meet you in baggage claim. Bye.
Smooth, Queen. Real smooth.
I mean, would it have killed you to say:
"I love you. I can't live without you.
"Please don't take a cab home"?
Oh, come on. The arrow's green. Move!
Whew. At least she's not waiting for a cab.
Wait a minute. I know that guy.
Is that...?
Merlyn.
Princess Perdita has disembarked.
Her personal security detail
is bringing her out now.
Please stay behind the ropes.
This will just take a second, people.
We're sorry for the delay.
All clear.
Move! Move! Take her back up!
Sorry I'm late.
But you try changing clothes in a hybrid.
Green Arrow.
Justice League of America.
I'm here to help.
Oh, crap.
Okay, Princess.
Arms around my neck and don't let go.
Merlyn, the bird has flown.
You have your green light.
Come on!
That dragon almost got us.
You do realize I'm 10,
and do not require fairy-tale metaphors?
Sorry. It's my first time rescuing royalty.
It is quite a forgivable sin...
Robin Hood.
Thanks, I, uh--
Your leg!
Yeah. Minor setback. Unh.
You're being very brave, Princess.
I'm proud of you.
Can you make a bandage,
tie it around my leg?
Yes, of course.
Any idea why these guys are
trying to kill you, Princess?
Because I'm not a princess.
My father died last night.
I'm the queen now.
You're even braver than I thought.
Staying put's no longer an option,
Your Majesty.
- Get ready to run.
- You can run?
You've got an uncle, right? A Count?
My only living relative.
Count Werner Vertigo.
So if something happens to you--
He becomes King of Vlatava.
Now it all makes sense.
He's taken her back inside.
Inform the client.
Kill you! Kill you! Kill you!
Me? Weren't you after the kid?
Excuse me.
Kidding, Your Kidness. Kidding.
I got you! I got you!
No! Princess, let me go.
So, Arrow, once again
you've stumbled onto my stage...
...and horned in on my act.
That's me. Always hogging the limelight.
I seem to recall you lost our last duel.
All eight of our last duels.
- You lost?
- Yeah,
but I've been practicing. A lot.
One arrow each?
I accept your challenge. On three.
One.
Two.
- Three.
[COUGHlNG] What...?
If you want something done right....
Vertigo.
Count Vertigo to you, peasant.
Soon to be King Vertigo...
...once l've dispatched
you and the little bi--
Watch your mouth!
Ahh. What would you do without me?
Well, now that you mention it,
and since l'm on my knees anyway....
I can't live without you, babe. Literally.
Say yes. After all,
every queen needs a consort.
She's right. Every Queen does.
Yes. The answer is yes.