Any body out there ?
I need a little help.
You are  alive.
Oke.
Oke, All right.
All right.
Oke now.
You are going to live.
Can you stand ?
Come on, Hold on.
It is oke.
- What did you mean: I`m alive ?
You are on a boat.
My boat.
Why am, I ? On your boat.
Maybe you can tell me.
All right ?
I was dead.
I am sure of it.
No, But you are not.
You are  alive now.
Why am, I alive ?
I don`t know. You where in my net.
Net ?
You where drouning.
You swalot water. You sink.
Don`t ask me how.
Come on. Do you have it cold?
- Yes...
Com on. Hold on to me, Get up !
Get up !
Watch your step.
Keep it warm. You need a hospital ?
- No.
Why not ?
Because..I am fine...
You need to see a doctor. After a thing like that.
- No, I dont !
I don`t want to see any one.
- Well, I just disappear then?
I don`t mind seeing you.
You don`t mind seeing me ?
That`s nice.
Say it again.
- The most people do.
I don`t.
- Why not ?
Because, You fish me from the water.
How are ya ?
You realy don`t want people seeing you.
What is your name ?
I don`t know...
You lost your memory in the water ?
Maybe,
- I have heard it happends.
Is it ?
- People knock there head, Forget al lot.
And then it will all come back suddenly.
What is your name ?
My name is Syracuse,
- People call me Circus.
Why ?
What, To let on. You know.
- That am, I clown.
Clown ? In a circus ?
Something like that.
I think, I can get used to.
Syra.., Syracuse.
- Oke then.
I am taking you to the hospital.
I have a car on the shore.
Are u one of those asylum seekers?
- What?
You swam here all the way from Arabiya?
That is a hell of a swim there.
Let me go now.
Do you realy want to drown ?
I can`t die twice .
- You can die once for real.
Please...
I don`t need a hospital.
I know a place where people won`t see you.
Come on.
Who owns this place ?
- It was me mams.
She lived here ?
- On and off. She was a kind of loner.
A loner ?
- A bite like you.
She did not like people..Much.
Why ?
She was a kind of a gypsy.
Where is she now ?
She`s with her maker.
You mean she`s dead ?
- Yes. - Like me.
You are not dead.
No, Maybe.
I should, I should have been.
Have some sandwiches. On Me lunch.
All the strange fishing today,
- I forgot to eat it.
Thank you.
Al right, Can, I  leave you now ?
If you have to.
- I do. Yeah, Got to be somewhere.
Oke.
She has been waiting for you.
- I know, I`m sorry, Something came up.
The oppointment is at six.
- She gets upsad. I`l make it up to her husband baby ?
Bye mom.
You just have to fuck it up, Dont ya ?
- Yeah, It is genetic.
Right, Up you get.
Anything strange or wonderful ?
Why do you always say that ?
I don`t know, Annie.
- Kind of a wish.
A wish ?
- Yeah, That is something... Strange.
Or wonderfull might happend.
No, Dad. Nothing strange or wonderfull.
Eh, Wel thats good then.
Hello.
- How are you ?
Is doctor Hannon Around ?
- No, You just missed him.
Oh, I thought he was gonna be here.
- Something came up. In Cork.
How long this time ?
- Same as usual. An hour or a half or so.
Does she have a book ?
No book. Maybe tel her a storie.
I`m inside if you want me.
- All right.
Well..
Go on.
- Go on what?
You said you tell me a storie.
Oke.
Once upon a time...
Does it always have be once upon a time ?
That`s..How, Stories begin.
And a very good time it was.
Yes...
It was a good time.
And this was a bad time..
How are you feeling, Love ?
Never a mind a bout me.
- Go on.
Once upon a time..
There was a fisherman.
And he was pulling at his nets..
And it was a normal day.
And?
And what?
What was she?
- Was she a mermaid?
No, She wasnt a mermaid.
Was she a Selkie then ?
What is a Selkie ?
- A kind of a sailorwoman.
You can hear them singing on a sailrock.
Who told you that?
The teacher. She comes out of the sea.
Losses her sealcoat. Lives on land,
- Untill the sea to call her back.
She did not had a sealcoat.
What ever that is...
She seems to remember drowning.
And?
And...
That`s it.
That is a realy shit storie.
Yeah, Maybe.
Remember that thing we ordered from the C.R.C ?
What thing?
Wait till i show you.
Now...
You should rest as musch as possible.
- Until we sort you out.
Oke.
You got wheels now, Annie.
Look at this, Alex.
Does not do bumps.
Did your daddy buy you that ?
- No, The C.R.C.
As, I guest.
How is the fishing, Circus?
- It is Syracuse.
Syracuse, How is the fishing ?
- Same, See you.
When?
- Tomorrow.
So, Did you see the doctor ?
- He wasn`t there.
That`s because you where late you fool.
- Clown.
Yeah, Ya clown. He did not do any tests, Circus.
- She needs a kidney.
Something about..What was that word?
- Compatibility.
O, You understand what that means ?
- It has to be the right fit.
Bloodgroep, You fillping clown.
- You had to ask him, To use.
Goodbye.
Still here?
You thougt, I would be gone.
- No, But, I dreamd it.
That you fisht me from the water ?
- Something like that.
So, You are still dreaming now?
- That is my mothers coat.
Sorry. I had to wash my dress.
- Doesnt suite the dream.
No ?
No. She was large. My Mom.
And kind of an strange.
- Strange ?
Yes, was not like you.
I can be strange.
So can the most of us.
Going fishing?
- Yes.
I tought, I might cath another.
Another.. Girl like me ?
Yes.
Maybe the sea is full of them.
Can, I come with..?
- No.
Why?
I, Tought you wanted to be seen.
I, Can hide again.
Only bad luck.
A girl an a boat?
- For the fishing.
Have you been having good luck lately?
No.
Okee, Then. Get in.
What was that song you where singing ?
Just a song.
- But you remember it?
Must have.
- Do you remember your name?
You can call me Ondine.
That`s nice
What does it mean?
She came from the water.
Ondine means:
- She came from the water.
No. Ondine was the girl that came from the water.
When?
- Long time ago.
Want to help?
Move that over there.
Over there.
They are empty.
- So, They are.
Did someone get it out then?
- I, hope not.
My God.
What?
Are u playing games with me?
No, I`m not.
What did you just do?
I , sang.
- Yeah, I know.
Come down here.
Sing again would you?
You bring me luck.
Luck?
I , Haven had much.
Evereyone needs luck.
- You do. But not evereyone gets it.
Maybe it is your turn.
- That would be nice.
Right. Come overhere.
Help me...
Right. Put one between your legs.
- So, It doesnt bite ya.
And the other one like this.
What do you do whit them?
- What do you think?
Eat them.
- No. Sell them.
You always cath this much?
- No, Olmost never.
Right.
There you go,
- Close there.
Grab that.
It wasn`t your song, You know.
-It couldt have been.
No.
They where already in the pots.
Why do you put them back?
I am saving them for a rainy day,
- And sell the rest.
We will get something for these.
We?
- Your share of the catch.
You did sing. Just don`t go out and sing voor evereyone.
Follow me to the Co-op, Will get Ten Euro for a pound.
I do not want to meet any one.
You have met me.
You are the only one.
How are you, Mary?
- Hello, Circus?
Oh, You did well today.
- Yes. For a change.
They say there are no lobsters left.
- They don`t.
Thank you very much.
- Lovely..
Can I, Help you , Circus?
- Tracy, Would this go near you ?
You want me to try it ?
- Oke.
It is a bit tight around here.
At least you are not invincable.
- What?
Nothing, I will take it.
For who?
Just for Annie.
This will never fit Annie.
It wil someday.
What do you think, Circus?
- I think that`s not my name.
Sorry. Dad.
Do they give you a hard time ?
- No. They are jealous.
How many of them got wheels ?
- Motorised wheels.
What are we doing?
I was going to drive you home,
- I wil race you.
Annie...
- Yes ?
We won`t so.
So, Whats the storie?
Oh, She sings.
- Who sings?
The woman of the storie, I told you about.
- With the fisherman, Yes.
She sings to the fishes,
- And he catches them.
Are you sure that you are not dreaming, Dad? Dreaming.
Yeah, You are sure this is not some weird,
- Wishfuling thing a kind of thing.
How did you learn words like that ?
- I go to school.
And i didn`t?
- No, Let be honost. You didn`t
You move with your mouth when you read,
- Is that bad ?
No, But it means something,
- So, She sings does she.
Yeah, A song in a language that he has never heared.
That would be Selk.
- Selk?
A kind a sailor talk? And do you know why she sings?
That`s how they comunicate under water.
They don`t speak they sing.
So, The lobster heard her singing?
- What lobster.
What i mean is, Under the water they hear her singing.
The villans of the deep.
- Are you sure?
She is a seal, she is not human.
- She looks human.
In the storie?
- Yes, In the storie.
Who`s storie is this ?
- It`s mine.
You make it up ?
- Yep, For you.
What are you planning for the weekend?
- Practice mine new wheels.
Curious.
I brought you some things.
- Things ?
Messages.
- Messages ?
Yeah, Food and stuff.
Even girls from the water need to eat, Right.
Need clothes.
Need to...
Tie those shoelaces.
Curious, And curiouser.
You know my size ?
Tracy in the shop
- She looked like..
Your size.
Thank you.
Can I..
- What ?
Can, I , Clean up this place ?
- I suppose.
How long wil you stay?
It depends, I gues.
- On what ?
On you.
On me?
If it depends on me,
- You can stay forever.
Forever?
- Forever .
Happenly ever after,
Once upon a time..
I have been telling my daughter a storie.
A fairytale.
What is the storie dad?
It`s great, See you, Deirdre.
Hi, Annie. God, You have a lots of books there.
I`m researching
- Researching what ?
Something on seals, Is it?
My name is Syracuse,
- And I`m a alcoholic.
I, Told you before Circus, Confessions,
- Is not a chapter of AA.
There is none in this town, Father.
I have been sober, Two years, Seven months and eighteen days.
This is where they clap there hands, Father.
Where did you see that in the movies ?
- Yes.
Thank you.
Son tel me.
- I had a dream, Father.
I`m at a funeral, She`s beside me,
- And I`m panicking again.
Maybe you still want to be with her.
No, No, I`m panicking beacause.
- I`m back with her.
It can`t happen. She`s still drinking.
- What, I want is Annie.
Perhaps you would need to talk someone, Circus.
It is Syracuse.
- And, I`m talking to you.
No, I mean a counsil.
I can put you both in one,
- But, If you would give me permission.
You have no permission, I, Only talk too you,
- Cause it is in secret.
When ever you feel your able to,
- Tell me and I, Set in motion.
Until then...
Try to control your feelings.
Anything else?
I, Supose there is.
Yeah, I , Stole.
Oh, Dear. What did you steal , Syracuse?
Some lady`s clothes.
Oh, Dear, Dear, Dear.
I don`t like this at all.
- Syracuse, This is a bad development.
This is not what you think, Father.
- There was a reason. What was the reason ?
I stole them because, I was embarrassed
- To be seen buying them,
Why did you want them for ?
- They for this girl a meet before, Father.
A girl ? Where did you meet this girl ?
I, pulled her out of the water, In mine net.
In your net ?
- In mine, Fisshing net.
You are joking truly, Syracuse?
- No, I`m not joking.
Dreaming maybe. But You know,
- I, went to mine boat this morning...
And there she was,
- And did she.. Ehe.. Spend the night on the boat ?
No.
- No ?
So, Where did this girl sleep?
I`m not telling you..
No, I, Can`t force you to, Can, I.
No, And you can`t tell any one either.
No, Mine lips are sealed.
But you will keep me informed,
- Of developments , Syracuse?
Definitely Father.
So, wil, I see you at mis on Sunday ?
- You know you won`t, Father.
Suppose you do.
You only avail of the confession.
Cause there is no AA, In this proxy town.
You wouldt say of couple of Hail Marry`s,
- On your way out would you ?
Legends of the Selkie.
What are you reading, Annie?
- For school. Selkies.
Selkies? That is a Scotishe ting.
This one isn`t.
Curiouser and curiouser.
What is that?
- What Alice said to the White rabbit.
Come again?
Curiouser...
...And...
Curiouser.
See, I knew you where real.
O, It is real?
- Yes. I, Knew it was not a storie.
What wasn`t a storie ?
- The fisherman, The girl in the net.
Mine dad told me a storie about you.
Your dad is Syracuse?
Yeah, The fisherman.
So, Do you have magic powers?
Do you?
- You know, I don`t.
Oke.You don`t.
Can you make me better?
Better ?
- I`m sick.
I, Have got kidney failure?
- Didn`t he tell you.
What is your name?
- It`s Annie.
Annie.
I`m Ondine.
Ondine.
I`m examining it for webs.
Well, Do I, Disappoint you?
Ondine it`s French isn`t it?
What is a French Selkie doing here?
Who said that I, Was French?
- You got lost, Did you?
Yes, I, Suppose, I did get lost.
Your cold?
- Suddenly.
Cause you are on land now.
- Your natural habbit has it in the water, You see.
You seemed to know a lot about me.
Yes, I have been reading...
Researching...
Want to come inside?
If, I cross the treshold,
- You might put on hex on me.
What is a "Hex" ?
- It`s bad news a hex.
Maybe under water feels better.
- Better then what?
Some days I`m sick all the time.
- Does it feel better under water?
I`m not sure, I know what you mean.
Oh, Come on, Let`s not try and fool each other.
- We both know the truth.
And if we are not safe for it,
- There is no point of being friends.
So, We have to be friends then ?
We could be,
If we play fair to each other.
I need you to be specific.
Feel any better in that home of yours under the waves?
But, Definitely feels different.
And I, Know you don`t talk down there,
- You sing.
Yes, Singing travels by under water.
What about the cold?
You get used to it.
Oh, Of course you have a sealcoat don`t you ?
Mine sealcoat?
Look, There is no point of being around the bush.
- I, Do know these things, I , Have been studying them.
So, Tell me about mine sealcoat.
You lose it when you get out of the water.
And you can`t go back until you find it again.
And if you do find it, And bury it on land.
You can stay for seven years,
- And you cry seven tears.
But when the crying is done.
Youre kind of folk can not find the excepted happienes.
- With the..
What is it called?
- Are you lost for words?
A landsman, That`s what.
Selkie women often find unexpected happienes with a landsman.
And that`s all, I know.
This is my granny`s place.
He misses her.
Where do you live?
With, Me mom and it is not underneath the waves.
She, Will be wondering where I`am.
See you again.
Your cheek is wet?
- Is that one of the seven tears.
Maybe.
- You have only six left.
Can I, Help you there Circus?
Yeah. Have you any books from Selkies.
Selkies,Yeah, We do have actually,
- What strange enough there all out at the moment.
Out?
- If you want to read them, Your daugther has it.
Annie?
- She is doing a project she said.
Yeah, Just trying to help her.
- Get a head of the game.
Your a good man.
Does it do stunts Annie?
- What you mean stunts?
Stunts like this.
It`s not a recreation.
- So it is only for spasms?
You don`t say spasms.
You say, Specially`s, Do it Johny?
Yeah.
See ya ficking retard, Say it.
- Specially`s.
Specially`s, Annie.
- Give us a go.
Does it float ?
- I, Don`t think it`s amphibias.
Specially`s, mine ass.
Come on guys.
Is mom up yet ?
No.
What`s there something up?
- Why did you think?
Was it battery trouble?
- It got wet.
Come here, I don`t bite.
O, your getting big.
You said you had Selkies in Scottland.
All right.
We invented Selkies.
- In the old happier days.
You mean you made them up?
- No , There are a Scotishe thing.
There you go.
She doesn`t speak like you.
Who?
Well we got secrets, Have we, Little girl?
Well you could say thanks.
- Thanks.
Your weclome.
Do you want to come again?
- Fishing?
Only if you want.
You promise, I see nobody but you?
I, Promise you see nobody but me.
Your swimming in mine dress?
It was a gift from fisherman.
Can, I help?
You can bend the tilla.
Right, Straigt out to sea.
Keep her steady would you.
- Fisherly blar.
You can`t realy guide a boat with your foot.
I`m not doinig wel ?
- No, I never said that.
Oh, Shit.
Look at that !
My, God.
- What?
That`s weird, Salmon.
Weird?
You don`t get Salmon`s from shaling.
- Shaling.
Only with a gear net.
Curiouser and curiouser.
- Where did you hear that?
Alice said that.
- To the White rabbit.
Annie says it too.
- Annie? - Mine daughter.
Ah..fu..
- What?
They are going to come on board.
Leds.
I see you catch Salmon.
- I did.
How did you catch them ?
- Trouling.
And you expect us to believe that?
- No, But it is the truth.
Show us your gear nets. Hold on.
That`s not wet.
- I know.
So, how did you dry them?
- I didn`t. I told you, I didn`t use them.
There is a girl here, Circus.
- Where?
In your net.
Is that illegal?
- No, But...It`s unusual.
And you can see her?
- She`s right here in front of me.
Ask her how, I caught the Salmon.
How did he catch them up?
Trouling.
And you want us to believe in fairytales?
Yes.
What did she say?
She said: Yes. Realy.
- You got to believe her.
Right. Times are up.Lads.
So. They saw you.
Is that all right?
- No.
That it is a relief in a way, Things are not in my mind.
These will talk.
- Of course they will.
What wil they say?
Take your pick.
Circus. Clowns. Salmon. A girl.
I`m going to the harbor.
- Do you want me to drop you off.
It is done isn`t it, What`s done?
I have been seen.
Look at the girl on the boat.
Not bad, hey.
It is a small town.
Everyone stares.
You can say that again..
What`s wrong with been seen.
Nothing.
When you look good.
You look better.
I going to need these Circus.
- They have already seen.
Who?
- The fishery`s.
They are fine, Believe me.
Thanks, Mary.
Can I, Buy you a present?
Clothes, But can I, Choose this time?
You don`t like the dress?
- No I, Like I, just...
The underwear could be better.
- Didn`t fit?
Tighten on the edges.
You have edges?
I, Knew it wasn`t a storie.
- What wasn`t a storie?
Youre just a shit storie teller any way.
I, Knew it had to be true.
Ondine, This is my daughter, Annie.
We have met before.
- Yes, We have.
What are we doing?
Buying clothes.
- Oke.
This town is what you call.
- Southorely challenged.
What does that mean?
A supermodel`s nightmare.
Does Selkies do lingerie?
Why not?
They wear seaweed knickers,
- And a skelpy bra.
But that`s underwater,
- Won`t do here.
I suggest you don`t buy them all dad,
- Just a selection.
That`s where I, Found her...
...Roan Carraig.
You know what it means?
- Searock.
It`s a kind a sanctuary,
- For her kind.
Her kind?
- Yeah.
The well dressed kind.
What do you think?
Or should we say what do they think?
You have cleaned the place.
Like Snowwhite.
Is that all right?
I`m not a dwarf you know,
- I`m little, But not a dwarf.
Who is Snowwhite?
- Does it matter ?
She didn`t swim.
Can you swim, Annie?
No, There is no pool in the town.
- I never had lessons.
I think it could relax you a lot.
Unless you a have fear of water.
I wouldn`t have a fear of water,
- With a water creature a round me.
Oke then, Come on.
What will a wear?
Underwear.
She`s gone already.
Where?
- The caravan on the Poulin.
Is that where she sleeps?
- Your waterbaby.
I tought, I might take her out for the day.
The regatta starts at three.
- Oh, The three of ya.
Diving for pearls?
Something like that.
What kind a stories are you spinning?
Just relax.
Laydown now.I hold you.
You see?
You see? You are a sea-creature.
You think?
- I know.
Relax...
Okee, Let`s go on the raft?
What`s That?
Just something, I found.
- You found your sealcoat.
Maybe.
- Are you goinig to bury it?
Would you like me to bury it?
Yes, Because that means you wil be here for seven years.
Would you like that?
- I would like that a lot.
You better bury it then.
- What do you think, Absolutely. Okee.
Help me.
Will, I remember where it is?
- In seven years time.
Watch this.
Seventeen steps.
And, It is our secret,
- We tell nobody.
You know dad, If she bury`s her sealcoat.
- She stayes seven years on land.
Annie, It`s true.
- Withe a..What`s it called again ?
A landsman.
Unles her Selkie husband claimes her back.
- I, Don`t have a husband.
Maybe you don`t remember.
- But you do, All the Selkies do.
Nice fries.
- Here..
And the last thing is that she can make a wish come true.
Please, Annie.
If you are a Selkie men.
- But I`m not a Selk.
Okee, You are not a Selk.
Come on you guys, Pull harder.
So, You are not a Selk.
- Proof it.
What?
Annie!
Annie. Come here.
Come here, Baby. I, Got you.
What happend?
The brakes swept.
- What?
- Let mee see them. Come here...
I was lucky wasn`t, I ?
- Lucky? How?
That she breathes underwater.
What happend?
- She fell in the water. Chassing that rock.
The brakes went mad.
- By the pier she saved me.
Your waterbaby? Clown.
Come on, Will get you upstairs and you go to the bad quik.
The brakes they didn`t go did it?
No, She did it herself.
Why? Did she do it herself?
- To test me maybe.
See how much I do for her.
Strange, Feels like home.
Who is this woman, Annie?
She`s from the Orkney Islands.
- She swam around the coast to here.
What if she was?
I might be imaging.... scratch over there.
A little bit cold around the thigh region.
Stop him ma,
- Close the door.
Your Clown of a fisherman,
- He wouldn`t notice though, Now would he.
Close the door ma.
Did he claimed her to the fishery`s board?
How much would you do for her?
You are testing me to?
I`m sorry..
So, Why do they call you Circus the Clown?
Because I was one for years..
I drink.
What made you stop?
Annie.
I Came back from a week on the trollers.And..
Found her without conscious, Her mother out in the pis.
I tought one of us better be sober.
And then she kicked me out.
You could take Annie with you ?
- Ah.. This is Ireland.
Men like me don`t get custody.
Some one was looking for her. Who ?
- A man.
A dark haired man?
- Yeah...
You didn`t tell them ?
- What is her name ? - Ondine.
That is not what he called her.
Men like you?
- Fisherman.
Are you dry ?
Didn`t Annie tell you?
When a Selk make love to a fisherman..
She weeps...
Salt tears.
You said you died in the water.
How many lives do you have?
For you?
I, can`t count..
My name is Syracuse, And.
- I`m alcoholic..
And you have been sobber for,
Two years, Seven months and..
Twenty-one days.
You are doing very well, Syracuse.
- It`s about the girl father.
Oh, Yes. The one you have met out fishing.
I drew her up in the net, Father.
- She look prettty real to me.Circus.
Syracuse.
- Sorry. Syracuse.
So, What a bout her?
You have sinned with her?
- I, Suppose.
Offcourse.
And I, Don`t suppose,
- You want the absolution.
No.
-No?
So, Why are you here, Syracuse?
You know the storie about the king?
- Who had a secrect.
It drove him mad, So...
- He told it to the tree.
Okee, Son, Pertend I`m a tree...
She brings me luck, And, I don`t know why..
I`m afraid, Father..
Cause..
I`m beginning to hope..
We should never lose hope,
- Syracuse.
She was drown father,
- Mine net brought her back to life.
It doesn`t make sense.
- I know.
None of them make sense,
That`s why, I`m afraid.
I know somethings going to happend,
- Something wonderfull.
Or terrible..
She is the kind a girl she is.
She is the kind a person she is.
And that is my secret.
So, What kind a tree are you father?
I don`t know,
- I suppose an, Oak.
You look more like,
- One of the Ones they make the harley stiks out of..
An, Ash then.
As long as you are a tree.
Hey, you Syracuse?
- Yeah..
Syracuse, The fisherman?
- What is it to you?
You got a light?
The girl on the boat.
What do you call her?
My mascot.
You where upsad last night?
- Not so much.
Your mom sad you where.
- She imagine things.
Doe you imagine things dad?
I leave that to you.
- It`s a kind of to much time on mine on.
My blood goes from here to there,
- Trying to imagine a happy ending.
It is hard,
- Some days it is hard.
Where is every body ?
- Oh, God. In town for the regatta.
The regatta?
Yeah, There are bands playing.
- Late night opening.
Mom told me, I forgot...
Have you got a key?
- Yeah, But I, Left inside.
Annie.
Come on.
Where does she drink these days?
Skippers.
Hello?
I have don it mom.
- Oo.. You are a good thing ah.
Becareful. They don`t serve naglers here...
Just give me those keys Mary, I take her home.
- The barman, Doesn`t hurt anyone.
Please, Mary.
- You had a few in your time ah.
She`s coming to mine place.
- She is not, Get back to your caravan.
What would your mermaid say, Circus?
You know he has got himself a waterbaby.
I`ll be fine.
Just go, Dad.
Two shots, All right?
- Two shots is it...
That`s it.
Middelpocket, Right?
Right middelpocket.
Ahh, You mist.
Ondine!
Tought i get seven years?
Remember the bit a bout the Selkie men?
The husband?
Well he is here.
- And he is taking her back?
Yes.
I`ll see you at home then, ha...
A guy was batterised in Glassgow,Ha..
No, Seriously, He was six times over the limit.
What if I take foot path?
Look darling, You are still charching a flipen vehicle right?
I`l go slowly.
Tell him to pis off.
- I wish i could..
Wish then.
- I can`t.
You can grand a wish.
- You sure?
Annie say so.
Oke.
I wish she wasn`t sick.
So do i.
And i wish you would stay.
That`s two wishes.
One for you,
- And one for me.
Have you got your lights on, Hey?
- The cops will get you if you don`t.
Maybe it is all a lie.
Maybe you walked in to the sea,
- To get away from a bad marriage.
Would you believe that?
I did it once.
What happend?
I got wet, Got sense, Got sober.
That`s not the storie though.
- What is then?
Like Annie says, I`m a Selk.
Somethings up.
A crash.
No... No ,Annie.
Get out of me way.
Annie. Annie.
Syracuse. Syracuse.
She`s oke. She`s in good hands.
Tell me what happend!
A terrible accident, But Annie is All right.
- Annie is fine...
You where wearing , Your seatbelt, Love?
What happend?
- We don`t know yet.
She`s all right. Father ?
Please God forgive me.
Can we just continue, Move to another room,
- Do you want to follow me.
Something wrong?
What is happening?
- I don`t know.
- The doctor will explain.
Syracuse, Can we talk in private?
- What`s going on?
Alex had a donercard.
- What?
We have a tissue match,
- Strangest thing but, it has happend.
Are you serious?
Come on.
So why are you here?
Do you speak their language now?
I`ts softer than ours.
I wish you where dead.
- None of us have that luck.
So, The sea spit you out did it?
Can swallow me again...
We don`t belong here?
- Do we...
So,..Go home.
I can`t,
- Police want to talk to me.
About what?
She came from nowhere. Drunk.
They should talk to her not me.
Tell them that, I will.
- And then you tell me.
Nothing.
Where is mom?
She is a sleep, She can`t see you right now.
- She will later.
Where`s Ondine?
- Ondine is close by.
You will see her too,
- Just rest.
Just rest...
He had a wife, three children in Scotland.
Where are they now ?
- They said we where welcome to him.
I`m sorry it happend like this.
Sure, I can take us in?
- I know.
It is hard.
Why aren`t you blaming me?
Just for once you had nothing to do with it.
Why do if feel if as i did?
Beacause you are Circus,
- You get everything wrong.
I met him on this ferry.
Where was, I?
Where you always where,
-  At sea.
Take Annie home, When she`s stronger then i,
- Get out of this thing. I can`t..go up.
That`s what you have always wanted, Ins`t it?
- Yes.
So, you got it.
But, I don`t want that woman there.
Take me to his waking up.
I can`t
- Oh, I insists.
Two whisky`s and ice.
- One.
Two.
Maura, I don`t
- Show some respect, It is his funeral.
Get rid of her , Circus.
Who?
- Your waterbaby.
She brings good luck than bad.
Two more Maggie.
Are you all right?
Property of the finder.
Why are you looking at me like that?
- Cause you are a Selkie.
I`m a alcoholic.
Kiss before a night sleep had you?
No, He..Is..Still outthere some where.
Oke, I am taking you home.
That part a bout the husband...
- He is not mine husband.
What is he then?
My Peshta..
(Pimp)
What is that, Selkie for squeez.
Look, Your home.
You will be safe there.
- You could sing your song.
Who am i singing to ?
- To me.
Go on sing, Let see this dance.
I can`t, Why not ?
- Cause your dronk.
I will be sober in the morning
- You can sing to me then.
I have fisht here for years,
- I never knew this Selkie stuff.
I wish you would never be update.
- And i fisht you back to life. Yes..
And now you are goinig to hunt me?
- Huh.. forever...
What does hunt mean?
- Huh...What does hunt mean?
You want some?
Selkies don`t... Drink ?
So... You are safe here,
Is that right?
How is Annie?
- She is fine.
She is safe too.
I got another bottle on the boat.
Syracuse.
What does hunt mean?
Things what your doing...
With me.
Don`t do it.
Syracuse!
Don`t !
What are you doing?
- It`s not how fairytails end.
But, this one does,
- This one does, It has to.
What do you mean?
- What do you mean !
I mean, Your kind and mine kind.
We don`t belong together.
I have to say goodbye
- No, Way.
To Annie.
Syracuse.
Hey, Buddy,
- Well, I am your buddy am i.
Yeah...You are.
You are my soberise buddy
Where were you last night.
- I needed you.
You fell of the wagon?
-..Bigtime..
Circus of fools.
I was turning around the big tub.
I`m back in saw-dust now.
And it takes like shit.
You know what my problem is, Buddy?
You can`t take good luck.
Ten out of then, Sherlock.
Misery is easy, Syracuse.
Happines you have to work at.
Why didn`t the tree say that?
The tree is not going to tell you anything.
What a bout the girl?
- Ah.. She`s gone.
And Annie?
She`s getting out today.
I am taking her home with me.
After that, There is no..Choices,
- Is there buddy.
No.
Why are you crying?
I am not,
- Yes, You are i can tell.
Maybe because you are back in the road again.
- You are home.
Where is Ondine?
- Ondine... Had to go for a while..
That`s why you cry ?
- It`s not, I swear.
Did her husband come?
- It must have.
Cause she`s gone,
- On sea business.
She will be back you know.
- Do you think.
I know,
- She left something here.
What?
What time is it ?
- Half one.
Why didn`t you wake me?
- Cause you where sleeping like a baby.
I tought you where the baby,
- It doesn`t look like it.
You want breakfast ?
- Lunch.
There you are baby.
Annie, That song.
What song ?
- Just a minute ago.
It`s real.
- Off course it`s real, Sigur Rs.
Annie, I have to go out for a bit.
I`l take you to your moms.
- No.
I can`t leave you on your own.
- Yes you can, I feel much better.
Are you sure?
You have got some unfinished sea business?
I suppose.
Go on then.
I`m kind a busy here any way.
There were seals down there.
- Blasting on the rock.
Mine kind, Ha.
I didn`t say that,
- No, But you thought it.
And the storm came up.
They slipt in to the water one by one.
-..I was going to joined them...
What changed your mind?
What changed yours?
She was switching channel`s on the T.V.
Your song came on.
It was never mine song.
So, Tell me,
- No, Take me home.
Where is home?
- Where do you think ?
You tell me the truth now.
The truth?
The truth is, I`m a creature from the sea,
- That found her a sealcoat...
And buryd it, Because she found a family,
- That she liked.
Please.
That`s..ehh.
That`s one truth.
You don`t want to know the other.
Try me.
Oke.
I`m a prisoner and a drug mule from Romania.
I said, The real truth.
This is the real truth.
I was on a boat, With a kilo of heroine in a backpack.
The coastguard came Vladic let me swim for it,
- Vladic.
My Selkie husband.
Mine Peshta. (Pimp)
He was like a monster,
- From a fairytail.
But, He couldn`t swim.
So, He made me take to the water.
I was always a good swimmer.
But, Your Irishe waves woar me down.
I swam til i couldn`t swim no more.
Then i floated.
Then i sank.
It was olmost an relief.
I said, Here goes..
I die..
And that is the truth.
You brought me back to life.
I found a caravan,
- A family.
Now its gone oke.
The caravan is going nowhere.
What is your real name?
Joanna.
Just, Tell her you where all  your way on sea business.
Sea business?
I told him nothing.
- Told who?
Not true, Little girl.
You told us a bout the seven tears.
- And the Selkie island.
And how Ondine came out of the water.
But, It is nothing important.
- I swear.
Seven tears are important.
- Surely.
And the Selkie island.
Still some details, I got to get more clear,
- Do you want to eat some..Dad.
Who the heck are you.
- Circus, The clown.
We got seal, Selkies, Clowns.
- Someone out bring in sense here?
Is she a good swimer?
- Yes.. I swim like a fish.
She the one that last it?
- I`l get it back...Just put that thing down.
Where is it?
- Where is what?
He want her sealcoat, Dad.
- What is she a bout..Yes i want the sealcoat.
Don`t give it to them.
- We have to.
That means you go.
- We don`t know that, I know..it.
Tell her, Tell her  What?
- That you don`t care a bout me.
I don`t care a bout her.
- You want us to come with you...
Listen to me... Let them go,
- Put that thing away!
I`l show you...
- Where !
It`s oke.
Give her to me
Come here.
Here Annie,
- Come here.
What? It was here, I swear.
- I swear...
Stop it !
Listen to me..
Look at me little girl,
- Don`t make me bite !
Did you move it, Annie?
- Selkies way, is the way to go..
He digs it out,
- And she doesn`t stay for seven years then she goes.
Tell me, Where did you move it,
- Before they hurt somebody.Oke.
I don`t want you to go..
If you tell me where you moved it,
- I promise i stay.
How long?
- As long as you want...
I find a job on a fishing boat, Anything.
- Just tell me...
Cross your hart?
- Cross my hart..
The lobsterpot
- The lobsterpot?
What lobsterpot?
There for storage. Show us.
- Right there. Show us..
Give it.
It is full of water.
He is not an Selkie?
- Is he.
No, He isn`t
- But you still are.
It was vacumed.
Always.
Help.. I..Can`t..Swim..
Help.
So, He couldn`t breathe under water.?
No, He couldn`t.
Does that mean he drowned?
Don`t you wory a bout it my love.
That`s it, Boys, Overhere.
Good, We are gone.
Is this not an AA meeting?
I don`t know.
The ting is father, She`s up on the front of the judge.
- Next week.
And?
She is a non-national.
This is an confession, Father
- We are not talking gossip here?
I`m still an oak
- I thought..you where what did you call it?
An ash.
- An ash. Well..
Her solicitor said that, she will be departed,
- If she desn`t become a national.
- So, She has to apply to the departmend of justice. Yea...
..Or.. She.. Gets.. Married..Ah.
So, Who is going to mary her , Syracuse?
It is not there is a Q? Father..
I can`t marry her.
- No, You are a tree.
Exactly...
And i threw the Selkie coat in the water.
- And i told a lie a bout that too.
It wasn`t a real lie was it.
- Beacause i wanted her to stay forever.
She`s staying forever ?
Yeah, Haven`t you heared they getting married,
- Next week to make her national.
So, I suppose, She isn`t a Selkie realy.
Cause you can marry a seal,
- Can you...No, You definitely can not.
Not, In the real commodity world any way.
Commodity?
- Yeah, Means the one we live in.
- If you was a seal doh,
- Would you still do the wedding? Me...
What a bout your past lifes?
Are you sure, I have them?
O, Yeah, Everybody does,
- It is just a matter of remembering
Stop! Peeping would you?
- I don`t peep.
I mean, You could have been married me.
- One day.
Subs by: Sch13d@m A.k.a Schiedam31(14)