Access the footage from Wesley.
We got to the temple this morning,
and sent the unit advisors away
right after lunch.
Funny the way things work out sometimes.
The only reason we found this place
is because they were looking for weapons
of mass destruction that didn't exist.
God definitely has a master plan.
The tomb was undisturbed,
but it'll probably take
another couple of days to get to them.
Dr. Chandler completed his assignment
this morning.
He was ready.
We all know the sacrifices we have to make.
Never seems to get any easier.
I miss Moray.
This could be a chance
to change things forever.
Fulton says I'm crazy,
but I want to get closer.
I need to get closer.
I stopped Fulton and the others
from leaving.
They scared them in.
It always starts with hallucinations.
Then what could happen?
I can't believe it's come to this.
No one can leave.
Get it out, get it out of my head.
Who do we send?
I know the perfect person.
All my life, I've been a soldier of fortune.
Did what I had to do to get the job done
and get my team out alive.
This mission shouldn't have been
any different.
But it turns out,
some things can't be killed with a bullet.
Dr. Cardell is on the ground.
I repeat, Dr. Cardell is on the ground.
Thunderbird 307
heading back to civilization.
Have fun, boys and girls.
I could put you out of your misery, rookie.
-You ever flown combat before?
-Yeah, a bunch of times.
-Videogames don't count, man.
-screw you all. All you all.
Elite unit, my ass.
-Target practice, Hammer?
-lt ain't loaded, boss.
Give me that.
All right, listen up. You've all been briefed
about where we're going.
This is Dr. Cardell,
she's here to tell us why we're going.
Meet the Angels.
Yoshi, Hicks,
this is our medic, sergeant Harrington.
-You can call me Doc.
-Nickels.
-Com tech.
-You can call me Nickels.
This is our computer specialist, Click.
-And the big guy is...
-sergeant Diego Garcia.
-I've been briefed on your unit, Captain.
-ClA puke.
As you know,
the research station at shabaka
was hit by a seismic event 36 hours ago.
All attempts to reestablish contact
since then have failed.
And what kind of research are they doing
in the middle of the desert?
-The work is classified.
-That's all right, we can keep a secret.
It's an archeological site.
Its previous owners used it
as a storage facility,
but when we acquired it,
we found something.
something that cannot be moved,
something that my superiors say
we don't need to know about.
-Yeah, same shit, different day.
-What do we get to blow up?
Actually, sergeant, it's an extraction.
This is a fucking joke, right, boss?
With all due respect, honey,
but you don't need this hurricane of pain
to dig a bunch of scientists out of the sand.
He's right, Mack, we're shake and bake, man,
not search and rescue.
We're not here to rescue
a bunch of scientists. Just one.
Who? King Tut?
Dr. Lee Wesley.
Can you pass that around, please?
Nothing else is to be removed
from that station. Is that clear, sergeant?
Wouldn't he have contacted somebody
by now if he was still alive?
There is a safe room.
But if the quake knocked out their uplink,
there's no way that...
Getting a signal,
that would be impossible. Yeah.
Anything else we need to know
before we get this stupid mother-fucker
out on his ass?
-Actually, there is one other thing, sergeant.
-Oh, yeah? What's that?
That stupid mother-fucker is my father.
It's getting pretty nasty on the horizon.
Let's load up.
-I'm hit. I'm shot.
-Hicks.
-Hey, don't you let him die.
-Fuck!
What the fuck happened?
It's another ClA cluster-fuck, sir.
The locals aren't getting the message.
Well, next time remind me
to get a translator.
-You look like shit.
-sorry, boss.
-Can you move him?
-I'm working on it.
-Wilcox?
-He's dead, sir.
-You want this?
-Get the fucking thing away from me.
Goddamn heathen.
Mack!
Buckle up and finish your smokes, ladies.
It's going to be a rough one.
-What's the forecast?
-Look for yourself.
We going to be able to find the beacon?
Fortunately, we got a strong signal.
Probably wouldn't be able to see anything
in that shit storm.
synch on my mark. Now.
Better be ready in six hours,
or you're marching out.
This wind will bore in your skin
like a blowtorch. so stay tight.
-Move out. Go, go, go, go.
-Go, go, go.
Move it, rookie. soldier up.
I got to go, Mack. The wind's too strong.
See you in six hours.
-Base camp's been totally blown away.
-stick together and find the hatch. Hooah?
Move out.
Eye on the prize, Captain.
On my mark. Three, two, one.
Clear.
Let's move it.
Hustle up.
Yoshi, clear the perimeter.
Hicks, two-by-two formation.
Damn, it's hot in here.
Quit bitching, rook.
It can't be no more than 80 degrees in here.
Feels like fucking Cancun to me.
-Clear.
Clear.
Down!
-ls he all right?
-Yeah.
-Give me some room.
-Jeez.
-What's wrong with him? Is he contagious?
-I don't know.
Hey, you know, l, I really don't want
to spend a month in quarantine
when we hit stateside.
He's not febrile, all right?
If I had to guess, I mean, this looks like...
Like radiation poisoning.
But I don't know.
Well, I got nothing on the Geiger counter.
What is a priest doing here?
Alfeo Jacoby. He's from The Vatican.
-I thought you were a doctor.
-My doctorate's in anthropology.
Man, that's some sick-ass shit, bro.
It's like when Blakeley and l
were in the swamp for two days.
-Blakeley?
-Our last CO.
Yeah, we came out, our whole bodies
were covered in two-inch leeches.
Feel good, having something that big
in your pants, Nickels?
You want to take a little peek, huh? Kiss it?
-Mack.
-All right, guys, come on.
Let Doc work her magic.
Didn't mean to hit on your girlfriend, Doc.
-You okay?
-Yes. I mean, no.
-Well, which is it?
-someone's in the safe room.
-ls it Wesley?
-I can't tell.
There's people wandering
around everywhere.
And the bad news?
Look, lady, I ain't got time
for bullshit games.
If you know something, you need to spill it.
Well, the whole base is locked down.
We can't go any further
without an override code.
Or a really good hacker.
-Click.
-Yo.
Get over here.
We need you to get into that network
and get the elevator working.
I'm on it.
Listen up, we're going down in five.
Get your gear in order.
-Hey. What's up?
-Cardell was wrong.
The quake didn't knock out
this com system.
They got torn to shreds from the inside.
How long is it going to take for you
to get it working?
Patch this up, about an hour.
There's no power running to this thing.
Could be a blown relay downstairs.
Boy got skills, or what?
I can see
why The Pentagon didn't cut you loose
after you hacked into their database.
Oh, yeah, you company men.
Know all, see all, hear all.
Don't worry, your secret's safe with me.
Hell of a first step.
You're not going to piss yourself,
are you, Click?
How deep did you say this hole was,
Dr. Cardell?
-A thousand feet?
-Just ignore them.
Yeah l...
I'm not worried about them. It's this.
What's the Gehenna Project?
I don't know.
Yeah, it looks like a bunch
of encrypted data files.
But they won't be encrypted for long.
Come on, come on, breathe.
Breathe, God damn it, breathe.
Breathe.
Breathe, breathe, come on, Nate, breathe.
-You look like shit.
-sorry, boss.
Mack.
We'll get you out of here, son.
-Can you move him?
-I'm working on it.
-We got to pull rank, Captain.
-I can't breathe. I can't breathe.
That's what happens
when you get a chest wound.
What the hell are you doing?
-I'm cleaning out his airways.
-That's disgusting.
-Give me that.
-Here you go, boss.
-You okay?
-I'm trying to get this guy stable,
but his vitals are for shit.
-Maybe he's got allergies or just bad acne.
-Would you shut the fuck up?
-Mack, we got to get him out of here.
-Well, can we call the chopper back?
Not in this storm, not without the uplink.
May I remind everyone,
nothing is to be removed from this station.
That includes him.
You know what? That's bullshit.
No, Doctor, that's a direct order.
You know, this is exactly
what you said wouldn't happen.
I'm not leaving him.
-Yes, you are.
-No, I'm not. Mack, he's a priest. Okay?
That may not mean anything to you,
but it does to me.
Well, set Nickels up with what he needs
to do and pack your gear.
-Him?
-Me?
Cardell's right. Our orders are no souvenirs.
so pack your gear.
No, no, no, no, l... I ain't touching him.
-Yes, you are.
-Yes, I am.
We'll plug the power back in downstairs.
I want that uplink fixed
by the time we're back. Hooah?
Hooah.
It's like Tal Afar all over again.
Asses flapping in the wind.
You're up, Hicks.
-Fuck.
I want this to go by the book.
We get Wesley, we get the hell out of here.
-Ready?
-This badass was born ready, boss.
Let's move.
I love this shit.
-No grab ass, you two. Get in here.
-Come on.
Dr. Cardell, you reset your transponder.
Hicks, rig the rookie, would you?
Happy hunting.
Keep your safeties on.
Hey, this ain't so bad.
Welcome to hell.
You want something for that?
Lock and load.
You know, in our line of work,
nothing gets you killed quicker
than dragging civvies into a hot zone.
Especially those wearing panties.
stay with us, lady.
Earthquake.
-Hold it.
-ls everyone okay?
What the hell?
This place is coming down on our asses.
Where do these leads go?
When Wesley's team found this place
it was booby-trapped.
They hauled out enough C-4
to blow it up two times.
-Who's maintaining this place?
-Dr. Wesley's team.
Enough chatter. Hammer, Yoshi, take lead.
-Let's move.
-Okay.
stay sharp.
How many people did you say
were down here?
Twenty scientists, some security personnel.
It's up ahead.
What the hell is that?
For God so loved the world...
Over here, boss. What is that?
Who's that?
Now why would God make such a bad deal?
-ls that Wesley?
-I can't tell.
Identify yourself.
We've been called many things
throughout the millennia.
-But Wesley isn't one of them.
-son of a bitch.
Where do you turn for the answers you seek,
Dr. sarah Harrington?
The Authentic, the Barclay,
the Contemporary, the New American,
the New English, the New Evangelical,
the Revised, the Restored, the Worrell?
Have you ever wondered
why there are so many
if only one truly showed the way?
I'll bet you have, Doc.
We got no time for this shit, Mack.
Without the shedding of blood,
there can be no remission of sin.
Let me help you repent.
Doc, get over here.
Doc? Doc, what's wrong with you?
He knew my... He knew my name, Mackie.
He just said my whole name.
shit.
-That son of a bitch is spitting battery acid.
-All right, just hang on. Let me help you.
-How'd he know my name?
-What was he talking about?
-scripture, Old Testament. Hebrews 9:.22.
-What does it mean?
It means all her friends has gone loco,
that's what it means, Mack.
shit.
sedate him, Doc. I don't want
this guy wandering around down here.
Hey, soldier up.
Knock him out, Doc.
If we have to, we'll lock him in the elevator.
Okay, now just keep it open, all right?
Captain.
I don't think you got anything
to worry about with this guy there, Click.
shit.
Good thing the bullet didn't hit the tank,
or none of this shit
wouldn't be here anymore.
-You're the only one who can help me.
-What?
-Why didn't you get it out of me, sarah?
-I'm sorry.
Why did you let me die, you bitch?
I don't...
You're the only one who understands.
It says, "Welcome to hell."
-You can read that?
-Yeah. I speak a bunch of languages.
What? You can't?
How we doing, Doc?
sergeant Harrington?
Harrington, do you copy? Doc?
-Click!
-Yeah?
Get up here.
-Where is she, Click?
-shit, I barely have a signal.
Find her.
straight ahead a hundred yards.
Moving fast.
Then so do we.
Dr. Cardell, what's down here?
-Engineering.
-Hicks, Yoshi.
-sir.
Get to communications relay
and get the power back on,
-so Nickels can get us out of here.
-Yes, sir.
-Click, you go with them.
-Yeah.
Don't forget your gun, rookie.
And don't screw up.
-Hammer, take point.
-You got it.
Nickels, do you copy?
Hey, yeah, yeah. Barely, you're cracking up.
How's the priest doing?
Priest? The priest is...
No change. still passed out and creepy.
Watch out for him.
No, he, he's not supposed to get tranqued
for another 15 minutes.
That's not what I mean.
Yeah, but you're breaking...
You're breaking up.
stay clear of him and get the uplink fixed.
Go... Go again. You're... You're breaking up.
Hammer, do you copy?
-Can we move him?
-Yeah.
Let's get him out of here.
We got to pull back, Captain.
-Don't you let him die.
-I can't breathe.
That's what happens
when you get a chest wound.
Incoming.
-Hammer blew the shit out of them fuckers.
-Get him up.
Keep moving, Dr. Cardell.
All right, stay sharp. Let's find that relay
and get the hell out of here.
Go that way.
-Don't shoot, don't shoot, don't shoot.
-I will shoot you. Get down here.
-What was that?
-I don't know.
Come on.
It's coming from in there. Click, open it.
All right.
-This is it.
-Open it. Fast.
You ever stop to think
that maybe it's locked for a reason?
You're not here for your opinions. Open it.
-All right, here we go.
-Move.
-Here we go.
Yeah, move it.
What is that fucking smell?
Oh, fuck.
Mack. Mack.
-What the hell happened here?
-Keep moving.
Who are they trying to keep out, boss?
Or who are they trying to keep in?
Cut him down, Hammer.
There are those devoid of divinity.
Mack, listen. That's Dr. Wesley.
Dr. Cardell.
Hospitals cramped with the mentally ill.
Those who see clearly the truth.
This cosmic game of good cop, bad cop.
We all fell for it.
It's a recording.
And God looked upon the earth,
and, behold, it was corrupt.
Hammer, it's me. It's me.
-What's going on with the power?
-Low-level transformer's fried.
One of the locals grabbed a main bus.
Both hands.
Was it Wesley?
Have you seen what 299,999 volts
does to your complexion?
-sir, what the fuck is going on down here?
-Yeah, what she said.
And nobody said nothing about crawling
through a bunch of dead bodies
-and barbed wire.
-Mack!
-Doc's signal. It stopped moving.
-How far?
Give me that.
About 199 feet that way. storage room.
All right, go, go, go. You two, stay here.
Anybody gets passed us...
-Take them out.
-That's right. Let's go. Come on.
Yeah, something's getting past him. Right.
Way too many rat holes in here.
Let's keep moving.
-Click, position.
-Twenty feet ahead, down the stairwell.
You sure you're reading that thing right?
Yeah, we should see her
at the bottom of the stairs.
They move about the earth with such ease.
Hospitals cramped with the mentally ill.
Those who see clearly the truth.
What is this bullshit?
-ls it Doc?
-No.
No one.
-We bounce topside and wait for the cavalry.
-Quiet.
-Hey.
-Oh, it's you again.
Where's my soldier?
she's not your soldier anymore.
You blind fools.
We offer the same salvation,
just without the rule book.
-Where's sarah?
-Come with me. I'll show you the way.
Together we will dine on the afterbirth
of her new becoming.
-What's that?
-I don't know.
The coms aren't working. Mack?
stay here.
Hey, get over here.
We did our part, now you do yours.
Dr. Wesley?
This cosmic game of good cop, bad cop.
We all fell for it.
Some of us harder than others.
Slaughter one another,
and anoint ourselves with ash.
Mommy?
-We got some C-4 that can help you, Doctor.
-Just hurry up.
This is Dr. Elissa Cardell,
is anyone in there?
Yoshi?
What the fuck?
Look at your conflict.
You try to convince yourselves
your existence on this ball of dirt
is not a dead end.
Then I show you the truth of your faith,
and you don't accept it.
Make up your mind!
I think you got him.
How the hell is this bitch still wiggling?
Nickels.
Nickels, do you copy? Nickels? Nickels?
I want you to tell me
what the hell's going on.
-I don't know.
-Bullshit.
-What are they doing down here?
-I told you, I don't know.
I'm done risking my team
for some Agency jerk-off.
-This isn't a ClA project.
-But covering up is?
Fuck this. Let's move.
You don't have the authority
to make that call, Captain.
I think he just did, lady.
You want to stay? Be my guest.
I have no problem leaving your ass.
some kind of biohazard down here
that I wasn't briefed on.
It's not your job
to worry about what's down here.
-It's your job...
-What the fuck do you know about my job?
My job is to get my team out alive.
When I shoot somebody and they don't die,
makes it hard for me to do my fucking job.
You can't do this.
I told you we'd get you down here.
I didn't say anything about staying.
Captain!
Dr. Cardell. It is you.
-Are you alone?
-Yes.
Who is this, Doctor?
This is Father Jacob Fulton.
He's part of Wesley's team.
-What's going on down here?
-He wouldn't understand.
I just saw a dead man
quoting chapter and verse. Try me.
I want my soldier back.
Is my father still alive?
The last time I saw him,
he was in the temple.
That's where your friend
would have been taken.
How did you know she was taken?
Mommy?
Yoshi.
Where are you?
Hi, Mommy.
-Hey, baby.
-Look what I found, your bear.
My mommy gave me that bear
on my fifth birthday.
My mommy never gave me anything.
No bears, no birthdays. Nothing.
Except a place in hell!
I asked you a question, Father.
How did you know she was taken?
God wiped us out once before.
It's all part of his design.
I don't give a damn
what game God wants to play,
-I just want my soldier back.
-Your soldier is going to die.
We're all going to die if we stay here.
And you know the way
to this temple you spoke of?
-Yes. But... No...
-Let's go, come here.
-I want to go back.
-Lead the way, Father.
Go.
-What the hell are we shooting at?
-What are we shooting at?
-What's wrong with you?
-she was here.
-Yoshi.
-I saw her, I swear to God, Marcus.
-someone talk to me.
-It's Yoshi, she's seeing things, boss.
Hallucinations.
It always starts with hallucinations.
-What did you see, Yoshi?
-I don't know.
I didn't see shit, boss.
It didn't just look real, Mack, it felt real.
To the temple now.
she can't come with us.
They use visions to tempt us.
Wesley thought he could contain it.
I tried to convince him
it's down here for a reason.
I don't give a damn
what you think is down here.
You take us to the temple right now
or I put a bullet through your head
right now.
stop. He'll take us.
All right? Please.
We got to pull back, Captain.
Incoming.
Get him up.
Let's go.
-What the hell happened?
-Bad day at the office. We lost Wilcox.
Everybody outside.
You okay, boss?
Never better.
I hate this horror crap.
I can't go, I can't let it happen. Not to me.
You fools don't understand.
All you're going to find in the temple
is despair.
-You're going to find despair, old man.
-Wait. I got a better idea.
Is this really necessary?
Absolutely.
You appeared. Oh. Wow.
Blasphemous.
shit.
Hey.
Captain, Captain.
-Doc.
-Open the door.
-I don't know.
-I promise I won't tell.
Look, you need to listen to me, okay?
You can't trust them.
Especially that bitch, Cardell. All right?
I know what's going on here.
It's not good.
I can get us out of here, come on.
Open the goddamn door, Click,
get me out of here.
Captain...
No, get off me.
Let me give you your penance.
Then you can be beautiful, just like me.
Come on.
-Come on.
-Be right with you, boss.
-What the hell was that?
-Nothing like your videogames.
Eat this.
-What happened?
-Fed Click's new friend some C-4.
Blew a 599-pound shit bag into next year.
The blast caved in the passage.
There's no going back that way.
Oh, that's great. That's just great.
Now what are we supposed to do?
-Man, how could you be so stupid?
-Oh, yeah? I just saved your ass, didn't l?
And what the hell you were doing
back there anyway, huh?
There's an access tunnel
that runs parallel to this corridor.
-We can use that.
-You heard the lady, Click.
-Get the door open.
-Yeah, yeah.
Okay.
That's going to have to do.
Hicks, get him inside.
Yoshi, Hammer,
burn anybody that isn't Doc.
Come on. Go.
-What about Wesley?
-Fuck Wesley.
Where is she?
-You told me my soldier was here.
-I told you we had to leave.
Mack, look at this.
It's like a bunch of
ancient-fire-and-brimstone shit.
There's stuff here from all over the world,
different religions.
Hebrew, Christianity, Buddhism.
-Click.
-Yo.
What's it say?
I can't read spanish.
You can read Latin,
but you can't read spanish?
-Hammer, get in here.
-Yes, sir, boss.
-What is it, boss?
-What does this say?
Let's see.
It's a testament from a farmer.
He said he saw an angel cast from heaven,
2,999 years ago.
What the fuck?
It moved. Mack, it... It moved.
Look, look, check it out,
check it out, check it out.
I'm telling you, it moved.
What the fuck is that thing?
Huh?
Doctor Chandler sacrificed himself
to stop it from spreading.
All right, I want to get out of here.
Yeah, I want... I want to go.
I... I'm cold, I'm hungry,
and I'm tired of you gung-ho mother-fuckers
pretending you got this shit under control.
Quit acting like a little bitch.
-He's right.
-What?
It is cold.
It's coming from somewhere over here.
Behind this door.
-It's freezing.
-Go on.
scream if he moves, rookie.
Mommy?
Over here.
This way, Mommy.
Doc. Where have you been?
Do you believe, Yoshi?
-Do I believe what?
-What you see, what you feel.
sometimes our faith changes who we are.
sometimes who we are changes our faith.
What are you doing?
Come in. Look.
-You can see her?
-Of course I see your unborn child.
she's beautiful.
I told you it was cold.
-What am I looking at?
-The wrath of God.
You might not believe this, Father,
but you are expendable.
And I'm about two seconds away
from expending your brains
all over this floor
if you don't tell me what the hell that is.
-A nephilim.
-A what?
A nephilim.
Go on, Father, tell him where it's from.
Was he down here studying spacemen?
It's not from space.
-Yeah? What is it, then?
-An angel.
Not an angel from heaven,
an angel cast from heaven.
An angel at war with God.
Nephilim are present
in almost every religion.
In the Bible, the Torah.
Even obscure scriptures
make reference to them.
Genesis speaks of the sons of God
coming to earth and assuming human form.
They corrupted mankind.
Ignored the boundaries
of their own domain,
until God passed his judgment
and wiped the slate clean.
started over.
Imprisoned them in tombs like this.
That's not ice. It's the hand of God.
That's why the adjurists are here.
-The what?
-The adjurists. A group with one purpose.
To find the fallen angels
and exorcise their evil.
They sacrifice themselves
to absorb the nephilim spirit,
to make sure that they never escape again.
-Like that?
-Exactly. But we were too late.
We found dozens of them down here.
But not like this one. It's evil.
He's in Wesley.
Why didn't you tell me any of this before?
You are on the front line of the biggest
battle mankind has ever fought, Captain.
-Besides, would you have believed me?
-Bullshit.
-ls this a dream?
-It's a gift.
It's a chance to make things better.
I didn't have a choice.
Not if I wanted to stay with the team.
-With Marcus.
-With me.
seeing her hurts.
I know. But you don't have to hurt anymore.
You don't have to hide your pain.
Or your desires.
What are you doing?
Why'd you drag us down here?
Why couldn't you just bring this thing up
to the surface and pick it apart up there?
You're not listening. That's what they want.
To be free from the tomb that God created.
The fools never listen.
They'll come to you in ways
you can't imagine,
Iike a wife, a lover, a child.
Child? Yoshi.
Yoshi?
-she's gone, Mack.
-Click. Click.
Get Yoshi back here AsAP. Hammer.
I know your pain, Yoshi.
My sister, she trusted me.
The tumor on her spine, it was so small,
but I didn't get it all.
And the cancer ate her up
from the inside out.
I won't let that happen again.
Is this the way out?
-ls this the way out?
-Yes.
-What's on the other side of this door?
-The possessed.
Besides the possessed,
you simple son of a...
-I have no idea.
-How come I don't believe that?
-Click.
-Yeah?
-Get this door open, we're leaving.
-Thank God.
-What the hell happened?
-Bad day at the office. We lost Wilcox.
Everybody outside.
-How much longer?
-Just another couple of seconds.
It's clear?
-so we can go now, man.
-Easy.
-We leave when I say we leave.
-Man, we got to get out of here.
Where the fuck is Hammer, you know?
Hammer.
Yoshi.
Mary, Mother of God.
Hammer.
-Hicks, what the fuck are you doing, man?
-Don't let him hurt me, Marcus.
I know where Yoshi is. she needs you.
-she's one of them.
-she's one of us.
Don't you get it?
This is what the priest said.
she's fucking with your head.
Put your weapon down, that's an order.
-I can't do that.
-No!
Doc?
-What are you doing?
-I'm not checking out
unless I got proof
of what you people are doing down here.
Nothing can leave from here.
Lady, quit holding him up, okay?
I mean, I'm not waiting here
for more of these moaning mother-fuckers
to bust in.
Fuck. Hammer...
Get her off of me!
Move!
Come on, Click.
-Hey, Captain.
-What happened?
It's Hicks. He's gone completely loco.
-He just shot at me.
-Why?
I saw Doc. she looked like one of them.
It doesn't look good, boss.
-It's not much better here.
-shit.
There's more fuckers out there, Mack,
and they're probably coming this way.
Are you all right?
Look at me. Does it look like I'm all right?
I mean, this is some shit-covered,
marshmallow kind of evil
that I did not sign on for.
-Take a seat, soldier.
-I ain't no fucking soldier, okay?
I mean, I shouldn't even be here.
Click, sit.
You know, I got you down here,
and I opened up your Gehenna files.
You told me I'd be safe,
I don't feel fucking safe anymore.
Oh, God. Oh, God, you did it, didn't you?
Holy Jesus,
now I understand why you're here.
To access Gehenna.
Hey, hey, Father! Hey, Father!
What was he talking about?
Yoshi.
-Yoshi.
-Marcus.
Marcus.
-Jesus.
-Help me.
Come here.
I found her.
I found our baby, and I held her in my arms.
-What?
-she has your smile.
Calm down, baby.
Everything's going to be okay. I'm here now.
-Who did this to you?
-Doc.
she's helping me.
Well, I'm here now,
I'm going to take you, okay?
Okay. It's my back.
I... I don't know if I can walk.
Is it bad?
sorry, Marcus.
Do you want some help with that?
I asked you a question.
What was he talking about?
-The explosive rigs by the elevator.
-What about them?
Wesley's team didn't disarm them.
They installed them,
in case something like this happened.
-Come again?
-To incinerate everything.
-so you pushed a button?
-How long?
Hey, how long?
Twenty-nine minutes, 32 seconds.
It's counting down.
I don't get it, why would you...
Why would you detonate it
before the shuttle's due back?
How are we supposed to get out of here?
We weren't.
This never was about getting Wesley out,
was it?
You were sent here to make sure
that he doesn't. That none of us do.
You sick bitch.
We should waste you right here, pendeja.
-Why not blow this place from the surface?
-I couldn't. Wesley changed the code.
-Then how did you activate it?
-I didn't. He did.
No, no, no, you did not just say that.
I needed a really good hacker
to pull the trigger.
I didn't know. I didn't know.
You used us.
I did what I had to do. Did what I was told.
If anyone should understand that, it's you.
How do we shut it off?
Only from the surface,
and only with the code.
What's the code, lady?
Weren't you guys listening?
Wesley is all Four Horsemen rolled into one.
He hits the surface,
what's happening down here
will be happening everywhere,
and there will not be any way to stop it.
-Give me the code.
-Get that thing out of my face.
Give me the goddamn code!
It's not going to work.
she's not afraid to die. Are you?
-I've been ready for this since I was born.
-Fuck.
My father trained me.
so this whole ClA thing was just a cover?
More like a means to an end.
You completed your mission
before we even got in the elevator.
Why still go looking for Wesley?
shit.
so what do we do
if we can't find our way back?
One problem at a time.
If anyone can hear this,
you got 15 minutes to get the elevator
before you're a permanent resident
in this hell hole.
-Come on, go!
-Let's move.
-Come on.
-Mack, I can't hold it.
-Come on! Come on!
I can't hold it.
-Come on!
Go!
-You're a soldier now, man.
-Come on, Captain!
It's an honor, boss.
We got to go, sir. We got to go!
Go, go, go, go, go!
Come on!
Father, let me help you.
Bye, Father.
Which way? Which...
-Don't tempt me.
-This way, Captain, this way.
shit. Eyes on me, Click.
We're almost out of here.
Elissa.
-Dad.
-shit.
What little is left of your father
is very sorry to see you here.
You look just like your mother.
I'm surprised they sent you.
You're not ready. I thought I was ready.
But I was just a child as you are now.
What's happening to him?
Why doesn't he look like the others?
The nephilim is inside of him.
We can't let him leave, Mack.
Why is he still here?
I'm waiting for you
to follow your orders, Mack.
My time in this skin suit is almost over.
I need for you to bring me
a new set of clothes.
Yeah, right.
Remember what you said when you arrived?
You told your friends, "You find Wesley
and we get the hell out of here."
Well, you have no idea how right you were.
Hey.
Nickels.
I got your message, man,
and I'm ready to roll.
-Don't you fucking move.
-Click, lock and load.
Now.
Click! Click!
-Click!
-Captain!
Click.
Click, Click, Click?
You look like shit.
I never felt better.
You know,
you and I aren't that different, really.
Both of us bred
to do the dirty work of bosses
who will never truly appreciate our skills.
You'd make a great angel.
I am ready.
Baby, you're a very, very naughty girl.
-Jesus.
-stop name-dropping, Mack.
Well, if you won't let me in,
how about someone you actually care for?
We could try your ex-wife,
the one who left you.
Or maybe the daughter
you never got to see grow up.
Or how about someone special,
like your best friend?
-How you doing, Mack?
-Blakeley.
I heard you ended up with the angels.
That's a pretty good tradeoff.
But I got to be honest with you,
I'm not too impressed
with your leadership skills.
Pretend to be whoever you want to be,
I know you're not real.
Really? You've had a memory of me,
of what you did, for the past five years.
If that don't make me real, you're crazy.
Mack, do you know the seven deadly sins?
Man's roadmap to his failures.
Guilt isn't a sin,
but in your case maybe it should be.
It wasn't my call.
You don't remember what happened. Why?
You never did answer that question, Mack.
What are you doing?
-Why did you do it, Mack?
-I did what I was told.
What a good little soldier.
You ever stop to think they might be wrong?
Did you really have to do me in
to shut me up?
I did what I was told to do.
What makes you think
one more would make a difference?
Do you know how many millions have died
in these deserts
in the name of the Father and the son?
But they couldn't do it without
people like us to carry out their plans.
People who blindly trust their actions
to others.
Lie, deceive.
I never believed in the Father or the son.
You weren't chosen by chance.
We knew you'd do what you were told.
And do it well.
You are on the front line...
We can't let him leave, Mack.
Why did you do it, Mack?
All right, maybe I am going crazy.
Let me show you the way, Mack.
I knew you wouldn't let me down again.
I knew it.
-Maybe God does have a plan.
-God?
Don't talk to me about God.
He gives you pathetic creatures
the gift of choice, and what do you do?
You use it to turn your back on him
first chance you get.
You chose to take this mission.
You chose to kill your best friend.
You chose to seek me out.
Thank God for free will.
Yeah. Thank God.
Dad?
-We have to go. Now.
-I can't go.
-What have you done?
-What I was trained to do.
To free my father's soul,
that was my mission.
You have to leave.
-I'm not going to leave you like this.
-You have to leave me like this.
You understand.
No. But I believe you.
For the first time, I know my purpose.
My place in the world.
I have a new mission, bigger than myself.
I'm a new soldier in a very old war.