- Okay. Lets go.
Barks
Hey! Hey! Hey!
Hey!
Another ticket.
Damn!
Parking on the wrong side
of the street?
This is a Ford Dyslexia!
Barking
Its gonna be a great day today,
Jerry Lee. Come on.
Man
Park it over there.
Jerry Lee Barking,
Growling
Man
What? What? What? Its bank day.
All right, I know were here
to get some Kibble money.
I’m gonna go to that ATM machine
and get some cash.
Stay here and watch my car. I spent
a lot of money restoring this car.
- You protect my car.
Whining
And don’t
change the music.
Stay.
Don’t bite my-
Watch for bad guys
near my car.
Woman When’s your car gettin´
done? Man Wednesday, I think.
Woman What a hassle. Man Yeah.
ATM Beeping
"Checking, savings. "
No savings, checking.
"Smoker, nonsmoker?"
Nonsmoker.
"Democrat, Republican?"
Democrat.
Man
Didn’t I tell you to stay in the car?
Get in the car.
Good boy.
Jerry Lee Barking
Get down!
Police! Get down!
Police!
Down, get down!
No, not here.
Not by my car! Oh, man.
Guard Code Red! Code
Red! Were under fire.
Repeat, were pinned down
and under fire.
Some partner you are.
Why didn’t you warn me, at least?
Guard Is this guy after the money,
or is he just pissed at your car?
Can you reload, please?
Thank you.
Gunfire Continues
My speaker!
My stereo.
Were gonna take this guy out.
You cover us,
and don’t be afraid
to use the gun!
Come on, Jerry Lee!
Hey, come on.
Open up.
Come on.
Shut the door.
Okay, so I forgot.
Its a bulletproof window.
All right, you son of a bitch,
we both have armor now.
We got him.
No, no, not the running thing.
I hate the running thing.
- Lets go.
Growling
Jerry Lee Barking
Grunting
Coughing
Grunting, Groaning
Jerry Lee Barking
- Jerry Lee!
Panting
Man
Jerry Lee!
Moaning, Gasping
Come on.
Jerry Lee, come on!
Screams
Aah!
Motor Revving
Jerry Lee Barking
Damn it!
Grunting
Whining
Groaning
Hey!
He’s gone.
Coughing
Why didn’t you jump?
Come on.
Whining - What do you
mean- Imitates Whining
What, are you leavin
it all for me? Huh?
Christ, what’s with you lately?
What’s with you?
- We almost had that guy.
Whining
Panting
You know why cops have dogs?
So they don’t have to do this!
That’s the deal.
Management, labor.
Foreman, employee.
Boss, secretary.
I walk, you run.
I cuff’em, you catch ´’em.
You get treats, I get a promotion.
Gasping
I cant breathe!
My car! Jerry Lee,
look what he did to my car!
Look what they did!
I couldn’t even sell it
to a cheese factory.
Hey, Dooley!
Check this out.
Its a modified M-16.
A company called...
Armaments 2000s
doin´ the retrofit.
Its supposed to be
for military use only.
- Where did you hear that?
- I saw it in a gun magazine.
- Did you pick that up on the street?
- Yeah.
- Are you supposed to be messin’ with evidence?
- No.
Give me that.
Go get me some coffee.
Well, Jerry Lee, so much
for the Brady Bill, huh?
- Dooley? What are you doing here?
- Hi, Captain.
Sighs
What happened?
Uh, well, there was a,
uh, equipment failure.
- Equipment failure?
- The bad guy had Air Jordan’s on. It was no contest.
What about Jerry Lee?
He needs four little Air Jordan’s too?
- You mean they make those for dogs?
- That was a rhetorical question.
You know, Captain, you should let people
know when you plan to be rhetorical,
cause your tone of voice
never changes.
- You think you’re funny?
- Sometimes.
- This isn’t one of those times.
- Jerry Lee, he just hit me!
- Quit bein’ a smart-ass. Tell
me what happened. - Again!
The bad guy had
a full body armor on.
- That should have given you the advantage.
- It was that lightweight stuff.
What can I tell you?
The guy had a rocket up his ass.
- What the hell is that?
- This here?
Uh, this was the shooters.
This is a modified M-16.
A company named Armaments 2000
does the retrofit.
Its apparently
for military use only.
- How do you know all that?
- I’m trying to better myself by taking night seminars.
Ah, shut up, will you?
You better sit down. You look pale.
- Probably because you hit me.
- And give that dog there a drink of water.
Jerry Lee is fine,
and so am I.
You don’t look fine.
Sit down before you fall down.
- Now. Detective Harris?
- Yes.
- Its the smog!
- Take this to the lab and check it for prints, okay?
You know, Dooley,
every time you go someplace lately,
people try to kill you.
- Well, I’m a popular guy.
- Look, I’m serious here.
- You’ve lost three suspects
in three weeks! - Come-
- You are either out of your league...
- I am not out of my league.
- or you’ve lost a step.
- What are you talking about, "lost a step"?
You should have taken
time off after Tracy died.
- That has nothing to do with it, Captain.
- Oh. Are you sure?
Absolutely sure.
When was the last time
you had a physical?
Physical. Is that the blood pressure,
when they do the-
Laughs, Whimpers
I want you both checked out.
You understand me?
I obviously cant
count on you anymore.
Hey!
What about my car?
Have your detailer look at it.
He can probably rub it out.
Rub it out?
I guess I can drive it at night.
Nobody’ll see it.
Come on, Jerry Lee.
Come on, get in.
My poor car.
Sighs
- Aw, he got my cup holder too.
Barks
Motor Starting
Woman
I’m so sorry we’re late.
Man Its okay, I haven’t been waiting long,
and thank you very much for meeting me.
Dooley
Ah, you know what? Its my fault.
Woman Devon Lane, this is
my husband, Detective Dooley.
Dooley Nice to meet you. Devon
Oh, the pleasure is all mine.
Devon I’m so excited
- Dooley Can we get some drinks over here?
- "De
-vawn," you want a beer? Devon Its Devon.
Dooley Devon. Sorry. What’s
with the tape recorder?
Devon I’m a writer. I tape
everything. Tracy Devon,
I just want to say that I see
real potential in your work.
Devon Potential? Really? Tracy Oh, yeah.
He’s been a cop a long time. Maybe he
can help you with some of that cop stuff.
Devon Would you? Dooley Well,
yeah, sure. You okay, honey?
Tracy Ill be fine. I’ll be
back in a few minutes. Excuse me.
Devon
Tracy told me you read my manuscript.
Dooley Yeah, I did. I
didn’t read the whole thing.
I read the first
and the last chapter.
That’s really
all I had time for.
Devon The first and last
chapters? Dooley I gotta tell ya,
uh, its-
it wasn’t really that real.
Devon It wasn’t real? Dooley No, it wasn’t
real. I didn’t believe a lot of the-
all that cop stuff you have in there-
the shootouts and the bank robbery.
That’s not really
how it happens.
Devon It wasn’t real? Dooley That’s all
right. It’s your first attempt, man.
Don’t worry about it.
You’ll get there.
Woman Any loss of appetite?
- No, I’m eatin´ pretty well.
- Not you, the dog.
- Oh, uh-
No, he’s fine.
- Okay, I’m gonna increase the speed and incline.
- Why?
Thuds
- Well, that’s the standard test for canines, Detective.
Oh.
Jerry Lee Whining
- What?
I can hold the handrail.
Humans can hold the handrail.
All right,
all right, all right.
Have you noticed
any changes in him?
Yeah, he doesn’t chase the little chuck
wagon across the kitchen floor anymore.
Any loss of hearing
or smell?
Well, that depends on
what you mean by "any. "
Well, maybe sometimes,
a little bit.
- Well, there’s nothing wrong with your dog.
- Really?
He’s just suffering
from the effects of aging.
- You should slow him down a bit.
- Why?
Would you send your grandfather out
to try and do your job?
I wouldn’t send my grandfather
to microwave popcorn.
- So why would you send out Jerry Lee?
- Cause my grandfather’s too old.
- So is Jerry Lee.
- What do you mean? Look at him. He looks great.
Do you know that dogs are leading
longer and healthier lives these days?
- Where did you hear that?
- Seminar. At night. I try to better myself.
Oh, you’re trying to better yourself?
Maybe you should get a checkup.
You’ve got high blood pressure.
Your face is bright red.
That is a drinking problem!
Well, what do you know?
You’re a vet.
You both need to be
on special diets.
- The same one? - No. You should
be on a low-fat, low-sodium diet.
The dog needs to be on
a senior maintenance meal plan.
Whining
- What the hells that?
Lamb and rice
for older dogs.
It might give him some flatulence for a
week or so, but nothing to worry about.
Sighs Nothing for you to worry
about. I gotta live with the damn dog.
- You trying to be funny?
- No.
I forgot my wallet,
so can I write a check?
Do I get
any free samples?
Jerry Lee Whining
- Senior maintenance.
Hey, your day.
You checked out great.
You just, uh-
- You’re out of shape.
Whines
Come on. Lets go.
Come on.
Lets jump.
Barking
Grunts
Come on!
Hey, hey.
Come here, you. Come on.
Barking
Come on, just do it.
Ow! Ow!
- Come on!
Jerry Lee Whining
Jump, jump, jump!
Hey!
What are you doing on my spot?
Whining
That’s my spot.
Here.
Whines
That’ll make
you feel better.
You all right?
What’s the matter
with your lamb and rice?
You don’t like it?
Here.
Huh? Here.
How’s that?
Nothin´,, huh?
Telephone Ringing
- But this is good for us.
Think we should
work out every day.
- Very tribal.
Ringing Continues
Yeah, some insurance company you are. I
called the office three hours ago about my car-
Hey! Jeez!
Jerry Lee! Come here.
Lie down. Down.
Man
I just saved you 300 calories.
- Who is this?
- You should be drinking light beer.
Less filling,
and it wont slow you down.
And Dooley, you better pay attention
to the "wont slow you down" part.
I could have beat you
running backwards, old man.
- What do you want?
- Don’t tell me you haven’t figured it out yet, Detective.
Three times
in three weeks, Dooley.
I could have taken you out
anytime I wanted.
I want you to know how it feels to have
someone else control your destiny.
- Jerry, down!
- How it feels to have someone else destroy your life.
- What do you want?
- Its hard to lose a loved one.
Isn’t it, Dooley? But then,
sometimes life just has a way...
of kicking you in the face,
just when you think you’ve got it made.
Hey, why don’t you
come in.
You and I, we can have
a beer, we can chat.
And then
Ill bust your ass.
You’re in no position, literally,
to start playin´ bad guy, Dooley.
Growling, Barking
Motorcycle Engine Revving
Dooley ... about my car. Hey! Jeez!
- Jerry Lee! Come here. - "Chapter
Six. Spoon-fed information by our hero,
Detective Dooley finally
figures out he is the target.
But he still
has no idea why.
Dooley’s Voice Who is this?
- Life is about to get a little more real. "
Man On Tape I could have beat
you running backwards, old man.
Don’t tell me you haven’t
figured it out yet, Detective.
Three times
in three weeks, Dooley.
I could have taken you out
anytime I wanted.
Dooley Well, at least we
know now were being set up.
Now, if we could just keep
Byers off our back.
- You let me do the talkin, huh?
Jerry Lee Growls
Oh, am I sore.
Groans
Okay.
Dooley How are you
feelin’? Come here. Barking
Come on. Stay with me.
You know what, Jerry Lee?
That vet was wrong.
Were not getting old.
Were getting sexier
and better and wiser.
Barks
Chattering
Man
Everybody duck. Its Dooley.
Don’t listen to him.
Whining
- Lay down, Jerry Lee.
Whines
- What’s with him?
What?
He’s not a morning dog.
Listen, last night the shooter called.
Took a shot at me.
- Hit my beer.
- Why didn’t you call it in?
I got another beer. But wait a minute,
he said something weird.
Something really strange. He said, "Its
hard to lose a loved one, isn’t it?"
- Is he talkin about Tracy?
- I don’t know.
Could be anything. Could be a revenge
act, it could be somebody I know.
- I-I-I don’t know.
- Harry Stipe. Harry Stipe.
He swore that he would get you
after what happened to his brother!
- No, Harry Stipes doin´ five to ten.
- Not anymore. He got paroled.
- Harry Stipe is out?
- Yeah, it just came in.
- Stipe is out, and nobody told me?
- Just came across my desk.
- Give me the parole officers name. I want his address.
- Not so fast, Dooley.
- Come on! Give it to me.
- Sit.
Whines
There’s some guy out there gunnin´ for you.
You’re not going anywhere alone anymore.
- Not this again.
- Welles, get in here.
- Welles?
- And bring Zeus with you!
- Zeus?
Snarling
Growling
- Hey, whoa-ho-ho!
Meet your new partners.
No way!
- You’re not gonna actually let them in here, are you?
- I certainly am.
- Detective Dooley.
- Officer Welles.
- Sergeant Welles now.
- Oh. Sorry, I didn’t know.
- Good, you two know each other.
- Yeah, we had a moment a little while ago.
- Before he, uh
- Coughs Mumbling
Look, I don’t see what that dog
has gotta do that Jerry Lee can’t do.
Zeus!
Speaking Dutch
Very impressive, Welles.
- Dooley?
- What?
He was trained
in anti-terrorist tactics.
Could he go into a mini-mart
and pick up a six-pack of beer?
He attacks through windows.
Well, Jerry Lee
has mastered Windows 98.
Got his own chat room.
"Dogs for Dogs"?
Shouting In Dutch
Jerry Lee
can do that.
- You can do that, cant you?
Whining
Captain? I really don’t
think this is a good idea.
- I couldn’t agree more with her.
- Dooley shouldn’t even have that dog.
He’s not trained as a canine officer.
He’s a dog with a pet.
Growls
- Ooh! Aren’t we a little moody?
- Zeus and I can handle this case alone.
I got news for you. Once I get a
parolees address, this case is closed.
Then I got news for you.
A parolee doesn’t even fit the profile.
Profile? What is this,
an Olympic moment?
- This is a police investigation here.
- Really? I wouldn’t have guessed.
You don’t need a profile
to catch a bad guy.
All you need is a good cop
with good instincts.
I’m glad you said "good cop,"
because so far, your instincts suck!
You two are gonna
get along great.
Dooley, I need to talk to you alone.
No offense, Sergeant.
No offense
taken, Captain.
See you outside,
partner.
Hey! If you’re
gonna ride with me,
get out of that uniform and
be on my desk in five minutes.
- "At. " He meant "at. "
- No, I meant "at. "
"At. "
At my desk.
- "At. "
Muttering In Dutch
What is wrong with you? Didn’t you go
to the sexual harassment seminar?
I missed that one.
I was- I was at another seminar.
All right, forget about it.
Shell probably be cool about it.
- Ah, look. Put Jerry Lee outside.
- H-He cant testify.
- Look, just have him wait outside.
- He can keep a secret!
- Have him wait outside!
- All right. Come on, Jerry.
Uh, I got a delivery
for, uh, Detective Dooley.
Sign, please.
- Uh, there’s a complementary card in there.
- Thank you.
I saw the vet report
today, and uh,
Sighs
- you need to-
Dooley What? Jerry Lee Whines
You better give
some serious th-
- You need to give thought to getting a newer dog.
- What?
- Well, one like Zeus. Yes.
- Zeus?
That crazy, psycho dog?
Are you kiddin’ me?
He wouldn’t last five minutes
with me- I’d kill him!
Look, he probably
doesn’t even drink.
I don’t need a new dog. You know what
I need is a bigger gun- one like this.
- Will you put that away, you idiot?
- Or one like this.
- Where did you get this? This-This is
L.A., not Dallas. - How about this one?
Look, I got a guy out there
with an M-16 takin’ shots at me,
and all I got...
is this.
Dooley, firearms, that’s not
the problem. The problem is Jerry Lee.
- What?
- Well, if he misses a step, you could lose your life.
Don’t you understand? That’s why
I’m giving you both new partners.
I read that vet report.
The vet report said you were in the best
shape you’ve ever been in your life.
Alert. Responsive.
He’s a killer!
You’re a stud dog,
Jerry Lee.
Whines
- See?
You see that?
You see his sly and uncanny way?
He’s pretending to be
asleep so he can pounce.
Good boy, Jerry Lee.
Come on. Lets go.
Come! Jerry.
Hot dogs!
Hamburgers! Chili!
Whining
Hey, Dooley. These flowers
were just delivered for you.
Must have been
a wild night.
"Was last night as good for you
as it was for me?"
- Who gave you these?
- The delivery guy.
- What did he look like?
- Green pants, black belt.
You saw him from
the waist down, that’s it?
- I was sittin’ in- - What are you
doing? Touching evidence again?
Puttin’ your prints
all over this? Listen to me.
- You see these gloves? I want you to wear these things. Forever!
- Yeah.
- Okay.
- Take these down to the lab and have them dusted.
Welles Zeus! Come!
- Come on. Lets go.
That Welles and that stupid psycho dog
is probably sittin up at the desk.
You and I can go get
the bad guys ourselves.
Hey!
We were just looking for you.
- Weren’t we, Jerry?
- Check this out.
If you look at the holes,
they actually spell out something.
It says, "Even though
I’m older and slower,
I’m still the same asshole
as I was before. "
Very funny. That’s very funny.
You think that was funny?
Sighs Come on, Jerry Lee.
- Zeus!
Dutch
I can do that.
All right, look.
I want to get one thing straight...
before we go on here,
all right?
What went on between
you and me is history.
Now, you have got
to let it go.
I don’t even think
about it anymore.
And neither should you.
Okay?
- Okay.
- What do you mean, okay?
- I mean okay.
- Okay, you agree with it,
or okay, you don’t
think about it anymore?
- Okay. I don’t think about it.
- How can you not think about it?
- You said you don’t think about it.
- Well, of course not.
- I mean, Im-I´mm-I´mm-
- But what? What?
What? You’re so irresistible,
how could I not think about it?
- Well-
- Because, you know, it was one night.
- Heat of the moment stuff.
- Absolutely right!
- Right.
- Get in.
Sighing, Swearing
In Dutch
- What was that?
- What? Nothing.
And you, dog, lets get one thing
straight between you and me, all right?
Number one: No barking,
no drooling, no f-
passing of gas...
or performing any bodily functions
in or about my car.
Number two: You always
sit in the back seat.
Number three:
Never give me any lip.
Growling
- That’s negotiable. That’s negotiable.
Just relax.
Jerry Lee, watch him.
Slams Door
Ticket!
Look at that!
I think she follows
me around.
Just put it in
the glove compartment.
Dooley! How many
parking tickets do you have?
- Put’em in the glove compartment and shut it.
- Do you know how to park a car?
- Shut it!
Camera Shutter Clicks
Ugh, I’m gonna need a tetanus shot
from just sitting in this car.
Engine Starts Dooley Were
going to Harry Stripe’s.
Were going to arrest him, and you’ll
never have to see me again, all right?
Fine.
Dooley Your dog likes to look through windows?
- He attacks through windows.
Dooley Yeah, but can
he sing? Welles What?
- Jerry Lee can sing.
Chuckling Yeah, right.
Dooley
Jerry Lee Howling
- Hear that? Come on, Jerry Lee.
Howling Continues
Welles I’m tellin´ ya, he’s
not the guy we’re lookin´ for.
- And how would you know that?
- Because he doesn’t fit the profile.
Profile. Clears Throat Welles,
this is a profile.
A profile is only good when
you’re trying to narrow down suspects.
We need a list
of suspects first.
- Its not him.
- Okay, then. Stay in the car.
- And you too. You stay.
Jerry Lee? Lets go. Growling
We are not staying
in the car.
- Don’t look at me like that.
- Look at you like what?
Not you.
Him.
I got a weapon.
Ill use it.
We are trained K-9 officers.
We don’t do "stay in the car. "
Why don’t you...
and your little puppy
go in through the back?
He’s not a puppy. And why do we have
to go in the back? Why don’t you?
- We don’t do back doors. Come on!
Barking
Muttering In Dutch
Shouts In Dutch
Wow.
Look at this.
You know, I hear they’re
converting this to condos?
If we take some out
of your money market fund,
we can buy one of these
and use it as a rental.
I hear conversions
can be a great investment.
- Condos and- Jesus!
Jerry Lee Barks
I mean, Jesus,
I’m glad you’re here.
Watch our backs, please.
Couple Yelling
- All right, Jerry Lee. Time to go to work.
Wait up.
Come on.
Yelling Continues
In Foreign Language
Softly
Jerry Lee. This is Harry Stipes.
Remember?
Come here.
Whispers
Sit down.
Whining
Where is she now?
We should have went around back.
Barking
Man Groaning
What’s the matter, Harry?
I hit ya?
Harry You son of a bitch!
You ruined my best pants, man!
Ooh, you got
a potty-mouth there, buddy!
You kiss your mom
with that mouth?
Throw out the shotgun,
and any other weapons.
- And don’t forget any.
Thumping
I got Jerry Lee
here with me.
- You know what hell do if he
finds them! Thumping, Crashing
Hey, listen, man. You just keep
that dog away from me, all right?
I don’t want to deal
with Jerry Lee again, man.
You know, last time we met,
it wasn’t a good thing.
Jesus, Harry.
- What, are you planning to go back to night school?
- I need a little protection.
- You know what I’m saying, man?
- Is that everything?
Jerry Lee Growling
- Yeah.
- Okay, Jerry Lee.
Barking Fiercely
- Oh! Oh! Hey, man, you get that dog away from me, man.
- Back it up, Harry.
Easy, Jerry Lee. Easy.
Check it out. Back up, Harry.
- Hold it right there. Stipe
Easy, doggie. Calm down.
- Shh!
- So, where you been lately, Harry?
- Shootin at armored cars? Makin´
midnight calls? Welles Zeus!
- What?
- Step away from the window, Harry.
- Huh?
- The window, Harry. Step away.
All right, man.
Shrieking
Whimpering
- So, where were you yesterday?
- What do you mean, man? I was right here.
- Don’t lie to me, Harry.
- I’m not lyin´ to you, man.
Look, you see this?
Its not a social beeper.
Its a house arrest bracelet.
It’s like a LoJack on my leg.
It goes off,
everybody’s here.
Cops, SWAT team,
my parole officer, everybody!
A- All right, okay.
Let me see your parole papers.
I’m really happy you’re here, man,
I gotta tell you. And you too.
They’re out there
and they want to kill me.
They want to kill me.
Here you go, give it to him.
Shudders
Ooh! Hey, easy.
- Thank you, Jerry.
- Hey, man, you know what?
- I want to thank you for putting my brother in.
- Where’d you get the gun?
Oh! They were here when I moved in!
Oh, really? I didn’t see the sign
when I came in: "Free cable and ammo. "
- Oh, yeah. There’s a sign.
- Jerry Lee?
Fat Tommy, man.
Fat Tommy got’em for me.
- I thought you couldn’t leave the place.
- He delivers.
So, if he didn’t make it
in 30 minutes, you get free ammo?
Hey, you know,
I didn’t think about that.
- Fat Tommy get military weapons too?
- Oh, yeah. Military stuff.
He’s got everything, man.
He’s got a big-time supplier.
- Who?
- I don’t know.
- Police, freeze!
- Aah!
I heard gunshots!
Wait. Where’s my dog?
- Dog? What dog?
Whining
Great instincts, Dooley.
So, what now, big guy?
Dooley You know, after battle,
dogs and men like a treat.
Jerry Lee was good,
so he gets a treat!
Where’s he goin´?
Uh, he knows
its treat time.
- I cant believe you’re going
to feed your dog this.
Surest way to kill him
is with this garbage.
He should be eating nothing
but senior maintenance.
You know what? I tried that senior
maintenance. I liked it. I mean, with a beer.
Whimpering
I don’t have any money.
I forgot my wallet at the station.
- You got $30 on you?
- Figures. Yes.
Whining
Zeus Barking
- Hey! What’s with your dog?
- What? He’s fine.
- I don’t think he likes me.
Barking
- What? What’s with this guy?
- He has to go to the rest room.
- Oh. Oh, to be a dog.
- Excuse us.
No, no. He wants some privacy.
Do you mind?
- The dog?
- The dog.
- Thank you.
- I like it myself sometimes.
Excuse me? Excuse me.
Have you seen
a white poodle?
- White?
- Mm-hmm.
Inhales Deeply
No. Mm-mm.
Hurry up!
Jerry Lee Whining
- Where’s your dog?
- Jerry Lee? Jerry Lee!
Panting
- Hey, what language is it
that you speak to that dog?
Dutch.
He was trained in the Netherlands.
Oh, the Netherlands!
Scuse me!
Jerry Lee
was trained in Oxnard.
You know, the best K-9 dogs
come from Oxnard.
I could learn so much
from you, Dooley.
God, I hate it when people
don’t pick up after their dogs!
Breed their dogs
in the park.
They don’t take care. They breed dogs
in the park. That’s the worst thing-
Groaning
Dooley! What the hell are you doing?
Have you lost your mind?
- Jesus, do you always throw women around the park?
- Stupid kid.
Screaming
Let go. Tell the mutt get off.
- Clog! Heineken! Heineken!
Oppenheimer. Dutch Schultz! Sighing
- Come on, let go. Let go!
- Zeus! Speaking Dutch
Moaning
- Moron.
Dutch
Groaning
- My shirt. He wrecked my shirt.
Welles Cursing In Dutch
Jerry Lee!
Groans
Shit!
Where have you been? What,
did you take her out to dinner too?
Come on,
I got your hot dog.
Scoffs
You get lucky, I get shit.
Come on.
What took you so long?
Dooley Hey, Welles, give me a
- I thought he was gonna shoot ya.
Welles What? A kid with a
toy gun was gonna shoot me?
Welles Continues,
Indistinct
Checkmate.
Welles Why are we parking
all the way out here?
I don’t want anybody
bangin´ my doors.
Banging your doors?
Your doors are all shot up.
- Don’t be so negative.
- Oh, Zeus. Dutch
- Come on.
- Hey, Jerry Lee. Come here.
Sniffing
What is that smell?
- Smell?
- Oh!
Yelling, Chattering
Mikey.
What’s up, man?
Excuse me.
Knocking
- Hello!
- You know where Fat Tommy is?
- Never heard of him.
- Fat. Tommy. Big guy.
- Never heard of him!
He’s big. He’s got a big belly.
Is he at brunch now?
- Don’t know who you’re talking about.
- Buffet? Lunch? Dinner?
- Nope.
- Come on, you must have seen him walkin down the street.
- With a light on him, he looked like a fire truck?
- Never.
Jerry Lee, you hear that?
He never heard of Fat Tommy.
Thanks, man.
Nice haircut.
Jerry Lee Whining
- What?
I can do that.
Keep your elbows up.
Little higher.
That’s it, that’s it. Yeah.
Jerry Lee Whining
Gonna get some tape.
Gotta wrap the tape.
Inhales Sharply
All right, everybody. Listen up!
Yo! Listen up!
Yo! I’m talkin´
to you, Rocky!
I’m lookin´
for the Fat Man.
Oh, I didn’t know this was "I’m not
talkin´ to the cop" day. I understand.
Hel-lo!
That’s quite a command
you have there, Dooley.
Well, smarty-pants,
I thought maybe Id let you and the
psycho dog, you know, do a little work.
I think we will.
Zeus!
Shouts In Dutch
Fight Bell Ringing
Zeus Growling
Panicky Shouting
Man Shouting
Come on, lady, call your dog off!
You know, your dog
has some real control issues.
Think you should
work with him at it.
- You know.
Zeus Growling
Dutch
Man
Whose mutt is this?
Okay. Now watch
some real police work.
Man
Get this dog outta here!
What the hell are you idiots
doin up there?
Hey, Fat Tommy,
how ya doin?
Keep that dog
away from me!
Wow! Look at you!
You’ve lost a lot of weight.
You’re lookin´ good,
Fat Tommy!
- What, did you have your stomach stapled?
- Keep that dog away from me.
Ill sue you
this time, I will.
You might have to, unless you tell me
who’s sellin´ the M-16 retrofit.
I don’t know what you’re talkin´ about.
I’m a legitimate businessman.
Say hello to Jackie Hammer.
Maybe you heard of him.
They call him
"Fists of Steel. "
He’s the super middleweight
kickboxing champion.
He’s the ultimate
fightin´ champ.
I don’t get that
pay-per-view, you know?
I’m sure he’s very good. I’m very
impressed. You impressed, Jerry Lee?
Show him, Jackie.
Shouting, Yelling
Fat Tommy
Jackie, stay away from that dog.
Hey, Fat Tommy, what are you
worried about? He’s a good doggie.
Ooh!
Good thing your boys
got a cup on, huh?
- Otherwise, he’d be known as
Little Jackie Hammer. Whimpering
I bet you got a lot
of money on this guy, huh?
What kind of a psycho would teach
a dog to do something like that?
Actually, he taught himself.
Jerry Lee.
Crowd Groaning, Moaning
Yelling
- Yah!
The name, fat man,
or the boy loses his nuts.
Speaking In A High Voice
Tell him. Please.
- Phil Cage.
- Phil Cage? As in, "Phil’s Salvage Yard"?
- Yeah.
- Jerry Lee.
You can let go now.
Jerry!
Whimpering
By the way, you look good.
You’ve lost a lot of weight.
- Keep it up.
- Thanks, Dooley. I’m in the zone.
Yeah, its
workin´ for you.
Fat Tommy I told you guys never
to get caught in the corner.
- What was all that Kung Fu crap about?
- It wasn’t Kung Fu.
It was Krav Maga.
God, Dooley, get out of the 70s.
Zeus and I trained for two months
at the Israeli Defense Force.
Oh, yeah? What did they feed him?
"Kibbutz n´ Bits"?
Ah, "Kibbutz n´ Bits. "
Did you like that?
Come on, now, I know you thought that
was funny. You’re laughing inside.
You shouldn’t hold it in like that.
It’s not good for your health.
Boxers Chattering
Coins Clattering,
Phone Dinging
Phil’s Salvage.
This is Phil speaking.
Dooley and the police
are raiding your place in ten minutes.
Who is this?
Hangs Up Receiver
Dial Tone
Get the boys,
get the money,
get the guns, we gotta
get the hell out of here.
Welles Whistles
This is the perfect place for your car.
- Shall I call and have a
black-and-white pick us up? Chuckles
Very funny. Cute.
Almost quaint.
Engine Rattles, Stops
- I’m gonna go and talk to Phil.
- I want you to stay in the car.
- What?
- Stay!
- I’m not a dog.
Well, that’s obvious. Dogs listen.
Guffaws
This time,
were going in the front.
- Fine! Its your choice!
- Oh, you’re actually giving me a choice?
- Yeah. Front, back?
- Well take the front.
- Fine.
- No, no, no, no, no. I see what you’re doing here.
- What do you want?
- I want the front.
- Then well take the front.
- FinI’lllll take the back.
- What happened to "Jerry Lee and I don’t do back doors"?
- I’m trying to compromise, dear.
- You want the back?
- Yes.
- Then well take the back.
- Fine. I’ll take the front.
No way! That’s what you wanted me to say,
and that’s what you wanted me to take.
- Well take the front.
- Fine! Take the front!
- I don’t care!
- Sure you don’t. We’ll take the back.
- Zeus! Whispering Bad dog. Bad dog.
Works every time. Come on.
Chuckles
All right.
Keep your eyes open, Jer.
Man That you, Dooley?
- Yeah, its me, Phil.
Hey, Phil. What’s goin´ on here?
I thought you went legit.
Oh, I could bullshit you, Dooley,
but the truth is, its easy money.
Zeus Growling
- Come on!
- Those new guns, Phil?
- How do you like’em?
Well, from this point of view,
they’re quite impressive.
You know, Phil,
this is your third strike.
- They’re gonna throw away the key.
- Why do you think I’m shootin´?
- Its nothin´ personal.
- That’s nice to hear.
- That’s very caring, loving and supportive.
- I had a good mother.
- Zeus, stay!
Growls
Oh, boy.
- Dance! Dance!
Screaming
- Dance!
- Ah, what is life if not to dance!
Screams
Growling, Barking
Phil Screaming
- What kind of piece you usin’?
- 9mm, standard issue.
- Yeah, I could set you up with something special.
- Yeah?
Tell me about
that M-16 retrofit.
Chuckles
Little too pricey for you, Dooley.
- You got any names?
- I didn’t ask it!
- You know what he looked like?
- I wasn’t looking at his face, I was looking at the money.
I’m sure he looked like your average,
creepy kind of gun nut.
- A lot like you!
- Well, Phil, you’re gonna need that sense of humor...
when they lock you away
for the rest of your life...
Wearin’ that
cute little sun dress.
Whispers Okay. Whining
Screaming
- You cook too?
- A lot of takeout.
Cuff him.
Call for backup.
I’m goin´ after Phil.
Come on, Jerry Lee.
Oh-oh-oh, man!
Down! Down!
My car!
Move, move, move, move,
move, move, move!
Down!
Jerry Lee Barking
My car!
Oh, no.
Not the running thing again.
Come on!
Sighs
Yeah, yeah. Look at that.
Look at that bike.
Grunts
Come on, come on!
- Drop the gun!
- I cant.
Dutch
Growling
Jerry Lee Barking
Jerry Lee?
Where are you?
Dooley
Jerry Lee!
Oh! Oh!
Holy shit!
Groaning
Groans
You’re under arrest!
You have the right
to remain unconscious.
Anything you dream will be held
against you in a court of law.
Barking
- Its about time you got here, Jerry Lee!
Jerry Lee?
- Everything okay?
- Yeah.
Jerry Lees fine.
He only drinks water every couple days.
Just like a camel.
- Probably on his fathers side.
- That’s an interesting trait.
Its very efficient too.
He pees all at once.
Is your dog on steroids
or something?
- No. Why?
- I’ve never seen a dog like that not pant.
He’s not tired.
- How old is Jerry Lee?
- Oh, I don’t know.
Well, how long have
you two been together?
Its the longest relationship
I’ve ever had.
You’ve got everything
tied up here,
so we’ve got a couple of
personal things to take care of.
Come on.
Man Ah, too bad, Dooley.
Where are the marshmallows?
Can somebody
give me a ride?
Sighs
Oh, this is a hill!
Ohh.
Grunting
Ah, this is too much.
Phew!
You know, this isn’t a bad mode
of transportation, Jerry Lee.
No gasoline, no insurance.
No parking tickets.
I gotta get a little carriage seat
for you in the back, though.
- Hard day, huh, Jer?
Whines
A lot of action today.
Hey. Come here.
Come up
on my spot.
You can sit up on my spot.
Attaboy.
There you go.
I just love ya the way you are.
Good dog.
Powerful dog.
- Handsome dog. Pretty dog.
Whining
Yeah.
Hey, you want
some chili?
Oh, you want
more brush?
You want some chili?
I can make you some chili.
Got pretty ears.
Look at your ears, how pretty they are.
Look at that.
You’re so handsome.
Alarm Beeping
Slaps Radio,
Alarm Stops
Truck Motor Rumbling
- Hmm.
Glass, Metal Crashing
Hey! Hey!
Hey, that’s my car.
No, no, no, no.
Its not junk. It’s not junk.
Hold on, hold on,
hold on, hold on!
Get this thing out of here.
No, no. Not my car.
Get this garbage truck
out of here!
Back it, back it. Back it.
Back it up. Up! Up! Up!
Look, I just had it
towed back here.
What the hell
do you think you’re doin´?
My car!
For cryin out loud.
A ticket!
Whistling
Jerry Lee?
Continues Whistling
Hey, Jer?
Made your
favorite coffee.
Half cream,
three tablespoons of sugar.
Hey, Jer.
I think its a good idea
you stay home today.
Take a nap.
Get a little rest.
I’m gonna put on
some videos for ya.
There, look, I got, uh-
I got Beethoven, your favorite.
The original.
Jer?
Dooley
Oh, Jer.
Sighs
Jerry Lee?
- What are you doing?
Whimpers Softly
- We cant go in this car.
Whimpers
Jerry Lee, you cant go.
You cant go to work
with me today.
Jerry Lee, come on.
Go inside.
Oh, you’re playing
Mr. Deaf, are ya?
Do you want a time-out?
You want a time-out?
Fine.
Time-out!
Time-outs over. Now you’re grounded.
You are grounded, young man.
You go up into your room, no music,
no TV, no Beethoven, no park!
You gotta go to the bathroom?
Backyard for you.
Backyard!
Come on!
I’m gonna count to three,
and if you’re not upstairs,
in that room,
you’re in big trouble.
Whines
- One.
Motorcycle Approaching
- Two.
Two and a half.
- Three! Fine!
Barks
Fine, go!
Run away,
Mr. Independent,
I- Dont-Need-Mr. Dooley!
Go on, Jerry Lee!
Go with your friends!
- Sure, grass is greener on the other side, huh?
- Who are you yelling at?
- Jerry Lee.
- Why?
Oh, Mr. Big Shot
decided to run away.
All right, so,
jump in the car.
- Well go look for him. Zeus will seek him out.
- No, no, no, no.
He has to come to me. That’s the prodigal
son. He’s gotta go and come back.
I would be doing him damage if I went
and chased him down the street.
I am not gonna do it.
Whistling
Jerry Lee?
He’s just been actin´
so weird.
- Did he ever run away before?
- No.
- He’s very sensitive.
- Just like you.
- I’m not sensitive. He’s sensitive. I’m
- Barking
I’m just moody.
Dooley
Jerry Lee!
Well, maybe Byers is right.
- Maybe Jerry Lee just cant cut it anymore.
- Byers said that?
- Yeah, more than once.
- So, that’s why he assigned us to you.
Yep.
Where is he going?
Barking Dooley There he is!
Welles
In front of the storage building.
Jerry Lee!
Jerry Lee,
what are you doing?
I’m sorry, Jerry Lee.
Did I hurt your feelings?
- What’s with you?
- He’s not running away, Dooley. He wants you to follow him.
Jerry Lee Barking
Zeus, come!
- I think he’s on to something.
- I hate stairs.
Jerry Lee?
What do you got?
He’s keying in on something.
Whimpering
- Okay.
Okay, Jerry Lee,
back off.
- Move out of the way.
- What are you doing?
I’m picking the lock.
We do it all the time.
That’s what worries me.
Sighs You have a better idea?
- Yes.
One of us will stake out the room from across
the hall, the other will go get a warrant.
Jerry Lee and I
do not do warrants.
Or back doors.
What else don’t you do?
We don’t do flavored coffee. We don’t
do aroma therapy. We don’t do raw fish.
- Normally known as sushi.
- Yes, we don’t do that.
We don’t do tofu. We don’t do collagen.
We don’t do colonics.
We don’t do e-mail. We don’t do head
shrinkers, group therapy, social workers.
We don’t do cute little doggy outfits.
We don’t do shopping.
- We don’t do Near Beer or little speedos.
- Thank God.
- And we don’t do sporks.
- I get the point. I’ll get the warrant.
- Don’t touch the lock.
Jerry Lee Whines
And we don’t do, "Ooh, is that a pimple
on your back? Can I squeeze it?"
Zeus Barks
- Jerry Lee, she didn’t say we
can’t touch that lock. Gunshot
Jerry Lee Howling
- That’s it.
Howling Continues
You’re a good singer.
Howling Intensifies
- Okay, were done singing now. All right? You happy?
Stop it! Stop! Come on.
The bad guys gonna hear us.
Yeah, see? Look. I could stuff you
and put you on the wall.
See?
Like a moose head.
You know, you’re
the best dog I ever had.
You’re the only dog I ever had,
but you’re still the number one guy.
You know, this is hard
for me to say, but-
Whimpers
Sniffing
- Get away from me. Is that
you? Was that you? Whimpers
Oh, my God! That is rancid!
Groaning
Banging On Door
Gagging
- What did you eat?
Banging Continues
Did you just cut another one?
Did you?
Gagging Continues
There’s something alien in you!
Whew! Whew!
You’re off that
lamb and rice diet!
Oh, God!
Coughing
Dooley!
- Oh!
Whimpering
Oh!
What is that smell?
- What? What smell?
- Oh, don’t tell me you don’t have a sense of smell.
- My God! My eyes are watering.
- It was Jerry Lee!
- Stop blaming the dog.
- Honest to God, it was Jerry Lee.
- That is so sad, man. You need to go to a doctor.
- No!
- I swear! It was Jerry Lee!
Whimpers Softly
All right, I got the warrant.
Shoot off the lock.
I advise you to wait, however,
considering the gas in this room.
- You’re gonna blow us up.
Gunshot
Seek.
Oh, yeah,
he’s a gun nut, all right.
Welles
Looks like he’s some kind of writer.
Everything’s written
under a different name.
He’s got pictures of his girlfriend
or his wife hanging up.
What?
Its not his wife.
It’s mine.
Jerry Lee Whimpering
Welles They’re picking
up the manuscripts later.
So, what do you think? I mean, they’re
all cop stories. Every one of ´’em.
Tracy was an editor.
That rejection letter
she wrote was really nice.
Tracy was nice in every way.
That’s why you disappeared
that night that we, um-
Kissed?
Yes.
I’m sorry about that.
No, don’t be sorry. It was nothing to
apologize for. You just weren’t ready.
Maybe.
Dooley, you really gotta stop
blaming yourself for what happened.
No, I’m serious.
Listen, people die.
That is a fact of life.
You’re a really good cop.
And so is Jerry Lee.
You got really great instincts.
You know?
And they cant teach you that.
Trust me, I know.
- Thanks.
- You’re welcome.
Barking
- Is he gonna bite me?
- Probably.
You know, that dog
is very co-dependent.
- Can I take him in the other room?
- You can try.
- Zeus? Ham, cheese?
Chuckles
- Look what I got. Look what I got.
Growling
Come on. Lets go
in the other room.
That’s good. Come on.
Come on. Come on.
That’s my finger.
No, that’s my finger. That’s my finger.
You want a time-out?
Want a time-out? Want a time-out?
My finger, my finger.
Let go, let go, let go.
- Thank you.
- Dooley!
- I’m not gonna share.
- Dooley, come here!
- What?
- Come here.
- What? - This guy- This
guy is writing about you.
He’s got everything. He’s got the
bank shoot-out, Harry Stipe, Fat Tommy.
- Who wrote this?
- Um, I don’t know. A guy named Jeffery Barnes.
- Probably a fake name.
- Barnes.
- No.
- These all have different pen names.
Who’s the hero?
Devon Lane.
Right? Yeah.
I don’t know why I-
I know Devon Lane.
Devon Lane turned in
a manuscript to Tracy.
She rejected it,
but she wanted me to meet with him...
to talk to him about
what is was like to be a cop.
He was really strange.
He kept staring at her
through the whole-
Wait.
I’m gonna have an APB
put out on him immediately.
- Good work.
- You too.
Man On TV, Indistinct
- Hey.
- Hi.
Chuckles
I’m kinda hungry.
- You hungry? You wanna eat?
- Yeah.
- Yes!
- I am a good cook.
I am a great cook.
I’m gonna fix you something.
Okay.
You’re gonna love it.
You’re just gonna love it.
Glass Breaks
Growls
Ill clean it up.
I’ll clean it up.
Glass Breaking
Whimpers
Damn!
I’m gonna get tupperware.
Man On TV The government bill to
crack down on laboratory experiments...
on animals is expected
to become law today.
Man #2 ... then you should try
Smith Kennels Table Scrap Snacks.
They taste and look just like the scraps
your dog begs for at the table.
Small, delectable pieces
of toast crust, scrambled egg bits-
TV Continues, Indistinct
Your dog will beg for more.
Here are some happy users.
Man #3 Yeah, I came home
for dinner late last night,
and I saw the dog was just
chomping away-
Growling
Growling Continues
"Coldsky. "
"Brrrsky. "
All right, all right.
I’m dropping it.
Hey.
Wanna go for a walk?
Go for a walk?
Whispers
Watch her.
Okay, don’t move.
TV Continues, Indistinct
Okay, a date.
I wanna take her out on a date.
Date.
"Daten-wagen. "
"Daten-varganaire. "
"Daten-schwarnenegger. "
Tulips.
Heineken, Amsterdam, clogs.
I gotta get
a Dutch dictionary.
All right.
I mean, she, you know-
She came on- What?
You gotta go?
Zeus Urinating
You know, I like this neighbor. She’s
a really nice old lady. You shouldn’t-
Oh, my God.
All I got are twenties.
That’s all I got is a twenty.
Oh, my God!
Man On TV
Call this toll-free number now...
to order this revolutionary
new dog snack risk-free.
If your dog
doesn’t really love them,
just return the unused portion
for a full refund.
Smith Kennels Table Scrap Snacks-
the healthy alternative.
If your pet experiences drowsiness,
hair loss or diarrhea-
TV Shuts Off
Whispers
Good night, Zeus.
Whimpers
Sighs
Cat Screeches
Barks
Come on.
Go to sleep.
Zeus, lets go.
Door Closes
Good morning.
Jerry Lee Whimpers
- Good morning.
Good morning.
"Guten-morning. "
Barks
What do you think?
Like it?
Okay, bud,
its you and me.
Growls Softly
- Don’t blow it.
Breakfast, anyone?
Whimpers
- Was it something we said?
Did she leave?
Well, its you and me again,
Jerry Lee. Come on, outside.
Whimpers
- Come on, come on, come on. Leave me the marshmallows.
Telephone Ringing
She’s calling, probably to apologize.
Come on.
Ringing Continues
Hello. You know,
you could’ve stayed for breakfast.
Devon I heard you finally got
around to reading my masterpiece.
Poignant, huh?
You wanna know the ending?
If you get to her first, she lives.
If you don’t, she dies.
How’s that for real, Dooley?
See you soon.
Dial Tone
Shit.
Where’s that number?
Dialing
Ringing
Zeus Barking
Pick it up. Pick it up.
Come on. Answer it.
Ringing
Barking Continues
Pick it up!
Damn it!
Groans
Telephone Ringing
Byers.
Hey, Dooley.
What?
Wait, slow down. Slow down.
What are you talking about?
He’s after her.
Welles, that’s who! Welles!
Oh, no, no.
Come on. Huh?
He would never come here.
He’s not that crazy.
- Listen to me! Welles
You’re completely surrounded.
- Shut up!
- You’re in a police station,
- for Gods sakes.
- Oh, my God.
Indistinct Yelling,
Shouting
Gunfire Continues
Barking
- Hey!
Hey!
Hey, what are you doing?
What are you doing with all these
tickets? You’re following me!
You got a vengeance-
A boot? You put-
I need a ride! There’s an emergency
going on. I need to take-
Here. Here, I’m sorry.
You want this?
That’s what I think- Hey!
Get in.
Ill show her.
Hmm!
Officer
Get down! Get down!
- I cant see him! Officer
#2 We’re under fire!
Devon
Take your shot!
- Goddamn it! Put your gun down!
Byers Hold your fire! Get down!
- Stop that man! Welles
Everybody get down!
Devon Shut up!
- Its all over.
Byers
Lay down, everybody! Lay down!
Oh, for crying out loud.
Byers
Hold your fire! He’s backing out!
- Okay, lets move up! Come
on! Officer Move! Move!
Come here!
Zeus, go on back!
Gunfire Continues Welles Back up!
- You’ll never make it out of the building.
- That’s not the ending I wrote.
- Hey!
- Well, the good guy finally arrives,
just in time to see
another loved one die.
Let her go.
This is between you and me.
I got the station locked down, Dooley.
He cant get out.
Now, put the gun down,
Devon, and nobody gets hurt!
Did you know
he killed his wife?
I didn’t kill her.
Tracy was very sick, and she died.
Sick of you.
Sick of being a cops wife.
You drove her
to an early grave.
Growling
- Get your dog back. Get him
back, Dooley. Dooley Cant do that.
You think
he listens to me?
Get your dog back, Dooley. Get him
back, or Ill shoot him right now.
Tracy loved that dog.
- Loved that dog more than anything.
- Not more than me.
- She didn’t even know you!
- Yes, she did. She read my book.
That’s me in that book.
She said I had potential.
She believed in me.
Dooley I’m sorry I didn’t like your book.
- You didn’t even read it.
I read part of it.
Devon Tracy didn’t have any
problems with my writing being real.
She liked my work!
I wont shoot the dog. I’ll shoot her.
- Shoot him, Dooley. Just take him out.
- Shut up!
- Shut up, Byers! - Shut
up, Byers! - Shoot him!
Shut up!
I’m not gonna shoot him.
- He needs help!
- I don’t need help.
- Yes, you do.
Growling
Tracy would want you
to get help.
- She would?
- Yes, she would.
- You’re just saying that.
- No, I’m not.
- You’re lying to me.
- I’m not.
Yes, you are.
You’re lying to me.
All right.
I’m lying to you.
I cant help you.
I don’t wanna help you. You’re an idiot.
You’re a nut. You’re a jerk.
You understand English,
or do I need to speak in Dutch?
Zeus!
Dutch
Yelling, Shouting
- You all right?
- Yeah.
Byers
He’s going upstairs! Let’s go!
Come on, Dooley!
You can make it!
Only two more flights,
Dooley!
Jerry Lee Barking
Devon Come on, old man!
Groans
Jerry Lee Barking
I need E.M.S. vehicles and a SWAT team
on the roof. Right away!
You’re pathetic, Dooley!
What Tracy saw in you,
Ill never know.
Groaning
- You didn’t deserve her!
Aah!
She said my character
was strong.
She said I had potential!
Come on, Dooley!
Come on, old man!
Panting, Groaning
She wrote me a letter, Dooley!
She ever write you a letter?
You moron!
That letter she wrote you
was a rejection letter!
Rejection?
- Aah!
- How do you like the ending to my book, Dooley?
- Do it!
- Ill do it when I’m ready.
Do it!
Go ahead!
Shut up!
I’m in control here, Dooley.
This is my story,
not yours!
Where do you want it?
Cause I’m deciding where you
should get the next bullet.
You got any preferences?
Is this real enough for you,
Dooley?
- You did it! What took you so long?
Whimpering
Indistinct Shouting
- I knew you could do it, buddy.
Welles, cuff him.
Jerry Lee Barking
Wait!
You cant have dogs in here.
They’re police officers,
ma´am.
They’re dogs!
Get them out of here.
The California State Health Code,
section 4578, says absolutely...
under no circumstances are dogs
allowed in the hospital.
Woman On P.A.,
Indistinct
Whimpers
Barks Softly
Muttering
What? Come on.
Jerry Lee.
Come on. Don’t slime me.
Your breath is so bad.
What have you been eating?
Chuckling
Okay. I’m okay.
Don’t do that!
Groans
Welles, I wanna thank you
for picking me up.
Are you actually showing me
some gratitude, Dooley?
- Well, yeah, I’m trying.
- Good boy.
- I am not a dog.
- Yes, you are.
- Dogs get treats.
- Treats?
Dinner. What do you want?
Chinese or Italian?
Oh, you pick.
Your choice.
- Oh, you’re actually giving me a choice?
- Yes, your choice.
- Well, then I pick Chinese.
- Chinese is fine.
No, that’s what you wanted me to say.
We’re going for Italian.
- Well, Italian is fine.
- You actually want Italian?
- Yes.
- Then we are going for Chinese.
- Chinese is fine. I don’t care.
- Yeah, sure you don’t.
Works every time,
Jerry Lee.