those words have
a different meaning.
A darker meaning.
Yeah, everyone knows that.
They get people programmed
to do whatever.
Could be for sex
or, you know, kill a guy.
They're out there.
The dolls.
Seeming to crop up
first in the late '80s,
the Dollhouse is one of L.A.'s
most enduring urban legends.
The story is simple.
Somewhere in the city
is an illegal establishment
that rents out to the very rich
and the very connected
programmable people.
People who can take on
any personality
except their own.
Nothing more
than science fiction
according to most everybody,
a big foot for the big city.
But what's interesting
about this urban legend,
is the wide spectrum
of reactions we encountered
from everyday Angelenos
to the very idea of a Dollhouse.
Oh, it's happening.
is if they is one already.
Volunteers. You must be
out of your (bleep) mind.
So, being a doll,
you do whatever.
And you don't
got to remember nothing.
Or study.
Or pay rent.
And you just party
with rich people all the time?
Where's the dotted line?
A spokesperson
for the Governor insists
that this legend
is nothing more than that.
And stories of an F.B.I. task force
investigating the Dollhouse
have been flatly denied.
But the rumors persist.
And like every good fairy tale,
the story grows more intricate,
and more divisive,
every decade.
(T.V. clicks off,
remote clatters on desk)
You're out of
hand cream again.
This the alleged victim?
Guy said she had
a face. Damn.
No wonder you're foraging
for hand cream.
Had a million bucks,
I could blow it on that.
Did you track this
payment from Crestejo?
The Mayfair fund?
Told you to stay out
of my soup, Ballard.
Afraid you'll have
to reopen the case?
Act like a federal agent
for five minutes?
This is my report.
If there is some
giant conspiracy that's
sucking the brains
out of nice, young people,
then this bit of tail
that you're chasing
is A: effectively dead,
and B: a whore.
A mindless whore,
just your type.
No disrespect.
I'm sure she still
has a heart of gold.
(Tanaka grunts)
What happened there, Ballard?
I strike a nerve?
Yeah.
I mean it.
Someone's going to put you down.
And I pray to God
I'm there to see it.
(groans)
Come by any time.
Sierra is alone.
I like to be alone sometimes.
It's peaceful.
Sierra sits with us most days.
Am I wrong?
When we go to sleep,
I hear her.
Maybe she
didn't see us.
Do you feel
uncomfortable at all?
No. Should I?
No.
Did Victor
upset you,
do you remember?
Victor wants to pretend.
“pretend”?
He pretends we're married.
I see.
Something's up?
Yes.
Sierra's had sex.
No, sir.
You know for sure?
Her last engagement was
with the Governor's niece
at a children's
cancer ward.
I examined her
post-engagement anyway.
This happened
while she's been here.
What did she say about Victor?
That he liked to play.
Wait, the dolls
don't have sex drives.
That's part
of the deal, right?
them abusing each other.
If Victor's off-program,
then he could be
Jekyll and Hyde-ing
just like Alpha did.
We can't jump
to any conclusions.
No, but we can go
to the videotape.
How long has she…?
Two days.
If Victor was alone with her,
it won't take long to find.
Mr Hearn,
when you figure out
what happened…
Then I go to DeWitt.
If Victor is
playing doctor
when not imprinted
with an MD,
then he goes to the attic.
(door slams)
Victor wouldn't…
She did scream
when she saw him.
And we both know
he's been focused on her.
There's a difference
Between being attracted
to someone and hurting them.
Has she shown
any other sign?
Anything you can remember?
Echo:
When we go to sleep…
When we go in the pods,
Sierra cries.
I think you're right.
This is the Crestejo account.
Big payment to the Mayfair fund,
which means nothing.
Mayfair is a hedge,
and it's spread thin.
But that
payment went in
right when his daughter
was kidnapped.
And you still think he hired
the Dollhouse to get her back.
I surely do.
Now you have a similar sum
transferred to the Mayfair fund
from Q-Field.
And this is the fun part:
You have the same amount,
from Q-Field to Mayfair,
every year on
the exact same day.
Q-Field is a subsidiary
of Redwing,
a majority share of which
is held by…
Joel Mynor.
And Joel Mynor is
on your list of potential
Dollhouse clients.
Man, even I know
about this guy.
He's that internet mogul.
He created Sourceress,
with a fabulous nobody
on his arm.
I've liked this guy for a while.
You ever thought
about asking him out?
I'm never going to get
to Caroline.
Whoever she is,
the Dollhouse has buried her.
I've got to get to them first,
and Joel Mynor is my ticket.
Whatever he's paying for,
it's happening soon.
I need
everything on him.
You mean everything
admissible by a warrant
that you got,
because anybody
in the whole wide bureau
believes you're not insane.
I mean help me out.
Getting shot didn't even make
you pause, did it?
I'll help you.
The Director sees
what we're up to,
he's going to help you out.
So the one fund got transferred
to the other fund,
How do you think
I can afford
To take you to all these
fancy places?
Hey, this is the nicest
offer I've had this month.
Or last month.
Weren't you,
um, seeing someone?
Hmm?
Rick.
Dick.
Really?
I thought it was Rick.
Oh, his name is Rick.
Oh.
Mm-hmm.
He said he didn't see me
as “a long-term investment.”
Said he wanted to, uh,
“dump the stock
before it went public.”
He talks like that.
He works at a doughnut shop.
What a Rick.
Yeah. Hey, I get that I'm not
the gold standard in I.A.
Please, you're gorgeous.
But I do have access
to important
government information
that I don't understand.
It boils down to this:
Today was a slightly better day
for the good guys
than it was for the bad guys.
Just one more tiny step to get
me closer to bringing her in.
“her” is being held captive
by “them.”
Along with a lot of other
people, if I'm right.
So if I really catch
my client in the act tomorrow
with a doll, I'm closer
to freeing them all.
Including, but not limited to,
“her.”
Is that fair?
It's your job.
We're all clear in there.
Okay, I don't want
to see anybody
in the house
or around the house,
and that includes the boys.
They get it.
You'll be very much alone.
Louanne's covering for me,
so this can't
take forever.
You may have
to owe her one.
I did something.
Something bad?
Woman:
Oh, Joel.
Joel:
The oven, uh,
gets food so hot,
it actually goes
through this thing called
the “cooking process.”
It's very scientific.
(woman giggles)
Um, and I think there's
something in the fridge.
I'd like you both to
turn around very slowly.
If they'd had it in my day,
I'd have had Betty Grable
every night.
Or Ida Lupino.
Every man that fought
for his country
should have the right
to an Ida Lupino.
You mean if it was real?
If I could hire a doll
and he could
be anyone and do anything
with no consequences,
I think you've
made a mistake.
What's happening?
Caroline?
Okay, you've definitely
made a mistake.
What do you call her?
Please put the gun away.
My name is
Rebecca Mynor, and this
is my husband, Joel.
We just bought
this house.
We did, right?
You didn't just break
in to impress me?
No, it-it's paid for.
This is all a big mix-up.
Please tell me
your name.
I'm Paul Ballard.
I'm with the F.B. I…
I knew it.
What?
It's porn, isn't it?
The internet venture
that suddenly pays off.
You did porn!
My husband does porn!
No, I don't do porn!
You're in huge trouble.
Your name is Caroline.
You don't know this,
but you're being fooled.
You're being used.
Okay,
I'm giving you
one last chance to leave.
Joel,
please don't make him angry.
I would never hurt you.
(taser clicking)
(grunts)
I'm so sorry, Mr Mynor,
he attacked one of our men.
Sweetie…
I…
(men grunting, Echo screaming)
God!
Joel!
You need a treatment.
(screams)
Joel…
Porn.
(all grunting)
(tires screeching)
(engine roaring)
(coughs)
Hope you're not thinking
about leaving, Mr Mynor.
Can I assume
none of my security guys
need an ambulance
or a hearse?
They'll be fine.
Why don't you, uh, tell me
what you're looking for?
(laughing):
The doll…
Uh, it's pink and it opens up
and there's teeny furniture,
and you put the boy doll
on top of the girl doll
and we learn about urges.
What's her name?
Rebecca—
she told you.
Really?
How do you
know Rebecca?
We've been married
for seven years.
(chuckles)
So that's your fantasy?
All the money in the world,
the most elaborate,
high-class underground
operation ever designed,
and you just want
to play house?
I guess the rich
really are different.
Why, what's your fantasy?
Oh, I'm okay right here
in the real world, thanks.
Oh, don't, no,
you have a fantasy.
Okay, we all do.
We need it to survive,
and I think your fantasy
But then
the brave little F.B.I. agent
whisked her away
from the cash-wielding losers
and restored
her true identity,
and she fell in love with him.
It doesn't go like that.
(scoffing):
I saw how you were with her.
It was,
it was almost cute.
We're not here to talk about me.
Hey,
I don't have to be here at all.
I mean, you're not going
to arrest me.
Pretty sure you're not going
to kill me, so…
If we're going to talk,
we're both going to talk.
I mean, she,
she changed things for you.
So you're the head
of this F.B.I. task force
to uncover the Dollhouse,
and you're working hard,
you're chasing leads,
you're cracking skulls,
but it's just work.
And suddenly…
(cork pops)
it gets personal.
Tell me you haven't
thought about it.
You know, her,
her grateful tears,
her, her welcoming embrace,
her warm breath.
Are you married?
Was.
Oh,
That's…
Is there someone
in your life right now?
This is getting old.
Of course not.
No, there's no room
for a real girl, is there,
when you can feel
Caroline beckoning?
(chuckling): You know, I have to say
I-I think your fantasy
is even sadder than mine.
Won't know until I hear it.
Well,
it didn't involve
drinking alone.
Sierra is different.
How is she different?
I'm sorry.
Victor,
do you remember being in
the showers with Sierra?
You were watching her?
How does Sierra make you feel?
Better.
I can't believe this.
I'm filling in
for Ramirez for a week and
my active invents rape?
We don't know
what happened yet.
Victor might have just
triggered a memory.
Well, Hearn's
out for blood.
Hearn hasn't found
anything on the tapes.
Nobody has.
How is that
even possible?
Every square inch of
this place is monitored.
If two actives
are going at it…
What do you think
DeWitt'll do?
You think she'll
come down hard?
It was probably
just a mistake.
They're all broken.
Rebecca was amazing.
She was a nurse and…
(laughing):
I was a basket case,
So, you know,
not a, not a bad match.
I was the guy
with the almost great idea—
floogle
and blahoo! And facebooger.
I was, I was just always
one step behind,
and she was cool with it.
And did she look
exactly like Caroline?
No, but—
Eat it, f-bitch-I—
she was beautiful
and she knew it
and she loved me.
I mean, I had been…
(sighing):
I had been given a gift.
And now you're hiring zombies.
Place is empty.
Shame— big place.
(scoffs)
This place.
This place could fit
in my bathroom.
I mean, this place could fit
in my guest bathroom.
All right?
I mean, I finally got
one step ahead.
“Bouncy the Rat.”
Kids love it.
Ooh, they do.
I mean,
long story still kind of long,
my first check had more zeros
than the Luftwaffe.
The Japanese—
They had the Zeros,
not the Germans.
(sighs)
It was money.
All right, it was
roll-around-in money
and Rebecca had no idea.
She'd been supporting
the both of us for years.
I mean ridiculous hours.
We were living
in a one-room shack,
and I knew this house
was exactly her type.
I paid cash and I called her up.
I said,
“meet me at this address,
it's really important,”
and she was worried,
you know,
thinking about the look
on her face
when she saw this place
and I told her it was ours.
Sanitation truck…
sideswiped her car…
three blocks from here,
and I heard the impact and…
(sighs)
they said it was quick.
I guess that, you know,
they always have to say that.
Right?
But she never got
to see this house,
and she never knew I made good.
So every year on this date,
And then you sleep with her.
It is a fantasy.
I'm sorry for your
loss, Mr Mynor.
It doesn't make you anything
other than a predator.
Well, I'm sure I'm in need of
some serious moral spankitude,
but, uh, guess who's not
qualified to be my rabbi.
Well, I'm perfectly happy
to let a federal judge…
Throw you in jail, hmm?
I mean, we got trespassing,
we got assault,
and what you've
got is a girl
you're obsessed with,
who I think we can both agree
is not here.
I mean, this is not
“beat up the geek,” big guy.
This is
the internet establishment.
You put me in front of a judge,
he'll take you down.
He'll throw the Kindle at you.
(siren wailing)
(chuckling):
Oh… Oh.
You might not be punished
and I might not be alive,
but this house will fall.
The first hurdle
in my business is the people
who will not accept the change
that's already happened.
Go.
Go live in
your real world.
If you ever did.
Happy anniversary.
If you could have somebody be
the perfect person,
the moment you wish for that you
know you're never going to get,
and someone signed on
to do that,
to help you…
I think that could be okay.
I think that could be
maybe beautiful.
This is Boyd Langton
for Mr Dominic.
I did something bad.
What did you do?
Nobody will tell me.
Victor, I need you
to come with me, please.
Where?
I need you to come
with me, please.
Why did Sierra scream at me?
Bicks:
Who authorized this?
I didn't rape
the doll.
Lawrence, Lawrence,
I didn't do this.
You know me, man.
I wouldn't do this, man.
Come on, you know
I didn't do this!
Where are they
taking Victor?
Why don't you go
paint something?
Nice work, man.
Not anymore.
Mellie:
Is this enough?
Thanks.
Are you, uh, always
gonna show up bleeding?
'cause it's kind
of funny
how I'm not
getting used to it.
It was her.
You met Caroline?
I saw Caroline.
I met Rebecca.
And I let both of
them get away.
So, it's all true.
I knew it was true.
I just didn't expect…
If it had been
anybody else,
the jail cells
would be full,
and I'd be busy writing the
great American arrest report.
I never thought
it would be her.
Did you get the guy?
The… John,
the… client.
What are they called?
I talked to him.
And?
I'm sorry.
I'm not.
I mean, I am.
I-I mean, you are.
Don't do that.
Don't inflate the stock
before you dump it.
Uh…
Don't think about her
and kiss me.
I wasn't, uh…
Forget it.
I think it's best
we forget it.
Would be stupid, anyway.
We're neighbors,
we should just…
we should be
neighborly.
Great.
Yes.
Neighborly.
Can I borrow
a cup of sugar?
(both laughing)
Like that.
So, why don't you tell me
about today.
The guy's name was Joel Mynor.
Joel Mynor from
Bouncy the Rat?
Do you trust me?
With my life.
Do you want to play the game?
No.
But you remember to be very
quiet during the game, right?
Noise is upsetting.
Lift up your dress.
That wasn't quiet.
He had to be flush
with success,
or he'd never
have tried again.
You will never take
action like that
on your own again
inside these walls.
Am I clear?
You're clear.
A bonus has been wired
to your account.
I don't need a bonus.
Well, I need to give it to you.
That's all.
Ms Dewitt.
(sighs)
What do we do with Hearn?
I'll let you know.
And you saw the other
thing, the tap?
Joel Mynor from Bouncy the Rat?
He was on the cover of Wired.
Do you have an
exit strategy?
We have a handler
abusing an active,
a federal agent
interrupting an engagement,
spilling his guts
to the nearest civilian.
I take much of that
as my responsibility,
but the higher-ups
will target you if
this all goes south.
Your concern is touching,
but my bags are not packed.
You will bring
the handler to me.
And as for the intrepid agent…
Tell Topher to prep Echo.
I think they're ready
for a second date.
Hey, everyone's got
their fantasies, right?
A guy wants to know
what it's like,
you know, to be
with another man.
just once,
nothing queeny.
(chuckles awkwardly)
Oh-ho.
You're bad.
Mmm.
You're a naughty girl.
Oh.
Okay.
Uh… But you're
not that girl.
That girl has
control issues
that don't mesh well with the
enhanced combat skill set.
You can re-cluster
the inhibitors
to offset the dissonance.
Don't we want aggression?
And precision.
I need a
soupcon of rage.
(sighs)
Find out if the kitchen
has the almond-crusted salmon.
I live to serve lunch.
Uh-huh.
And hello, gorgeous but deadly.
Tsk, tsk, tsk.
Upload imprint to file drive.
(humming)
Topher.
I'm in my process.
I'm…
What's the scuttlebutt?
Echo's been engaged.
That's 48 hours chill time, min.
What is she doing?
Echo?
Oh… Life coach gig.
You know, remind some doctor
why he helps kids
who have, you know, gross kids.
They don't think
I can handle that?
Uh, not everything
is about you, infinite ego man.
You know, you did
nail the guy
who was messing
with Sierra.
You should go out and get drunk
and beat your chest.
Echo will be here
when you get back.
Hey.
How did you figure out
it was Hearn, anyway?
Is it a cop thing?
Reading people?
You do the work.
Well…
Good work.
(humming)
(typing)
Ready to play?
Adelle: Can you imagine at all
why it is you are not dead?
You probably got
something worse planned.
You gonna erase my brain,
turn me into one
of your fantasy boys?
I find it a bit sad
that you think of yourself
as a candldate
for anyone's fantasy.
Ah, you know you're
a little sweet on me.
(screaming)
(Hearn hyperventilating)
You think I'm
gonna beg?
You want to kill me?
You want to put me in the attic?
I can't stop you.
The jig is up.
How many times?
(panting)
I can find out, but I want
to hear it from you.
it makes it better
because she thinks
she's in love for
all of a day?
We're in the business
of using people.
You understand less about
this business than you think.
And you don't get how it
actually works down there.
You put a bunch
of stone foxes
with no willpower
and no memory
running around naked.
Did you think this
wouldn't ever happen?
Did it make it better?
That she didn't struggle?
No.
It made it easier.
Mr Dominic, would you leave us?
Ms Dewitt, I…
I'll be perfectly safe.
Please.
We are in the business
of using people.
The question is,
what is the best use
for someone like you?
really.
I need her killed,
and it can't be clean.
This is your chance
to avoid the attic.
You may even consider it
something of a promotion.
After all,
this one will…
probably struggle.
(breathing heavily, moaning)
My God.
You're so…
Neighborly.
(both chuckling)
So…
Can I borrow a
cup of sugar?
(laughing)
(groaning)
I'm not gonna
freak out on you.
Uh… good.
When you tell me this
is all a mistake
and we should forget
it ever happened,
I'm gonna be very cool.
You're gonna be bothered
by how cool I am.
What if I don't say that?
I'll still be cool,
But not as cool.
What if you tell me
it was a mistake?
Oh, God, you're
gonna be so clingy,
weeping and moping,
texting me.
It's too embarrassing.
I am not a piece of meat,
you know.
I have a heart.
(chuckling)
Blah, blah.
I was thinking
about Caroline.
I think what they're
doing is wrong.
And I don't love seeing
you get beat up
and shot, but…
I think your work
is important.
Then help me out.
Is this the part where you
dress me up and use me as bait?
'cause those movies
never end well.
It's the part where I run
down to Tiki Port
and grab us dinner
and we go over my files
and you give me your
perspective on some stuff.
Might see something
I didn't.
You think I'd be helpful?
Yeah.
That's the sweetest thing
you've done for me all day.
Well…
What about the,
um…
the other things?
(chuckles)
Fetch me spring rolls.
Then we'll bust this case
wide open.
(distant traffic noise,
horns honking)
Whoever you are,
I swear I don't want
to hurt you.
I know.
(groans)
I'm counting on it.
You think it's not happening?
You think they're not controlling you?
Don't worry about it.
Just sit back
and wait for them to tell you
what to buy.
(groans)
(grunting)
(pots clanging)
(groans)
(bowls and plates crashing)
(grunting)
(groans)
(groaning)
(panting)
The Dollhouse is real.
They know you're
after them
and they are going
to have you taken
off the case.
That's why they sent me.
(panting)
Why are you
telling me this?
This is their first
communication.
Security inside
is very tight.
Where is it?
You can't know that.
You're going about this
the wrong way.
I have to take down
the Dollhouse.
There are over 20 Dollhouses,
in cities around
the world.
They have ties
to every
major political power
on the planet.
You cannot possibly
stop them alone.
You're going to help me?
The person that
sent this message is.
Why?
The Dollhouse
Deals in fantasy.
That is their business,
but that is not their purpose.
What is?
We need you to find out.
We'll contact
you again—
if possible,
with this same body.
But you have to let
the Dollhouse win.
Make them back off.
You have to trust me.
(footfalls)
he's got
No.
You have to go.
They don't want
to kill you, but they will
protect the information.
Call an ambulance!
Officer down!
Go!
You can't just….
They will protect
the information.
They don't want
you dead.
But anyone else….
Mellie.
(door lock clicks)
(screams)
(crying)
(grunting)
Paul (on machine):
Leave a message.
Adelle: There are
three flowers in a vase.
The third flower is green.
(groans)
(groaning)
There are three flowers
in a vase.
The third flower
is yellow.
(crying)
Forget morality.
Imagine it's true.
Imagine this technology
being used.
Now imagine it being used
on you.
Everything you believe,
gone.
Everyone you love, strangers.
Maybe enemies.
Every part of you
that makes you more
than a walking cluster
of neurons
dissolved
at someone else's whim.
If that technology exists—
It'll be used.
It'll be abused.
It'll be global.
Dominic: I understand.
Thank you.
We'll talk soon.
Agent Paul Ballard was
suspended of duty pending
an investigation into the
shooting of Officer Hardin.
Accusations of violent
paranoia, the attack
on Mr Mynor's bodyguards,
the feud with
the Borodins,
as evidenced by the break-in
at his apartment.
I replayed the tap.
More than once?
It did not lack
for poetry.
Bring her in so Topher
can run a diagnostic.
Are we pulling her?
Now that Ballard's
off the case?
No. A man like Ballard
doesn't take himself
out of the game,
just because of this.
Besides…
She loves him.
You played
a good hand, ma'am.
I played a very bad
hand very well.
There is a distinction.
Of course.
I want you to contact
your counterparts
in all the other houses,
tell them about what
happened to Sierra.
That won't look
good for you.
It can't happen again.
Anywhere.
She's alright?
Topher did everything
he knows
to remove the experience.
Ignorance in this case,
Good day.
You have a book.
I enjoy looking at it.
Would you like to see?
Hello, Echo.
You've drawn a picture.
It's very good.
It isn't finished.
The picture?
You'd like it to be finished?
you'd be the first one
that I see
and I the last one
that you keep
the dream would go on and on
while we sway
against all things
thrown our way
and the morning
would be so cruel
when it came
with sunshine
and warmth to bring
for announcing the end
of my sweet dream
for announcing
the end of my sweet dream.