"24 HOURS TO DIE"
Your dog is beautiful.
What's his name?
- Pooch! We call Pooch.
Hey, Pooch? Come here!
Good girl.
Look.
She's awesome. Remember the dog
I had as a child.
Napoleon ...
That dog was crazy.
Do not remember you.
Live around here?
We lived here for years,
with Pooch.
Right ...
Can you do me a favor?
You can get in the car?
- What?
- The car.
Get in the car.
Frances, see this.
Now coming in?
Get in the car!
Help! Help!
They'll kill me?
I want the money from her husband.
He can give you.
Can you give all you want.
Hope you keep alive,
really.
Looks like a nice person.
It will not bury me alive, are you?
Can not do that.
Can not bury me alive.
Please, can not
do this. You can not!
I implore you, for God's sake.
Please do not.
- Handsome, how are you there?
- Near the end.
Help, please!
Help!
- No one will hear you.
- Help!
Do not shout, no one will hear you.
Nobody.
Well ...
Get undressed.
Got enough air
for a day, Frances ...
... If not panic.
No, please!
Wait! Please!
Come on.
I'm afraid of the dark, please!
Give me a torch! I beg you!
- Come on.
- Please, a flashlight!
We could give her.
No!
No! Please!
I beg you, please!
Shut up, Frances.
Shut the hell up ...
or not to tell anyone where it is.
The decision is yours.
Bury it, or will be next.
Please give me the flashlight.
Please!
A flashlight.
Please. Please.
No, please!
Please, no!
Handsome, you do not
want to do it!
Please let me out!
Let me out!
Get me outta here!
This town is too hot.
Today two boys of 10 and 11 years
entered a shop on the second. Av
They were armed.
The weapons were unloaded,
but the clerk did not know.
Was Pakistani.
He thought it was going to die.
He handed over the money, right?
No! No, the boys thought
was in the bag, they would get.
$ 20 would be rich one day.
Just did not know that
Pakistani was crazy.
While the boys surrendered,
He reached into his desk ...
grabbed a pistol and began
throwing candy on the shelf.
I arrived ten minutes later. The
boys were on the floor, dead ...
there was blood everywhere, and the
guy was eating chocolate ...
drinking soda and saying:
"These marginal asked."
Time and time again.
I hate summer. The people throwing out
because he is a hothead.
What is it? I'll buy you a Coke.
It will cool your head.
Why not pay me
a beer?
Funny.
It was not, but so what?
Do not worry Tim If you happen
again, I speak with my husband.
Is this true?
Talk to me?
Maddy ... Honey?
Not in service, remember?
What have you got?
It's 10-85.
- I can not do anything.
- I can.
Ask the radio-enhancement of the subway.
-Wait.
Excuse me.
Damn!
Step aside.
- What is happening?
- Out! Get out! Get out!
Step aside!
What the hell ...
- Beware!
- My goodness!
Stop, please!
Careful, you idiot!.
On foot!
Show your hands and stand!
Not you!
I'm a cop.
I want to show their hands ...
and stand up now!
Get down!
He's armed!
Hurry!
You are going to the subway!
- Get him on the subway!
- Let's get him!
- He is coming!
- Get down! He's down!
Do not you even move!
You bitch!
Ready, Detective.
Let us take care of him.
My goodness!
Hello?
- It's me.
- I knew you'd call again.
- Where have you been?
- Busy.
Want to come over?
Are you sure?
So tell me.
- I want to go there.
- No way.
- Say again.
- I want to ...
I want to go there.
Again.
I want to.
Please.
I want to go there.
Want some?
I want to.
Do you?
Please.
Hey shooter!
Where were you?
I'm beeping you half an hour ago!
- I'm not in service.
- No more answers his pager?
Is in the bag.
What do you want?
I iron, if we are to
precinct. Get in the car.
What happened?
- Kidnapping. We are in search.
Jess, I am not
feeling good.
It is not a party, okay?
We both have to go fast.
Or Tim's going to kill us.
Do yourself a favor ...
Suck bales.
You can pick up.
It smells to drink.
Caramba!
Damn!
Fuck you!
Damn it!
C'mon!
BHP!
Sorry.
We must go,
he has begun meeting.
I'm going.
Damn!
Foster already know and Dillon.
Are also in this case.
- One more minute, and would not.
- How lucky to be married to the boss.
Madeline, Jesse,
this is Clark Hannon.
You may not know that he
owns a collection of art ...
worth millions of dollars.
The kidnappers know that.
As I was saying ...
Mrs. Hannon was seen
last at 3 pm.
Is the time coming out with the dog.
Mr. Hannon arrived home at 7am ...
and surprised the woman was not there.
He thought he was still with the dog.
An hour and a half later
Porter league ...
that you have reached
a videotape.
The guy who delivered
was between 20 and 25 years ...
was white
and had brown hair.
This is Mrs. Hannon.
Help me, Clark.
They want money,
and I said they could ...
without having to do all this.
I do not want to hear.
No! Do not!
What will they do
is to bury me, inside.
And only if you tell them where I am
der $ 1 million in cash.
If you call the police ...
never tell where I was buried
or anything else.
No, no, please.
They want U.S. $ l million
cash ...
up at 6 am.
Take to the cemetery in Queens ...
the grave of Harry Houdini.
If you take the money
and not call the police ...
where I'm going to say
and you can save me.
You must do this,
I promised them.
Do that and not spoil it!
Do not spoil everything ...
and do not call the police!
- How often do I see it?
You can stay outside, but is
important to be present.
Do not want to die.
Do not want to die, Clark.
I'm afraid.
Take the hammer
and nails, Handsome.
No, do not!
No!
Get me outta here!
- She will die, will not you?
- No, it will not.
I called the police,
though it should not.
- Let's try to find it, really.
- How long does she have?
There should be a means
ventilation.
If not, she has 24 hours,
if not panic.
Do not panic? Are you crazy?
She was buried alive!
Can you tell me how
she's not going to panic?
I think that Ronald.
I do not care, it will solve.
I want the money at 5 am.
I want a map of the cemetery,
the streets around ...
and buildings that can
use in the ambush.
Straightaway.
- Will you tell me where I was?
- In Judy.
I was shaken after chase
and could not find you.
Did not look right.
- What we have right now?
- Not really.
- Are less than 2 hours from NY.
- That's right.
The kidnapping happened at 3 am,
and the tape was delivered at 18:30.
- Buried in the meantime.
- What would it take two hours.
But they are in the middle of nowhere
they left the dog barking.
There are no prints on the tape.
The doorman did not recognize
the delivery man in our book.
Who gave was the Handsome.
Not the head.
- How do you know?
- The head is the face of the gun.
He gave all the orders and filmed
the other guy closing the coffin.
- It has power and does not want to work hard.
- Who goes to the cemetery?
- The head or Handsome?
- The head.
Handsome obeys orders,
but can not be trusted with money.
The head will not suspect
we are on the case?
- Who knows?
- Wonder where she lives ...
his name, he left with the
dog, the husband was not ...
and they have $ 1 million net.
We assume that in the case.
There is no option.
Now there is no return.
I want you two commanding
operation in the cemetery.
Canti, Peters,
you will stay in the area.
I'm here to coordinate.
It is better, so do not lag behind.
If he does not talk, can ...
"There once was a man
who buried a shoe.
Who was the man
that buried the shoe?
I wanted to know.
There once was a man
that a buried shellfish.
Who was the man who
buried a shellfish?
I wanted to know.
Once upon a time ...
a man who buried a boat.
Who was this man? "
"Let me out!
Let me out!
Help, let me out!
Let me out! "
Guys, once again.
When it appears calm.
If he gets the information,
seize him when I have them.
If not, I do not want
know you are being followed.
Only Jesse and I go after him.
Jesse reply.
What?
I knew my father
was buried here?
Really? No kidding!
I'm not kidding.
In these tombs flights.
If it was not kidnapping, we could
take up some flowers and pray.
If not for the kidnapping,
I would not be here.
My dad just saw me
when I was perfect.
And who is perfect?
Well ...
You're doing great.
I bet he'd be proud.
You did not know him ...
- Maddy ...
I hate to interrupt, but stay
ready. I'm seeing someone.
Who is checking the card?
- You got me.
Very good.
Only when I have acted.
- Where does it go?
- Dunno.
I think the scare.
Madeline, he did return.
It's coming back?
The head out of the car
Is walking.
He called the cops?
If called, it dies.
- I did not call.
- I think the police are here.
Are you mike? I will not
frisk you, trust you.
I know you love your wife.
Here we are.
- The money is there?
- It only takes to say where she is.
Are you threatening me?
Will give me orders now?
Stay tuned, folks.
Just want to know where she is.
- Spend the money, Clark.
- Where is she?
- In the woods.
- I know that. But where?
- In the backyard.
- Where?
Are you losing your temper, Clark.
I thought it was money
staying calm.
All those millionaires auctions
and even breaking a sweat.
Your money is here.
I made your game.
Take the money and go away,
but tell me where she is.
- I want her back.
- "I want her back."
Spend the money
and I say where she is!.
I kept my word,
will keep his?
I am a man of his word.
I'll tell you where to bury her.
But you must give me the money.
There goes the money.
If it passes the information
await my orders.
Caramba!
- Where is she?
- It's a beautiful woman! So cute!
- I loved her panties!
- Where is she?
- Why has sex with his secretary?
- You hear me? Tell me!
If you tell now, I'm screwed.
- Say it, please!
- Relax! Go play tennis!
- I'll call you in an hour.
- We had an agreement.
I handed over the money,
and you say where she is.
Bastard!
You bastard!
Son of a bitch!
Jesse, I'm behind you.
- Identified the card?
- It was stolen in Forest Hills.
There are no witnesses
or fingerprints.
Maddy?
He is entering the city.
Damn!
Want to play?
I think I was identified.
I need reinforcements now.
Crazy cow!
Excuse me!
He dropped something.
For God's sake,
how long it takes!
My wife is dying
and it does not open its beak.
Any results?
This is a joke. We call
The FBI immediately.
- I can not stand his silence!
- It is not the case for the FBI.
- This is not an interstate case.
- Do not give a damn about it!
You know who I am?
I will denounce you,
their incompetent!
- He is not very optimistic.
- We can not blame him.
- He said nothing?
- Not at all.
Jerome Jersey is inside,
trying to fold it.
He only asked for a pack of cigarettes ...
and nothing else.
Time is running out.
Send Clark Hannon enter and finish
to race him until he speaks.
- I like the idea.
- It's the best so far.
Listen ...
... My wife is well?
- She's great.
- I tried to talk to the hospital ...
- It is only a little silly ...
and probably very angry.
They found his fingerprint
and Handsome?
We're checking the Handsome,
but this one ...
Must have passed the acid in the fingers.
He does not want his identity revealed.
Well, we need
find out his name.
You can not negotiate
if one side does not speak.
So you will not do.
We should be moving or it dies.
- I'll wait a little longer.
- You know what?
I'm ready to talk.
I'll open the beak.
- I'm getting.
- But not with the Polish!
And even with no
these incompetent!
I will only talk to one person.
Bring the cow that
ruined my plans!
- You can talk to someone else?
- We tried for half an hour.
- He will only talk to you.
- I can not do that.
- We have no choice, sorry.
- This is the life of a woman.
It'll be fine.
You're a good cop.
- I have faith in you.
- You?
I've always had.
It is ...
- Always have.
- But you never believed.
We need to talk, right?
And let's talk after bringing
Frances Hannon back alive.
Good luck.
I was waiting.
I knew.
- Mario Andretti ...
- In the flesh.
Very good. Why was the
chosen to talk to you?
Want me to shut up again?
- It was not what I said.
- So do not worry.
I chose you because it was
who spoiled my plans.
- Could have been a millionaire.
- It was not a perfect plan.
Clark knew that Hannon
call the police.
- Do not think it was stupid.
- Donkey?
The guy's wife is buried
alive and know where she is.
I told him to not call the police,
or I would not count.
If he called it, is stupid.
- He killed his own wife.
- Not yet.
It's true.
The clock is ticking.
You're a beauty, you know?
I mean, to a policeman.
What's your name
true, "Mario"?
Detective Foster.
Name ...
Madeline.
It's a beautiful name.
Beautiful name for a beautiful woman.
And what is yours?
Harry. Want a cigarette?
- No smoking. Harry who?
- Do not smoke?
Harry who?
Houdini.
Harry Houdini.
- You know Harry Houdini?
- Will talk about what matters?
Time is running out,
you do not want her to die!
I do not want? Do not think
're assuming too much?
- Awareness of Harry Houdini.
- You or the other?
The other. I know not
know anything about me.
It was a magical and he is dead.
It was an escape artist.
The greatest of all time.
In 1921 he was buried alive
a shirt-jacket. And he escaped.
He was 7 feet,
in a locked box ...
wearing a shirt-jacket,
and escaped.
He was too good.
What a pity!
Frances is not as smart.
Too bad thing!
It's cool to be smart.
I'm smart.
Keep your hands up!
Do not move!
- Want to see your hands! Do not move!
- Easy! Okay, guys!
- I found a wire.
- I was just showing off.
- Are you okay?
- Yes. It's okay.
Okay. I was just showing the
that she will never hold me.
Unleash it.
It's okay, guys.
Unhook it and leave. Thank you.
This guy has accumulated anger.
I can not talk that way.
Enough already.
Captain ...
Enough already. Everything is under control,
and want to continue the conversation.
Tim!
Get out!
- Thanks.
- I appreciate that.
Shut up!
- It was exciting.
- If you repeat, I'll kill you.
Okay.
Beautiful alliance.
How long have you been married?
As there will be more trapped?
Ever been in jail?
Why your husband
burned his arm?
As there will be more trapped?
Ever been in jail?
Answer my question,
and respond to her.
Her husband burned you with
cigarette because it was evil?
What is it, Madeline?
He's watching?
It's a cop?
Close the window.
We need privacy.
- Will remain open.
- I do not like snoopers.
- You'll feel more comfortable.
- No way, they must observe.
- I will not hurt. Just ...
- The window will stay open!
"Get me out of this, the coffin,
please!
- It's so dark! "
- My goodness, that excites you?
- You are pissing me off for real!
- Nice to know that chafes.
But at what point?
- Do you like blood?
- Go to hell!
- I will.
- She will die, will help or not?
I think I've helped.
- Tell me something.
- What?
Want to talk about the burns
front of her husband strip or not?
- She is losing control.
- I know.
The time of amateurism over.
It was easy, you know?
Very easy.
Kidnap her?
Imagine kidnapping her.
I used to think
about it in bed.
Sleep was impossible.
It was not so easy,
you got caught.
Really?
Did not I think
about it too?
- I do not know.
- Of course you do.
I think you know very well what
is to surrender to the fantasies.
- Madeline, to talk to you.
- Not now, Tim
"Not now, Tim
We are making progress. "
Hello, Mr. Madeline.
You are jealous of
Smoking mysterious?
Come, Madeline. Now!
Goodbye.
- The FBI will take over.
- Are they here?
Clark Hannon pulled strings.
The case is theirs now.
Go downstairs
and pass the report.
Tim ...
What happened to Madeline?
Where is the beautiful Madeline?
The party's over?
Time to get serious?
I have not voted in the governor.
I'm not from NY, came to service.
And if it did, would vote at the opponent.
He scares me. It is a weak
who acts as if he knew everything.
He knows nothing, thinks only he knows.
Have you seen the suits him?
I'm not crazy about fashion,
as you can see ...
but if I were governor,
I would only use hand-made suits.
The guy is all powerful and not
know how to use a tie. Asshole!
I'm talking about him because
even being so weak ...
he is a pawn to
some conservatives.
This governor has plenty of power.
He reinstated the death penalty
NY. Now they can kill people.
They say that lethal injection
is not so cruel.
Have you heard?
It is horrifying.
A bullet would be less cruel.
But think otherwise.
Sages always think otherwise.
The idea of sleeping
and never wake up ...
is so appalling that
makes my heart ache.
Imagine falling asleep slowly,
be stoned for this ...
Dreaming with family and friends.
Whether you dream of good things ...
but can not,
because he knows he will not wake up.
It starts fighting
against sleep ...
and to think of himself,
No cause of death ...
the person who killed him.
Soon the dreams will stop
everything will be darkness ...
no light, just death.
Nothing more.
Begins to fight the sleep ...
You need to wake up
and stop these people.
"Stop, please!
Can not sleep!
They can not make me sleep and dream
with these horrible things. "
Only one problem,
a nightmare.
So clear, cold and perfect
as the very evil personified.
Can not wake up ...
no matter how hard you try.
Can not.
Then you die so
in the most horrible torture.
That's what this governor weak
calls "not cruel".
It's what they do with
murderers in this state.
- But that monologue beast!
- Where buried, Harry?
- Where is he buried?
- Time to negotiate?
- No more monologues beasts?
- Enough.
Very good.
Can you bring me a sandwich
meat and a Coke?
I'll tell you
you need to know.
Let's play "let's make
agreement. "You're Monty Hall.
Pego and 20 years probation after
10 years for good behavior.
Promise me
and tell you where it is.
Toward Poughkeepsie
near Highway 9.
I want three teams waiting
when you get there.
I also want to paddle
and goat-feet, understood?
And doctors, too. She'll need
care once it is saved.
I want everything ready!
I want this woman alive!
I had never been
helicopter!
Do not do it.
- Do not drink!
- No stuffing, Tim
Damn! We promise that
we would not drink any more.
What do you do?
Want to throw it all away?
Check This Out!
His arm is all burnt!
What are you doing?
- There goes his perfect wife.
- I never asked that.
I cheated on you.
And drank hidden.
You do not know me.
Still love me?
Lie!
Madeline!
I'm sorry.
Do not follow me.
Please, I ...
Not worth the sacrifice.
Just a little bit.
A little more ...
I was looking for you.
Okay?
You did very well.
Do not think I messed up.
Do not worry.
I thank you, but ...
Just wanted to say could
impressions of Handsome.
- The party is no longer ours, remember?
- Not interested?
What gave?
The name is Greg Evans.
Thief second.
Booked into Miami and San Francisco
for prostitution, drugs and theft.
A nobody.
- Do you think they will find Sra.Hannon?
- I do not know.
Why Harry told the FBI?
If she dies, he gets life imprisonment.
The show gets better
if the feds get into.
- I do not think he's acting.
- Foster?
Madeline Foster?
Mollino, FBI.
- The psycho was something with her.
- Mine?
When entering the helicopter,
asked to give you this.
Sent thank the loan.
It is not so honest
managed to steal matches.
- Strange.
- Very strange.
Not lent any match.
ROOM 10
A guy came in here all day,
exactly at 13 h.
I think I was a teacher. Vineyard
every day, sitting right there ...
asked for a drink, took
denture, put on the counter ...
and drink till you drop.
Then he died.
- Nice story, Sally.
- Really.
The machine! We can find the name
Harry through the device.
- What are you talking about?
- Listen ...
We can not take fingerprints,
but he uses the device.
- You must go to a dentist.
- The barber, too, but so what?
It is a ridiculous shot,
but it must have been about 25 years.
How many guys in this
age wear braces?
We sent a picture of him at all
dentists in the city ...
by fax, email or by hand.
Someone will identify it.
All dentists in NY?
- You gone crazy?
- Does anyone have a better idea?
Does anyone have repellent?
They are eating me alive.
- Kids!
- Come on!
I found it!
I'm listening to something.
Damn!
- They are holding?
- 1,2,3 ...
How it got there?
It is not my patient.
Sorry, never seen this guy.
Yes, sir.
Okay.
Right now.
- They found her?
- Do you know who was buried?
- Who?
- The dog of Frances.
Harry turns around and says, "They wanted to know
where she was buried, no?
There is a 'she'. "
It was a bitch.
Damn!
What?
- Do you know why he sent us here?
- Why?
To show she is a murderer.
We can not say: "Tell me where
it is before I die ...
and not be accused. "
He changed the rules.
It's all a game to him.
The Feds are screwed.
- There are not.
- How so?
- You are you.
- Me?
They talked with Harry, and he said
Frances Hannon see only alive ...
if he talk to you alone.
The party is yours.
Planned it, right?
- Hi to you too.
- Answer!
- I did not plan to get caught.
- Really?
Then he took the trouble to create
these bad jokes for nothing?
- Do not see the dog engradaçada?
- No. ..
... I did not find anything funny.
- I thought it was hilarious!
Nor were we funny
we find her boyfriend dead.
There is no agreement with you.
Go get the death penalty, right?
Stop playing strip.
If I wanted it,
would have made fools of the FBI ...
dig every inch
Westchester County.
And just for his government ...
Handsome was not my boyfriend.
I'm not an idiot deer.
Needed someone to dig,
who could have got ready.
- I want to be clear.
- Killer, all right, but not gay!
That's it. We can make a
demonstration right here at the table.
- I brought cigarettes
- Fuck you!
You are uptight!
Will getting my period?
Your husband can get you
borrow a towel.
Make yourself at home.
We both felt
pleasure with pain.
I'm not like you.
Really?
I think it's just like me.
In one hour, Frances will
running out of oxygen.
So, we'll stop
to talk to you ...
you stop having fun and will
the rest of your miserable life ...
a cell of 3 m by 5 m.
Is this what you want?
That does not scare me.
I've been to prison.
Like you said, it will be charged
murder. Do not want deal.
By the way, from which he
one hour of oxygen?
Frances would be surprised if
still alive.
He said he dreamed about doing this.
- Eat a teacher too.
- Why? By chance is a game?
- Want to get revenge on the police?
- You're smart.
- Close the window and tell you everything.
- Have you ever been arrested, right?
- Must be willing to take revenge.
- Became a student of psychology?
Close the window and tell you everything.
- Go tell her where he buried?
- I will tell all!
But close the window, turn
the microphone and get rid of the cops.
I want privacy.
If you do not,
I do not open the beak.
It will be so for years and years.
Mr. Hannon will
dreaming of worms ...
eating the body
nude of his wife.
I know him.
- It's my patient.
- Are you sure?
I look like a liar?
- I said, I know!
- Has the name or address?
No. Do not register my patients.
Neither use anesthesia in surgery.
Absolutely!
I have everything!
No need to do this.
- Accurate, yes.
- Need? Why?
- When I look in his eyes ...
- What is it?
- What happens?
- Foster ...
if you need
anything, yell.
Three armed men ready
to enter that room.
- I will not need.
- He has nothing to lose.
It means that everything is possible.
- I get it.
- The helicopters are stationed.
If he speaks, we're ready.
- How long do I have?
- Look at it this way ...
anyone would agree with him.
She is already dead.
20 minutes at most.
And then?
Frances is so close that
can find her alive.
I'll tell you at the right time.
Okay.
- Tell me.
- You already know.
No, I do not know.
- You know, yes.
- I do not know, must tell me.
- First, let's talk.
- For what?
I was lucky to find you
and like you.
He planned everything and do not see why
stop now. What do you want?
I intend to hold these
chains and run away.
I plan to stay with that famous
This miracle will happen before or
after telling where he buried?
She is in the backyard.
He said this at the cemetery.
But where?
- Where?
- You already know.
Just need to think.
Come on!
I cover, you go!
C'mon!
Come on, guys!
What type of girl are you?
- She was nice or nasty?
- Tell me now where she is!
Conflicts to decide?
Want to be good because
everyone expects it?
Or evil, because
is what is real?
We can not talk.
We have no time.
When I saw the burns,
know that we are equal.
I'm not like you.
These marks do not mean
that are similar.
Know that we are equal.
So again.
You can learn from me.
We like to feel pain ...
... and sadness.
- Not the same thing.
Do not see a little
me in you?
It may not be the same level,
but exceeded the limits.
Not the same thing.
- I do not agree.
You think you understand me?
What is your theory of student
psychology? Maltreated?
My father handcuffed
and raped? Nonsense!
I'm just like everyone else!
Some women have
the fantasy of being raped.
But do not want
happen for real.
But you, Madeline ...
eventually succumbed to their fantasies.
Me too.
You did what you should not.
Why?
Why, Madeline?
Get me out ...
Get me out!
Captain!
I think you should see this.
Which side will you choose?
What makes you feel
sad and useless ...
or what makes you feel
so sad and useless, which is good?
What your friend "butt"
has what you need and search?
Tell me what it is.
Tell me where you go,
and everything will be clear.
Say.
Tell me.
Tell me! C'mon!
It is the only place
where I feel free.
Me too.
Not scary?
- Doesn 't panic?
- Yes.
And can not tell anyone.
- Your husband will never understand.
- Not true.
I never dared tell him.
You hate that side.
You know, he'll never
would love to know.
- Not true.
- See?
Still, conflicts, Madeline.
I've already won.
Always feel free.
Think like me.
Will you tell me where he buried
Frances Hannon?
Think!
Think like me.
Think like you.
- Come on! I know you can.
- He wanted to play because it's good.
It's good because it is wrong.
- You know it's good to do something wrong.
- Are you doing your little game.
It's so good that
got to stop.
Because the little game
down was wrong.
So wrong that every little
detail you excited ...
you let on.
Details excite you?
Plan ...
Planning is the best part
is not it? That's it.
- That's all.
- Plan everything.
Everything.
Just to get here.
I planned it.
Until coming to the police station
Poughkeepsie.
Yeah, Madeline.
The yard is behind this building.
FRESH INK
There, sir.
POLICE IN POUGHKEEPSIE
Good heavens!
- Phil Kline.
- Where's Madeline?
- Are you Houdini.
- Alone?
- Yes, but ...
- Hey, it was all a plan!
He planned to stay
alone with a cop!
- What are you talking about?
- Get there now!
Damn!
See the beauty of it all.
I wanted to be rich or be
superfamoso a kidnapper.
Ever wondered what the
newspapers say?
Within a week, call the police.
I say we will find the body of
Frances and a young strip ...
buried together.
And I am free forever.
In hindsight, I am a great
escape artist, is not it?
Must admit.
I'm even better than Houdini.
Do not you dare move.
Okay, time for fun.
Come here!
Stay there.
Come on. Time to
join the "Sra.Caixote.
Is it still alive?
That uncomfortable having to share
space with a corpse, is not it?
Ready for your worst nightmare?
She was so beautiful.
There seems to be at peace?
Do not even think about leaving here!
- What will you do?
- I do not know.
I'm torn between throwing
or bury you alive.
It will not do either.
Frances, what do you think?
Shoot or burial alive?
Bury this bastard!
You heard what she said.
Bury me, Madeline!
Go ahead!
I love it!
Bury me!
I want more, baby!
More! Bury me!
C'mon!
Let me, bury me!
Bury me, I'm here!
Bury me!
More! Plus, c'mon!
More!
Bury me!
Bury me, baby!
Madeline ... Madeline ...
What?
Now you're free.
The wife of millionaire
was found still alive ...
after spending 24 hours buried.
As for the kidnapper ...
Police still keeps secret
about the circumstances ...
Subtitles
by
Yavari