Dude, how much longer are
you going to play the fool?
I'm telling you,
she's a ripe, little melon,
just waiting to picking.
Look at her.
Look at her over there,
all lonely at that lonely
little lemonade stand.
Swagger over there
and say, hey, babe!
You, me, Saturday Night?
Prom? Be there.
- Be square. Huh?
- Give it a rest.
All right, play it safe then.
Walk over there and say,
hi, ah, Sandy, I was wondering
if you had a date for the prom?
How hard can that be?
You should talk.
You don't have a date.
Yeah, well, my periscope hasn't
settled on a target yet,
but it's obvious yours has.
Asking a girl out is something
I have to ease into,
otherwise I'll scare her off.
Shoot, Stan. The only
one scared is you.
No. I'm not scared. I'm cautious.
There's a difference there.
Cautious is for people
with weak bladders.
Stan, look at her.
The time is now. Okay?
You have to
claim that property now,
before some other sap will.
Maybe tomorrow. Okay?
No! There's no more time.
The prom is in three days.
Stan, look, the cards
are in your hand.
The Joker is wild.
Bet it all, or fold, baby!
Oh! Hi. Can I help you?
Two hot dogs.
Everything on 'em.
Right.
- Hi, Sandy.
- Hi.
- How's hot dog business?
- Oh, great. Great.
We're not too busy
right now though.
Yeah, I know. Me neither.
Ah, can I get a lemonade?
Sure.
So, are you going to be
taking summer school?
No, I'm taking the summer off.
There you go.
Thanks. How much do I owe you?
Do I owe you a buck?
- It's on the house.
- Thanks.
Maybe I can get
a hot dog sometime.
Oh yeah. Great. Yeah.
Do you want one right now?
- No. Ha, ha, no. Thanks.
- Okay... okay...
So, ah, are,
are you going to the--
- Hi.
- One large lemonade. Lots of ice.
Sandy, prom? You and me,
Saturday Night? Good deal?
- SANDY: There you go.
- Oh, God.
Sandy, would you like
to go to the prom with me?
- Saturday night?
- Stan.
- What?
- What are you doing?
Um... are you going to be going
to the prom by any chance?
- Nope.
- Nope?
That's cool.
I'd love to go.
So, ah, I guess I'll
see you around then?
Yeah. I'll see you at school.
Yeah, school... school.
That's right.
We go to school together.
- Well. Has the eagle landed?
- Oh, yeah. It sure has.
Cool.
She's really going
to the prom with you?
Well, she doesn't have
anyone else to go with.
Wow!
TV REPORTER: ...covered six
hundred forty-one million gap
in this year's budget.
The Los Angeles county
board of supervisors set in
motion a plan of action
Thursday, that can result in
reductions in health services.
Now, back to the studio
with Brea Walker.
Mr. Vonn.
Ah, Mr. Vonn.
Please, please sit.
Thank you.
I'm a bit short on time.
I think you'll find last nights
news cast very enlightening.
With us now, live, from Ucla,
is archaeology professor,
Dr. Rachel Richman.
Dr. Richman?
- Can you hear us?
- Yes, Brea. I'm... I'm hear.
Doctor, explain to us the
significance of the ancient ring.
The ancinet rings of power
were forged of solid gold.
As a pair, these rings have been
officially ruled as priceless.
One of the rings
has been missing
for over eight hundred years.
However, it's counterpart
has been on display at
the L.A. county
art museum since 1963.
Until tonight,
that ring was stolen.
WALKER: Police believe that the
theft was a solo operation,
which occurred earlier this evening.
No arrests have been made.
You did very well, Mr. Vonn.
I'm very pleased.
Me, too.
Perhaps, you can be of
service to me again someday.
Perhaps.
- First, the ring.
- The ring?
Yes, the ring. Where is it?
You mean, this ring. Ha, ha, ha.
It's not funny, Mr. Vonn.
Take it off.
Well, I would. But it doesn't
seem to want to come off.
Little bugger seems
to be stuck.
Mr. Vonn, take it off your finger...
or I'll have someone
take your finger off.
I suggest you honor your
deal with Mr. Deriva.
Well, I appreciate
your concern, Mr. Mosh,
but I've altered the deal.
You see, I'm going to keep
the ring and take your money.
I don't think so.
I do. Thank you, Mr. Deriva.
And this story, just in
to the CRN news center,
a powerful ring has been stolen
from Ucla art museum.
Authorities have no leads
as to the whereabouts
of the ring at this time.
Car 612. We have a 211 in
progress. Second street tunnel.
- Good evening, gentlemen.
- We came for the ring.
Ah, yes, Mr. Mosh. The ring.
Now, the ring doesn't seem
to want you, does it?
Aaaah! Get him!
Car 612.
I'm going to need back up.
Mr. Mosh, please tell Victor,
if he continues to pester me,
I'll send for his soul!
GIRL IN CAR: The cops in coming.
Have a nice evening, gentlemen.
Hey!
Officer needs assistance at the
corner of figueroa and second.
Suspect is heading...
east on second.
He said he'd send the
devil for your soul,
or something along those lines.
Kid's got a lot of nerve.
First he double-crosses me,
and now he treatens me.
That ring's supposed
to have powers.
That ring is worth
a lot of money, stupid.
He went through five of us like
we weren't even there.
- He was wearing the ring.
- Give me a break, Mosh.
Let me tell you what kind
of power that ring has...
5.5 million dollars.
That's what I paid Raymond Vonn
in advance to steal it.
And that's why he's
holding out on me.
It has nothing to do with this
hocus-pocus voodoo nonsense.
- It's chinese!
- Yeah, well, whatever it is.
We'll find him again.
We'll find him.
You do that, Mosh.
Shit.
Hey, loser.
Why don't you just shut up?
What's your problem?
Hey, loser... loser...
Loser, Mom's looking for you.
Where have you been? I've been
looking everywhere for you.
I called Dr. Maxwell's,
but they said the police
has already been there.
I know what you're thinking,
but you must let me explain.
They don't know what
happened. The police don't.
The doctor's don't.
They weren't there.
I was there. I know.
Everybody agrees on that,
but they won't believe me.
They won't understand.
They won't listen.
They won't let me go to trail.
They think... I'm crazy. Do you?
- Yes, Charice, I do.
- No! No! No, no, no, no, no!
As God as my witness,
I will prove my sanity.
I will prove it to you all!
I'll prove I'm not mad.
[ Begins Sobbing ]
- Too much?
- A little.
It'll be there.
So... did you get a date
for the prom yet?
I told you, Mom.
I'm not going to the prom.
Honey, how can you say that?
This is a very special time
in your high school career.
Boy, I remember my first prom.
It was one of the
highlights of my life.
Now, that's scary.
Look, there's a young girl
in my action class.
Her name is Amulet.
She's nice, she's very pretty.
She's a wonderful actress.
She's a virgo.
- You'd be perfect together.
- No.
- Why not?
- Because I don't want to go.
No, because he's
afraid to ask someone.
Honey, you don't have go be
afraid to ask a girl out.
No, but I'm afraid
to ask what that is.
- I wa trying something, huh.
- Ha ha ha.
- Did you taste it?
- [ Doorbell Rings ]
Okay, wise guys.
You can pay for the pizza.
Thank God he delivers.
Hey, how are you doing?
I'm going to bed, sweetie.
I've got an audition in the morning.
- Okay, good luck.
- Thanks. Stan...
promise me you'll ask at
least on girl to the prom?
- Mom!
- Please?
Okay, one. Maybe.
Who are you fooling?
I know you want to go.
- Good night, Mom.
- I'm outta here.
One turn down won't be so bad.
I will have your brother,
and we will be complete.
And together we will reign.
We will all reign supreme.
[ Chanting ]
Stan... Stan...
Stanley Dryer? Are you awake?
- [ Bell Rings ]
- Okay, saved by the bell.
Class dismissed.
Now, just because it's
the last week of school,
does not mean you don't
have to do your homework.
Everyone read chapter
67 in your text.
You never know when those
pop quizzes are coming.
- Stan, can you stay for a moment?
- Busted.
I was going through the test
last night when I got to yours.
- Yeah?
- You got an F.
I failed?
Stan, this is your
second F this semester.
Now, when this year started,
you were a decent A-B student.
Now, I want girls off your
mind and poli-sci on it.
We've got a final exam coming up
and I want to see Stan,
then student, not Stan
the romantic.
I'm sorry. I'll try harder.
As I return there
test results to you,
I pose one simple question
why do you insist
on wasting my time?
We have spent the whole year
discussing the history
of this nation
and I have given my services
to your education,
and what do I get in return?
C minus... D...
B minus...
D...
And how many time must I tell
you that the war of 1812,
was in 1812? F.
Ha, ha, hello?
This is my favorite
time of the year.
We get to throw away
all the homework
they made us do
for a whole year.
I take great pleasure
with every single tear.
- What the heck is this?
- I can't believe it.
That's the friday exam which
I didn't finish at lunch.
I thought I'd eat it later.
Man, that was like a month ago.
Sick!
You know, I can't believe I
shared a locker with you
for a whole year.
Hey, that ain't as bad
as Leon Crinkle.
He used to put his dirty
jockstraps on his locker.
So, did you finally decide
where you're going to take
Sandy after the prom?
- After?
- Yeah, dork. What hotel?
- Hotel?
- Hotel!
You've got to get her
a hotel room.
You can get a cheap room for...
twenty bucks.
It will impress her.
- Think so?
- Hell, yeah.
I can't believe it.
I love it, man.
My pal, Stan Dryer's getting a
hotel room with Sandy Applegate.
Just make sure old Leon
doesn't find out about it.
What are you talking about?
I thought she broke up with him?
Yeah... but that doesn't mean
he broke up with her though.
There he is. There he is.
That's the guy who's
been hitting on Sandy.
- Where?
- Come on, let's go.
STAN: You were drunk.
Anything's possible.
Hey!
Guys, lay off here, will you?
I hear you asked
my girl to the prom.
- What?
- I don't think you got the point.
Next time, think twice before
you ask somebody to prom.
- Leon, what are you doing?
- Get lost, Sandy.
- You betrayed me.
- What?
How could you go to
the prom with this loser?
What are you talking about?
I'm not going to prom with him.
- He didn't ask you to prom?
- No.
- You didn't ask her to prom?
All right, let this be a lesson then.
Nobody asks my girl to prom.
I'm not your girl, Leon.
We broke up, remember?
That's besides the point.
Come on.
You got lucky this time, punk!
- You never asked her out?
- No.
Cowardice knows no boundaries.
You know,
it's a good thing I didn't,
otherwise he might
not have stopped.
Hey, you know, that karate
stuff you're taking
is really paying off.
All right class, this is a
lesson in technique,
speed, focus and control.
Now, that's the end of class.
I want everybody to make sure
you're ready next week.
We have testing for capa.
Understand?
Let's everybody get up and bow.
Very nice. Dismissed.
Very, very nice.
Stan, I want to talk to you
for a minute. Come over here.
Stan, you have so much potential,
but you're not using what you
have. You lack confidence.
Do you realize how good
you could be
if you believed in yourself?
And you wouldn't be sporting
that black eye, either.
- I have to leave.
- Just think about what I said, Stan.
You know, I'm really
tired of driving you around.
- Why don't you just take a bus?
- Six weeks of karate,
and you would think
that you'd be
able to at least lay
one punch in.
What are you talking about?
There were five of them.
- That's five to choose from.
- So!
Sinsei is right.
You lack what it takes.
You understimate yourself,
so you end up getting
your butt kicked like today.
I don't want to hear it.
Tell Mom I'm going to
get my own dinner, okay.
- Where are you going?
- The park.
Later, loser.
VONN: Old man!
You waste such power on a boy.
Your vanity is surpassed only
by your ignorance, Mr. Vonn.
Hmm, hmm, hm.
Give me the ring.
You shall not have it.
You will be defeated.
Look out behind you!
Get in! Come on, get in!
Who are you?
Why is going on here, man?
He's coming after us.
OLD MAN: Faster, boy.
Stop the car.
I said, stop the car.
Stop the car, boy, now!
Okay, okay. Just stay calm.
Just remain calm, Stan.
There's a perfectly... logical...
reasons why I'm standing here,
on the beach.
Yes! But it is too
simple to understand.
Okay. I want an
explanation, old man.
The best explanation
for all things... is time.
What? Now,
what's that supposed to mean?
Okay, okay. Wake up Stan.
Just wake up.
OLD MAN: Boy!
Oh, great.
You could of helped, you know.
But, I did.
Look, just please tell me--
There is an answer
for every question.
You will learn them only
in their... due time.
For now, my body grows
tired for the last time.
Give, give me your hand.
Boy! Please!
Give me your hand.
The ring is not
the source of power.
It is... but a doorway
to the Power Within you.
Wait!
Hold on! Just stay with me.
God. We've got to
get you to a doctor.
Open your eyes!
I have been on is Earth
for eighty-seven years.
I am ready to leave.
No.
Don't leave me! Please!
No!
Dude, I'm telling you, man,
it's a red wire.
- It's a green wire, man.
- No, it's the red wire.
- Get that lighter down here,
dude. I need some light.
- You're going to burn the dash.
If you touch that...
You're going to get a shock
if you touch that wire.
- Ha, ha, ha, haaa.
- Ah!
Shut up, man.
Get that lighter down here.
- [ Others Continue to Laugh ]
- It's the red wire.
Oh, here comes some
little kid, man.
Hey, guys.
Mind getting out of my car?
[ Everyone Laughs ]
Your car?
[ Belch ] We're sittin' in it.
- Doesn't it make it our car?
- Look...
I'm tired and I've had a long night.
I just want to go home, okay?
He's tired. It's late.
And he just wants to go home.
[ Laughing Continues ]
We want to go home, too.
So why don't you give us the
keys... and we'll go home.
Would you please
get out of my car?
He doesn't want to
give us the keys, man.
Keys, man!
Come on, get the keys.
He's going to get the keys.
Watch it, man.
He's got a hell of a right.
Come on, man.
Come on, little boy.
[ Belch ]
Oh, is this your car...
Oh, sorry man.
TV: Only one of you can
emerge as a champion.
Pay your respects.
Stanley, do you know
what time it is?
Loser, you're missing magic kid.
- Look, I'm sorry I'm late. Okay?
- Stanley...
I don't have any excuses,
I just want to go to sleep.
All right? is that okay? Okay.
- Go check out your brother.
- Okay.
Yeah, dip lips. Where were you?
- Get out of my room.
- What's with the peanut butter?
- Get out!
- I don't think so, cheesehead.
Okay, let go.
- How did you do that?
- I don't know.
- Get out of my room.
- Okay, okay. Chill.
Foolish old man.
Curse your dead soul.
[ Breathing Heavily ]
[ Heartbeat Heard ]
[ Laughing Heard ]
[ Laughing Grows Louder ]
- Sweetheart... honey, wake up.
- What?
- Are you all right?
- Huh?
- Mom, what are you doing?
- Trying to wake you up.
You're waking up
the entire neighbourhood.
- You okay?
- Yeah, sorry.
It's all right.
What did you do?
- Meet Freddie Kruger?
- God. It was so intense.
I was fighting all these
ninjas at Culver Bridge.
Hmm. Ninjas at Culver Bridge.
Wow!
Well, it's only a dream.
You know,
after your father died,
- I had nightmares every night.
- Did they stop?
Sure. As soon as I decided not
to let them scare me anymore.
- Easier said, than done.
- You know, sweetheart,
we have to choices in life,
and we face them everyday.
To be, or not to be.
Hey, I'm serious here.
You either are, or you aren't.
You do, or you don't.
And the world doesn't make
those choices for you.
I don't make those choices
for you. Kids at school don't.
The only one who can decide
who and what you are, is you.
To be, or not to be, Stan.
That's it.
Hey, how'd that
interview go today?
Oh, well, after I signed
three autographs,
they said no one would
accept pig-tailed "Peggy"
as a Raving Lunatic. Ha, ha, ha.
Who cares what they think,
I know you can be
a Raving Lunatic, Mom.
- That's all that matters.
- Thank you.
- Good night, sweet prince.
- Good night, Mom.
- Sleep tight.
- Okay.
- [ Indistinctive Chatter ]
- [ Bell Rings ]
Okay, our next set of questions
will involve the cold war era,
and they would be directed
towards... Stanley Dryer.
Explain what death blow was
dealt to the communist party
by Gorbachev in 1989.
Um... he ordered that party
members could no longer enjoy
private privileged access
to food and housing,
and communism suddenly lost its
appeal to card carrying members.
That's good. Next question.
What kind of tactics were used
to gain freedom from
the party conservatives?
A political shift towards
western style presidency,
and a cabinet system
of government,
utilizing the popularly elected
people's congress.
Well, that's right. Next question.
What was the result of
the Sinatra Doctrine?
Well, it replaced the
Brezhnev Doctrine,
so, it was quite electrifying.
Um...
solidarity put gorby to
the test by demanding
a dominant voice in
polish government.
But, with little assistance in sight,
Solidarity won stunning
election victories over poland.
Reformers drove out
communists,
and free elections
were set for 1990.
The fresh winds of change
have finally arrived.
Any more questions?
- Ha, ha.
- I'm impressed.
I don't know where
you got your cheat sheet,
but I want a copy.
I have in my possession,
the graded results of
the final written exam.
And I say to you once more,
why do you torment me
with your blatant disregard
of my educational services?
F...
D...
C...
I feel as if we had accomplished
nothing during the past year,
except to fix your position
as belligerent students,
and my position as
an old windbag.
A... plus.
An f?
[ Bell Rings ]
Sandy, we dated
for over four weeks.
I mean that's a month.
Doesn't that mean
anything to you?
Could you hold your
voice down, please, Leon.
- People are watching.
- Oh, come on!
Look...
Remember all the
good times we had?
Remember how you used
to stay after school
and watch my football practice?
Remember all the beer parties?
I remember sitting home
on friday nights
while you went out
with rock and goobie.
I remember watching TV
all day on weekends
with your older brothers,
who by the way, are all pigs.
How could you say that?
They all went varsity.
- Everyone of them.
- God.
Man, that sap doesn't
know when to give up.
Somebody ought to shove a
jockstrap in his mouth.
I think I could
do better than that.
What?
It's not going to happen.
I'm tired of it.
- Enough.
- Stan, where are you going? Stan?
Excuse me one second, guys.
Sandy, would you like
to go to the prom with me?
- What?
- Prom? You and me?
- You're dead meat, Dryer.
- Oh, but, Leon. Wait, wait, wait.
Stan doesn't know
what he's talking about.
He's... a... suffering delusions,
he hasn't been himself lately.
- You got to forgive him.
- I've got one work for you, Graves.
Move your butt,
or I'll move it for you.
Isn't that like,
eight words to many.
- Leo, no!
- Hey, that's it, Dryer.
It's like a cuisinart
thing you did there.
Jockstrap in the mouth
is a bit extreme.
Yaaah!
Speed and execution.
That's what it's all about.
I want you to remember, when
you're performing breaks,
it's dangerous. Speed and
execution is very important.
Excuse me, Sinsei.
Don Wilson is here.
Don.
Don, it's a pleasure
to see you again.
It's a pleasure to see you.
Everybody, we have
an honored guest today.
Retired Kickboxing Champion,
Don "The Dragon Wilson."
I want everybody to
get up right now. Quick.
Courtest bow.
Don "The Dragon Wilson."
Good to see you, Don.
All righty, sit down.
Johnson stay up,
Dryer, stay up.
Johnson, I want you to be
very, very careful with Dryer,
he's only a green belt,
you understand?
You're a black belt.
Ready? Bow here.
Bow to each other.
Ready, set.
Careful, guys.
Easy.
DON: Sensei, let me speak
with Dryer for a minute.
You did great.
Your technique and strategy
was right on the money.
You also seem pretty
sure of yourself,
- Set.
- all of a sudden,
I have all of this
power and confidence.
I mean, you saw me
beat up that black belt.
Yes, I did.
But that was the easy part.
What do you mean?
Marital Arts has more to
do with mental toughness
and more responsibility, than
just beating up black belts.
Ha, ha, ha.
What are you talking about?
You had a whole career
of beating up people.
No, I didn't.
That was kickboxing.
It was just a sport.
I had the utmost
respect for my opponments.
It's true, you're good,
and someday you might be
a champion yourself.
But remember there's a
responsibility that comes
with your abilities,
and it's the proper
use of power that's important.
Dude, are you on, like,
on steroids, or something?
What?
Well, you kicked Leon's
booty in class today,
and that's not like you.
Nah, I've just been
working out. That's all.
What was that Einstein
stuff in class today, huh?
- I've been studying.
- No, no, no, I don't buy it.
You've been taken over
by an alien life form,
haven't you? Yeah, you have.
You can tell me.
It's okay, I'm your buddy.
I was reading about
it in the enquirer.
- Excuse me, Stan?
- Sandy, hi, how are you?
- Can I talk to you a minute?
- Oh, yeah. Sure.
What? Oh, I'm sorry.
Excuse me.
I was thinking about
what you asked me today,
- you know, about prom.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
- And?
- Yes.
- Yes?
- Really?
- Really.
- Oh, that's... that's great!
So, what are you
doing right now?
Right now?
I was thinking if
you're not doing anything,
then maybe we could
do something.
Um, actually right now,
I'm not doing anything at all.
Ah, Eric, you said that you
could handle things alone?
- Alone, me?
- Yeah.
Oh, yeah! Oh!
hey, you two kids go!
Play! Have a good time.
Yeah, I'll man these dogs myself.
Hot dogs?
[ Rock Music Playing ]
# Oh baby come on let's close
our eyes and hold on tight #
# We'll try our best to hang on
to this wild ride called life #
# Don't think about tomorrow
it will soon be yesterday #
# But you live for each moment
isn't that what people say #
# Ten million mysteries are
stored inside my head #
# Why in the world
do we glee instead #
# When you're mine all mine #
# I look at the future
now with tear filled eyes #
# You're mine all mine #
# And everything just
seems to fall in line #
# That you're mine #
# You could fill the ocean
with all of the men #
# Who told you they loved you
with truth in their eyes #
# You might have felt it
you might have seen it coming #
# But I guess to me
it's still a big surprise #
You know, working here,
I forgot how much
fun this place can be.
I know I really
love this place, too.
# You're mine all mine #
# I look at the future now
with tear filled eyes #
# You're mine all mine #
# And everything is
sure to fall in line #
# Now that you're mine #
# Come on baby let's
close our eyes #
# You hold on tight to
this ride called life #
# Let's talk about tomorrow #
# Let's talk about tomorrow. #
I can give you a
ride to your car.
No. Uh, thanks, but it's not far.
Well, I guess I'll
see you tomorrow night?
- Got your tux rented?
- Yep.
Okay, so, uh,
I'll see you soon?
Okay.
Hi, Stanley.
It is Stanley, isn't it?
Oh, you can run, but you can't...
Well, you know.
Hey, kid. Remember me?
The man of your dreams.
You've got something
I want, Stanley.
Must we play these games?
Get in! Get in,
if you want to escape.
Hello, Mr. Vonn.
How's it hanging?
Persistent little bugger,
aren't you, Mosh?
Actually, Mr. Vonn... I am.
- STAN: Who are you?
- Hin-See.
Master Yung was
my grandfather.
STAN: He's the old man
who stuck this on my finger.
Why was I being chased?
Where are we going?
HIN-SEE: Stan! Very soon,
all your questions
well be answered.
We're here.
What?
Where are you going?
Where am I?
The house of my grandfather,
Master Yung.
Why did he put this ring
on my finger?
YUNG: Surely you can do such a
simple task as removing the ring?
Yung! Yung!
What?
He was just talking to me.
- He said something to me.
- This is Jendo.
He's a chimpanzee.
[ Sighing ] Yeah. Yeah. Right.
- Are you all right?
- Yeah. Fine.
He hasn't been the same, since
my grandfather passed away.
YUNG: I'm a good boy,
but not that good.
You... You're dead!
No. I'm alive! More alive
than I have ever been.
No. I saw you die.
You're dead!
Your fear is your weakness.
- Who are you?
- Master Yung. Who are you?
- What do you mean, who am I?
- I see, you do not know either.
- I'm Stan Dryer.
- Very good.
- We're off to a good start.
- Start?
- All right! Cool! Yeah!
- CABRELL: He fought with that man.
That's what the report says.
Lieutenant Cabrell,
my son is anything
but what you just described.
Well, what I described
to you was attested to
by a dozen different witnesses.
They all saw Stan fighting
with that man.
How can a dozen different
witness be wrong?
- Are you saying his mother is wrong?
- No.
I'm saying his mother
wasn't there to see it.
He's sixteen, he's never
been in a fight.
Believe me! He's a good boy.
We're off on the wrong foot,
here. That's my fault.
I'm sorry. I don't mean
to be pointing fingers here,
I just need to settle
the facts of this case
the best way I can.
And to do that,
- I'm going to need your help.
- Sure.
You mind if I ask you
where your husband is?
- I'm a widow.
- Oh. I'm sorry to hear that.
So it's just you
and your two sons?
Uh-huh. Is there
something wrong with that?
No. There's nothing
wrong with that.
Listen, I have my men out
looking for Stan right now.
- If anything comes up--
- You'll call me.
I'll call you.
- Can I ask you something?
- Yes.
- Are you?
- Yes, I am.
I knew it.
I grew up on that show.
Um, so did I.
I had such a crush on
"Pig-tailed Peggy,"
back when I was eight years old.
Do you mind if, if I get...
- What?
- Your autograph?
Oh, sure.
I'd say it's for my kids,
but I don't have any kids.
I wish you did. Because then
you'd understand,
how ridiculous these
accusations are.
Mr. Deriva, it won't come off.
Use a knife.
Ah, Raymond!
Welcome to the party.
Mr. Mosh here, is about to
take what you owe me.
- And whatever else comes with it.
- I owe you nothing.
I paid you! I gave you
everything you asked for!
And you served your
purpose well.
Ha. You do have an ego, don't you?
I would of played
it straight with you,
but you're the one who
double-crossed me. Why?
Oh, because you're a fool,
Mr. Deriva.
And I would be a fool
to follow you,
and I can't have that now, can I?
I would rather the boy
have the ring, than you.
Boy?
- What boy?
- The boy with the other ring.
Other ring?
I don't have time to explain
right now, Mr. Deriva,
but, I'd like to make
a new deal with you.
[ Chuckling ]
Do you think I'm stupid.
No deal! Cut the finger!
I think you'll like this
deal quite simply.
Obey me, or die!
Now, can I have
everybody's attention?
[ Groaning ]
Let me repeat my proposition
one more time.
Quite simply, obey me, or,
I think you remember the rest.
Victor!
Please. There you go.
I think you'll make a fine
example to your boys.
- What do you say?
- Work for me!
Oh, I think you should
have taken heed
to Mr. Mosh's warnings.
This ring does harbor power.
Power greater than you
can imagine,
and I wear it on my finger!
YANG: You're the one chosen
to carry the ring.
What do you mean,
I was chosen?
You make it sound like the
ring makes its own decisions.
It does. The ring is a vessel,
a key to the secrets
and strengths each and
every man holds within.
It is a doorway to the
power of the will.
- It selected you as its bearer.
- Why me then?
It is not for you to question.
It is for you to accept.
Okay. Okay. So, I'm going
to pass this thing
through my family,
for let's say,
the next eight hundred years?
Only until the ring
decides different.
I'm as baffled by its
selection as you,
but, that is of no matter.
What does matter,
is that you were chosen.
Yeah. I'm the chosen one.
It's time for rest.
Shhh!
Your grandfather's not
that great
in the explanation department.
My grandfather thinks that
the best explanation
- for everything is--
- Yeah, yeah, I know.
Don't tell me. Time.
Right.
Stan, listen to me. Long ago...
a great emperor longed
for strength.
He entered a volcano,
and three days later
he emerged with
two matching rings.
The rings of power.
When he put these two rings on,
the emperor became all powerful,
but he misused his power,
bringing death and misery
to his whole village.
And one day,
the volcano erupted,
destroying the emperor
and his whole city.
The only survivors...
were the two rings themselves.
These rings must be split up,
and never again
worn by the same man.
And as bearer of this ring,
it is your responsibility to
uphold this commandment.
Vonn is in search of the
other ring to abuse its power.
You must make sure
he never acquires it.
Because if he does,
neither you, nor anyone,
will ever be safe again.
Do you understand?
[ Door Bell Ringing ]
- Oh, Lieutenant. Come in.
- It's, it's Jim. Remember?
I'm sorry. Jim, come on in.
No, no. Actually,
I'm just stopping by.
You left this at the, ah,
at my office.
- Oh, thank you.
- No problem.
- Any word?
- No.
But, as soon as I know something,
you'll know something.
Thanks.
- Well, good night, Mrs. Dryer.
- Clyda.
Clyda.
[ Vonn's Voice Screaming ]
Stanley!
YUNG: Don't be afraid.
[ Ominous Laughing ]
Yung! Yung!
I had a dream!
- You don't have to yell, boy.
- What are you doing, fishing?
Heaven is different for everyone.
For me, it is fishing.
- Last night I had a dream.
- Not a dream, boy, a vision.
What do you think
I should do about it?
With the ring...
You will experience power
greater than ever imagined!
Understanding it is like a seed.
Nurture it, and it will grow.
Oh my God! Oh my God!
I'm totally late! I've got to go!
I'm late for a date.
Boy, wait! The ring brings
you many strengths...
but you will be strongest,
when you use your own
true abilities.
Okay, gentlemen.
I'm going to tell you
a story of a wicked boy,
named Stanley.
Listen closely. You'll all get
to know him very shortly.
- Would you hold still?
- Mom, where's my mascara?
Oh, sweetheart, I don't think
you need any more mascara.
You know, where's your
ivory broach?
What do you mean I don't
need any more mascara?
Well, I think you're
wearing enough already.
I mean, any more and
you'll need a red nose,
and big floppy shoes. Now,
where is your ivory broach?
What do you mean red
nose and floppy shoes?
Are you saying I look
like a clown?
You know, I have to find
that ivory broach.
What ivory broach? Mom!
Am I wearing too much
make-up? Mom!
What ivory broach?
The ivory broach your older
sister wore at her prom.
The ivory broach that I wore to
my prom, that ivory broach.
Should I put on some more
lipstick, you know,
- to subdue the mascara?
- No.
The ivory broach that
my mother gave to me,
that her mother gave to her.
It's been in our family
for generations!
Oh God! I can't just
cake it on or
I will look like a clown.
I can't believe this!
If I have lost that
ivory broach.
- I will never forgive myself.
- [ Door Bell Rings ]
Oh my God! That's him.
Oh my God! Oh my God!
Oh! I can't go
through with this.
- What are you talking about?
- I look like a clown.
What? What ever
gave you that idea?
You did.
Oh, sweetheart!
I was only kidding.
Sit down. Look in the mirror.
Huh?
You look like a princess,
right out of a fairy tale.
Now, you finish getting
dressed. Huh?
- I'll answer the door.
- Stall him.
Yes!
- Hi.
- Hi. I'm Stan Dryer.
- Hi. Come on in.
- Thanks.
- I'm Gail, Sandy's mother.
- Hi, it's nice to meet you.
Well, I've heard
so much about you.
Sandy's so excited.
Uh, have you been driving long?
- Hi.
- Wow. You look great.
- Really?
- Yeah.
- You both look wonderful.
Uh, this is definitely
a kodak moment!
I'll be right back.
Okay. Ah, Stan, maybe a
little closer. Ah... okay.
Ah, no. Ah, Stan,
put your arm around Sandy.
- Is that okay with you?
- Yeah.
That's good. Okay, let's see.
Ah, come on you guys!
You are going to a prom,
not a funeral!
[ Up-Beat Music Playing ]
[ Crowd Talking
Music Continues ]
- Thank you.
- You are most certainly welcome.
Well, look who's here, Sandy.
- Dryer. Let's go.
- Thank you.
- You're certainly welcome.
- Thank you very much.
- Looking very spiffy.
- Thanks.
- You seem different, Stan.
- Is that okay?
Yeah. I like it.
I mean, not that I didn't
like it before, I do.
- You did?
- Yeah.
I just didn't think you'd
be interested in me.
[ Door Bell Ringing ]
- Yes?
- Mrs. Applegate?
- Yes.
- I'm Clyda Dryer. May I come in?
- Please.
- Thank you. My son Stan...
- goes to school your daughter--
- You're "Pig-tailed Peggy."
Oh my God! "Pig-tailed Peggy."
I can't believe it's you.
Yes. Well, anyway,
you see my son--
I have seen a fan of yours
since I was six years old.
I wore my hair in pigtails until
I was seventeen,
because of you!
- Great! I'm very flattered.
- Look, the reason I'm here--
Do you remember that show,
when you hair
got caught in that meat
grinder? And oh--
Mrs. Applegate! My son is missing.
I found your daughter's
name and address
- written down in his room.
- Missing?
- Yes.
- Well, I don't understand.
- He took my daughter to the prom.
- He what?
[ Slow Tempo Music Playing ]
I can't believe I'm
actually at the prom
and having a good time.
- Why?
- Because, I came with you.
Not that I didn't expect to
come to the prom with you
and have a good time, but,
well, yeah,
because I didn't expect to
come to the prom with you.
Or to have fun. I just thought
I would be Leon's
arm-piece, you know? Boring!
- I hope you're not bored with me.
- No. Are you?
You know what I want.
Have fun!
[ Music Continues Playing ]
[ Music Stops Abruptly ]
Stan, what's going on?
Sandy. Leave.
I think you have something
that belongs to me, kid.
Leave!
Take him!
Stanley, where have you been?
What are these handcuffs
doing on you?
Handcuffs, cool!
What are these handcuffs
doing on him?
Strong, why don't
you take deke, and show him
where we keep the
cookies around here.
Your son was arrested tonight
for the assault on twenty men.
Twenty? What is this,
some kind of joke?
Come on!
Take the cuffs off him.
It's not a joke.
He was just beginning
to explain to me,
not only how he was able
to beat up twenty men,
but what he's doing in
possession of a stolen ring,
that's now stuck on his finger.
Well, Stanley, explain!
The best explanation
for all things...
- Is time.
- Well...
- there you go.
- [ Sighs ]
Dr. Rachel Richman,
Professor of Archaeology.
Oh yes, of course.
I'm sorry.
Lieutenant Cabrell.
Nice to meet you,
and thank you for coming.
- There's the ring.
- Well, couldn't you have
at least removed it
from his finger?
That's part of the problem.
It isn't coming off.
Doctor, would you excuse us
for just a minute, please?
Be gone. Be gone.
You're of no use to me.
Look, I may have to detain
him possibly overnight.
What? You mean
put him in jail?
The ring is stolen property,
and it's not coming off
of his finger.
- I can't let that leave the station.
- I don't believe this!
Did you try butter?
Would you please hold still,
young man?
Oh my heavens! Oh my God!
- It is your ring, isn't it?
- No, it is not.
What do you mean?
Lieutenant, may I use
your telephone?
- What's the matter?
- DR: RICHMAN: It's the other ring.
Other ring. What's going on?
It's the missing twin ring,
thought to have been
lost for over eight
hundred years!
Give me President Hathaway!
VONN: Stanley!
Dreams do come true.
- Come on, Stanley.
- No!
Stanley, she's scared!
That is not the ring stolen.
It's the stolen ring's
counterpart, a twin ring.
When worn with the other,
is said to make the
wear invincible.
Stanley! Stanley!
What are you doing?
- Hey! Stop that kid!
- Stanley!
You come back here
right now!
Stay right here!
Hurry get in the car!
- Why would he go crazy like that?
- He was called.
Called? Called by who?
Called by what?
By the other ring. has your
son been suffering nightmares?
Culver Bridge.
Oh God! Somebody!
Oh God!
SANDY:
Somebody help me please!
Stay here!
Hey kid, so we meet again!
SANDY: Stan!
Good show, Stanley.
Wonderful!
- How about an encore?
- [ Thugs Hollering ]
SANDY: Stan!
Very impressive, Stanley.
But, they're not wearing
the ring, are they?
I guess it's just you and me.
Wait! No!
He was to do it himself.
Come here, please.
Yaah!
SANDY: Stan! No!
Stay here!
YUNG: Boy, the rings are
not the source of power.
The true power lies within you!
You destroyed them! You fool!
Stanley!
Don't hurt me, Stanley. No.
Please, I'm fragile. Really.
- You lose!
- Yes! Yes! I lose.
- I lose, Stanley.
- You're powerless, Vonn!
- Yes! Yes!
- It is Vonn, isn't it?
Oh, gee!
CLYDA: Are you okay, Stan?
Thank you! Thank you!
Stan!
- You saved my life!
- Piece of cake.
- Are you okay?
- Yeah. Great!
Oh!
Raymond Vonn is wanted in
three countries for art theft.
I think we've found
our ring theft.
Jim?
- Thanks.
- You're welcome.
Well, it looks like that
about raps it up?
That hardly raps it up.
You've got a lot of
explaining to do, mister.
Well, Mom, the best
explanation for all things--
Don't even say it!
Come on. Let's go home.
YUNG: Boy, the power
has always been within you.
You defeated Vonn with
your own true abilities.
You have fulfilled the
destiny of the rings.
I have come to the end
of my journey,
but, Stanley, yours...
has just begun.
Captioned by Grantman Brown