Hey! Excuse me. You there.
Looking for work? Trabajo? Trabajo?
Hey, my father is looking for somebody
to clean the pool.
"Hard-Pressed in the Heartland - Peter Rachleff"
"Between the Devil and the Deep Blue Sea - Marcus Rediker"
Going boating?
Where the fuck have you been fratboy?
You trying to get an education on the sly?
Yeah. He steals books for the donut lady.
Ew. Not Marta. She's way too old.
- Yeah it's sad.
Fuck you trailer trash.
When did you last have a date that wasn't your hand?
Damn I miss you boys.
Come on, let's get some juice.
No man, it's all sugar. It should be illegal.
- Work, uh need work.
- No work. Go away.
- Please. I good worker.
- Hey, what are you deaf son?
I said no work! Nada. Adios.
Please give me work.
- Hey buddy, did you hear the man?
He said there's no work.
Oh shit. Call the cops.
I'll take care of it.
Listen chico. You leave or were calling the cops.
Policia. Policia.
Boten a este chico a taco bell
Let's hit the border.
Before the border hits you!
There! He's heading back to the fence.
Put the brights. Now now now!
Fucking beaner.
Look at him run
David! Shit!
Come back!
Come back to the Marlboro Land!
Come on in!
Disneyland is just a half away!
You can have it all!
Eat all you can!
A Walmart for every family!
USA all the way! USA all the way!
Call it in!
Calling Officer Sherrot. Calling Officer Sherrot.
This is the warboys.
We got a whole herd stateside just at
the Deadman's Canyon. Get them while they're hot!
Let's go track 'em!
- What? No no way!
- David stop fucking around
- That's asking for trouble man. No.
Pussies
Come on! Come on!
USA all the way! USA all the way!
Storm Lake, Iowa
Wakey wakey
Get out of my face
You still got a pool?
- Sure. Its in the top right drawer.
Nature calls
Don't shoot. I'm a US citizen.
Honest!
Scared me half to death.
I'll take her home
She says the bike's her own but it can't be.
It's a thousand dollar bike.
Look. I borrowed the bike.
You're in trouble miss.
- I am trouble mister
OK. Lets say 3 o' clock.
And look I'm gonna have to postpone
that trip to Houston.
My son's in town. I know. I know
But it'll wait
They need me
Well, its good to see you boys again.
Still working weekends on the
garage, Gregorio?
Ahh. That's me. Actually I'm thinking
of helping my dad out with his business.
María I'll have those eggs now por favor.
And you Greg?
Still at the library Mr. Welch.
- But I'm thinking of taking some night classes.
- Good for you.
We still miss your father
He was one of our finest at the border patrol.
Boys, sorry to say..
but i've got to steal David for a couple of hours
this afternoon. Father and son, you know
Heart to heart
We miss him didn't we George?
He begged to fly home weekend after weekend.
I said no, wait till spring break
and show 'em what your made of.
And they will show you the...
The ladder to the top
Dad
My son needs his studies and the sports.
And what with his looks
God knows how much sex
Dad they're not interested.
- But they are! Aren't you boys?
Maria some more syrup for George here
and Greg here, have another donut.
My son. Straight A's.
Sports trophies up the yin yang.
Landed at the 5th best school in the nation.
- And now..
- You're boring them Dad.
Well then entertain us my son.
Tell us what's new.
- Quit!
- I got a call from the dean last night.
What do you suppose he had to tell me?
Christ!
We must bring our entertainment to a close
David. Noon at my office.
Its good to see you boys.
What's your Dad so pissed about?
- You and me Greg, he thinks we're trash.
Nothing to do with you
I'm not on break from school.
I was suspended
What?
- You cut classes?
I went to all my classes
And got naked
- Bullshit!
Sitting in class one day I just felt
constricted so I took my clothes off
Piece by piece
I left my socks on though
Sat the entire way through
my first class bare-assed
And the second class someone objected.
It was a political science class.
That is fucked up man.
- What are you gonna do?
What gets me is how long it took anyone to object.
Nobody asked me what the hell I was doing.
They just pretended I was dressed.
Ok, why'd you do it?
They were asleep. Fuckin' zombies.
They needed a wake up call
- Jesus. You put your nuts on display
for the whole world to see. No way!
I was tired of waking up every morning
and thinking what the fuck am I doing here?
So I shed my skin and headed home.
Adios duke! This is where I wanna be.
We love you too buddy
How you doin' David?
You back from spring break?
I thought I should check in with my boys
- Well, give your father my regards
Return of the conquering hero eh?
We missed you, George says he can at least
write a postcard and I say you got hands, write him yourself
But no...
Hey Cactus, you look good on that bike
George, George sweetheart I need your help a minute.
Cortex Taxi Service. Always running.
Saw it on a film
Got to go
Take this and get rid of it.
Thanks boys.
I don't know where she keeps finding them.
Brought you another book
- Griffiths - These Are The Times
- Yeah, these are the times
- How about tonight?
- What exactly is your criteria for choosing my books?
When I was on the return pile
You know I'm risking jail
stealing these books for you
- You owe me a date
- Not tonight
Tomorrow night?
I know that happened
Yeah, everyone knows what happened
You know her?
So we got a date tomorrow or what?
Well, it's a start I guess
You got a sweetheart up at Duke?
Someone special?
I haven't met any of them too special
- Things ok? You seem kinda...
- Jumpy?
Here have my sandwich. I'm not hungry.
- You lost weight.
- Dad, what's the problem?
- Tell it to me straight
- Debts, David
Lean and mean times
It's always something. So...
you got to take risks and when you do
everybody gets a little jumpy
But you stick with it.
Competition strangles the best of us
It's knowing how far you can bend
the rules of the game
Tell me Dad, you know you can trust me
My trucks carry all sorts these days
And so you have to make arrangements
with the border patrol
Jesus Dad
- Drugs?
- Televisions
Designer Jeans
- Black market?
- I knew it
- It's called the free market
But my concern is your future not mine
Listen Dad, I got this all figured out
I quit school, I stay here with you
It'll be like you used to say
after mom died
"It's just you and me now we've got to stick together"
And we can do that here working side by side
Go on
I'm natural when it comes to business
I don't need a degree in law
I've got everything I need right here
We'll take over, you and me
Are you finished?
- No, Dad remember?
It's the wild west out there
and we can tame it
You're going back to school
- No, Dad, listen
How did you think I've felt when that dean called me?
And why did you pull such a pathetic stunt?
For attention? We're you feeling lonesome?
Did you need a hug?
You have no idea. You think I didn't try to fit in?
Huh? That I didn't try to make it work?
The only place that I'm happy is here with you.
I'm not going back
I love you, but you are going back to school
and you're gonna be the best damn lawyer in the state
Things are gonna work out just like we planned
- Fuck him! Fuck! Fuck!
Would you two like to make some serious money?
- How?
TVs, truckload. Easy steal, risk free
From my Dad
That's low
That's scraping the bottom of the barrel
I'm in
No. I'm..
To a parent like that? It's like Original Sin
So? He won't miss 'em.
They're black market from Mexico
Whose gonna complain? And no one will suspect us
I'm in
You already said that. Give me back my hat
I'm getting out of here. I'm not wasting myself
Shit
How much are we talkin'?
Thousands
Hey, put the books back on the shelves
Why are you doing this to your Dad?
- Coz it's a thrill
And we need a thrill. Fuck it
- Fuck it?
Cmon David don't bullshit me
What the hell's with you?
Talk to me or I'll hit you
I don't know
I don't fuckin' know
It's ok, I guess
I missed you
Yeah
It used to be a frontier out here
Kill or be killed. Be a slave or be free
And now what are the choices that matter?
Paper, plastic, Lubricated rib?
Regular, decaf, eat in, take out
- Pay to go or contract - To rent or to buy
Let's do it!
Fuck it!
Want to get us shot?
10:30. She's due
Where is everybody?
- They'll hit the canteen before it closes at 10:30
It's cool. Done my homework
Does anyone else have a sense of doom?
Greg, bolt cutters are yours
- Right boss
Log in, change in drivers.
Tell a few jokes. Take a leak
Ok. you've got about 3 minutes.
Ready?
Let's go
Shit!
Are you sure its gonna be ok here?
- Scrapyard will think its the army. Army will think its the scrapyard
Need to find someone to sell them to
- Your Dad won't report it, right?
No way
- Oh man. He's gonna be pissed
So when do we sell them?
We need to get down low in a few days.
We need to make an increase, right George?
How much time do you need?
- Two, three days at the most
I know just the guy
Fuck it
Thank you
Always old fashioned.
One sugar donut
And six donut holes.
Make it quick
Got a long day ahead of you partner?
- Long enough
You heading for the border?
You with the law?
- Whose law?
Roger, Slater, morning
Roger listen, bad news. We had a theft last night
Yeah. Fully loaded
Of course I do. That's not it
I didn't want to wake you
Trust me I'm taking care of this
Yeah, I'm gonna send them out to
find the usual suspects
Exacly. Relax
Relax, we'll find it
I'll call you back
I didn't get much sleep last night
- It looks that way
Hey David you up for a swim?
- I don't think so
Well, I'll leave you alone then..
What the hell?
Zero out of ten for that dive.
What's up Dad?
One of our trucks was stolen last night
- Shit
Can we get it back?
- Unlikely
Our concern now is to find out who took it
and keep a lid on this
This is a well planned operation
Professionals?
- Yeah
But we've got our own professionals
who will find them.
In the meantime, you just get your head ready
to get back to your educaton
I'm gonna fuck who ever did this
None of your fuckin' business
Don't move
Did they hurt you?
I got a hard knee
I don't look like an illegal, do I?
I just got mugged. I think I'm owed
to something nice. Nourishing.
Nourishing?
You need to teach me how to make donuts
- Howdy
- Hi honey
Where's Kat?
She went to get you donuts
- Hey hey, on the nail please
Old tuber Tyler says he saw you the other night
- Oh yeah?
Still out with the border patrol?
I would rather not you doing your partying on the border
- We're not partying out there mom
Patrol's worth shit without us
Hey, I will not have that kind of
trash talk in this family
Sorry mom
When I was five, I used to sit on
his shoulders and play drums on his head
We used to be friends, but now
I'm just a beaner to him
The ones that are here I love
but the others I don't know about
Have you given up a daughter?
Maybe you forgot
Me too, I have to get this
donuts to my brother
Not so thick. Just half an inch
How come you don't have a boyfriend?
Now, If I make the perfect donut...
Will you go out with me?
I like older women
Older women. The way you say it
sounds like you starters
Show me
Now those are perfect donuts
What time should I pick you up?
Mom, I want to be a vision to the devil himself
My devil is out back
Great, did you chew them up especially for me?
I got them for you
- Have you seen your pillow?
Who cares about my pillow?
Who cares?
Shit. You know what when you came to us as a baby I used to spit on your head everytime I walk by your cradle cause I knew how you'd turn out
You liar
Speak English, Jesus!
I'm just waiting for the day you disappear to
one of your detours so I can have some peace
Why don't you move out like a real adult
and give me some air to breath?
It's an embarrassment to be your sister.
Look at your skin
Your not my sister
Yeah, I am
Where to sir?
Anywhere but here
Didn't ever bother you and mom when you adopted her?
Never
She's not one of us
What bothers me is whats what I knew
I'm just a regular shit
Hey give me a smoke will you?
Me and David
We're gonna make some money
And were gonna travel
Sorry I got no cash
Walch, your name is Walch?
- Yup, that's me
Slater Walch?
- My father
I don't want your money.
You're not welcome here, please leave.
Wait a minute...
- Tell your father his business stinks
I'll have no part of it. Go
I have to meet George and David later
on at the Old train depot
You ever been there?
Well, we used to hang there when
we were kids, you should come.
Ok, but I've got to stop by
at the garage first and check a leak
So it's a date right?
Don't count on it
You used to wear that T-shirt back on tenth grade.
Look cool on you then
- Thanks
- Looks cool on you now
Shit. Have to fix that
He's pretty pissed about the truck
I thought he'd just ride it off
- I said he'd be pissed
He's pissed
Well I'm a thief, you're a thief
Right?
Right
So you got a girl up at dock?
Girl up in dock to fuck me
No time
Well I'm gonna introduce you to some of my ladies.
Show you the spell of relief
Keep an eye on him and make sure he doesn't steal anything
You know of anyone who could use some TV's?
My little girl wants one in her room
How many you got?
- A truck load
Do I look like someone who could use a truckload?
I'm dirty because I'm a mechanic
not a criminal
Besides nothing good on TV in it, right
What about a legit ID? You have driver's license
I'll give you forty dollars
- No, thank you
Why not? You can get another one
I thought you weren't a criminal?
- Helping poor folks get a job, criminal?
I'm not giving my ID to some illegal
Why?
- Coz you're legal?
I was born this side of the border
Really?
Which border?
That one?
What if I just stepped across your
border like it wasn't even there?
I'll give you a dollar for a smile
No, maybe a quarter
Can I kiss you?
- No
Do you wanna hear something funny?
I'm still a virgin
- What?
Do I have to say it again?
I'm a virgin. Ok?
- Wow
But hey I mean, I don't need a map
I just never did the.. you know..
all the way
But I'm a fast learner
Give me your best shot trailer trash
Oh I'm so jealous my Daddy
can't buy me a new truck
Nope
We just got this old taxi and
drive in circles forever
You know? I didn't miss you, fratboy!
Old high school game. See who flinches first
Greg always lost
Want to get something to eat?
How about some dogs?
All this time
You've been the donut lady
Now here you are
What do you mean? That I'm an ancient
and I'm mark from the neighborhood with
surprise, suprise, little life still left in her?
Or that I'm an aztec statue?
That miraculously comes a lot than all her fierce beauty.
Any other choices?
- Have some respect fratboy
I can take care of myself.
- Hey Gregorio
Did you hear about those uh...
six greasers who fell asleep on the railroad tracks
there are strips of bacon by the morning.
George you're ruining my appetite
The six less of Greg's compadres
over here to steal my job
What job? You don't do beaner jobs
Oh wow, what a date. Grade school fighting
and trashing beaners at the same time
How do you boys do it?
- We ain't pleased baby
Didn't Greg told you?
We're the war boys
Back in high school, we used to have
chicks like you running scared.
How frightening. This little wetback
is just shivering in her slippers
She's... an aztec beauty
and she's shivering in her slippers
She's an aztec beauty...
I'm getting dizzy
Stop it!
Stupid gringos!
All of you
Shit
I was always alone in high school
Most of the kids in my class were white
Then one of them asked me to join the war boys.
You know, it was on of those chase the
beaners high school club
Sometimes we'd spot an illegal and
call the border patrol
Sometimes we chase them in our cars
Mostly we drove around and made noise
We never hurt anybody
Not everyone just drove around.
People got hurt
Some people get killed.
Not by us
When they asked you to join the
war boys, did you think you were white too?
I was ready to be anything they
wanted me to be
And now?
What do you wanna be?
With you
- And what would you do to be with me?
Anything
I don't believe you
- Try me
Ok
Show me that you want me
- How?
Come
Come where?
Just come. Right here. Now
Your kidding?
- It's payback for your little stunt back there
No way
All right well, I'm going home
Wait, sit down, sit down
Talk to me
How?
- Just talk, just talk
Tell me something nice
Talk to me
Breathe
What else do you want me to do?
We're sorry
- Yeah
I was really obnoxious, ok?
Well look, we'll make it up to you Marta
So look, we're going boating
I don't think so
What do you mean boating?
Well here's our lady - Marta de Asis
- We'd like to talk to you alone
Who were you?
- You used to work for Welch Trucking?
I was a temp driver for a lot of different
companies but that was a long time ago
What do you want with her?
- Stay out of this
They've got a truck stolen. They're very upset
- That's too bad for them
That's not my line of business
We found out that you and your wetback friends
have anything to do with this, it's gonna hurt. Comprende?
I gotta go. I should go home
Wait a minute, stay with me
I'm sorry
Damn
This here is a pretty thorny mess
Goddamnit! You're pulling askew with those things
Last one's in deep
I think I can feel your breath on my ass
Is that your breath on my ass?
- I'm trying to get the thorns out, will you shut up?
Are you getting the thorns out of my ass
or you know...
touching... my ass
I'm touching your ass to get the thorns out
I just want to make sure the
lines don't get crossed here
They got crossed some years ago
Once
And I hardly remember it
I remember everything
The only thing that felt better
than you putting your hand on me...
is when I put my hand on you
Shut the fuck up.
We we're just kids
Sure
And you know where that line is now don't you?
- You damn right I do
So just to be certain...
Why don't you tell me where it is?
Is it here?
Most definitely. Yup
So that means... I could touch you here?
Right?
All american ok. Check
And...
Here?
David, I know who I am
What if I crossed it?
And touch you here
Say you want me
Get the hell away from me
All right
What would it mean if I said that
I wanted you?
Anything you want?
No, no, go to the garage
Our plan is fucked
- What?
Your Dad has sent goons
to find out who took the truck
They found Marta
- What's Marta got to do with any of this?
Hell if I know. They were at her place
- You didn't tell Martha, did you?
Hell no. Shit man this is serious
Drugs, drugs, it's gotta be drugs
- George is right
There's something else
- This isn't about TV's
There is now way that they would get this
hired for some TV's, there's drugs in that truck
They were TV's, my Dad wouldn't lie to me
- Wake up idiots. We need to make an anonymous call
and tell them where the truck is
Get out
- No, no fuckin' way. We didn't do all this for nothing
We wait till tomorrow
When it's light, less conspicuous.
We search the truck, take what we can carry
leave the rest then
we make the call
If they get 90 percent of
their shit back, they're gonna be happy
George is right, we can't walk
out of this empty handed
It's gonna be alright. So will Marta
Hey Greg wait up
You're going home?
You've been sitting there all night
Not moving
Are you dead or something?
Come here a minute
Sit
Look Kat, I've got to ask you something
- If you've got something to ask, ask your sister
She's sitting right next to me
Yeah I guess she is.
Fire away
Something happened to me last night
It's like I was walking down this street
That I knew really well and..
I didn't even have to look to where I was going
And all of a sudden I've
found myself somewhere I hadn't...
I've never been before
I feel like I've been there my
whole life
And I wasn't afraid anymore
What happened when you got there?
Well...
I kissed my best friend
David
On the mouth
You know, the way mom and dad
do sometimes
How come you don't like me?
Not that I don't like you Cat,
it's just you're a..
different..
from me, that's all
Is that a bad thing?
No
I guess it's not
Are you gonna kiss David again?
I don't know
Maybe
What would you think about
having a brother like that?
You alright?
- Look, if this is about last night
- It has nothing to do with you
This is all shit
- The truck those guys are looking for
We stole it.
- What?
Welch Trucking Company, it's Davids' dad
- Jesus Christ
But I want you to know we're going to return it
We're gonna bring it back
It'll be alright. We're gonna take care of it
What's in the truck?
- Black market stuff
Televisons, I don't know
- You don't know anything
We wanted to make some cash
I'm sorry you got involved
Trust me
We'll fix it
We're gonna take care of it today
High school punk
Stop worrying
I'm sorry
I'm really sorry
Turn over
Fratboy
Wait
It hurts
I'm not going in that pool
You're spending a little too much time
with that kid you can do better than that
You're David Welch
Yeah, I'm David Welch
But Welch is a dirty word to
some around here
I got my credit card thrown
at my face, why is that?
We all make enemies in this business
What have you done?
- What have I done?
Well, I paid the mortgage.
Sent you to an expensive university
Brought you a new truck
We used to tell each other everything
Yeah
There was a time when we did
No secrets
What change between us...
Why don't you go on and give
George a ride home now
Dad, there's something I need to tell you
- Please, don't
Its this that conversation where the son
says to the father, "Guess what Dad, I'm a fag"
Well, if that's what you want
It's not a problem for me
But you could at least fuck somebody
whose got some class
George is dead end.
What could he ever do for you?
George knows who I am
Do you know what that feels like?
To have somebody to look at you
and know who you are and what you want
It's like waking up over and over again
And ever sine mom died you pushed me aside
I've never pushed you aside
I've pushed you to the top
I don't want you to be like me David
- That would've been enough, to be like you
I want you to be better than me!
- See that's the difference
I've always loved you
just as you are
And you've only fuckin' loved me
for how you want me to be
Cool, it looks like George
No, I understand perfectly Roger
No, of course
Of course!
You've got papers on all the goods in the truck?
- Yeah, I've got paperwork there on the desk
For 500 bucks is a children's toys
Very cute. It's too cheap in Mexico
These are routine questions for a theft Mr. Welch,
I'm just doing my job
Well do your job Lane and watch my back
Maybe if you've done a little better watching
my back, we wouldn't have this God awful fuck up right now!
Shit, I thought you said he was coming alone?
What the hell did you bring her for?
- Cause I know what assholes you are
Fuck you
Go home, we can take care of this
Have you ever seen how white
a knee cap is when it breaks the skin?
I have! And that's just for starters
These people will hurt you
Do you even know what's in there?
- Yeah, drugs and TV's
We're taking some of both and
then we're gonna split
I had a friend who helped himself when no one was
looking and after they crippled him, they put a knife in his gut
Shut your mouth, my father is no killer
- You don't know what he is
I am not leaving empty handed
George don't!
Oh my god
- What the fuck?
You gotta leave
You gotta go now.
Come on Greg
No, I'm staying
I know, I know
We'll get the stuff and drive the container out
into the dessert and dump it
Yeah, burn everything
No, I'll talk to the boys.
I'll see they understand
Listen to me Roger
I'm the one whose gonna deal with this
Roger I got enough on you, I warn you
You're gonna burn those?
Well I don't give a fuck about them right now.
I'm gonna get my son out there
And no one else counts? What about those people?
It's all just business to you?
Stop your moral bullshit please
I'm the one who gets them the shitty jobs and
the packhouse in Iowa and sometimes things go wrong
But you risk nothing!
- I risk everything that was important to me a long time ago
So you really think you can get away with this?
Don't burn them!
What are we gonna do?
- Shut up I'll figure something out
It was your father's cargo.
Why didn't you know what was in there?
How could I know?
Over and over again I asked him, he wouldn't tell me...
We killed them!
- I told you to shut up
Jesus we killed them
They must have been shouting!
To die like that? In the dark...
No one knew
We gotta bury them
They had families.
They had names
Where's George?
David get in the car.
Shut up I know what happened
George, you two take his truck and follow me
What about the semi?
- They're gonna burn the semi. We're gonna clean up this mess
David you've got to get in the car
Boys get in the truck we don't have much time
David...
Who the fuck is that?
- Dad?
You think I ran this game on my own?
Get in the car.
David, what's going on?
No, you can't burn them
- Cmon. Get in the goddamn car
You can't just burn them!
- I planned it Dad. It was me,
I was the one who planned the whole thing
- I don't care just move it
We need to tell the cops.
If he won't, I will
You're not getting away with this
- Don't you dare threaten me you son of a bitch!
I will put you in the truck with
the rest of them. One less wetback to deal with.
Get in the car!
Give me the gun
- No secrets right Dad?
No secrets between us
You son of a bitch!
If you trusted me. If you've told me the truth
Stop! Stay where you are goddamnit!
We killed them! We fuckin' killed them
Please
David! Fuck
Oh god
Get the fuck away from me.
Don't touch me
I'm so sorry
Sorry?
You're sorry? Is that what you're going to say
to those dead fucks?
Well you know what I am?
I'm one of them
Put the gun down!
Put the gun down or I'll shoot
I'm one of them now!
Cmon!
Fuck you!
You put the gun down or I'll shoot
We need help!
We need help down here!