KING OF THE AVENUE (2010)
[gentle howling
of the wind]
[soft beat music]
[male voice
sings indistinct]
Релиз подготовлен
специально для сайта firebit.org
(male voice)
All I gotta say
is one name.
Chi-chi Rodriguez.
Puerto Rican. Bam.
Mother fucker. Puerto
Rican, professional golfer.
And all respect due,
I don't think you'd never
ever have a professional
black golfer.
I don't know
about that.
Oh, come on,
now, Scooter Pie.
Next thing you know
he's gonna be talkin' about
a black president too.
You better do
whatever the fuck you gotta do
to make sure you count
boss man's money right too.
Y'all need
to apologize.
Fuck him.
Man, kiss
my ass.
Done deal, right?
With all that
shit talking
you did,
y'all just woke
boss man's
baby boy,
Where your
daddy at, boy?
He's taking
a shower.
Let me ask
you something.
Do those pajamas hide
the pee stain when
you wet the bed?
Go on back into the bed
before your daddy
catch you
while you're
awake, go,
go ahead.
Why you go say
some dumb shit
like that?
[distorted female voice]
Mommy just needs to take
her medicine.
Hey, Daddy.
What's the
flashlight for, Taz?
I told you I ain't
raisin' no punk.
I got the same
dream again.
It's just
a dream,
little man.
Your momma
Ioved you,
you know that.
Get some sleep.
Daddy?
Do you kill people?
What made
you ask that?
I got into a fight
with Malcolm
at school.
Did you get
your ass kicked?
No, I beat
him pretty bad.
[chuckles proudly]
Yeah. So
what's the problem?
He gave me his
Iunch money and
apologized, but
some kids told me
that my daddy
was gonna kill
his daddy.
Two things:
one, it doesn't
Iook like you're
gonna need
lunch money tomorrow,
and two
I'm not ever
gonna lie to you.
Now, I wouldn't kill
somebody's daddy
for a fight
between two
little kids,
but if somebody
took something
from me,
or hurt somebody
that I loved,
I mean, if somebody
hurt you real bad
I wouldn't kill
their daddy.
I'd kill their
whole family.
I love you, Daddy.
I love you too.
There now.
You get some sleep.
Guess what?
One day, this is
gonna be yours.
Woo! I'm digging
this shit all day, son.
Fucking-h right. This the
mother fucking future
right here, son.
Hey, Dooney,
turn on the TV.
The Lakers on.
Right, Boss.
(male voice from TV)
In sports-
Walk away
from the TV, Dooney.
What?
I said walk
away from
the TV.
[cocks]
Come on.
Just walk away.
[voice from TV]
Uh-huh. Now
walk back toward.
Oh, come on.
Shut up, mother fucker.
Walk back to me.
[voice from TV]
You see
that shit?
Hm.
What?
Shut the
fuck up.
[whimpers]
Open your shirt.
Wha-?
Shut the fuck up.
[gasps]
What the
fuck, man.
Open your shirt.
You better be
quiet about it.
[grunting]
[gasps]
Now, you're
gonna tell them
everything's cool.
Everything -everything
is cool, man.
Tell them you gotta
go to the bathroom.
-I'm going
to the bathroom
for a minute.
Now take your fuckin'
pants down now.
No, what
the fuck, man?
Take your
mother fucking
pants down.
[heavy breathing]
Take your mother fucking
pants off.
Huh?
[thud]
What the
fuck, man?
Open your mouth.
They were giving
me 25 years, man.
Open your
mother fucking
mouth, huh?
[loud]
You fuck over
your niggers, right?
[muffled speech]
Suck that shit
like a good bitch.
Get your bitch ass up,
come on, keep the shit
in your mouth.
Keep it in
the mouth, easy.
Twenty five
years, man.
Come on.
Are you okay,
Uncle Dooney?
I'm as far away
from okay
[sniff]
as you can get,
little man.
How come?
I betrayed my friends.
They were gonna
give me 25 years.
[sniff].
They were gonna
take me away from
my family
for a long time.
That's a
Iot of time,
huh, Dad?
Yeah, that's
a long time, son.
I think you did
the right thing,
Uncle Dooney.
Because I wouldn't
want to be away from
my dad that long.
Turn around and
sit straight.
[coughing]
You seen that?
Yeah.
See, that's what
happens when you
betray your friends.
You know better
than to talk about
this to anyone,
you got it?
Okay. I love
you, Daddy.
Yeah, I
Iove you too.
(Taz, off)
My father's life,
a drug dealer,
A killer
and dead at 38,
He left behind
a son that loved
him very much.
And I did,
He was my world,
Despite what he did
and who he was,
I loved him as if
he was a doctor,
a fireman,
a humanitarian,
but he wasn't,
He was, for
the most part,
one of those people
that society
could probably
do without,
Nevertheless, he
was my father,
my first example
of what a man
should be like
I watched people
treat him like
a god
so to me he
was a god,
I feared him
as much as
I loved him,
and I wanted to
be just like him.
That's probably why I
became a drug dealer,
I tried to make sure
my father's fate
wasn't mine,
Like most people
in my Jine
of work,
I thought I was
smarter than
the game,
I didn't play it
like everyone else,
Although I could afford
to live anywhere,
I chose to live
somewhere upscale
but not too upscale
where my finances
would be an issue,
Nobody wanted to see
someone too flashy
in a
conservative neighborhood,
So to the people
who lived around
me and my family,
I was Joe Ordinary,
I lived what I
considered the
sucker's life,
nine to five
till you die.
But most importantly,
I had a routine.
Good morning, Taz.
Good morning, Greta.
Kiss my wife, Amanda,
and our son
who I named after
my father, Norman,
Remember we play
the Tigers today.
At six o'clock.
Have I
ever forgotten?
Taz.. .
Done, I'm there,
Mwah. Bye, baby.
Bye.
I told everyone,
including Amanda,
I was the East Coast
rep for a West Coast
consulting firm.
That way no one could ask to
come by my job or see where
I worked.
You know, Greta,
you water that same
spot every morning.
Mm-hmm.
Now this,
this was
my dope house,
I just call it that because
I would never have drugs
of any kind here,
I'm the boss.
I leave that to
the soldiers.
I just all it that
because it's where
I do all my dirt.
After Mom died,
nobody wanted to let
a known black drug dealer
adopt a white orphan
but hey, cash is king,
And after years
of fighting
with courts,
I was his,
There you are again,
with that photo album.
When I got older,
I realized that family
is someone that
you end up with,
You don't have
a choice in
the matter,
I swear you look
at that thing
a hundred
times a week,
But what he did to
make me his son
was a choice
and it made me
love him even more.
Baby.
You gotta be
fucking kidding me.
[scoffs]
[cell phone vibrates]
Hello?
Alright, I'll see
I'll see you in
a little bit.
Am I not on
the fucking phone?
[soft rap
music, indistinct]
[birds chirping]
I'm taking
your car.
No you're not.
I'm taking it.
You take
the truck.
I don't feel
like driving that
big old thing.
You're the one
that wanted
the SUV
with 20
TVs in it,
not me.
That shit is ghetto.
Oh, I know
you didn't
call me ghetto.
I'm not saying
you're ghetto.
I'm saying driving
around in a SUV with
20 TVs is ghetto.
But, baby,
isn't that
what you say,
the man makes the car,
not the other way
around? Right?
You're always
saying that.
Uh-huh. Uh-huh.
Yeah, you're learning.
The answer
is still no.
Why?
As calm as
I was playing,
what was about to
happen would be huge,
[alarm chirps]
So huge it was
sure to make me
king of the avenue,
I was getting
ready to make a
deal with the Mexicans,
I start by getting my product
at wholesale, that's
about half,
only thing was,
you better promise
to buy a minimum
every month,
Come hell or high water,
you better buy
that minimum,
But I wasn't worried,
I was moving
so much shit,
I was already
doubling minimum.
I had just hooked
up with these bikers,
See, they were
white supremacists
and would buy from me
before my black and
Latin peers,
I used to think
how my father
would feel
about me working
with racists,
[scoff]
But then, I figured
he woulda told me
to take their
money first,
Cal, My most trusted
friend and general
of my operation,
The son of Scooter Pie.
You'll be
king of the avenue
for sure after this.
King? No. This
is just about
the money.
Fuck that.
Your daddy was
fucking king, man,
it's your
fucking birthright.
Yeah, look what
happened to him.
I'm not going out
like that, man.
I'm just getting
my cake and
I'm out.
Then you could
be king.
[chuckles]
Fuck it.
I'll be king
after you? Shit.
White folks don't
wanna see me living
next to them
acting like I'm
a fucking consultant.
No, we don't.
You know
what I'm saying?
I was playing it
cool to Cal,
Being the king
was my birthright
and I wanted it
more than anything,
And I mean anything!
I would do it or
gladly die trying.
Pop! What
the fuck!
You fucking
back-doored
my deal?
You shouldn't disturb
what we got going
on here.
We already
made the deal.
My deal? Hector,
I thought we had
an understanding.
You guys ain't
my family.
I don't give a
fuck about you.
What I care is about
me getting my money.
I don't care
who I make
the deal with,
Dooney Jr,
son of the man
my father killed
when turning informant.
Current king
of the ave,
What the fuck
were you thinking,
white boy?
Not supposed to buy
from anybody but me.
That's the rules.
You know 'em,
mother fucker.
The only reason
you ain't stinkin'
in a fuckin'
dumpster right now
is 'cause Scooter
Pie talked me
out of it.
The only reason
I listen to him
is because he's
my general.
And his son
is your general.
Otherwise -I woulda
come to your house
and kill
you myself.
I'll tell
you something,
white boy.
King of
the ave
was made for
men like me.
And as much as it
kills me to say it,
for men like
your father.
Get this
through your head.
You're never, ever
gonna be king.
(Hector)
I suggest we go
into my restaurant
and have a
couple margaritas,
King, baby.
[door slams]
Who the fuck
did you tell?
I didn't
tell nobody.
Fuck!
What do you
want to do?
Nothing. Let's
go home.
But we need
to talk this
shit out.
We seen Dooney Jr.
kill for much less
than this.
Fuck that shit
he was saying.
Only reason
he didn't
try something
is he didn't want
to get Hector in
the crossfire.
Just go home.
Come on, man.
Go!
Mother fucker, Hector!
Fuck!
Taz, you
missed the game.
I know,
I'm sorry.
Work just got crazy.
I got to go to the
west coast.
When?
Now, I
gotta go now.
[scoff]
The kids are all
meeting for pizza.
Alright.
Okay.
You know, he didn't
even let them clear
the scoreboard
until his daddy
saw how good
he did.
Fifty five to five. That's a
good old-fashioned
butt-whipping.
Sorry, little man.
Daddy'll see you
next time, okay?
[gym door slams]
Stop. Here.
Do me a favor
and just go out
to dinner with
your friends
or something, alright?
Are you okay?
Yeah, I'm fine.
I just need to take
some shit out.
But what
about you?
Jesus Christ,
you not fucking
listening to me?
I said go!
Why be a fucking
ass to me all
the time?
Sorry.
[sigh]
[beeps]
Cal. Yeah,
what's up?
Yeah, meet me
at the spot tomorrow.
Tell everyone to
stand alert. Alright.
[beep]
Fuck.
[beeping]
[distorted]
Mommy just needs
to take her medicine.
Fuck!
Damn.
Tia.
Tia!
[distorted]
Cumegu. Amulachio.
[crackling flames]
Shh.
Out of the frying pan.
Who are you?
Who do I
appear to be?
Yeah.
I'm him.
What do you
want from me?
A favor.
And in return
for that favor,
I will deliver
you right where
you want to be.
King of the avenue.
For my soul?
We're overcrowded
with souls.
We get
thousands a day.
Not to mention
the billions we
already have.
Your one meager soul
makes no difference
either way.
But why?
Why you?
You're one of
my best workers.
You're just providing
a service. They have
to get it from somewhere.
Might as well
be you, right?
I don't want this
anymore. I'm done.
You know, Taz,
sometimes we do
too much to turn around.
How do you know
when you've crossed
that line?
How do we know
when it's too
Iate for us?
Call me conservative,
but when I appear in
your living room,
as a rule of thumb
you can probably assume
you've crossed
that line.
Dooney Junior's king.
He's the one
doing your work.
You need him.
The world sees Dooney Jr.
as a common street thug.
Only com for table
in the hood.
He can't go
to the places
I need him to go.
You can.
You're an
all-American
white male.
Blue-eyed to boot.
That's all I need
to put you where
you need to be.
So here's
the deal plan.
You become king
and do my bidding
and I will save
your family from
Dooney Junior.
You've got no choice.
Let's face it.
He hates you.
For what
your father
did to his.
And he's been
waiting for
a reason .
Dooney Jr. is plotting
to kill your family
as we speak.
And once he's had his way
with your precious Amanda,
her summer
dress pulled up,
bent over
your kitchen sink,
back dooring her,
he's gonna go to
work on your
little boy.
Little Norman
as he makes you watch.
Whatever you decide,
deal with me.
I will meet you
tomorrow at midnight
at your father's
final resting place.
If you're not there,
I'll take that
as a no and
Ieave you alone.
(Tia)
Baby.
What are you
doing on the floor?
Something told
me to come home.
Let's get you in bed.
My father broke
by the rules, right?
Well, what
happened? Huh?
Taz's father
killed him, right?
Two days
before my fuckin'
tenth birthday,
how the fuck you think
I felt on my birthday?
You know, I'm the wrong
motherfucker to ask
for forgiveness.
You cannot live
by your father's life.
You're not getting
what I'm saying, man.
It's a done
fuckin' deal.
What are you
talkin' about?
I already sent
one of my boys
to nail him.
You gotta have
permission from
the commission
before you
kill a boss.
They're gonna find out
where his girlfriend lives,
where his son lives,
they're gonna do 'em too.
Why the boy's family?
'Cause I'm not gonna
make the same mistake
his father did.
See -Taz's son
will grow up
one day, man,
and the only way
to keep the weed
from growin'
is to take it
from the roots.
And don't
worry, man.
I told him
to make sure
not to touch Cal.
Let me ask you
something, Scooter.
What side
are you on?
I'm on
your side,
boss man.
[beep]
I don't
wanna go.
It's too dangerous.
But I'd rather be
in danger with you
than stay
without you.
Where the fuck
are my keys?
[doorbell rings]
[muffled shot]
[piercing scream]
It's all right.
Shit.
You all right?
Fuck.
You okay?
Yeah.
[indistinct].
I'll get the car
and put it
in the garage.
Are you okay?
Yeah, I'm fine!
Go clean up.
[birds chirping]
You know, Pops called.
Said Daddy Junior
put out the hit.
We need to
do something, man.
I thought
I heard
a scream .
Where do
you live?
I live next door!
Right next door?
[gasps]
You didn't
hear shit.
[swallows hard]
Okay, man. Okay.
I didn't
see anything.
And I didn't
hear anything.
Okay. All right.
It appears as
if we have
a deal.
So what now?
You become
the king.
What, so, you
just wave your
hands around
and do some magic
or something
or what?
Do I look like a
Ieprechaun to you?
Then what?
Open it.
What?
Fuck that!
Aren't you
the devil?
Can't you just raise
him out of there
or something?
Contrary to popular belief,
I don't just wave
a magic wand.
Different events
have to take place
for you to
become this king.
For those
events to happen,
I must bring
forth a demon.
This demon
needs a host.
And to show that
this is your will,
kind of like
the signing of the
proverbial contract,
the host must be
only the people
you love the most.
The only
reason to do this
is to save my family.
I'm an opportunist,
I really don't care
why you're doing it.
As long as you're
doing my will.
Thanks.
Jesus!
You've signed your contract.
I'll take it from here.
[cell phone vibrates]
Hello?
(Amanda)
Taz.
Amanda.
Honey, you need
to come home.
Why? What's wrong?
Baby, I don't know
how to tell you this.
Why? What happened?
The people from
the cemetery called.
Somebody dug up
your father's
grave and
and stole
his remains.
Did you hear
what I just said?
[flat tone]
Yeah. Oh my God.
That's horrible.
What did they say?
Don't worry about
that right now.
Can you please
just come home?
I'm really scared.
Okay. Uh
I gotta call
you back.
Give me
your hand.
Why?
Now.
[scratching]
[moan]
[loud thud]
[squeaky footsteps]
You need anything?
Why?
Scooter Pie
gave me your stuff.
I never got
rid of it.
You want
something to eat?
I don't eat.
So, what do
we do now, Pops?
My name
is De'Sha.
Oh.
Okay.
[chuckles]
Let's get
one thing clear.
I don't give
a fuck about you.
I'm a demon
straight from hell.
Sent to wreak havoc
and do whatever
is necessary
to make you
king of the avenue.
So don't think,
just because I'm
in this body
that it somehow
ties us emotionally.
I'm here to
do his will.
And if
I'm commanded
I'll take you out
and leave you on
the field for dead.
That's just
what I do.
And that's
the story of
you and me.
Now go
get dressed.
Whoa, how'd
you know
about that?
I know
everything you know.
Pop the trunk.
[cell vibrating]
Yeah!
Council meeting?
I didn't know
anything about
a council meeting.
Huh. That's
'cause it's
about you.
(Dooney)
So now J'm the
motherfucking bad guy?
Dooney, you know you
can't put a hit
on a boss
without all
us votin' on it.
Those are
the rules.
That mother fucker
broke the rules first.
I agree
with Dooney.
You would.
What the fuck's
that supposed
to mean?
Nigger. It means Dooney
gives you your shit
for a discount.
So you're gonna
agree with anything
he says.
You his bitch.
Stanley, shut
the fuck up.
I'll sell my shit
to whoever the
fuck I want
for whatever the
price I want to.
Anybody got
a problem with that?
I don't blame Taz
for doing what
he did.
Shit. You ain't
showing nobody
no love.
A nigger gonna fuck around
and starve to death
dealing with you.
Motherfuckers, I am
the mother fucking
king! Me!
And the rules are:
nobody can buy
shit from nobody
but me
unless I
say otherwise.
I chose these
mother fucking bandits
from wild wild west.
Dooney, calm dow-!
Calm down!
We don't need
to start a war.
I think what we
need to do
is let Taz
answer some of
these accusations.
Mother fucker, of course
you gonna say that!
You mother fucking
white boys
stick together.
White boy?
I'm Italian.
[scoffs]
Same shit to me.
A white boy that
eats good.
I didn't come here
to get disrespected.
Mother fucker, I'm the one
that disrespected in
this bitch!
Dooney, come on.
Dooney, just chill.
I mean nobody's
disrespecting you, alright?
Right, Ed?
Stanley?
I'm just sayin'
what's on my mind.
Ain't that why we
had these meetings?
Let's just fucking
vote, alright?
Who's not in favor
of the hit on Taz?
Raise your hand.
And who's
in favor
of the hit?
See? Vote
came to an end.
That's it.
His ass is mine.
[gunfire]
Prepare for
a baptism.
[gunshot]
Now who said
your vote
didn't count?
Three things. One,
this never happened.
Two, Taz is now
the new king of
the avenue.
And three
y'all gonna get
your shit for half
price from now on.
See? That's what
the fuck I'm
talkin' about.
Yeah.
It's not
like we don't
appreciate
all this.
But you just
killed five!
Watch your
tone, mother fucker!
You just killed
five bosses
and the king.
It's gonna be all-out war
out there on the streets.
I'll handle
that shit.
Y'all just go about
business as usual.
And you remember, when
the mother fucker's
in the room,
you just talk to
the mother fucker,
you don't
yell at him.
You got that?
Yes.
Say I'm a
bitch-ass nigger.
I'm a
(Taz, off)
At the time, I wasn't aware
of what had just happened,
especially because the
demon showed the
same emotion
as if he had
just swatted
a fly.
But that was
only the tip
of the iceberg,
It would've been
an all-out war
if the crews of
the dead bosses
woke up the next
morning and found
out what happened
to their Ieaders.
Except for
the crews of
these bosses,
waking up
was not
an option,
That night, I drove
the demon around
as he massacred 28 of
the most influential
people in the gang,
Sometimes it's not
how many you kill,
it's who you kill.
It was actually
pretty easy
for him.
No one even knew
there was a war,
Everyone just had
their guards
down, so
he just kind
of picked them off
like fish in a barrel.
[sigh]
[knocks at door]
Ask them
what they want.
What do
you want?
A lot of people
died last night.
die every night.
Yeah, but you're
not one of them.
Fancy police work.
You think
this is
a joke?
I think the joke
is you guys are
here at my door
saying that you're here
'cause I'm not dead.
A lot of your
constituents were
murdered last night.
Constituents?
Yeah. You're a
drug dealer, right?
Drug dealing is illegal
in the state of Florida.
Where were you
Iast night?
Where were you?
What?
What you're basically saying
is I'm a suspect because
I'm alive.
That would make you
a suspect too.
Where were
you last night?
I know
where he was.
I came over
Iast night.
Twice. Okay?
I looked at this boy
straight in the eyes
and I told him,
''Turn the music down.''
He wouldn't turn
the music down. He
wouldn't listen to me.
Hey, wh -where you
guys going?
Hey! Hey!
I told them what
you wanted me
to say.
Please don't
hurt me. Please.
Please.
We have to meet
with the Mexicans.
(Hector)
Twenty eight
bodies in one night,
You had a busy night.
And it shows.
Man. That gotta
be some kind
of record.
I'm not impressed.
I don't know
what you're
talking about.
So I take it you're here
for the same deal I
gave Dooney Jr.
Yeah. The deal
that was supposed
to be mine.
I don't trust him.
Hector, what's up
with your boy?
Dooney was gonna
get him tickets
for a game.
Well, tell him
I'll give him
season tickets
if he just
shuts the
fuck up, alright?
Taz -don't
Hector. I'm here
to do business.
The deal's yours.
Good.
We'll be
in touch.
Look, you taco
eating mother fuckers
Wouldn't that be
chicken eating mother fucker?
[chuckles]
Well, I guess we all
gonna be some chicken
taco eatin' mother fuckers.
The old
deal is off.
The new deal
is 10% less.
Dooney Jr. and all
the crew's gone,
we gonna be moving
40% more weight,
making a lot
more money.
So pony up,
mother fuckers.
(girl)
Hi, guys.
Your order, please.
I guess
we'll be having
chicken tacos.
Okay.
[soul music]
[insistent knocking
at door]
[knocking continues]
[more knocking]
What the fuck?
Who is it?
It's me, boy.
Come on, Pop,
use your key.
Well I'll
be calling
your ass.
It's about Taz.
Baby. Go take
a shower.
Police have few leads,
but the question in
everyone's mind is
vigilante justice
or the biggest turf
war in decades?
Where's Taz?
I talked to two
of the other bosses.
And they say that Taz
is the new king of
the avenue.
In one night?
Hold up, Pop.
They're saying
Taz did all this?
I, like this they ain't
speakin' all of it.
but he's now
the fucking
top dog.
Who the
top crew?
Holy shit! He
fucking did it!
We top crew?
I gotta get dressed.
I gotta find Taz.
Good. 'Cause
I'm going with
your ass.
Let me go
throw some
clothes on.
[eIectric guitar music]
My boy.
What's up?
You the man,
How you
pull that off?
I'll fill
you in later,
all right?
Hey, Scooter.
Taz.
So, uh, I
gotta leave for
a little while.
I need you to run ship
while I'm gone, okay?
Done deal.
Son, I gotta talk
to Taz for a minute.
About what?
Well, get your
ass in the car.
Hey, Cal,
give us a
minute, alright?
Alright.
We top crew.
What's up?
Did you
do this?
I did what I had
to do to protect
my family?
I know.
Now look.
I need a job.
Done.
Taz.
My son, Cal,
he's all I got.
I do whatever
I gotta do
to make sure
that he's safe.
I didn't want
this life for
him, man.
But you know,
kids see everything.
Even though we think
they're not paying attention,
they are.
Shame on us
for that.
We tried to
make you tough.
I mean, we used to say
''We ain't raisin'
no punks''
and with that, we gave
our kids a front
row seat
to our
world of death
and destruction.
And all
I can ask
of you is
if you need
some bad shit
to be handled
let me
do it, man.
This boy
Ioves you, man.
And he
Ioves his life,
and he ain't about
to walk away, man.
I'm gonna make
damn sho that
he's gonna be safe.
Okay.
Promise me.
I promise.
Now you go home,
take your ass to bed,
get some rest 'cause
you look like shit
on a stick.
Boss man.
(Taz, off)
The demon told me
to go home for 30 days
to let everything
cool down,
[alarm chirps]
I told Cal the things
I wanted him to do
and that I was
gonna be out of
sight for a month,
He didn't
understand why but
but Cal was
my best friend,
my absolute soldier,
He didn't question too
much of what I said,
He just did it.
Wow.
Baby. I'm sorry
I passed out
Iast night
without saying anything.
Well, no.
You came in
on Thursday night,
passed out and
didn't say anything.
It's now
Saturday morning.
[birds chirping]
No shit.
Yeah, no shit.
I just figured you were
still upset about
your father.
What do you mean?
About your
father's remains.
How'd you
know about that?
Taz, I'm the one
that told you.
Oh.
Oh, yeah.
[sigh]
Is everything okay?
Everything's fine.
Could we just
not talk
about it right
now, please?
Yeah.
Sure.
Gonna take
a shower.
Throw the
ball, Dad.
Ah, those 30 days
were the best 30
days of my life,
Being the king was what
I thought I always
wanted to be,
[chuckles]
And now that
I had it,
I'd have gladly
given it all away
just to relive
those 30 days,
How long are you
gonna be gone, Dad?
Just a couple of days
and I'll be back
to my normal schedule.
[sniffles]
But I don't
want you to go.
Stop crying, Norman.
Hey, I said stop
crying! I ain't
raisin' no punk.
[sniffles]
Daddy?
[sniffling]
I won't be
a punk anymore.
[sniffling]
[romantic music]
Is Norman sleeping?
Yeah.
What's the matter?
He was crying
'cause he didn't
want me to leave.
I told him I wasn't
raisin' no punk.
Taz!
That's what my dad
used to say to me.
He knows you
didn't mean it.
Hey
Can I enjoy
a glass of wine
with my husband
before he leaves?
[squeak of cork]
Norman's gonna
be fine.
He's strong.
Just like
his daddy.
Cheers.
[male voice sings
romantic tune]
We made
more money
in one month
than we have
in the past
six months.
The shit with the Mexicans
is gonna set us forever.
Everyone is scared of us.
We're a fuckin' powerhouse.
Pops even said
he ain't seen a
king more powerful.
You the shit, Taz,
and everyone
knows it.
What the fuck's
wrong with you?
You ain't said two
words since you
got in the car.
You wanna get
married, man?
Have some kids?
Where the fuck
did that come from?
Man, don't waste
that shit on me.
I mean, that's cool
for you 'cause you
the boss man.
But me?
I'm a rider.
You and Pops,
the only family
I want.
That's it.
After that,
I don't give
a fuck.
Change this
radio station.
Let's put on some
white boy music.
Why you always gotta
go playing that white
boy shit, man?
Hip hop's
where it's
at, dawg.
Hip-hop's dead.
Stanley wants to
meet us here?
Yeah, he asked
for a meeting
with the king.
It's like
being the mayor.
You gotta shake
some hands, kiss
some babies.
(crowd)
Surprise!
[cheering
and clapping]
What's this?
Everyone's here
to show you respect.
Welcome you
as the new boss man.
I love
you, mother fucker.
We made it.
Taz. I've been in
the game a long time.
I'm gonna tell you
it ain't never
been this good.
Appreciate it.
Thank you. We
appreciate it too.
Of course.
Congrats.
Now let's go party
with these ladies.
# [indistinct] #
Dude, for real.
You know
what I mean?
[ice clinking]
Watch out.
What the fuck
you say to me?
You heard what I said.
Get the fuck out
of my way.
Fuck you, nigger.
What you wanna do?
Wanna die?
Hey! Hey!
Hey! Relax.
Hey, man.
Who are you?
Who are you with?
You don't know
who I am, man?
They call me
Homicidal, boss man.
And if he with you,
then I apologize.
Well, he
is. Relax.
Then I apologize, man,
for that reason.
For that reason only,
believe that.
Keep smiling.
Bitch.
We gonna
talk later.
We got
your bitch-ass.
What's wrong with you?
Let that shit go.
Fuck that nigger.
You see gangsters?
Gangsters?
They go to jail.
Time of the street thug?
That shit's over. Done.
You will never ever
see anyone from
my crew
wearing saggy pants
and the oversized shirt.
The only thing
missing are
floppy shoes
and the red noses,
fucking clowns,
See, this is a
business. Alright?
Like the military uses
camouflage to blend into
their surroundings?
Our camouflage are suits,
conducting ourselves
like gentlemen.
Keeping the violence to
an absolute minimum, Cal.
I'm watching
you, homey.
Reach out.
Apply these principles
to your operation,
I guarantee you the
era of prosperity
will be here
for years
to come.
Hear ye,
hear ye, mother fuckers.
Cheers.
Drink up!
# [indistinct] #
Baby, pour my man
some more drink.
Okay, baby.
Thank you, sweetheart.
Everything that we've
been dreaming about
I was
telling you
about that shit
Hey, Cal! Hey!
I let this
shit go once.
What's up, nigger?
What are you?
[thud]
[girl screams]
What the
fuck I tell
you, mother fucker?
Excuse me.
Somebody come get
this mother fucker
outta my party.
What the fuck
are you doin'?
What's wrong with you?
Stupid ass mother fucker.
# I'm not braggin'
I'm a fuckin' dragon #
# They don't
Wanna fuck
With me #
# I got my 9 mm
Bitch with me #
# Now they 'bout
To feel a nigga's fury ##
Shit. Mother fuckers.
[approaching footsteps]
[demon chuckles]
What did
you do?
Why the fuck would you
kill this nigger at
my party
and bring this
heat to me?
I told you three
mother fuckin' times,
nigger. I didn't do it.
You know what, Cal?
You need to deal
with this shit.
Why the fuck
do I need to
deal with it?
'Cause you broke
the bottle over
his head.
He was
a bitch!
Well, take this
bitch to the swamps.
Fuck! Go ahead,
handle it, Cal.
We appreciate
your hospitality
we'll get
this cleaned up.
Thanks a lot,
boss man.
I'll do it
to keep the peace.
But this shit
is fucked up.
I'll do it.
Just help me
get him in the
back seat.
(Taz, off)
After that
little glitch,
things went exactly
according to plan,
making money
hand over fist.
We had everything
we wanted: money,
houses, cars,
and the women, oh,
the women would
do anything
just to be
in our world.
We were young, rich,
and unstoppable,
Since Cal was running
the business so well
I started spending less
and less time in
the hood
and more time
with my family.
Got to the point where
I hardly even seen the
demon anymore,
Hey, look, my mom
collects these.
Is that
cool, Mommy?
Yeah, look.
Look, Daddy.
Grrr.
Norman, put
that back.
I'm gonna
get yah. I'm
gonna get Daddy.
[harshly]
Stop it! Okay?
I ust take that off.
You might rip
it -or something.
[sigh]
Sorry.
[motorcycle revving]
Can we go see
the motorcycles?
Yeah, go ahead.
I'm gonna
stay here.
Taz? Be nice.
Whoa. Cool!
No, you can never
have one of
these, son.
Holy shit,
it's the king.
(Norman)
Is this
your motorcycle?
That's right,
little fella.
A pleasure having
the king's son on
my bike.
Dad, what are
you a king of?
The streets haven't been
the same since you taken
over, my brother.
It's definitely
a pleasure.
Come on,
Iet's go.
Is that
your lady, too?
You don't know me,
you made a mistake.
Okay?
Yeah, you
got that.
You got that.
You the king.
Come on,
Iet's go, son.
What was
that about?
He thought
he knew me.
Then why
did he?
[brusquely]
That's all !
[cell phone vibrates]
What's up, Cal?
Shit.
(Cal)
We made the streets
flourish like this.
We paid you every
fucking month!
And now you
want more money?
You might as well
put a gun to our head.
I'd rather not.
Well, if it's
on, it's on.
[chuckles]
Cal
let me talk
to Hector.
[chuckling]
Your boy needs to
Iearn some respect.
Maybe. But like me,
he said we had
a deal.
Taz, Taz, Taz.
You take care of
your people well.
That makes them
respect you,
Iove you.
That is something
that is going to keep
you on top for a long time.
If I allow it.
I made you.
I can
make Frank,
Eddie or Stanley.
You might be
the king of
the avenue,
but I am king of
the fucking world.
[chuckles]
What happened?
Done.
Are you
good with this?
No, but fuck it.
That's the way
it is.
25% more, whatever.
We're still getting
four times as much as
we were before, right?
Hey! Trust me. This
is how you keep
the peace.
Fuck that!
Done, Cal!
It's fuckin' done.
Just let me worry
about that, alright?
Whatever you
say, Taz.
Come on, that's
not even a problem.
Listen, you've
been keeping all
of our bellies full.
It'll be my pleasure.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, I know
the little restaurant.
The one on
Common Street?
Through the kitchen.
Okay. Then I'll see
you there.
Perfect. Alright.
Come back to bed
for a little while.
I can't,
I gotta go.
I can't seem
to get enough
of you.
It's not my fault.
Stop being
so adorable.
[snorts]
You know what?
You always find a way
to distract me from
my work.
That's good every
now and then.
Some might
think otherwise.
[kiss]
Let's go have
a quickie.
Whoa, whoa, Stan,
what the fuck
are you doin'?
You ain't gotta put
deli cuts in my face
or poison me.
Fuck all
that craziness.
You put one
right between
my eyes.
Calm down, man.
What the fuck's
the matter with you, man?
Come to my house
waving a fuckin'
gun around
talkin' about
killin', man?
What happened?
They sliced his
whole face up, man.
[shouts and screams]
Peeled his
skin right off.
[screams continue]
And Frankie, poisoned.
He tried to tear his
own tongue out of
his fucking mouth.
It's some straight
evil shit, Taz.
Think our
sins finally
caught up with us.
Man, pull yourself
together, alright?
I don't want Tia
to hear this shit.
You upset?
You were gonna snitch,
weren't ya?
Breathe.
Stick your
tongue out.
tongue out!
Stick your
tongue out! !
Why did
you do that?
Why do you gotta
kill everybody?
He was good, man.
No one was
a threat.
You killed Eddie
and Frankie,
didn't you?
Hector said you
weren't the only
game in town.
I bet you are now.
Get rid of
the body.
Cal. Shit's
out of control, man.
You're mother fucking
right it is!
Hector killed
Eddie and Frank,
nobody knows where
Stanley is and that
Ieaves you.
And nothing's
gonna happen
to you.
No, no, no,
it wasn't them, man.
They're killing
our people, man.
The peace is over.
What?
Taz, you getting
too fucking soft.
I've been
runnin' this shit.
Cal, listen to
me very carefully.
Not this time,
boss man.
I'm not asking,
you mother fucker.
I'm telling you!
What?
Hello?
Fuck!
What are
you doing?
When I was a kid,
I thought you were the
best thing that coulda
happened to me.
I told you
I'm not
your father.
Fuck you!
You're gonna
listen to me!
I loved you so much.
I was your little boy.
Everything I learned
about right and wrong,
you taught me.
Mm-hm.
Getting into this life,
I knew
exactly what
I was doing.
Maybe if I'd had
a better start,
this coulda had
a better conclusion.
[chuckles]
Now I gotta
go stop Cal.
You still don't
understand, do you?
You made a deal
with the devil.
The most evil
entity known
to God or man.
You can't just
turn that shit off.
The floodgates
of hell are open
So whet her I'm
with you or not
I still have
to do his will.
Nothing -nothing will
jeopardize you becoming
king of the avenue.
Cal's about to fuck up.
And everyone
that fucks up,
you kill.
U h-huh.
Not Cal.
That's my heart.
Uh-huh.
Get the fuck
outta my way.
No.
I got no problem
putting an end to
this nightmare right now.
This should definitely
jeopardize me being
king of the ave? Huh?
I don't see Taz.
That's not a good sign.
I will see
what he wants.
Where's Hector?
Is he in the truck?
Don't worry about that.
[indistinct].
Is he in
the fucking truck?
No, he's not.
Yeah?
Yeah.
I think he is.
[gunshot]
Go! Go!
[gunfire]
Parking lot on 3rd.
Kill everything you see.
[engine speeds up,
tires screech]
I fuckin' told ya!
Let's get
the fuck
outta here.
We gotta burn
him up first.
What? Pops!
We gotta go!
You fucked around
and let him grab
your arm.
You got too
close to him.
Now you got
hair, particles,
and shit all over you.
Those forensic dicks
are gonna find
that shit.
What do I do?
Here, take
the fucking gun
and go to the car.
Shit.
Pop's crazy.
He's back there
burning up the body.
Body? What'd
do you do?
I smoked the loud mouth.
Oh, no.
He told me Hector
wasn't in the truck,
but I knew he was.
You fucked up, man!
Man, they killed!
Cal! It
wasn't them.
You killed
all those bosses
and everything
just fell into place.
That was
brilliant, Taz.
I just wanted to do
like you did.
I gotta go.
# Swing low #
# Sweet chariot #
# Comin' for to
Carry me home #
# Swing low #
# Sweet chariot #
# Comin' for
To carry me home ##
Cal!
No!
No! !
Cal! !
[demon chuckles]
Where you
going, mother fucker?
Fuck! You're
not real.
I'm real enough
to make you kill.
Mm-hm.
I made you
kill Eddie.
Frankie.
That Stanley,
who by the way,
is still in the trunk
[ahhh ahhhh]
And then there's
your boy, Cal.
Oh, yeah.
Double bless 'em.
He really
Ioved you,
And how about
poor little Tia?
Oh, you don't
remember that, huh?
All that little girl
wanted to do
was love you.
I make you see
what I want you
to see.
And I make you
do what I want
you to do.
[gunfire]
And you have the audacity
to say I'm not real? Ha!
I'm as real
as it gets.
Your whole damn life
is one big tragedy!
Son, you dysfunctional.
You had to create
a mother fucker like
me to protect you.
Just like your
daddy said.
I told you I ain't
raisin' no punk.
The punk is exactly
what you became.
Until I came along.
Until De'Sha
came along.
Then nobody
fucked with Taz.
Yeah, you kept me
hidden all these years
but then I had
to come out!
Get out of
my fucking head!
I'm your daddy.
I'm just fuckin'
with ya.
And I'm always
gonna be fuckin'
with ya.
Because I like
to fuck with people.
So I'm always
gonna fuck
with ya.
[blows]
[crash]
[horn honks]
(lady)
Are you okay?
Amanda!
Amanda! !
Amanda, baby, baby!
Oh my God.
I killed everybody.
It was me.
I fucked up.
What are you
talking about?
You gotta get out
of here, baby.
He's gonna
kill you too.
Who? What are
you talking about?
My Dad.
He came back as
a demon or me.
I don't fuckin' know!
Taz. Your
daddy's dead.
You're just
upset because
No, that was me!
You're really
scaring me.
You're covered
in blood.
Not my blood.
It's Cal's.
He made me
kill Cal.
Daddy?
Don't let him
see me like this!
Go up to
your room!
Mommy and Daddy
are just talking.
Whatever is going on,
I can help you.
Baby, listen to me.
You gotta get Norman
and get the fuck
out of here.
Why, Taz??
I love you! !
I'm not going anywhere
until you tell me why?
Baby.
[sigh]
I'm a drug dealer.
One of the biggest drug
dealers on the Florida coast.
And -I kill people.
A lot of people.
And 30 miles from here,
I got another house with
a girlfriend named Tia.
I killed her too.
And I was the one
who dug up my
dad's remains.
And that's the dead body
of one of my drug lords
in the trunk of my car.
Baby, the demon in my head,
he makes me do things
so listen to me.
Get Norman
and get the fuck
outta here! Now, okay?
Go! Go!!
Go.
Uh-uh-uh.
Now what the fuck
did you do that for?
You told
her everything.
Now you have
to kill her
and your son.
No.
Mm-hm. You
have to.
She knows everything.
Fuck you!
No! Fuck you!
Wasn't my fault
that you told
her everything.
Now I'm a-give
you a option.
You can go in there,
put one in the back
of their heads, painless,
or you know
how I work.
No.
# Swing low #
# Sweet chariot #
You're not
gonna hurt them.
# Comin' fo' to
Carry me home #
Amanda, go!
Fuck! !
Daddy?
No! !
# Comin' fo'
to carry
me home #
Now my son
will grow up
without a father,
without the
proper guidance,
He'll always wonder
''What if my dad
was here?''
I'm sure one day
Amanda will find
someone eJse.
She's a good woman,
so she'll probably
find a good man,
And they'll raise
my son without me,
But I know
nobody will ever
Iove them like I did,
And under different
circumstances, we
could've been so happy,
But I guess we'll never
know the answer to that,
'Cause I wasn't strong
enough to break
the cycle,
Are you?
[gunfire]