Excuse me really Dorothy Walt.
She was a wonderful girl.
Thanks for coming, Al.
"Spectacles, Testicles, Wallet, and Watch"
Look how the old man scandal
Ashley looks to.
He can not even mean
at the funeral, Mom?
What did you expect?
Dad is still living in the'50s.
He expects that his granddaughter
a little more fashionable clothes.
Yes, if your children wear a jersey Timbervolves
I am sure that the AR values.
My point is that nobody can do anything
that the old man would not disappoint.
It is inevitable.
Therefore we do not celebrate together
Thanksgiving.
Remember that deal with the motorboat,
the broken geboortebad,
there is always something with him.
What we need with him?
Do not you think that he is in trouble,
there all alone in the old neighborhood?
Why does he not you withdraw?
Death is often a bittersweet event
For us Catholics.
Bitter in the pain.
Sweet in salvation.
Bitter in the pain
which caused the death ...
for their families.
Sweet for those of us
the salvation know that wait.
And some wonder;
"What is death?"
Is this the end?
Or is that the beginning?
And what is life?
What is that thing
that we 'live' call?
All these questions can frustrate
in times like this.
And therefore you need to reverse the Lord.
- Jesus.
Because the Lord is the sweetness.
Is that dad?
- No, that's Grandpa Walt.
Third platoon, Company E,
two in March 1952.
Korea?
- Where is Korea?
There are many people
taken to the funeral, huh?
I think they have heard
that there would be much ham.
I go to the basement
a few chairs to get.
I can do that, Dad.
- No, we need them now,
not next week.
Cool, I've found a medal.
Look at this post.
How long should we stay here?
This slum is hell
for my phone and I bored me.
Ashley, honey, you want Grandpa Walt
help with the chairs?
Me?
- Yes, you. Windscreen, go ahead.
Grandpa Walt, would you help with this ...
These seats?
No, you have probably
just your nails painted.
Grandpa makes me crazy.
Why did you ask me that?
Come on, let's go.
How many swamp rats
you get a room?
Grandpa, when you
that old-timer?
1972.
I never knew you
a cool old car had.
Yes, there is but
before you were born.
What will you do if
you something ...
as die?
What about those retro super bank
you have in your house,
I 've been thinking,
I go next year to the State,
and I think it would be in my room
and I have no furniture.
Oh, God.
Who are you?
- Hi, I'm Tao.
I live next door.
- Come on, say what you have to say.
I ...
- Tell me what you want.
Do you have jumper cables? My uncle is his car ...
- We do not have a jumper.
And have some respect, empty head.
We are here to mourn.
How does the volume, Walt.
Mr. Kowalski.
What?
- Mr. Kowalski, that's my name.
Well, Mr. Kowalski.
Your wife and I were
these last few months is very close.
She asked me to watch over you
when she died.
I told her
that I have my whole flock wake
but she let me promise
I am in the extra holes would hold.
I appreciate the kindness,
you have given to my wife.
Now that you have expressed your peace,
why not go to another sheep?
Good?
Dorothy said specifically that she wanted
that you would confess.
She said she could not remember,
when you last had.
Is that so?
- That's it.
I confess that I never much
have given to the church.
The only reason why I
I was, it was because of her.
And I confess that I have no desire
to confess
to a boy who just
training of the priest comes.
I wish I could help, Dad
but I must go home with the children.
Do not pressure?
- Yes, well, just go ahead.
I still call to hear how it goes.
- Good.
It kills you,
an American car.
Jesus.
Did you see how he looked into the truck?
It's always Rice-Burner this
Jap-buggy that.
Mon her own funeral
he can not let go.
He said nothing this time at least.
- That he did not.
What did you expect, Mitch? The man
has all these years, worked in the Ford factory.
I suppose it was my fault.
Let the rest, okay?
The kids want the radio on.
If your music? Well.
Fucking barbarians.
I have a broken heart pain.
I want my daughter
another man is.
If she marries again
there is another man in the house.
How is that Tao?
The man in the house is here.
Look at him.
He does the dishes.
He does what his sisters
like he does.
How can he ever
man in the house?
Be patient, as he once over,
he is the man in the house.
Really.
Today is a blessed day
the born child.
I offer food to the child-rearing.
I offer clothing
to the body of the child protection.
This child is blessed
with a mother and father.
Oh, spirit of this child,
go back home and not stray.
Go home spirit and soul,
go home.
Have a good life and old.
Jesus.
Polarski would turn in his grave,
if he would see his lawn.
Why are those slit eyes
moved to this neighborhood?
Why is that old white man?
All Americans have moved from the area.
Why are you not yet left?
Why do not deer paramilitary road,
you clumsy figure.
Why do not bark,
are you deaf or something?
Hi, Walt.
I am not a friend of you
Why Walt always called me?
Sorry, Mr.. Kowalski.
Where you wake today, Reverend.
- Nothing.
I came along to see how it went with you.
I have a time not seen in the church.
Now your good deed done again,
why not go back on the road?
I would like to talk to you, Mr.. Kowalski.
- Not in this life, son.
Why?
Do you have a problem with me, Mr. Kowalski?
- That you do not want to know.
No, I do.
I think you have a highly educated,
27 year old virgin, you
who like the
superstitious of old women hold
and promised them eternal life.
Are you a boy or a girl?
I can not say.
Hey, Chicito. Use your glasses?
What are you reading?
Jackass and Rice Stalk?
Yes, fun walk.
- Continue through.
Look at me when I talk to you.
- There is waste your step, man.
What are you looking at, man?
This is my little cousin, there.
- Is that your cousin, man?
That's my little nephew.
- Is he someone down?
No, he is on his own, Smokie.
- Is he solo?
Let us just look
what they are.
I love your sister.
Hey, how are you?
- I talk to you?
I talk to you?
- Transfer yourself.
We can do this now.
- Yes, right now.
Go fuck you back to your own country.
Fuck that, man.
- Yes.
You're a fucking nigger rice.
- Do you have something against Chinese food?
Damn Vietcong swamp rats.
Go back to your fucking rice country.
We get you.
- Windscreen, gas. Outta here!
Tao, let me see what you have.
Tao, come on get in the car.
Tao, get in the car.
- Get in, man, come on.
Tao! Waren fucking Mexicans
to torment you?
Come on, we are just coming up for you.
Tao come on, get in hell.
- What are you doing, man?
Get in the car, man.
Come on.
Two of us, man.
We just come up for you, man.
Come on.
What a bastard.
Come on, Tao.
- Bursting with him, let's go.
Come on.
- Let him crack.
Forget it, let's go.
Let him crack.
Tomorrow we see you.
Apply it on, little girl.
- Tomorrow!
Come on, man, we go.
We have the gun.
If the thunder here.
Wimp!
Hey, Tao.
How is it?
How is it, Tao?
What are you doing, little man?
Why do women's work?
What do you want?
What? I can not just
with my little cousin to talk?
He will not talk to you.
I'm still here.
- Hey, Spider, who is that?
How is it?
- Spider?
Is that how you just said, Fong?
Spider?
- Is there something wrong with Spider?
What are you doing here?
How old are you anyway?
Mentally I'm much too old for you.
- What?
You're a butthead.
I go inside.
Well, Sue!
Help your brother gardening.
Still, blockhead.
Hey, go with us a ride?
Friend.
Come on, go with us.
- Hang around a bit with us.
You need someone to protect you.
That's great for cousins.
Look, I've seen it all man.
Previously everyone wanted to beat me.
But now nobody is interfering
with me.
Come on, let's go.
- We are cousins?
Come on.
We are family.
A brother of Spider
is a brother of mine. Come on.
Do those things.
- Come up, come on.
This is women's work, man.
- Your hands are dirty, man.
What should I do?
Spider was on your neighbor.
Talked about his car.
Come on.
Good.
- Yes, my little cousin is a small man.
This is a nice car.
1972 Gran Torino,
fastback.
Cobra jet engine.
- Yes, that keeps him busy.
He is perfect condition, man.
I got one.
There are a Mexican, a Jew
and a Negro in a bar.
The bartender looks up and says:
'Do you guys out of here!
So here is my flock together
if they are not in the church.
Hi, Pastor J.
- Hey, Mel. Hi, Darrel.
Hello minister.
- Hi, Walt.
What brings you here, Reverend.
The meat lottery?
No, I came here to Walt
to talk, if that is good.
Damn it, Reverend.
You are persistent or not.
I have promised to your wife.
Well, let's take a seat.
I want a Pabst and a dash of Jack.
And what do you, Reverend?
I want a Diet Coke.
- Nonsense, this is a bar. You must drink.
I want a Gin and Tonic.
- Well done!
What do you want?
I promised your wife
I will make you confess.
Why would you do that?
- She was so persevere.
They did me.
You can not promise things
you can not make it, Pastor?
Let's talk about something else.
- What?
Life and death.
Life and death. What do you fucking
about life and death?
I think I know a lot from it.
I am a priest.
Yes, you are preaching to
about life and death.
But the only thing you know
is what you learned the priest training.
Direct from the new Priest Manual.
I know nothing of.
This is bittersweet.
Bitter in the pain
but fresh in his salvation.
That's what you know about life and death,
and that is pathetic.
What do you, Mr.. Kowalski?
I know a lot. I lived
nearly three years in Korea. Thank you.
We have men shot.
We strike them with banjo networks,
we hakten seventeen-year-old's death in Spades.
Things that I will remember my death.
Terrible things,
things which I have to live.
It's the life?
Well, I ...
I survived the war.
I am married
and got a family.
It sounds more
know about death than life.
Perhaps, Pastor.
Perhaps.
Asshole.
Hey, man, get in the car!
- Tao, get in!
Come Tao.
- Come on. Let's go. Get in!
Damn it, get in!
Hello?
Hey, good morning porridge.
This is your number one son, Mitch.
Tomorrow? It is one hour in the afternoon.
It is not morning.
Well, right.
Good then.
What do you want?
- What?
No, nothing.
I mean, what would I want?
I do not know. Is your wife is already
off with your mother's jewelry?
No, Dad, I just called
to hear how you are.
Any news from the old neighborhood?
Yes, no.
- Great, calm waters.
Yes.
- Okay, okay then.
Oh, hey, Dad.
- Yes.
Do you happen to that guy from the factory
Lion who has season tickets?
Dad?
Are not they sweet?
Come on.
How is it?
What are you doing, man?
- Nothing.
Interfere with our own affairs.
- Just hanging around.
What are you doing here?
We are ready.
I can not just
my little nephew to come?
I have good news for you.
- Really? And that is?
Only men talk.
- I do not think so.
Why not?
- Come on, we give you another attempt.
Do not go with you, Tao.
- Mind your own business, girl.
Come on, go.
- Come on.
Lift him.
What is this?
Get up.
- Get off my lawn.
Listen old man.
You do not want to interfere with me.
Did you not hear me?
Now go out of my lawn.
Are you crazy?
Go back into the house.
Yes, I blow a hole in your face
and then I go into the house.
And I sleep like a baby.
You can count on it.
We stacked ball things as you
two and a half meters high
and if you use sand bags.
Ok.
You can now continue to look back better.
Thank you.
Get off my lawn.
What is this?
No, no.
No, no, come on. Not more.
Stay there.
Why can you
me alone?
We have a couple of shallots
purchased for your garden.
I want them.
- They are permanent plants.
They grow every year.
- Why you bring me all this waste?
Because ...
Because you have saved Tao.
I have saved no one. I have only a few
kwebbel income gap chased eyes of lawn.
You are the hero of the neighborhood.
- I'm not a hero.
Unfortunately you are.
So get the gifts.
Please, take them.
- They are wrong.
I want to be left alone, thank you.
- Wait!
This is my mother, Vu.
I'm Sue, and that is my brother, Tao.
We live next to you.
- And then?
Tao wants to say something.
Excuse me.
- Regret what?
The attempted
to steal your car.
Let me tell you one thing, boy.
Put another step in this area,
and you're dead.
Good afternoon, Walt.
I said you do not go I confess.
- Why did not you just call the police?
What?
I'm working with a number of Hmong members,
and heard that there were problems in the neighborhood.
Why did you not call the police?
Well ...
You know, I have prayed
that they would come, but ...
nobody answered.
- What do you mean?
There was someone to be slain.
We are talking about life or death. "
If things are likely to go wrong,
you must respond quickly.
When we were in Korea, and up to 1000
screaming crack eyes were on our side
we do not call the police, we responded.
- We are not here in Korea, Mr.. Kowalski.
I thought
about our conversation about life and death.
About what you said.
About how all the terrible things
which was forced meedraagt you.
Terrible things that you do not let go.
It seems that you are well
to eliminate some of that guilt feelings to let go.
The things you do in the war
are terrible.
The order to kill ...
kill yourself to save
killing to save others.
You're right.
These are things that I do not know.
But I know of forgiveness.
And I have a lot of men their sins and guilt
see and admit their burden left behind.
Stronger men like you
Men during the war that orders
got a bad things to implement.
And now in peace.
I must admit, Pastor,
you had time enough to say.
Thank you
- And you had some things right.
About men stronger than me,
who have found salvation.
Damn, Hallelujah.
But something else did you wrong.
- And what's that, Mr.. Kowalski?
The thing that a man most opjaagt,
is that what he was not assigned to do.
Look, you look back at last
as a normal person off.
You should not wait until between
the haircuts, cheap bastard.
I am surprised
you still are.
I always hoped that you would die, and that
someone in your place who knew what he was doing.
Instead, you keep hanging around here
as a Do-Wop, Dago, who you are.
That is ten dollars, Walt.
- Ten dollars, Jesus Christ, Martin.
Are you a half-Jew, or something?
You always increase the price.
It has been five years, ten dollars, you know
as well as I do, Polish bastard.
Keep the change.
- See you again in three weeks, dick.
Not if I see before you, bitch.
That's cool, you know.
Man, check this out.
Look.
Come here with that tight ass.
Come here, girl. Let me see.
Can not you say hello?
You 're cocky.
What is this, man?
- This is cool, Dog.
What the hell are you doing in my neighborhood, man?
Nothing, we went to the corner, away,
some CDs and so on, it's cool, bro.
He called you bro, man.
- What? It's cool, bro.
Sounds good.
- Shut up.
Call me again bro
and I bite into your face.
Yes, you bastard.
- Why are you here?
Are you here to me
nice gift to bring?
This Oriental Yummy?
- Do not worry, I really care for her.
Get out here, man.
- Get out here, man.
Hey, kid.
We told you.
I told you that my friend
for her will.
You stay here.
- So, now it is up to me.
Oh, great.
Another asshole with an obsession for
Asian girls, which is already so old.
What is your name, girl?
My name?
Get out here, okay.
That is: 'Rags excessive, clearly come prepared
on every woman who passes and full stop. "
That is my name.
Who do you think
you're talking to?
To whom it seems.
- You find yourself very nice, right?
What she is tough.
- What? Please save me now?
That would complete the picture.
You must girl better defender.
Make a chain to the whore and pull out.
Of course, just a stereotype dictionary.
- Oh, yes.
Call me a bitch and whore in the same sentence.
- That bitch is crazy.
So I like them.
- Get that bitch.
You do not know when to stop you, girl.
- We will teach you a lesson.
Stop, let go.
Go there.
What are you, old man?
Where are you niggers doing?
Negroes?
You better make the right time,
now that still can.
That's right, that you can do much better.
Who do you think you are?
Never noticed that you occasionally
someone, it will
where you do not have to balls?
That I am.
Are you crazy man, on Thursday.
Get out before I
you kick your white ass.
He is really a bitch, man.
Is the bastard completely crazy?
- Damn. What?
Jump in the truck.
He is a real asshole.
- He really used his finger.
Hey, Dad easy.
- Keep your goddamn face.
You do not want to listen, do you?
And now in the truck.
- Get in the truck.
Well done, old man.
- Shut up, wimp.
What does all that stuff bro?
Would you like Superman, or something?
Those guys want to bro you are not
and I give them no wrong.
Make that you are away.
Take care of yourselves.
You too.
Oh, yes.
Damn, we were
nothing done, man?
We had him on his Thursday
to give.
Damn.
- It is not worth it, man.
He had the gun on your focus.
You could do nothing, man.
What's in Godnaam
the matter with you?
Are you trying to kill yourself?
I thought Asian girls
or were smarter.
To get to hang around in that area,
is a quick way for you to end.
I know.
I know, calm down.
And how about that fool
where you were together?
Is that your boyfriend or something?
Yeah, kind of, he is called Trey.
- Well, you should not deal with him.
You should treat your own people.
- In other Hu-Momgs, you mean Hmong.
Hmong, non-Hu Mmong
- I guess.
Where is Hmong, Mong I mean then?
You're the teachers, did you know that?
No, no place is Hmong,
its people.
Hmong people come from different
parts of Laos and Thailand and China.
How did you come in my neighborhood?
Why have you not been there?
It is a little Vietnamese.
We have fought on your side.
And when the Americans stopped them ...
started the Communists
all the Hmong to murder.
So we came here.
Yes. But why did you pick Midwest.
Snow on the ground, six months per year.
What is it? Jungle people want
on the frozen tundra?
Mountain People. We are people from the mountains,
no jungle people. Boo-ga, ga-Boo, Boo-ga!
Yes, it will be.
Enter the Lutheran debt.
they have brought to us below.
All the Lutheran debt.
Well, you would think that the cold
all these idiots would be absent.
Thanks for the ride.
You know, girl, you're quite right.
But what happened to that damn brother of yours?
Is this a little slow, or something?
Tao is actually pretty smart.
He not only knows what direction he should.
Poor Toad.
- It is really common.
Mhong girls adapt better.
The girls go to school
and the boys to prison.
The old witch hate me.
Your birthday today, Daisy.
This year you must make a choice
between two life paths.
A second chance is on your way.
Extraordinary events reach their
climax, which turns out to be anti-climax.
Your lucky numbers are: 84, 23, 11, 78 and 99.
What a nonsense.
Yes.
What is it these days
with children on?
Well.
Let me help you on it.
- Oh, thank you.
How about that?
How about it, Daisy?
It is too heavy for me to wear.
- No problem.
Karen Come, give it to him.
- Please.
Well, what is it?
- It is a Gopher.
So you can grasp things.
It makes things much easier.
This is mine.
It is a phone.
I see that.
I thought, well, we thought
that would make things easier.
Thank you, Karen.
There is nothing wrong with things
for yourself less difficult.
Karen, is right, Dad.
You've worked hard all your life.
Maybe it's time to think about it
to facilitate.
Another thing, Dad. You would really
cancer sticks that have been damaged.
But, we think about the house.
Now Mom is no longer here
There is much to maintain.
Keep everything clean.
And now here you are ...
Yes, there are great places.
Of those communities,
where you do not have to worry
about your lawn mowing or snow slide.
Where people like you, active and alert,
but only ...
and support of people
of the same age.
Yes, Dad, look. You should check here.
We have brought a few brochures.
These places are not like you think that they are.
- No, they are beautiful.
They are really beautiful.
They are real.
These are top boundaries.
It is almost like a hotel.
- They are beautiful.
They are real.
- Yes.
They take care of everything.
They are clean. They are really beautiful.
They have beautiful stores.
You can buy new shoes.
They are amazing,
they are real.
You have a nice time.
Maybe a little play.
Meet other people.
Fuck us out kicking his birthday.
I told you this was a bad idea.
I know. You were right.
- He leaves no one to help him.
Well, we have tried.
Can we just let the rest?
No one can say
that we have not tried.
Let him run the pump.
You know what we should do?
We were at home with Josh and Ashley
should continue.
They were smart enough not to come.
These kids have more sense than we do.
We miss Mom or not, Daisy?
Hi, Walt.
What are you doing?
We have a barbecue.
Wil you come?
What do you think?
- We have tons of food.
Yes, keep your hands off my dog.
- Do not worry. We only eat cats.
Really?
- No, I'm kidding, moron.
Come on, then you are my special guest.
- No, I did it myself.
Yes ...
Asshole.
- Okay, what have you eaten today?
A piece of cake.
And a piece of dried beef.
Come and get something to eat.
We have beer.
Well ...
I might as well drink with a stranger
than just drinking. It is my birthday.
Really? Congratulations, Wally.
- Call me 'Wally'.
You do not have enough beer Pabts
- As they say: 'when Mhong. "
What am I doing wrong? Every time I
someone to look, they look at the floor.
What she says?
- Welcome to our house.
No, she says not.
- Yes, she says not.
She hates me.
- Yes, they hate you.
Ok.
Where you see fish heads
also at?
I think we
to the other room. Sorry.
Many people in the room are traditional.
Number 1, never touch a Hmong person
on his head on.
Do not kid. Mhong people
believe that their soul to the head.
Do not that.
- Sounds silly, but good.
Yes, many people find it Mhong
in the eyes look very rude.
So they look away when you look at them.
- Anything else?
Yes, some people laugh Mhong
and grin as they scream.
It is a cultural thing.
The press embarrassment or uncertainty.
It is not that you laugh, or something.
You people are mesjokke.
But the food ...
Looks good, smells good.
- Of course, it's Mhong eat.
Okay, I can brag half time?
Please.
- Thanks. You said ...
they are not for people watching,
but he tail me all night.
That is Kor Khue.
He is a family medicine Lor.
What's that, a doctor or other magic?
- If something.
Yes, boeki books.
- Very funny, Wally.
Kor Khue is interested in you
He has heard what you've done.
He likes you want to predict.
It is rude to him not to do.
It is a great honor.
Yes, of course, I think the best.
- Well, sit down,
He says you do not respect our people.
They want you do not even look at.
He says, as you live, your food has no taste.
You make you worry about your life.
You have in your previous life is a mistake.
Are you not happy about?
He says you do not have joy in your life.
It is as if you have no peace.
Goes well with you?
Yes, it is good to me.
It goes well with me.
I have more in common with this slit eyes
rotten with my own family.
Jesus Christ.
Congratulations on your birthday.
All right with you?
- Yes, I'm fine.
You bleed.
- I have bitten my tongue.
It is nothing.
Let's go down and slit-eyes
food to eat. I die of hunger.
Well.
It is beautiful.
This stuff is really good.
Come on, wolverine.
- What is it?
Let's go.
- Why?
To us the people to mix.
- I mix me all right.
Come on. You've told me
you not only to them.
Thank you very much.
I must go now.
I'll be back.
Let it not interfere road.
Well, look who it is.
- Yes, that guy who wanted to steal my Torino.
My brother Tao.
- He tried. He has learned.
He was a bit wobbly.
I have made.
What is this?
A bit of rice alcoholic drink.
Here, try it.
Well.
My friends and I asked ourselves
here is what you do.
That's a good question,
what I do.
My name is Walt.
- Hi, Walt. I am Wa Xam.
Wa Yum?
- No, Wa Xam.
Wa Xam, good.
- What are you doing?
I fix things. Things like that.
- Like what?
I have just repaired the dryer.
I have just the sink
my friend repaired.
I drove my great-aunt to doctor
recipes for her to explain.
I have the door repaired
that piece was not even.
You're funny.
I am mentioned frequently but never funny.
Well, I go by. Have fun.
- Okay, Yum Yum. It was a pleasure.
She goes. Come on.
Relax, empty head.
I 'm not gonna shoot.
I would look down on her,
if I were you.
I know you a little sucker was
when I first saw you.
Never thought that you were even worse
women than to steal from cars, Toad.
It is Tao.
- What?
It is not Toad, it's Tao.
My name is Tao.
Yes, you verknalde while the
the girl was there.
Not that I do anything
a Toad as you.
You do not know where you are talking about.
You have the wrong spring rolls.
I know exactly what I am talking about.
I am perhaps the most enjoyable
persoontje to deal
but I had the best woman
on this planet, who married.
I was sure it was the best
what ever happened to me. It.
But you ...
You let Ding Dong Click Clack and Charlie Chan
Miss with 'what-is-its-face' walk away.
They like you, you know.
No idea why.
Who?
Yum Yum!
You know, that girl in the purple sweater.
They looked at you all day, chucklehead.
You mean, Wa Xam?
- Yes, Yum Yum. Yes, nice girl.
Nice girl. A very charming girl.
I have spoken with her.
But you, you let her go
with three slaves.
And you know why?
Because you're a big fat wimp.
Well ...
I gotta go.
Fine day, soft cake.
No, not more.
Okay, put them down.
No, no. no more.
Not anymore. Come on.
No more, please.
I ...
Is that kipknoedel
the last time you had?
Okay.
Better than that worthless beef
I can tell you.
What is wrong?
- Toa is here to put things right.
He is here to work for you.
- That he is not.
He does not work for me.
My mother says that the family shame
has and must now repay his debt.
He starts tomorrow morning.
- Oh, no. Not tomorrow. Never.
I do not even want him on my land.
I thought that we had had.
It is very important for my mother
that you accept.
It would be an insult to
if you refuse.
Why turn against me?
He tried to steal my car ...
and suddenly I'm the bad.
Look, my family is very traditional
very disappointed and would be made
Tao if it does not repay.
Sue, if he does not want to do,
let him go.
Keep your mouth!
Yes, you keep your mouth.
Well, tomorrow.
Come on, tomorrow. Thank you.
Thank you.
Jesus, who Mhong Mokkels
just cops.
The son of a bitch, I thought he
would not come up.
Well, where are you in?
Like what?
- That I ask you.
If you work for me
I must know where you are good at.
I need to know what you can.
- I do not know.
That is about half of what I
expected that you would say.
See that tree over there?
Go back and count the birds.
Do you want me count the birds?
- Yes, you can still count?
All you slit eyes
are still good at math, right?
Yes, I can count.
- Good.
One, two ...
What do you have for me to do?
Wil you that I watch the paint dry?
You may want to
I count the clouds that come?
Do not be so brutal to me, boy.
I'm not the one who tried to
to steal. Remember that.
Go ahead.
I don 't care if you insult me
or says racist things.
Do you know what? I accept it.
- Of course you accept it.
Because you have no teeth
and have no balls, kid.
Look, I'm here to adopt. Why search
you do not something sensible for me to do.
I am not like you. I am not useless
and I maintained my own property.
You swamp rats
there may be nothing to do.
How long do I have?
Toad, how long?
Until next week Friday.
Well, get the ladder from the garage.
When you're done with that roof,
you can gutter again carpenter.
It bothers me for three years.
Yes, what you say, comrade.
Hello.
Grandpa asked whether you can ensure
Toa that the large hornets' nest
under our porch away.
Hornets' nest?
That is terrible.
I think that after the lunch
to regulate.
Holy God, quit.
Hey, it's my last day.
What do you have for me to do?
Take today, Friday
You've done enough.
Taod!
Nothing.
Forget it.
Kowski?
Mr. Kowalski?
Good morning.
I have viewed your paper and I think we
should immediately begin a series of tests.
I feel that this is the best way to all
issues that you had to check.
Excuse me, what happened to doctor Felmon,
my doctor, happened?
Dr. Felmon retired three years ago.
I'm his replacement, Dr Chang.
It is Grandpa Walt.
- Take on you.
You talk to him!
Mitch.
I am the accounts to do it.
- You talk to him. It's your father.
Hi, Dad.
Hey, Mitch.
I am your father.
Yeah, I know.
What is going on
Nothing, not much.
How are you?
Well, all right.
Good, and Karen and the kids
Well, everybody does it.
They do well.
Good. And the work?
Press. Yes ...
Yes, I thought that al
Dad, talk about pressure, I have
much to do, so if nothing is urgent ...
No, nothing.
Why call you the weekend?
Sure.
Well, nice to have just spoken, Dad.
Thanks for calling.
Thank you.
HOSPITAL TOELATINGSFORMULIER
MEDICAL TESTING RESULTS
This guy has no chance.
What do you know of cranes?
I know everything there, boy.
Go to the side.
Jesus on earth.
- What?
It should be here to 100 degrees.
Put the fan.
Please, this dondert together.
Man, where you have all this stuff come from?
What are you talking about?
- About the tools and everything.
Well, it will be for a thief
a surprise,
but I have all these things here
bought with my own money.
Yes, yes. That is not what I meant.
I mean, there's so much.
Yes, each tool has a purpose.
Everything has a job to do.
All that is required.
- Okay, what's that?
That is paalgatgraver.
- And that?
Hand Schep.
You know it is a hand shovel, come on.
This is a metal scissors,
and that is a saw.
This is a hammer
You can 't be fooled, kid.
Well, what are you like.
It is just ...
I can imagine all this stuff not afford.
Well, I think that even a dolt like you
will understand
that somebody will get together
over a period of 50 years.
Yes, but ...
- Well, look. Here.
What you need is here.
WD-40 and a pipe wrench
and ductape.
Any man who is worth anything, the half
the chores at home with those three things.
Everything else you need
you just borrow, that's all.
Well. Cool.
Fuck you.
- What is that?
Nothing.
What?
Nothing? I saw you expectorate blood.
That is not good. You have to go to a doctor.
Look, ...
Those boys who were here on that night ...
on my lawn, how about with them?
- Just a mess. Hmong gang.
Yes, I thought that al
What did they do here.
She wanted me to take. They were angry
I had my first inauguration blow.
Yes, you're a wimp if you
that kind of guests want to hang around.
What did you inauguration should be.
My Gran Torino?
Toad, do you mind?
Here he is.
This is the deal.
I take the top
because this is the worst. I pull out
and you are there and pushes.
And each step up to help me push.
Just that way.
- Let me take the top.
No, I take the top.
He seems pretty heavy.
I'm not crippled.
I take the top.
If you have the top does not take
I do not help and I go back home.
Listen to me, zero.
- No, you listen, old man!
I'm here because you need help.
So it is the top
I'm outta here.
Well, you take the top
and I push.
Leave him out of your small
girl hands slip and crush me.
Bring me ideas.
That thing weighs a ton.
But it runs like a clock.
If they do not anymore.
What will you do with it?
- Selling, I think.
How many?
- Sixty dollars.
I'm sick of that in the basement
to leave.
Why?
Are you looking for a freezer?
Those of us play.
- Okay, twenty-five dollars and he is yours.
Twenty-five?
But you just said sixties.
I know, but it saves me money for a
ad in the newspaper to continue.
Come on, let him
drag to your house.
A bit ironic, huh?
- What?
Toad a car wash
he tried to steal from you.
Yes, if he misses a spot
then it all again.
Nice as it provides you.
He is not really an example in his life.
I am not an example.
- But you're a good man, Wally.
I wanted you as our father had been.
- Give me no more Wally.
No, I'm serious. He was really
hard against us, very traditional
and really old-fashioned.
- I'm old-fashioned.
Yes, but you're an American.
What do you mean?
You like him or not?
- Take me in your leg?
He tried to steal my car.
And time you bring with him,
teach him to fix things.
And saved him from the fucking cousin of us ...
- Hey, watch your language, lady!
And you're a good man.
- I am not a good man.
Give me another beer, dragon lady.
It is empty.
You know, Hmong believes
gardening is that women's work.
Yes, that's why I see you always in the garden.
Furthermore, we are not in Hu-Mong.
- Funny.
You should stop.
That is bad for you
- Yes? Like a gang go slow duikelaar.
Did you not hear what I just said?
I saw you expectorate blood.
You should stop.
What does the fact that emblem?
First cavalry.
I have since'51.
What do you do with your life, son.
I thought perhaps sell.
- Sale?
My oldest son is in the sale.
- Is he right?
Oh, yes.
License to steal.
I have fifty years worked in the Ford plant,
and he sells Japanese cars.
Have you built cars?
- Yes.
I placed the steering column in the Gran Torino
in 1972, when he rolled the tape.
You are old.
So cool.
Yes, so you want in the sale. You think about it
perhaps to go to school?
A little, but school costs money.
- Maybe you should take a job.
You can not sit
manure and straw under my garden.
Maybe you can pay me.
- Yes, very funny.
What kind of job can I get?
- Yes, you're right. No one will you never take.
Yes, I know.
- I kidding, zero.
I mean, you get a job.
You get a job anywhere.
Like what?
What about the building?
- Me?
Yes.
- The construction?
- Do you have Alzheimer's or something.
No. You get a job in construction.
I know people in the box.
Of course, I tell you what training
and a bit 'opmannen.
Me "opmannen?
- Yes.
And I think you Miss Yum Yum
must interrogate.
It would do you good.
It would
Now how do you guys talk.
Listen to the way
Martin and I go back and communicate.
Are you okay? Are you ready?
- Sure.
Well, let's go inside.
Perfect.
Pool and gook.
How are you, Martin,
you mad Italian dick.
Walt, cheap bastard,
I know that you came.
I had just such a nice day.
- What have you done?
Got a blind man
afgeholpen of money?
Have you given him the wrong change?
- Who is the Jap?
Oh, he's the wimp of the neighbors.
I try a little man of him to do.
See your kid?
So guys talk with each other.
Do they really?
- Did you shit in your ears?
Come on and come in
and talk to him as a man.
If a real man.
Come on.
Get to come out.
Come back now.
I am sorry for that.
It is good.
How is it, you old Italian dick?
Get out of my shop before
I bang your head off, damn gook!
Jesus Christ.
Oh, shit.
Take it easy. What the hell are you doing?
Are you crazy?
That is what you said.
That is what you said, say it!
Something you do not, you will not
and insulting the man in his own shop.
If you say the wrong
knalt than he spleetooghoofd you off.
What was I supposed to say?
- To begin with: "Hi or 'hello'.
Yes, come in and say: 'Sir, I would like
my hair cut, if you have time. "
Yes, keep the people of
but you should not creep into his ass.
In fact, you can have a job in the construction
talk to you today is just.
Or tell your friend
and your car.
Bastard, I just
my brakes repaired,
and those bastards have caught me.
They screwed me in the ass.
Yes, do not swear at the boy.
Talk about people who are not in the room.
You can whine about your boss,
you work late as the bowling night.
Right, if my wife zeurt
two hours long, about how she ...
they are not in the grocery
expired vouchers take
and as I was back in the game,
she starts to cry why we never talk.
See, now go out.
Come back inside and talk to him.
It is on earth,
not rocket science.
Yes, but I have no job,
no car or a girlfriend.
Jesus, I had his head should pop off
when I had the chance.
Yes, maybe. Okay, I want you
you turn, and goes beyond
and come back and not talking about
you have no job,
no car, no girlfriend, no future,
no dick. Good? Turn around and you just go.
Excuse me, sir.
I want a haircut if you're not too busy.
Italian bastard,
bastard of a barber.
Boy, my butt hurts
all those guys in the building.
Fuck you.
Everything ready for this to continue, right?
- Yes, yes.
Not so, yes, to me.
Just say: 'yes, sir, I do my best. "
Yes, I do my best.
- If I am guaranteed to anyone,
means that I gave them my word.
I do not want you put me in front.
No, I do my best.
I go for it.
Explain you can not accept that.
Look him right in his eyes and the man
may know a lot about you by your handshake.
Here, do this in your back pocket.
- Cool.
Verknal this.
Hi, Kennedy, drunk Irish dolt.
How are you?
Sucks, but who is listening?
- Not me, that's for sure.
Help yourself, Walt.
Stupid Pool.
Well, this is the guy that I have told you.
Toa, this is Tim Kennedy
he is the best in this work.
What we have here, Walt?
He knows about the building
and he is a smart kid.
He does everything
which you need him.
Are you sure?
- Yes.
Do you speak English.
- Yes, sir.
Are you born here.
- Oh, yeah.
I see that Walt brought you here.
Do you have a vehicle?
At this moment. I am now going by bus.
- The bus? Jesus Christ, you have no car?
My head gasket is broken. Those in the dick
Shop wants $ 2100 to the docks.
Please, I got the transistor radio
in my Tahoe substituted.
And the mother left me many things docks.
Just under $ 3200.
Fucking thieves. That is wrong.
- Since you have right.
Well, come Monday
and then we find something for you.
Thank you, Mr. Kennedy.
It is Tim and what was your name again?
- Tao.
T. .., okay.
You owe me anything, Walt.
Yes, I buy for Christmas
a fruit cake for you.
Fuck off with that fruit cake.
Why do not you give me the key
of Gran Torino?
Why would anyone my car?
- Well, I'm not surprised.
Yes, you know not even half.
Well, come on, empty head.
Let the Mick here
and play with themselves.
What do we do?
What do you do?
Your tools in a carry bag?
Here.
You can use one of these ...
and you have a need.
Here.
I can not afford.
I got it. You can pay back
with your first salary.
Cool.
- Here, you have something like this.
This is what I was looking for.
Here, a tool belt.
Please.
I do not want to be unkind,
but I do not what tools are needed?
I have tools, but I leave you
not borrow my tool belt.
You can deal with tools when you go.
I really appreciate it.
- Forget it.
No, I really do.
Thank you.
How are you, comrade?
What are you doing?
What is going on, man?
- What do you relschoppertje.
Let's see how it goes with my little nephew.
- Yeah, man.
Our little cousin ...
What is this?
Where are you from, man?
- I come from ...
'm on my way home from work.
Not that you know something about.
It is true? You have a job.
- Can you leave me alone?
What?
You're scared, huh?
Who did that stuff for you bought your father?
- What do you want from me?
Did your father bought this stuff for you?
- Get your hands off my stuff.
I need that helmet.
- Why you let me look so bad, huh?
Get your hands off my stuff!
Give me that.
- Come on, that's my stuff.
Would you like smoking, bad at!
Let me go!
Give me that, man.
Give me that.
What's the saying
I'm looking for?
Oh, yes, red face. "
Hi.
I am in a hurry.
I have you all seen a few days.
Where have you been?
I'm busy.
Busy?
What the hell happened to you?
- Don 't worry about it.
What do you mean, 'do not worry. "
Look at your face.
I said, 'do not worry. "
Okay, it's not your problem.
When?
It took me a couple days ago
when I just came from my work.
Cowards.
I did what I could do.
But what they have
Your tools destroyed.
I will be replaced.
- Do not worry for the tool.
Where lives your cousin?
No, Walt.
It is all right with me.
I do not want you to do something.
- Good.
If you need additional tools
let me know.
Well, I can use a roofing hammer.
- Well, go to my garage and get it.
That would be the last.
Well, this is the deal.
You stay away from Tao. Understood?
You say to your friends
that they remain near Tao.
And if they do not listen to you
they will never see him.
That was it. Understood?
I take that as a 'yes' because if I have
in can be very unpleasant.
Walk me in the way.
How do you want your 'dog'?
I mean your steak?
Funny.
- I told you, we only eat cats.
I've never been so you have seen.
I feel good.
I have beautiful women, great food.
And Tao.
- And even Tao does not bother me.
You have great meaning to you, I see.
- Yes.
It never.
What's also
with your knuckles happened?
I slipped in the shower.
No big problem.
Look, Yum-Yum. If he can not ask out,
I would ask you out.
Wa Xam, do not listen to him.
He is the white devil.
Yes, I am.
I'm the white devil.
I would like to Walt,
but he has you.
Really? Unbelievable!
From food and a movie, or what?
Yes, they go by bus.
No, you can not take the bus.
You need something with more style.
Like what?
With a limo?
How about that?
Gran Torino?
- Yes.
You let me take the Gran Torino?
- Yes, I let you take the Gran Torino.
Really?
Yes, really.
Is everyone OK?
Tao!
It is good.
Where is Grandma?
Where's Sue?
- She is our aunt.
To her aunt? Are you sure?
- Yes.
Take the phone and call if it is.
Sue ...
I knew this would happen.
What am I doing here?
Perhaps one of her friends
call and have made other plans.
Yes.
During the war I lost many friends
but it is still on.
You do it.
Mr. Kowalski?
All right with you?
Yes, it is good to me.
The police has finally gone.
Nobody speaks.
One thing about the Hmong
and they keep their lips together.
Yes, that was me noticed.
You know, Tao and Sue will be in this
world never find peace ...
that as long as there are gangs.
Until they are gone.
You know, forever.
What do you say?
You know what I say.
I have Sue to the hospital.
She is afraid.
They are all afraid.
- Yes.
Special Tao.
He sits there staring at your front door.
You know what he expected Mr. Kowalski.
What would you do?
What would Tao to do?
- I know what I would do if I was you.
If you think you should do.
- Really?
If I was Tao
I would like to take revenge.
I would be shoulder to shoulder with you
and guests who want to murder.
And you?
- What would I do?
I would come here
and talk with you, I think.
I know that you are close with these people
but I also touch on the zeik, Mr. Kowalski.
Do you want a beer?
- Sure.
There are some in the fridge,
behind you
Fucking shit.
It's just not fair.
- Nothing is fair, Pastor.
What will you do now, Mr. Kowalski?
Call me Walt.
Well.
What will you do, Walt?
I do not know.
But I remember something.
Whatever it will be
they will have no chance.
What do you do?
Think.
Thinking?
Think time is over.
Now is the time in which acorns
off.
I know that you do not want to hear
but now it is time to remain calm.
Quiet?
Wil you that I remain quiet?
Keep quiet or else
mistakes are made.
We must take this same distance.
No. Let me fall, Walt.
Not you.
This will stop today!
Sit down.
I do not want to sit.
- I said, 'Sit down'.
Listen to me.
We need this plan.
And very careful plans.
We can not make mistakes.
You have the right man for the job.
I want you to go home, remain calm
at 4 o'clock this afternoon and return.
What should happen, will happen.
- I say that we are going. Now!
And then what? Those of you nephew murder
and the rest of the zeros?
Mr Stoere, out for blood.
You know nothing of.
Now go home and ...
stay calm and come here
four hours back. Good?
Good?
Well.
I know. Do me a favor, please.
The first time I smoke in the house.
Let the man enjoy the same,
wants you, girl?
Ready.
Ten U.S. dollars.
I suspect that
bibber using your hands enough
for a smooth shave to give?
- A smooth shave?
You've never
for a smooth shave requested.
I know, but I got you
always wondered how that is.
Unless you're too busy.
- No, let me warm up a towel.
And here's twenty.
Keep the change
in case you touched my neck vein.
Yes, it takes me an hour.
We need this here a little shorter.
We must make the appropriate shoulder.
Yes, I have never
one-styled suit had.
Yes, sir.
It looks very good.
What can I do for you, Mr.. Kowalski?
- I am here to confess.
Oh, what have you done?
- No, you do now but easy.
What are you planning?
- Do you take me to confess, or not?
How long ago is that you
last gebiecht have?
Forever.
Bless me, Reverend, for my sins.
- What are your sins, my son?
In 1968, I kissed Betty Jablonski
Christmas at the factory.
Dorothy was in another room
with the other women.
It just happened.
Yes, go on.
I have nine hundred dollars margins
by a boat and engine sales.
I have no tax paid
and that is the same as a steal.
Yes, good.
Finally ...
I was never very close with my two sons.
I do not know them.
I do not know how.
Was that it?
- That was it.
It was my entire life like.
Say ten 'Weesgegroetjes'
and five "Our Fathers."
God loves you and forgive you
And relieved you of your sins.
In the name of the Father,
the Son and the Holy Spirit.
Thank you, Pastor.
Will you ever take revenge
what has happened with Sue?
I go to that house today, Mr. Kowalski.
Is that so?
- That is so.
And every day until you see
that stupid is what you're planning.
Busy day, I gotta go.
- Go in peace.
Oh, I am peace.
Mighty God!
What is mine?
Have you ever shot with a gun?
- No.
I want you in it.
I have something I
you want to show, come on.
What?
In 1952, we were sent out
Chink-a strong point to overcome.
They had us nice suits.
I was the only one who came back that day.
This gave me a silver star.
Here it is.
Here, I want you to have it.
Why?
We all knew the danger that night
but we went anyway.
Thus it can also go tonight.
There is always a chance that you do not come back.
- The dead Thursday not.
We are going to go in there
and let them smell a poopy.
Yes, that would be stupid.
That is exactly the reaction they wait.
Come on, quit this.
How many?
- How much what?
How many men have you killed in Korea?
Thirteen, maybe more.
- How was it to kill a man?
That is you do not know.
Make it up.
Walt! Walt!
What are you doing?
Calm down, because you can not.
- Let me now!
Let me out! Son of a bitch, let me out.
I kill you if I'm out!
Shut up!
Want to know how it is
to kill a man?
Well, it's horrible, it is.
The only thing worse is that you have a medal
courage to get, because you kill a poor boy,
who had just given.
That's all.
Yes, as a frightened gook, just like you.
I shot him right in his face with that gun
you just have taken down there.
Not a day goes by that I do not think.
You don 't want your soul.
I have blood on my hands.
I'm tainted.
So tonight I go alone.
Walt, take me with you!
Let me out!
Look, you've come a long way.
I am proud to say that my
friend. But you have your whole life for you.
But I? I end things.
That is what I do. And I go alone.
No, wait.
Walt!
I want you on my dog pass.
Yes, I love yours
Yes, she is also old.
Her name is Daisy.
Hello.
- Here is Walt.
The key to my house under
the ceramic turtle at the front.
Let yourself within.
Your brother is in the basement. I gotta go.
Sorry, Reverend.
We gotta go.
I tell you,
if you are not there, there will be blood flow.
We have been here hours.
We can not afford
to a unit in a location to hold.
I beg you to stay.
I have command of my sergeant.
We pull the plug out.
I'll stay.
- No, you do not.
We have a clear mission.
You came with us and you can take us away.
Watch your head.
Sue, on this side.
This side.
Let me out.
He is left without me.
He has gone without me Smokies.
Tao!
Are there within swamp rats?
I did not think that you would come.
- Shut up, gook.
I have nothing to say, under door.
A dwarf like you.
Yes, yes.
Go ahead, look out for your boyfriend.
Because it was either he or you or anyone else
someone of your own family raped.
Create your own blood, in hell.
Go ahead and you pull your gun,
as dwarf Cowboy's.
Go your way.
Where is Tao?
Could not that what you are?
Do not worry about Tao.
Tao has no second time for you.
Who says that?
You?
What do you do to hell, old man?
What are you doing, old man?
- Pussy.
A little schrikkerig, or not?
- Shut up.
Keep you mouth.
Got a light?
- Fuck you.
No.
I ...
I have a fire.
'Hail Mary, full of grace. "
Yes, sergeant.
What happened?
- You must make a pass backwards.
He is a friend of mine.
- He said: 'a backward pass. "
Hey, have you heard him?
A pass backwards.
What happened?
- Hey, a pass backwards.
Let me, he is my friend.
Please, it's important.
He took his lighter
and they shot him down.
He had no gun with him.
This time, we have witnesses.
These guys we wanted
have long detention.
Chang Agent! Send these people back!
- Now a pass backwards, okay?
If the thunder here.
Get them here.
Walt Kowalski once said to me,
I knew nothing about life and death.
Because I trained a lot, 27 year old virgin,
that the basis of superstitious old women did
and promised them eternal life.
Walt had no problem with that
to name as he saw it.
But he was right.
I knew nothing about life and death,
Walt until I know.
And guys, what have I learned.
Then I leave my house to the church after
because Dorothy would have wanted.
That brings us to the last point. And again,
Excuse me for the language,
in the testament of Mr. Kowalski, I read
simple as it is written.
And I would like my Gran Torino in 1972,
Failure to ...
my friend ...
Lor Vang Tao.
Provided that your roof is not fucked,
as one of the cocks,
paint no stupid flames out, as
that 'white trash' boerenkinkels,
not gay spoiler and place at the end
as you'll see that other nitwit cars.
It does not look.
If you  all abstains
it is yours.
Translated by
al_kabalawy@hotmail.com
www.opensubtitles.org