- The USS Kelvin Starfleet Fleet.
- Here Starfleet Fleet.
I sent a message.
Did you received?
Kelvin, you've checked the data?
Sensors gravity took it
crazy. It's incredible.
It looks like an electrical storm.
You seem possible data
that you have sent.
Yeah, Mrs. I understand.
That's why we've sent.
- Report.
- Contact video over 20 seconds.
Captain Fleet recommends Robau
act with caution...
polarized screen.
- Whatever it is, is somehow Klingon
- We have visual contact.
- Repeat. E Klingon.
- Negative, It.
Klingon border e
to 75,000 km away.
Captain, you see?
My God.
Reception data.
They opened fire on us.
Red Alert.
torpedo boat in the course for us.
20 degrees, vector 2.
evasive maneuvers Delta 5.
m coming fast.
Fire all phasers.
Report damage.
warp engine is out of service.
I never saw anything like that.
guns do not work.
Main supply is 38%.
- They launched another torpedo.
- All the energy in front shields.
Lieutenant.
capacity maneuver affected.
I had the shields active?
We have confirmed victims
on decks 17 and 13.
11% and dropping. 10%.
Shields are at 9%.
deviate all energy
available to front shields.
navetele Prepare for evacuation.
Hello.
My master calls
the master of your
to negotiate the cessation of fire.
You come on our ship in a
shuttle. It would be unwise to refuse.
Come with me.
If you do not get to hear me
in 15 minutes, discharging crew.
- Sir, can...
- I have no help here.
Use automatic pilot
and leave the ship.
Yes, Captain.
You are the master now, Mr Kirk.
Are high pulse.
Look at this ship.
- You know the model
- Who's the master?
- He's
- I talk to the captain Nero.
Then ask him Captain Nero:
what the attack a ship of the Federation?
You know where
Ambassador Spock?
Do not know
the Ambassador Spock.
- What is the current date stellar
- Date stellar?
2233.04.
How come?
liquidated.
- Sir, we have taken in the viewfinder.
- They opened fire and.
Good attack scheme 6.
Initial orders generally 13. Evacuated.
Sir.
All the bridges, the master here.
Ship evacuated immediately.
Now. Go
navetele to the rescue.
- Is the voice of George. What happens?
- I born in the shuttle. Come on.
- George.
- Thank God you are alright.
37 medical ship is waiting.
Go to it now. Can you reach?
- Yes.
- Everything will be fine.
- Do what you say. Shuttle 37.
- George. Baby arrives.
- I was born now.
- Coming soon.
The pilot has been automatically disabled.
Command only works manually.
Hurry up. Go to the shuttle.
- Faster.
- Continue to breathe. I will be fine.
- And baby, right?
- And the baby.
This way.
to master the shuttle 37.
It's my wife on board?
- Yes, sir.
- Get out now.
- I wait for you
- No off immediately.
- Is an order.
- Yes, sir.
Wait. We can not leave.
Please, stop.
George, the shuttle leaves.
Where are you?
Honey, listen.
I will be there.
- No.
- Just so you survive.
Please, no. You must be here.
Navetele they have no chance
that does not cover.
George, can not do this without you.
Push now.
The surrender
collision course
- What?
- Boy.
Boy?
- Tell me how?
- It's very nice.
George, you should be yourself here.
alert impact
- What name should I give?
- Name of your father.
Tiberius? Are you kidding? No.
It's too bad.
Let's put the name of your father. Jim.
Jim. Well. Jim is.
- Honey, can you hear me
- Yes.
I love you much.
I love you.
Star Trek
A new beginning
Translation and adaptation
Michael
Have you lost your mind?
Car thing is precious.
Do you think one's face away
because your mom's not on the planet?
Come back home now. Live
in my house and that's my car.
If you see a scratch on it,
you have to...
Johnny.
citizenship, do the right.
No!
Is there a problem officer sir?
citizenship, how is your name?
My name is James Tiberius Kirk.
- What is the formula volume sphere
- Four pi times the radius of three to the third.
...1.26
- What are the dimensions?
- Dimensions are...
...neexcludere and non-rivalry...
...four three-pi
fold range in the third...
...from the moral
is good, but not required.
Spock.
I assume that you have devised
November insult to today.
Affirmative.
It's a 35-time when trying
to give me an emotional reaction.
There are neither man nor vulcanian.
You Do not place in this universe.
Here. Are human eye.
Show sad, huh?
Perhaps an emotional reaction
needs physical stimuli.
Your father is a traitor.
Because married
bitch with that man.
I have called foul.
emotions are deeply rooted
in our race.
Even deeper than people.
Logic provides a serenity
rarely touched by humans.
We control feelings,
let them control us.
suggesting to be fully vulcanian,
but you married a human woman.
As ambassador on Earth,
is my duty
to observe and understand
human behavior.
marriage with your mother was... logic.
Spock.
You are perfectly able
to decide your own destiny.
The question is: what way
you to get?
Only you can decide that.
Spock. Come to see you.
- No.
- Spock.
You have nothing to be nervous.
It will be good.
I'm not angry, mother.
And the "good" is ambiguous.
I find unacceptable.
- Can I ask a personal question?
- Anything you want.
complete discipline
vulcanianã Kolinahr
and to remove all emotions?
I hope I did not think that you judge.
Spock.
No matter what you choose to be,
you always have a mother proud.
You have competed expectations
your instructors.
Your file is impeccable final.
With one exception.
I see that you applied
Fleet and Starfleet.
It was logical to have more options.
Logic, but not necessary. You accepted
Vulcanianã Academy of Sciences.
It's remarkable, Spock,
you made so many
despite your disadvantage.
Stand up.
Mr. Minister, you can clarify
what disadvantage you meant?
Your mother human.
Gentlemen minºtri Council,
must answer.
No vulcanian refused na
admission to the Academy.
What are half-human,
your reputation remains intact.
Spock, you are committed
vulcanianã respect tradition.
Why do you come today
Council before?
To give ongoing need
to get emotional mutiny?
The only emotion I want
gratitude is so transmitted.
Thank you, gentlemen, ministers,
for your attention.
Life long and prosperous.
- Hi.
Hello, I would like some tea klabnian,
three Budweiser,
Two cocktails cardassiene and...
- Try Slusho. Good.
- A Slusho. Thank you.
So many drinks for a woman.
- And a swig of Jack Daniels without ice.
- Two. I paid for it.
I am paying for myself.
Thanks, but no.
You want to know my name
before you reject me?
I'm no good.
You did okay without him. I'm Jim Kirk.
If you tell me the name,
you up my part.
- E Uhura.
- Uhura? No more days.
Just the name I thought.
- Uhura and how?
- Just Uhura.
- You name
- Uhura's name.
When you have no name?
So you cadet. What study?
Xenolingvistica.
Do not know what is that.
The study of alien languages.
Morphology, phonology, syntax.
Are you good at languages.
I'm impressed.
For a moment I thought
you are an oaf sluggish
that sex
only with farm animals.
Not only.
locals that bothers you, right?
Over extent.
But I can make one side.
Can you cope?
It's an invitation?
- Be careful what you mean.
- Calm down, sweetie. Just kidding.
Listen, peasants.
Maybe you can not count
but we are four
and you just one.
Then bring some May
to be an equal fight.
Stop it, guys.
Stop.
That is enough.
You guys get it.
Leave out all.
- Now.
- Yes, sir.
- What the hell?
- I just had a drink.
- You okay, son?
- Can you whistling loudly.
I came to believe
where bartender told me who you are.
- And who is Captain Pike
- Son of your father.
May I get one?
USS Kelvin was
my dissertation topic.
I admire your father because it was believed
in landlocked.
- And the lesson learned.
- Depends how you look victory.
- You know, right?
- Thanks.
And he was sitting in the fire
to dash blindly.
In my opinion, Fleet Starfleet
lost this quality.
Why are you talking to me?
Because I read the file
while saliva on the floor.
You have excellent results in tests
aptitude. So what's the problem?
You like to be the only
criminal genius of the Midwest?
Maybe I like it.
Your father dies and thank you
Living with a below normal.
But you feel that you are supposed
to something better, especially.
- Înroleazã back to parc.
- Let me enlist?
Do not rule comes in recruitment?
If you are even half
as your father, Jim,
Fleet would need you.
Can you reach the officer four years
and have their own ship in eight years.
You know what's Federation
It is very important.
It's a humanitarian armada
for keeping the peace...
I have done?
I have done.
Riverside sites. Shuttle
by new recruits leave tomorrow at 8.00.
Your father was the captain
the boat for 12 minutes.
He saved 800 lives,
including you and your mother.
I dare you to be better than him.
Nice engine.
It's yours.
Four years? I get it in three.
At ease, gentlemen.
No I noted surname.
- You need a doctor.
- I said.
I need a doctor.
I'm a doctor.
- Place your place in your
- I had a place in the bathroom without windows.
I'm suffering from aviafobie.
Fear of dying in a plane.
Sir, that take place not
sure I sit down.
- Okay.
- Thanks.
This is Captain Pike.
I got permission off.
I might throw up on you.
- Navetele these are safe.
- Do not tickle me, boy.
If you have a crack in the fuselage,
give us blood boil in 13 seconds.
A sudden rash sun
will come in prãjeascã chairs.
And if you pricopseºti
andorian with herpes,
to see how to be a calm
when to have your eyes bleed.
The mean disease threats
wrapped in gloom and silence.
I hate to give you news of me,
but the fleet does in space.
No place to go. Former wife
the entire planet to get a divorce.
I have left
ciolanele than.
- Jim Kirk.
- McCoy. Leonard McCoy.
Three years later.
Captain Nero.
You are called on deck, sir.
Ayel says the time has come.
I arrived at the coordinates calculated.
There's nothing here. What order?
We wait.
I expect that we left
the home to be destroyed.
As I wait for 25 years.
- And after you kill him?
- Let's kill him?
No to kill him.
I put it to look.
Capture ship.
Welcome back, Spock.
- Why are you so happy?
- I do not know what you mean.
- I guess not.
- Hello, ladies.
- I give the test again.
- Kidding.
Tomorrow morning.
And I want to participate too.
I have better things to do than to see
how do you embarrass a third time.
I am a doctor, Jim. I'm busy.
Bones, do not disturb
nobody passes the test?
Jim, it's Kobayashi Maru.
Nobody passes the test.
And no one give the
the second time darmi third.
We have to study.
studying my ass.
Jim, I think I love you.
- What strange.
- Light.
- You said it was weird?
- Yes, but...
Do not you love me?
- Oh, no. My.
- I thought you said it away.
Obviously, there's Quick, get under the bed.
- Under the bed?
- Down with you. Do not see you here.
- Why not?
- I promised not get guys.
- How did you guys...
- Jos.
- Hi.
- Hi. What are you doing?
Okay. What is strange.
I was in a laboratory sensor
the long range.
Yes. I hold that all night.
monitor systems
and we received an SOS transmission.
- Really?
- Yes.
Near a prison planet
Klingon.
- No.
- Yes.
A Klingon armada
was destroyed. 47 ships.
So you go back
in the lab tonight?
- Gail, who is it?
- Who is?
The under the bed
the mouth breathing.
- I hear the breathing
- Tu.
- I have a days tomorrow.
- A shipwreck.
- Gail, see you.
- Out.
- If you take the test, my first name mean?
- No. I would take him.
It seems interesting
you received a transmission.
I receive an SOS message
from USS Kobayashi Maru.
The ship has no power
and is immobilized.
Fleet Starfleet has ordered us to save.
Fleet Starfleet has ordered us
to save, Captain.
Two ships broke klingoniene
in the neutral zone and we were in sight.
- Nothing.
- Nothing?
Yeah, no worries.
- He said not to worry about?
- Will take seriously simulation?
Three other ships klingoniene
decamufleazã and we shall take in the viewfinder.
- No it is not a problem, right?
- Shooting, Captain.
Let infirmary
be ready to receive
All staff
the damaged vessel.
And how to save when we are
klingonieni surrounded by, captain?
Let infirmary.
- collected hits. Shields at 60%.
- I understand.
I should retort?
- No.
- Of course not.
What? What happens?
Aim torpedoes. Get ready
to launch to klingonieni.
- Yes, sir.
- Jim, have raised shields.
Really?
- No shields.
- Fire in all enemy ships.
A torpedo for each.
Do not be wasted ammunition.
I took all the ships in sight.
I opened fire.
All ships have been
destroyed, Captain.
Start saving survivors.
So I managed to remove
all enemy ships.
We have no one injured on board
survivors and rescue
the Kobayashi Maru is in progress.
What has gone kid
that of your test?
I do not know.
I have convened this meeting to
solve an unpleasant matter.
James T. Kirk, out in front.
Cadet Kirk, the Council had been
made aware evidence
that you violated the ethical code of conduct
under regulation 17.43
Code of Fleet Starfleet.
want to say something
before we start?
Yes. I have the right
to know my acuzatorul.
Come forward, please.
He's the commander Spock, one
of the best of our graduates.
A scheduled exam
Kobayashi Maru during the past four years.
Commander.
Cadet Kirk, you somehow managed to install
and execute a subrutinã
code programming
changing test conditions.
- Why fight?
- In academic language, you cheater.
Let me ask a question
although I think everyone knows the answer.
It is very unfair, no?
You can not scheduled to be passed.
Your arguments do not include the
possibility of a situation without exit.
I think in situations without output.
So you not only violated the rules,
but you never understood the lesson.
Enlighten me.
Cadet Kirk, you should know best
that a captain can not outwit death.
- Bestsellers
- Due father.
Lt. George Kirk took command ship
before being killed in combat, right?
- You hate that I passed the test.
- I didn't understand the purpose test.
- You light me once.
- The goal is to know fear.
Fear of death in the safe.
Up fear
and you keep control
on you and crew.
It's a necessary quality
all masters of the fleet.
Excuse me, sir.
I received an SOS signal
from Vulcan.
How are the bulk of the fleet
in the Laurentian,
ordering all fall
to submit immediately to hangar 1.
Free.
- Who was that bastard moke
- I do not know.
But I like it.
Bracer, USS Farragut.
McCoy, USS Enterprise.
McGrath, USS Walcott.
Spader, USS Hood.
Welcome to Fleet Starfleet.
Good luck.
I cried name.
Commander, I've cried name.
Kirk, James T.
Kirk, you are suspended
the academy. Stay on the ground
...Academy leadership to
give a verdict.
Jim, I give you a favorable verdict.
Most likely.
You go, Jim.
Yes. Go. Take care.
- Excuse me.
- Yes. Sorry.
Shit.
Come with me.
Uhura, USS Farragut.
Chomsky, USS Antares.
Go to your items.
Success.
- Bones, where we going?
- I see.
- Commander, can we talk?
- Yes, It.
- I've been chief schoolgirl
- Yes.
And you've demonstrated many times
an amazing auditory sensitivity
and I quote, "an unsurpassed ability
to identify abnormalities sonic
in transmission tests
subspaþiale?
Yes, repeatedly.
And although you know you want
to serve on the USS Enterprise,
Farragut are apportioned?
It was an attempt to avoid
suspicions of favoritism.
Do not. Are apportioned on the Enterprise.
- Yes. So it seems.
- Thanks.
- What are you doing?
- You do a service.
I could not let you so
unhappy there. Sit.
Let me make a vaccine
against viral infections
from puricii melvarieni.
- What?
- As you dare symptoms.
- What are you talking about?
- No longer see the left eye.
Yes, already no longer see.
You gonna go head pain
and to sweat a lot.
- You call this service?
- Yes. I remain indebted.
Kirk, James T. Not allowed
to serve on the Enterprise.
The code says that medical treatment
and transport a patient
is decided by his doctor.
I am the doctor
and take him on board by Mr Kirk.
Or you want to explain
Captain Pike
Why Enterprise flew in a crisis
without one of its medical officers?
- Continue.
I might throw up on you.
Jim, look.
- Jim, look.
- What?
You have to change.
I do not feel well. I'm sweating.
Damn, damn that moke.
- Mr Spock.
- Captain.
- the engine room is ready for launch.
- Thanks.
Ladies and gentlemen,
first trip of the new ships amiral
fast deserves more
than we can afford today.
Botezarea they will reward us
return to.
Continue.
All the bridges, this is Captain Pike.
Ready to go.
Pilot, propulsoarele.
The facilities were docului
withdrawn all, Captain.
I started propulsoarele.
Docul We separate the space.
Fleet out of docul space captain.
All ships are ready to warp.
- Set course for Vulcan.
- Yes, Captain.
Exchange introduced.
Maximum speed. Let him beat.
- Lt, where is the pilot McKenna
- E lung sick, sir.
I was able to undergo post.
- I'm Hikaru Sulu.
- Are you a pilot, right?
Indeed, sir.
I do not know what does not work.
Forgot hand brake?
Do not.
I realize it. Just...
You have disabled amortizorul
external inertial?
- Ready to warp, sir.
- Let's beat.
- Where are we?
- In the infirmary.
- He.
- It hurts a little suffering.
What are you doing?
- itching are normal?
- Symptoms will not last long.
- I give you a sedative easy.
- Better not meet you.
Stop grumble.
How you...
Unbelievable.
The motors are full,
Captain.
The guy from Russia. What you said
you name? Chekov? Chirpov?
- Sublt. Chekov, Pavel Andreev, sir.
- Okay.
Chekov, Pavel Andreev,
send us e crew mission.
Yes, sir.
authorization code for sublt
95 Wictor Wictor 2.
Authorization unrecognized.
authorization code for sublt
95 Victor Victor 2.
access permitted.
Be careful, please.
At 22.00, telemetry devices
have detected an anomaly in the neutral zone.
It seemed to be
an electrical storm in space.
Soon after, he received Fleet
SOS signal from Vulcan
that the planet is record
seismic activity.
Our mission is to evaluate the
situation on Vulcan
and to help exhaust
if needed.
We arrive at Vulcan over three minutes.
Thank you for your attention.
Electrical Storm.
Jim, you were awake. How do you feel?
- God.
- What?
- What the hell is this?
- A response to the vaccine.
Nurse Chapel, give me 20 cc
of cortisone.
Yes, sir.
It seemed to be
an electrical storm in space.
We have to stop the ship.
Jim. No kidding. No need
to accelerate your heart rhythm.
Captain, show it on It. Uhura.
I have never seen reaction
so severe in medical school.
- flying into a trap.
- Do not move, Jim.
Stop.
- Uhura.
- Kirk. What are you doing?
What about the message said planet
Klingon prison?
- What happened to your hands?
- Who gets attacked klingonieni?
- They romulani
- What ship?
- What I mouth
- I was numb tongue.
- numb Language
- Got a cure.
- What ship?
- Romulanã.
- Romulanã
- Yes.
- Yes what?
Nero Prod seven ships
federal way to us.
- Jim
- What?
- Jim, come back.
- Captain.
Captain Pike, the ship must stop.
Kirk, how the hell
did you get on board Enterprise?
Captain, this man has
a severe reaction to a vaccine.
delirious.
The Vulcan is not a disaster
Natural. It attacked the romulani.
Romulani? Cadet Kirk, you were
the attention of quite a day.
McCoy, take him back to the infirmary.
Talk later.
- Yes, Captain.
- Sir, this anomaly...
Mr. Kirk may not have
to be on this ship...
- I understand. I wear a grudge.
- Under the regulations...
I would like to do it again.
- As you remove the cadet...
- trying.
Cadet that tries
to save the deck.
suggesting to stop on the way
during a rescue mission?
There's rescue mission.
Listen to me. It's an attack.
Based on the information?
The same anomaly today,
electrical storm from space,
and came on the day of my birth.
Even before a ship
romulanã attack USS Kelvin.
You know that, sir.
I have read the dissertation.
ship, arms
incredibly advanced
never been seen since.
Kelvin was attacked
Klingon border area.
Last night, at 23.00,
was an attack.
47 ships klingoniene
were nothing romulani.
It was reported that romulanii
were in one massive ship.
And you know where
the attack on klingonienilor?
Sir, I intercepted
and translated the message.
- Kirk's report is correct.
- Going into a trap, sir.
Romulanii we expected. I'm sure.
The explanation is logical fall.
And It. Uhura's expert xenolingvisticã.
Conclusions are reliable.
Scan the vulcanian.
Search romulanã the transmission.
Sir, I do not know if we can distinguish
romulana of vulcanianã.
How about you? Talk romulanã, cadet...
Uhura. All
three dialects, sir.
- Uhura. It replaced the lieutenant.
- Yes, sir.
Hannity, calling USS Truman.
All other vessels have come
from warp to Vulcan
but I lost contact with them.
Sir, receive transmissions
romulane or any kind.
Because are attacked.
Up shields. Red Alert.
Vulcan to come
over five seconds.
4... 3... 2...
- avoidance maneuvers.
- Right, sir.
- Damages to larboard.
- Deflectoarele resist.
Stay on Job.
Technician Olson, report.
Revers up.
Return of 90 degrees to starboard.
Take us under them, Sulu.
- Sir, another ship Federal.
- Destroy it and this one.
launched torpedoes.
Captain, armeazã torpedoes.
auxiliary energy deviate from nacelle
larboard in front shields.
- Sulu, report.
- Shields at 32%.
They have strong arms, sir.
Stop resist another shot.
- Call Fleet Command.
- Captain.
The ship dropped romulanã
a pulse of energy
volcano in the atmosphere.
The signal of our ability blocks
teleportare and communication.
All the energy in front shields.
Ready to respond with all guns.
Weapons prepared.
Wait.
- Increase the body image.
- Yes, sir.
Captain, we call.
Hello.
I am the captain Christopher Pike.
Who is speaking?
Hello, Christopher. I am Nero.
You have declared war Federation.
Take Yourself
and I will convene a conference with leaders
romulanii in a neutral place.
Do not speak on behalf of Empire.
Act separately.
As you vulcanian officer.
Right, Spock?
Excuse me, but I do not think
I did know.
Do not.
Not yet.
Spock, I want to show you something.
Captain Pike, your system
teleportare for not working.
See what I did with the rest of
your armada. You have a choice.
Will you come on a shuttle Narada
negotiations.
That's it.
- You know you'll kill.
- Survival is unlikely.
Captain, we will not
nothing to do with diplomacy.
It's a mistake to go on the boat.
- I agree. Rethink your strategy.
- I understand.
I need officers with training
the grapple.
I am training, sir.
Come with me.
And you, Kirk. You still
not supposed to be here.
- Chekov, just shipping.
- Yes, Captain.
Prepare red material.
Yes, sir.
No carrier, we can
Teleport on the ship.
We can not help Vulcan,
we can not perform the task.
Mr. Kirk, Mr. Sulu and technician Olson
will jump shuttle.
You land on your
they descended into the atmosphere
and we deregleazã equipment,
you disable,
and then you ship the Teleport.
Mr. Spock, I let you
to order Enterprise.
Once back in service
communication systems and teleportare,
contact Fleet
and report what is happening here.
And if everything fails, withdraw your
and then the junction with Fleet
Laurentian system.
Kirk, I promote
the rank of First Officer.
- How?
- Captain.
Sorry. There are
farsele with normal people.
Not a farce, Spock.
And I am no longer captain, but you.
Let's go.
Sir, what happens to you
after you disable the probe?
Obviously, you need to save me.
Take care with the ship, Spock.
E shiny new.
- Dr. pure, report.
- Are McCoy.
Doctor was puri deck 6.
It's dead.
When I assumed the powers of
as chief medical officer.
Yeah, what news.
shuttle 89, of permission
off.
- You explosives, right?
- Yes.
Can not wait
to thrash some romulani.
- Yes.
- Oh, yes.
What training did you battle?
Fencing.
Prepare to jump.
shuttle commander, out
of the radius USS Enterprise.
Gentlemen, we are approaching the zone of salt.
You have a chance
to land on the platform.
It could be defended,
so you jump in the last minute.
3... 2... 1.
Enterprise will not be able
Teleport if you disable the probe.
Good luck.
Team Intervention
enter the atmosphere, sir.
20.000 feet.
Is platform
the 5800 meters.
Kirk to Enterprise.
Target is 5,000 feet.
4.600 meter platform.
4.100 feet.
4.000 feet.
3.000 feet.
2.000 feet.
Open parachute.
- 1,000 meters.
- Open parachute, Olson.
Not yet.
- 800 meters.
- Open parachute.
- Olson, open parachute.
- 100 meters.
Olson.
Olson died, sir.
Kirk landed, sir.
Give me your hand.
Olson had explosives.
I know.
- What do we do?
- Take it.
jitter of the signal disappeared.
We teleportare capacity.
transporter
works again.
Chekov, check the gravity sensors.
I want to know what planet do.
Yes, Commander. Sorry, Captain.
Sonda was sabotaged, sir,
but I have reached the planet.
Launch red material.
Kirk to Enterprise. Launched a
object in the hole drilled through the earth.
- I read, Enterprise
- Yes, sir.
Captain, sensors gravity
have jumped in the graph.
If I calculated correctly,
creating a singularity...
...that will consume the planet.
Creates a black hole
in the volcano?
Yes, sir.
How long has the planet?
Minute, sir.
Command vulcanian alerts
to order the evacuation of the planet.
On all the channels and frequencies.
Stay on standard orbit.
Yes, sir.
You go where?
To evacuate the High Council Vulcanian.
They protect cultural history.
- My parents are among them.
- I can Teleport?
It is impossible. I'm in Room Katra.
I gotta go get him.
- Chekov, you command.
- Yes.
Kirk to Enterprise.
Teleport us from here.
Wait. We fixãm signal.
- Withdraw the probe. Let's go.
- Yes, sir.
Pick one.
I can not fix them. Do not move.
Sulu.
Hold on.
Gotcha.
Open my parachute.
Kirk to Enterprise.
Fall without parachute.
- Teleport us.
- Trying, but can not drop the signal.
We move too fast.
I can do this.
- Hold the post.
- Yes, sir.
black hole expands. If you go
immediately, we will not be able to get away.
Move. Can I do this.
Teleport us.
- Enterprise, where are you?
- Wait.
Now! Now!
Wait. Compensation
gravitational pull.
You got it.
- Thank you.
- Sure.
Free platform.
Teleport me to the surface.
What area?
Te Teleport down?
Are you mental?
- Spock, do not do that.
- Enables.
- Spock.
- Urgent need to leave the planet.
Mama now.
Spock to Enterprise.
Teleport us.
fix signal.
Do not move. Stay there.
Teleportare in 5... 4... 3... 2...
- Mom!
- I lose.
I lost it.
Official master provisional
date stellar 2258.42.
I received news
the master Pike.
I consider therefore hostage
killer of war named Nero.
Nero, which he destroyed the planet mother
and the six billion inhabitants of them.
Although the essence of culture survives
the elders are now on the ship
I estimate that I have escaped
more than 10,000.
I am part of a
endangered species.
Sorry.
Tell me what you need.
Tell me.
I need all...
...to continue to do his job.
I think you got more questions
for me.
I have one for you.
I need frequencies subspaþiale
Federal border protection.
Especially in the area of the Earth.
Christopher, answer my question.
No, you answer to genocide
committed against a peaceful people.
I p®evented the genocide.
In time to come,
it is a mining vessel.
I chose a life of honest work.
Let me have a wife pregnant.
I was left on the planet
and I was doing the job
ta Federation and he did nothing.
I left to burn people
planet when its broken in two.
Spock And we helped. He betrayed.
Are you confused and poorly informed.
Romulus was destroyed.
I still exist. Blame Federation
what not happened yet.
I happened.
I saw with my eyes.
Do not tell me that never happened.
And when I lost her,
I swore revenge.
And for 25 years, I planned
vendetta against the Federation.
I forgot how to go
a normal life.
But I forgot the pain.
The pain that you feel now
all survivors volcano.
My goal, Christopher,
is not only to avoid
home loved destruction
but to create a Romulus
issued by the Federation.
But then you will be saved.
That's why you destroy
all federal remaining planets.
Starting with yours.
When we talk to you.
You give me frequencies systems
Defense Earth.
Limacºi Centauri.
Trunk is attached to the brain.
Secret toxin a
will force you to answer.
The frequencies, please.
Christopher Pike
captain of USS Enterprise...
How you want.
You have confirmed that Nero
is heading for Earth?
their trajectory shows
other destination, Captain.
Thank you, It.
Earth could be next stop,
but must assume
that all planets
Federation are targeted.
Get up on the chair.
If the Federation is the target,
us what we have destroyed?
Why waste ammo
There was a threat.
No e. He said that he wanted to show me
thing: the destruction of my planet.
And how did that?
How did they put romulanii
hands on such weapons?
technical knowledge necessary to
create artificially in a black hole
suggests an answer.
A technology may also
be used theoretically
to create a tunnel
the space-time.
What the hell? I am a doctor, not physicist.
suggesting that came
from the future somehow?
If you eliminate the impossible, what
remains, however improbable,
the truth.
What poetic.
Why would an angry romulan
future with captain Pike?
E master. Know details
about defensive systems.
We need to get of the ship,
so incapacitãm
and make it up on the Pike.
We are the technological inferiority.
A rescue attempt is preposterous.
Nero's ship should be
out of the warp so that we get.
To ask the technicians to work
at warp speed boost.
The crew working on repairing
radiation leaks
on lower decks.
There must be a way.
You must join to equal Fleet
sorþii next conflict.
I will be no further conflict.
When we are together
will be too late.
You said it was the future and knows
what happens.
It's logical to be unpredictable.
You assume that Nero knows
how events will take place.
Instead, the presence of Nero
changed our history
since the attack on USS Kelvin,
events culminating in today's
creating a new chain of events
can not be anticipated by anyone.
A parallel reality.
Right.
Whatever has been our lives
if it was not disturb
space-time continuum,
Our destinies
have changed.
Mr. Sulu, to enter the course
Laurentian. Warp 3.
Spock, do not do that.
Go back to the fleet
is a big waste of time...
These are orders
Captain Pike when he left.
We ordered more
go back to rescue him.
- Spock, you are the master now.
- I know the responsibilities.
With every second wasted, Nero
approaching its target.
Right. Therefore, please admit
that I own...
No to let give bir fugiþii with
instead of hunting him on Nero.
Security, escorting him out.
- No.
- Jim!
To disappear from the ship.
Computer, where are they?
On Delta Vega, the planet
Class M. uncertain.
There is an outpost of Fleet
13 km north-west.
- Stay in capsule...
- kidding.
stellar Date: 2258.42.
...4 times... never mind.
Captain Spock provisional
abandoned me on Delta Vega.
I consider this a breach of protocol
security 49.09,
on treatment
prisoners on board.
James T. Kirk.
- What?
- How did you find?
How do you know my name?
I am and always will be your friend.
Listen, you know.
I am Spock.
Rubbish.
I am delighted to see you, buddy.
Especially after the events
today.
I am grateful
that helped me today,
but if you Spock,
you know that we are not friends.
I hate. Have you abandoned
here for sedition.
- uprising
- Yes.
So are you captain?
Do not. You are the captain.
Pike was taken hostage.
For Nero?
What do you know about him?
It's a very disturbed romulan.
Please. Allow me.
It will be easier.
- What are you doing?
- We will merge minds.
More than 129 years, a star will explode
and threaten to destroy the galaxy.
Is that where I come from, Jim.
The future.
Steaua became supernova.
destroy everything in your way.
I promised romulanilor
co to save the planet.
I have fitted the fastest ship.
Using material red after
to create a black hole
that would absorb
star hit.
I was on the road when
a catastrophe occurred.
Supernova has destroyed Romulus.
There was time.
I had to extract the material red
and so throw the supernova.
When to start on the road
return, I was intercepted.
She said Nero,
last of the Romulan Empire.
In an attempt to escape, both
I was captured by the black hole.
Nero passed first
and arrived first.
For the next 25 years,
he expected arrival.
But while Nero
years have passed...
...have passed to me
just seconds.
We went through a black hole.
And I expect Nero.
I quarrel with me
loss of his world.
I caught a ship
and he spared my life.
From a single reason:
to know the pain.
Ma Teleport here
to private revenge.
Just as he has not been able
save planet
no I do not I could it
save mine.
Billions of lives lost
because of me, Jim.
Because I failed.
Forgive me. Transfer emotional
e effect of contopirii minds.
- So you nervous.
- Yes.
Getting your time
changed our lives.
Jim! Let's go.
Not far from here,
is an outpost of the Fleet.
Wait.
where you live...
...I met my father?
Yes.
I often say that he has inspired
to enlist in the parc.
He lived to be proud that you
captain on the Enterprise.
Captain?
A ship that should
come back as soon as possible.
- Speed constant.
- Course 151, vector 3.
- The Laurentian.
- Thank you, gentlemen.
- Did you call?
- Yes, Doctor.
I know that James Kirk is your friend.
I imagine that has been
difficult to get support.
I thank?
- I just recognize the difficulties.
- Permission to speak freely.
- Please.
- Really?
Okay. Have you lost your mind vulcaniene?
It's the logical choice to remove him Kirk
Probably. But it is correct?
We have a proverb. If you want
to participate in a race in Kentucky,
do you let the stallion barn.
curious metaphor, Doc.
Stallion must tamable
before-and fructify potential.
You could even pretend you
that was a tough decision.
I intend to make every effort
to restore contact with Fleet.
But if I can cheer
bocind crew on hallways,
I will be happy
medical recommendations.
Excuse me.
green monkey blood.
What?
You know how unacceptable
's situation?
- Fascinating.
- What?
I am sure that you work,
but he could not have come sooner?
I'm here for six months, living in cans
and the promise of good meals.
And I know exactly how things stand.
There are still punished for
what was clearly an accident.
- You Montgomery Scott.
- You know him?
Yes, I am.
You've come to the right place.
Only if no other officer's Fleet
as toiling and hungry here.
- I.
- Shut up.
You do not do anything. Eat only
one grain and you sick.
I real food.
But now you are here
so where is it?
Are you that Scott who developed
teleportãrii transwarp theory.
For this is about.
How do I get here?
I had a little dispute
with my instructor
in matters of physical relativist
how to link to subspaþialã trip.
He thinks that range transport
is a kind of grapefruit.
The limit to 160 km.
I said that not only can Teleport
a grapefruit from one planet to another
in the same system, which
what is pretty easy,
but the forms of life.
I tested on copoiul
Admiral Archer.
I know the dog. What happened?
I will tell you when reappears.
I do not know. I feel somewhat guilty.
If I say that theory
transwarp is correct?
That is possible to Teleport
on a ship traveling at warp?
If there would have been discovered,
I have heard of it.
The reason that I have
heard of it, Mr Scott,
is that I have discovered it yet.
- Are you in the future?
- Yes. It's Me, no.
Great. Have sandwiches there?
It's a little old.
But to handle.
I've changed it a bit.
Everything is ready.
So went Enterprise
for the first time in space?
It is a well endowed lady.
I would like to put a hand on nacelele
general. Forgive technical language.
Even if I believe what I say
what we do, where you live
what do not believe everything remains the problem
teleportãrii the Enterprise
when traveling at speeds supraluminice,
without a platform upon arrival.
Get out. No room for climbing.
The concept of teleportare transwarp
's like trying to hit
a bullet with another smaller
when you are blindfolded
and ride a horse.
What's this?
The equation for ta
teleportare transwarp.
Let's see.
I imagine. I went in thinking
that is the mobile space.
Come with us, right?
No, Jim. This is not my destiny.
Destiny...
Spock no other I believe.
But you can explain them.
He must not know
of my existence. Promise me.
I can not say that you follow your
orders. Why not? What happens?
Jim, you should not break
this rule.
To block Nero, you alone
must take command of the ship.
How? Over your dead body?
Preferably not.
But there are rules Fleet 619.
Under 619, if an officer commanding
's emotional compromise of mission
quit must command.
So everything we do
is to compromise your emotional?
Jim, I lost planet.
I'm already emotionally compromised.
Pregnancy's push to get
to show this.
Okay. If you go, come on.
Have you how to live with me. Go.
Let's go back in time and change
history means to cheat.
I learned that
from a old friend.
Life long and prosperous.
Mr Scott?
Mr. Scott, can you hear me?
Wait a minute.
Do not.
valve opening
Start valve opening.
Are you okay?
My head is spinning and wet,
but the rest are okay.
Captain Spock, detect access
Third to the tank water.
Displays on display.
Security, isolate the engine room.
We intruders in Section 3.
Set phasers on paralysis.
Wait.
Come with me...
...avarice.
Who are you?
- I am with him.
- It's me.
Getting to warp speed.
How you Teleport on the ship?
You are genius. Find yourself.
As a provisional captain
the ship, I order you to answer me.
And I do not respond
provisional captain.
You are not upset or mad
by my lack of cooperation, right?
- You are the membuat Fleet
- Yes. I need a towel.
The death Court martial
I order to explain
how did you ship the Teleport
while we go to warp.
I respond.
You answer me.
- I prefer to remain neutral.
- What's with you, Spock?
Planeta he was destroyed, my mother,
and killed are not upset at all.
If you assume that these experiences
I affect
the ability to order
ship you wrong.
But you say that fear
is required to order.
I have seen the ship?
You saw what he did?
- Of course yes.
- So you afraid, right?
Do not you let me hold sermons
about emotions.
- Then do not stop me?
- Get away from me.
How is it you feel anger?
Or despair?
Or the need to retaliate by whatever
means the death of your mother.
- Get away from me.
- I feel nothing!
Probably does not mean
anything to you.
Have you ever loved her.
Spock.
Doctor, you are apt
to serve.
order release based on the fact
that I was emotionally compromised.
Evaluate the time and date in the log ship.
I like the ship.
It was exciting.
Congratulations, Jim. Now we have
no captain nor first officer
to replace him.
I have.
- What?
- Pike called him first officer.
- No kidding.
- Thank you for support.
I hope you know what you do, captain.
I hope so too.
Warning, the Enterprise crew.
Here James Kirk.
Mr. Spock gave up the post and called me
me master provisional.
I know you expect
to join the fleet.
But I will start tracking
enemy ship for Earth.
All departments and positions
battle to be ready in 10 minutes.
And you perish in November, or her.
Kirk finished.
Say what troubling you, Spock.
It would be unwise.
What you need
not ever cautious.
I am as confused as in childhood.
You should always be a child of two worlds.
I am happy for that.
And for you.
I feel anger at
who killed my mother.
An anger that no one can wield.
My thoughts, as she said...
...is not to try.
I once asked you
why I married your mother.
I got married because I loved her.
Either way, you must get
the ship undetectable to Nero.
You will not have barged in there
with gun in hand, Jim.
The calculations do not support your idea.
- Captain Kirk.
- Yes, Chekov. What?
Analyzing the Naradei
from Vulcan
I have determined that Nero
will pass Saturn.
As you said we should hide
by Nero, otherwise we will destroy them.
If Mr. Scott succeeds
warp speed to 4,
and if you leave the warp behind one
of the months of Saturn, such as Titan,
magnetic distortion
planet's rings
we will be invisible
sezorii for his Nero.
From there, while probe
not on,
We can Teleport to the enemy ship.
Yes. It might work.
- Wait. Kid, how old are you?
- 17, sir.
Has 17 years.
Doctor.
Mr. Chekov is right.
I confirm data telemetry.
If Mr. Sulu brings us
in a favorable position,
I will ship to the Teleport Nero,
I will steal the black hole,
and, if possible, would bring
back Captain Pike.
Do not let you do that, Mr Spock.
Romulanii and vulcanienii
have a common ancestry.
cultural similarities will help me
to access the computer
and locate the device.
My mother was human. Earth e
only homeland I have left.
Friday with you.
I would cite the regulation,
but I know that to ignore it.
See? Already begin to know.
Prepare probe.
Stop full 3... 2... 1.
Go for 5 seconds
at quarter speed boost.
Then go on propulsion.
At my signal.
Yes.
Run.
Transport Hall. We are
in position above the Titanic.
Really? Bravo, Mr Sulu.
- Situation, Scotty
- Unbelievable. The ship is heading.
Anything that would happen, Mr Sulu,
if you consider that the tactical advantage
to pull the ship that even
if you are on board. It's an order.
Yes, sir.
We will contact you when we are Enterprise
Teleport ready to be back.
Good luck.
- I will be back.
- So be it.
- O you monitor frequency.
- Thank you, Nyota.
- First it's Nyota
- No comment.
Okay. If the enemy ship
was built logically
a Teleport to the cargo hold,
where no one.
Enable.
Captain, Fleet officers
we approached the ship.
- One of them is vulcanian.
- No.
Ayel.
- Learn what you can.
- Are you sure?
Yes. I cover you.
You know where the hole negeri?
And Captain Pike.
Move.
They enabled the probe.
Communications and teleportarea
does not work.
Sulu, tell me that i have located.
Otherwise I will not be able
Teleport back.
Kirk and Spock are on their own.
provide complications. Ship model
is more advanced than I expected.
Voice print analysis
facial recognition enabled.
Welcome, Ambassador Spock.
Weird.
Computer, which is the date of manufacture?
Date stellar 2387. Ordered
Vulcanianã Academy of Sciences.
It seems that you hid
important information.
Can you fly the ship, right?
I feel that I have piloted it.
- Good luck.
- Jim.
Statistically speaking, chances of success
is less than 4.3%.
I work.
If I back
tell It. Uhura...
Spock, one to go.
Fascinating.
startup sequence initiated.
Nero, ordered disable
probe that does not...
You know the face
in the history of Earth.
James T. Kirk was considered
grand man.
He became captain of the USS Enterprise.
But that was another life.
A life that I missed,
as I did with your father.
Captain Nero. Ship vulcanianã
was stolen. We destroyed the probe.
Spock!
- Open a channel.
- Yes, sir.
Spock, I had to kill you
when I had the chance.
confiscate illegally acquired this ship
and I order you to surrender
unconditional ship.
Shoot him.
- Sir, if red light matter...
- Spock I want the dead.
- go to warp.
- Watch it.
Yes, sir.
Your species is lower
than I expected.
You can not talk to.
What?
I got my gun.
What to do?
Ambassador Spock,
are on collision course.
Fire all weapons.
launched missiles. If the ship is hit,
red material will ignite.
I understand.
Captain, detect another ship.
- What are you doing here?
- Follow orders.
Enterprise, now!
Good timing, Scotty.
I never Teleport three people
from two different places
on one platform.
- Jim.
- Bones.
It was remarkable.
Captain, the enemy lost ship
supply. They dropped the shields.
- Call them now.
- Yes.
Here Captain James T. Kirk
the USS Enterprise.
The ship's compromised.
It's too close to singularity
to survive without
which we are willing to offer him.
Captain, what are you doing?
compassion may be the only way
to win peace with Romulus.
It's logical, Spock.
I co you like.
Not this time.
I prefer to see die Romulus
a thousand times,
I prefer to die in agony
Just accept your help.
You got it.
Aim phasers.
Pull with all weapons.
Yes, sir.
- Sulu, go home.
- Yes, sir.
- Why are not the warp
- You are, sir.
Kirk to the engine room.
Take us out of here, Scotty.
To be sure, Captain.
Captain, we are caught
the gravity field.
Maximum speed warp. Now.
You give everything you are, Captain.
Well, everything is not enough.
What other ideas do you have?
If you evacuate warp core
and it detonated,
is likely to burst free,
but not promising anything.
Do it!
- Clear the area.
- Yes, sir.
Pa?
You are our father.
They left few vulcanieni.
We afford to ignore.
Then why did you sent the ship Kirk,
when you could explain to me the truth?
Because had needed each other.
Do not want to miss a chance
to achieve great things together
a friendship that will define
both
the ways in which
still no figures.
How did you sure
to keep secret?
He inferred that appear paradoxes
catastrophic for the universe
if it will violate the promise.
You lied.
- I insinuative.
- A bet?
An act of faith.
Which I hope to repeat it
in your future in Starfleet Fleet.
We are faced with extinction.
It's logical to resign from the fleet
and to help rebuild
our race.
But can you be in two places at once.
I suggest you stay in the fleet.
I found a planet suitable for
vulcaniene foundation of a colony.
Spock, make your own good
in this case.
Let logic and do what you feel is good.
The traditional greeting
I feel selfish,
I just wish you luck.
Meeting his name
Captain James Tiberius Kirk.
Your courage and inspiring devotion
from comrades
falls in the
best traditions of Fleet.
And I do honor you,
and your crew Federation.
I am honored to have your agreement
this medal.
Of Fleet Order 28455,
you to present the Admiral Pike
the USS Enterprise
to replace him.
take command, sir.
Sermons order.
- Thank you, sir.
- Congratulations, captain.
Your father would be proud of you.
Propulsoarele rest.
Propulsoarele maneuvering engines
impulse are available, sir.
The arms
and shields are pending.
Command docului
report that is done, Captain.
Bones.
Put your seat belt.
Scotty, how we doin '?
dilitiu room is full,
Captain.
Get out.
Mr. Sulu, get ready
to enable propulsoarele.
Requesting permission
to get on board, Captain.
Permission granted.
How you have not yet chosen a first officer,
I wish to offer applications.
If you want, can present
letters of recommendation.
I would be honored, Commander.
Propulsoarele maneuvering, Mr Sulu.
- Propulsoarele prepared.
- Get us out of here.
Yes, Captain.
The last frontier.
These are travel
spacecraft Enterprise.
its ongoing mission:
to explore strange new worlds...
...to discover new forms of life
and new civilizations...
...enter hardily
na where nobody ever came.