WHAT?
WHO IS IT?
YOU'RE KILLING MY FUCKING HIGH,
MAN.
WOW.
DO I KNOW YOU?
OOH. SHIT.
YOU SURE I DON'T KNOW YOU?
I'M GONNA FUCK YOU, FUCK YOU
TILL YOU DIE.
REALLY?
OOH. OHH.
WOW.
OH, SHIT!
OHH! OHH! OHH!
OHH! UGH! UGH!
UGH! AAH!
AAH!
AAH! AAAAAAH!
NO! AAH!
AAH! AAH!
SPREAD YOUR LEGS, YOU GODDAMN
BRAT!
AAH! AAH!
AAH!
FUCK, YEAH!
OOH!
AAH!
YEAH, WANT TO FUCK?
OH! OH! OH, GOD!
AAH!
AHH!
MEG!
MEG! M-MEG! W-WAIT. WAIT.
HEY.
YOU'RE NOT GONNA BELIEVE
THIS.
WHAT?
HAVE YOU SEEN JUSTIN?
HE WON'T ANSWER HIS PHONE, AND I
CAN'T FIND HIM ANYWHERE.
I'M NOT GONNA BELIEVE THAT
YOU CAN'T FIND JUSTIN?
NO, NO.
WELL, I'M SUPPOSED TO MEET
HIM AT RAY'S ROOM.
WE'RE STUDYING FOR OTTIE'S QUIZ
TONIGHT.
N-N-NO, NO.
Y-Y-Y-Y-YOU CAN'T GO IN THE --
IN THE DORM RIGHT NOW.
OKAY, WHAT ARE YOU ON?
A L-- A LITTLE SPEED.
NO, I'M NOT.
I GUESS YOU HAVEN'T HEARD, THEN.
HEARD WHAT?
WHERE THE HELL'S JUSTIN?
"SPAZ," I JUST TOLD YOU.
WE'RE MEETING AT RAY'S ROOM, AND
WE'RE STUDYING.
JOE, WHAT'S WRONG?
I-I-I-I-I DON'T KNOW HOW TO SAY
IT.
SH-SH-SHIT.
JOE, JUST SPIT IT OUT.
WHAT? SPIT IT OUT.
SHIT.
I GUESS
YOU GUYS HEARD.
NO.
RAY'S DEAD.
H-H-H-HE WAS RAPED AND MURDERED,
MEG.
IT'S TRUE. IT'S RIGHT HERE.
I TOLD HER FIRST.
WHAT?
OH, DUDE, MATURE.
OH, MY GOD.
GROW UP, SICKO.
YOU GUYS, STOP.
WAIT. WHEN DID THIS HAPPEN?
WE JUST SAW HIM ON SATURDAY.
I DON'T KNOW -- LAST NIGHT
SOMETIME.
SHOTS FIRED...
UGH.
I-I CAN'T BELIEVE --
IS THIS A JOKE?
DOC-- DR. OTTIE, UH...
NOW, WE'VE HAD AN UNFORTUNATE
OCCURRENCE.
OH, MY GOD.
IT'S OKAY.
YEAH, I SURE DIDN'T KNOW RAY
WAS GAY.
ANNIE, HE'S NOT.
UNTIL FURTHER NOTICE,
EVERYONE, UH, PLEASE COMPLY WITH
THE POLICE IN THIS INVE-- IS
THIS AN INVESTIGATION?
WITH THIS INVESTIGATION.
UH, IF YOUR ROOM -- YOUR DORM
ROOM IS IN "C," UH, SEE
MR. WILCOX IN ADMISSIONS.
CLASSES WILL RESUME A-AS --
AS -- AS SCHEDULED.
They're canceled this
afternoon.
CLASSES A-ARE CANCELLED --
I'M SORRY -- UNTIL FURTHER
NOTICE.
UH, GRIEF COUNSELORS -- WE HAVE
MANY OF THEM.
THEY WILL BE MADE AVAILABLE --
We have two.
WE HAVE TWO. UH.
AAH!
DID YOU HEAR ABOUT RAY?
...PULL IT TOGETHER NOW...
OBVIOUSLY.
...AND, UH...
WH-WHAT DO YOU WANT?
I DON'T KNOW, SPAZ.
I HEARD YOU WERE THE LAST PERSON
TO BE SEEN WITH RAY LAST NIGHT.
S-S-S-S-SO?
WH-WHAT IF I WAS?
WELL, IT LOOKS LIKE SOMEONE
GOT TIRED OF THE SCHOOL DRUG
DEALER FUCKING THEM AND DECIDED
TO DO SOMETHING ABOUT IT.
YOU INTO MEN, SPAZ?
Y-Y-Y-YOU GOT SOME BALLS.
AS LONG AS YOU DON'T TOUCH
THEM, HOMO.
I OUGHT TO --
YOU OUGHT TO WHAT?
YOU WERE THERE LAST NIGHT?
N-N-N-NO.
Y-YEAH, I-I-I JUST -- I JUST
W-W-WENT BY TO GET SOME PRE--
PRELUDIN.
I-IT TURNED OUT --
IS THAT WHAT YOU'RE GONNA TELL
THE COPS?
"O-O-O-OFFICER, I JUST
ST-T-TOPPED BY TO SC-C-C-ORE
SOME P-P-P-B-B-S-S-B-B--
YOU'RE A FUCKING ASSHOLE.
Y-YOU KNOW THAT?
WELL, I KNOW NOW.
DUDE, HAVE SOME RESPECT.
YOU GUYS DON'T SEE THAT RAY
WAS INTO SOME SERIOUSLY SICK
SHIT?
WHERE'S JUSTIN?
RAY?
JUSTIN.
HUH.
RAY?
JUSTIN.
DUDE, THIS IS FAR OUT, MAN.
WHAT HAPPENED?
WHO DID THIS TO YOU?
YOU!
HEY!
JOE?!
HEY, JUSTIN.
WHAT IS THIS?
WE'RE JUST SHOOTING THE SHIT,
IS ALL.
OH, YEAH, SHE LOOKS LIKE A
REAL BLABBERMOUTH, MAN.
YEAH?
YEAH.
I THINK SHE LIKES ME.
OH, THAT'S -- OH, I SEE THE
CONNECTION, MAN.
IS SHE -- ARE YOU ALIVE?!
ARE YOU OKAY?!
MAN, THAT IS NOT COOL!
WHAT?!
NO, SERIOUSLY, MAN, BECAUSE YOU
GET IN TROUBLE...
N-NO, MAN, JUST G-G-GIVE ME
ANOTHER --
NO. HEY!
WANT SOME ECSTASY?
NO!
NO?
NO, I DON'T WANT ANY ECSTASY!
I-I GOT SOME EXTRA.
DUDE, I HAD THIS DREAM, MAN,
ABOUT RAY.
YOU'RE HARSHING MY MELLOW.
I JUST WANT TO CH-- I WANT TO
TALK TO YOU ABOUT RAY, MAN,
ABOUT THIS DREAM BECAUSE, MAN,
IT'S --
NO, NO, NO.
IT'S HARD TO, YOU KNOW --
IT'S HARD FOR ME TO SAY IT HERE
WITH THE MUSIC, YOU KNOW?
AND TH-- IS SHE -- I DON'T THINK
SHE'S BREATHING, MAN!
DUDE, WAIT.
YEAH?
DUDE.
DO YOU WANT SOME ECSTASY?
NO, MAN.
NO?
I'M GONNA GO. I'M GONNA GO.
MEG WAS LOOKING FOR YOU
EARLIER.
REALLY?!
YEAH.
WHAT DID SHE SAY?
SH-SH-SH-SH-- SH-SH-SH-SH--
I DON'T KNOW, BUT YOU SHOULD --
YOU SHOULD --
YOU SHOULD TAP THAT. YEAH.
YOU SHOULD TAP THAT.
NOT COOL.
GET HER SOME WATER, MAN.
TAKE CARE OF YOURSELF, MAN.
I-I LOVE YOU.
I LOVE YOU, TOO, MAN.
I LOVE YOU, TOO.
I LOVE -- WAIT. OW! WAIT!
ALL RIGHT, I'LL -- I'LL SEE YOU
LATER, JOE.
ALL RIGHT.
JUSTIN?
ANNIE?
DUDE, WHERE HAVE YOU BEEN?
I, UH, TOOK A XANAX.
I WAS OUT OF IT LIKE ALL DAY.
MEG'S WORRIED SICK.
YOU JUST DISAPPEARED.
WITH EVERYTHING THAT'S
HAPPENING -- NOT COOL.
I SAW RAY, ANNIE.
GREAT. YEAH.
JUST BE LIKE ONE OF THOSE
ASSHOLES WHO JOKE ABOUT THAT.
NO, NO, NO, IT'S A --
I HAD A DREAM, YOU KNOW?
AND I SAW RAY AT THE -- AT THE
MORGUE --
RAY IS DEAD, JUSTIN.
I KNOW HE'S DEAD, BUT I SAW
HIM IN THE MORGUE, AND HE WAS
TALKING TO ME.
DO YOU HEAR YOURSELF TALK?
I SOUND NUTS, HUH?
NO, YOU KIND OF SOUND LIKE
SOMEBODY ON DRUGS.
WHOA, WHOA, WHOA, WHOA.
ARE YOU OKAY?
AAH!
YEAH.
I'M DIZZY.
BREATHE.
ARE YOU OKAY?
YEAH.
I CAN GET YOU SOMETHING.
OKAY, SO, I WAS ASLEEP, YOU
KNOW?
OKAY.
I PASSED OUT.
AND I HEAR RAY'S VOICE.
SO I WAKE UP, BUT I'M NOT IN MY
BED.
I'M IN THE MORGUE, AND RAY IS ON
THE SLAB WITH THE AUTOPSY SCAR,
YOU KNOW, RUNNING DOWN HIS
CHEST.
BUT HIS EYES ARE OPEN.
JUSTIN.
AND HE'S -- HE'S LIKE LIVID.
COME ON. LET'S GO INSIDE.
HE WAS TRYING TO SAY
SOMETHING TO ME.
SO I-I WALK UP CLOSER TO HIM,
RIGHT?
AND I GET REAL CLOSE TO HIM.
AND I ASK HIM, "WHO DID THIS TO
YOU?"
AND HE GRABS MY ARM AND SHOUTS,
"YOU!"
IT'S OKAY.
WHAT IF THIS HAS SOMETHING TO
DO WITH THE DRUG?
HAVE YOU TAKEN MORE?
NO.
A VIAL DISAPPEARED THAT NIGHT.
I THINK RAY MIGHT HAVE --
YOU THINK RAY WHAT?
HE TOOK IT AND SOMEONE KILLED
HIM FOR IT?
I DON'T KNOW.
YOU TOOK A XANAX EARLIER,
RIGHT?
MM-HMM.
A FULL BAR?
THAT'S YOUR ANSWER, MAN.
IT'S JUST A CRAZY FUCKING DREAM.
DON'T -- DON'T KILL YOURSELF
OVER THIS.
IT'S NOT YOUR FAULT.
YEAH.
OKAY?
ALL RIGHT.
YOU WANT TO GET A DRINK?
OKAY.
YEAH.
I'LL TAKE THAT.
HEY, WAS MEG REALLY ASKING
ABOUT ME EARLIER?
YEAH, YOU SHOULD TAP THAT.
WHAT?
YOU HEARD ME.
I COULDN'T HEAR.
OH, COME ON. YOU HEARD ME.
'CAUSE IT'S A THICK ACCENT.
OH.
TELL ME. YEAH, I -- WHAT?
YOU HEARD ME.
UM, YOU SHOULD CALL HER AND
TELL HER THAT I'M HERE.
SURE, I CAN DO THAT.
BET YOU WEREN'T EXPECTING TO SEE
ME TONIGHT, WERE YOU, FRIEND?
WHAT YOU GOT, TOM?
DON'T -- DON'T DO THAT --
COME IN HERE AND STARTLE
SOMEBODY.
FOR A MAN YOUR SIZE, YOU'RE
SURPRISINGLY LIGHT ON YOUR FEET.
GOT TO BE IN THIS LINE OF
WORK.
YEAH.
I SUPPOSE.
WHAT YOU GOT ON TWINKLE TOES
HERE?
WELL, WE'RE STILL WAITING FOR
THE LAB RESULTS.
BUT YOU CAN SEE FROM THE, UH --
THE TRACKS ON HIS ARM HE'S BEEN
RIDING THE RAILS FOR AWHILE.
THAT WAS FOUND ON THE
NIGHTSTAND NEXT TO THE BODY.
"TALDON."
TALDON -- I NEVER HEARD OF IT.
I'LL GET IT TO THE LAB.
THEY'LL GET A POSITIVE ON IT.
RAPE POSTMORTEM?
NO, HE WAS ALIVE FOR IT.
HIS TONGUE'S BEEN BITTEN OUT OF
HIS MOUTH.
SOME TEETH.
YEAH.
JAGGED BITE, POSSIBLY SOME SORT
OF SPECIAL DENTURE.
MM.
THAT WHAT KILLED HIM?
NO.
HIS COLON WAS PERFORATED BY A
PHALLUS NEARLY 4 INCHES IN
DIAMETER, 15 INCHES IN LENGTH.
WHOA, WE'RE LOOKING FOR A
BLACK MAN.
DETECTIVE FULLER, I'D
APPRECIATE IT IF YOU'D REFRAIN
FROM COMMENTS LIKE THAT IN MY
PRESENCE.
IT'S -- IT'S UNPROFESSIONAL.
LIGHTEN UP.
FUCKIN' "A."
15 INCHES.
HEY, MAYBE IT WAS AN ARM?
AN ARM?
NO.
IT WAS NOT AN ARM.
OKAY, OKAY.
JIZZ?
SEMEN.
AND NOT JUST SEMEN, EITHER,
FULLER.
IT'S UNLIKE ANY SEMEN I'VE EVER
SEEN BEFORE.
WE FOUND LARGE QUANTITIES OF IT
AROUND THE ANUS AND THE -- THE
MOUTH.
IT'S NOT SURPRISING DURING A SEX
CRIME.
WE'RE STILL WAITING FOR THE
RESULTS FROM THE LAB ON THAT, AS
WELL, BUT...
HELP ME OUT WITH THE BODY HERE,
FULLER.
I WANT TO SHOW YOU SOMETHING.
THERE'S ALSO...
I WANT TO SHOW YOU THIS.
YEAH.
...A THIN LAYER ALL OVER THE
BACK.
THE TRACE AMOUNTS WERE FOUND IN
LACERATIONS HERE AND HERE.
SEE THAT?
I DO NOW.
MM-HMM.
MEANING?
I-I DON'T KNOW WHAT IT IS.
I'VE NEVER SEEN ANYTHING LIKE
IT.
CAN YOU GET DNA FROM IT?
CAN SOMEONE --
JUST HOLD THAT THOUGHT, FULLER.
COLLINS.
DISGUSTING.
YEAH.
TELL THEM I'LL HAVE THE BODY
READY IN ONE HOUR.
I SAID ONE HOUR.
DNA?
PROBABLY. PROBABLY.
YOU'RE ON TO SOMETHING, FULLER.
YOU KNOW, IT REMINDS ME...
...OF A VICTIM THAT I HAD WHOSE
NERVOUS SYSTEM WAS SO
OVERSTIMULATED THAT THE
FAST-TWITCH MUSCLES WERE JUST
GOING LIKE A SECOND HAND ON A
CLOCK.
SON OF A BITCH.
MRS. HARRIS?
WE'RE SO VERY SORRY.
BITCH.
THIS IS ALL YOUR FAULT.
OH, HE'D FOLLOW YOUR SMELL
AROUND LIKE A DOG.
I CAN SMELL IT FROM HERE.
HE WAS A GOOD BOY.
NO, HE WAS A GOOD BOY BEFORE HE
STARTED HANGING AROUND YOU ALL.
OR YOU, WITH YOUR DRUGS.
YOUR WILD, PERVERTED SEX.
YOU BURN IN HELL.
COME ON.
HOW DARE YOU?
COME ON, MOM.
YOU AND YOUR CRAZY, PIOUS
FAMILY RIPPED EVERYTHING RAY
TRIED TO ACCOMPLISH INTO PIECES.
YOU NEVER SUPPORTED HIM, AND
THAT'S WHY HE STARTED TAKING
DRUGS, MRS. HARRIS.
IT WAS NOT BECAUSE OF ME, AND --
AND IT WAS NOT BECAUSE OF THEM.
IT WAS BECAUSE OF YOU.
WE RAISED OUR SON WITH THE
WORD OF GOD.
HOW DARE YOU?!
MY SON'S FUNERAL!
MRS. HARRIS!
MRS. HARRIS, PLEASE.
TAKE A STEP BACK.
LET GO OF ME!
CALM DOWN. RELAX.
"CALM DOWN"?
MY ONLY SON IS DEAD.
DEAD!
AND THESE DEVIANTS CAUSED IT!
WE'LL DO ALL WE CAN.
HE'S GONE.
COME ON, MAMA.
LET'S GET OUT OF HERE.
AND IT'S BECAUSE OF THESE
BASTARDS.
YOU ARREST THEM ALL!
IT'S ALL THEIR FAULT.
JUST LET IT BE. COME ON.
NO, NO. THEY KILLED RAY.
COME ON.
THEY KILLED MY BABY BOY.
YOU STILL HAVE ME.
I CAN'T BELIEVE SHE CALLED US
DEVIANTS.
SHUT UP.
I WANT ALL YOU DOWNTOWN.
WH-WH-WHY?
WH-WH-WHY DO YOU WANT TO
KNOW?
OW! OW!
WHAT YOU GOT HERE, SON?
POLICE BRUTALITY.
WHAT YOU GOT THERE?
IT'S MY COUPONS FOR POPEYE'S
FRIED CHICKEN.
I KEEP --
OxyContin.
OH, YEAH, IT'S OxyContin,
RIGHT.
I HAVE A PRESCRIPTION FOR THAT.
I BET YOU DO.
I DO.
I SWEARETH.
HMM.
IT'S OUR PRESCRIPTION NOW.
IS THIS THE MAN DANCE?
CONSTABLE, PROTECT --
OW! OW! OW!
AAH!
TELL ME A JOKE.
OKAY.
TELL ME THE ONE ABOUT THE
LITTLE PUNK WHO DISRESPECTS A
MOTHER AT HER SON'S FUNERAL!
TELL IT TO ME.
OKAY.
THERE'S A SON...
OH!
...GOING TO A FUNERAL...
GET HIM DOWNTOWN BEFORE I
KILL HIM.
OH, DETECTIVE YOUNG.
SINGLE FILE.
I WANT IT NOW.
I WANT...NOW.
DO YOU HEAR ME?
THEY FORCE US TO COME DOWN
HERE AND MAKE US WAIT -- WASTE
OF MY FUCKING TIME.
I-I DON'T -- I DON'T LIKE
THIS.
OH, BUT I LOVE IT, SPAZ.
YOU KNOW WHAT, SPAZ?
YOU'RE A FUCKING LOSER, JUST A
LITTLE BIT.
STOP CALLING ME THAT!
HEY, HEY, HEY!
YOU BETTER NOT SAY SHIT ABOUT
SATURDAY NIGHT'S PARTY.
DON'T MAKE A SCENE HERE.
I JUST DON'T WANT TO GET
KICKED OUT OF MED SCHOOL 'CAUSE
HE'S ABOUT TO RAT ON ALL OF US.
HE'S ABOUT TO CRY.
IT'S NOT WORTH IT, JOE.
SIT DOWN. GOOD GIRL.
THAT'S WHAT YOU NEED TO BE
DOING.
GOOD GIRL.
YOU JUST DON'T WORRY ABOUT
ME, P-PRICK.
SEE WHAT I'M TALKING ABOUT?
MM.
SO, HOW YOU DOING?
I HAVEN'T SEEN YOU AROUND.
WHAT'S UP WITH YOU AND
DR. WELLINGTON?
HUH?
WHAT'S IT'S LIKE TOUCHING HIS
POTATO FOR THOSE GOOD GRADES?
FUCK YOU.
I CAN'T BELIEVE WE WERE
ACTUALLY F-F-F-FRIENDS WITH YOU.
YEAH.
YOU WERE NEVER ACTUALLY
F-F-F-FRIENDS WITH ME, SPAZ.
WE JUST GOT HIGH TOGETHER, DID
DRUGS TOGETHER.
THERE'S A DIFFERENCE.
IN FACT, IS MEG EVEN YOUR
FRIEND?
SIT.
HEY, HEY, I'M GONNA TAKE DOWN
YOUR NUMBER, AND THAT'S --
CAN'T DO THAT, MAN.
JUSTIN.
HEY.
HOW ARE YOU?
WHERE WERE YOU?
I'VE JUST BEEN OUT OF IT.
I'VE BEEN REALLY SICK -- REALLY.
ARE YOU OKAY?
I DON'T KNOW.
EVERYTHING WAS FINE, AND RAY --
HIS MOM JUST --
OH, YOU MISSED IT, JUSTIN.
YOU WERE TOO BUSY AT
CLUB COCONUT TO SEE RAY'S MOM
RIP HER TO SHREDS.
OH, COME ON.
DO YOU WANT TO TALK ABOUT IT?
NO.
WANT TO TALK?
YOU WERE TOO BUSY SLEEPING IN
TO JOIN US AT THE FUNERAL.
THAT MUST HAVE BEEN A BIG PAIN
IN THE ASS FOR HIM.
WHAT, YOU THINK I'M WRONG,
ANNIE?
SH-SH-SH-SHE COULDN'T.
THEY CAN'T REALLY THINK O-O-ONE
OF US KILLED RAY.
WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
RAY'S MOM AND TH-TH-THE --
MAYBE ONE OF US DID KILL RAY,
SPAZ, HUH?
AND I THINK THE GUY WHO HOLDS
THE KEY IS THE GUY WHO SAW RAY
ALIVE LAST.
THAT WOULD BE YOU.
SO, THE OTHER NIGHT, SPAZ, WHEN
YOU GUYS WERE PLAYING
TOUCHY-FEELY OR WHATEVER YOU
GUYS DO TOGETHER IN RAY'S DORM
ROOM, DID YOU S--
NO, I TOLD YOU ALREADY!
I SAW NOTHING.
YEAH?
I JUST WENT BY TO PICK UP MY
TEXTBOOKS, A-AND -- AND I LEFT,
IS ALL.
IT'S PRETTY CLEAR TO ME THAT
THIS GUY, THE GUY WITH THE
HANDICAP, THE STUTTERING -- LOOK
AT HIM.
HE'S ABOUT TO CRY -- IS THE
GUILTY PARTY.
LOOK, THE ONLY REASON HE'S AT
THIS SCHOOL IS BECAUSE OF SOME
FUCKED-UP GRANT THAT --
FUCK YOU!
HEY! HEY! HEY! HEY! HEY!
STOP.
JESUS!
THEY PROBABLY HAVE THIS PLACE
BUGGED.
SIT DOWN.
WE JUST BURIED OUR FRIEND
LESS THAN AN HOUR AGO, AND
YOU'RE SITTING HERE SQUABBLING
LIKE LITTLE CHILDREN.
MEG.
WHAT?
WHAT PISSES YOU OFF MORE --
THE FACT THAT YOUR
EX-BOYFRIEND'S DEAD OR THAT HE
WAS A FAG?
UH-OH.
STAND UP.
GOOD JOB.
HIPPIE MUSCLES.
ALL RIGHT, LISTEN, I KNOW YOU'RE
PISSED OFF, DUDE, BUT JUST...
YOU WANT TO TAKE A WALK?
I JUST CAN'T STAND FOR THAT
SHIT, MAN, YOU KNOW?
LISTEN, MAN, I DON'T FEEL
GOOD.
SAY YOU'RE SORRY, OKAY?
I'M SORRY.
JUSTIN.
WHOA.
I KNOW EVERYONE'S PISSED OFF
'CAUSE I'D BE A LITTLE UPSET,
TOO, RIGHT NOW IF MY
EX-BOYFRIEND WAS, YOU KNOW,
PLAYING BOTH SIDES AND HAD THE
DIRTY BUTT.
OKAY, SEBASTIAN, IT'S ENOUGH.
DISEASE-CONTROL SHIT.
WHAT YOU DID AND WITH HIM, AND
NOW YOU, BRO -- YOU GUYS ARE
FUCKED UP.
MEGAN?
YEAH.
COME WITH ME.
UH, JUST MEGAN.
I'LL GET TO YOU LATER.
I'LL BE RIGHT HERE.
WOULD YOU LIKE SOME COFFEE?
NO.
THANK YOU.
FOR THE RECORD, STATE YOUR
FULL NAME.
MEGAN LAURA WAGNER.
Louder.
WHY DID MRS. HARRIS ATTACK
YOU?
I DON'T KNOW WHY.
WERE YOU AND RAY AN ITEM?
NOT REALLY.
HE HAD A LOT OF PROBLEMS.
SUCH AS?
HIS MOTHER.
WHEN WAS THE LAST TIME YOU SAW
RAY HARRIS?
THE LAST TIME I SAW HIM WAS
SATURDAY NIGHT.
THAT'S WHEN WE ALL GOT TOGETHER.
PARTY?
NO, NOT REALLY.
ANY DRUGS AT THIS PARTY?
I DON'T USE DRUGS, AND IT
WASN'T A PARTY.
WE ALL JUST GOT TOGETHER TO...
TO WHAT?
JUST TO HANG OUT, I GUESS.
IT'S WHAT WE DO.
WE ALL JUST GET TOGETHER, AND WE
RAG ON EACH OTHER.
"RAG"?
YOU KNOW, LIKE, MAKE FUN OF
OUR DYSFUNCTIONAL LIVES.
WAS RAY HOMOSEXUAL?
NO.
DID YOU EVER SEX WITH HIM?
HOW DO YOU KNOW, THEN?
I JUST KNOW.
SO, THEN, WHY DIDN'T YOU AND
RAY HAVE SEX?
BECAUSE I JUST WASN'T
ATTRACTED TO HIM IN THAT WAY.
ARE YOU ON MEDICATION?
ZOLOFT.
THOUGHT YOU DIDN'T USE DRUGS.
ILLEGAL DRUGS.
I DON'T USE ILLEGAL DRUGS.
AND WHAT DRUG ARE YOU ON?
IT'S AN ANTIDEPRESSANT.
ARE YOU DEPRESSED?
ISN'T EVERYONE?
YOU GUYS ARE ALL ABOUT
INTERROGATING IN HERE?
MIND GIVING US A DNA SAMPLE?
NO.
YOU'RE DOING THIS?
YEAH.
YOU'RE QUALIFIED TO DO THIS?
IT'S STERILE?
OPEN.
AH.
FOR THE RECORD, STATE YOUR
FULL NAME.
MY INDIAN NAME?
MY NATIVE AMERICAN NAME?
MY HINDU NAME?
JESUS CHRIST, YOU EAT TOO
MANY LEAD PAINT CHIPS?
YOUR FUCKING BIRTH NAME.
YOU WANT MY ANGLO NAME, MAN,
THE NAME THE MAN GAVE ME?
YOUR FULL NAME.
JUSTIN WILLIAM CARTER II.
SECOND?
YEAH, THE SECOND.
WRITE IT DOWN IN YOUR LITTLE
BOOK -- THE SECOND.
WHEN WAS THE LAST TIME YOU
SAW RAY?
I SAW RAY THE OTHER NIGHT.
AT YOUR HOUSE?
NO.
WE WERE AT THE HOSPITAL.
WHY THE HOSPITAL?
WE WERE RESEARCHING, DOING
SOME RESEARCH.
ALL RIGHT.
OH.
Shit.
WHAT THE FUCK?
HEY, KIDS.
MEET JOHN AND WILMA HOPPER.
THEY WERE RESPONSIBLE FOR THAT
DEBACLE BACK IN '73.
YOU REMEMBER THAT.
NO, YOU DON'T. WE WEREN'T ALIVE.
BUT IT HAPPENED.
WHAT IS ALL OF THAT?
THIS?
THIS IS ONE OF THE
THE MOST BIZARRE EPISODES IN THE
HISTORY OF AMERICAN CRIME,
STUDIED RIGHT HERE, ALL THIS
DOCUMENTATION.
IT'S TRIPPY, MAN.
THEY DON'T SEEM SO
W-W-W-WEIRD.
JOE, THEY RAPED THEIR VICTIMS
TO DEATH -- RAPED THEIR VICTIMS
TO DEATH.
THEY WERE COMPLETE FUCKING
SOCIOPATHS.
KINKY, EH?
YEAH, YOU'RE -- YOU'RE INTO
THIS STUFF.
HEY, MAN, WHAT'S THIS?
THAT IS TALDON.
AND IT'S UNBELIEVABLE.
WAIT. HOLD ON.
YOU TOOK THIS ALREADY?
I TOOK IT, AND IT TOOK ME,
AND WE'RE IN A SYMBIOTIC
RELATIONSHIP.
HMM.
YEAH.
WELL, THAT'S GREAT.
TOLSTOY USED IT IN HIS, UH --
IN HIS THERAPY WITH THEM, AND
IT'S UNBELIEVABLE.
ARE YOU CRAZY, JUSTIN?
GIVE ME YOUR PULSE.
WHAT? THAT'S -- WHAT?
NO, I'M FINE.
I'M KEEPING THE BEAT.
HAVE YOU EVER DONE PCP?
NO.
DMT?
THAT'S LIKE -- I'M TELLING
YOU 'CAUSE IT'S -- IT'S --
IT'S -- IT'S LIKE -- IT'S LIKE
OTHERWORLDLY.
ARE YOU CRAZY?
IT'S EXTRATERRESTRIAL.
LET ME SEE YOUR BELT.
YEAH, I'M AHEAD OF YOU ON
THAT.
WHAT IS IT, ON TALDON?
WAIT. HOLD ON.
RAY, DON'T TAKE IT.
YOU DON'T EVEN KNOW WHAT'S IN
IT.
3 cc IS THE DOSE.
DID YOU READ ALL THIS?
YEAH.
I'M ON THE LAST TAPE RIGHT NOW.
ARE THERE ANY MORE NEEDLES?
YES, I DO HAVE PLENTY OF
NEEDLES.
THERE YOU GO.
YOU GONNA CATCH SOMETHING?
DON'T CATCH ANYTHING.
DON'T GIVE ANYTHING.
FUCKING -- DO YOU WANT TO
JOIN MY BAND?
WANT TO JOIN MY BAND?
NO, I DON'T.
YOU WANT TO JOIN MY BAND?
GOOD?
WOW.
G-G--
ARE YOU
GUYS -- DID YOU GUYS HAVE A
CHANCE?
WAIT. LET ME GET IT.
WHAT DO YOU PLAY?
I PLAY THE "HURRY UP."
COME ON, JOE.
WE NEED A THEREMIN PLAYER.
A WHAT?
A THEREMIN PLAY-- YOU KNOW
ABOUT THAT?
THE FUCKING ROOM'S SPINNING.
I CAN PLAY THE BONGO.
YEAH, WE'RE CALLED
THE INVISIBLE WIZARDS.
I THINK IT'S UNBELIEVABLE,
YOU GUYS.
YOU COOL? YOU COOL?
DO YOU WANT ME TO KISS IT AND
MAKE IT BETTER?
ARE YOU HIP TO THIS?
CAN YOU GET HIP TO THIS?
IN, IN, OUT, OUT, OUT, RIGHT?
YEAH.
RIGHT?
YEAH, YEAH.
YOU WANT TO DO ME?
YEAH, IN YOUR DREAMS.
HELP ME OUT HERE.
OKAY, HERE WE GO. HERE WE GO.
ALL RIGHT, GO.
NO, NO, NO, DON'T SHAKE MY
ARM.
YOU ALL RIGHT WITH THAT?
ALL RIGHT.
WHERE IS MY BEST FRIEND?
PLAY THIS SHIT.
ALL RIGHT, YOU WANT TO HEAR
THIS?
ALL RIGHT, UH...
ALL RIGHT, ALL RIGHT, EVERYBODY
GATHER AROUND.
SESSION 26. MARCH 23, 1973.
DR. WILLIAM TOLSTOY.
THIS WILL BE A JOINT SESSION, A
JOINT HYPNOSIS SESSION, WITH
PATIENTS WILMA AND JOHN HOPPER.
JOHN, CAN YOU HEAR ME?
YES.
WILMA, CAN YOU HEAR ME?
VERY GOOD. EXCELLENT.
BOTH PATIENTS ARE UNDER
HYPNOSIS.
NOW WE CAN BEGIN.
JOHN, AS PROMISED, WILMA IS HERE
WITH US.
WOULD YOU LIKE TO SPEAK TO HER?
WILMA?
SHE CAN'T HEAR YOU, JOHN,
UNLESS I ALLOW IT.
AND I WILL ONLY ALLOW IT IF I
SPEAK TO HIM.
IS HE THERE?
HE IS ALWAYS THERE, DOC.
MAY I SPEAK TO HIM?
HELLO.
WHO AM I SPEAKING TO?
YOU KNOW WHO, DOC.
JOHN IS UNDER HYPNOSIS, AND ALL
IN HIS MIND ARE, ALSO.
THEREFORE, YOU WILL ANSWER MY
QUESTIONS.
WHAT IS YOUR NAME?
I WOULD LOVE TO FUCK YOU...
...FUCK YOU TILL YOU DIE.
ARE YOU THE ONE THAT KILLS
THROUGH JOHN?
WE ALL KILL...AND FUCK...
TOGETHER.
WE'RE ALL ONE BIG HAPPY
FAMILY, DOC.
WILMA?
SUCK MY FUCKING CUNT, YOU
FAGGOT!
LISTEN TO ME, WILMA.
I WILL COUNT BACK FROM 10.
10, 9...
YOU PLAY WITH THE DEVIL, DOC...
AND THE DEVIL'S GONNA PLAY WITH
YOU.
...7, 6...
FOLLOW US INTO HALLOWED
PHALLUS.
DOCTOR?
25cc OF THORAZINE!
JUST DO IT!
AAH!
JOYCE!
WE WANT TO FUCK FOREVER!
FOREVER!
WILMA! NO!
HERE THE FUCK I AM!
OH, STOP IT, MAN.
WHAT?
NO, MAN, STOP IT, PLEASE.
STOP IT. JESUS CHRIST.
YOU ALL RIGHT?
UGH.
JOE, ARE YOU OKAY?
JOE, YOU ALL RIGHT?
YOU ALL RIGHT?
AAH!
SHIT!
OH, MY GOD! OH, MY GOD!
OH! OH, MY GOD.
DUDE, AH!
YOU SHOULD HAVE SEEN YOUR FACE.
OH, MY GOD.
OH!
OKAY, YOU GUYS, I FOUND SIDE
EFFECTS ON TALDON.
WAIT. WAIT. WAIT. WAIT.
SHUT UP. SHUT UP.
SIDE EFFECTS INCLUDE --
SHUT UP.
HEY, HEY. WHAT?
OKAY, SIDE EFFECTS INCLUDE
ANXIETY, AGITATION, HEADACHES,
NOSEBLEED, EXCESSIVE SWEATING,
DRY MOUTH, DIZZINESS, INCREASED
SEXUAL APPETITE...
...ANEMIA, HALLUCINATIONS,
PSYCHOSIS, STROKE, AND POSSIBLE
COMA.
OH, GREAT.
JUSTIN, HOW THE HELL --
THAT'S LIKE 1% OF 1% OF 1%.
OKAY, I THINK 1% IS ENOUGH IF
THERE'S, LIKE, THE POSSIBILITY
OF COMA.
HEY, YOU ALL RIGHT?
SHIT.
DID SOMEONE JUST KNOCK?
DUDE, WHO COULD THAT BE?
GUYS, PUT THAT SHIT AWAY.
HEY. HEY.
HEY, COLLECT THE SHIT.
...A NEEDLE.
WHO'S THERE?
HELLO?
WHAT?
NO ONE'S THERE.
IS IT COOL? IS IT COOL?
THAT WAS A CLOSE ONE, DUDE.
DUDE, WAS THAT THE FUZZ?
IS THE FUZZ COMING?
LET'S GO.
MAYBE IT WAS JOHN AND
WILMA HOPPER.
SO, THAT WAS IT, MAN.
THAT WAS ALL WE DID, YOU KNOW?
WELL, FUNNY YOUR GIRLFRIEND
DIDN'T MENTION ANY OF THIS.
MEG?
YEAH, MAN, SHE WAS JUST TRYING
TO COVER FOR ME.
SHE'S JUST BEING A STAND-UP
CHICK.
BUT I'LL TELL YOU WHAT -- YOU
GUYS CAN THROW THE BOOK AT ME
FOR THAT ONE, ALL RIGHT?
YOU CAN LOCK ME UP AND TOSS AWAY
THAT KEY.
I WILL TAKE FULL RESPONSIBILITY
FOR GETTING INTO THAT PLACE.
RESPONSIBILITY FOR GETTING
RAY HOOKED ON THAT DRUG, TALDON?
NO, NOT RESPONSIBILITY FOR
THAT BECAUSE I DON'T KNOW
ANYTHING ABOUT THAT.
WE FOUND A VIAL OF IT, NEAR
EMPTY, ON HIS NIGHTSTAND.
WELL, THEN, THAT'S HIS GIG,
MAN.
THAT WAS HIS THING.
HE MU-- HE -- HE MUST HAVE TAKEN
IT.
WHY DID YOU GO MESSING WITH
PATIENTS' RECORDS?
I DON'T KNOW, MAN.
I JUST WAS -- I WAS INTO SOME --
I WAS TRYING TO GET INTO SOME
DIFFERENT STUFF, MAN.
I WAS TRYING TO DO SOME
RESEARCH, YOU KNOW?
AND...DR. TOLSTOY WAS A
PHYSICIAN AT THE HOSPITAL YEARS
AGO.
HE HAD DONE SOME, UM, WORK ON
ALTERNATIVE THERAPIES, STUFF
THAT I'M INTO, YOU KNOW, CRYSTAL
THERAPY -- FIRST GUY IN THIS
TOWN TO DO CRYSTAL THERAPY,
FIRST GUY TO DO RADON
TREATMENTS, MAN.
HE WAS AHEAD OF HIS TIME.
HE WAS ON -- HE WAS INTO ASTRAL
PROJECTION...
YOU KNOW, ASTRAL
PROJECTION --
OKAY, GREAT.
"ASS"?
"--TRAL."
AS-TRAL PRO-JEC-TION.
IT'S OUT-OF-BODY STUFF.
YEAH, MAN, IT'S JUST -- IT'S
EXPANDING YOUR MIND, MAN.
IT'S GOING BEYOND THE PHYSICAL
DIMENSION, BEYOND SPACE, BEYOND
TIME, MAN, AND GOING TO --
YOU LOST ME.
THAT'S COOL, MAN.
IT'S NOTHING TO DO WITH ASSES,
ALL RIGHT?
I KNOW.
I HAD A BOOK OF ECKANKAR TO
IMPRESS THE GIRLS, TOO, OKAY?
YOU KNOW, WHEN I WAS 17, I
THOUGHT I WAS THE REINCARNATION
OF JAMES DEAN, BUT THEN I BECAME
FAT AND HAIRY, AND THAT PUT
THINGS IN PERSPECTIVE.
WHAT?
YEAH, I WAS SO BUMMED ABOUT RAY.
UH...
WOW, I NEED SOME WATER, MAN.
DO YOU HAVE SOME WATER HERE?
YEAH, SURE.
PLEASE.
OH, MAN.
WHAT'S THE MATTER?
I DON'T FEEL SO GOOD IS
WHAT'S THE MATTER.
TOO MUCH "ASS-TRAIL" PHYSICS
ON THE MIND?
LOOK, YOU GUYS, SERIOUSLY --
I MEAN, I'M -- I SUPPORT -- I
SUPPORT WHAT YOU GOT GOING ON
HERE.
I'M INTO DETECTION.
I'M INTO ALL THOSE THINGS, BUT I
JUST -- IS THIS GONNA BE A LOT
LONGER 'CAUSE I GOT A -- I GOT
SOMEWHERE I GOT TO GET TO, YOU
KNOW?
THERE'S A SEMINAR.
MMM.
BUT SERIOUSLY, I-I DIDN'T EVEN
KNOW WE WEREN'T SUPPOSED TO BE
IN THERE.
I-I WAS JUST GOING ALONG WITH
EVERYONE ELSE.
DID YOU AND RAY EVER DATE?
WHAT ABOUT THE DRUGS?
OH.
PLEASE DON'T TELL MY PARENTS.
I J-J-J-J-- WAS JUST
G-G-GOING ALONG WITH EV--
EVERYONE ELSE.
I J-J-J-JUST ASSUMED THAT...
...J-J-J-JUSTIN HAD PERMISSION
T-TO BE DOWN THERE.
DO THE OTHERS MAKE FUN OF
YOU?
N-N-N-N-N-NO.
DIDN'T RAY CALL YOU "SPAZ"?
I-I G-G-GUESS SO.
DIDN'T RAY ALSO CALL YOU
"SWEET CHEEKS"?
H-H-H-HELL NO!
WHO S-SAYS?
SEBASTIAN.
HE'S A -- HE'S A LIAR!
QUITE SOME TEMPER YOU HAVE
THERE, SON.
S-S-S-S-S-SORRY, S-SIR.
WHAT FIELD ARE YOU STUDYING?
I-I-I-I'M S-ST-ST-STUDYING...
P-P-P-P...
P-P-PATHOLOGY.
I-I F-FEEL M-M-M--
I-I F-FEEL M-MY B-B-BEDSIDE
M-M-MAN-- MANNER WOULD B-B-B--
THAT'S ENOUGH.
THAT'S ALL WE HAVE FOR YOU.
YOU CAN GO, SON.
R-R-R-R-REALLY?
YEAH, JUST BE AVAILABLE FOR
FURTHER QUESTIONS.
SH-SH-SH-SHOULD -- SH-SHOULD
I W-W-W-WAIT IN TH-TH-TH-THE
W-W-WAITING ROOM?
NO. NO, NO.
I DON'T USUALLY GET THESE.
WELL, YEAH.
BLOW WILL DO THAT TO YOU.
NOW...
...RECORDS ROOM, SATURDAY
NIGHT.
WASN'T THERE.
YOUR FRIENDS SAY DIFFERENT.
UH, THEY'RE NOT REALLY MY
FRIENDS, SO...
YEAH.
WELL, RAY WAS YOUR FRIEND,
RIGHT?
WHY DON'T YOU TELL ME HOW YOU
AND RAY USED TO LIKE TO FUCK
EACH OTHER?
WAS HE THE CATCHER AND YOU
THE PITCHER?
FUCK YOU TWO FAGGOTS.
AAH!
YOU GOT A BIG FUCKING MOUTH,
PUNK -- SAME MOUTH YOU'D SUCK
RAY'S COCK WITH?
I WANT MY LAWYER. I WANT --
FUCK YOU AND YOUR FUCKING
LAWYER.
I WANT MY LAWYER.
WHY DID YOU KILL HIM?!
I DIDN'T DO SHIT!
I WANT MY LAWYER!
I WANT MY FUCKING LAWYER!
WAIT.
YOU WANT TO PLAY HARDBALL,
GET YOUR DUMB ASS EXPELLED FOR
THAT PARTY YOU THREW SATURDAY
NIGHT, OR YOU WANT TO PLAY NICE
AND TELL US WHAT WE NEED TO
KNOW?
IT WAS JUSTIN'S IDEA, ALL
RIGHT?
HE THREW THE PARTY.
HE'S ALWAYS COOKING UP SOME
STUPID HIPPIE BULLSHIT.
I THOUGHT YOU WEREN'T THERE.
WHAT ABOUT JOE?
RAY AND JOE WERE REALLY GOOD
FRIENDS.
OKAY.
STAND UP AND PULL DOWN YOUR
PANTS!
WHAT?
I'M THROUGH TALKING WITH YOU.
ALL RIGHT, THIS IS
RIDICULOUS.
I'M NOT GONNA STAND UP AND PULL
MY PANTS DOWN FOR THIS --
RELAX, OKAY?
THE GUY WE'RE LOOKING FOR IS
VERY DISTINCT BELOW THE WAIST.
LOOK, I DON'T KNOW WHAT YOU
GUYS DO IN THE SQUAD CAR --
GET THE OTTIE GUY ON THE
HORN.
HE DOESN'T WANT TO PLAY NICE.
WAIT. STOP. STOP.
STOP, ALL RIGHT?
OKAY.
DEFINITELY NOT OUR MAN.
HECK, I DON'T EVEN THINK THIS
IS A MAN.
PULL IT UP, PEEWEE, AND GET
THE FUCK OUT OF HERE.
HEY, HEY, HEY, HEY.
OKAY, NOT SO FAST.
HEY, HEY, HEY.
ALL RIGHT.
HEY, NOT SO FAST.
WHAT IS THIS, LIKE A SQUARE
KNOT?
IS THIS WHAT YOU DO IN EUROPE TO
KEEP BOYS AWAY?
HEY.
HOLD ON.
LET ME LOOK AT THOSE THINGS.
HEY, HEY, HEY.
HEY.
DON'T BE A TEASE. COME ON.
I THOUGHT IT WAS KIND OF HOT
THE WAY YOU SPOKE TO THE COPS
EARLIER TODAY.
COME HERE.
DUDE, NO, NOT SO FAST.
HEY. NO, DUDE, NO!
NO MEANS NO!
STOP THINKING WITH YOUR LITTLE
DICK!
OHH!
GET THE FUCK OUT OF MY CAR.
GET THE --
ARE YOU INSANE?
JUST GET THE FUCK OUT OF MY
CAR!
GET THE FUCK OUT!
ARE YOU INSANE?
HEY, LET ME IN!
NO, YOU'VE GOT MY PHONE!
HEY, YOU'VE GOT MY PURSE!
LET ME BACK --
FUCK!
SEBASTIAN?
HELLO?
SEBASTIAN!
SEBASTIAN, THIS IS NOT FUNNY!
HELLO?
SEBASTIAN?
BREATHE!
OH.
AAH!
OH
AHH!
THEREFORE, YOU WILL DO AS I
ASK.
WHAT IS YOUR NAME?
I WOULD LOVE TO FUCK YOU...
...FUCK YOU TILL YOU DIE.
ARE YOU THE ONE THAT KILLS
THROUGH JOHN?
WE ALL KILL...AND FUCK...
TOGETHER.
ONE BIG HAPPY FAMILY, DOC.
UH-HUH.
WHO'S THERE?
I'M SO GLAD YOU CAN HEAR ME.
STEP INTO THE LIGHT.
UH, I DON'T THINK I WANT YOU
TO SEE ME.
PUT YOUR HANDS ABOVE YOUR
HEAD AND STEP INTO THE LIGHT.
LISTEN, I'M TRYING TO HELP.
I DON'T NEED YOUR HELP. MOVE.
NO, LISTEN. LISTEN.
THINK. THINK. THINK.
SHOCK TO THE SYSTEM, DOC!
OPEN YOUR FUCKING MOUTH!
AAH!
FOLLOW US
INTO HALLOWED PHALLUS.
UGH!
25cc OF THORAZINE!
JUST DO IT!
AAH!
LET'S SEE HOW DEEP I CAN GET.
TAKE IT UP TO THE HILT!
TAKE IT!
AAH!
UNH! AHH!
UGH!
WAS THAT GOOD FOR YOU?
AAH!
OH, BOY.
MMM.
THAT WAS AMAZING.
I HOPE YOU'RE NOT JUST SAYING
THAT.
MNH-MNH, NO.
OKAY.
IT WAS.
NO.
HEY.
DON'T.
ALL RIGHT.
MMM. MMM.
YOU PERJURED YOURSELF TODAY.
YEAH, WELL, FOR THE MAN
THAT'S GONNA DEFEND MY HONOR...
MMM.
...I'D DO ANYTHING.
MWAH.
MMM!
WHY DIDN'T WE DO THIS SOONER,
HMM?
'CAUSE SOMEONE WAS TOO SHY.
NO, I JUST COULDN'T BEAR THE
THOUGHT OF YOUR REJECTION.
OH.
WELL, I WAS TALKING ABOUT ME.
MWAH!
BUT, OKAY.
MMM.
ALL RIGHT, LET ME GET UP.
WHY? WHERE ARE YOU GONNA GO?
THE BATHROOM.
I'LL BE RIGHT BACK.
OKAY.
MAKE IT QUICK.
MMM.
MMM. I'LL BE RIGHT BACK.
OKAY.
MMM.
WELL, GO.
ALL RIGHT, I'LL BE RIGHT
BACK.
OKAY.
GO.
I'M GOING.
MMM.
HURRY UP.
ALL RIGHT.
JUSTIN, WAKE UP.
HUH?! WHAT?!
WHAT? WHAT? WHAT?
ARE YOU OKAY?
HUH?
NO.
YOU ALL RIGHT?
YOU OKAY?
I WAS...
WHAT?
...IN THE HOSPITAL...
IN THE RECORDS ROOM...
WITH RAY.
JUSTIN, IT'S THAT FUCKING
DRUG.
MNH.
OKAY?
YOU AND THE OTHERS HAVE TO GET
CHECKED OUT, OKAY?
PLEASE?
I DON'T KNOW.
JUSTIN.
I'M OKAY.
OKAY.
IT'S OKAY.
PATIENT...
HE SUFFERS FROM SCHIZOPHRENIA.
WHILE CONDUCTING TALDON
RESEARCH AT THE UNIVERSITY OF
MINNESOTA, I ADVANCED A THEORY
THAT A MASSIVE RELEASE OF
ENDORPHINS...
...FROM THE PINEAL GLAND PRIOR
TO DEATH...
TELL THEM, NURSE.
THERE'S A POSSIBLE LACK OF
PANIC INVOLVED IN THE CLINICAL
SETTING AND DOSAGE DIFFERENCES
BETWEEN THOSE ADMINISTERED AND
THOSE ENCOUNTERED IN ACTUAL
N.D.E. CASES.
SEVERAL SUBJECTS ALSO REPORTED
CONTACT WITH BEINGS -- HUMAN,
DEMON, ALIEN-LIKE, INSECTIZOID.
SUBJECTS ALSO REPORTED THEY
WERE TORTURED AND EVEN RAPED
BY THESE THINGS.
THE EXPERIENCE MIGHT BE HIGHLY
INFLUENCED BY THE ACTUAL USER'S
LIFE, SHOWING WHAT THE PERSON
NEEDS -- GIVEN THEIR PERSONAL
STORY OF THE MOMENT, MORE THAN
WHAT IS WANTED.
HOLD HIM DOWN, NURSE.
SECURE HIS ARMS.
BREATHE.
OH, MY GOD.
HELLO?
HELP!
HELP ME!
NO!
PLEASE!
AAH!
BREATHE.
WHAT?
HEY, SEBASTIAN.
WHO IS THIS?
IT'S ME -- RAY.
GOOD ONE, JOE.
FUCK YOU, B-BUDDY.
FUCKING D-D-D-DETECTIVE THAT --
LISTEN, SPAZ, YOU'RE MESSING
WITH THE WRONG DUDE.
..."S-S-S-SWEET CHEEKS"?
ALL RIGHT, WHATEVER, FAGGOT.
FUCK O--
WHAT THE FUCK?
OH.
HEY.
I'M SORRY ABOUT LAST NIGHT.
REALLY?
YEAH.
WELL, I THOUGHT I COULD MAKE IT
UP TO YOU.
YEAH?
DO YOU LIKE IT?
YEAH.
DO YOU WANT ME TO FUCK YOU?
YES.
ALL RIGHT, GET READY.
DO YOU LIKE MY COCK?
UH-HUH.
YEAH.
HEY, SLOW IT DOWN.
SLOW IT DOWN A LITTLE BIT.
OW!
HI, BABY.
AAH!
JOE. JOE.
WH-WH-WH-WHAT IS IT, MAN?
CALL ANNIE.
CALL ANNIE AND SEBASTIAN.
OKAY.
WH-WH-WH--
JUST CALL THEM AND SEE IF
THEY'RE OKAY.
WHY?
JUST DO IT, PLEASE.
ALL RIGHT, OKAY.
NO!
FUCK! NO!
OH, NO, NO, NO!
NO, DON'T GET IT!
OH, IT'S OKAY.
IT'S OKAY. IT'S OKAY.
JUSTIN.
IT'S ALL RIGHT.
OH, MY GOD.
OH, JUSTIN, IT WAS HORRIBLE.
YOU'RE IN THE HOSPITAL.
I KNOW. I KNOW.
YOU'RE IN THE HOSPITAL WITH A
POLICEMAN.
IT'S OKAY.
JOE...
IT'S JUST A POLICEMAN.
IT'S OKAY.
...I'M GONNA NEED YOU TO STEP
OUTSIDE.
I KNOW.
UH -- UH --
IT'S OKAY. JUST RELAX.
I-I-I'LL BE RIGHT OUTSIDE,
M-MEG.
I'M JUST GONNA TALK TO HIM
FOR A MINUTE, OKAY?
IT'S OKAY.
I'M GONNA BE RIGHT OVER HERE.
CALL THEM, OKAY?
DO YOU HAVE ANY IDEA WHY YOUR
PARTNER ATTACKED AND TRIED TO
RAPE MY FRIEND?
I'VE KNOWN
DETECTIVE FULLER FOR 10 YEARS.
HE'S THE FINEST MAN I EVER MET.
HE WAS A PSYCHOTIC PIG.
SHUT YOUR PIEHOLE!
I'M SORRY.
AAH!
AAH! AAH!
STOP!
AAH!
JUSTIN!
UGH!
JUSTIN, WAKE UP.
WAKE UP, PLEASE.
JUSTIN.
WH-WH-WHAT THE HELL ARE YOU
DOING, MAN?
DID YOU GET AHOLD OF
SEBASTIAN OR ANNIE?
N-N-N-NO ANSWER.
BUT WHY THE FUCK WERE YOU
HITTING HIM?
ANNIE AND SEBASTIAN ARE DEAD.
WE FOUND THEM AN HOUR AGO.
THEY WERE RAPED TO DEATH?
YEAH.
BREATHE.
COME ON. BREATHE. BREATHE.
BREATHE, BABY. BREATHE. BREATHE.
COME ON.
YOU CAN DO IT. COME BACK.
WHAT DID HE TAKE?
BREATHE.
AAH!
IT'S JOHN AND WILMA HOPPER.
COME BACK.
BREATHE.
THEY'RE WITH US.
THEY'RE WITH US, AND THEY'RE
FUCKING US TO DEATH.
YEAH.
YEAH. THIS CAN'T BE
THIS CAN'T BE
REAL.
ONE, TWO, THREE, BREATHE.
ONE, TWO, THREE.
DO IT. YOU CAN DO IT.
COME ON AND DO IT.
THIS CAN'T BE REAL, MAN.
THIS CAN'T BE REAL.
CLEAR!
STOP IT!
I DON'T KNOW WHAT TO DO.
UNH!
ALL RIGHT.
THAT'S ENOUGH.
D-D-D-D-DUDE, CALM DOWN, MAN.
J-JUST CALM DOWN, BUDDY.
IT'S NOT REAL, IS IT?
HELP!
GOD, HELP ME!
I DON'T KNOW WHAT TO DO!
BREATHE!
HOW MUCH DID HE TAKE?
PUT THE FUCKING GUN DOWN!
J-J-J-JUST --
COME ON! CLEAR!
TIME OF DEATH, 1:45 A.M.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT TO DO.
CLEAR!
UGH!
FUCK!
O-OH, SHIT!
D-D-DUDE, YOU FUCKING SHOT HIM,
MAN!
HE'S A FUCKING COP!
JUSTIN, STOP!
NO. N-N-N-N-NO, MAN.
IT'S OKAY, JOE.
IT'S NOT REAL.
J-J-J-J--
JUSTIN!
WHY? WHY DID YOU DO IT?
OH, BABY!
OH, GOD!
PLEASE?
BABY, WHY?
I LOVE YOU.
JUSTIN.
JUSTIN, STAY WITH ME.
PLEASE STAY WITH ME.
PLEASE, JUSTIN,
COME ON.
COME ON, BABY.
AGAIN.
BABY, WAKE UP.
WAKE UP! WAKE UP!
BREATHE. BREATHE.
UP!
THAT'S GOOD.
GIVE IT JUST ONE GOOD ONE.
ONE, TWO, THREE. AGAIN.
CLEAR.
CLEAR!
JESUS CHRIST.
COME ON, KID.
COME ON, JUSTIN.
COME ON.
PADDLES.
CLEAR!
THERE'S NOTHING.
MAN. HE'S GONE.
NO, NO, KEEP TRYING.
KEEP TRYING, PLEASE.
CALL IT...
JUSTIN, WAKE UP.
WAKE UP, JUSTIN.
...1:45.
NO.
JUSTIN, WAKE UP!
HONEY, LISTEN TO ME.
HE'S GONE.
NO.
WE DID EVERYTHING WE COULD.
NO, YOU DIDN'T!
KEEP TRYING!
HIS BRAIN HASN'T HAD OXYGEN
IN OVER 10 MINUTES.
HE'S GONE.
PLEASE.
NURSE.
PLEASE, PLEASE, GET HER IN A
ROOM.
GIVE HER SOME --
NO! LET'S KEEP TRYING!
NURSE.
PLEASE! PLEASE!
PUT HER IN THE ROOM.
NO!
GIVE HER SOME DEMEROL.
YOU HAVE TO COME WITH ME,
MA'AM.
NO.
WE NEED TO KEEP TRYING!
I'M SORRY.
NO.
LET THE DOCTOR FINISH HIS
WORK.
NO, PLEASE, NO.
I TOLD HIM NOT TO TAKE IT.
I TOLD HIM. I DID.
NO!
NO, PLEASE!
NO, STOP! LET ME GO.
NO! GOD!
KEEP TRYING, PLEASE!
GET OFF OF ME!
LET ME GO.
PLEASE!
MY GOD.
WHAT A SHAME.
JUSTIN!
WHAT THE HELL WERE YOU KIDS
INTO?
DON'T BE WORRIED
EVERYTHING WILL TURN OUT
FINE
DON'T BE WORRIED
FRIEND, JUST PUT YOUR HAND IN
MINE
DON'T BE TROUBLED
EVERYTHING WILL TURN OUT
RIGHT
DON'T BE TROUBLED
FRIEND, JUST TAKE MY HAND
TONIGHT
DON'T BE WORRIED
EVERYTHING WILL TURN OUT
FINE
DON'T BE TROUBLED
IT'LL BE OVER WHEN YOU DIE
NOW AND AGAIN, I-I TURN TO
LOOK BACK, SEARCHING THE SHADOWS
FOR EVEN A GLIMPSE OF THE BARON
AND THE GENDARMES WHO WERE
FOLLOWING ME.
NOT ONCE DID I SEE THEM.
I COULD HAVE SWORN THEY WERE NOT
THERE.
I TURNED THE CORNER.
ANNE?
YES. IT IS I, ANNE.
THAT KNIFE, SHINING IN THE
LIGHT!
IT'S COOL, MAN.
I TAKE FULL RESPONSIBILITY.
OH, WOW. WOW, NOBLE.
WOW, YOU'RE JUST A KNIGHT IN
SHINING ARMOR, AREN'T YOU?
MM-HMM.
WHERE WERE YOU WHEN RAY WAS
GETTING FUCKED IN THE ASS WITH A
SUBMARINE?