There was a time, long ago,
when evil men with greed in their hearts
would lay siege to the king that possessed
the ancient treasures of the Dark Ages.
But the king was in league
with creatures of magic,
forest spirits.
Leprechauns,
these guardians summoned from the earth
to protect the gold
from falling into the hands of evil men,
of wicked men.
The legend of their ferocities
spread through the land
and all would know not to trifle
with these creatures.
The kings reign would come to an end,
and the leprechauns would find their home
again back in Mother Natures embrace.
Except for the myth of the one,
the one that did not go back.
No, no!
Jacob!
- Where is it?
- It's gone.
You can't hide it from me, Jacob.
The rainbow always points to me treasure.
Never again, foul creature.
You're going back to hell tonight,
and the Lord will help me send you.
Poor misguided Jacob, even if you steal
for God, you still have to pay the Devil.
Damn clovers.
The Lord is at my side.
In the name of the Father, I condemn thee
to the valley in the shadow of death.
I shall not fear your evil.
Take it all, take it all!
Just don't send me back.
I am sending you back to the earth,
back into the grave whence you came.
I banish thee, spawn of Satan!
No! Help me! Please!
Help, help.
I'm sorry. Sorry.
They hiring at the salon?
Fool, it's a women's salon.
What do you think
you're gonna do up in there?
I can give massages.
I can help with those bikini waxes.
- Bikini wax?
- Yeah, you know what I'm saying.
A little Mohawk, a little triangle.
I'm the fucking bomb
with that shit, for real.
- Shut up!
- Yeah.
They got everybody's hopes up
for no reason.
Yeah, they broke as a motherfucker now.
Anyone ever figure out
what happened to the money?
No. It vanished.
I guess the project died with Father Jacob.
Damn! How come every time something
good is about to happen
somebody always gotta go and fuck it up?
She looks fine as hell.
- Girl! Hey!
- Girl what?
Come here.
Yeah, you, punk.
- What's up, Watson?
- Don't Watson me, motherfucker!
What the fuck is this shit?
Well, that was a Christmas gift
from my mom.
Shut up, punk. Turn this fool over.
All right, wait, listen. Hold on.
No. Why do you got to do this, man?
Watson! Listen... Come on, man!
What the fuck is this?
You need something, punk?
I didn't think so, motherfucker.
You better have my shit
by the end of this week.
You understand me, motherfucker?
And give me these motherfucking shoes.
End of the week, punk.
Hey, girl, what you gonna do
with all that cash?
I'm saving up for college.
I want to go to Kansas State.
What you gonna do with
your ashy ass in Kansas?
Ain't no black people in that motherfucker.
Girl!
She's going somewhere over the rainbow.
- Excuse you, grandma!
- That child is always tripping.
Can I get some service up in here?
Will you be having work done
to your extensions?
First of all, this ain't no nappy-ass weave.
Go ahead, feel it. Feel it.
Right, so like I said,
can I get some service up in here?
Hurry up!
Girl, this ain't what I wanted.
See, I knew I should've had Yolanda cut it.
Oh, no. I can just...
Let me trim a little off the edges.
I need to layer it in the back anyway.
This don't look like no Julia Roberts.
- I look like Raggedy fucking Ann. Yolanda!
- Emily, come here.
I'm sorry. She kept changing her mind.
She said she wanted long and curly.
Don't back talk, girl.
We got customers waiting,
and if you can't cut heads faster than this,
you gonna get your dumb ass replaced.
...good on this motherfucker, man.
- Wallet!
All through the 'hood, son.
- Where you off to, Jackson?
- Nowhere.
Punk ass nigger, drinking Kool-Aid.
It's Powerade, you illiterate motherfucker.
That's why you don't drop out of school
before you learn how to read.
- Motherfucker, I'll beat your...
- Cedric.
Doing good for yourself, little brother.
You only on the streets a few months
and already you're a big spender.
- Just making ends meet, man.
- Yeah.
Only problem that you're making is
you're not a part of this, motherfucker.
I don't want to fight you, Watson.
We understand each other.
My brother.
Punk ass motherfucker. What, nigger?
Yeah. Get the fuck out of here.
He shook like a motherfucker.
"Watson, I don't wanna fight with you."
Bitch-ass, nigger.
Watson, man, you had the nigger's heart
going like this, son.
You should have let me pop
that motherfucker.
- Kill that motherfucker!
- Fuck.
You all right?
Hey, you want to go out Friday?
No.
What, you got plans?
No, I ain't got no plans.
- What's up then? When we gonna hang out?
- We ain't gonna hang out.
Besides, what will we do, anyway,
if we went on a date?
See, look, first of all,
we'd go somewhere real nice.
You know what I'm saying?
Then we'd drive to the beach.
You know what I mean? Lay out a blanket.
You could have one of them
tight ass bikinis on,
then all the dudes'll be staring, like,
"Damn, she is fine!" But the thing is,
you with me so they will suffer.
That sounds good.
For real?
Except for a few things.
One, you ain't got no car to drive us in.
Two, you ain't got no money,
and three, you ain't got me.
What about Saturday?
No? Sunday?
Well, how about dentistry?
Girl, I do not want to be sticking my hands
down people's nasty ass mouths all day.
Oh, my God.
Looks like we're gonna be
taking the bus to school.
Come on, it's just a car.
When's it gonna get better for us, Em?
Why our lives got to be like this?
We just got the bad end of things right now.
But it's going to get better.
- Promise?
- Promise.
Besides, you don't want
that old beat-up car.
- You're too cute for that car.
- I know, huh?
Come on.
- I thought you were saving your money up.
- You coming or what?
This building should've fell down yesterday.
I'm not going in there.
Well, if you're scared, okay.
I'm not scared.
Hi!
Good to see you again, Erica.
- It's Emily.
- Close enough.
What are you laughing at, Lisa?
How do you know my name?
Come, sit. All will be revealed.
I see peril coming.
Danger awaits you.
Rory?
- Is that why we came here?
- Hush, Linda.
- Lisa.
- You suffered a great loss,
like so many other times in your life.
It began with the loss of your parents,
and it has come to this.
The nest egg you have created is gone,
along with the bird that stole it.
I see wealth in your future.
You'll come into it very soon.
Oh, child!
I speak of riches
beyond your wildest dreams.
It sounds good.
But it must be denied,
for it will come at a high price.
- Wait. Wait. Why it got to be denied?
- At what price?
The very fabric of your essence
will be torn apart. It must be denied.
Heed my words, Erica and Linda.
An evil so dark will come to reclaim it.
Does that always happen?
This that good shit, dog.
Rory don't play.
Yeah, you know you want some of this, dog.
No, no, you can't have none. This is my bud.
And if you want your own,
you better go out and get a job.
Get paid and then you get
to buy your own shit.
What the fuck is this?
Oh, Rory got some fucked up agriculture
going on up in this motherfucker.
Boy, you talking to my dog again?
Just the man I was looking for.
Man, I'm gonna tell you right now,
there ain't no clovers in my bud, all right?
So chill with that shit.
Man, it was filled with the motherfuckers.
Satisfaction guaranteed.
- And I ain't no satisfied customer, yo.
- Satisfied customer?
Do I look like a Kmart?
Man, I know my rights,
and that shit wasn't right.
All right. Where are the clovers?
See, I knew you was gonna say that,
and that's why I brought these bitches.
You know what I'm saying?
They're right here.
A real bag of motherfucking Lucky Charms.
Man, I must have left
the motherfuckers at the crib.
Left them at the crib?
Well, check this out, next time make sure
you bring 'em with your sorry ass,
'cause no proof, no motherfucking refund.
All right?
All right, man. Damn.
You ain't got to get all over my shit.
I'll bring them. You'll see.
- Filled with clovers, ninja.
- Ninja?
- Nigger, did you just call me a ninja?
- Hey, man, hey.
You need to get out more, man.
Don't nobody say nigger no more.
Yeah. Like, "What up, ninja?"
"Look at them ninja's over there."
You need to stop smoking that shit,
you dumbass nigger.
Ninja, please.
- Who's the mafia guy?
- Hey, homie.
Shut the fuck up, man, or leave.
This is business. All right?
What's up, Marcos?
- Got something for you here.
- Got something for you.
I'm gonna be needing some more
in about a week.
My clients love this shit.
I swear I sell more because of this chronic.
All right, man, just make sure
you hit me up before you do. All right?
I'm sorry, "hit you up"?
- Call me.
- All right. My nigger.
What?
Man, who you calling nigger, nigger?
- I thought we were cool...
- No one says that any more, all right?
- It's ninja. My ninja.
- Yeah.
Okay.
- My ninja.
My bad, fellows. Play on, players.
You look good. That guy looks good.
Baby Jordan over there. Okay.
I'll look for you in the pros.
Oh, God, oh, God, oh, God.
Somebody got his ass kicked
coming out here.
No matter, man. It's all green,
you know what I'm saying?
Why we couldn't do this at the park,
like normal people?
What park? You see any parks around here?
How about the beach?
Now, why you want to go to the beach
when we got all of this right here?
'Cause I need to work on my tan.
- Girl, you're a mess.
- Yeah, that's right.
All my hoes be cooking.
Where my dinner at?
You are so ghetto.
Hey, daddy's home.
Yeah.
How could you afford this?
Well, I had a little help.
Jamie, I'm gonna kill you.
What? I had no money for the food,
and I asked him would he float me.
He said, "No".
Then he asked me what for,
and I told him we was having a barbecue
and that you was going to be here, and
that's when he bought all this extra shit.
Asshole.
Look, he even bought wings
and some hot sauce.
You know how much
I love my hot sauce, girl.
- What's up, man?
- What up?
- Not much.
What's up, Em?
- You told her I was coming, right?
- Hell, yeah, man, she just shy.
Here, have a 40.
It's a shame they never finished this, huh?
We ain't got nothing
to say to each other, Rory.
I didn't choose this life for myself.
Look, don't act all high and mighty.
I never asked you for anything.
No, I was just dumb looking out for you.
- I didn't want you to give up shit for me.
- Yeah, but I gave up everything.
- And I tried to pay you back, right?
- With drug money.
You think I was going to take that, Rory?
Then you really are stupid.
Oh, shit. Are you all right?
Yeah, get me out of here.
- Here take this. Okay.
- Okay.
I'll be right back with some rope.
Emily! Emily!
Emily!
- Yo, you scared the piss out of me.
- You don't have to worry about me.
- You're welcome. What's that?
- I don't know.
- Let's see what's in it.
- Wait a minute.
Holy shit.
- How much do you think they're worth?
- Weigh about eight ounces.
I say about four or five K apiece,
maybe more if they're old.
You would know the weight.
That's like 200 coins,
that's a million dollars.
- That's 50 coins each.
- Nice.
What are you talking about?
- Sounds fair to me, baby.
- Of course it does to you. She found it.
- Fuck you.
- Yeah.
Hey, there's more than enough.
We can all benefit from this.
Lisa, I want you to take some of this money
and buy yourself a new car,
so you don't have
to take the bus to school. Okay?
And...
Rory.
I want you to do the right thing.
- Jamie.
- Yeah, what's up, baby?
You cannot use the gold to buy bud.
- What?
- No bud.
- Damn!
- You heard me.
What you laughing at? It ain't funny. Shit.
We're in the money!
All right. All right. Yeah, baby.
Welcome to my lair!
You have it, right here. Your medicine.
Hey, look at this, this is my first one.
I got it when I was in the fourth grade.
- Damn, fourth grade?
- Fourth grade. Yeah, for real.
- That explains a lot.
- Yeah.
- That's bad, though. I'm liking that.
- My motherfucker, right here. Okay.
- What about this?
- Man, I can't even touch that.
Yeah, you can touch it.
You just gotta stroke it.
Stroke it right. She likes to be stroked.
You know what I'm saying?
Yes, that will put you on your ass.
- I need to get it out right now.
- Yeah.
Oh, man.
- Hey, my baby.
- What's up, baby?
Y'all fucking?
- Hey, you know how we do it, baby.
- Hey, you do your thing, man.
You don't mind if I sit back
and run one of these, right?
Oh, no, it's all good, man.
Hey, my shit is your shit, baby.
Man, we need more black people
like you, man.
What's up, girl?
He did not just walk up in here
with that skeeze.
Oh, this is some good shit.
Oh, no.
What's up, little man?
How you living, dawg?
- You want a hit, man? You want a hit?
- Yeah.
I haven't smoked a good pipe in a long time.
Keep going. Keep going. Keep going.
Now let go. Let go. Yeah.
- Yeah. You like that, huh?
- That's good shit.
Good shit, nigger.
It comes straight from Korea.
I mean, this ain't gonna stunt
your growth or anything, is it?
Yeah, you my nigger, man.
I like you, dude. I like you a lot, man.
You know what I'm saying?
I'm gonna get you smoking up.
I'll get you some more, dude. I can manage.
Don't be stingy with my shit, though.
I swear, man, you cool.
Oh, man.
Where did you get that?
Hey, man, you don't need
to worry about that, little man.
We just here to smoke, all right? You know.
That's me gold. Now give it back.
There's a good boy.
What? I'm gonna get you high and you have
the nerve to ask me for my money, man.
Man, fuck you. You don't get it, man.
Fuck you. All right? I'll hit a midget, man.
I mean, get the fuck out of here,
you hallucinating motherfucker.
What? What, you gonna get in my face?
Man, give me my bong back, bitch.
Damn.
Oh, man.
Thanks for the smoke.
Yeah.
Man, who the fuck just took my shit?
Man, you niggers is crazy.
Can't a motherfucker enjoy
a smoke in his own goddamn house
without somebody stealing shit? Fuckers!
You put that girl to shame.
So you ain't got no beef
with nobody on the street, huh?
You think this might have been
Watson's gang?
No, man, I told you I squared everything.
What about all that ganja
you guys been smoking?
Ganja? What ganja?
Oh, man. My mom's Italian.
She likes a lot of oregano with her lasagne.
If you know anything,
now is the time to speak up.
- Told you everything, man.
- We don't know anything else.
- Don't bullshit me!
- Hold up, man.
You've been making a lot of moves on
the street in the past couple of days, Rory.
Something tells me you know
exactly what's going on.
Hey, look, don't trip. We gonna get you out.
Man, I can't be nobody's prison bitch.
Don't leave me in there.
I know what they do.
I can't be tossing nobody's salad.
Knock it off. Knock it off.
Yo, don't worry, man.
We're coming to get you.
It's gonna be okay, Jamie.
It's real.
Can we speed this up, please? Thank you.
How long this gonna take?
So fly!
Yeah, I'm gonna look good.
You see that shit, man?
Man, that's a big fucking account
he just took from us, man.
I mean, fuck this shit.
I say we go ice this motherfucker
right fucking now.
No, no, no.
- Why not?
- He deserves better than that.
What the fuck you talking about?
We're gonna do this right.
It's gonna be loud and messy.
I'm gonna make his ass a cautionary tale
for the rest of the fucking hood.
Hell, yeah.
It don't pay to be a nice guy.
Hurry up.
This is my last day.
You can't do me like this.
What?
You are still on my clock. Got it?
It's gonna take me three hours
to rub her down.
- I'm out of here.
- What?
Girl, you better get in there
and rub her down and leave her satisfied.
Now I want you to remember
I kept your ass employed
through all your bullshit with Rory,
when you would float your ass in here
and do nothing for an entire month.
Now I have no idea what kind
of crazy bullshit that you're mixed up in,
but I don't like it.
The Emily I remember always kept her word.
That is the shit.
Don't I need some more of that, honey.
I need more oil.
How much they put in them small bottles?
- They don't come in beached-whale size.
- What?
Nothing. I need some more oil.
Get that Caribbean coconut.
That shit is the bomb.
Hurry up!
Come start rubbing me before I cool down!
Oh, God.
This is wonderful. Work it, baby. Work it!
Oh, you got magic in those little hands.
Yeah, I've always had a way with the ladies.
Where's me gold?
Me eye.
Irish eyes will soon be smilin' again.
Rory! We can't spend any more money.
It's a leprechaun and he's after us.
He wants his gold back.
He's the one who killed that guy,
that guy at the party.
What the hell are you talking about?
Are you smoking Jamie's stash
or some shit?
Girl, you need to calm down, acting all crazy
talking about leprechauns and shit.
What's up, y'all?
We have to get Lisa. Come on.
Come on, we have to go.
Get in the car. Get in the car.
I just got here.
Just head home and I'll call you
when it's over with. All right?
This doesn't concern you, all right?
Here, take this. Okay?
What...
Come on, Em.
Into the bath, my pretty.
I like my girls nice and clean.
Die, you little motherfucker!
Come on. Come on.
9-1-1...
I can't believe she's gone.
I'm sorry, Em.
I know how much she meant to you.
Did you?
- All right, so what's next, y'all?
- We return the gold.
No. Hell, no. There's gotta be another way.
Fuck that.
We return the gold and everything that's left
and maybe all this stuff will stop.
Everybody ante up.
- Hey, easy come, easy go.
- We're fucked.
You done it again.
How could you spend all of it?
What the fuck is wrong with you, woman?
Oh, shit.
This shit is heavy as hell.
Impossible.
Shit.
What you waiting for?
Yo, why you bullshitting?
I say we jump in
the motherfucking '64 outside,
and haul ass
and don't stop till we get to Mexico.
You in it, partner?
We are not spending any more gold.
We're giving it up.
That's a fucking shame.
- I can't believe you left this up.
- It was only four months ago.
It was a lifetime ago. You're right, Em.
We gotta give back that gold.
It's your only play.
- You found it. I knew you would.
- What is it?
None of you are safe.
The accursed one
will not stop until he gets it back.
What are you talking about?
Where's Rory?
He said he had to get something
from his bike.
Where's the gold?
Oh, shit!
Shit.
- Come to bed, my sweet.
- I don't have your gold.
I know that. I'm not here for me gold.
- I'll catch that thief soon enough.
- What do you want?
Revenge. An eye for an eye.
Come on, baby. Come on.
Rory, where the hell you run off to?
You better call me back.
I'm not playing with you. Call me back.
Fuck.
Hello, there.
How the fuck you get in here,
you crazy-looking motherfucker?
That gold didn't even belong
to the one you stole it from.
Listen, don't hurt me.
I ain't have nothing to do with this.
Leprechaun.
Goddamn crackers,
always breaking into niggers' houses.
You have such a nice smile. Say, "Ah."
Pull over right now.
Rory, come on, pull over.
What?
Yo, Emily, we don't have time for this shit.
Why should I trust you?
Everybody was right about you.
You are no good.
You're right. I ain't no good.
But I'm trying, Em.
I'm trying to do the right thing.
Hit it. Take the alley and cut him off.
- Where you going in such a hurry, boy?
- We're being followed.
- You shut your trap.
- What you got in that box?
Nothing.
It's my dirty laundry.
Just give us a ticket and let us go.
Hey, hey!
- Here.
- Let her go!
What the fuck are you?
A little early for Halloween, ain't we?
- They have me gold.
- Oh, it's your gold.
Of course, you're a leprechaun.
So we'll just hand it over to you.
- I'd appreciate it.
- Why don't you go home to your mama?
What did you say about me mother?
You want some more?
Come on!
Give that back.
Shit.
Come on.
Watch out, kiddies.
Revenge will be mine tonight.
Oh, bloody hell.
Jamie.
We don't want none. Man, damn.
Hold on.
What's up, y'all?
Y'all want some smoke smoke?
- We got to get rid of this gold, right now.
- We have to go.
- Why?
- We are being chased by a leprechaun.
- Yo, come on.
- Man, you can't be smoking your own shit.
That's the first thing they teach you, ninja.
- Ninja?
- Don't ask. Come on, man, let's go.
Hey, big spender.
How's the business treating you?
What the fuck you got here?
Oh, shit.
Oh, fuck. You slick motherfucker.
No wonder you be acting
like a fucking pimp.
Yo, we cool, right? You got the gold.
- No, motherfucker. We ain't cool.
- Shit.
Police, nigger.
Hell, man, that's nasty.
What the fuck is that?
- Yo, Watson, shoot that little freak
for real. - Shut the fuck up.
Hello, lads,
I think you got something of mine.
What the fuck you want?
You Lucky-Charm-looking motherfucker.
You have stolen
what's been stolen from me.
Hold on, hold on.
- Yeah?
- Where the fuck are you?
Hey, hey, baby, how you doing?
- You think youre really slick...
- No, baby, I can't get into that right now.
You with some skanky ho, aint you?
No, baby, I ain't with nobody. Look,
I'm with you and only you, baby. Come on.
I know, look, look, I can't. I got a problem,
a small motherfucking problem.
- Look, why don't you call a brother back?
- Okay, love you.
Me too, baby.
Now, you were saying, little motherfucker?
You have stolen
what's been stolen from me.
Now, be a good lad. Give it back.
Oh, the gold is yours?
Of course, a fucking leprechaun.
- And you want the gold back?
- Aye.
- Well, hold on. Let me get that for you.
- Yeah.
Come on, motherfucker, get up. Come on.
- You hit like a wee lass.
- Yeah? Okay, motherfucker.
- Come on.
- Yeah.
Who's the wee lass?
The weak lass, the motherfucker.
We start this class, bitch.
Welcome to the hood, baby.
Come on, man.
What's the fucking big deal, man?
Getting tired, are we?
Watson!
Fuck you!
Damn, Watson.
Fuck, man!
What the fuck?
Who the fuck...
- What's up, ninjas?
- What the fuck?
Kill this motherfucker.
Rory, jump in.
- Let's get out of here.
- You said it.
Yeah.
- Hello?
- Who the fuck are you? Wheres Watson?
Watson?
- No. He's unavailable. Sorry.
- Are you one of his boys?
You better not run with no skank.
What you look like?
What do I look like?
Well, I got red hair and a nice smile.
- That sounds good.
- Yeah, and I'm a pretty sharp dresser.
- Okay.
- Yeah.
- You work out? You got a good body?
- Yeah, I think I got a good body.
- How tall are you, sweetie?
- How tall am I?
- Well, about 3'6".
- 36!
Yeah. But I make up for it in other areas,
if you know what I mean.
Hello? Hello?
Why we stopping?
Man, it's all done. Oh, man.
There ain't nothing we can do, man.
He's gonna fucking kill us all, man.
Just like he tore apart Lisa.
Just chill out, all right?
This is your fault, man.
I ain't keeping quiet no more.
- You better slow your fucking roll, you...
- Bitch, out of my face.
Get out of your face? Nigger...
You fucking crazy?
- Stop it! Stop! Stop it!
- Man, you said you weren't going hurt me!
You said you were my friend, man.
You supposed to look out for me.
It ain't my fault I'm scared, man.
Just don't hit me no more.
- He started this shit!
- You started it!
Both of you, shut the fuck up!
That thing is gonna kill all of us
if we don't get our shit together.
The only way
we can survive this is together.
So stop acting like a bunch of mama's boys!
My bad, man.
Are we cool?
Yeah, we cool, man.
- So, what are we supposed to do now?
- No more running.
So, we just sit here
and just wait for him to kill us?
No. We gotta kill him first.
How? Bullets don't do shit.
Neither does getting squashed
by a two-ton car.
- How do we kill it?
- I don't know.
But I know just the person to ask.
- We need to talk.
- What about my dead wife?
She'll still be dead tomorrow, man.
Come on, let's go.
- Get off me.
- Come on, man. Let's go.
Did you heed my warning? Of course not.
No one ever does once they have the gold.
And now you have his wrath upon you.
- How do we stop him?
- Why should I help you?
How about that?
These creatures, the Leg're Ghaun.
They are guardians from the Dark Ages.
They were protectors of the king's fortune,
born of earth magic,
and retrieve the king's gold
and punish anyone who would steal it.
But after the king died,
they were all whisked away,
back into the earth. Except for one.
He stayed in this mortal world
and became twisted and evil.
How do we kill this little motherfucker?
This creature's only weakness
are two things.
His gold and the four-leaf clover.
Four-leaf clover?
Where the hell are we gonna get
a four-leaf clover in the hood?
Yo, come on, man.
This ain't no time to be lighting up.
Told you. Clovers.
My ninja.
How do we use this to kill the Leprechaun?
- What about a crucifix?
- This creature predates Christianity.
- What about garlic? Will that work?
- Lf he is hungry.
That's it. A silver bullet.
Man, why you even buy a Glock, man?
Those bitches always jam.
Hollow tips.
What you doing?
Time to go fuck up some little people.
Here you go.
Man, how the fuck you get a gun
and all I get is a goddamn bat?
What am I gonna do? Hit a homerun?
Jamie, I just need you
to watch my back, man.
Man, look,
all we gotta do is wait until the morning
and the little fucker's toast.
- Morning?
- Yeah. Sunlight and shit.
He's not a vampire, you dumbass.
Oh, look at you.
Look who's the expert on leprechauns now.
How you know sunlight ain't gonna work?
You don't know.
How come you think
you know everything all the time?
All right, you hold right here.
I'm gonna go check on Em, all right?
You better come back, too.
Leave me and this motherfucker by myself
with a goddamn bat!
Good luck, my child.
I thought I had problems before.
Baby, I'm...
- I was just, you know...
- Yeah.
Setting up a trap for me, boyo?
Fuck you, you little mick motherfucker.
Damned clover!
Don't kill me.
Take your gold. Take it all.
Just spare me life.
I'll never harm you again. I swear.
You swear?
Say hello to Saint Patrick for me, bitch.
It's jammed!
Stay away from my friend!
- You used me gold.
- That's right, bitch. I bought me a new car.
I bought some ice, bought some new kicks
and an assload of bud, too.
And I smoked that shit and it was good,
you motherfucker.
I have no quarrel with you, witch.
Well, that will have to change.
Run, Emily.
I have an unwanted guest to deal with.
You can't take the gold. You can't take it.
It's mine. I want it back.
No!
You son of a bitch!
Rory!
Sorry, that hurt the old knee, did it?
Fuck you up!
This is what you want, isn't it?
No!
My babies!
Come and get them.
No escaping from you this time, darling.
You're going to hell
with all the others who stole from me.
No!
I'll kill you!
I like her.
We've had our fun.
Now give me what's mine,
and I might spare your miserable life.
Why did you kill them? For this?
- You evil fuck.
- Don't presume to tell me right from wrong.
You compromised all you believed in
once you got the gold.
Just like all those before you.
Your kind is weak
and will always give in
to your selfish yearnings.
Brings out the worst in us, doesn't it?
You really want to die so badly?
You can't live forever.
No!
I'm melting!
Come on, Rory.
Wake up.
- Where is he?
- He's dead.
- It's all over.
- How did you get the gun to work?
- Gun?
- The clovers.
Nothing like a nice fire to warm the soul.
Come on!
For 2,000 years, you filthy mortals
have tried to steal my riches
to satisfy your greedy urges.
And it always ends the same,
with you begging for your miserable lives.
- Rory!
- Fucking...
I'm slipping!
Was it all worth it in the end?
One day your kind will learn
that the treasures of the Leprechaun...
Hey!
All out of clovers, lad? That's too bad.
Check out my ninja.