[pensive string music]
[ Skipped item nr. 2 ]
[thunder rumbling]
[drum flourish]
[ Skipped item nr. 7 ]
[explosions and gunfire]
[indistinct shouting]
- [gasps]
[grunts]
This is Oaptain Kyle Fierson,
United States Marine Oorps.
Does anyone copy?
[radio static]
Damn it.
[sighs]
[radio static]
l repeat,
this is Oaptain Kyle Fierson.
Does anyone copy?
[radio static]
[man speaking Filipino]
[machine gun fire]
[grunting]
- AH! AH!
[man shouting in Filipino]
[machine gun fire]
[explosion]
[gasps]
[splashing]
- [speaking Filipino]
- Here's the dossier
you requested, Ms. Oarlisle.
[heels clicking]
Board members
have been calling all morning.
Stocks dropped another 6%
after the analyst downgrade.
- Yeah, l know.
l read the report.
lncreased competition
in the contracting industry.
l'm taking care of it.
Ari, it's Saturday.
l plan to enjoy my weekend.
Hold my calls.
l'll let you know.
- lt seems you're saying
that your recent discovery
could potentially solve
the world's energy
and power crisis.
Saving the planet,
ending war?
This news sounds a bit too good
to be true.
- The field of nanotechnology
has always been alluring
for this very reason.
The possibilities
far exceed anything
that could be achieved
by conventional means.
The time has come when
we will create a nano generator
no bigger than your watch
that can power an entire city.
- lf you don't mind,
in layman's terms,
what are these possibilities
of which you speak?
- We can control devices
and materials
at the atomic
and molecular level,
allowing us...
- lncredible, truly.
Thank you so much, Doctor,
for sharing with us
the inspiring news
of your groundbreaking research
and developments.
Again, Dr. Alan Kaitan,
esteemed Nobel Laureate,
who has served
as Professor of Material Science
at Oambridge University.
Thank you.
- Thank you.
[buttons beeping]
[phone ringing]
- Oolonel?
- Yes, Lilian.
- Ready to earn
your early retirement?
[door shuts]
- Take me back to...
smack!
- The plan is in motion.
The Abu Sayyaf leader
has taken the bait
and is in Hong Kong.
And we've been monitoring
his actions,
and we believe
that he will be in Mindanao
with the scientist
in the next few hours.
As soon as
the American military find out,
they will of course initiate
a rescue.
And that'll be your team's cue
to move in...
discreetly...
destroy everything,
save the chip, of course.
[phone beeps]
[hard rock music]
[ Skipped item nr. 94 ]
- Daniella,
how's the book?
- Have you ever read
a book, Oabrerra?
Pick a card.
- Seever.
Oaptain Fierson.
Do you have any queens?
- No, but l had your sister
last night.
Go fish.
Attention!
- Thank you, Oaptain Fierson.
At ease, gentlemen.
Dr. Alan Kaitan,
a leading American researcher,
has been kidnapped
by Abu Sayyaf rebels
out of Mindanao.
Their leader is this man,
Bin Malik Ambat.
lntel confirms
that Kaitan's work
can be used to produced
miniaturized nuclear weapons.
l don't think l need to tell you
the ramifications of this.
This technology consists
of two components
a prototype microchip
and the specs for its use,
which are only housed
on a flash drive,
to our understanding.
Your mission is to acquire both.
Any questions?
- What about the scientist, sir?
- His liberation
is secondary protocol.
- Okay, gentlemen.
Pack it up.
We leave at 0400.
Details of the targets
are on OD for review.
Sir.
- Yes, Oaptain.
- Are there no SEAL teams
in the area, sir?
- Orders came directly
from DOD.
Our team was selected due
to the proximity to the targets
because of the urgency
of this matter.
- Yes, sir.
- ls your team not capable,
Oaptain?
- We are prepared and ready.
[phone rings]
- Lilian, why are you calling
on this line?
- Oh, hello, Mr. Secretary.
lt's nice to speak
to you too.
Have you chosen
your disposable team?
l'll take that as a yes.
Well, l'm sorry,
but it's time to send them in.
My men are standing by
to eradicate all targets
and secure the chip.
And as promised,
the media will convey
to the public
that the technology died
with the heroics
of your soldiers in the attack.
l'll contact you shortly
with the exact location.
[phone beeps]
[intense string music]
[ Skipped item nr. 150 ]
[door squeaks]
[fingers snap]
- We are here, doctor.
Let us go meet your new team.
[birds calling]
[ Skipped item nr. 156 ]
- Target ahead.
- Take him, Oabrerra.
-  Row, row
Row your boat
gently down the stream
Merrily, merrily
[gunshot]
Merrily
Life is but a dream
- God One to God Five,
all targets have been removed.
- Oopy, God One.
Satellite shows
no other activity.
- Seever, cover six.
God One on the ground,
ready to move.
- Oopy.
Breach the east perimeter.
[snapping]
- You will be happy to see
l have picked up
some of your lab equipment.
Hmm?
- Allahu Akbar.
You are now in the service
of Allah.
Hmm?
You will work
throughout the night
with our scientists,
and you will show them
how to read your blueprints.
Huh?
- [yips]
- lf you and your lovely...
assistant...
want to live...
you will cooperate.
Huh?
[speaks Filipino]
- Stay alert.
Radio's open.
- Ten-four.
[grappling hook clanging]
Fierson, you clear?
- Hold there, Oabrerra.
- How many?
- Half dozen at most.
[galloping string music]
[ Skipped item nr. 202 ]
[muffled grunting]
- Hold on, Seever.
- Dan and l
are moving in.
Oome on.
- Oopy. Oopy.
Exit secure.
- Don't be nervous, buddy.
l'll be back in five.
- l've heard that before.
[toilet flushing]
[muffled grunting]
[thudding]
[man speaking Filipino]
[men conversing
in Filipino]
[silenced gunshots]
- Put your hands
where l can see them.
- You're an American.
- l need the microchip
and the flash drive.
- l'm not the enemy.
Please, she's innocent.
l-l've got what you need.
- Slowly.
[radio static]
- Fierson, ambush.
lt's a goddamn ambush.
[gunshot]
- [grunts]
[gunshots]
[silenced gunshots]
Why are you doing this?
- l'm not here
to destroy your work.
Where's the chip?
- We can't hold these guys.
They're coming from everywhere.
- Dan, what's your situation?
Dan?
- Fierson,
we're under heavy fire.
Lost communication
with God Five.
Need backup.
Oabrerra and Seever
are cornered.
- On my way.
- Oebu.
[grunts]
[gunfire]
- Seever, on the wall,
upper left.
[machine gun fire]
- Dan, movin' in on your three.
- Agh!
- Kyle, watch the barrel.
[gunfire]
- [grunts]
- Move in.
l got you covered.
[machine gun fire]
- Goddamn it, Oabrerra,
hold your ground.
[gunfire]
Oover me.
- l got you.
[gunfire]
[man grunts]
- Grenade!
[booming explosion]
- Goddamn it. Goddamn it.
- Seever, wait.
Oabrerra, hold your ground.
- Ah!
- Oabrerra!
[gunfire]
[grunts]
- Agh!
- Kyle, behind you!
[gunfire]
- Dan!
[gun clicking]
[panting]
[mournful music]
[ Skipped item nr. 278 ]
[birds calling]
[groans]
[phone rings]
[phone beeps]
- Yes, Lilian?
- Did you clean up
your mess yet?
- Almost.
- Really disappointed
to hear that.
- Well, l've taken out all
but the special ops team leader.
Got a contingency plan
in case-
- You know, Oaine,
in my book,
plan B stands for bullshit.
Have you at least acquired
intel on Kaitan's assistant?
- l'm working on it.
- Work harder.
What about the soldier?
What's his name?
- Um, Fierson.
Oaptain Kyle Fierson.
- Yeah, lucky for you,
l can make finding
Oaptain Fierson easier.
You just concentrate
on getting the chip.
Your best lead
is the girl.
You want to find the chip,
you find out where she is.
- [sighs]
How did this happen, huh?
- Sir, our hard drives show
that the blueprints
were uploaded.
- [breathes deeply]
And the chip?
- Gone.
- [speaks Filipino]
- [whimpers]
- Weaponry is useless
if there is no chip.
Do you understand?
- We've captured
video surveillance.
- Find him.
[dog barking]
[children giggling]
- [grunts]
[kids giggling]
[dog barking]
[rooster crowing]
- [speaks Filipino]
[dog barking]
[man speaking
in Filipino]
[speaking Filipino]
[dog barking]
- [grunts]
- [speaking Filipino]
[groans]
[grunts]
[dog barking]
[pants]
smack!
- Ooh!
[men conversing
in Filipino]
[woman speaking
[door opens]
- Hey.
- [speaking Filipino]
- Understand.
Okay, l say ''telephone.''
- Oh, okay.
- Okay.
Okay, Sa/amat.
[phone beeps]
This is Oaptain Kyle Fierson,
United States Marine Oorps.
Does anyone copy?
[radio static]
Again, this
is Oaptain Kyle Fierson,
United States Marine Oorps.
Does anyone copy?
This is Oaptain-Fierson-
Marine Oorps-copy.
Again, this
is Oaptain Kyle Fierson,
United States Marine Oorps.
Does anyone copy?
- Yes, Oaptain Fierson, copy.
This is Private Kerwin, sir.
What are your coordinates?
- Mindanao,
approximately 20 clicks
southeast of target.
- You're along
the west end of the shoreline.
We can arrange for evacuation
50 kilometers off the coast
at dawn.
- Oopy.
- What's the status
of your mission?
- All dead.
- [speaking Filipino]
- Something went wrong.
The intel we received
was corrupted.
- Okay.
- What's your current situation?
- Hostile.
- Any word, Private?
- No, sir, all quiet.
- All right.
[indistinct background chatter]
- l was contacted.
Team leader's still alive.
l gave him
the pickup coordinates.
- l see.
Well, you've done your country
a great service, son.
l won't forget this.
[sighs]
[guns clicking]
Okay, ladies, listen up.
Kid came through.
Always have a backup plan.
Our local recruits here almost
fucked the whole thing up.
- l'll take care of it.
- Goddamn take care of it.
l'm gonna give everybody
another chance
tomorrow morning.
You got it?
[speaking Filipino]
You hear me?
- [speaking Filipino]
[boat engine puttering]
- Put it down.
[gunfire]
[indistinct shouting]
Where's the chip?
- Nita.
l'm not the enemy.
[helicopter blades whirring]
[engine buzzing]
[birds chirping]
- [sighs]
So you're Fierson, huh?
- Where's Major Burke?
- Far from here.
At ease, Oaptain.
This spot used to be
an old World War ll lookout.
Now they use it
for weather surveillance.
l like coming up here.
Get away from everything.
Privacy, you know?
All right, let's go inside.
We got to talk.
That's Sergeant Wylan there.
So, Oaptain,
based on your final transmission
and the reports
that we obtained,
your mission was a failure.
- The intel we received
was compromised.
- Oompromised?
How do you figure?
- lt was an ambush, sir.
- Well, it's possible
that the intel was tainted.
We could look into that.
- Look into it?
My entire team is dead.
- Well, these things happen,
Oaptain.
You and your team
should be well aware
of the dangers
that come with your duty,
especially at this level.
- Sir.
- However,
seems pretty clear to me
that neither did you eliminate
all your targets
nor did you retrieve
the desired objective.
- l obtained the flash drive
with the tech specs.
The microchip
was nowhere to be found,
and as for the targets,
we eliminated all
that were present.
Bin Malik Ambat was not there.
This is before the ambush,
sir.
- What about the woman?
Did you see her?
Nita Santos.
- No, sir.
- No?
Did you at any time acquire
any information
as to the whereabouts
of Ms. Santos
or the microchip?
- No, sir.
- No?
Nothing?
Hell of a job, Oaptain.
Hell of a job.
Dismissed.
[gun clicks]
Get him!
- Ooh!
[grunting]
[gunfire]
[bullets whizzing]
Goddamn it!
He knows everything!
[man singing in Filipino]
[ Skipped item nr. 477 ]
[dogs barking]
- Oan l help you, friend?
You look far from home.
- Yeah, just visiting.
- Mm.
- Looking for a friend,
actually, who lives in town.
- Well, if you're looking
for someone,
you have to visit Tomagan.
- Oh, yeah? Who's he?
- His tentacles
is in everything around here.
He owns a little store nearby
and very popular
with tourists like yourself.
- Thanks for the info,
my friend.
l'll keep that in-
- Ah, hey, hey, hey,
you know what?
Uh, l'm going that way.
Oan give you a lift.
- You always this nice
to tourists?
- That's Filipino hospitality
for you, man.
Hop in.
[upbeat instrumental music]
[ Skipped item nr. 499 ]
Who is this friend
you're looking for out here?
[horn honking]
You don't talk much, do you?
- Do you ever stop?
- [chuckles]
Well, are you American military?
Still not talking, huh?
Hey, l'm
the Buruanga captain here.
lt's my business
to ask questions.
So if l see a tall white man
traveling alone,
not much on his back...
[chuckles]
l got questions.
- Tough job.
How do you handle the pressure?
- Listen, wise ass.
You and l both know
that you're not here
to see a friend.
- Oh, my god.
Are you psychic?
- Watch your mouth, man.
- Wait a minute.
So let me guess.
Oaptain's training
was a test
of questions and answers,
but you just sat back and
knew everything with your ESP.
- Yeah, well,
fuck you.
- Watch it!
[tires screech]
Bet you didn't see
that coming, huh?
- Get out.
- What?
- 'Oause l predict
l'm going to shoot you.
- We're in the middle
of nowhere.
- The resort
is one kilometer away.
You can handle it.
- Okay.
You got it.
[engine putters]
Thanks for the lift.
[tires screech]
Nice piece.
[gong resounds]
Hi.
Towel?
- Yes, sir.
Sir.
- Thank you.
- Sir. Sir.
- Have a good one.
Ladies.
How you doing?
- You checked in here?
- l'm looking for Tomagan.
- Who's looking?
- Just me.
- So what's your business,
American?
- l'm looking
for a woman.
And l hear he's the man.
- How you find this place?
- Where you from?
- Gentlemen,
we do not want to be rude
with so many questions.
Give him the VlP treatment.
[snapping]
So you are looking
for a girl?
We got plenty of girls.
- l was told you know
a lot of people.
l'm looking for
a woman named Nita Santos.
- Nita Santos?
There are a lot
of people looking
for Nita Santos these days.
- So you do know her?
- [laughs]
Got a funny sense of humor,
doesn't he?
Everyone in Oebu knows me.
And everyone knows
l hate Americans.
Now, l was told,
if anyone came looking
for Nita Santos,
l should put a bullet
in their skull.
[gun clicks]
You are not just anyone,
are you?
[chuckles]
- Hoo.
[grunting]
- [grunts]
[clanking]
[gunshots]
[gun clicks]
- Fuck.
- Ah.
- Ah!
[grunting]
Ah!
clank!
- Thanks for the rice.
- Oh!
[groans]
- Where is she?
- [coughing]
l don't know.
Ooh.
- Where is she?
- Please.
Please don't kill me.
[grunts]
l'm hurt.
she was spotted
in the village,
about 50 kilometers south
of here.
- Yeah, what village?
- They didn't say.
You're over your head,
American.
They're going to kill you.
[coughs]
- So negative.
[motor revs]
- Ouch.
- [speaking Filipino]
- Leave us.
- l have always been
a supporter and friend
of Abu Sayyaf.
- l have received word
that, uh...
you have the American.
This is very good.
- Had the American.
Slippery piece of shit,
that one.
- You let him get away?
- No, l tried.
- Tch, tch, tch.
From the looks of you,
it appears that he was
the better man, no?
- l have not wasted your time.
l know where he is.
- And you think
that helps me?
- l told him
the girl was last spotted
in a village
50 kilometers south.
- That is where we were going.
[speaking Filipino]
You led him.
- l didn't tell him
what village.
Now you can find them
both in the same area.
- Ah, duh-duh.
You are a pathetic
little girl
that talks too much.
Disgusting.
- No.
[crying] No.
Please.
No. No.
No!
[gunshot]
[thunder rumbling]
- And now we have breaking news
coming out of Southeast Asia.
Seven US marines are dead after
a daring raid on a weapons lab
in Mindanao, Philippines.
The botched attempt
to rescue an American scientist,
Dr. Alan Kaitan,
occurred when
US forces discovered
Kaitan was not actually working
against his will
but in fact aiding Abu Sayyaf.
The rogue terrorist
group appears
to have been experimenting
with handheld nuclear devices.
- Tch, tch, tch, the world
is such a dangerous place.
- The technology died with him
in the raid.
ln a dramatic turn of events,
it now also seems
that the lone surviving marine,
Oaptain Kyle Fierson,
was working as a mole
for Abu Sayyaf.
He is now on the run
with Kaitan's assistant,
Nita Santos.
Local authorities warn
these two
should be considered armed
and dangerous.
Any information that leads
to the capture
of these international fugitives
will be rewarded.
- Anything else?
- No, thanks.
Actually, maybe you can tell me
how to get to Talisay.
- Just down the road.
[phone rings]
- l'm sorry.
l'm gonna have to take this.
- Okay.
Don't work too hard.
- [chortles]
That was quick.
- l saw the news.
You're turning my men
into terrorists now?
- Yeah, well, somebody needs
to take the fall
for this little misstep,
don't they?
would you prefer it
to be you, Mr. Secretary?
You know, this whole situation
with Oaptain Fierson
might actually help us,
because everybody's
so completely focused on him,
leaves us to get on
with our work in peace, right?
- Do we have the chip yet?
- No.
But l'm pretty sure
l know who has it.
- Then we're safe.
Yeah, hardly.
This is gonna be
a much easier exchange.
You're gonna be
a very rich man, Henry.
l'll be in touch, okay?
[rhythmic drum music]
[ Skipped item nr. 702 ]
- Juan, l'm worried
about you breaking this story.
l don't want you to sell out
to the highest bidder.
- Are you kidding?
With a lead like this?
l can go from shit reporter
to real journalist.
- Juan, you're our best option,
family.
l'm trusting you.
- Look, if what Nita says
is true,
l'm gonna get a big promotion.
You can count on me.
- Okay, primo.
We got a deal.
- Hey, guys.
Sorry to interrupt.
Oouldn't help but overhear
your enlightening conversation.
- That's my goddamn gun.
- A mistake.
- You guys know each other?
- Okay, shut up.
Where's the girl?
- You mean my daughter,
asshole?
[crashing]
- So we meet again.
smack!
Not bad.
- Hey, hey.
Hey, hey, hey.
- Okay, okay.
- Hey, that's enough.
- You killed Dr. Kaitan.
- No, l didn't.
He's the one that told me
you had the chip.
He made me promise
to help you before he died.
[gunshot]
[woman screams]
Do you see them?
How many?
- Shit.
We got to hide.
- Juan.
l'll speak to them.
Everyone hide in the galley.
l can take care of this.
Good day, boys.
- You the only one here?
- Right.
Just me, myself, and l.
What's the big deal?
- Kaitan told me you'd fight.
- Why should l trust you?
- Haven't you seen the news?
They're calling me a traitor.
They're framing me
just like they're framing you.
They want us dead.
Now l need you and l need
that chip to clear my name,
to clear both our names.
- Shit, they're coming.
thud!
- Oh!
[thudding]
- See?
Nothing here.
Beautiful day.
- What's in there?
[gunshot]
[punching sounds]
[man grunts]
- Ooh!
[splashing]
- Oan you guys untie me now?
[rain hissing]
- We'll take that boat.
There's an island not far
from here
where we can hide out
the rest of night,
maybe head to Mindoro
tomorrow morning.
Got a cousin there
who can help us.
- Jesus, what's the plan?
Are we island hopping?
We got to get back
to Oebu.
- No.
Everyone's looking for us
in Oebu.
- Yeah, and there's only one
road in and out of this town.
Bet Abu Sayyaf are following me.
We'll take that boat.
[engine starts up]
She's all yours, Oaptain.
- l don't feel good
about this.
We can't just
leave civilization.
- The newscast got you
all crazy, huh,
thinking about
that big cash reward?
- Hey, are you loco?
l don't know
what you're talking about.
- Let me ask you something.
Were you gonna turn us in
to Abu Sayyaf or the Americans?
- What? No, man.
[splashing]
- l hope he can swim.
- That's my cousin.
- So l've been meaning
to ask you,
how did you get out of there,
off that island?
- Well, it wasn't so hard
after you killed everyone.
Plus l'm pretty sure
l blend in with the locals
a little bit better than you do.
- You still
don't fucking get it, do you?
l was doing my job.
- Then why didn't you save
the doctor,
an American?
Wasn't our primary objective.
- ''Primary objective.''
[knife clacking]
l'm sorry l dragged you
into this.
l made you an accomplice.
- Don't say that, Nita.
l am a willing accomplice.
And you are
my brilliant daughter.
l couldn't be more proud of you.
Everything will be fine.
We'll fix this, okay?
- My objective hasn't changed.
l still need that chip
before we can finish this.
l know you have it, Nita.
- So what?
Oan you hold onto the chip?
Do you think
you're that indestructible?
- lt's safer with me.
You know that.
Thank you.
- Relax with the gun.
We got a deal here.
- Where'd they go?
Unless you're a complete fool,
you'll tell me everything
you know.
- The money.
Oh, yeah.
Said something about Mindoro.
[computer beeping]
[birds chirping]
- Start collecting some wood
for a fire.
- What do we need a fire for?
- You look hungry.
[birds calling]
- Mmm, mmm.
l needed this.
l finally feel
like my brain's working again.
- What does that mean,
more questions?
- Actually, yes.
Who are these mercenaries?
Where do they come from?
- Military contractors.
Private armies hired
by big corporations.
- Why do they want
to kill their own men?
- They're not my men.
They don't answer
to our government.
They don't adhere
to our military code.
- [sighs]
- Nita, are you okay?
- The device that we created
is just a prototype.
The chip is literally
the first and the only one.
They knew our research could
be used for nuclear weapons.
But Dr. Kaitan refused.
That's why he contacted Yates
in the first place.
- Yates?
- Peter Yates,
his old college friend,
the British journalist
who flew over to Hong Kong
to interview him
the day all of this began.
- lt's late.
You should get some sleep.
We got an early morning.
l'm gonna go check
this place out,
see if it's not safe enough
for us to get some shut-eye.
- [snoring]
- His whole life has been
all about taking care of me.
l'm all he's got.
- What about your mom?
- l only know her through
his stories and memories.
She died when l was born.
Take the trip to Manila
once a month,
visit her grave
and bring her fresh flowers.
l do it now too.
Tell her my problems.
[sniffs]
Swear l could feel a presence.
- Well, it sounds to me
like you had a good family.
[fire crackling]
[computer beeps]
[door opens]
- Let me guess.
You're back again,
empty-handed.
- Look, we know
where he's going.
- Yeah, yeah, we know
where he's going, uh-huh.
Let's just finish it, okay?
lt's bad enough already.
[insects chirping]
- Oan't you sleep, soldier?
- lt's Yates.
Kaitan ever get
to talk to him?
- No.
He was kidnapped
after his interview.
- Well, that's it, then.
We get the chip to Yates,
he could write our story.
- He's all the way back
in London.
We need to get to him.
- But you're getting ahead
of yourself there, Nita.
We have to get the chip before
we get it to Yates, don't we?
- l gave it to you already.
- You mixed it with a decoy.
- What are you talking about?
What makes you think
that's a decoy?
What the hell
did you do that for?
- Don't play games, Nita.
- [sighs]
- Sorry about Dr. Kaitan.
Sounds like he was a good man.
- He was.
- All right.
[rhythmic drum music]
[ Skipped item nr. 924 ]
[car horn beeps]
Luiso.
[laughs]
- Como esta?
[laughter]
[both speaking Tagalog]
- Kyle, my cousin,
he's a resort-
- Como esta?
[speaking Filipino]
- He says you have good hair.
- Nice.
How about a phone?
[both speak in Filipino]
[Big Ben tolling]
- Since it's 500,
l'm expected at the club.
And after that...
[phone rings]
l believe
l'm supposed to meet my wife.
Don't really want to see her.
Ah.
- Oall on line one.
- Thank you, Oheryl.
Excuse me.
Hello.
- Peter Yates, please.
- This is Yates.
- Oh, thank goodness.
This is Nita Santos,
Dr. Kaitan's-
- Yes, l know who you are,
and l know everything
that's being said about you.
- Please, Mr. Yates,
hear me out.
l was very close to Alan,
and l put my heart and soul
into our work.
What they're saying
about me isn't true.
l was kidnapped
just as he was.
- Mr. Yates, this
is Oaptain Kyle Fierson,
United States Marine Oorps.
Why the hell
would we be calling you
if we were working
with terrorists?
- l'm listening.
- We're being set up.
There's something much bigger
going on here.
We need your help
to uncover the truth.
Please.
- What can l do to help?
- You can break our story.
- You'll need proof
of your innocence.
What is this chip
they keep talking about?
Do you have it?
[door opens]
- Someone just approached.
He said some were Americans.
- Mercs.
We'll call when we can.
- Nita, stay here.
- We have to draw them
away from Luiso.
- Already there.
l'm gonna bait.
Listen to me close and neither
of us will get killed.
- Looking for two people.
Look at me.
Two people.
Big white guy.
Where'd they go?
You know.
Big white guy,
where'd he go?
- Finally.
- [speaking Filipino]
- Get them.
- [shouting in Filipino]
[kids talking indistinctly]
[galloping bell music]
[ Skipped item nr. 998 ]
[thudding]
[knife unsheathes]
- Ah!
clang!
[grunts]
[gunshot]
- Give it up.
The chip.
- Okay, okay.
- The chip, where is it?
- Take it easy.
lt's right here.
[grunting]
[gunshot]
- That was easy.
- That should take care
of them for a while.
[people crying]
- Luiso!
Luiso!
[sobbing] Luiso!
- Nita.
- Luiso!
- Luiso.
- Who did this?
- Abu Sayyaf?
[sobbing]
- Luiso!
- Papa!
- Get my husband help.
Doctor, doctor.
- Okay, the truck outside.
Okay, okay, get the truck.
Get the truck.
- Bring him out.
- Get the key to the truck.
Oome on. lt's okay.
lt's okay.
[grunting]
- You have to take him.
l can't go in there.
- l cannot go in there.
l can't risk being seen.
Oome on.
- Okay.
[grunts]
[men shouting in Filipino]
They are going to kill her.
- lf they wanted her dead,
they would have done it already.
- Then why?
- She knows where the chip is.
That's what this is all about.
- The chip?
You asshole.
You have it.
You have the chip.
Not my daughter, okay?
- The chip she gave me was fake.
All right?
She's smarter than that.
She was testing me.
- Why wouldn't she tell me that?
You think she don't trust
her own father?
- She lied to you
'cause she loves you.
You get that?
She's protecting you.
Sorry about that.
So what was that back there?
Why won't you go
in the hospital?
- And risk you stealing off
with the car?
- Very funny.
Sorry l asked.
- Worst night of my life
was watching my wife die
in the hospital.
- But you gained a daughter
that night, didn't you?
- Yes.
- Gonna get her back.
l promise.
- lf they torture her,
Oh, Jesus.
- Daco, l got it.
How could l be so stupid?
She told me right where it was.
- Did she?
- Her mother's grave.
Your wife's gravesite.
- What?
ln Manila?
- lf that's where the grave is,
that's where she hid the chip.
- We got to get to Manila.
We got to get to Manila.
- Okay, okay, slow down.
First we got to get a plane.
- A plane?
How do we get one of those?
Oh, no.
Steal one?
- You got a better idea?
[plane engine whirring]
- [speaking Filipino]
- Howdy.
- [chuckles]
$40.
- Oh.
Ooh.
- Okay.
- Yeah, all right.
Oh, man, this is so awesome.
Thank you, thank you
so much, sir.
l've always wanted to sit
in one of these things.
Wow.
l mean, look at you
with your outfit.
Wow.
Daco, take a picture.
This is great.
l love cockpits.
l've never been in one.
Oh, man, this is so great.
A real cockpit.
There's two steering wheels.
Daco, there's
two steering wheels.
And all these little knobs
and the buttons
and needle things.
Wow.
This is making me thirsty.
1 0 bucks if you bring me a soda.
- $1 0?
- $1 0.
- We have it inside.
- Deal?
Yeah, you got it.
Oh.
- Yeah, this is awesome.
Get me that soda.
Get in.
[propeller starting up]
- Hey.
Oh, this...
where's my $50?
[engine whirring]
- You know how
to fly this, right?
- Not at all.
- What?
You have never flown a plane?
- Nah.
Just messing with you.
- So you have flown.
- Yeah.
Once or twice.
- Twice?
- Okay, once.
- Oh, Jesus.
[speaking Filipino]
- Seatbelt.
- Oh.
[intense percussive music]
[ Skipped item nr. 1157 ]
[man vocalizing mournfully]
[ Skipped item nr. 1159 ]
[door crashes open]
- My Mariana.
- Visit her grave
and bring her fresh flowers.
l do it now too.
[can clattering]
- lt's here.
They haven't made it yet.
- What do we do now?
- We got to get to London.
- What about my daughter?
- Daco, she would want me
to go.
- They're going to kill her.
You want that
on your conscience,
that you left her to die?
That's what you wanted anyway.
l'll take care of this myself.
- You can't take on
Abu Sayyaf.
- You think you know everything
because of
your advanced training?
l tell you what.
You don't know anything.
You don't know
what it feels like
to fight for your child.
l'll kill all of them.
[cries]
We'll all be together soon.
[sobbing] Oh, Jesus Ohrist,
we're dead.
- We're gonna need guns
if we're gonna find
your daughter.
[rhythmic percussive music]
[ Skipped item nr. 1190 ]
- This was your beloved doctor
after we finished him.
l understand you have
a very big family, no?
l will make sure that my men
kill each
and every one of them
if you do not take me
to that chip.
And as for your father,
l will torture
and kill him personally.
Look at me!
- Jesus, Daco,
This is the meeting place?
- Don't worry.
He's a cousin.
- Seriously, dude,
how many cousins do you have?
And please tell me that guy
is not part of the plan.
- Hey!
Hey!
- Hiya.
[both speaking Filipino]
- Holy shit,
how does he get this stuff?
[militaristic drum music]
[ Skipped item nr. 1211 ]
- War hero.
Very much connected.
- You look really good
with that.
- This is sacrilegious.
You are sick.
- Do not speak to me
of religion, woman.
- Bin Malik.
Bin Malik.
- The chip.
What is this?
Who do they think they are?
Huh?
[speaking Filipino]
[door squeaks]
[guns clicking]
- Post up there.
- Guess they had no trouble
with our directions.
- [whispering] Nita.
- Shh.
[man shouts in Filipino]
- But Nita.
- Be still.
[gunfire]
[men shouting indistinctly]
[gunshot]
Oover me.
And don't freakin' shoot me
in the back from up here.
- l'll go with you.
- l'll take care of this.
[gunfire]
- [grunts]
- Bastards!
- Oome around back.
Man off to the right.
[gunfire]
[rooster crows]
[knife whooshing]
clang!
[grunts]
[grunting]
[dull thudding]
- [grunts]
[grunting]
[grunts]
Oome on.
- Not bad.
l'm really starting
to like this guy.
- [gasping]
[machine gun fire]
- Just keep saving your ass,
don't l?
- Did you have to waste
the whole damn clip?
Let's make this snappy.
We got a long way to London.
- Long way.
[intense instrumental music]
[ Skipped item nr. 1273 ]
[gunshot]
- Papa.
- The chip.
- lt's right here.
Now you and your terrorist
friends will be very happy.
- Terrorists.
''Terrorists'' is the word
for your political leaders.
Not me, huh?
- l'm a soldier.
We're not much for debating.
Why don't you put
that gun down,
show me what you got?
- Why don't l shoot you first
and take my chip
out of your dead hands?
Allah-
[gunshot]
thud!
- Hell of a shot,
if l do say so myself.
Hell, l almost didn't have
to earn my paycheck.
Y'all are doing
all my work for me.
- Doing work for you?
Selling out my country?
l don't fucking think so.
- Shit, son,
you are so dead wrong.
Even our friend Bin Malik there,
he knew more than you do.
- He may have been delusional,
but at least he believed
in what he was doing.
- That very passionate belief
is what allowed him
to be manipulated so easily.
- You told Bin Malik
where we were going?
- Please.
Listen, if your friend
the good doctor
hadn't rejected
Warburton's offer
to fund his research,
what were they expected to do?
You see, our government
doesn't just walk in
and force somebody
to turn over their research,
even if it is
the right thing to do.
No, America's got
to keep up appearances, see,
keep up our public image.
- So you tip off
some terrorists,
hoping that you'll get it back
after they steal it?
You risk putting the chip
in terrorist hands.
Then you kill your own men,
my men!
Just to make a nice cover-up?
- Yeah, well, l'm sorry about
the hard facts there, Oaptain.
Wasn't long ago
l was in your shoes.
- Oh, so that's how you justify
killing United States Marines.
You're a fucking coward!
- You finished?
Let me alert you
to something, Oaptain Fierson.
We'd lose everything
if we let this technology fall
into enemy hands.
People talk about world peace.
Give me a fucking break.
You don't get world peace
from a renewable energy source.
You get it from manufacturing
the most powerful weapons
in the world
and scaring the rest of the
world into fucking submission.
Now stop fucking whining
this bullshit
and hand me the fucking chip!
And maybe l'll let
the rest of you live.
[guns click]
l'm waiting!
Soldier!
- Sir.
- Thank you, son.
- Listen.
l'm sorry about the men
that died.
Take comfort in the fact that
they died for their country.
Good luck.
Let's go.
- No.
- ls he okay?
- You-l trusted you.
- You can trust one thing.
- What?
- l would never throw away
a perfectly good replica.
- Let's go.
- Shall we begin?
- Absolutely.
- So this will go
into the hands of Ml6,
along with the tape
of our interview
and Dr. Kaitan?
- Yes, is the response.
Amazing that something
so small
can create change
of such great magnitude.
- You have no idea.
- Shall we?
We're here
with Oaptain Kyle Fierson
and scientist Nita Santos
to discuss one of the greatest
cover-ups of all time.
- [groans] No, no, no.
- l'm sorry-l'm sorry, ma'am,
it just isn't functional.
There's nothing
but ghost files and-
- lt's a fake,
that's what you're telling me.
- l-l'm sorry, ma'am.
There's nothing l could do.
- l need you
to tell me right now, of course.
- Actually, Ms. Oarlisle,
there's something.
An email was sent
to our DO office
and it was uploaded
across the board.
There's a video attachment,
and l think you should see this.
- My office, now.
- Hey, there.
lf you're watching this video,
that means
you've recently acquired
your very own precious
nano nuclear microchip.
And, yes, unfortunately for you,
it is a replica.
And, yes, you have me
to thank for that.
But don't worry.
l'll give you the opportunity
to do that soon.
Because l'm coming for you.
Have a nice day.
[electrical zapping]
[upbeat rock music]
[ Skipped item nr. 1393 ]
-  Gone to save
The lives
That l'm still searching for
Away
Our war
ls taking place
As someone
ls given to
The lies that break us
Lay me down
Just aid these feet
To sleep
Do we, do we,
do we, do we decide
How we live,
how we're gonna survive
Release me
l'm still living in hell
Do we, do we,
do we, do we decide
How we live,
how we're gonna survive
Release me
Good God,
l'm living in hell
Out there it's cold
l'm not myself
l see you've called
lt's time
To face
The lies l've heard by now
These guns
Have brought
So many tears
Don't lay me down
lf only you knew
Aid these feet
Lay me down
lf only you knew
To sleep
Do we, do we,
do we, do we decide
How we live,
how we're gonna survive
Release me
l'm still living in hell
Do we, do we,
do we, do we decide
How we live,
how we're gonna survive
Release me
Good God,
l'm living in hell
[ethereal electronic music]
The sun has come
To claim what lives
still exist
And, oh, if you can catch
These rays that shine
Oh
To
To release me
Release me
Do we, do we,
do we, do we decide
How we live,
how we're gonna survive
Release me
l'm still living in hell
Do we, do we,
do we, do we decide
How we live,
how we're gonna survive
Release me
Good God,
l'm living in hell
Do we, do we,
do we, do we decide
How we live,
how we're gonna survive
Release me
Good God,
l'm living in hell
Do we, do we,
do we, do we decide
l'm still living in hell
- Let's go.