I've been alone with you inside my mind.
And in my dreams I've kissed your lips a thousand times.
I sometimes see you pass out side my door.
Hello!!.
Is it me you're looking for?.
I can see it in you eyes,i can see it in your smile.
You're all I've ever wanted.
My arms are open wide.
Cause you konw just what to say.
And you know just what to do.
And i want to tell you so much.
I love you.
I long to see the sunlight in your hair.
And tell you time and time again how much i care.
Sometimes i feel my heart will overflow.
Hello!!.
I've just got to let you know.
Cause i wonder where you are.
And i wonder what you do.
Are you some where feeling lonely.
Or is someone loving you?
Tell me how to win your heart.
For i haven't got a clue.
But let me start by saying.
I love you.
Hello.
Is it me you're looking for?
Cause i wonder where you are.
And i wonder what you do.
Are you somewhere feeling lonely.
Or is someone loving you?.
Tell me how to win your heart.
For i haven't got a clue.
But let me start by saying.
I love you.
Hello.
Is it me you're looking for.