(GUITAR STRUMMING)
Don't jump in the pool.
The water we
put in next week
for the summer.
MALE REPORTER ON TV.
... in South Vietnam
ground war.
The U.S. Command reports
148 Americans killed
in the war last week,
the lowest weekly
figure in six months.
1,612 Americans were...
FEMALE REPORTER ON TV.
... they barely look
like they've been warned.
MALE REPORTER 2 ON TV.
There was exchange
of fire south of
the Sea of Galilee and
across the Suez Canal.
These exchanges and raids
are now a daily part
of Israeli life,
and the country is
prepared for anything.
NBC news correspondent,
David Burrington, reports.
MALE REPORTER 3.
In spite of all
the border turmoil,
Israeli intelligence
officers do not expect
all-out war this summer
unless the Arab
nations get reckless.
And that's the
main worry here,
that Arab frustration
will suddenly explode...
(COMMERCIAL PLAYING)
MALE REPORTER 4. In a day
of intensive activity,
Captain Neil Armstrong
and his crew
entered the final
phase of preparations
for the July 16th
launch of Apollo 11.
(BELL DINGING)
NASA officials report
that the third and final
day of launching pad
tests proceeded smoothly,
while inside
the training center,
the astronauts performed
simulated moon walks
in their space suits.
What?
Excuse me.
I can't possibly stay.
This establishment
isn't fit for
human habitation.
Fine, go.
Yes, well,
here's your key.
It didn't fit the lock,
but the door was
open in any case.
You went into the room?
I did, yes.
And now I must insist
on you returning my $8.
After you already
used the room?
What kind of scam
are you running?
And besides...
Well, this is ridiculous!
The so-called air
conditioner was just
an empty plastic
box in the window.
The room was filthy.
Indeed, I discovered a small
hair on the pillow.
There wasn't even
a towel in the bathroom.
ELLIOT: Ma.
What?
Please, we're late already.
My son,
thank God you're here.
This man is
threatening me
for a refund!
I'm sorry. You're over
$5,000 in arrears
on the mortgage.
The home office is
breathing down my neck.
Mr. Spiers,
the El Monaco Resort...
It's a resort now?
...and Motel is my
parents' lifeblood.
With the addition
of the swimming pool
and these new town-wide
marketing initiatives...
Initiatives?
As you know,
I have been elected
the President
of the Bethel
Chamber of Commerce.
The youngest president
in their history.
We've decided to erect
a tourist information booth,
right off 17B.
I have agreed, on behalf
of the El Monaco,
to lease at no cost
some road frontage
to the endeavor,
which should coincidentally
drive heavy tourist traffic
right to our door.
In addition...
Please, Elliot,
you know
I do everything
I can to help.
We even bought one
of your paintings.
But don't try to sell me
on those singles weekends
or the culture festival
or whatever other schemes
were supposed to dig
you out last summer.
We've decided to
go classical with the
festival this year,
maybe a string quartet,
more contemporary,
like Morton Feldman?
Very avant-garde.
And we've got a theater
troupe in the barn.
You have a theater
troupe in the barn?
The Earthlight Players.
Vassar graduates,
some of them.
They live in the barn?
They do everything
in the barn.
ELLIOT: You haven't
seen the sign?
What sign?
The sign in
front of the barn.
Mr. Spiers, my God, please.
We come here, begging,
begging for mercy,
and what do you give us?
This fixation about the barn.
What is it with you
and the barn?
I was just...
I'm an old woman,
Mr. Spiers. I've suffered.
I walked here all the way
from Minsk, in Russia,
in 20-foot snow drifts,
1,000 miles across Siberia.
I escaped the pogroms,
the Tsar's secret police,
with nothing but cold
potatoes in my pockets.
Mrs. Teichberg, please...
And for what?
For more persecution!
It's because we're Jewish.
I know it, isn't it?
Mrs. Teichberg, please.
This is the Catskills.
Half the summer
colonies are Jewish,
they're all our clients.
Until the day they
need you, and then
on goes the gas!
ELLIOT: Ma,
calm down, please?
Jackson, just give us
a couple of months.
The summer season's
coming up, I honestly do
have some real money
owed me from
my interior design
business in the city.
Please?
WOMAN ON PA. Mother-son
ballroom class will start
immediately after, at 11.00.
That's kinder-dancing
for the kiddies
in 10 minutes.
Dad, you gotta
get Ma to lay off
the Nazi stuff and
let me handle this.
You think I can tell
your mother what to do?
I gotta get back to the city.
I'll see you Friday.
We'll get the money.
Let them take
this miserable dump.
I'll die in peace,
in Florida.
Mr. Tiber.
George.
I admitted your
sister some time ago.
Thanks.
And some gentlemen
from the moving company.
Oh, yeah.
There you are.
Hi, Sis.
How did it go
at the bank?
How do you think it went?
Till the end of the summer,
that's it.
What about the money
those mobsters owe you
for that nightclub
you designed?
They have a surprisingly
strict policy about
paying designers.
They don't.
(SIGHS)
You want some
more paintings?
No,
I already have 10 of them.
And you know Joe hates them.
Of course you're broke,
after all the money
you've sunk into that
hellhole of theirs.
And I bet Ma's
never even said a word
of thanks, has she?
No, but I can sense it.
The special way
she sometimes
looks at me
with just her left eye,
you know.
Elliot. Now is your time
to go to California
like you've always wanted,
to paint and design.
Be free, stop throwing
your life away up there.
I can't give up
on them now.
Why not?
I'm the one they
still want around.
I guess that means they
love me more than you.
That must be a great
consolation to you.
Dad, that's bleach
for laundry.
It kills the germs.
What's the difference?
Elli? What?
What are you doing
with those sheets?
They're dirty.
Let me see. Nothing.
Those two, they
didn't do nothing in there.
Shake them, put them back.
But, Ma...
Electricity, detergent,
who's paying
for all that?
And you, theater girl,
get back in the barn!
All of you!
Lazy people.
Let's call to order.
Come on, everyone.
Last meeting, we all said
we'd each bring some
new ideas to the table.
Well, okay.
We got a lot of dairy farms
around here, right?
And a fair number of bulls.
Okay, you've all
heard of the running
of the bulls in
that town in Spain,
Pampoona.
Pamplona.
Well, no one's doing
one in the Catskills.
Seems to be a big
draw over there.
It would be very amusing
to see all those Jews
from Levitsky's
summer colony,
you know, the ones
with the black top hats
and the curls,
running for their lives
chased by our
local livestock.
Wouldn't that be
a wonderful sight!
(ANNIE CHUCKLES)
We're writing it all down.
Any other ideas?
What about the monorail?
Marge,
you can't bring that up
in every meeting.
I've written
to the Governor,
but I think a letter
from the entire
Chamber of Commerce
would be much
more effective.
A monorail linking
downtown New York
to White Lake
would be a tremendous spur
to the local economy.
Jesus. Look, people,
I said I would come
back to these meetings
if you could stay
out of cuckoo land,
just once.
We have some
serious local issues,
serious business to do.
Such as?
For starters,
I need a permit
for the town landing
for a fish-toss
tournament next month.
I knew it. I knew it.
You're just back here
for your own purposes.
Now, come on, Marge.
All right, let's see
the application.
I got it here.
Yeah, that's all
in order. $1.
Here you go.
And I've got
my application
for our annual
El Monaco summer
music and art event,
which will also inaugurate
the first season
of the tourist
information kiosk.
Annie, if your
grandson and his friends
want to play again this year,
tell them to
give me a call.
Okay.
Do I hear a motion to
approve these permits?
I so move.
Okay. Seconded?
Seconded?
Oh, for crying
out loud, seconded.
Good night.
Good night, Annie.
Night, Elliot.
MAN: See you, Elliot.
Bye, everyone.
CAROL: Night, Elliot.
Good night, Carol.
Fuck! Fuck!
Take him down, motherfuckers!
Jesus!
DAN: Billy,
get back in the car.
What?
Back in the car.
Hey, Billy, you're back.
That's great.
Yeah.
Staying with big brother Dan
and his beautiful wife
Carol here
till I get my own pad.
Yeah, 'cause
little brother Billy
made a tiny little
pit stop in Bangkok
and blew all his Army pay.
Didn't he, Billy?
Bangkok, man.
Fucking Bangkok.
Come on, we gotta go.
Great seeing you
back home, Billy.
(ENGINE STARTS)
Hey, Elliot.
Dave.
The usual?
Extra bacon, please.
You got it.
Hey, Elliot.
Max.
I hear you've moved
up here permanently.
Just helping Mom and
Dad for the season.
Well, I hope you have
another one of
your festivals.
Miriam and I just love
listening to your records
out on that lawn.
Sure, Max. This year,
I'm going to try to
get a live quartet.
BOB: Looks like
you're gonna have
some competition.
What, there's a recall
vote down at the
Chamber of Commerce?
This says here
that Wallkill's
gonna have
a music festival, too.
Some hippie thing
got thrown out of Woodstock
so they've set
themselves up in Wallkill.
Wow, Janis Joplin.
Guess that beats
playing a bunch of
records on a lawn.
Then again,
it'll probably turn into
some kind of antiwar riot.
Let Wallkill have them.
DAVE: Extra bacon.
You want your receipt?
Thanks, Dave.
See you later.
See you tomorrow, Max.
(SLOw MUSIC PLAYING
O VER SPEAKERS)
(ALL HUFFING)
WOMAN: No, no, no,
that's horrible.
(ALL RETCHING)
Tonight's dinner
will be roast turkey
and for dessert,
an apple tart.
(WOMEN WHOOPING)
I killed it!
That clock was
our mother's.
(ALL HISSING)
Your mother.
Maybe I didn't break it.
Maybe it only looks
like I broke it.
Maybe we only
think we exist,
when really we don't.
Hi, Elliot.
(DEVON EXCLAIMING)
Thank you, Elliot.
It hasn't been touched
since my glory days
in the Midwood
High School band.
How's the show
shaping up?
We're really getting into it.
Great. Hope you guys
are prepared.
You're probably gonna
outnumber the audience.
Only takes one extra soul
to make it theater, man.
And theater
is transformation.
But it's hard,
concentrating.
Concentrating on?
We're just,
I don't know, hungry.
Hungry? As in...
(STUTTERS) Yeah,
as in hungry, you know.
For, like, foodstuffs.
You don't have any
potatoes or sunflower
seeds or anything?
I can barter some
very special grass.
No.
Me and grass,
you don't want to know.
But let me see what I
can steal from my mom
and you guys can pay us
after the first show.
Or not, I guess.
Front row seats, man.
On the house, for you.
I'm bored!
(ALL HUFFING)
That house was ours,
not his.
But he took out
that mortgage,
and now his wife
has all the money.
I can't take it any longer!
I can't! I can't!
Please throw me out,
just throw me out!
I can't take it!
(ALL EXCLAIMING)
(TELEPHONE RINGS)
Hello?
STEVEN. Hey, Elliot.
Steven, hi.
What are you doing
calling long distance?
I just made bail.
The pigs raided
the bar again.
Can you believe it?
But you should come back.
I think we're going
to have another riot.
Come up here.
You can start a riot
here in White Lake.
It would be wild.
I was just calling,
you know.
New York hasn't been
as much fun without you.
I mean,
it hasn't been as depressing,
but, you know, in a fun way.
So, me and Marcus,
we're hitching a ride
with the art dealer.
Do you remember him?
The one with
the doll collection?
Mmm-hmm. Yeah.
We're moving to
San Francisco, man.
You wanna join?
Elliot? You there?
Yeah, I'm still here.
Hey, thanks for the call.
It's good to hear your voice.
And drop me a line
when you get there, okay?
Okay.
Elli. There's something
moving in the bushes!
Take cover, man.
Billy.
What is it?
We're surrounded, man.
Can't you feel it?
It's like, when
the radio was busted,
and we fragged
that fucking sergeant,
so then they just
leave us out here.
But someone's gotta go back
and call in air support,
'cause I gotta
stay with O'Connor.
He doesn't have
any feet, man.
(PANTING)
It's okay, Billy.
The radio's working
in the office.
I can call from there.
And you can cover me, right?
And I'll do some
recon with the squad,
they can send up
some reinforcements,
and the VC
will never see me.
And I can call in
the coordinates.
What the fuck you
talking about, Elliot?
I don't know.
I thought maybe
I could be in your
flashback or something.
If it made you
feel any better.
That's cool.
You all right?
Man, I am fucked up.
You think I should
take those pills
they gave me at the VA?
I should probably just
take those fucking pills,
but then I just
sleep all the time,
and then there's the
fucking nightmares. Fuck.
Never thought I'd
end up back here.
Me neither.
I'm thinking,
maybe I should
do another tour.
That doesn't sound
like such a good idea.
Over in 'Nam,
I'm fucking normal.
Do you know what I'm saying?
Hey, you should join up.
Me?
Yeah.
No. They wouldn't
take me even if I wanted.
Yeah?
Flat feet.
(CHUCKLES) Right. Feet.
Fuck.
Yeah, you're not
fucking normal, Elliot.
No.
I guess not.
All I know is we're
fucking surrounded here.
Eat.
Thank you, Elliot.
For the backdrops you
painted for all of us.
Everybody loves the colors.
It's like a mandala.
Actually, it's not
like a mandala.
Well, the colors,
it's more like M&M'S.
You're welcome, Dev.
Hey, you guys
want some? Cholent?
Uh...
Maybe next time.
No, I'm cool.
Hey, man,
what's up with this?
The festival.
The locals killed it.
They pulled the permit.
In Wallkill?
The Wallkillians
killed it.
DEVON: Bummer, man.
We were all hoping
to score some tickets
and go over for it.
Could have been beautiful.
Joan Baez, Grateful Dead,
The Who.
Maybe even Dylan.
DEVON: Yeah, Dylan.
Dylan.
Can I get that
paper for a sec?
DEVON: Is everything
all right, Elliot?
(CLICKS PHONE)
Operator.
Hi, Alice.
Can you connect me
with something called
the Woodstock Ventures
in New York City,
a gentleman by
the name of Michael Lang.
SONIA: Elli! What is this
with the sheets?
What does it look like?
I'm making a big
cross on the lawn!
With the clean sheets?
Jake, our boy's gone crazy!
Making a Ku Klux Klan
rally on our property!
No, it's so
they can find us.
Who?
(HELICOPTER APPROACHING)
(EXCLAIMING IN DELIGHT)
Hey, man.
Good to see you.
Hi.
You don't remember
me, Elli?
Do we know each other?
Bensonhurst, 73rd Street.
I lived down
the street from you, man.
We played stickball.
I'm Michael Lang,
you're Elli Teichberg.
Yeah, yeah, I kind of
remember, yeah.
Mrs. Teichberg.
Hey, it's Michael,
from the neighborhood.
Excuse me.
You! Cover your parts!
We have company!
In the barn.
Get in the barn!
All of you! In!
SONIA: Get inside!
Far out.
So, here we are.
Right.
Yes, as I mentioned
on the phone...
You have a permit.
That's very cool, Elli.
It's a start.
Very cool.
Please.
Mr. Teichberg.
(GRUNTS)
Hey, people!
Welcome to Elliot's place.
Hey, Elli, can we
take a look around?
Of course, I'll show
you the whole place.
You've got some
open land here, right?
Absolutely,
just up here and down.
So...
(SPLASHING)
(GRUNTS)
MAN: Shit!
Michael, for Christ's sake,
it's a swamp.
Maybe we could get
some bulldozers in here
and level it, right?
You're kidding me.
He owns it.
He's got a permit.
He's the President of
the Chamber of Commerce.
And because of that you
wanna drown thousands
of kids in a swamp?
Look, honestly,
you guys can do whatever
you want to here.
That's fine
with us, really.
You could... For example,
you could detonate
an incredible amount
of explosives
and it would dry
everything out immediately.
And then you
could just compact
the ashes down, you know,
and people could
sit on that.
Radical thinking, Elliot.
I assume you got
a permit for that, too?
Or... Okay,
we get some big cranes
and hang, like,
a parachute over the field,
and everyone could sit on it.
No?
How about you just
nuke the whole place?
Hey, don't lose
that creativity, man.
Jake, they are leaving!
Elli, have you
offered accommodation
to everyone?
We may not have
vacancy for everyone,
as the season is...
Ma, they're not staying.
Stay! Stay! Look.
My husband is
bringing refreshments.
Here.
Thank you,
Mrs. Teichberg.
Here. Try some of this.
It is the best
chocolate milk in New York.
Made just down the road.
Have some water.
Or some chocolate milk.
What's his name?
Or her.
Lou.
Wow. That is excellent
chocolate milk.
Yeah, it comes
from the local cows.
Far out.
They eat local grass.
That must be
some healthy grass.
And there's a lot of it,
in big fields,
just a couple of miles
down the road from us.
I've always been
a big supporter of Elliot,
here in Bethel,
and I always enjoy
his music festival
every summer.
That's why we're here.
Miriam and I donate
the yogurt and the milk.
It's fate.
It's beautiful.
Although some of
the local young people,
the music they play
can be a little trying,
if you know what
I mean, honestly.
Yeah, but it's
the effort that counts,
isn't it, Miriam?
And they do
enjoy themselves.
There's a lot of joy
in music, Mr. Yasgur.
And we'd love to
bring that joy to your
beautiful farm, wouldn't we?
Now, I know it's
going to be something
of an imposition,
but we're more than
willing to do anything...
You say you want to
use these fields here?
Then you'll be
needing the land
beside the barns as well,
I'm guessing,
for access to the roads.
And parking.
Probably best
across 17B.
I own the piece
down the road, but there
are a couple of lots.
You'll probably
want to avoid dealing
with the Browns.
And you'll clean
up after yourselves,
I'm hoping.
Of course.
Well,
would $5,000
do it for you?
Five?
But you'll have to tidy up,
and you'll have to pay
for any damaged crops,
of course.
Sure, Max.
That sounds fine.
Good. Wonderful.
Well, why don't you
all come into the house
for some chocolate milk?
Far out.
You know,
we're gonna need a place
for people to crash
while we prepare
the festival.
Your place looks
pretty cool.
How many vacant rooms
do you have for the
next couple of weeks?
Well, it depends on
how you define room.
You know,
how many people
can crash with you.
What do you guys charge?
Let's see. It's $8 a night,
but that can be for doubles,
and we give
a weekly discount,
of course.
Plus the cabins,
you can get cots,
so four people,
about 150, I'd say.
You can get
about 200 people.
Hey, man, let's make it easy.
Why don't we just
buy the El Monaco out
for the season?
Just figure out the costs,
write it down, and
we'll take a look.
And if we don't
use all the rooms,
you can rent out
the free ones.
We need to keep
some cleanup crews
around afterwards.
And if you've got
some bigger spaces,
for offices,
that kind of thing.
We need to put in
some phones and have
some space to park vehicles.
You know where we're going?
Mmm-hmm.
There you go.
That's the...
Looks like we can
work with this, Elli.
Cool.
You know, I was thinking,
I've got that theater
troupe in the barn.
A theater troupe
in the barn?
Yeah, the Earthlight Players.
It's okay if they stay, right?
Maybe you guys could
find some work for
them or something.
They could really
use the pay.
They're all hired, man.
Not a problem.
Great. Thanks.
And I hope you don't mind,
but we like to pay cash
in advance.
And not only that,
he made me a local community
liaison for the festival,
and we're going to be
the exclusive local
ticket agency, too.
They think at least
5,000 people are gonna
buy tickets, or more.
Five thousand coming
here to White Lake?
Elli, you're an idiot.
Twenty people, thirty,
okay, for a weekend.
But 1,000, 5,000?
They'll steal everything.
Ma...
We'll be sued in
court by the neighbors.
What kind of meshuga, hairy,
barefoot person comes
here in a heliocoptic
that we should lay
our good white sheets
on the grass and ruin them,
and then plot
and revolutionize
to take our hotel.
Ma, he pays cash.
Everyone pays cash here,
you shnook!
No, Ma, really.
Open it.
That's $5,000 for the rent,
and another $5,000 for
my services as liaison.
Plus, think of
the money we're gonna
make off of commissions
(SHUSHES)
From the ticket sales!
And also...
(TELEPHONE RINGS)
El Monaco
International Casino
and Bar Mitzvah Center.
MAX. Elliot?
Hey, Max.
Hi. Well, the phone
hasn't stopped ringing
since you left.
And they're saying...
I know, wow.
... thousands of people
might be coming to this thing.
Yeah.
Well, you know,
that's gonna cost
quite a bit to put
things back in order,
and to get the cows
situated and so forth.
I can understand, sure.
Now, Elliot,
you know I don't wish
to mess up your festival.
You know that.
'Cause I think what was
done to those young
people in wallkill
was just plain wrong.
But I've been
talking with Miriam,
and we think if you
could just go back
and tell those people...
How much?
Seventy-five thousand.
Not a penny less.
Okay, I'll let them know.
Okay, good. Bye-bye.
What?
Don't spend any of
that money. That was Max.
The deal's off.
What? Impossible!
Ma. Ma. Ma.
Elli, don't try to stop her.
She can't get far.
And I read in the papers,
you've already sold
thousands of tickets,
and that's a lot.
And so you'll be
needing to use,
practically,
my whole place here,
not just the alfalfa fields.
Now, wait a second.
I mean, I could...
I mean, I could buy
a farm for the kind of
money you're asking for.
I could buy five farms.
From what I read in
the papers, Mr. Roberts,
you've already
spent a million dollars
in Wallkill,
and you've only
got until the 15th
until your festival.
Now, I'm sure
a wealthy young man
such as yourself
could, indeed,
buy a lot of farms.
But that's neither
here nor there.
All I'm saying is...
Yeah, all you're saying
is that you've got us
over a barrel.
Well, if I didn't,
you wouldn't be on
your second carton
of chocolate milk
now, would you?
But I tell you this, fellas,
when you make a deal
with me, it's a deal.
Okay? So long as
you promise to put
things back in order,
I'll stand by you 100%.
These people
are my neighbors,
and I know how
to deal with them.
I won't let them
run you off like
they did in Wallkill,
'cause this is my land,
and let's just see them try.
Wow, Max,
that is very cool.
And you're right.
We're going to
have a lot of people
come here and
enjoy your place.
Michael, if I may,
I wouldn't describe
$75,000 as cool.
$5,000 is cool.
Hey, it's your bread, guys.
I'm just trying to
put you together here
with Max's vision.
Right. Look, Max,
if we were willing to
consider doing this,
you're really gonna have to
let us make it work.
Mike, listen, really,
if this doesn't
shake out with Max...
I'm sure we're
gonna be fine.
John and Joel and Max,
they're all gonna
come together.
I can feel it.
Good vibes.
MAX: He won't let
them near it.
Smithson? Who's Smithson?
MAX: I don't own
the property down there.
You don't own the property?
MAX: I own this
and I own that,
which reminds me,
I'm sure you'll be
willing to put up a bond,
just in case there's damage.
I was thinking $75,000.
JOEL: Fuck!
A $75,000 bond, too?
Can I ask you
a question?
Please.
Is Mike for real?
I mean, he's so relaxed.
Michael, yeah,
he's totally real,
so long as
the cash is real.
And the cash is real
so long as John
and Joel are real.
And I guess John and Joel
are gonna stay real because,
between us,
they've already
sold 100,000 tickets.
And who wants 100,000
freaks coming after
them for refunds?
MAN: So Mikey is trying
to sell those six acres.
MAN 2: It's got a lake?
Yeah.
Hey, Dave.
I'll have the usual.
Geez, sorry, Elliot.
I think we're
out of the usual.
Out of the usual?
Wow, that's unusual.
For crying out loud, Elliot.
How could you?
Okay, then I'll try
the waffles.
(EXHALES)
"To ensure three
days of peace and music,
we've left Wallkill
"and are now in
White Lake, New York.
"Certain people of Wallkill
decided to try to
run us out of town.
"Our new site,
it's twice the size
of our original site."
You did this, Teichberg.
You know what those hippies
are gonna do to our town?
They'll be high on drugs.
Robbing us by day
and raping the cattle
at night.
We ought to run
you Jews out of town.
WOMAN: You and Yasgur.
We're gonna boycott
Yasgur's milk.
MAN: Shut the hotel down, too.
(PEOPLE CHATTERING ANGRILY)
MAN: Get out of here,
you hippie.
You're disgusting, Elliot.
You know what, Elliot?
You're not the only...
Elliot! God bless you.
Hi, Annie.
You can't imagine
what happened this morning.
What?
I'm fully booked!
Every room!
Yeah, me, too.
For the first time
since Herb died.
Thank you, Elliot.
You're welcome.
(TIRES SCREECHING)
Hi.
Those motherfuckers
in there wanna
fuck you up, huh?
That seems to be
the sense I'm getting.
Well, you're gonna
have to carve some
fucking hearts out, man.
Fry them on a stick
over a fire pit
and then sit down
and eat them, before
those motherfuckers
do the aforesaid
fucking to you, man!
Billy, can you just stop
with the motherfucking this
and motherfucking that.
Please?
Fuck.
Yeah. Fuck.
This could really
be a down trip.
My brother and his wife,
they're getting
fucking organized.
Then what should I do?
Get fucking
organized yourself.
Rally your troops.
Do I have troops?
Fuck, yeah.
You got your mom, don't you?
She's a fucking battalion.
And the Chamber of Commerce.
This whole thing is
about commerce, right?
Right on!
Right on.
I'm off to HQ.
At ease, men... Man.
Go fry those fuckers.
Elliot!
We were in Wallkill.
Hanging with some friends,
making the scene.
Rapping on each other.
And they said this
is where it's at.
So we rode our
thumbs up here.
Can you dig it?
Elli, help.
It's these two.
They want a hole.
To dig their thumbs.
After they hit each other,
they made a scene
in Wallkill!
What are they
talking about?
Just looking to score,
you know, the magic tickets.
Dad, get the tickets.
To the festival.
(GIRL SCREAMING)
(LAUGHING)
MAN ON TV. Okay, Neil,
we can see you coming
down the ladder now.
ARMSTRONG. Heading back up
to that first step.
But it's adequate
to get back up.
Roger. We copy.
Takes a pretty
good little jump.
Hey.
Hi, Tisha.
What is it?
You've got
a couple of visitors.
Hello? What can
I do for you?
Mr. Teichberg?
Yes.
Here. That's 47 citations.
Wiring, plumbing,
health code violations.
Quite a place
you've got here.
It's humble, but it's home.
Away from home, I mean.
And here's 14 more fire code.
You're way over the
occupancy limits.
You've got five days
to pay up and repair
or else we're shutting
you down for good.
Have a nice day.
What's going on?
Your mother says we
can triple our money.
Three times the rooms.
You're kidding me.
They don't seem to mind.
Honest. These people,
they like it.
SONIA: I'm finished here,
you start on the bunking.
WOMAN: I don't know.
White Lake sounds
better than Wallkill.
Don't ask me why
they call it Woodstock.
Everyone's gonna drive
to the fucking real Woodstock
and be really bummed
when they get there.
DOT's letting us
put signage up.
Just not on the Thruway yet.
But we're working on it.
We're gonna want to run lines
all the way
back to the fence.
MAN: Can you trench here?
No, man. Everything,
water pipes, juice,
all the cables
gotta run aboveground.
I got the
specs from Hanley,
for the speakers.
(CHUCKLES)
That's a lot of juice.
When Hendrix lights up,
there won't be a bird
left in Sullivan County.
Hey, I spoke to Wavy Gravy
and the Hog Farmers.
Wavy?
Yeah.
His real name's Hugh.
He's got 80 freaks,
the Hog Farmers.
They've got a commune
in the desert.
They drop more acid
than Timothy Leary.
There's 80 of them
coming in on a
jumbo jet next week.
Hey, man,
I can't find the
keys to my room.
Ask my mom.
Hey, how's your room?
Fine, man.
Trip tents?
Yeah, where the kids
can come down...
From the trip.
WOMAN: Wait, wait.
What have you got here?
No, no.
Don't put it down there.
He and his people
are willing to work
with you on security.
You know,
they really like your
non-confrontational approach.
You know,
they wanna call it
a"Please Force."
Not sure how Fabbri's
going to like that moniker.
We're still going
to need real police.
(EXCLAIMS)
Hey, Mike,
do you have a second?
I'm just feeling
a little anxious.
Did Tisha tell you about
these code violations?
Hey, Elliot.
Just the man
I wanted to see.
You know,
I'm getting the feeling
that we're really
going to be able to use
your community
relations skills.
My what skills?
Because, Elli,
the rumors are
already swirling,
and we need to
put a local face
on the reality here.
And you, Elli,
are a local face.
I'm a local face, yes,
but about these violations.
There's not a hotel
around for miles that
could pass inspection.
Those inspector dudes?
Don't worry about that, Elli.
Tisha told me all
about those guys.
Just give us the papers.
We've got some
heavy lawyers. Right?
Heavy lawyers. Right.
Because right now,
Elli, I need you
to focus
on the positive message
that we're sending.
You know,
rapping with
the local townspeople,
finding some time
with some of the papers here.
Wait, you mean like
a press conference?
A press conference. Yeah.
Radical idea, Elli.
I love it.
No, actually, you don't.
Me and public speaking,
I can guarantee you,
not one of my strong suits.
I'm speaking from
experience here.
Hey, Michael.
Hey. I want you
to meet somebody.
Let me introduce
you to Reverend Don.
He's helping with
our community outreach
and he'd love it if
you could help him
get to know the locals.
Hi. It's really
great to meet you.
I don't know how
much Michael's told you,
but we're thinking
of putting on
a little free concert
for the local people here,
and we thought it
would be a great idea to
include a scene from
your theater company.
Do you think
they'd be open to it?
Yeah, they'd love that.
But you said it's
for the locals?
Because the play's
very contemporary.
Cool.
Hey, hey, you guys,
the phones are alive.
Mike.
Hey, your dad wants you.
I'll get some paint,
but they're just
going to do it again.
They set foot here again,
I break their heads.
Dad, let me call...
Call who? That little
putz in the green shirt,
he's the son of
that state trooper.
I could boil him
and his putz of
a father in tar.
Just, Dad,
let's just get this painted
before Mom sees it.
Then you can start
warming up the tar.
Thanks.
Put some more of
those in the cooler.
Dad, this is all we got.
You didn't order more?
I did.
And I called Karpen's,
too, for the kitchen.
I asked them all to
bring 10 times our usual.
Well, when they
come tomorrow,
you tell them to
bring 20 times more.
No, 30 times.
Where are we
going to put it all?
These people,
they eat and
drink like animals,
and there's more of
them every minute.
It doesn't matter
where we put it.
It'll be gone in a day.
Yes?
MAN: Couple of Buds, please.
$2. Thank you.
(JUKEBOX DINGS)
You got that
thing working?
Yeah.
Don't touch those wires.
Let's see what
you got to put on.
Nothing much.
(SLOw JAZZ MUSIC PLAYING)
Judy Garland live.
Haven't heard
this in a long time.
It's hard to
believe she's gone.
Actually,
I can believe it.
I met her once.
Wow. Was she fun?
She was brimming over.
(CHUCKLES)
I'm Elliot.
Hey. Paul.
Construction. You seen
the stage we're building?
No.
It's huge.
Wow. Do you want
another beer?
No, thanks.
I've got a thing going
with some Lebanese Red
right now.
Your old man doesn't mind
if we light up in here?
He can't smell.
Too much roofing tar.
(CHUCKLES)
Cool.
More. More, come on.
Okay, okay.
Good. Good, good, good.
$40.
ELLIOT: Ma.
Ma. Tisha says you're
trying to charge extra
for pillows and soap again.
We talked about this.
Don't accuse me!
I got nothing to sell anyway,
not even toilet paper!
Which leads me to ask,
where do you think
all these people
you're renting space to
are going to do
their business?
You've got to stop, Ma.
Enough with the money.
We just paid
off the mortgage.
Think about it!
Can't you just be happy?
What're you doing?
Hey!
No! No!
No shtupping
in the bushes!
Ma, come on.
Come on.
MALE HIPPIE:
Excuse me, when does
the ticket office open?
Not yet! Soon!
Good morning.
You must be the
lovely wife and child.
What's up, Dad?
We were just
telling your pops here
it looks like you
guys are getting
some nice business.
Yeah?
So, it looks like
you can use some help.
JAKE: He's talking
nonsense, Elli.
Something about
exclusive transportation
and security for $10,000.
I get it.
No, you don't get it.
We get it.
You got live entertainment
happening here,
beverages, etcetera.
Yeah. We cover the hotels
around the racetrack in
Monticello. We cover you.
And what if I say
you don't?
Charlie, what do we
do if he says we don't?
You're trespassers.
Get out, or I make
you get out.
Is that so?
You hear this?
Enough with these bums!
(GRUNTS)
Dad, what're you doing? Stop.
Hey, come on. Hey!
ELLIOT: No, stop!
(SCREAMING)
Come on, get...
Christ almighty!
(GRUNTS)
Go on.
Get out of here!
Jesus! You people
are like animals.
Get out!
Get out of my property!
I'll show you!
Get off my property!
Get out! Don't try
to come back here!
Next time we
won't be so nice!
My arthritis is killing me.
I told you not to
stand at the bar all night.
Dad, Ma,
you're superheroes.
(PEOPLE CHEERING)
FEMALE HIPPIE: Far out.
JAKE: You didn't
tell me anything.
How would you
know what I tell you?
You're deaf.
(ROCK MUSIC PLAYING)
Hey, Elliot.
Hey.
What do you think
of the mess we're making?
It's...
Wonderful, isn't it?
It is. Yeah, Max.
I'm just sorry
everyone in town
hates our guts now.
Yours more than mine.
If that's even possible.
Sorry? Hell,
these kids are fantastic.
I've heard more
thank yous and pleases
in the past three days
than I've heard
in a lifetime from
those shmucks.
And believe me,
no matter what they tell you,
they're all trying
to make money off
this thing, too.
I saw Bob charge
a dollar to fill a bottle
with water for
one of these kids.
A dollar?
Yeah, can you believe it?
A dollar. For water. Geez.
FEMALE HIPPIE: Four extra.
MALE HIPPIE: Four.
Yeah.
Elliot. You're
Elliot Tiber, right?
Yeah, that's me.
How can I help
you, Miss...
Vilma.
Vetty Von Vilma,
but you can call me Vilma.
Vilma.
What brings you here?
I'm supposed to
say hi from Steve.
Steve?
From the Village?
Steven?
He's gone now.
Off to San Francisco
with a flower in his hair
on his sugar daddy's lap.
Yeah.
Actually,
my ex-sugar daddy.
Good riddance.
He does like
them mean and rich,
doesn't he, our Steven?
He's very...
Anyhow, he said you might
be starting some sort
of a gay resort here.
Well, resorting as
well as reclining
is my specialty.
And as I was on my
way to visit my
mother in Buffalo,
I thought I'd stop by.
(CHUCKLES)
Look what I stumbled into.
By the way, those clowns
you and your dear
parents chased off...
Not nice people. I know.
I was playing the horses,
if you know what I mean,
over by the racetrack
in Monticello.
Nice bedroom community,
actually,
until that bunch tried to
confiscate my earnings.
You think they'll
be back? Here?
All I can say
is you need help.
What kind of help?
Oh. Um...
That's nothing.
You should see what
I'm packing up here.
My God.
I know.
But keeping to
the subject at hand
for the moment,
you do need some real
security around here.
And you're real security?
What?
Well, you don't look...
Okay, I may be
a grandfather, but...
You're a grandfather?
I married young,
the night before
I shipped out for Korea.
You were in Korea?
Semper fi,
you little prick.
Sergeant, U.S. Marine Corps.
No kidding.
Yeah.
Wow.
That's me with the cigar.
The other one was
the love of my life.
Killed. Sniper.
I went out on patrol,
found the Chinese
pissant who did it,
and broke his neck
with my own hands.
Jesus.
Actually, I made
that last part up.
But I would have
if I'd gotten a hold
of the son of a bitch,
and I'd do it today
if I found him.
Vilma, you're hired.
Thank you.
Welcome aboard.
You won't regret it.
Do you need some
kind of uniform?
I've got uniforms, baby.
Wow.
(HORSE NICKERING)
Hey, Elliot.
She's a beautiful ride.
Great way to
commute to Max's.
That's a nice suit.
It's for the press.
Conference.
Sure.
You okay?
A little nervous.
Got just the thing.
You know, actually,
I'm feeling
a little nauseous.
Hey, grass is a perfect
cure for nausea.
Really?
Seriously.
Well...
Yeah.
It's good shit.
Very good shit.
...and in these next few days
before the concert,
we'll also provide
daily briefings
and we're all here to
provide any follow up.
But without further delay,
here is Mr. Elliot Tiber,
the proprietor of
the El Monaco,
President of the Bethel
Chamber of Commerce,
and a community liaison
for Woodstock Ventures.
Mr. Tiber.
Good afternoon,
ladies and gentlemen
of the press.
Do you have a legal permit
for the concert in White Lake?
There will be a music and
arts festival held here on
August 15th, 16th, and 17th,
part of my ongoing yearly
music and arts festivals
that have made White Lake
the truly international
cultural center that it is.
As evidenced by the fact
that you wonderful
ladies and gentlemen
of the press are
here to report on it.
I have been proud
to be the artistic
director of the festival
in its prior incarnations,
and I hope that...
Yes, but do you
have a legal permit
for the concert?
(RAIN PATTERING)
Of course.
Need I remind you,
I am the President.
I am the President
of the Bethel
Chamber of Commerce.
Would a leading civic
leader such as myself
break his own laws?
That doesn't make sense.
Do you realize
that the police
are now estimating
that perhaps as
many as 100,000 people
will attend the concert?
What will your
people here in White Lake
think of 100,000 hippies
and what they
will do to the town?
My people?
You say my people.
Native White Lakians
cannot be considered people,
you know,
mine or anyone else's.
Can you tell us something
about these free programs
for the local community
happening this week?
Will there be a cap
on the number
of tickets sold,
and how will you deal
with people showing up
without tickets?
You are asking
about freedom.
The very essence
of the enterprise,
of all enterprise,
especially free enterprise.
And freedom
could be considered,
and is often considered,
you know, to be just
another word for being free.
Therefore, there will be
no train to freedom. Train
has already left the station.
How can the music be free
when the people of White Lake
are enchained?
Huh?
If one song is not free,
then all songs are not free.
That is why
we are going to free
all the songs in White Lake.
(WHISPERING)
Any idea what the hell
is going on here?
(PEOPLE CHATTERING)
Wow, Elliot.
You stood strong up there.
That freedom rap, yeah.
That was heavy.
Thanks, Mike. You smell good.
Like an apple fritter.
Far out.
(LOW RUMBLING)
(PEOPLE CHATTERING)
What's happening?
Didn't you hear?
It's free, man.
FEMALE HIPPIE: Come on.
The concert's free.
(PEOPLE CHEERING)
(WHISTLE BLOWING)
Come on, let's go.
Stop. Here.
That's it.
Come on.
Let's go. Let's go.
Come on, let's go.
Dad!
(WHISTLE BLOWING)
JAKE: Let's go.
Come on.
We've got an artist here.
He's been out here
two hours already.
Won't budge.
All right, come on.
Come here. Just wait.
All right. Hold it!
Your dad says
you're a painter.
When did he say that?
I had him give me a tour
of the property, you know,
getting a lay of the land.
He talked a lot about you,
about Brooklyn.
He showed me
some of his favorite places,
the oaks down by the lake.
Nice.
ELLIOT: Wait.
Are you sure that was my dad?
Maybe it was somebody else's?
I mean, he doesn't have
any favorite places here,
he hates it.
He doesn't talk.
I didn't say it was therapy
or anything, you know.
It was just chatting.
Chatting?
His mind must be going.
Don't worry, Elliot.
I'll keep an eye on him.
If he starts to laugh
or smile or anything
suspicious like that,
I'll let you know.
Yeah. You do that.
(BREATHES DEEPLY)
In fact,
I have to go collect his bat,
we've got dawn patrol.
Vilma?
Does my dad know,
you know, what you are?
Elliot.
I know what I am.
That does make it easier
for everyone else,
doesn't it?
After the concert,
we've got tables
set up near the barn.
I understand your mother
is preparing her specialty.
Cholent? Oh, no.
And the Ladies Auxiliary
has made dessert.
DON:
We just have to make sure
somebody rations them.
There's a lot of hungry
kids out there.
Don, I just want to say,
I have a feeling.
Feelings?
Feelings are good.
STEVE COHEN:
Get over to the south field,
find what-is-his-name,
and round up all those...
They don't really
know where to put all
the sunflower seeds.
How many sunflower seeds
did they buy?
can you get into the back of
a triple-axle trailer truck?
I'm not sure. I'm sorry.
We actually have
another meeting...
(INDISTINCT CHATTERING)
Everybody's working
hard for...
Yes. Very hard.
JOEL: Hey, John.
That's him.
That's the prick
who told everyone
that the concert's free.
MEL: Fuck the alfalfa...
Considering that
we haven't managed to
build a ticket booth yet,
can't really
argue with him.
It's incredible.
Knocking down the walls,
and all kinds of stuff.
Well, we gotta make
some space in here, but...
Doris? Doris,
he doesn't... Doris?
He doesn't even know
what a purchase order is.
I'm trying to help organize
moving everybody
from here in the horseshoe
up to the site.
Trucks, trailers,
everything, gotta go.
Gonna miss this place.
Yeah, well,
we'll keep some rooms here.
The one concern is
the big towers
for the speakers.
They're not staying up?
No, they're good. Solid.
It's just that
if there's rain, lightning,
well, might get a little...
A little what?
Electrical.
We're working on it.
Yeah, we don't wanna
fry too much of the audience.
Yeah, that's a good point,
Joel.
Thank you, John.
Hey. It's August.
It's not gonna rain.
Remember, okay?
Rice, bananas,
anything that's gonna
keep them from shitting.
Because I'm worried
about our toilet numbers.
(SINGING)
Now we're together nearly
every single day, singin'
ALL. Do wah diddy diddy
dum diddy do
we're so happy
and that's how
we're gonna stay, singin'
ALL. Do wah diddy diddy
dum diddy do
No, no one stole the car,
I just gotta keep it
for a few days.
Sure, it's legal.
Everything is fine, Mom.
Don't worry. I've met so
many beautiful people here.
Whoa-oh
ALL. Do wah diddy diddy
dum diddy do
Do wah diddy diddy
Thank you.
Hairy Pretzel, thank you.
It's so great that you have
let us share your music
with all your friends
and your parents,
here in white Lake.
Now we would like
to introduce to you
the resident theater artists,
here at the El Monaco
this summer,
the Earthlight Players,
who have adapted
Anton Chekhov's classic,
Three Sisters,
to a contemporary,
happening interpretation,
and they would like now
to share a part of that
experience with you.
Ladies and gentlemen,
the Earthlight Players.
Artifice and imagination!
Truth and fiction!
The players play!
But you, the audience,
you sit and judge.
You sit and judge.
EARTHLIGHT PLAYERS:
But the revolution requires
the roles must be reversed!
(CHUCKLES) The players
are the judges now.
Your revelry must end,
and your souls
will be bared for all to see.
Christ who died for you,
but not for me!
Now we are Christ!
Our nakedness
will reveal your own.
Indecent legions of decency!
EARTHLIGHT PLAYERS:
Fascist pornographers!
Racist warmongers!
Republican cocksuckers!
Indecent legions of decency!
(CAR HONKING)
Fascist pornographers!
EARTHLIGHT PLAYERS:
(CONTINUE SHOUTING)
SONIA:
Put your clothes back on.
(LAUGHS)
Billy. Billy.
Jesus Christ.
DEVON: Racist warmongers!
Fascist pornographers!
Billy!
Get your ass down here!
(EARTHLIGHT PLAYERS CHEERING)
Billy!
(PS YCHEDELIC ROCK SONG
PLAYING)
(INDISTINCT CHATTERING)
MALE HIPPIE:
Everything is gone...
ELLIOT: Annie?
Elliot. Namaste.
Hi, Elliot.
Namaste, dear Elliot.
ELLIOT: Hey, Georgette.
GEORGETTE:
How are we doing?
Hey, Elliot.
Hey, guys.
Hey.
Here.
Thanks.
All right.
Where we going with these?
Barn.
Stan and your theater guy
set up some
medical volunteers.
The combination
of the bare feet
and the brown acid...
Real.
Yeah.
Anyway, I hope you don't mind,
we just were grabbing
everything we can.
And your mom gave me
these blankets.
My mom? Gave?
Yeah. She's cool.
Hey.
ELLIOT: Hey, Dad?
Dad.
REPORTER ON TV.
The New York State Thruway
has been backed up all the way
from the
George washington Bridge
to the Catskills exits,
and from there,
it's basically a parking lot.
Police are now planning
to put into effect
a first-ever
emergency closing of
the entire Thruway.
We go now to John Stevens,
who is in the field...
Ma, you okay?
The nisht-gute....
Evil!
You seen the chicken legs
on some of these hairy people?
Mom, they're kids,
not evil spirits.
You don't know!
They've made all the roads
one-way now, Elli,
one-way just to Max's.
God forbid,
what if your father
should have a heart attack
from all this running around?
He couldn't get
to the hospital.
You're really worried
about him, aren't you?
Him? It's you
who brought this.
How will you live
with the guilt?
(BONGO MUSIC PLAYING)
(PEOPLE CHEERING)
Hit him in the kisser,
hit him in the guts,
nine, ten, out!
(ALL LAUGHING)
Hey. Give me three.
How you doing, Dad?
How should I be doing?
I haven't slept in three days,
my hip is killing me,
and the beer's warm.
So, you're good?
Yeah, I'm good.
Hand me that bottle.
You're ready for one?
I thought you'd never ask.
How you doing, kid?
I haven't
slept in three days,
the beer's warm,
I'm actually not
making this up,
but my hip is killing me.
So, you're good?
(LAUGHS)
FEMALE HIPPIE:
Come on, Elliot.
(PEOPLE CHEERING)
(DEVON GRUNTING)
MALE REPORTER: I'm standing
near the intersection
of Route 17B and 55,
where state authorities
now estimate that perhaps
half a million kids
have already made it
to the White Lake area,
and there's another million
trying to get here
who will just never make it,
putting upstate communities
in an uproar at this major
hippie invasion.
Bob!
What's this all about?
We got the permit pulled,
you idiot! We're shutting
this thing down!
But there's a half a million
people over at Max's.
How do you think
they're gonna react?
That's the same thing
the cops said...
Before they laughed at us
as if we were children.
So we're doing it
ourselves!
Right.
(JAKE GRUNTING LOUDLY)
Hi, Elliot!
VILMA: Come on.
Not so tough anymore,
are you?
JAKE: Come on, you.
MAN 1: Go to hell!
MAN 2: Fuck you, old man!
JAKE:
You get off my property,
you thugs.
MAN 3: You faggot freak.
(GROWLS)
(LAUGHING)
MAN 1: Hippie lover!
(SIGHS)
This is where
we rinse the sheets.
MALE HIPPIE:
Hey, brother.
(SOFT MUSIC PLAYING
IN THE DISTANCE)
You hear that?
It's starting.
Elli,
you should go.
What?
To Max's.
I can't.
You guys would...
We can take care
of things here.
Dad...
JAKE: You go.
Go see this thing.
VILMA: Go.
See what the center
of the universe looks like.
Yeah, sure.
Wow.
OFFICER: Bet you thought
you were just gonna drive
right up to the thing, huh?
Actually, my family,
we own the motel here.
The El Monaco, huh?
So you're the guy
they're all blaming for
bringing all this here.
Governor just declared
this whole county
a disaster area.
Yeah, it's a disaster.
I'm the disaster guy,
officially.
No kidding.
I was looking forward
to just coming up here
and clubbing
a bunch of hippies
over the head.
But instead,
I don't know.
I must be getting
high off the fumes.
Peace, man.
See what I mean?
Groovy.
I think I'm gonna head over
and check it all out.
On foot? It'll take you
all afternoon with this crowd.
Here.
ELLIOT: Thanks.
(ROCK AND ROLL SONG
PLAYING)
(INDISTINCT CHATTERING)
Officer.
What do you say to all those
young men fighting in Vietnam
while you're here
enjoying yourselves?
FEMALE HIPPIE 1: We're waging
peace, man. We're teaching
peace to the world.
REPORTER: You think they're
gonna understand that? While
they're bleeding and dying?
FEMALE HIPPIE 1:
Why won't they...
FEMALE HIPPIE 2:
Find your buddy, girls!
FEMALE HIPPIE 3:
The innocent people
of North Vietnam...
Bombs for peace!
DEMONSTRATORS:
War bombs for peace!
OFFICER: Yeah,
dream on there, buddy.
MALE HIPPIE 1:
Hey, it could happen.
MALE HIPPIE 2:
I know you can do it.
Come on, just for fun.
Okay, thank you.
Thank you, Sister.
SISTER: Peace to you.
MALE HIPPIE 2:
Thank you.
God bless you.
(wOMAN SINGING BLUES ROCK SONG
IN THE DISTANCE)
FEMALE HIPPIE 1:
Come on, burn them, sisters!
FEMALE HIPPIE 2:
Burn your bras and read this!
(MALE HIPPIE PREACHING)
You've gotta join
this demonstration.
MALE HIPPIE:
Stop the pollution.
Keep our rivers clean.
(MALE HIPPIE CONTINUES
PREACHING)
(FOLK ROCK SONG PLAYING)
(INDISTINCT CHATTERING)
(SLOW SONG PLAYING)
(PEOPLE CHEERING
IN THE DISTANCE)
MALE HIPPIE: Hey, man.
ELLIOT: Hey.
Hey.
You look thirsty.
I am.
Thanks.
Have you guys
been down to see
the festival yet?
We're cool,
and we'll get there again.
We got to the top of the hill,
and looked down at the sea,
and the tiny little people
on stage with their waves
of tiny electric voices.
Like ants making thunder,
man. It was cool.
But you couldn't really tell
who was jamming down there.
And we left our trip
in the car.
And the shit
they're passing around
down there, not quality.
Ours is beautiful.
I see
you have California plates.
Is that where you're from?
There, and New Mexico...
And Oregon.
You're from everywhere.
We're from everywhere.
I'm from here.
You're from here, man.
That's so cool.
I guess so.
Man,
you're amazingly from here.
Here, man,
take a ride to here and now.
Eight miles high.
I'm actually
a little afraid of heights.
What the heck.
Hey.
Come on in, sit.
So...
MALE HIPPIE: Yeah?
You sure that was acid?
I didn't really taste any...
It just takes a while.
Hey, let's listen to some
of our own sounds.
(PS YCHEDELIC ROCK SONG
PLAYING)
What? What's that?
Hey, it's okay.
Just breathe.
Hey, it's okay,
just breathe.
It's okay, just breathe.
Just breathe.
Hey, it's okay.
It's okay.
(EXHALES)
Just breathe.
Where are my arms?
Where's my arm?
It's right here.
Just breathe.
Hey. Let's go down
to the ocean.
Let's go swim.
(TIN RATTLING)
Elliot. You look well.
I want you to meet the ladies
from St. Paul's in Liberty.
They made 5,000 sandwiches!
Vilma,
don't exaggerate.
We made 4,000.
Honey, please.
Anything more than one
is a miracle in my book.
My God! Look at him!
Where have you been
all day and night?
How was the concert?
Well, I met some friends
on the way there.
It was great.
SONIA: Are you hungry?
I'm starving.
So I was thinking,
when this is over...
What a mess.
It'll take months
to clean up.
ELLIOT:
We can keep some of these
new people on, right?
We can afford the help now.
And with the place paid off,
maybe it's time
you thought about
some permanent staff.
Some people
to help run the place,
make some improvements.
What are you talking about?
That's why we have you.
I'm just saying. I was
thinking when this is over,
with all the money now,
I could take a trip.
And where did you
get those pajamas?
You're not going anywhere
dressed like that.
(DOOR OPENING)
We've made brownies.
Wonderful brownies.
Very special brownies. Elliot?
We'll take a pass.
Right.
You see, Jake?
That's just like him.
He doesn't want dessert,
but does he think
to ask his mother?
You know what?
That's enough.
You know,
I'm the only one here,
out of hundreds and hundreds
and hundreds of thousands
of people, who's having
breakfast with his parents!
Do you think Janis Joplin's
mom is standing backstage
telling her to tuck her,
I don't know,
her whiskey bottle back into
her pocket or something?
Or Jimi Hendrix's mom
is telling him
to wash his hair?
I'm gonna lie down,
then I'm going to Max's
and I'm gonna enjoy myself.
And you know what?
Go ahead. I'd love to
see you eat a brownie.
You should have two!
(DOOR SLAMMING)
(THUNDER RUMBLING)
FEMALE HIPPIE: Elli!
(INDISTINCT CHATTERING)
(COUNTRY ROCK SONG PLAYING)
BILLY: Hey, Elliot.
Hey.
See you guys later.
(SOFT ROCK SONG
PLAYING IN THE DISTANCE)
Billy?
Man,
I remember this hill.
Remember remember,
or, like, Vietnam
flashback remember?
Remember remember, man.
Homecoming. Senior year.
We fucking
massacred Monticello.
I caught like
three touchdown passes.
Rum and Cokes.
And we fucking tipped
three of Yasgur's cows,
man, right there,
at the top of that hill.
And Shirley Livingstone,
man, right there,
at the top of that hill.
Wait a second.
That was you?
Was.
Is.
And that's
the Shirley Livingstone,
the one who works
at the animal hospital?
Yeah.
We were engaged, man.
Come on, man.
I love this fucking hill.
(PEOPLE CHEERING)
(BLUES ROCK SONG PLAYING)
(WHOOPS)
ELLIOT: Billy!
(YELLS)
I love this hill!
We love this hill!
VILMA:
The prodigal son returns.
Well, you know,
I didn't quite,
you know, go.
(CHUCKLES)
I got it.
I'm happy to see you,
Elliot. Come on.
I want you to meet some
very, very groovy people.
(JAKE AND SONIA
LAUGHING HYSTERICALLY)
You gave them
the hash brownies?
They told me
you said I should.
How many?
Four each.
(JAKE SCATTING)
Elliot! My baby!
Her baby!
My little baby.
My filthy baby boy.
Give Mamma some of that dirt.
(JAKE CONTINUES SCATTING)
(JAKE AND SONIA
CONTINUE LAUGHING)
(SONIA STOPS LAUGHING)
(JAKE STOPS LAUGHING)
(SHUSHING)
Dad.
She got up in her sleep,
walked over there and...
What's with the money?
We've been
depositing everything
that's come in this week.
Where did
all that come from?
Ma, what the hell?
Don't come near me,
you two.
But what...
This is mine.
It's my savings
for 20 years.
It's my savings.
Jesus,
how much you got there?
None of your business.
(MUMBLES)
$97,000.
Dad, did you know
about this?
You think she'd tell me?
You'd have let
the bank foreclose?
Let me put all my earnings
into this place.
And you...
Elli.
Why does it matter?
We're rich now.
(SONIA SOBS)
Elli, I was scared.
Mom.
I've got to
fix your father
his lunch.
(PEOPLE CHATTERING)
MALE REPORTER: Hey, man.
What do you think
of the kids here?
I think it's great.
I got one here myself
and I got one in Vietnam,
and I wish he were
here in the mud.
(MAN ANNOUNCING ON PA)
TISHA: Hey, Elliot.
What?
Just come around.
Stay on the wood.
(GRUNTS)
Yeah,
everything's electric now.
(FEEDBACK SCREECHING
THROUGH SPEAKERS)
What are you up to?
Thought I'd try to see
the concert finally.
(CHUCKLES)
Maybe later.
They can't get anyone
to play right now.
There's too many shocks.
That's a bummer.
How's your day going?
Uh...
Yeah.
No, no.
My family, you know...
Sorry.
It's trivial compared
to what you guys
are going through.
Maybe it's the most
important thing happening
in the whole universe.
How do you know?
I'm pretty sure it's trivial,
you know, in perspective.
Perspective is what
shuts out the universe.
Everyone with their
little perspective.
It keeps the love out.
I'm so tired.
I'm starting to talk like
that swami what's -his-face.
Far out.
Anyway, I'll see you.
(KNOCKING ON DOOR)
Yes?
Come on in.
You're up early.
I couldn't sleep.
Hey, Dad.
I was gonna
come say goodbye.
I hope that's okay.
Listen.
Sit.
A month ago,
I was a dying man.
I would think to myself,
"It's nice of Elli
to come back here
"to tend to a dying man."
Who knows?
Maybe tomorrow I'll be dead.
But now,
I'm alive.
You understand?
No.
It's because of you.
Because of you I'm alive.
And what should I want now,
but for you,
my son, to live, too?
(ELLIOT SNIFFLES)
Huh?
That's not so much to ask.
No, it isn't.
They're all
starting to leave,
the young people.
Who knows where?
They don't even know.
And now you're one of them.
You go.
I'll stay in touch.
I'll be back.
Yeah, sure you will.
Elliot.
(GROANS)
My hip, my...
Elli, that business
with your mother...
Don't worry about it.
No.
Dad, can you just
tell me one thing?
What?
How have you done it?
I mean,
how have you lived with her
more than 40 years?
I love her.
(ACOUSTIC ROCK MUSIC
PLAYING)
Hey, Mike.
Elli, you made it.
Yeah, finally.
It's amazing.
It's beautiful, isn't it?
(BREATHES DEEPLY)
Hey, thanks for calling
and welcoming us to your
international resort, man.
The whole world came,
and now everyone's
pulling together.
Yeah. It's all just like
you said, Mike, isn't it?
Yeah, three days
of peace and music.
So what happens now?
Man, who knows?
Everybody's gotta
chase the money now,
right?
Yeah.
We're all probably
gonna sue each other,
but that's cool.
We'll figure it out.
What about you?
I don't know.
I put all my stuff in my car.
Hey, that's a sign.
If your car moves,
come look me up.
I'm going to San Francisco.
Me and Chip
and some of the guys,
we're gonna help out
with a truly free concert.
It's gonna be
even more beautiful
than this one.
Wow.
Yeah.
The Rolling Stones.
Rolling Stones?
Yeah, Stones.
Beautiful.
(URGING HORSE)
(ROCK AND ROLL SONG PLAYING)
(FOLK ROCK SONG PLAYING)