- You know they're all whores,
right?
Yeah.
All of 'em.
I'm not just talking
about the little skanks
that hang out around your dorm
or your frat or whatever,
but actually every woman
you've ever known
and every woman
you'll ever meet.
Mom, Grandma,
Aunt Ellen.
And the fact that
they're related to us
doesn't make a difference,
'cause at the end
of the day,
given the right
set of events,
they will fuck you over
for the sole reason that they
have a vagina and they can.
- Now, can I get you gentlemen
anything else?
- Coffee.
More coffee and, um,
I'd actually like
some cigarettes
if you happen to have them.
- We don't sell cigarettes
here, sir.
- Fine.
Coffee, then.
And this new one
of yours, Peter.
Jesus Christ.
I mean, you know,
you could have
at least preyed on
a couple high school girls,
get used to the thing.
And if they fuck you over,
well, it's not anything
that a night of heavy drinking
wouldn't take care of.
- She's a good girl, Caleb.
- Mm-hmm.
Tell me
where you met her again?
- No, don't do that.
- Do what?
- What you're doing.
Like you forgot already.
- No, I know where
you met her.
I just mean, you know,
give me all the details,
like we're getting our fucking
nails done or something.
What the hell
is the problem?
- How much further
do we have to go?
- I'm not paying
for your meal
unless you tell me
how you met her,
and I don't think they take
student loan checks in here.
Wow, that was fast.
Come on.
It would be
awful embarrassing,
two grown men, one of them
has to play dine and ditch.
Still waiting.
- I met her at the frat house.
- Yes, I know this part.
- She was
seeing a guy there,
and I ran into her
visiting him.
- Mm-hmm.
And what did the other boys
in the frat house
have to say
about you seeing her?
- How should I know?
- Well, I know, Peter,
and I was on your campus
for 45 minutes.
- She's a good girl.
She just has-
- Hey. Hey, hey, hey,
look, I'm just trying to prove
your dickhead roommate Pierre
wrong.
- Pierre said
something about Emma?
- Don't act surprised.
Pierre?
The kid's a fuckin' dick.
I could tell
before I shook his hand.
It smelled like
patchouli oil.
- If you're asking
if she has a reputation
for sleeping around
amongst those dickheads-
- Well, I guess she did cheat
on her boyfriend to be with you.
It's not a promising start.
- Okay.
You know what?
I'm really not even hungry.
And I told you
my stupid story,
so I'm gonna go wait
in the car.
- Wow.
- Give me the keys.
That's-that's rude.
- Yeah, well, you've been rude
since you picked me up,
so consider us even.
Please give me the keys,
Caleb.
- What do you want,
my keys?
I think they're in here
somewhere.
Ah, that's my lighter.
Oh, that's my dick.
You want to try and open my car
with my dick?
You know, squish it up
against the keyhole?
I don't think
that's gonna work at all.
Oh, here we go.
Check and see if they
have cigarettes next door?
- They're closed.
And they don't
sell cigarettes anyway.
- Well, thank you for that.
- Can I get you
anything else?
- Yeah,
you can warm this up,
and you can maybe
grab my check,
if you find the time in
your precious little schedule.
Fuckin' slut.
- # I had a long #
- Wrong keys, dickhead.
# I had a long,
long dream #
# I had a long dream
about swimmin' #
# Across the sea #
- Are you not sleeping again?
Caleb.
- Yeah?
What?
- How long has it been
since you slept?
- I don't know.
A week?
- How safe is it to drive
with you when you haven't slept?
- I'm not gonna lie
to you, Peter.
It's not that safe.
- Em!
- Hi!
God.
I thought I heard knocking,
and then I saw
your brother's car.
That's-is that your brother?
- Yeah, yeah.
- Oh, hi.
- Hi.
I feel like I haven't seen
your face in forever.
- I know.
- Are your folks awake?
- Oh, God, no.
You know, they're probably
still drunk at this hour.
- Oh.
So should we-
should we go?
- Yeah, oh, can you help me
with that one?
- Oh, yeah.
I'll take this.
- Thanks.
- Caleb, this is
Emma Gainsborough.
- Hey.
- Hey, Caleb.
- Nice to meet you.
Emma.
Gosh, I've heard
so much about you,
I feel like you're famous.
- Okay.
Are you guys
gonna get in, or-?
- Yeah, I just thought
you two should meet
before we all
cram in your car.
- Well, I am so sorry,
your royal majesty.
Next time I'll-
I'll bring the rolls
so you can stretch out.
The fuck
is wrong with you?
- Do you want
the window seat?
'cause it might be
a little more comfortable
since you don't know him.
- Oh, no.
No, it's fine.
- I can, uh,
I can totally hear you.
FYl.
- I'm right here.
I'm, like,
four feet from you,
so if you want to-
oh, you're done chatting?
Okay, come on in.
- Hi-oh.
- This is tough.
You might want to-
just lifting the leg over is-
- Right.
- Wow, you're pretty good
at that.
Whoa!
Ready?
Sorry.
All right, one more,
one more.
Watch this.
Arrr!
Kgghh!
Sorry.
Oh!
- Sorry.
- That was-I usually
put my arm up.
- I thought we talked
about smoking in the car.
- Oh, no, no.
It's fine, honey.
- No, it's not, because
I know you don't like it,
and I specifically told you
not to smoke.
- Okay, okay, I got it.
Take it easy.
- Don't tell me
to take it easy.
- Your parents' home
is beautiful, by the way.
- Oh, thank you.
- Now, do you know
the architect,
by any chance?
- No, I don't.
My parents built it before
my sister and I were born.
- Oh, you have a sister?
- Yeah.
- I told you she had
an older sister.
- No, I don't think
you did, Peter.
The only thing you told me
was not to smoke in the car,
which I forgot.
My mistake.
But nothing about
an older sister,
as far as I remember.
- I told him.
- That's fine.
I don't care.
- Anyway, it's a lovely home,
and, uh...
- Thank you.
- And I would love to know
who built it sometime,
if you're ever talking
to your parents and remember.
- Oh, sure.
- Great.
- Yeah.
- Thank you.
I build homes.
I don't know if Peter-
he probably
mentioned that you.
- Oh, no, he didn't.
- Well, I didn't tell her that
because that's not true.
- I'm sorry?
- You're a construction worker.
- Uh-huh.
- Okay?
- Yeah, I construct homes.
See, the words "construct"
and "build"
are synonymous, Peter.
I don't know
if you don't know that
or if you just
are playing around.
- By asking about
the architect
and then immediately
thereafter
saying that you
build homes
implies that you were
an architect
which you are not.
- Uh-huh.
Okay.
- Are you gonna be joining us
for Thanksgiving, Caleb?
- No, no.
I'm afraid
this car ride
will be our only time
together, Emma.
Unless, of course,
Amtrak decides
to take every yahoo with a phone
seriously
when they call in
a fuckin' bomb threat.
- They'll be running again
by Sunday.
I already checked.
- Let's hope.
- Why won't you be joining us?
Are you working?
- No.
- Oh.
- My dad and I aren't
on the best of terms,
so that's all that is.
- I'm-I'm sorry.
- No, don't be.
It's not a big deal.
Okay, who's hungry?
I could use a cigarette.
- You're not gonna pull up
any further?
Okay.
Well, I guess
we'll be going, then.
- I got it.
Thank you, Caleb.
- Hmm, don't mention it.
- I think that's it.
Okay.
- Oh, hey, you guys,
if you need anything
while you're in town-
a ride,
you want to borrow some money,
a massage,
go ahead and ask that
fucking asshole Donald.
Okay?
- Thanks.
- Bye.
- Do you mind
if I move this stuff?
- Sure, yeah, that's fine.
Just keep chapter seven
on top.
- Chapter seven.
- Thanks.
- Hey, you weren't
kidding there, boy-o.
She's like a little angel.
Dark angel, really, which is
kind of sexier in a way.
- Dad, please, not everybody
is as deaf as you are, okay?
She'll hear you.
- So what?
You think
a young lady like that
doesn't like hearing
how goddamn gorgeous she is?
Shit, you gotta tell it
to 'em every ten minutes.
Boy, I bet she's a tiger
in bed, huh?
- Dad!
I really don't feel comfortable
with you asking me about that.
- All right.
Jesus, Peter.
When did you become
such a stick in the mud?
Jeez, you're like
my old man.
Hey, come on.
I'm just breaking your balls
a little bit.
Come here.
It's just 'cause I'm so damn
proud of you.
You know that, right?
- Yeah, I know,
I know, I know.
Just be nice to her, okay?
- Yeah.
- Leave the compliments
up to me, okay?
- I'll do my best.
- The table's set
if you guys are ready.
- We're sure ready
for you, darlin'.
No, Emma, I can't believe
for one minute
that your older sister
is half as pretty as you.
- Oh, I don't know,
Mr. Sinclaire.
She's awfully pretty.
- Please: Don, Donald,
Donny.
Anything
but Mr. Sinclaire, okay?
- Okay, sure.
- Does your sister dye her hair
jet black like that?
It's very flattering on you
with your-with the blue eyes.
- You know, Emma's at the top
of her class, dad.
- You don't say.
- Mm-hmm.
- What might you
be studying, Emma?
- I'm a psych major.
- Really?
So are we all
as fucked up as they say?
Um...
Uh, I don't know.
Actually, the only thing
we seem to be studying
is why men
hate their fathers
and want to sleep
with their mothers.
- This world needs
sharp women, Emma.
I swear to god,
every time I turn on
the television,
there's a woman
with something to say,
and I'll be damned
if I've seen one of them
I can listen to
for more than five minutes.
- Oh, thank you.
- You're welcome.
- I kn-
Hello.
Hello?
- I can hear you breathing,
Hannah.
I know what your breath
sounds like.
Why are you doing this?
- Either say something
or don't fuckin' call me, okay?
You're torturing me
with this.
You're fuckin'
torturing me.
Hey. Hey.
Look-look at the camera.
Thanks.
- Hey, Caleb.
Caleb!
- What?
- Why are you nailing
that hard?
Are we supposed to be nailing
harder with this one?
Hey, you ever watch
the Spanish channel
that's on your television?
- No.
- You should.
The girls
are wicked hot.
- You just discovered
boners?
Discovered, like,
what it is, what it means?
- No, actually
I was watching, uh,
that creep show girl,
Elvira, when I was little.
She had that long, dark hair?
- Elvira?
- Have you ever seen
her tits?
- Yeah.
And she's, like, 60.
- If you look at the pictures
of her when she was younger,
and I used to watch it,
and I used to think
that I wanted to be
in that show with her.
Like, we could be friends,
you know?
Like, she could take care
of me and stuff
and I could hang out
with her?
- That's quite a fantasy,
J.T.
- Just-can I tell you
the story?
- J.T., do you ever just think
about the shit you say
and-and think, uh,
"Wow, I should definitely
kill myself. "
Do you ever think that?
- Hey, Peter, you sure you don't
want to use my bowling shoes?
- Yes, Dad, I'm sure.
- What, is Andy Rooney
dressing you now?
- Right?
Come on, take the shoes.
They're just
sitting up there in a box.
- Yeah, well, maybe you
shouldn't have gotten
thrown out of the league.
- The league president
is a total faggot, okay?
Now I say one thing,
and I mean,
literally,
one thing as a joke,
and I get thrown out
of the league.
- I'm not a homophobe.
Do I look like
a homophobe?
I love the gays.
I mean, not, you know-
- Yeah.
- Not like-
- Yeah, okay, Dad.
We're leaving.
Go back to your book, okay?
I'll say hello to your
old cronies if I see them.
- At least take my ball.
- Dad, I bowl, like,
once a year.
I don't need a custom
bowling ball.
- Hey, my ball and I were
legends in this town,
and it's your responsibility
to carry on that legacy.
- Bye, Dad.
- Bye.
- Wait!
- # She's my alibi #
# And she gets me high #
# Well, she's a worker
at the grocery #
# And she's to care about
only me #
# Baby, get back #
# She's my 9:00 to 5:00 #
# And she makes me smile #
- Hey, Caleb,
I got you a beer.
Whoa.
Is that Hannah, man?
- No.
- You know, dude,
I think it is.
- No, it's not, J.T.
And you just
shut the fuck up
or I'm gonna knock your
fuckin' teeth out, okay?
- Okay, sorry.
I think it's your turn
to bowl, though, man.
- Take my turn.
I don't care.
- Caleb, it's the sixth inning.
I don't think Rocky-
- It's the sixth frame.
We're in the sixth frame,
J.T.
How many years have you
been playing this-
Here, give me a ball.
Here.
Yeah?
How's that?
Is that good enough for you?
You asshole.
- Do you want your beer?
- Where the fuck
are you going?
- I need smokes.
- He's like a goddamn fart
in a frying pan.
- Hey.
- Hi.
- Hi, Molly, how are you?
- Hi, Caleb.
Good. How are you?
- Can I just get a pack
of cigarettes, please?
- Yeah, um, I got, uh,
I got menthols.
I got, uh-
- It's-anything is fine.
- Whatever? Okay.
- Yeah, that's-
- You're easy, huh?
- Yeah.
- These menthols.
- Okay.
- No, no, no, no, don't-
don't give me your money.
I don't want it.
- Really?
- Yeah, really.
- Thank you, Molly.
- You're welcome.
- I guess I'll-
I'll-
I'll see you around.
- Yeah, I hope.
- Caleb.
- Hey.
- Hi.
- How are you?
- Emma.
- Yeah, no, I know.
I'm-
- Oh, you bowl here?
- Well, it's the only
bowling alley in town, so...
- Oh, yeah.
- Kind of...
- That's true; oh, did you
see Peter over there?
We're in-
we're in lane one.
- I did, yeah.
- Do you want to come
and join us?
- No, you know,
I'm in the middle
of a league match right now,
so I'm kind of-
- Oh.
- It's fuckin' lame.
- But, uh, anyway...
- What?
- Hey, can-
can you tell me why Peter
is all of a sudden,
he's dressing like, uh, like
Mike Wallace or something?
- Is he-is he a Republican
now or-
- Yeah, your dad said something
about that too.
- Well, no, it was nice to-
to see you.
- Yeah.
Good to see you too.
Oh, Caleb, um...
- Yeah?
- Can I maybe bum a couple
cigarettes off of you?
- I thought you didn't
like cigarette smoke
or something.
- Well, actually Peter
doesn't.
I- I smoke.
He doesn't really
know that,
so I kind of sneak a couple
at a time.
You know.
Please?
- Sure.
How many?
- Just two.
- There you go.
- Thank you.
Oh, sorry.
It's just easier
to hide 'em there.
- I don't care.
Oh, and could you
just not tell Peter?
- Yes, if-if-
can you do me a favor
and not tell Peter
you saw me?
- Sure.
- Thanks.
And don't tell Donald.
- Sure.
- Is that okay?
- Good to see you.
- Thank you.
Okay.
- That was some disappearing act
you pulled on us last night.
- Uh, sorry.
- Yeah, well,
don't apologize to me.
Apologize to J.T.
He was like a lost puppy dog
the rest of the night.
He looks up to you,
you know.
- Yeah.
- Hey, look.
You want to prove to everyone
you're an asshole, fine.
J.T. is my nephew.
All right?
He's a nice kid.
He's dumber than rocks,
I know, but, uh,
he thinks you walk on water,
so, uh...
Don't be letting him down
again, okay?
- Sure.
- Okay.
What are you doing
tomorrow night?
- I don't know, Rock.
Are you
asking me out on a date?
- It's Thanksgiving,
you dumb shit.
What are you doing?
- Oh, nothin'.
I don't celebrate the fact
that my ancestors
exterminated
a race of people.
- Well, I do.
My old lady's
a hell of a cook.
Why don't you come over?
- I'd rather not.
- I'm not asking.
Be there around 7:00, all right?
Bring a bottle of wine
or something, okay?
- All right.
- I'm gonna get you fucked up,
and I'm gonna send you home
with my niece.
She's ugly as hell,
but she gives great head.
- I-I-I don't want to know
about that.
- Hmm.
So I'm told.
- Jesus, Rock, just-
- Well, whatever, yeah.
- Take it easy.
- Caleb?
Hi.
- Hey.
We keep, uh, running into
each other, don't we?
What-what are you
doing here?
- I'm grocery shopping.
I think that's pretty much
what everyone's doing here:
grocery shopping.
- No, that's not
what I meant.
I meant, I'm sure Donald
sent you here.
He likes to keep
his houseguests busy,
so it makes sense.
- Are you a big red wine
drinker?
- What's that?
- You like red wine?
- Oh, uh, not really.
It's-
- I love red wine.
- Yeah, me too.
- Hey, are you okay?
- I'm just-
I'm-I'm in a hurry,
and I don't, uh,
you know,
I don't really like it here,
and so I'm trying to hurry.
- Oh, okay.
- Are Donald
and Peter here?
- Um, no.
It's just me.
Are you sure you're okay?
- I'd like to talk to you.
- Okay.
You want to talk here?
- Um, I want to talk
about my brother.
But...
- Okay.
- I don't want-
I don't want to do it here.
- When do you want
to talk about him?
Caleb.
- I didn't want
to do this here,
but I don't know when
I'm gonna see you again.
Look, I don't want you
fuckin' my brother up.
Okay?
- Oh, okay.
- I know you're
a little whore, okay?
You don't fool me with
your flirty little tops
and your fuckin' cliché
punk-rock bullshit, okay?
I know you slept with half
the fuckin' frat guys
at that stupid school
of yours,
and I don't want you
destroying my brother.
You understand me?
He's a sweet kid,
and he's a goddamn virgin,
and I just know that
you're this train wreck
that he's not gonna be able
to get out of the way of.
- How dare you talk to me
like that!
- I asked around.
I asked about you, okay?
I asked about you, and I know
you're a little whore.
Don't try and tell me
otherwise, okay?
Now I am never gonna
see you again.
But I swear to God,
if you fuck him up,
I will dig a hole,
and I will put you in it.
I will kill you, and I will
put you in the fuckin' ground.
I don't care
that you're a girl.
I don't give a shit, okay?
You understand what
I'm saying to you?
You understand me?
You better nod your head
or do some fuckin' thing
so I know that you hear
what I'm telling you.
- Hey.
- Stop.
- Stop, no, don't-
don't come near me!
I'll scream,
I'll scream!
- Wait, wait, wait, wait.
Don't scream.
I just wanted to say
I'm sorry, okay?
So I'm sorry.
- Why the fuck would you
say those things?
Are you crazy?
- No, no, I swear I'm not crazy.
I'm not-I'm not crazy.
I'm sorry I'm crying.
I'm fuckin' crying.
I don't-
I'm sorry, okay?
Just please don't say
anything to Peter,
okay, or Donald.
Please don't say anything
to Donald, okay?
I'm-I'm-
- Don't fuck with me!
Fuck.
Oh, shit.
- God.
- Oh, shit.
Look, I'm a little fucked up
right now, okay?
Just please don't
tell my brother,
and please don't tell Donald
about this.
Don't tell anybody about this!
- I won't, I won't!
Just shut up.
You're making a scene.
- Okay.
Okay.
I'm done.
I'm sorry.
- This is all
really delicious, Emma.
Where did you learn
to cook like this?
- My mother, mostly.
Before she, uh,
started drinking
every afternoon and evening,
she was
a pretty good cook.
- A drunk, huh?
Is she single?
What?
I'm making conversation.
- No, my-my mom and dad
are still together.
They have an arrangement.
- Caleb?
- Whoa!
What the fuck
are you doing out here?
- What am /
doing out here?
- I'm-I'm-I'm leaving now.
- No, no, wait.
I think you owe me
an explanation.
- Okay, I think
you're underestimating
how awkward this is for me.
- You want to tell me
why you called me a whore
at the grocery store?
- You don't want to know
why I'm out in front
of Donald's house
in the middle of the night
with a camera?
- Not really.
- Uh, do you have
another cigarette?
Thanks.
- So?
- Right.
Peter told me that you-
you cheated on your boyfriend
to be with him, and-
well, hearing that, I-
you know, I was cheated on
very recently,
and, uh,
I don't want you
to hurt Peter.
Also, I haven't slept
in over a week,
so there's that.
Literally over a week.
So I'm-I'm kind of,
you know,
I find myself in, uh,
sort of in a-
in a daze between being
asleep and awake,
and I find myself doing,
you know,
strange things.
A small example of that,
the other day,
I actually introduced myself
to a tree.
So, um,
it's not a joke.
You know, suddenly I'm in
the middle of doing something.
I'm talking to somebody
or I'm driving
or thinking about how small
they could make a T-shirt.
I'm sorry.
- I'm not a whore.
- Okay.
- Are you growing a beard?
- No.
Just haven't shaved
in quite a while.
I should probably
get going, so...
- Yeah.
- I think I landed
on a sprinkler.
- Okay.
Okay, time-out.
Just a little break.
- The old man needs a breather.
- Donald?
- Yes, my dear?
- Peter hasn't really
told me anything
about his mother,
and if you wouldn't mind,
would you be good enough
to share with me
a little bit
while we're walking here?
- Okay.
What would you like to know?
- Anything, I guess.
He told me that she died
when he was 12,
and that's all
I really know.
- I don't know how much
Peter really remembers.
He was probably ten
the last time he saw her.
- Oh.
I didn't know that.
- Yeah.
- Donald?
- Yeah?
- If it's okay,
I'd like to hear
a little bit more.
- Is there a reason
you haven't asked Peter this?
- No, I have.
- I don't know if it's-
Okay.
All right, it's not
a happy tale, I'm afraid.
Diane-
that's Caleb
and Peter's mother-
She was having an affair
with another man.
I found out about it,
and I asked her
to leave the house.
I was pretty devastated,
as you can imagine.
When I told the boys
about it, they-
they didn't want
to see her,
didn't want to talk to her
or anything.
You know,
they felt like me.
They felt
they were betrayed.
And then,
about a year later, she-
she was diagnosed
with cancer.
Four months after that,
she died.
It was a pretty dark time
for all of us.
- And Peter never saw her
that entire time?
- Not just Peter.
None of us did.
- J.T., may I ask you
something?
- Yeah.
- Have you ever thought
about hurting someone?
- Sure, all the time.
Remember that night,
drank the pony at Blue Ribbon,
I was getting
fuckin' hammered.
I told you I thought I killed
some dude on my walk home?
- No.
- Yeah, remember when we were
working on the place in Norfolk,
and we were doing
the drywall?
I'm pretty sure
I told you that day.
- No, I totally would have
remembered that.
That is fucking crazy.
- Yeah, maybe I dreamt
I told you.
But anyway,
it turns out
I was blacked out at the bar
the whole night.
Wicked, though, right?
- Yeah.
- You need me to help you put
the drop on somebody?
I'd do it for you.
You know that.
- Nah, thanks, but I've been
thinking a lot
about hurting Donald,
which I suppose
if I were a teenager,
it would-
it would be normal
or healthy even,
but you know,
I'm getting old, boy.
You know, I saw my brother's
new girlfriend last night,
and it occurred to me
that I'm becoming
that fucking cocksucker.
- Your dad wants to fuck
your brother's girlfriend too?
- No.
Well, I don't know.
Maybe.
- Thanks for coming over
last night, asshole.
My niece had to fuck
one of my cousins.
Real awkward.
- Sorry.
Oh, hey, uh, Rock,
I did get some sleep
last night, though.
- Wow.
- 45 minutes' worth.
- Did you hear that?
Hey, should we give him
a medal?
Did you dream of Venus,
play with your penis?
- Love him.
- Hey, Dad, how are we
doing over there?
We're getting pretty cold.
- Keep your shorts on there,
pencil dick,
'cause the masterpiece
is almost done.
- Masterpiece.
He's burning the shit
out of whatever he's cooking.
- Voilà.
- Nicely done.
- Come on, you just gotta,
you know, scrape off the-
- The scorched black cocoon
you've created
around the chicken breast?
- Emma, I assure you,
it'll be delicious.
- Oh, no, it's great.
Thank you so much, Donald.
- You're welcome,
my dear.
- What was that?
- One of
those damn raccoons.
- What the hell
is he doing?
I'm sorry.
- Your dad has a shotgun.
- Jesus, Dad,
what are you doing?
Dad!
Dad, have you
fucking lost it?
- Don't shoot!
Stop! Don't shoot!
Stop!
- Dad, it's Caleb!
- Stop! It's me!
- Put the gun down!
- Stop shooting the fuckin' gun!
- Are you okay?
- Yeah, yeah, I'm fine.
- Why were you in the trees
just now?
What happened to your lip?
Hey, Donald.
- Were you hit?
- No, no, I'm fine.
I think you caught
a little bit
of the Lang's chicken coop,
though.
Actually, that's
a pretty good range on the, uh,
what is that, your.870?
Yeah, not bad.
- Yeah, pretty good.
Are you losing your hair?
- No.
I don't know.
Well, maybe a little.
- Yeah, well, you couldn't
blame me for that.
You know, you get that
from the mother's side.
- Okay.
- Wait, Caleb.
Why were you
in the trees just now?
- Oh, uh, just, uh...
I was just taking
some pictures.
- Trespass on my property again,
I will shoot you.
- Better work
on your aim then.
- I think you really,
really freaked Dad out.
Like, you guys go eight years
without speaking to one another,
and then you just appear,
literally, out of a puff
of smoke in the backyard.
I mean, dad could have
killed you.
Maybe the single most bizarre
thing I've ever seen.
I'm going to the restroom.
Don't eat my fries.
- I won't.
- What are you doing?
- What do you mean?
- I know you're taking pictures
of me, Caleb.
- Okay, I know
what you're thinking,
and you're wrong.
I don't have feelings
for you.
I don't even like you that much,
if you want to know the truth.
- I don't understand this.
You're-you're semi-normal
one second,
and the next second,
you're a complete lunatic.
I barely even know you,
Caleb.
- What do you
think about me
now that I said
that I don't like you?
- I don't know.
I don't know.
You-just stop, okay?
- Okay.
- Please, just stop it.
- It's just weird.
- I know it's weird.
- I don't want to have to
discuss this with Peter.
- Oh, well, you're not
gonna do that.
- I will if I have to.
- No, you won't.
- What-what do you-
what do you want from this?
- Just don't break his heart.
That's all.
You're so beautiful.
Don't break his heart,
please.
- I think
that you need help.
Stop it!
Stop!
- I started sleeping again
since we started, uh,
conversing.
I've been able to sleep.
I can't explain it.
- Oh, shit.
- Are you gonna be needing
a cigarette tonight?
Yes or no?
Oh, my God,
these are good.
Mm!
- Hi.
- Why are you guys so quiet?
- Hmm?
- Were you talking about me
when I was gone?
- No.
- Huh?
- Oh, hey, are you guys
gonna need a ride
back to school on Sunday?
I probably don't
have to work, so-
- Are you seriously offering
to give us a ride right now?
- Yeah, sure.
- Well, you kind of acted
like I needed to give you
my firstborn
to pick us up
in the first place.
- I know.
I must have been
in one of my moods, you know.
- Uh, well, the trains
are running again,
so you know-
but thanks anyway.
Hey, what did you say
happened to your lip?
- Oh, you don't
want to know.
Excuse me.
Peter?
Can I talk to you
for a sec?
- Uh, yeah.
I'll just-I'll see you
inside, okay?
- Okay.
- I just wanted to, uh,
talk to you about something.
- Yeah?
Well, what is it?
- Emma.
Are you serious?
Like, you should be
fuckin', like, dead right now,
like, with buckshot
in your chest,
and-and-and this is still
what's on your mind?
- Yeah, well,
this is important to me, man.
And I just think,
you know...
- I think you need
to be careful with her.
I'm serious.
I catch her looking at me,
and I don't know.
I just, you know,
I just wanted you to be aware
of it, that's all.
- I think that's
in your head, Caleb.
And I think
I would have noticed
something like that,
you know?
- Hey, you know what?
I hope it is.
I really do.
- You haven't noticed at all
the way we look at each other?
- What do you mean?
- I mean,
I think we're in love.
Oh, sorry, but-
What?
You're-you're not serious,
are you?
- Yes, I'm fucking serious.
- Why would I make that up?
- Oh, that's hilarious.
- She wants to-
- She wants to?
- I'm-I'm a virgin, okay?
- I know.
- Yeah, well, she wants
to take my virginity.
So we're gonna-
anyway, it-
I'm in love with this girl.
- Are you sure about that?
- Yeah.
I'm sure.
I'm sure about how I feel,
anyways.
- Well, have you told her?
I mean, have you-have you
told her how you feel?
- No.
But I want to.
And I think this is-
I think I might do it
on this trip.
I think this-spending time
like this together,
it's-it's good for us,
you know?
What the hell's the matter
with you?
You look like
you're gonna be sick.
- Oh, no, no, no.
I'm just-
I'm just really tired
right now.
I'm-I'm really
happy for you, Peter.
I guess I was wrong
about her being a whore.
That's terrific news.
- Uh-huh.
Thanks, Caleb.
- Sure.
Uh, hey, Peter?
You know I love you,
though, right?
Like, I've got your back, or
whatever they're saying.
- I'm serious.
- Yeah, yeah, yeah.
- I'm serious, you know.
- Thanks, Caleb.
- You know, um-
Never mind.
I'll talk to you later.
- Yeah, sure.
- Your dad told me that
you never saw your mother
in the hospital
when she got sick.
I told you
all about my parents:
their drinking,
my panic attacks.
You don't have anything
on me.
- What my dad said is true.
Except that Caleb did see
my mother before she died.
He was the only one
to see her,
and he and my father
haven't spoken since then.
- Have you ever been in love
with the idea of someone?
- Idea?
I don't know what you mean.
- Okay.
Say there's-
there's someone in your life,
and you know you can't
be in love with them.
You don't really know them.
Maybe you know
that you're-you're-
you're not really
right for them.
No, you know that whatever
it is you're feeling
is really just an attraction
towards an image
of that person
you've created
in your mind?
- I don't know.
- No, of course.
I'm sorry.
You were probably
molested as a child.
Were you molested as a child?
- What?
- Molested, you know.
- You have no right
to ask me that.
- Oh, right.
I fuck you in the ass
for 50 bucks,
but you get
bent out of shape
when I inquire
about your past.
That makes a lot of sense.
You know what? Fuck this.
I'm out of here.
Sorry I said that.
That was really,
really rude, okay?
Also, I-I didn't tip you
very well this time.
Have a good weekend.
- Oh, shit.
- Emma.
Hi.
Hey, um, don't-
don't be frightened, please.
I'm-uh,
I just wanted to
try and apologize to you
for kissing you earlier.
I realize now
how inappropriate
that might have been and-
Ugh!
I don't know
what I was thinking.
So you know, I won't be
coming around here anymore,
I can promise you that,
okay?
Whew!
God, this has just
gotten silly, hasn't it?
I mean, look at me.
I sleep in my freezing car
all night,
just with the hope that
I'd be able to see you...
To apologize to you.
Anyway,
I've been acting childish,
and-and-and-and
that's all I wanted to say.
All right?
Really, that-
that's it.
I'm, uh, I'm-
I'm done.
Do you think you-
you might attempt
to accept my weird apology?
- Sure.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
- Great.
Okay.
I feel better.
So I guess it's-
Good eve, m'lady.
All right.
- Caleb.
- Yeah?
- I'm locked out.
Do you know of another way
in the house?
- Yes.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I, um-
there's an old trick.
I'm sure I could still do it.
It's around the corner here.
It's right down these steps
over here.
Well, you're not exactly
in perfect garb for this.
How-how about
I go in first,
and I'll just-
I'll pull you in?
- Okay.
- Yeah.
- I don't
ever want to see you again.
Do you understand me?
Ever.
Okay.
- All right.
What the fuck is this?
- I think I may have to quit,
Rocky.
I'm not a good person.
- Well, I know that,
but don't you think we could
choose something
a little less dramatic than this
to get the point across?
- I'm gonna take
the rest of the day off.
- Jesus, you're a piece
of work.
- If you have to fire me,
well, that's okay.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
- You all right, Caleb?
I've never seen you
throw a hammer like that.
Have you fucked
your brother's girlfriend yet?
- No.
But I want to
very, very badly.
Very badly.
- Then what are you
so bent out of shape about?
I want to fuck
tons of chicks.
- Fuckin' assholes.
- You want to fuck
tons of...
- Fuck you!
- You know you want it.
- Oh, yeah,
she wants it.
She does.
- J.T., excuse me
a minute.
Let's see here.
- Yeah.
That's what I wanted.
- Oh, hey, bros.
Hey, listen, I have
a quick question.
Do you guys like listening
to shitty music
while you're butt-fucking
or after?
- Get him, you fuckers!
Well,
she's leaving tomorrow.
I'll probably never
see her again,
so thank fuckin' Christ.
I just wish I could get over
this strange compulsion
to protect Peter,
you know?
Because-
and the only way I know
how to do that
is to-
to hurt him.
- When I was a kid,
my pa used to beat me up
pretty good
if I messed something up.
He made me cry a lot,
but it made me tough,
you know?
- Mmm, no, no, no.
Up a little bit.
No, over a little.
Ooh, shit.
Fuck.
I'm sorry.
- No, it's okay.
It's okay.
- Almost, right?
- Yeah.
- Fuck.
- # Ah, ah, ah #
# Ah, ah, ah #
# Ah #
# Sleep don't visit #
# So I choke on Sun #
# And the days
blur into one #
# Bags under my eyes #
# All the things
I've felt and done #
# Sheets are swaying #
# From the old clothesline #
# Like a row
of captured ghosts #
- # Welcome home #
# Ah, ah, ah #
# Ah, come home #
- Your face.
- I know.
Go up to my old room,
take off all your clothes.
Now.
- # All my nightmares
escape my head #
# Bar the door, please #
# Don't let them in #
# You were never
supposed to leave #
# Now my head's splitting
at the seams #
# And I don't know #
# If I can breathe #
# Ah, ah, ah #
# Ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh #
- Ah!
Shh!
Shut the fuck up.
- Shh!
- I haven't seen these photos
in eight years.
- You didn't keep any with you?
- No, I did.
I just-
I moved out
in a hurry, so...
- Why were you
the only person
to see your mom
in the hospital?
Your dad, Donald,
he told me,
and Peter told me
a little bit, and...
I was really close
with my mom,
but I couldn't bring myself
to speak to her.
I wouldn't answer her calls.
I- I just-I shut her
out of my life completely.
She got sick
not long after that,
and when she went
into the hospital,
I started really pushing Donald
for information,
and it all just hit me.
He's totally full of shit.
So I just went straight
to my mom in the hospital,
and she told me that Donald
had been fuckin' around
on her for years,
and it finally got bad enough
that she just
packed up and left.
She didn't think Donald
would be vindictive enough
to take her fucking boys
away from her, you know?
- Why didn't you tell Peter?
- Well, he-
he was
12 years old, so I...
You know...
If I didn't know any better,
I would have thought that-
I don't know.
I would have thought that, uh,
it was your first time
or something.
I don't know.
It was...
I got a-
I don't know.
- No, no, no, you-
- Right?
- I'm sorry.
- You-you're not-
you-you-you-you-
okay.
Oh, I gotta go.
- Hey, wait, wait, wait.
Where are you going?
Caleb.
- Peter's in love
with you, okay?
It's my brother.
I'm sorry.
Fuckin' shit.
- Pretty sure I told you
I'd shoot you
if I saw you
on my property again.
Yeah, I guess you didn't
take that seriously.
- Not really.
- Did you just fuck
your brother's girlfriend?
Of course you did,
you piece of shit.
Well, are you gonna tell him,
or should I?
- Oh, no, you're not gonna tell
him a goddamn thing, Donald.
- Of course I am.
Jesus, he's my son.
- So?
I'm your son.
I'm your son, Donald!
I'm your son!
You left me,
you remember?
'cause I fuckin' found you out.
Why don't you
tell me something?
Why don't you tell me
how much of a fucking coward
you have to be
to erase your son?
- Oh, hey, hold on a second.
Come on,
I tried to reach out.
I found out
where your place is,
and I tried to come over
a couple of times.
- I've lived less
than two miles away from you
for more than eight years, Dad.
You were my fuckin' hero.
- No.
No.
- Peter.
- Hi.
- Who'd you think
it was gonna be?
- I thought-I thought
it was gonna be you.
Sorry.
- Are you okay?
- Yeah.
- You're not gonna tell him,
not ever,
'cause if you do,
I'll tell him your secrets,
and he won't ever
speak to you again.
I know you don't
want to die lonely, Dad.
- You look kind of sweaty.
I was having a bad dream.
What?
- Oh.
- Did-did you
want to sleep in here?
- Yeah.
I was just-
I was just thinking,
do you think
we could try again?
Well, thanks, Dad.
It was an experience,
as usual.
- My pleasure.
You two are sweet
as sugar together.
- Thank you very much,
Donald, for having me.
- Okay.
- Well.
- All right.
- Peter, could you-
hang back just for a second,
will you?
- I'll meet you inside.
- Okay.
- I don't know
where to start.
I haven't been
a perfect father.
I want you to know
that I know that.
I've made mistakes,
some of which were
unavoidable.
You know,
I can't really be
held responsible
for those, but...
What I'm trying to say...
You know,
you're old enough now
to know that sometimes
people do things that-
that they know are wrong,
but they-
they just do 'em anyway,
'cause-
'cause to do
the right thing
might be too painful.
And also...
I love you.
And I don't say that enough.
We don't say that enough.
I mean, I'm not-
I'm not-
I'm not blaming you,
necessarily.
Just, you could, you know,
you could say it more if-
I'm just saying,
you know?
Okay.
All right,
get out of here.
- # All of my dreams #
# They all roll on by #
- I love you.
I'm sorry.
I shouldn't
have said anything.
- No, no, no, no,
don't be sorry.
- What?
- # And hidden past
the business sense #
# As water lilies
over streams #
# Rivers browse
coffee beans #
# Pistol visions
in my hands #
# I want to see my blood
across the sand #
# Morning always
looked like you #
# And from my window
the only view #
- You want to come in?
- Yeah, sure.
- # As you walk away
not lookin' #
# Ooh, ooh, ooh, ooh #
# All of my dreams #
# My life spent awake #
# In the dark of my veins #
# Oh, nothing can stay #
# I continue through
a backlit world #
# Where the willows bend
like long black curls #
# Down your face from life #
# Through the kinks
in your spine #
# From the last thing
we spoke #
# To the very first line #
# Love is something that we
couldn't help but do #
# That something
turned to someone else #
# Somebody new #
# I just love to love #
# And you love to cry #
# I meant it
through each second #
# That we said good-bye #
# And I came up
past a station #
# Where the floors
are all blue #
# And somethin' 'bout
the way it looked #
# Reminded me of you #
# It might have been
how far I've come #
# So I dropped a match
until the floor was gone #
# All of my trains #
# I let them all go #
# Then I lit the thread
across the station door #
# Kentucky straight,
I hit the floor #
# The station
tousled up in flames #
# But I could only read
the bottle's name #
# And I weaned its breast
and turned it dry #
# Like the wake of summer
from July #
# And got up and tripped
over my knees #
# Which caved in
at the slightest breeze #
# Morning always
looked like you #
# All of my trains #
# I let them all go #
# I let 'em all go #