Where does it come from?
This quest, this need
to solve life's mysteries,
when the simplest of questions
can never be answered?
Why are we here? What is the soul?
Why do we dream?
Perhaps we'd be better off
not looking at all.
Not delving, not yearning.
That's not human nature.
Not the human heart.
That is not why we are here.
How's he doing?
- I'm sorry. Did I scare you?
- No.
No, I just... I keep having
these amazing dreams
every time I close my eyes and...
...never mind.
He likes me to read him the stock page.
Has he been conscious at all?
No.
Been a week now. I think he's close.
A couple more days, maybe.
You know I don't know
what he'd do without you.
- You got a real gift.
- Just doing my job.
No, you're like a son to him.
No, that would make us
like brother and sister.
Might be... might be a little awkward
if I ever wanted to ask you out.
I'm sorry, that was...
That was inappropriate.
No, it's sweet, it's...
I'm dating somebody.
Yeah. No, really, it's OK.
I need to change his IV.
I'm sorry, of course.
Man is a narcissistic species by nature.
We have colonized the four corners
of our tiny planet.
But we are not the pinnacle
of so-called evolution.
That honor belongs to the lowly cockroach.
They say that man uses only
a tenth of his brain power.
Another percent and we might actually
be worthy of God's image.
Unless, of course,
that day has already arrived.
The Human Genome Project
has discovered that tiny variations
in man's genetic code are taking place
at increasingly rapid rates.
Teleportation, levitation,
tissue regeneration.
Is this outside the realm of possibility?
Or is man entering a new gateway to evolution?
Is he finally standing at the threshold
to true human potential?
I'm sorry. I'm out of time.
I know, I know, I'm beginning to sound
like my father. I can't help it.
You know, they can fire me
too, if they like,
but there is something to it,
Nirad. As crazy as it sounds.
What is it?
It's your father.
He's dead.
How?
Driving a taxi in New York City
is a very dangerous job.
The wrong fare, the wrong time.
We may never know what really happened.
No, I spoke to him two days ago.
He was convinced someone was following
him, trying to steal his research.
He died because of his theories.
- That's crazy.
- Is it?
The man left his family,
discredited his career, to chase wild
theories halfway around the world.
Where are you going?
To his apartment, to get his papers,
his research.
He was this close
to finding the first of them.
His Patient Zero, he tracked him
to Queens, New York.
Mohinder, listen to me.
Your father was my
colleague and my friend.
A respected professor,
a brilliant geneticist.
But he had clearly
lost touch with reality.
I've followed in his footsteps.
My thesis is based on his research.
Yes, you always wanted his approval.
And now you're telling me
that it was all for nothing.
I'm telling you to let go.
I need to know why he died. I need to
know that it wasn't all for nothing.
And then I need to finish
what he started.
Hello?
Yeah, yeah, I'm at his place now.
No, no, no, he left everything behind
but his computer.
Research, the map.
Yeah, let's get a team in here
to bag and tag everything.
I gotta call you right back.
Pervert!
Time to get up, Micah.
Micah.
Micah!
Micah. Micah.
What?
Damn it, Micah, don't do that to me.
Do what?
Just you need to be
careful. All right?
And I don't want you talking to
any strangers, do you understand?
I'm just working on my computer.
The logic board was bad,
so I had to build a new one.
A new one...
Did anyone ever tell you you're the
smartest little man on the planet?
You do. All the time.
What's this?
It's a pinhole camera. It's for the eclipse.
The moon's gonna cover up the sun today.
We're supposed to look at it at school.
Speaking of which, you need to go
get ready. Can't be late. Not today.
Mom, I'm already dressed
and I've packed my own lunch.
That's what I've been doing this morning.
What about you?
Hey, don't get smart with me.
All right, I've been working to pay our bills.
Yeah, that's why they turned off our gas again?
Go grab your stuff and
wait by the back door, OK?
- Why?
- Just do it.
Mom, what's going on?
Never mind, just keep your voice down
and stay close to me.
Camera ready?
Yeah, almost! Hold on.
This looks like 70, 80 feet.
This is so unreal.
OK, I'm good!
OK. Oh my...
Oh, my God.
Oh, my God. Claire?
Claire!
This is Claire Bennet and
that was attempt number six.
You get out here, yes?
Yes, sorry. Thanks.
Mr. Linderman, I'm gonna have to call
you back in five minutes, OK?
Thank you.
I'm late. I've got a fundraiser and a
drinks meeting. What is it?
It happened two more times. Sometimes
I'm falling, sometimes I'm flying.
- Sometimes you're in 'em.
- I don't have time for this now.
They're not just dreams, Nathan.
Hold this.
I thought they'd go away, but they're not.
Jim, I need this back by 6:00, please. Thanks.
This morning when I got out of bed, my
foot hovered before it hit the ground.
Hovered. For a split second,
like I was... like I was floating.
I'm telling you, I think I can fly.
- These all are "Undecideds"?
- Mmm-hmm.
Tell you what, you think you can fly?
Why don't you jump off the Brooklyn Bridge?
See what happens.
Maybe I ought to start with something
a little lower first.
- Just like learning to walk.
- You're serious.
Oh, I'm serious.
You need to snap out of it, Peter.
Go see a doctor, get some drugs.
But do not pull a Roger Clinton
on me man,
I'm eight points down in the polls.
Look, this isn't about you, all right?
Look, something is happening to me,
and I have this feeling
that you're the only person
that's gonna understand this.
Why the hell would I understand that
you think you can fly?
Because you're my brother!
Mom, look, I can't talk right now. I've got...
What?
I'll be there in 10 minutes.
What'd she do now?
- She got arrested.
- Arrested for what?
Shoplifting.
I'm so depressed.
What? What are you talking about? Why?
I mean, I mean, besides the fact that it
was so gross that I almost fudged myself,
this is the single coolest thing to happen
to this town in like, 100 years.
Not if nobody finds out, it's not.
Why'd you want me to tape it?
I have my reasons.
I still can't believe you asked me.
You stopped talking to me
in like, 6th grade.
It's safer this way.
Why? 'Cause I'm not popular,
so no one would believe me even
if I did tell? Which I won't.
Something like that.
It's not like you're not gonna be
popular anymore.
Popular?
Who said anything about being popular?
My life as I know it is over, OK?
I've got the Bishop game
next week, SAT's in October,
homecoming's three weeks from today,
and I'm a freak show.
You're being a little
dramatic, don't you think?
No, I don't think.
I have busted, like, every bone in my body,
stabbed myself in the chest, I've shoved
a two-foot steel rod through my neck,
and I don't have a scratch on me.
What do you call that thing sticking out?
Great.
- Just give me the tape, OK?
- Sure.
I can give you a ride on my handlebars...
...if you want.
That's OK, I'll walk.
Look, thanks, OK?
I'll talk to you in front of people
at school tomorrow.
Promise.
- What do we have?
- Three clear.
- Give me a count.
- All clear.
How the hell did they know we were coming?
Railroad schedules from the
Nuclear Regulatory Commission.
Routes for transporting
nuclear material. Right.
Not much else. Couple of notes here,
mostly Arabic.
Except for this.
"Odessa." What the hell
is this, a name?
Oh, it's a town in Texas. Odessa.
What's that?
You asked me what Odessa is. It's a town
in Texas. And a city in Russia, I think.
What are you talking about?
What do you think? CIA or FBI?
No, she's dressed too nice for FBI.
Saw the test scores got posted this morning.
Don't worry about it, man.
Not everybody's a test-taker.
Who wants to be on SWAT anyway?
Too dangerous.
You all right, man?
What're you doing here, son?
You're not authorized to be in here.
Wait a minute.
Shh!
Don't shoot. Don't... Don't shoot!
Now, the train is registered to the
Nuclear Regulatory Commission.
And there has been no official statement,
yet, as to what was in the car.
But judging by the amount
of security around here,
it's pretty clear it was
something very valuable.
Reporting live from Odessa, Texas,
I'm Laura Lancaster.
I want a lawyer.
You lead me to the rest of your cell,
I'll think about it.
Until then, no one knows you're here,
which means no one will know if you're not.
You found him, didn't you?
You found the engineer.
He's here in LA.
Where is he?
This is LAPD jurisdiction.
We need to take him into custody.
He stays here till I tell you he leaves.
Who's the engineer?
Amid Halebi.
Saudi national with a PhD
in Nuclear Physics.
Was 20th terrorist on 9/11, until
he didn't show up for the main event.
Turns out, he fell for an American girl
he'd met a few months earlier.
September 10th, 2001,
he went off the grid.
And they tracked him here?
He brought the girl back to bury her.
She died of cancer. Funeral was yesterday.
He's back on the grid.
Let's see if the Amazing
Karnack here has some answers.
Who is he?
Matthew Parkman. He's eight
years on the force,
no commendations, no disciplinary
issues. He's undistinguished so far.
You, come with me.
Help me understand. How did you know
he was in there?
I don't know. I don't. I just did.
If you know where the engineer is,
I think you better tell me.
- The what?
- You recognize these?
Switching codes for rail transport.
Top secret Nuclear Regulatory routes.
Nuclear material, nuclear devices.
Meaning: anyone with these codes
could wreak a lot of havoc
if they decided to send two trains
down the same rail line.
But you don't know anything
about that, do you?
No, ma'am.
I see in your file here
that you've taken the exam
to advance to the SWAT team three times.
- Yes, sir.
You realize that there are
physical requirements.
I can...
I can lose the weight.
How does that make you feel, son?
Flunking that test that many times?
...Embarrassed.
I guess... angry.
Angry enough to do something about it?
Take revenge in some kind of way?
You think I have something
to do with this guy?
- Do you?
- I'm telling you the truth. I...
I heard his voice.
Do you have some place you gotta be?
It's my wife, yes. I have a meeting...
At a what?
At a therapy session.
It's couples counseling. We're...
We're having some trouble at home.
This guy's worthless.
Yeah, I was real sorry
to hear about your father.
He seemed like a good guy.
Man, I thought I was a slob.
They were here, too.
- What?
- Nothing.
I got a guy who can clean this
up for 100 bucks.
No. It's all right. I'll take it as it is.
We rent by the week.
I'm gonna need to know you can afford it.
I have a job.
Doing what?
Driving a taxi.
I'll get you an application.
Your son is a very intelligent boy.
Gifted, actually. That's not the issue.
His father's not around,
and sometimes I think he could use
a bit of a stronger hand, you know?
I work nights a lot,
but we can both work harder.
It's not about the work.
The truth is, I just don't know
if this school is the right fit for him.
But he's made friends.
I'm sorry.
- He's on the soccer team.
- I'm sorry.
I wrote a check for $25,000
to get him into this snob fest.
I was told that that's what it took.
That's on top of the tuition.
About the tuition. Your last
three checks have bounced.
Fine, take it out of the 25 grand
that I gave you.
That was a donation. And it was
very appreciated.
Well, I want my money back.
I want my money back, now.
That money went to the capital
campaign for the new wing.
- It's already been spent.
- Then unspend it.
I'm sorry.
We could maybe discuss an extension
of the money that you owe, but...
I want my money back.
That's not possible.
Come on, baby, let's get out of here.
You're too good for this lousy school.
Mom?
Leave me alone.
For God's sake, Ma.
Are you OK?
They dropped the charges.
I have to fill out a form. No big deal.
No big deal? I'm running for Congress.
Do you have any idea
what this is gonna do to me
if it gets out, with our family's past?
What could you possibly need so bad
that you had to steal it?
Never mind, I don't wanna know.
- Socks.
- Socks?
Dad left you a fortune. What are
you thinking?
You know, it's been one ridiculous
stunt after another with you
for the last six months. Dad's gone,
just get over it.
You know what? Leave her alone.
She's OK, that's all that matters.
Thank God Mom's fine. She's a
criminal, but thank God she's OK.
Next thing you know she's gonna be
telling us she's a crack whore.
I gotta keep this out of the press.
You know what? Just get out of here.
Go worry about your image,
I'll handle this.
Yeah. Good. I gotta make sure
this stays buried.
- Thanks a lot, Mom.
- Mmm-hmm.
What were you thinking?
I just wanted to feel alive again.
Nathan only cares about himself.
Your father was the same way.
Alpha dogs, both of them.
You, in the meantime,
for all your selflessness,
and sitting with dying people...
What? You're gonna retire on what you make?
Maybe I'll shoplift my socks.
Don't get smart.
When you put everyone else
first, you end up last.
You always put Nathan first,
he took advantage.
Yeah, it wasn't you that was just
pushing him right out in front of me?
He takes up more space than you.
Demanded more attention.
And besides, it's not my fault,
you allowed it.
He's my brother. I love him.
Love is overrated.
He loves me, too. I know him.
We've always been close.
Rose-colored glasses.
That's cruel, Mom.
Look, since Dad died, I know you've
been feeling free to speak your mind,
but it wouldn't hurt to edit
yourself, every once in a while.
I'm sorry if the truth hurts.
I'm just saying you hero-worshipped him.
And those feelings were never returned.
You're wrong. It's biological,
and I can't help it, we're...
...we're connected.
I never told you this, but when
Nathan had his accident,
I knew it.
We all got the same call.
No, I'm saying before the call,
like he was telling me, 300 miles away.
I woke up, and I knew that he'd been hurt.
I hate it here. She doesn't even
have any books to read.
Baby, I'll be right back,
I'm just gonna go and
pack up a few things.
We should really go see Dad.
What good would that do?
He could help.
He should know that
someone's trying to hurt us.
Your dad's not in any position
to help us right now.
Look, I made some mistakes,
I admit it.
Mom, what'd you do?
Hey. I need you to know that I would
never let anything happen to you.
I promise.
Mom, why'd you look at yourself
like that in the fish tank?
- How long?
- Just a couple hours, tops.
There's some ice cream in the fridge.
Go ahead.
- What happened?
- I went to see Linderman.
- How much?
- Thirty.
You gambling again?
No, it's just bills.
And I used the rest to get Micah
into private school.
They didn't know what to do with him
at public, and I just...
I needed them to think
that we had money.
From the mob?
Hell, Niki.
You weren't born yesterday.
I'm just two weeks overdue.
I mean, I thought that I could
handle it, OK? It's just...
- I'm under a lot of stress right now, OK?
- Gee, I wonder why?
I feel like I'm kind of losing it a little bit.
I'm seeing things.
Like?
Like I keep feeling like
someone's watching me.
Yeah, Linderman wants his money back,
so he sends some mouth-breather
that's gonna put you in the hospital.
No, it is someone else.
It's someone that I can't see.
Does this make any sense to you?
No.
I'm sorry, you know what?
But I'll tell you what does...
I shouldn't be telling you this.
No, no, let me tell you
what does make sense.
You need to come up with that 30
grand plus interest, now.
Or you gotta run.
Watch him.
All right.
Hiro.
Cool, huh?
How hot do you think it is in there?
Turn on the camera.
Scotty! Scotty! Come on!
Take it easy, you're all right!
I'm OK, I'm fine!
Take it easy.
There's no burns.
Get going!
One, two, three, four, five, go.
One, two, three...
I missed you, Amid.
Our bond is too strong
to be broken by a woman.
We are bound by our beliefs.
I don't believe in anything anymore.
We trained together, we prayed together,
went on haj together, we're still brothers.
You flatter yourself.
Everything you planned is coming to pass.
The computer virus got us
the NRC switching codes.
It's all happening right now.
We derailed the train
in West Texas two hours ago.
We have the device. When we get
the plutonium,
we'll meet up in Idaho next month.
We just need you to assemble it.
What makes you think I would do that?
We started this together,
we need to finish it together.
Allah forgives you, so do I.
We can't do this without you.
It's because of her, isn't it?
I killed someone I loved.
I killed my own wife.
I will not kill anyone else.
What are you talking about?
She died of cancer.
I read the obituary.
When they bombed our camp in Pakistan,
you and I buried 20 children that day.
We dug their graves with our own hands.
Put flowers on them, cried, said prayers.
Just because you found love, doesn't
make the rest of the world stop suffering.
People don't respond to love.
They respond to action.
I'm sorry!
There was a big bust this morning.
Can we still make it?
Sure. Six minutes ought to be plenty
of time to face our marital problems.
And you're the one that
wanted to do this, remember?
No, I wanted this for us, OK?
You're unhappy, that's a problem.
Oh, right, it's my fault.
No, I didn't mean that.
I didn't pass. Again.
If you think that makes
a difference to me, then...
I never put any pressure
on you to move up.
I don't care.
I just want you to be happy for once.
I want to be where the action is.
I've told you this. I'm not
gonna retire a beat cop.
People get their dreams, why can't I?
We've been together 11 years, Matt.
I've made my dreams come true.
How long are we supposed to wait for yours?
Why don't you just tell them the truth?
Yeah, that's a great idea.
I'll just walk in there and tell them
I can barely read.
I mean, half the words I see backwards,
the other half I can't even see...
Lots of people have dyslexia, Matt.
It's nothing to be ashamed of.
I'm under so much stress
right now, honey, you've no idea.
Yeah, well, so am I.
Actually, I think there's something
wrong with my ears, my hearing.
Well then, go to a doctor.
No, honey, listen to me.
I'm hearing, like, voices in my head.
Like a crazy person... telling you what to do?
No, no, it's more like thoughts.
I'm hearing people's thoughts.
You know what, Matt, I have to go, OK?
I'll see you at home.
No. Please, listen to me.
- This is...
- I can't stand it anymore.
You suffocate me.
What are you doing?
Hello? It is 2:30 in the
morning. Who is this?
You've been looking for me.
Yes. Yes.
Thank you for returning
my call, Mr. Sylar.
How did you find me?
Mr. Sylar? Anyone there?
Using the Human Genome Project,
I created an algorithm that mapped
and traced chromosome changes in...
It's very complex to describe in layman's terms.
I'm sure you have lots of questions.
Oh, I have questions,
lots of questions.
Am I good or evil?
Are we cowards or heroes?
Does God even know the difference?
Saint John of the Cross said there
are two sides to a man's soul.
These two are at war within all of us.
Has God abandoned me, Professor?
I know how confusing this must be,
but you need to know that you are not alone.
There are others. How is it
manifesting itself for you?
Manifesting itself? That's good.
I have so many questions for you.
Can I meet you somewhere, someplace safe?
There's someone following me, so...
No, I'll find you.
Don't worry.
And what time does that one leave?
And it takes, like, what, couple hours?
Well, can I just buy it
there at the station?
Who are you talking to?
Nobody.
Great, I'm going down to the corner for
a pack of smokes.
You wanna come?
I'll be right back.
It wasn't easy, Nathan, but consider it gone.
I know I owe you big on this one, Tom.
I'm not gonna forget it.
Yeah, I won't let you forget it.
- Thanks.
- Sure thing.
Mom's rap sheet is now officially buried.
It only took half my political capital
to pull it off.
Why can't she get herself a hobby
like a normal person?
They were married 41 years.
It's a plea for attention.
She's lonely. Give her some time, will you?
I don't have time.
I got eight days to make up ten points.
I need all the help I can get, which
is what I wanna talk to you about.
I wanna offer you a job.
- A job?
- Yeah.
I trust you.
You're good with people.
I need a coordinator to help organize
the volunteers,
and you got nice guy instincts,
I could use that.
I'm a shark, Pete, everybody knows it.
And it's starting to
show up in the polls.
I bring you on, and it kind of reflects
well on me, you know what I mean?
Yeah, all right, so I make you look good.
That's a new one.
No, it makes me look like I put family first.
I mean, I know that sounds self-serving,
but this is for you, too, right?
You've got to think of your future.
- Why do you do that?
- Do what?
Even try to make it look like this has
something to do with me?
You didn't hear anything that I
said earlier today, did you?
That bit about how you can fly? Yeah. I did.
I'm gonna pretend for both our sakes
you didn't say anything like that.
I'm trying to do the right thing here.
Look, I already have a job.
Yeah, watching old people die,
now there's a career.
It's not cute anymore, man.
The dreamy kid, sitting in the back
of the classroom, staring out the window?
It's time for you to grow up.
Look, I cast a big shadow, Pete, I get it.
Life isn't fair.
But there's nothing I can do about that.
I'm trying to do the right thing
by you here, OK?
I don't want your pity.
Hey. Corner of Center and Canal, please.
Wow.
Solar eclipse.
Yeah, yeah, I wonder
if it's gonna be total.
Not here, no.
Some other part of the world, yes.
A global event.
Makes one appreciate just how small
our planet really is.
And we're all quite small really, aren't we?
What's your name?
Mohinder.
I'm Peter.
Let me ask you something, Mohinder.
Do you ever get the feeling
like you were meant
to do something... extraordinary?
I'm driving a cab, you may have noticed.
No, I'm not talking about what you
do, I'm talking about who you are.
I'm talking about being special.
Yes, we are all special.
That's not what I meant.
Some individuals, it is true,
are more special.
This is natural selection.
It begins as a single
individual, born or hatched,
like every other member
of their species, anonymous,
seemingly ordinary,
except they're not.
They carry inside them the genetic
code that will take their species
to the next evolutionary rung.
It's destiny.
Hey. Hey.
I can't believe you just left like that.
Yeah, I know, I was there.
You saved that dude's life, he was OK.
Welcome home.
Get over there. Fifty grand
is a lot of money.
Fifty?
It was 30. Even with interest...
Mr. Linderman wants to be nice about this.
You should have read the fine print.
Look, I have a son.
I'm all he's got.
Mmm.
Please, I can get you the money.
I'll tell you what I'm gonna do.
I'm gonna make you a little
business proposition.
You make, what, 40 bucks for every
20 minutes you take off your clothes?
Well, I'm gonna give you a chance to
lower your debt a little.
And see where it goes from there.
Come on.
Come on, show me what you got.
Lift up your shirt, baby.
Oh, look at that belly.
Smile for me.
Is that what you want?
Ah, yes.
What's the matter, baby? You just
started getting good here.
What's the problem, baby?
I said, what's the matter?
Screw you.
Screw me?
Nathan Petrelli. He served his
country in Bosnia.
Hey.
Oh, God. What? The silent treatment?
Oh, boy.
Isaac?
What the hell is wrong with you?
Isaac.
OK, stop.
What... What, are you crazy?
Clearly.
I don't even remember painting these.
- I was high, OK? I lied to you.
- Damn it.
I've been chasing for a month.
Well, then, get yourself back into a program
and make it stick this time.
These are fantastic.
No! They're evil.
What are you talking about?
What am I talking about?
You know what I'm talking about?
You see this?
Suicide bombing in Israel.
I painted it three weeks ago.
Yeah, so?
So? That's this morning's paper.
Look at the number on the bus.
This happened yesterday.
Yesterday.
It was just a coincidence. You were high.
For all you know, you could have
painted it this morning.
No.
This is what I painted this morning.
Something's wrong with me.
OK, we'll get you some help. OK, Isaac?
I tried that, twice. There's only one way left.
And you know it. You can't go
cold turkey, not alone.
I mean, let me help you, please.
No!
I'll drag you down with me,
I swear to God, I will.
Just leave me alone.
Get out of here!
Now!
Manifesting yourself. That's good.
Ten percent of nothing is nothing.
Jerk should be grateful I even signed with him.
It's not like I don't love her.
I just got horny, that's all.
Love isn't a pie. There's enough to go around.
In the quietest of places, in
the smallest moments,
God is within me always.
Captain.
Captain. Captain, I got to talk to you.
I can find out where they are.
- Where who are?
- The rest of the cell.
What are you talking about? How?
The same way I found him. I just...
I just have to ask him.
And I'll need a translator.
It's gonna be in Arabic.
- Arabic?
- Yeah.
If he knows, I'll find out. But...
there's a condition attached.
Hi, this is Niki. Leave me a message.
Niki, if you're there, pick up. Niki, look,
please tell me that you have Micah,
because he's gone, along with
300 bucks from my purse.
Just call me, OK?
Thanks.
Where to, my friend?
JFK, please.
I'm going home to my family. These
business trips are wearing me out.
Suresh, huh?
I'm sorry?
Your name.On your llcense, there.
That's Indian, yes?
There was a Professor Suresh at the
University of Madras, a geneticist.
Interesting theories.
Don't think he's teaching anymore.
But you wouldn't know anything
about that, would you?
Probably lots of Sureshes
where you're from.
Like Smith or Anderson.
And then Carla had the nerve to tell me
he's not breed-worthy.
Like he didn't win five all-breed rallies,
two regionals.
She says he doesn't look
sexy enough to breed.
Can you believe it?
It's just not true, Mr. Muggles.
It's not true. He's a little stud muffin,
that's what he is.
He still humps my leg when I watch TV.
All right, enough about Mr. Muggles.
What'd everybody else do today?
Doug and I saw this Mexican guy.
A homeless dude, on our way to school.
We thought he was dead, but he wasn't.
I thought Dad was coming home today.
Well, I was gonna surprise you.
He finished up early, he's coming
home tonight. Isn't that great?
Just in time to read
my report card.
So what about you, Claire,
do anything special today?
I walked through fire and I didn't get burned.
What the hell is that supposed to mean?
God, you're so crazy sometimes.
Lyle.
I think I know exactly what you mean.
Oh, here I am, talking dogs again.
And you go and say
something really profound.
We come up against all kinds
of fires in our lives,
and when we test ourselves
and face our fears,
we usually don't get burned.
You are very wise, sweetheart.
Whatever it is you did, I'm proud of you.
And so is Mr. Muggles.
He's just so proud of Claire.
Aren't we? We're proud of Claire.
Yes, we're so proud of Claire, aren't we?
She's the best.
Hiro.
Hiro!
Oi!
What are you looking for?
Morphine.
What for?
I need you to come
with me someplace.
Where?
You'll see.
Look, there's... There's something
I need to tell you.
Now that is gonna have to wait.
No. Look, I need to tell you
about this, OK?
I need to stop living for other people.
My whole life I've had no idea
what I'm supposed to do,
what I'm supposed to be, if I
even have a destiny of my own.
I promise you we will
talk about this later, OK?
But right now I really
need you to come with me.
You're a nurse, you can give
out a shot, you can help him.
Help who?
I thought we could go to the movies
this Saturday,
maybe try on some shoes
at the new mall in Gardendale.
Sure.
I love you, Mom.
But?
No buts. I just...
I just wanted to tell you that.
Now you think I'm trying to be
your best friend again, admit it.
No.
It's all right, we can go to the
movies together. It's no big deal.
I just miss you, that's all.
I wanna be your mom, I wanna
give you advice.
But I don't wanna push you away.
I want advice, I do.
I won't push you away, I promise.
I just don't think you should be so
worried about fitting in all the time.
About being so popular.
I don't want to see you
make mistakes like I did.
I wanted to be someone more
interesting than I am.
You are interesting. You breed
show dogs. Whose mom does that?
No, I wanted to hitchhike across Europe.
Study art. Fall in love with
some... poetry-quoting Frenchman.
Not that your dad isn't
wonderful, but my point is,
you should know who you are
and know that it's enough.
'cause who you are is special.
About that.
There's something I need to say.
Something I never talked about 'cause
I thought it would upset you and Dad.
Sweetheart, you can say
anything to us, you know that.
I think I'm old enough for you
to tell me who my real parents are.
Of course you are.
Honey, I'm home.
Your father.
Hey, honey.
Bad, Mr. Muggles. No.
- I'm glad you're home.
- Oh, me, too.
I have such a headache. I slammed my head
getting out of a taxicab.
Hi, Daddy.
Hey, baby.
I'll ask you one more time.
And only one more time.
Are you in?
You found me seconds before I died.
How is that possible?
Fate.
Fate...
Maybe I was not meant to die.
And maybe she was.
Allah is merciful.
He always has a plan.
He has a plan for you, Amid.
You'll help us.
It's your purpose.
Bring me a glass of water.
The device you stole...
you'll need more plutonium.
How do you know that?
And not just plutonium.
You'll need enough P-235,
enough beryllium mixture,
and you will need a lot more
to take out your target.
- A lot more.
- Where do we get it from?
Untie my hands.
Six months ago, I woke to something extraordinary.
An ability.
A curse.
Where it came from? I don't know.
But now,
I think it might be my purpose.
I can emit 45,000 curies of radiation
from the palm of my hand.
Enough to give cancer to those I love.
Enough to detonate a five megaton
thermonuclear device.
Turn around! Get against the wall!
Get against the wall!
Get against the wall, now!
Now, damn it! Move it!
Hey, get your hands where I can see them.
Amid!
Matt?
Hello, New York!
You sure your ride's coming?
Yeah, I'm sure.
You be careful, son.
Sylar!
I'm just saying it's impossible, OK?
Nobody can predict the future.
I saw it with my own eyes, Peter.
Isaac? I brought someone here to help.
He's a nurse.
Isaac.
Isaac?
Maybe he went out. I don't know.
Isaac.
Simone!
Oh, God.
OK.
Oh, my God. Isaac?
He's alive. Call 911.
- I need a tourniquet.
- What have you done?
Yeah, I'm at 215 Reed Street, number 7.
I need an ambulance here immediately.
Someone has cut off his hand.
No, no, he's conscious. Just barely.
I know. Listen, could you just come?
Did you find something? I think
there's some towels in the sink.
OK, baby, it's OK, they're sending
an ambulance right now, OK?
You just hang in there, OK?
We have to stop it.
- Oh, baby...
- We have to stop it.
This quest, this need to solve
life's mysteries.
In the end, what does it matter
when the human heart
can only find meaning
in the smallest of moments?
They're here. Among us.
In the shadows, in the light. Everywhere.
Do they even know yet?
All right, I'm here. Now what do you want?
Peter?
I've been up here all night
thinking about this.
Thinking about my destiny.
What are you doing, Pete?
It's my turn to be somebody now, Nathan!
Come on, Peter, quit screwing around!
Peter!
Peter, hang on.
How did you... You're flying.
You're flying!
I don't know.
I don't know. Oh, God.
- Peter.
- Nathan!