It is only a test
an artist in martial arts
a challenge that can cause
true skill.
It's a test of life and death ...
The test of courage,
the will and pain.
Fans here at Empire Stadium
are standing.
How to welcome the fourth round of
of this fight here
the Ultimate Challange '98,
Revelation,
Joust deodorant submitted.
How to welcome the fourth round of
of this fight here
the Ultimate Challange '98,
Revelation,
Joust deodorant submitted.
Believe me, these two certainly transpire.
You're right.
Are you kidding?
The Hammer just struck again.
warrior DEATH
Come on.
A cavalcade of hits sfărâmătoare bone
be their tools.
Come on.
Come fight with me.
Mamma mia, I can not believe what I saw.
I saw the greatest comeback
Lazarus from here.
Listen to the crowd.
It's simply deafening.
- Unbelievable.
- Get up.
Wolf Jackson trouble.
Jackson just sent the Hammer
back to the floor.
All Jackson has done here
is to exploit hip.
He wants to give him over the head
if this situation is to escape criticism.
Incredible turn of events.
He did it again.
It's back to his feet,
Hammer hitting him on the ground.
What happens?
Jackson gathered his inner strength.
The referee is blocked.
Wolf Jackson wins by knockout.
What incredible turn of events.
Wolf Jackson just snatched victory
from the jaws of defeat,
making it a superlative way.
Just put the floor on one
of the best fighters in MMA.
That is, Stan. Wolf Jackson is one
of the most promising fighters
that I saw
mixed martial arts.
He smashed every opponent
Why I stood in the way
and now hang about
fight for heavyweight title
the champion, the legendary Rainerio Isandro.
And that struggle written all over years
when talking about Isandro,
talk of a kind
whose life story reads
as a script in Hollywood.
When he was only 14 years
was already involved
in the streets of his homeland,
Argentina.
He became the youngest world champion
mixed martial arts history.
We speak of a kind
who do not yet tasted defeat.
And I understand,
is present here tonight.
Winner by technical KO ...
Wolf Jackson!
Wolf, can you tell us your thoughts
struggle?
How could such a return
in the fourth round?
Hammer is good fighter,
but unfortunately,
have fought a good guy tonight ...
with me.
Someone has to give a lesson type.
Do not worry about it.
Tell us what is for you.
I tell you what follows.
I want the title.
No, honey.
The rumors are true.
Here 'Isandro.
He's way to the ring.
I want to fight with this man ... Isandro.
- Isandro, Isandro, Isandro.
- What? I will go down.
- Low. Accept the challenge.
- To do it.
You will be challenged.
You will be broken.
- S do.
- I agree.
You promised me that it was over,
I'll walk away from this shit.
Just one more fight.
Wolf has long wanted a piece of me.
I will give him a chance.
Why? to come home to me
face torn
or head end, or worse?
Look, this deal saved my life, right?
He taught me self-esteem.
In fact, if I'm going to retire,
to teach the torch in the ring.
We still owe a fight.
Ray, Ray, hello,
guy, Wolf, is absolutely huge.
I will make a fortune the next battle.
Even if we do lose a fortune.
Your confidence is overwhelming.
Come on, kid. You only fighter
known and never lost a battle.
I have yet met any fighter
was not lost a fight.
I do not want to offend you,
but sooner or later
an end to your luck.
Statistics do not lie.
My manager, ladies and gentlemen.
Thank you very much.
Girls, girls, come.
These girls work near my office
and I promised an autograph.
You paper or ...
I guess not.
Two of the biggest fans.
You may be able to write a letter.
Thank you.
Nice. Both are scholarly
in nuclear energy.
- Very good.
- Thank you, ladies.
See? I told you.
Thanks, Ray.
What the hell was that?
I'm just fan.
Hey, Russ.
- What are you doing love?
- Okay, man. How are you?
Well.
Remember my beautiful wife, Kira.
Sure. It's a pleasure.
Listen, I want to pass on the office
Wednesday.
The guys at Nagano Investments
want to make an action movie
to be broadcast only on mobile phones
and it will be the most talented man.
Are you interested?
- I know, that ...
- Of course you are interested.
Will look great on a screen of 2.5 cm.
How about, come Wednesday?
You bet.
Come home, Ray.
Here, May is one thing
you should do.
You must arrange things
in order to Wolf.
- What, are you crazy?
- Not now.
It will take just a moment.
Isandro.
What?
Good job.
And you did a good job, buddy.
Oh, you were both great.
I've almost convinced.
You know, become better.
Not already handed Oscars.
Approaching a fight.
Need to feel hatred.
Hate sells tickets.
No problem. You have to ask you something.
I hate to do it.
What?
Can I have your autograph
for my boy?
00:08:16,176 -> 00:08:18,144
- My autograph?
- Your autograph.
She loves you, man.
You have to be hurt.
Believe me, I have no idea.
Here, lad.
In honor of your love.
You think I have beautiful eyes?
00:08:58,685 -> 00:09:01,984
If you think you have beautiful eyes?
Where did all these questions
crazy?
Just ask.
Well?
I do not know. I never ever seen.
You are such an asshole.
Come here. You gonna learn to dance samba.
Samba? There are tango dancer.
No, no, no, that I learned
at times yesterday.
- Well, look at that.
- Okay.
Do so.
One, two,
and third, I spin it.
So. I can see again?
Steps?
No, no, that little twist
you made it.
- Twist?
- Yes.
So.
You want to do that?
- Stop.
- No answer.
- Do not answer the phone.
- You must respond.
Hello.
Dude, are Gus.
Gus, what do you want?
I just received a call from someone
who want to do advertising
at a energy drink.
- Really?
- I said that interest you
for half a million dollars
and said, yes.
This is fantastic.
- Come on.
- Kidding.
No, seriously.
God.
Come, come.
Thanks a lot, right?
So I want.
I just received a huge endorsement.
How?
In this and following my
second fight,
not we should be worried about money.
You said you have still a struggle.
No, no, no, I said
still struggle with Wolf.
- Yes.
- After fighting withdrawal in Vegas.
- No, no, not what you said.
- I owe him that.
Look, I think perhaps the two struggles,
That's then and I will withdraw
and we can do anything you want.
We can dance all day if you want.
And then this is?
And you leave forever?
Are you the only thing in this world
What really counts for me.
So what do you think?
What do I think?
Yes, what do you think?
Want to know what I think?
I ...
that trouble you, sir.
What is love?
I think I saw someone at the window.
On the roof?
Perhaps a child.
Should call the police?
- Where are you going?
- In the next room,
the phone.
Well, I come?
No, wrong. Stay here.
What the hell is happening?
Honey, where is your phone?
It's in the bag, where they always leave.
Run, run, run.
- Ray!
- Kira!
- Move it, move out.
- Ray.
Let's go.
Kira!
Ray, help me!
Ray.
You understand the idea, boxeorule.
Do not fight with fists against weapons.
If you could see the look on his face.
Calm down, calm down.
Nobody gonna hurt,
if you cooperate.
You know what I mean?
Comprende?
Want to move than the head
to know that you understand
fucking English?
Bravo.
Now I know, communicate.
Lift it.
96 beats per minute ... impressive.
Someone we do not like very much.
I am sure you are confused
about this.
I will explain.
Follow me.
Jesus, look at that?
You are a very lucky man.
You want to see it.
Jesus.
Lift it.
I just injected your wife
a small capsule.
This capsule contains
a very powerful neuro-toxin,
very deadly.
In a few days to start
to dissolve in its blood flow
and one to be hurt.
And then it will be increasingly worse
and then die.
Bastard, why do you want? Money?
Money?
No, no, you do not want money.
You know what I want.
Do not suggest
00:19:06,826 -> 00:19:09,818
to go to the police.
It's only one antidote to this,
so I keep him with us.
What?
It will be our little secret.
Good luck.
Bon chance.
Take care.
Help me!
I knew someone would come.
I know that you are you.
Wolf, what are you doing here?
Sorry.
Wolf, what the hell is wrong with you?
Why do this?
They took the boy.
They say it kills.
- Who?
- Fight with me.
Listen, you find him, I promise.
Not one of us must die.
We can not kill between us, okay?
That's the only chance you have a son.
Fight with me. Be.
Are you a better fighter than me.
You should kill me for my boy.
No.
You must kill me.
Kill me.
Bravo.
I removed his hat.
I saw some ugly fighting in my life,
but this surpassed them.
Easy, easy, easy.
I will not be the only one who dies
tonight.
I would remember this, if I were you.
Congratulations.
You passed the first round.
You know, the next two days
you will fight
with some of the greatest fighters
martial arts world.
The rules are ...
Well, I'm not rules.
Each fighter has to fight,
and each must fight
until death,
without exception.
What happens if I lose?
If you lose, you die honorably
and your friends and family
will be arranged for your life.
What does that mean?
It means he will receive the sum of 5 million.
So see?
Are not so bad.
But if you cheat,
or fail to behave honorably,
will be killed
and they will not receive anything.
Who the hell are you?
Who the hell are they?
My name ...
s Ivan Mikhailov,
for you.
What you get from this?
These fights are broadcast live
to certain privileged individuals
worldwide.
No need to say,
make large bets that the gentlemen.
So this is a show for the rich?
In a manner of speaking.
But it is much more than that.
It is an opportunity that you did not receive a
in 100 lives.
This happens when the world is,
the sand Coliseum
until today.
And you, my friend ...
You were born for this.
I saw anger
of you waking up.
No one is really alive
until death face to face.
You were killing
like a duck to water.
Bravo.
Welcome.
Now we belong.
Kira.
Kira, darling.
Thank God you are alive.
I did not know if they ...
I feel terrible.
Why are they doing this?
I do not know.
Going to die, Ray?
No, you die.
I will call my coach.
We will go to the hospital.
He knows more about medicine.
No.
What's this?
Just follow me.
I will not I let these people
to hurt you.
I promise you that, baby.
Eat this time, kid.
What?
Nothing.
I'm fine.
You must go.
You choose.
What is this, Rainerio?
I wonder
who will have to kill next.
Hello, sir Isandro.
My name is Anka.
I will look after you
in preparing your match tonight.
Can I offer something refreshing?
Why am I here?
Mr. Mikhailov me informed
that's a very important meeting
this tonight.
You will be treated
with any pleasure you could want.
Hello.
I am here to make you feel
comfortable as possible.
I can help you feel great,
Turn to your deepest desires
and passions
body and mind.
What about my wife?
You have a chance to start a new life with us.
I love my life as e.
Winner of the fight
I will give
over 30 million
and could choose to have us all
that company
until enough of us.
I do not think you will tire of me, Rainerio.
Believe me, Rain.
- I trust everyone.
- It hurts.
Why not finish the crap
and tell me what you really?
As you wish.
You must be very in love
to reject you, dear.
I can stay with failure,
dredges.
Clean garbage.
Prepare it for battle.
I heard that you killed the Wolf.
Look, we both
together, OK?
Same and you've told Wolf
before you kill him?
I will kill you, Rain.
They took family.
I will kill you, Ray.
All right. You have only dreamed.
- I dream?
- Yes, all right.
- How ama get here?
- I brought her here.
I thought you were dead.
I have to go before I call
to fight again.
to find out who is behind
all of them.
Ivan can not do this alone.
It must be someone
you all know it.
If they return? If you looking for?
We seek at all times.
Follow me on me.
I will find a way to protect yourself.
Fights Galaxy Incorporated,
struggle to make you,
number one.
Gentlemen, welcome to the family.
Welcome to the future of MMA.
You will not be disappointed, believe me.
Go. Take a look at this.
Look at them.
- Rainerio, how are you?
- Not too good.
Okay, okay, okay,
why not come on here?
What happens?
We hope to be able to respond
this question.
- What do you mean?
- Have you ever heard
a guy named Ivan Mikhailov?
- Yes. Why?
- Last night I was wracked house
of a group of trained assassins.
My wife was injected
with a time bomb that will kill.
Jesus, who the hell is that?
Bring it here. You learn together
who do this, right?
I know what will.
You were the police?
I can not. I can go to the police.
I need to know who do that.
I think that whoever is in power,
has serious ties to the military.
I do not know anyone of that kind.
Someone trying to get into MMA.
Everyone wants a piece of the Galaxy.
You know that.
But, come on, otăviri, right?
Blackmail, murder? You know what?
We need to calm down.
Let's finish this.
You are very angry.
The hell that is. And it should be, too.
When did you last talked with Wolf?
Probably there in Vegas.
Well, is dead.
What?
I was forced to kill
each other.
Left, right, strike.
That's right, now knees.
Left knee, right.
must be seriously hit.
Must have a fucking party time.
What the hell are you talking about?
What the hell do you mean speak?
You smoking drugs or something?
Biggest battle is coming
Your Career
and nobody knows where you were.
You did not answer the phone no.
Do not you ever trained
over two weeks.
A lot of shit happened.
I was worried for you.
You must go hell out of here.
Are you into trouble.
- Are you kidding?
- I look a fool?
- Jesus.
- Look, it forces me to fight me.
Kira will kill, if he will.
What do you do? What?
Talk to me.
Well, you know everybody
of town.
You must have heard something.
I hear some rumors, you know ...
some fighters from Russia, Brazil,
a guy named Chang, Lang, Bang ...
Kang Lai?
Yes. You know?
It must be a master ninja.
S good?
They say it best.
Find out who are the others.
Try to talk to them.
Warns him.
Do what you know, right?
I gotta go now.
How to keep a link?
I keep one. You gonna find me.
Keep guard up.
Yes and so do you.
I said it was Rainerio.
He is behind all this.
He has the most to obtain.
But I can not believe that would do that.
I mean, Andre,
always has been our friend.
Are you awake.
The show must continue.
That car should.
Stay here.
Take care.
Andre, what happens?
Why do not you tell me?
- We need to talk.
- We have what to talk.
Wait. I do not want to fight with you.
Andre, stop.
Please.
Okay?
You know I never would have done worse
your brother. You know that.
Andre, hear it, right?
Hear what he said.
Kill us all, Sophia.
You understand that?
If he wanted to kill,
Now you were dead.
Is that true? You have nothing to do with that?
They poisoned her on Kira. It's dying.
Sorry, man.
I thought it was your fault.
No, it's a guy who had said
Ivan Mikhailov.
Yes, I know.
What's around the neck?
It's a bomb.
Tie is called Shanghai.
If someone tries to give it out,
will fly head.
We must stop this.
- What do we do?
- You can go to my house,
to stay there as you want.
You take care of Kira for me.
You have to remove it from the neck before
someone to decide it a blow.
Look, I do everything I can
as to save her and Kira.
- To catch on nemernicii guys.
- No, Andre.
GPS says it's in the building.
Come on.
You have to leave the hell out of here.
Go to my house.
Leave your car here.
Listen to him.
Stop.
- Let go.
- Do not tell me twice.
Adunci, go.
Move it.
Move it, man. Let's go.
As before.
Rainerio,
Welcome to your new opponent.
Soon you will meet
a great master ninja.
Kang Lai.
Good luck.
No weapons will be used
to fight it.
You will be disqualified.
I was a grandmaster.
It's one thing.
This is not a true fighter.
Cost me a lot of money ...
a fortune for most people.
What a disappointment.
Take him away!
It is over.
May not kill anyone for you.
S over?
No, no, no.
It's far from over.
Have you forgotten your wife,
your friends?
Even I do not want to kill them,
but I will if you have,
to regain my money.
Take him away!
Yes, sir. Fasten it to the eye.
Close it.
I want him weak and vulnerable
for most of his life fighting.
Let's go.
He fled.
Where the hell have you been? It's here.
Where is it?
What the hell?
- It's out.
- Damn.
Security guards are outside?
Here it is.
I went here
to see if you are satisfied
the quality of those fun days.
Fun? That you think we here?
Well, no.
What I meant was
that you do here
will bring a new respect for MMA.
What about Russian?
What about the fucking Russian?
We have a little problem with it.
Negotiation never went too far.
It seems not to care what their relatives do.
I suggest you simply make an offer.
You know, Russell?
No amount of money worth
to die for it.
You can order a masterpiece.
You need to inspire.
Try again.
Find and weaknesses.
That's your gift, is not it?
Try again.
Yes, of course. Sorry.
What happens, Russ?
Afraid to get dirty hands?
I just want to tell me
what you do Kira, Ivan.
You know Rainerio not like others.
It may have awakened a sleeping giant.
Allow me to worry
the giant.
- Honey.
- God.
God, you scared me.
What have they done.
Nothing. I'm fine.
- I'm okay.
- Okay, let us sit.
- Rest, right?
- Can.
Sophia and Andre are here.
Stay here.
I will go for help.
No, you can.
Look, I have to do something.
It's my fault.
If it was for me,
did you have done that.
No, Kira.
Baby.
If you would have loved so much,
I would have had reason to keep me fighting.
We will find a way.
They put poison in me.
I'm dying.
Are all weaker every day.
- Still have time.
- What?
To be in November
and to love one another.
I love you so much.
Andre never came last night.
I can give it.
I have no news from him.
Please, I need to find him.
Any idea where to go?
He said he goes to kill Ivan.
If I go back in two hours,
go to the wharf on the island.
I will find you. O to bring aid.
Come here.
Wait, slow down.
What, your secretary is about to do 18 years?
What's the rush?
Gus, I would like to talk to you now,
but not, I was late
a very important meeting.
You will not believe who I came over yesterday.
- Over what?
- Marty Stillwell.
Wonderful. Who the hell is this?
Marty "Two Guns."
Do not you remember Marty?
Wolf's coach Jackson.
Gus, just be busy.
Well, listen, listen.
Wolf never been seen for about 2 days.
- No one ever heard of him.
- Show the nanny's fucking?
No, just that they are worried.
He and Ray have ...
Gus, Gus, what do you say?
He's a fighter, right?
I am sure that landed in Shangri La
with a couple of girls.
I'm sure that's good.
You think? That's a relief
to hear you say that.
Because I heard some strange rumors.
What?
I think someone
organizing the illegal fights
in the city.
Are involved some way with gravity.
- Where did you hear that?
- Not the one in particular,
but I heard a couple rumors
and developed a theory.
Guys I've seen Gus and Andre?
No.
How many did you say that?
Only you.
Well.
Not in local, sir.
We have found weapons at the gate.
He will return.
Go and collect them all.
Gus.
Ray.
Ray, sorry.
Freeze.
What happened?
Russell betrayed you you ...
all fighters,
jerk.
Take heart in the chest.
I promise ...
Sophia, come, come.
- You got everything?
- Yes, yes, come on.
Ivan wants to see you both now.
Okay, go ahead.
You sold.
Ray.
How you got for us?
It was worth it?
- Not sure what you mean.
- You know what?
What are you doing?
Don 't even think about,
for being president of Galaxy.
Damn.
I just found out
what happens, right?
I tried to help?
- Help me?
- Yes.
You made more money
than all the fighters
helping us, dipshit.
Come on.
Good.
I wonder if you know how it
in a real fight.
- Leave me the hell alone.
- Shut up.
It was easy to kill Gus, do you?
Where's Andre?
How the hell would I know?
What the hell do you know?
You know, in a fight, you always hit,
no matter how good you are.
And when you hit are those glimpses
white light.
You lose control of the body.
You can not breathe.
The arms and legs do not listen.
You want to throw up, but you can not.
You know why?
Good.
Okay, okay, okay.
Listen, I tell you everything, right?
I know of Kira.
I did what I was told.
I fucking nothing to do with it, right?
I gave only the fighters, that's all,
I swear.
You only have given fighters?
You gave more than that.
You gave our lives.
Why?
I gave them only information.
Supposed to be my friend.
You have cheated.
I had no fucking choice.
Guy is a fucking maniac ...
You know, Gus was my friend.
I had no choice.
We all have a choice.
I have made the choice.
Please Rain.
I beg hell. Please.
See you in hell, you piece of shit.
Also I have no word from Andre.
I hope that has not forgotten responsible ...
Wait a minute.
Russell, where were you? I was ...
Russell is not it, today.
Mr Isandro.
I want to meet. I want to talk.
Yes, of course.
I would do something on the run.
Once I have your wife
and sister of Andre.
I want to talk to my wife.
I will send you instructions
where we meet.
And to bring her.
Prepare it the Shaman.
Issues in one hours.
NIGHT FIGHT
PARI
Good evening, everyone,
and welcome to the struggle of life ...
Shaman against Rainerio Isandro.
I'm sure you will not be disappointed
of this great game,
of these great fighters.
You are pigs they are sent
slaughter him?
Come on.
Congratulations,
Mr Isandro.
It was wonderful,
a great show
My investors,
really equal to one of the great battles
of ancient Coloseum.
You promised that we could talk.
Discussions are to diplomats,
not men of action
like you and me.
In a few days, Kira will die.
Then everything will end for me.
I will tell you
when it ends!
Your next fight will be tomorrow morning
very early.
And because you were such a great warrior,
give you an opportunity
to see your beloved wife
one last time.
- Rain.
- You okay?
Perfect.
It never disappoint me, sir Isandro.
I would hang on chain
if I were you.
But I suspect they already know it, is not it?
A small ingenious construction,
do not you think?
I designed it myself.
That you determine
what kind of man you really are.
If I let go of it,
Your precious little
will be sliced
as a ripe grapefruit.
Keep your energy, sir Isandro.
You'll need it.
You fight
the first hours of the morning,
after sunrise.
I
that might be knowing your opponent.
His name is Andre.
I think you are old friends.
There are nothing but a coward.
You paid a lot of blood, sir Isandro.
I do not judge me.
I do not judge you.
I will rip your heart
I promise.
So I want.
We'll see how you feel
tomorrow morning
after sunrise.
Audience increase
every day.
Last night we collected 75 million
with Shaman.
Tomorrow will be even more.
Buenas noches,
Isandro señor.
All right.
Go ahead.
- Yes.
I will not let you die.
Stay here with me.
Can I ask a personal question?
How close are you
and your brother?
It is doing everything to save
sweet sister?
My brother never cared not
by anyone except him.
I do not care if you find or not.
I think that will pick you seek.
However, if you fail to fulfill
obligations that war ...
Hold it. Keep one foot.
Where is it?
I do not know.
I thought he would say something.
Where is it? Where is it?
Not remembering yet?
01:07:30,526 -> 01:07:32,756
I hope to find me dead
and hope that you will break
that the garbage you are.
It would be great sin
miss the great fight of your life.
You think your brother has a chance
Rainerio before him?
Dumb fuck
Rainerio is like his brother.
They will fight.
Wrong.
Rainerio will do everything
to and protect
on his precious little girl, Kira.
Bet on it.
Listen carefully, my dear.
The fun has just begun.
Do not lose your head.
Andre!
Let me die, Rain.
No, never.
I must say
that 's very surprised
to see you here.
Love. He conquers all.
Or is hatred? Love-hate,
love-hate, how is it?
Clean it.
Prepare it for battle.
Take him away.
Come on.
Start to like you.
You are a survivor.
Very attractive.
Do not worry about it.
It will end soon.
I ...
as one to take care of you,
whether living
or die ...
love.
Clean it and bring a
in my apartment.
Do it presentable.
Rain, you are?
Jackey, are you okay?
Yes.
Me too.
Will be fine.
How we feel?
I must say
you look much, much better.
We decided
keep you alive.
Hungry?
Do not worry.
This is the antidote
for neuro toxin, right?
Do not feel guilty.
Everyone has the right to stay alive.
Thanks. However good.
Everything's better.
I will be okay now.
Hungry?
Want to eat something?
I know you hate me, but that does not mean
they must hate me food.
In substance, it's just food.
I could not refrain from noticing you.
I know that everything will be fine.
I will have staff look after you
after your husband dies.
Please let us go.
Things in life
not necessarily go as you wish.
People live, people die.
Life goes on.
See?
I understand that there are only
a strange little crazy.
I look like a guy
giving everyone a chance?
I will fuck you.
And after you shoot one,
you sing a different song.
They are more male
than your husband ever will.
Okay, sorry.
Understand,
even understand.
Not bad.
I know how to choose a winner ...
not jealous that you a fag.
- You ...
- Let me.
You need a lesson in manners.
I thought that one should tolerate more,
but you are shy, is not it?
That's good.
It will be fun.
Sir, are ready to fight room.
Too bad.
I will finish this later.
I will go to see your husband
As will be killed.
In the few minutes I will send for you
and you can see and carnage as well.
Keep an eye
the dog that small.
Where is Kira?
How touching.
Even in death,
My warrior woman to miss her.
How noble.
You did not answer the question.
- Where is my wife?
- Your wife?
Do not worry about it. Good.
You know, have a special sympathy for me.
I will take care of it after your death.
What did you say?
It is a special woman.
Take it to room fighting.
What a shame.
He said that I could taste a little
if I want.
And not referred to the sandwich.
Well, or you or Ivan ... what's the difference?
The other party never arrived yet, sir.
People can be so ungrateful.
I do not think your brother
really loves you.
No, no, no.
What a waste precious.
You know what?
May You give him two minutes.
If not here in two minutes,
to detonate a machine that
around her neck,
to see if I pull the head.
Wait.
Ivan, fighting with me.
Come on, coward.
We have 10 seconds ...
until the countdown.
That should be somewhat interesting.
10,
9, 8 ...
- Wait.
- Seven ...
- Six,
five,
four,
three,
two ...
I'm here.
Sophia, are you okay?
Andre!
You late!
To start the fight.
Broadcast live to start now.
Welcome to the broadcast tonight
from around the world.
We present two of the largest
MMA fighters,
that will tear the dead.
After tonight,
one will be declared champion.
Ladies and gentlemen,
good evening.
Welcome to the last
great fight to the death,
the two largest of our fighters,
Rainerio "The Rain Man" Isandro
against
Andre "Hurricane" Fontaine!
To start the fight!
Cheat. Cheat.
Ensure perimeter.
Slaughtered them both.
Where is it? Where's the detonator?
Where's the fucking exploding?
One to keep them away. Open fire.
Are you crazy?
We must go back to save your sister.
Okay.
Where's the fucking exploding?
Warning.
Andre, no!
Run, baby!
Run, are good.
No!
Jackey.
01:23:33,021 -> 01:23:35,819
Hello.
Remember me, is not it?
Okay, I take you out of here.
We must be silent.
Well, come on.
Come with me, come on.
Do not compare anything with a maniac
with a fucking big sword
to ruin your day.
You were
a great disappointment to me.
I will slaughter you
as a lambkin.
Baby.
Kira.
Try not to talk.
How do I ...
Wolf's son was also held here.
I managed to escape and call the police.
I found his body lying next to Ivan.
Oh, you're beautiful.
You okay?
We have both.
I promise.
I love You.
love you too.
Have fun with Rajpal any time