I have a friend, Deborah,
a psychologist...
..who was asked
by the city of Philadelphia...
.,.if she could offer psychological
counseling to Cambodian refugees...
.. .boat people,
who had recently arrived in the city.
Deborah was daunted by the task.
These Cambodians...
...had suffered genocide, starvation,
relatives murdered before their eyes...
...years in refugee camps,
harrowing boat trips to the West.
How could she relate
to their suffering?
How could she help these people?
So guess what all these people
wanted to talk about...
...with my friend Deborah,
the psychologist.
It was all,
"I met this guy in the refugee camp.
I thought he really loved me,
but when we got separated".
...he took up with my cousin.
Now he says he loves me...
...and keeps calling me. They're married now. What should I do?'
This is how we are.
May I help you?
I'm Liz Gilbert. I'm writing
a magazine article on Bali.
I wanted to meet a medicine man.
Everyone said I should meet
Ketut Liyer. Am I in the right place?
Wait.
I mean, here I am with
a ninth-generation medicine man...
...and what do I wanna
ask him about?
Getting closer to God?
Saving the world's
starving children?
Happy to see you. I am Ketut Liyer.
Nope. I wanna discuss
my relationship.
You are a world traveler.
You will live a long time...
...have many friends,
many experiences.
You will have two marriages.
One long, one short.
Am I in the long one
or the short one'?
Can't tell.
Also you will loss all your money.
I think in next six to 10 months.
Don't worry.
You will get it all back again.
And you will come back to Ball...
...and live here for three or four
months and teach me English.
I never had anybody
to practice my English with.
And then...
...l will teach you everything I know.
Wait.
I have this for you.
Keep grounded so it's like
you have four legs.
That way, you can stay in this world
Also, no looking at world
through your head.
Look through your heart instead.
That way, you will know God.
Which is why you came here, no?
See you later, alligator.
I proofread all of her manuscripts.
My wife is very, very beautiful, but she can’t spell for anything.
Look at Uncle Stephen.
And Auntie Liz
I'm counting the minutes for this to be
over so I can get in my big girl pants.
You look fantastic.
You just had a baby.
Oh, you're lying.
I'm fat, I'm exhausted...
...I can't keep two thoughts.
I feel like Liza Minnelli.
Stephen, can you hold Jack?
-I'm gonna introduce you to Walter.
-Yeah .
Hey, dude, you wanna grab a beer
or something'?
My new book comes out in April.
Thank you for asking.
-Great.
-May.
May. May.
This is Andre. You two are
Times' Most Notable nominees
-50 glad to finally meet you.
-Nice to finally meet you.
I fed him nachos. Is that bad?
You look comfortable.
What'd you feed him, chloroform?
-Give him to his dad.
-l told you, nachos.
Know what? I'd be asleep too
if I had a dump like that.
-We'll give him to his mom.
-Come here then.
-Wanna help me change his diaper?
-Yes, I do.
Hey, how's the vintage car
thing going?
Oh, no, ho, ho. I changed jobs.
I'm a pastry chef now.
-You mean you're a baker
-Yeah.
You wanna get baked?
I know, I know.
It's hard, isn't it?
Oh, no. This is so much fun.
Did you know the exact moment
you wanted to have a baby?
I can't remember, but I've had the box
since before I got married.
What box?
It's girly and embarrassing,
and you'll laugh at me if I tell you.
I will laugh at you,
but you still have to tell me.
Come on.
Under the bed.
I’ve been filling it with baby things...
...waiting until Andy
was ready to be a father.
So sweet.
Does this come in my size?
I have a box just like this, except
it's filled with National Geographic.
...and The Times travel section.
All the places I wanna see
before I die.
Liz, having a baby is like
getting a tattoo on your face.
You kind of wanna be
fully committed.
So my trip to Aruba next week,
which is just a basic, you know...
..."where to sleep, swim
and stuff your face" piece....
I got a new bikini.
And it turns out,
I have unlimited mini-bar access.
-You know what that means?
-Jet lag?
You, me...
...macadamia nuts.
That was cute.
You know who I was talking to
at the party who was really inspiring...
-...was Tara's friend.
-Brian.
Brian. Unbelievable.
He's a teacher, you know that?
He’s a substitute teacher, isn’t he?
Yeah. He was talking about the
budget cuts that are happening now.
There's no money for anything.
There's no music classes
there's no arts classes.
They're volunteering their time
to do all of this after school.
They're educating our kids,
you know?
I think you'd make
a great teacher, honey.
Thank you,
but I was thinking more of like"'
...education. Getting my masters,
going back to school. I don't know.
You know?
I-- You know....
-Going back to school.
-I'm just thinking out loud.
I was getting the sinking feeling that
Ketut's prophecy was coming true.
Was I in the shorter marriage?
We’d only bought this house
a year ago.
Hadn't l wanted this?
I had actively participated
in every moment of the creation...
...of this life.
So why didn't I see myself
in any of it?
The only thing more impossible
than staying...
...was leaving.
I didn't wanna hurt anybody. I wanted
to slip quietly out the back door...
...and not stop running
until l reached Greenland.
Instead, I made a decision
To pray.
You know, like, to God.
And it was such a foreign concept to
me, that I swear I almost began with:
"I'm a big fan of your work. "
Hello, God?
Nice to finally meet you. I....
I am sorry I've never spoken
directly to you before...
...but...
...I hope I've expressed my...
...ample gratitude for all
the blessings you've given...
...to me in my life.
I'm in serious trouble.
I don't know what to do.
I need an answer
Please, tell me what to do.
Oh, God, help me, please.
Tell me what to do and I'll do it.
Go back to bed, Liz.
I don't wanna go to Aruba.
I don't wanna be married
You know, there's a whole
divorce section downstairs.
-"Pepper grinder."
-She's having...
-...a nervous breakdown.
-This is what girls do.
-She’s processing.
-Why doesn’t she get drunk or laid?
That's what I would do if you left me.
No, you wouldn't.
-No, I wouldn’t.
-She moved out, she filed for divorce.
They were together eight years.
She's got no home.
'Legacy'
Every word in Italian is like a truffle.
A magic trick.
Honey, I get it.
It's your life raft right now.
When Andy and I broke up
for two weeks, I bought a loom.
A frigging loom.
And he tried to start a microbrewery.
I don't know how you guys
aren't sick of me now. I'm sick of me.
Are you kidding me?
We love having you.
It's kind of like having
a writer in residence.
But you are a writer.
You should be writing something
Maybe I could write about a woman
who goes to Italy to learn Italian.
Call it
Carbohydrates and Conjugations.
I'll start looking for a place.
-I'm falling in love with you.
-I'm not who you think I am.
I'm just your fantasy.
No, that's bullshit. You're real.
Your scars, your talent.
The fact that
I own a piece-of-crap bar...
...and you accept that
that's all I'm gonna do.
Okay, this sucks.
-I second that.
-Don't be rude.
I love your pain.
And I love that when we're together,
I can make it go away.
-Oh, he's good'
-You're love...
-He's hot, theres a difference
-...is like a hot panini.
And when I look into your eyes,
I hear dolphins clapping.
I did not write that line.
Here's what he doesn't know yet
I disappear Into the person I love.
I am the permeable membrane.
If I love you, you can have it ally
My money, my time, my body...
...my dog, my dog's money.
I will assume your debts
and project upon you...
...all sorts of nifty qualities you've
never actually cultivated in yourself.
I will give you all this and more...
...until I am so exhausted
and depleted...
...the only way I can recover...
...is by becoming infatuated
with someone else.
-Elizabeth, hi.
-Hi.
Oh, really?
How you doing?
Cheers.
-Thank you.
-I owe you an apology.
-For the walkouts.
-Well, I'm not everyone's cup of tea.
I doubt that.
I, on the other hand, was shit.
-Although I was trying very hard.
-"Shit" is a strong word.
Thank you.
You seem shorter in person
than on the stage.
-Really? I hear that a lot.
-Sorry.
It's okay.
It's unnerving when...
...a total stranger sees you
more clearly than you see yourself.
That's what I mean
by saying you're short.
Are you hearing dolphins clapping
right now?
I took a few liberties
with your material.
I give you full permission to make
fun of me. I know you're dying to.
You're far too charming
to make fun of.
I'm still hearing them.
Is that your guru?
You're joking, but, yes, it is.
She's beautiful.
Yeah. A friend told me about her.
I was out of work and feeling
pretty desperate for something.
Not the last time I was out of work,
the time before that.
And I just had this feeling like
I was looking in all the wrong places.
Looking for what?
God.
She has an ashram in India.
I'm dying to go, but...
...you know, you have to get, like,
three stages of hepatitis shots...
...and my insurance always runs out.
I'll go when the time's right.
There's a gathering of her students
every morning.
If you want,
I could take you sometime.
If you're not unnerved by 100
crunchy people chanting in Sanskrit.
I need to be unnerved.
David. A yogi from Yonkers.
I didn’t exactly fall in love
with the guy.
What happened was
I dove out of my marriage...
...and into David's arms...
...exactly the same way
a cartoon circus performer...
...dives off a high platform
and into a small cup of water...
.. . vanishing completely.
Your underwear, my queen.
He just folded my delicates.
Oh, my God, baby,
you are in so much trouble.
Thirty-six?
My client is simply not interested
in a divorce.
Is he serious?
Is he really representing himself?
One semester of law school
right here, baby.
Great. Well, what would it take
to interest your client?
Okay, so here's the deal.
You have screwed up my life...
...but what I wanna know
is why couldn't you find yourself...
...in our marriage? Why didn't you
say what you were thinking?
-I did. You never listened to me.
-No. You never said:
"Hey, you know what?
You suck. I'm deeply unhappy."
You just took off. You never gave me a chance to address those problems.
That’s not fair. That’s just quitting.
I took vows.
Till death.
And I take them seriously.
I believe this is just a phase
and I'm willing to wait it out.
You are always waiting, Stephen.
Waiting for me to come home,
to wanna have kids...
...to make you dinner.
I don'! know why we can'! accept"'
...we don't wanna live
in unhappiness anymore.
I accept the fact that
I am occasionally unreliable...
...and I often get sidetracked,
but I thought you liked that about me.
I thought it was okay
that I had hopes and dreams.
Have a dream. Stephen, great,
fine. Do that. Just pick one.
Okay, I pick one. I pick you.
I know this is awful.
But I believe with every molecule of
my body that you will find the person...
...that wants just what you want.
That will give you what you want
and what you deserve. I'm not her.
Well, you obviously know nothing
about what I want.
My client would like to submit
a song he wrote...
...that he believes is relevant to these
proceedings. Goes something like this:
Are you kidding?
Quitter, quitter, quitter!
How about I take the blame?
I am the one who couldn't deal...
...with another weekend roaming
some box-shaped superstore...
...buying appliances on credit...
...and pretending to be a couple that
neither one of us ever knew how to be.
You wanted that toaster
"You like faking it, fine. You're stellar.
I'm the failure. I suck at faking it."
-It was not my finest hour.
-80 where do things stand now?
We're prepared
to offer half of everything...
...and my client's retirement accounts
Take it all then. Everything.
He still said no.
-He hates me now.
-He doesn't hate you.
His heart is broken.
I think he hates you.
I'm never letting you
out of the basement.
Why don't we talk next week
and we'll see where things stand?
-Okay.
-These things have a way...
...of working themselves out.
So why'd you become a vegetarian?
I saw some cows slaughtered
one time.
Barely touched your dinner.
He's 28.
This is hard for him, isn't it'?
And you?
The meditations help.
Liz.
You remember a couple of years ago,
when you threw yourself into...
...the renovation of your kitchen?
You were consumed...
...with being the perfect wife and cook.
I was trying to make it work.
Well, I think chanting and meditation
is the same thing...
...in a different costume.
Definitely give me that documentary.
I've been thinking
about vegetarianism.
My triglycerides
are through the roof.
Yeah. Thanks for everything.
Great to meet you.
-What?
-Nothing. It's just..'
...you know,
you used to look like Stephen.
Now you kind of look like David.
You know?
What I meant was, you know how
people start resembling their dogs?
Why would he say that,
we look like the same dog'?
-He was joking.
-Not funny.
Well, he had five Heineken's.
He was bombed.
Well, not funny.
We don't look like the same dog.
If anything, you're a collie
and I'm a Tibetan mastiff.
Don’t you wanna give me a chance
to miss you?
It begins when
the object of your affection...
...bestows upon you
a heady hallucinogenic dose"'
...of something you've never
even dared to admit you wanted...
...an emotional speed-ball
of thunderous love and excitement.
Soon you start craving that attention
with the hungry obsession...
...of any junkie.
When it's withheld, you tum sick;
crazy, not to mention resentful.
...of the dealer who encouraged
this addiction in the first place...
...but now refuses to pony up
the good stuff.
Just frustrated, I'm concerned.
I don't understand.
What don't you get?
What's going on?
You don't look me in the eye.
-You don'! finish your--
-Nobody's asking you to make the bed!
-You don't have sex with me!
Sometimes I'm not in the mood!
Goddamn him, and he used to
give it to you for free.
Next stage Ends you skinny,
shaking in a corner...
...certain only that
you'd sell your soul...
...just to have that one thing
one more time.
Well, then why don't we discuss it?
Why don't we sort it?
-Why don't we act like adults?
-Okay. Can I have a little space?
-How about that?
-Meanwhile...
...the object of your adoration
is now repulsed by you.
-You don't always make me miserable.
-There's a comfort.
I just-- Sometimes I need to
come home...
...and have a little David time.
He looks at you like someone
he’s never met before.
-Is that okay?
-Yeah. No, it's fine.
And not have to, like, you know,
justify it.
The irony is
you can hardly blame him,
I mean, check yourself out.
You're a mess.
Unrecognizable
even to your own eyes.
You asked me to come here?
Here I am.
And it turned into something else.
-Didn't it'?
-You are such a child.
-Right. I can't take this anymore.
-Great. Perfect.
That's a great response
to a conversation.
Goddamn it.
• You have now reached infatuation’s final destination
The complete
and merciless devaluation of self.
You wanna go away for a year?
Do you know what I felt when I woke up, Delia?
Nothing. No passion, no spark,
no faith, no heat. Absolutely nothing.
I've gotten past the point where
I can be calling this a bad moment.
• And it just terrifies me. Jesus,1 this is like worse than death to me..i
...the idea that this is the person
I'm gonna be from now on.
This happens to people.
They fall in love in their 20s,
get married...
...do the granite counter-top,
white-picket fence in their
...and somewhere they realize,
"This is not for me."
So they fail and they fall down,
they hurt like hell, they straighten
...and march their asses
to the shrink's office.
-They can’t just check out.
-I am not checking out.
I need to change.
You have a support system
here, Liz.
You have friends and family
who love you.
And do you feel my love for you?
My support for you? No.
There's, like, nothing. I have no pulse.
-l am going to Italy.
-Italy. Why Italy?
-What did you have for lunch?
-I don't know. A salad.
Exactly. I used to have this appetite
for food, for my life...
...and it is just gone.
I wanna go someplace
where I can marvel at something
Language, gelato,
spaghetti, something.
-You're talking like a college kid.
-I've been acting like one.
Since I was 15, I've either been
with a guy or breaking up with a guy.
I have not given myself two weeks of a breather...
...to just deal with, you know, myself.
What's going on
with you and David?
What, did you fall out?
I don't know how to be here.
You wanna know how to be here'?
Stop constantly waiting for something
I'm going to Italy and then I'm going
to David's guru's ashram in Indian.
...and I'm going to and the year
in Bali.
That's what I'm gonna do.
That's harder to argue with.
The beaches are nice. But why?
-Ketut told me I would.
-Guy with no teeth.
When you're desperate...
...and some guy who,
yes, looks a little like Yoda...
...hands you a prophecy,
you have to respond.
-Do you need a Xanax?
-Always.
Okay, I'm just gonna say it.
I'm gonna say it and be done with it.
What if it doesn't work?
My whole life
fits in a 12-foot-square box.
You know how many times
I hear that in a day?
Most of them never come back
for their whole life.
-Hello?
-Liz.
Good news. Stephen just signed
the divorce papers.
I'll probably be back in a weak,
penniless with dysentery.
You're my hero.
Hey.
If you stay,
we'll go out for Indian every night.
You never asked me to stay.
Go, go, go.
You know what's funny?
This is the first time in my life
there's no one waiting at home for me.
I don't even have a home
to come back to.
Oh, God. You'll make friends.
You'll make friends with a backpack,
of course.
It'd be great to get away.
Andy and I were talking about getting
a little villa in Florence for a month.
You know, and in 10 years,
when Jack is older....
What?
You know why I was giving you
such a hard time'?
I love my job, my guy and my kid,
but....
I wish I could go'
I love you and I'm proud of you.
Now go.
There is a wonderful
old Italian joke...
.,.about a poor man
who goes to church every day...
...and prays before the statue
of a great saint, bagging:
"Dear saint, please, please, please
let me win the lottery."
Finally, the exasperated statue
comes to life...
...and looks down at the begging man
and says:
"My sun, please, please, please
buy a ticket. "
So now I get the joke.
And I've got three tickets.
You heat the water on the stove.
So if I want to bathe".?
You put the water in the tub.
Okay
Yeah. It doesn’t really seem like
enough water to bathe in.
Not enough.
Yes, ifs enough.
Fill it up three, four, five times.
Everything that's important
gets cleaned.
Is this safe? This..'
...scaffolding? Scaffol...
It holds up the ceiling.
Otherwise it will fall apart.
Everything falls apart, my dear.
The only thing permanent in life
is family.
You're not married.
No, divorziata.
Why divorced?
We broke it.
You're more happy now'?
I have one rule.
No strange men spending the night.
You American girls
when you come to Italy...
...all you want is pasta...
...and sausage.
I'll take it.
Good. You chose well.
Cappuccino.
-It's a zoo in here.
-And my Italian sucks.
-How long have you been here?
-Two weeks. You'?
Six weeks. You'll get better.
Two cappuccinos, please.
And warm the milk this time.
Yesterday it was too hot
and burned my tongue.
-You like Napoleons?
-Of course.
And two Napoleons, please
Your Italian is fantastic.
I have a wonderful tutor.
I'll give you his number if you like
-He's really good and he needs work.
-Oh, great.
Are you Dutch? German?
Swedish. Even colder people,
if you can imagine.
-I'm Liz, by the way.
-8011.
You can say:
It's past
Too fast, but okay.
You can say:
Yeah.
What a beautiful word
Come on, it's "let's cross over."
It's so ordinary.
No, it's the perfect combination
of Italian sounds.
It's the wistful "ah," the rolling trill,
the soothing "ess."
-That's true.
-I love it.
All right, let me teach you a word.
Therapist.
-Come on.
-Good. You gotta learn humor.
-It's not.
-Come on. Cheers.
-Shall we continue Tuesday at 5?
-Yes.
-With another bottle of the therapy?
-of course.
-You're doing very well, Liz.
-Thank you.
And you must be very polite
with yourself...
...when you learn something new.
Yes. Grazie, I agree.
But your English-- How are you
even talking to me like this right now?
I think you're gonna teach ma
more than I teach you.
You have good Italian. Very good.
All right
I am alone.
I feel so guilty.
I've been in Rome for three weeks...
...all I've done is learn
a few Italian words and eat.
You feel guilty
because you're American.
You don't know
how to enjoy yourself.
-I beg your pardon?
-It's true.
Americans know entertainment,
but don't know pleasure.
This is Luca Spaghetti, by the way,
you know.
Your name is Luca Spaghetti?
Yes, that's what our family is called.
We invented it.
I’m serious. Listen to me.
You want to know your problem?
Americans.
You work too hard.
You get burned out.
Then you come home
and spend the whole weekend...
...in your pajamas in front of the TV.
That's not far off, actually.
But you don't know pleasure.
You have to be told you've earned it.
You see a commercial that says,
"It's Miller time"...
...and you say, "That's right.
Now I will go to buy a six-pack."
And drink the whole thing and wake up
the next morning and you feel terrible.
But an Italian doesn't need
to be told.
Ha walks by a sign that says,
"you deserve a break today"...
...and he says, "Yeah, I know.
That's why I'm planning on
taking a break at noon...
...to go over to your house and sleep with your wife.”
We callit "dolce far niente"
It means".
...the sweetness of doing nothing.
We are masters of it.
He's right. He says...
...you can't learn Italian like this.
You don't speak the language just with
your mouth, speak it with your hands.
Like this?
Okay. ls yelling.
'THAT MEAL WAS EXCELLENT'
'SUCK IT'
All this gives me a stomachache.
'SCREW YOU'
-I think that's my neighbor Lorenzo.
-Charming.
ANOTHER WAY
TO SAY 'SCREW YOU'
So anyway, to start off I'd say....
Excuse me.
Come here.
For the table...
...a big platter
of artichoke alla giudia...
...prosciutto with melon...
...and eggplant
with ricotta affumicata.
Then spaghetti alla carbonara...
...pappardelle with ragu of rabbit...
...and Iinguini with clams.
Then trips alla romana...
...and saltimbocca.
And two more liters
of the vino sfuso from Genzano.
Thank you.
You did it. Yes.
Liz Gilbert,
you are a Roman woman now.
No, only honorary.
That is a real Roman woman.
Yeah, with a lot
of international friends.
That one, I'd bite.
Maybe you and Rome
just have different words.
-Different words?
-Yeah.
Yeah. It's like each city has a word,
if you really think about it.
Like, what is the word for London?
-I would say "stuffy."
-I would agree with that.
-What's the word for Stockholm?
-Are you kidding? "Conform."
And New York?
"Ambition" or "soot."
What's the word for Rome?
It's kind of difficult to think about.
It's classic.
'Sex'
Of course.
So, what's your word, Liz?
I'm curious. I can't figure it out.
Well....
It might be....
It started as "daughter."
I was good at that. And then".
..."wife.“ Not so good.
"Girlfriend."
Not so good.
My word's writer."
Yeah, but that's what you do.
That isn't who you are, no?
Maybe you’re a woman in search of her word.
Hey, Sch, it's Liz. Let's go to Naples.
Maybe my word is 'pizza.". "
Listen, lady, I am only 7, but I
can tell you're a complete moron".
...because I am from Naples.
I love this place,
but Giovanni said to watch out.
His cousin got mugged here
in a museum.
-Are you serious?
-Watch out for the scooter. Yeah
I'm in love. I'm having
a relationship with my pizza.
You look like you're breaking up
with the pizza. Whats the matter?
I can't.
What do you mean, you can't?
This is pizza in Napoli.
It is your moral imperative
to eat that pizza.
I want to,
but I've gained, like, 10 pounds.
I mean, I've got this....
Right here. What's it called?
What's the word?
A muffin top.
I have one too.
I unbuttoned my jeans
five minutes ago just looking at this.
Let me ask you a question.
In all the years you've ever
undressed in front of a gentleman....
-Hasn't been that many.
-All right, well...
...has he ever asked you to leave?
-Has he ever walked out? Left?
-No.
Because he doesn't care.
He's in a room with a naked girl.
He's won the lottery.
I'm so tired of saying no
and then waking up in the morning...
...and recalling every single thing
I ate the day before.
Counting every calorie
so I know exactly...
...how much self-loathing
to take into the shower.
I'm going for it.
I have no interest in being obese.
I'm just through with the guilt.
This is what I’m gonna do I’m gonna finish this pizza...
...and then we're gonna go
watch the soccer game.
And tomorrow we're gonna go
on a little date...
...and buy ourselves
some bigger jeans.
Giovanni likes a muffin.
Attagirl
He's saying,
"For whom are you playing?"
Per chi, for whom.
Pull, pull. I'm sucking it in.
Put some Swedish muscle into this.
You think this happened
to Sophia Loren?
There it goes. Almost got it.
Go, go, go. You're not trying.
I've almost got it. I've almost got it.
I did it.
Oh, that's beautiful'
You should get it.
For whom?
For you, Liz. Just for you.
• No, I’m happy just with my big lady pants.
Thanks for the day.
And the leg room.
It was fun.
We're gonna go for food.
Wanna come?
No. No, I'm
The sweetness of doing nothing
Please. Please get off the Noon
Will you please just".?
Will you come up here?
What if we just acknowledge that
we have a screwed-up relationship".
...and we stick it out anyway?
We accept that we fight a
...and we hardly have sex anymore...
...but that we don't wanna
live without each other.
And that way we can spend
our lives together...
...miserable...
...but happy not to be apart.
Dear David:
We haven't had any communication
in a while...
...and it’s given me time
I needed to think.
Remember when you said we should
live with each other and be unhappy...
...so we could be happy?
Consider it a testimony to how much I love you...
...that I spent so long
pouring myself into that offer...
...trying to make it work.
But a friend took me to the most
amazing place the other day.
It's called the Augusteum.
Octavian Augustus built it
to house his remains.
When the barbarians came, they
trashed it along with everything else.
The great Augustus,
Rome’s first true great emperor...
...how could he have imagined
that Rome...
...the whole world, as far as he was
concerned, would be in ruins?
During the Dark Ages, someone came
in here and stole the emperor's ashes.
In the 12th century,
it became a fortress...
...than a bullring'
They stored fireworks in here
after that.
Nowadays, it's a bathroom
for the homeless...
...so you better watch your step
going down.
It’s one of the quietest
and loneliest places in Rome.
The city has grown up
around it over centuries.
It feels like a precious wound...
...like a heartbreak you won't let go of
because it hurts too good.
I like it messy.
We all want things
to stay the same, David.
I guess the guy before me
must've been some angel, huh?
Settle for living in misery...
...because we're afraid of change,
of things crumbling to ruins.
Than I looked around in this place,
at the chaos it's endured...
...the way it’s been adapted,
burned, pillaged...
...then found a way to build itself
back up again, and I was reassured.
Maybe my life hasn’t been so chaotic.
It’s just the world that is...
...and the only real trap
is getting attached to any of it.
Ruin is a gift.
Ruin is the road to transformation.
Hey.
You ready?
Yeah.
Even in this eternal city,
the Augusteum showed ms...
...that we must always be prepared
for endless waves of transformation.
Both of us deserve better than staying together...
I ...because we’re afraid well be destroyed if we don’t.
My mother's stuffing.
Stale bread, walnuts, got those.
Will you get me
some more potatoes?
Oh, I'm always getting you
more potatoes.
It's my dream,
a real American Thanksgiving.
The perfect way to say goodbye
to our Liz.
50...
-...you leave this week, huh?
-Yes.
And where are you going? Iran?
India.
Liz is making us
an American meal tonight.
-You are not married, yeah?
-No.
What's wrong with your friend,
is she a lesbian?
No, Mama, she’s not a lesbian And she understands Italian.
How’s she going to find
another husband and start a family...
...when she's on the other side
of the world?
If a man said, "I'm going to travel for
a year and meet wonderful people...."
But she's not a man.
It’s more difficult for a woman to feel that she has the right to make choices.
-It takes a lot of courage.
-Exactly.
You call it courage, I call it stupidity.
Mama, enough.
I know a number of people
who would agree with you.
Luca?
What time will the turkey be ready?
The turkey....
I haven't defrosted it yet.
Oh, shit.
You only had one thing to do
and you screwed it up.
I was distracted! It can happen!
Too much good food!
Too many women!
And I forgot!
Now, before we eat, everyone...
...it is Thanksgiving,
so let us give thanks.
-Yeah. Come on, join hands.
-Okay.
So we just say what we....
What we thank God for tonight
Sofi, why don't you start?
I am grateful for you, Liz...
...for helping me appreciate life...
...with all that comes with it...
...muffin tops and bad times.
And for Giovanni...
...for making me feel...
...loved and secure.
And Giulia
Me, I'm grateful for
my beautiful family
My two little daughters and my wife.
I thank God and the Holy Virgin...
...for this very, very special day.
And for this beautiful family...
...that today is so much bigger.
Very much bigger.
I thank you all for this new custom
of celebration.
And Liz's stuffing.
...and God...
...for my sexiness.
And you, Ruffina?
I thank God for...
...my sexiness.
Go ahead. Giovanni.
I thank God for...
...fear...
...because for the first time...
...I'm afraid the person next to me...
...will be the one who wants to leave.
Liz?
Well, this all makes me so grateful.
Seeing all you happy people...
...who know how to love each other
and take care of each other.
I look at the amazing women I've met
who I admire so much...
...and the great men,
taking care of their women...
...and putting their children to bed.
I just feel happy...
...to see it and to be part of it
I'm the luckiest girl in the world.
It's a good breakfast, huh?
I will take this to your room.
It has already started.
-I fell asleep.
-Yeah. Pity.
Probably the only person in the world
who ever fell asleep during meditation.
-This leads to the meditation garden.
-Is the guru here?
-She's always here.
-I know, but is she "here" here?
She's at her ashram in New York
But I came from New York
to see her here.
Sounds like one of her little tricks.
The meditation cave.
It’s open 2417
and it’s air-conditioned.
Corella?
-This is Liz Gilbert.
-Hi. Nice to meet you.
-Where did you get that button?
-They sell them in the bookstore.
That is exactly what I need. I need
something like that. I don't listen.
I never have. My mom used to
call me Little Miss Chatty Cathy...
...because I just ramble.
I am a rambler.
I am rambling now. I'm sorry.
Silence is a wonderful
spiritual practice...
...but if Corella could speak, she'd tell
you it's more challenging than it looks.
-Wait till you've been here for a while.
-Okay.
Thank you, Corella.
I'll be sure to tell her.
-What did she say?
-No idea.
Change into your work clothes.
I'll take you to your seva.
It's a Hindu word
for "selfless devotional work."
-It's required of everyone who stays.
-Okay. Thank you.
Is there anything in this world skinnier
than an Indian teenage boy?
-I'm Tulsi.
-Liz.
Where are you from?
The next town. My parents have been devotees of the guru for many years.
We spend a lot of time here.
But...
...they are trying to marry me off'
That's the custom.
-That's not what you want?
-No way. It sucks.
I want to study psychology, just as our
guru did when she attended college.
I prefer to be with God
than boys my age.
No one in my family understands
my coming all the way to India.
Do you ever look at them and wonder,
"What am I doing in this family?"
You have no idea.
The Guru Gita is an ancient text
182 verses long.
In it, the goddess Parvati
is asking Shiva, or God...
...for the secrets of fulfillment.
It's said to have
transforming qualities.
I would just like to take a risk here
and say....
Me and Guru Gita,
we just do not get along.
-What is it you have trouble with?
-Everything.
It’s long, it’s tedious,
I can’t keep up...
...and I get these insane anxieties
about everything in my life...
...and I've lost my place.
Sounds like it has a positive effect...
...if you're having such strong
emotions and physical reactions.
You keep trying.
It is most commendable
that you ended your marriage.
You seem like such a
happy, free person now.
I think my ex-husband
would describe me as selfish.
You mustn't be angry with yourself
or disappointed.
You don't have to make children
or be married to have a family.
Oh, man. They got mosquitoes
here big enough...
...to stand flat-footed
and screw a chicken.
-I love you.
-Liz, have you met...
-..,Richard from Texas?
-Hello, Richard from Texas.
-Nice to meet you, Groceries.
-Groceries'?
Yeah. Yeah, I heard you eating
before I saw you.
I never seen anybody
eat so much at one time.
You sure do enjoy your groceries.
You know, it’s been a rough day, and if no one takes it personally. J
...I'm going to take my large meal
someplace else to eat it in silence.
Oh, no, stay. I'm done.
Looked like you were
working through some...
...pretty rough stuff this morning.
Stuff with your ex-husband?
I got an ex-wife.
She thinks I changed my name
to "Motherfucker."
I...
I just spent some time in Rome
and I came here feeling so great.
And now here I am, at the source...
...and I feel more disconnected
than ever.
Why'd you come here?
I just want some peace.
Peace?
You wanna get
to the castle, Groceries...
...you got to swim the moat.
Here, you can finish that.
I know you can.
Okay.
Simply empty your mind.
Breathe.
What am I going to do
when this year is over?
Where am I going to live?
Well, maybe Chicago.
Oh, my God.
I could build a meditation room--
No. Stop thinking.
Why is this so hard?
Screw you, Corella.
How the hell does she do this?
She looks like
frigging Mother Teresa.
Oh, my God, kill me.
-Who's in the moat today?
-Shut up.
Sounds like you wrestled
some big-ass crocs.
You know what? If you're so goddamn
smart, what are you doing here?
If you're here,
it makes you smart already.
-Do you wanna talk about what--?
-No, not to you. Thank you.
I'm the only one here. You're gonna
talk about it sooner or later.
I cannot focus in there.
All I think about is my meditation room
and how to decorate.
Are you shitting me?
Are you kidding me?
The meditation room is within,
Groceries. Decorate that.
Do you always talk in bumper sticker?
I do, and here’s another one.
You have to learn to select
your thoughts the way you select...
...your clothes every day.
That's a power you can cultivate.
You wanna come here and control
your life so bad, work on the mind.
That's the only thing
you should control.
If you can't master your thoughts,
you're in trouble.
I am trying.
Yeah, hello, that's the damn problem.
Stop trying. Surrender.
Go out into the garden
and just sit there and still your mind...
...and you watch what happens.
Why don't you just let it be?
Has anyone ever told you
you look like James Taylor?
Every day.
God, he really does.
My prayers were always the same.
"Please, God, please.
Open my heart, send me a sign".
...because we both know
I ain't the sharpest tool in the shed."
Look at you,
floating through Calcutta
Locks like you had
a great meditation.
I probably have malaria now.
The bites will go away.
Eventually everything goes away.
You ever done that, Groceries?
Bagged for a sign?
That sounds vaguely familiar.
Be careful what you wish for.
You just might get it.
What is your problem?
Did you fall in love
with the wrong woman or something?
Excuse me, Miss Gilbert.
You have a phone call.
How's the Guru Gita treating you?
Fine. You'd like her.
Did you get my e-mail?
Yeah. I’m sorry I didn’t call sooner.
Why didn't you?
Because if! didn’t respond...
...we were still having a conversation.
I was still in it.
I'm sorry. We were just bad timing.
I just wanted things to be easy.
We were good when things were easy.
It's not that I need "easy" right now.
I just can't have "so hard."
Well, you sound good.
Stronger.
So do you.
Yeah, well, I'm an actor, Liz.
I got a part.
It’s off-Broadway, but it’s pretty cool.
I'm happy for you.
All right
Well, I'll see you around, kid.
Check you out.
I have never seen you so focused.
You need a Thums Up.
No, no. No lips on the bottle.
First rule in India is never
touch anything but yourself.
Oh, good God. That's, like,
five times sweeter than Coke.
I think it might have
methamphetamines in it.
We can only hope.
I know you feel awful.
But your life's changing.
That's not a bad thing.
And you're in the perfect place for it.
Surrounded by grace.
I thought I was over him, but...
...I love him.
Big deal.
-So you fell in love with someone.
-l really miss him.
So miss him.
Send him some light and love every
time you think of him, then drop it.
You know, if you could clear out
all that space in your mind...
...that you're using
to obsess over this guy...
...and your failed marriage,
you'd have a vacuum with a doorway.
And you know what the universe
would do with that doorway?
Rush in. God would rush in.
Fill you with more love
than you ever dreamed of. Man.
Groceries.
I think you have the capacity someday
to love the whole world.
What do they sell over there?
Ganesh. Remover of obstacles
I'm gonna need a lot of these.
Speaking of elephants, there's a rogue
elephant on the loose in the area.
He was with carnival.
They say he is very,
very unpredictable and volatile.
That just makes him more attractive
to her.
How'd you get to be so smart?
I'll bet it was the hard way.
Don't change the subject
Well, when is this grieving phase
going to pass?
You want a day on a calendar
you can circle?
-Can you give me one?
-No. You got to do the work.
Meditate and go to seva..
...and most important, get your butt
down to the Geet every morning...
...and something'il change.
I just cannot get through the Guru Gita.
I can't find that feeling of devotion.
Okay. Devotion's love. Pick somebody
or something you wanna devote it to.
It doesn’t have to be the guru.
It’s all the same to her.
This is about you.
Can I tell you something, Groceries?
You got some serious control issues.
Is it obvious?
All right, Richard,
get out from inside my head now.
Shut the door.
-That's him?
-That's him.
-He's hideous.
-No, he's not. He's cute.
He's a Sagittarius.
He studies computer programming
in Delhi.
He has very good grades.
And his family is very, very wealthy
He will be very conceited
and dictatorial.
My life is over at 17.
Tulsi.