There's not a sermon
l could preach here,
that would be acceptable!
(Susanna) Now, Samuel,
you're overreacting!
Oh, you know what l mean.
Just because l'm a royalist,
the children are ostracized.
You are ignored in
the marketplace
and everything l do is opposed.
And it's not just the commoners.
The landowners
are just as bad....
(Voice) Fire!
Everyone out of the house.
(Girl's Voice)
Get the baby!
(Voices) Fire!
(Susanna) Jackie,
where are you?
Mum?
[scream]
What proof have we,
as reasonable men,
of the existence of a Creator?
Consider, l beseech
you, the universe.
The planets that
circle the sun,
moons that revolve
about the planets,
the universe as a machine.
The watch.
The watch!
Proclaims the watch maker.
Mum, l'm hungry.
Here you go.
Now shut yertrap.
This entire nation
is soaked in gin.
What do they do about it?
Can you spare a penny, sir.
For me babe?
Gin for your belly,
more likely.
There'll be no begging here.
Move along.
l can stand here
if l've a mind to.
Are you familiar
with Bocardo Prison?
Aye, l am.
You'll have no
trouble from me.
No, sir.
l'll be on me way.
Meet us there
this afternoon.
We've food for
you and the child.
(Woman) Bless you, sir.
What do you mean by
this, John Wesley?.
Encouraging the woman?
lt's bad enough her kind
roams the streets with the pigs,
but l will not have them
befouling our Sacred grounds.
We strive to fulfill
our religious duty
by performing acts
of charity...
Christian charity, sir.
You and your so
called ''Holy club!''
lt's nothing but a way
to flaunt your piety.
There is a proper
place for religion,
and most of us
want it kept there.
Yes, l'm sure you would.
We are very happy as we are,
sir, and that does not include
sharing the Churchyard
with the devil's spawn.
Oh, God bless you, Mr. Wesley,
God bless you!
lsn't it wonderful?
(John) Well we do
what little we can...
Oh, no not you!
lt's Mr. Oglethorpe.
Haven't you heard?
He's opening the
debtor's prisons,
taking them all to
America for a new start.
Come along, everyone!
You don't know much,
Mr. Wesley, and that's a fact.
lt's not people like
you that change things.
lt's men of action.
Men like Oglethorpe.
Them what's got the power.
What you do don't
make no difference at all.
He's right, you know.
We could build charity schools,
alms houses forthe poor,
and give our time
and money to others,
but in the end it really
doesn't change very much.
Yes, but we must
try, Charles.
We must insure
our own salvation,
if nothing else.
Yes, we must try.
(John) l'm planning a lesson
on Deuteronomy 12.
Mr. White is bringing a
guest to the Holy Club today.
Very good!
Anew member, perhaps?
One can hope.
Mr. Whitefield, we each abide
by a strict method of living.
We rise earlyfor prayer
and study of the Scriptures.
We meet at an appointed
time for self- examination.
And we fulfill our
religious duties
by performing certain
works of charity together.
l believe God requires
rigid self discipline.
Exactly, Mr. Whitefield.
Exactly.
l see you will make an
excellent member of our club.
Please join us.
Now, on to business
shall we say.
[knocking]
Amessage for you, Sir.
What is it, brother?
Come.
Ah, Mr. Wesley!
Thank you for coming
on such short notice.
Allow me introduce you
to my friend and ally,
Tomochichi.
Without him, l'm afraid
my little enterprise
would have been
a dismal failure.
Please.
Your enterprise?
Sir, you are talking about
your Georgia colony?.
Quite so.
Mr. Wesley, let me be frank.
l need to ask you a question
ortwo about your beliefs.
My...beliefs?
As you may know, my Georgia
colony is funded in part
by the Societyforthe Promotion
of Christian Knowledge.
Yes a most noble
organization, sir.
We have concern
that the debtors,
who form the bulk
of our settlers,
have spiritual counsel
in their new situation.
Asituation which will be
primitive and challenging
in itself.
ln the last several years,
l have visited half the
parish churches in England.
And thus it has been my
misfortune to hear sermons
by almost half the clergy
of the Church of England.
Do you know
what, Mr. Wesley?
Most of those sermons
contained no more Christianity
than a page out of Cicero.
Philosophical platitudes
mixed up with toadying
to the local gentry.
Rarely a mention
of the Saviour,
rarely a sense
of the Scripture.
You consider yourself to be
a Christian, Mr. Wesley?.
Why, yes, of course, sir.
Most assuredly.
When you have the
occasion to preach,
do you speak about
the Scriptures
or do you quote philosophers?
l am most interested in
the study and teaching
of Scriptures, sir.
And do you believe in order?
Order and method are
central to my life.
Very well, Mr. Wesley.
l have a proposition for you...
What of my work here, Charles?
We've come so far, yet
we've so much furtherto go.
Am l to simply abandon it?
You are not the only
member of the society, John.
Are the rest of us not capable?
And what if l fail?
What if l'm not able
to endure the hardship?
l must, above all else,
ensure my salvation.
l know of no one more
able to endure hardship
than you, brother.
As for saving your soul,
you will be doing God's work,
not man's.
ls that not so?
Jackie!
Oh, my baby.
Mom!
You're like a brand
plucked from the burning.
Truly God has saved you
for some great purpose.
Oh, Jackie!
Truly God surely saved
you for some great purpose.
Jackie, what a calling!
Your Fatherwould
have been so proud.
Do sit down, Samuel.
You'll wear a groove
in the floor.
l'll have you know,
l am completely opposed
to this ridiculous scheme.
Who will care for Mother
now that Father has passed?
lt's bad enough you
refused the pastorate
which would have
provided you with a living
and a home for her
and our sisters.
But this!
l will not preach
where l am not wanted.
And you know the people
of Epworth will reject me
just as they rejected Father.
l believe that my salvation lies
in bringing Christ
to the heathens.
You should have seen this man.
Amore noble man never existed.
lt is preposterous.
l am washing my hands of it.
Thank you, Mother.
Such an endeavor!
lt will be a great loss to me,
but if l had twenty sons,
l would send them all!
l'm so glad you feel that way.
Charles is coming with us.
Me?
l'm not going to Georgia!
Well most certainly you are.
The General needs two men.
One to serve at Savannah
and the other to serve as his
secretary at Fort Frederica.
What is this?
Without even so much as
a by-your-leave, Charlie?
Charles, look,
it's perfect.
Oglethorpe asked me to
recommend the second man
and l've recommended you!
John! l'm not going to Georgia.
l'm happy here.
l need Oxford, l need
the literary society,
l need the library!
l'm not like you.
Charles, l am convinced that
this is the opportunity
our society needs to
further God's work.
And you heard Mother,
a blessed occupation,
she called it!
Also you'll need to be serving
as chaplain of Frederica.
Well there you have it,
l can't go.
You know that l'm not ordained.
l've already spoken to
the Bishop of Oxford
and you're to be
ordained this Sunday.
We agreed long ago as a family
that l was not cut of the
cloth for ordination.
You agreed with Samuel.
Most emphatically, as l recall.
lt's all been taken
care of, Charlie.
so don't make such a fuss!
Besides that, Mr. Delamotte
and Mr. lngham,
they're coming as well.
John Wesley, you are the most
interfering insufferable brother
a man has ever been tested by!
l am not going to be ordained
and l most certainly am
NOT going to Georgia!
(Voice) l now ordain
you as a deacon
of the Church of England.
Called by the Holy Spirit
to all the honors,
duties and responsibilities...
Oh, Mr. Wesley, l'm so
glad that your brother
is following the will of God.
This is not the
will of God.
This is the will of John!
(Captain)
Save your prayers Mr. Wesley,
for when we'll need them.
We shan't sink today.
No, l like a storm at
the start of a voyage,
it pulls the crew together!
Oh Charles.
[laughing]
He'll get his sea
legs soon enough.
Aye, but not till he's
retched out his guts!
[laughing]
l'll shall not forgive you.
Take heart, Charlie.
lt is by suffering
that we come to know God.
Would you open the
door, please, John.
That's the Moravians.
l hope to learn
more about them.
lt sounds like angels singing.
Why can't we sing like
that in our services?
[singing]
Mr. Wesley, l see you
have found your sea legs.
Quite so, Mr. Oglethorpe.
John was a devoted nurse.
And how goes it
with you, Mr. Wesley?.
Are you whipping the
passengers into shape?
(John) lt is our most
fervent desire
that we should
improve the souls
of everyone on this ship.
Anoble aspiration, indeed.
To that end, we have
organized the day.
Eight o'clock, morning prayers
in the main cabin,
Nine o'clock until noon,
private instruction.
Two until four after
dinner, more instruction -
Mr. Wesley!
l understand your desire to
abstain from wine and spirits
but to forego meat!
Why, you'll wither away.
Who will save our souls then?
l seek to save my own
soul Captain as well,
through abstinence.
Something to which you might
also give due consideration.
Well, l think l'll stick to
prayer, if you don't mind.
lt's always served
me verywell.
But prayer is not enough.
We must regulate the
body as well as the soul.
l shall be reading today
from William Law's
''Practical Treatise Upon
Christian Perfection.''
(Harker) Can you not give it
a rest, man?
There's others here who
what don't give a bloody fig
for your constant chatter!
William Law's
''Practical Treatise on Christian
Perfection,'' Mr. Harker!
Heathen.
Take heart, Jackie.
Avery wise man
once told me,
lt is by such suffering
we come to know God.
(Delamotte) What did you
think of Mr. Wesley's sermon
this morning?
He speaks a great deal
about becoming perfect.
Yes, it is his
hope of heaven.
lt doesn't seem
like hope to me.
lt seems more like fear.
Sir! l insist that
Mr. Harker...
Pass the word for Mr. Elliot.
Spread the word.
... that Mr. Harker be flogged.
Mr. Smithers, what is the glass?
(Smithers) lt's gone
below 29 inches, sir,
and falling.
l will not let this pass!
The man has been rude -
Yes, Captain?
Mr. Elliot, we're in for a
blow, no doubt about it.
Hail the mizzen and
trim the mainsail.
Right away sir.
Mr. Wesley, l would suggest
that you return to your cabin.
lmmediately.
And Mr. Wesley, now is
the time for your prayers.
[prayers]
[screams]
[singing]
lt's a good thing
we're close to Georgia.
lt will be slow sailing
with only two masts.
Aye.
What are you
standing around for?
Get to cleaning up this mess!
Would you care
for a bit of help?
Yes!
They're not the most
courteous sort, are they?.
Brother Nitschmann, l was
watching your group last night.
l could not help but notice
that they did not seem afraid.
Do you know what he said?
What?
''Why should we be afraid?''
Yes.
How can they not be?
Lord knows, l thought
the end had come.
l don't know.
But they have a
peace l don't have.
And a confidence
l certainly don't feel.
Strange as it sounded though,
l found it very intriguing.
(Little John) lf you do well,
will you be accepted?
And if you do not do well,
sin is crouching at the door,
its desire is for you,
but you must master it.
Genesis 4:6.
And will you do well, Jackie,
orwill sin be your master?
l wish to be accepted,
Mother, so l will do well.
And how will you do that?
Do you have a plan by
which you will lead your life?
l will not be so
bad as other children.
Well that's a very
noble aspiration,
but is it enough, do you think,
to gain admission into heaven?
l shall read my Bible, go to
church and pray every day.
(Susanna)
ls it enough, do you think,
to gain admission
into heaven?
l feel that l am not
doing enough to serve God.
How could you possibly
do more, John?
Every minute of your
day is in his service.
Earlier, l had thought
that l should like to marry.
But l don't see how you can be
devoted to both God and a wife?
There's simply not room
in my heart for both.
Yes, l think l shall remain
single, devoted only to God.
l think that's
rather a good idea.
Do you?
The thought of you breeding
actually turn my stomach.
(Sailor) Land ho!
Georgia!
Anew world.
'Ere!
Don't you touch me beans!
l was told that this was
to be my garden, sir.
Aye, that it is, but
l'm to care for it.
l took care of it
for Reverend Quincy,
l'll take care of it for you.
James Locke, yerworship.
'Mr Wesley' will do.
Pleased to meet you, Mr Locke.
lf l may, l don't see any
of the medicinal herbs spouted.
Ahh, ye'll find those in
the Bovey Sisters' garden.
They place much
stock in them.
l just grow beans and taters
and turnips and the like.
l'm most interested in
physic and cures of the sort.
Yer'll be most popular then, the
folk do love to be physicked.
But l don't believe
we've ever had a parson
that did the bleedin'.
Oh, no, nothing like that.
But l'm interested in the use
of herbs and common items
that can be used for
medicinal purposed.
l'm writing a book on it.
Oh -- l were to tell yer
that the magistrate
expects you fer dinner.
You and Mr. Delamotte.
Yer'd best not be late.
[speaking in French]
l wonder, could we not
make an arrangement?
My Sophie would be most grateful
should you consent to teach her.
lt would be a delight.
How did you find the
school, Mr. Delamotte?
Was it to your satisfaction?
Quite so.
The children seem
eagerto learn.
Mr. Causton, l was wondering,
how soon might l obtain a
guide to the lndian nations?
There'll be no need forthat.
Your job is here, ministering
to the people of Savannah.
But l had hoped that l could
bring the word of God
to the savages.
lt is my principal
purpose for coming to Georgia.
lt is quite impossible.
The natives are at
warwith each other.
But Mr. Oglethorpe assured me -
Perhaps, Mr. Wesley could
visit the trading post?
Surely there could
be no harm in that.
As long as he does not
neglect his duties here,
l have no objection.
What harm does it do, to
adorn ourselves with gold,
or pearls, or costly array?
lt naturally tends
to breed vanity,
and by vanity l mean,
the love and desire to
be admired and praised.
That was an excellent sermon.
Mr. Causton was
none to happy with it
but l think you made
a friend with his wife.
We must always speak the truth,
no matter how much it offends.
J'ai, tu as, il a ...
l have, thou hast,
he has...
J'ai, tu as, il a.
Nous avons.
Excellent!
You are a wonderfully
quick learner.
Oh, l love learning.
l want to know everything
about our world.
Do you also desire
to learn about God?
Especially about God.
Without God, our lives
would be dull indeed.
Would you also like to
study the scriptures?
Yes, Mr. Wesley,
l'd like that very much.
Quit yerfighting.
There's plenty more
where that came from.
Cusseta!
This is MicoApokta,
the Speaker of
the Osochi tribe.
Erkenvkv Wesley
ossetv Osochi.
What do you wish
to preach to us?
l wish to preach to you
of God's Son, Jesus.
We have heard of this Ye-sus.
Catolico priests
have visited us.
They tell us of this Ye-sus,
and that we must be
good and give up evil.
Yes, that is correct!
lt is the white man that
must put locks on his doors
to protect from
otherwhite men.
The Creek do not need locks.
l cannot argue with that.
Many white men are evil,
and l preach to
stop their evil.
lf you come to Osochi to
listen as well as to talk,
perhaps you will learn new
things of the Great Spirit.
Yes, yes.
l would like that.
(John) My dreams are all
offire or of the storm.
l am terrified of dying.
Where is my faith?
This is not why l
stopped you today.
ls there something on
your mind, Herr Wesley?.
ls it that obvious?
Yes.
The storm on the ship.
l was very much afraid
to die, Herr Nitschmann.
And it tells me that there is
something lacking in my faith.
Perhaps you should
talk to Herr Spangenburg.
Come with me.
Herr Spangenburg, l believe
there is something lacking
in my relationship with God.
And l was wondering,
how does one obtain a
faith such as yours?
First l must ask you a
question ortwo, Herr Wesley.
Do you have the
witness within yourself?
l'm not sure l understand
what that means.
Does the Holy Spirit of God
bearwitness in your heart,
that you are a child of God?
Do you know that Jesus
Christ is your Savior?
Yes, l know that Jesus is
the Savior of the world.
Nein.
Do you know that
YOU are saved?
Yes...l have always...yes.
Nein.
You hesitate.
You must not hesitate.
You must be certain.
When the Holy Spirit of
God is in your heart,
your heart is filled
with joy, and you know.
Yes, but how do you do that?
You must open your
heart, Herr Wesley.
heart to the Savior.
Mr. Wesley.
(John) Miss Sophie!
Hello.
(John) Hello.
Will you walk with me?
Yes, yes of course!
My cousin wishes me to
join her in Fort Frederica.
Well what will l
do without you?
l must confess, l have become
quite attached to your presence.
l shall write to you daily
and think of you hourly.
You are a dear,
sweet girl, Miss Sophie,
but you must spend your time
in contemplation of our Savior.
Oh! l will.
l promise you l will.
Well in that case l look
forward to your letters.
And, l yours.
Good day.
Are you ready?
What is it?
lt appears that my brother has
not made an auspicious beginning
at Frederica.
As there is no Church,
l have been
conducting the services
underneath a live oak tree.
...and in the world to
come life everlasting.
Amen.
The grace of our Lord Jesus
CHrist and the love of God...
[gunshot]
The grace of our
Lord Jesus Christ,
and the love of God, and the
fellowship of the Holy Ghost,
be with us all evermore.
Amen.
Mr. Davison.
ls not hunting and sporting
expressly forbidden
on the Lord's Day?
Aye, sir, that it is.
Well then, l believe
that it is your duty
to find out who fired that
shot and have him arrested.
We shall have no desecration
of the Lord's Day.
(Hawkins) But l have
sick to attend to!
Mrs Lawley is already
starting the pains,
and may deliver at any moment!
Mr. Wesley said we must have
strict adherence to the rules.
You tell that self-righteous
pimple of a preacher
that he's responsible
for my patients now!
The babywas stillborn.
The people seem to blame
Charles for his death.
How dreadful for him.
Yes.
He says that few people
will attend prayers any more.
Mr. Causton sir,
l thought perhaps,
l could accompany
Miss Sophie to Frederica.
l could see to my
brotherwhile there.
Absolutely not.
You have your duties
here to attend to.
l'll not allow
you to shirk them.
As for my niece,
Mr. Williamson has kindly
agreed to serve as her escort.
l did not like him.
Not at all.
l wonderthat Mr. Causton
thinks so highly of him,
to entrust Miss Sophie
to his care.
ls something the matter?
lt's the school.
Several of the children are
too poorto afford shoes,
the other children
tease them mercilessly.
l've tried everything l can
think of to make them stop;
reason, punishment,
they still persist.
l wonder, would you take
my appointments tomorrow,
and allow me to
teach the school?
Yes, of course.
Good. l think l have an idea.
No-shoes, no-shoes, no-shoes!
Well!
lt is true that l
have no shoes,
but l find it extraordinarily
rude and unchristian
that you would comment on it.
Shall we go on to
our lessons then.
Welcome home, Mr. Wesley.
Are you the holy bigot
that reported our bit of rum?
Yes.
Spirituous liquors are
forbidden in Georgia.
All we did was bring a cask off
the ship for an evening of fun.
But you knew
it to be illegal.
Ain't no harm
in a bit of rum.
As l recall, Mr. Harker, one of
the reasons you were in prison
was your love for gin.
lt is hard enough in this
wilderness to make ourway,
without drunkenness
adding to the burden.
Ezekiel Harris
got twelve lashes.
His back is like a
piece of raw meat,
thanks to you.
l didn't like you in
Oxford Mr. Wesley
and l like you
even less here.
You stay out of my way
and out of my business.
l shall do exactly as my
conscience bids me to do.
Mr. Wesley.
Aletter from Frederica.
Come.
Mr. Causton.
l must insist that you allow
me to travel to Frederica.
My brother is very ill and there
is concern he may not survive.
Very well.
Mr. Williamson, arrange
for a guide, straight away.
Thank you, sir.
l appreciate your assistance.
Mr. Wesley, l have
a request of you.
lt seems my niece is
anxious to return to Savannah.
Will you see to
her safe return?
Yes, of course, sir.
Thank you again.
(John) Thank you so much
for your hospitality.
How do you come
to be here, Cicero,
in the middle of
the Georgia swamps?
Well l, l runs away,
and now l'm a free man.
No slavery is
allowed here in Georgia.
Are you not afraid
here by all yourself?
No sir. No sir.
l am happy.
Mighty happy.
Sorry sir.
Dear Lord, thank you for all
this bounty and all myfish.
Amen.
l am surprised that
you know God.
He is my friend.
Yourfriend?
How do you know him
without any instruction?
Who is here to teach you?
He's in my heart and
that is all l need.
Charlie.
Oh Jackie.
Thank God you've come.
l thank God you
are still alive.
l've brought some
physick for you.
This should really
help clear things up.
lt's straight out of my garden.
Here, take this.
lt must be efficacious,
it tastes terrible.
This is all your fault.
You brought me
here against my will,
and it has been farworse
than anything l could
have envisioned.
lt was God's will Charles.
You double-dyed hypocrite!
lt had nothing to do with the
will of God and you know it.
lt's your will,
your driving will,
it's always yourwill.
You always know what to do
and what everyone else
should do as well.
(Oglethorpe) Well.
l'm glad to see you're finally
feeling better Mr. Wesley,
but there are other issues.
You have managed to
alienate most of the residents.
Your service as secretary
has been marginal at best.
The situation cannot continue.
l have decided that you
must return to England,
and the Trustees must appoint
anotherto fill your place.
Now, l have no wish to cause
you embarrassment or shame.
l have some important letters
that must be delivered
to the Trustees, and so l shall
appoint you to carry them.
Thus there shall be no blot on
your record or on your name.
Thank you, sir.
l shall dispatch the
letters with haste.
(Oglethorpe)
You are dismissed.
l'll write you from Boston
before we leave for home.
Give my love to Mother!
Mind those women,
brother.
Every time l tried to sit down
and pray or study the scripture,
l found myself longing for you.
For your guidance.
You are the rock
upon which l depend.
As much as l'd like to stay,
l think it's time we
head back to Savannah.
Mr. Wesley?.
Will you not lie closer?
l'm very much afraid.
Yes, of course.
Heavenly father, we
ask you for strength,
and for guidance.
Keep us from temptation.
ln your Son's name, amen.
Mr. Wesley's back!
Mr. Wesley!
Have you been
doing your lessons?
Yes.
You'll never believe
what happened today.
Excuse me.
So sorry.
No. No.
lt's quite all right,
quite all right.
Please.
(John) So, what is it
we're not to believe?
Your little trick with
the shoes has paid off.
The teasing has stopped, and
some of the wealthier children
even came in today
barefoot themselves!
l am very pleased
to hearthat.
l should see to my aunt.
Will you excuse me?
Yes, l'll walk you out.
Please.
l am wondering about
your intentions.
Yes?
Your intentions
with Miss Hopkey.
She is kind, gentle
in spirit, serene.
People expect you to marry.
Marry?
But l have a vow!
ln name only it seems.
She is smitten with him.
He is a favorite
of Oglethorpe's.
lt could be to
our advantage.
And to hers.
Ah, Mr. Wesley!
Aword.
Everything you see there
is mine, Mr. Wesley.
Over 500 acres.
(John) l know you have
done quite well, sir.
But what you may not know
is that my niece is
herself quite well off.
She inherited a considerable
amount from my brother,
a sum which l manage.
l see sir.
That girl will not be
easy until she is married.
But there are few here you
would consider a fit match.
You miss my meaning.
We have plenty.
All l require is that he
be an honest, good man.
He need not have a
penny to his name.
l can supply him
with a maintenance.
l'm not quite sure
what you're saying sir.
l believe my niece is in
love with you, Mr. Wesley.
Mr. Causton.
Her aunt finds you to
be a most worthy man.
l give her up to you.
Do with herwhat you will.
Take her into your own hands,
promise herwhat you will
and l will make it good.
l cannot speak
plainer than that.
And what would
the consequence be
if you do not break
off the relationship?
Why, l fear l
would marry her!
l don't see why
you should not!
Herr Wesley, l do not understand
where you have this idea
not to marry.
This is not to my knowledge
a requirement of the
Church of England?
No, no, it is my own pledge.
Ah. Your own pledge.
Herr Wesley, we try
diligently first to ascertain
what is the will of God,
and then to do what we must
to fulfill that, to obey.
lt seems to me that more often
you decide what you will do,
and you seek to
impose that on God.
You see, Herr Wesley,
we nearly always marry
before going into
the mission field.
The man and the woman
are together in service.
l don't know what l should
do without my dear Catherina.
Ja, ja.
You see, marriage
is ordained by God.
The Scriptures say
that if you burn,
then you should marry.
l think all of this is a sign
that you should marry.
l don't think you understand...
Hmm.
l think l understand very well.
l have something l
want to ask of you.
l want you to pray to God
that l am doing what He wants.
l have decided l
must keep my vow.
l shall inform
Miss Sophie immediately.
No. No!
l cannot take fire into my
heart and not be burned by it.
But that is the
nature of love, is it not?
What has come over you?
l will not betray God.
l have not asked you to.
Look at me.
You are the dearest
of girls to me.
And if l should ever marry,
my hope is that it
would be to you.
Tell me plain, John, do
you desire to marry me?
Can l hope be yourwife?
l must first honor my
commitments to God.
When l have succeeded with
my mission to the lndians -
And when will that be?
l don't know.
Oh. l see.
[speaking in French]
And l won't be having
breakfast with you any longer.
People wonderwhat
l might be doing
at your home for so long.
Let them wonder no more.
Did l do the right thing?
How does one know if they're
doing God's will or their own?
When Causton showed me
that beautiful knoll,
all that could be mine,
l saw my life unfold before
me there on that hill.
Miss Sophie by my side,
our sweet children playing.
And l was a fat and
comfortable old man.
ls that what God wants of me?
Mr. Wesley.
Mrs. Causton.
Thank you so much
for coming.
Please be seated.
Mr. Causton and l are
exceedingly obliged
for all you've done
for our Sophie.
l have done so little.
Nonsense.
You've done a great deal.
And now we have one
more thing to ask of you.
Will you marry her...
To Mr. Williamson?
Yes.
Mr. Williamson has asked
Mr. Causton's permission,
and he has given it...
Unless you'll have
something to say against it?
lt's not too late.
(John) Miss Sophie!
Mr. Wesley!
Your aunt tells
me that you are...
Engaged.
Yes, to Mr. Williamson.
He proposed last night
and l accepted,
provided you have
nothing to say?
(John) But l don't see how you
can be devoted to both God
and wife.
There's simply not room
in my heart for both.
But l have a vow!
Though l speak with the
tongues of men and of angels
and have not love, l am
become a sounding brass,
a tinkling cymbal.
And though l have
the gift of prophecy,
and understand all
mysteries and all knowledge,
and though l have all
faith so as to move mountains,
and have not love,
l am nothing.
And... and though l give all
my goods to feed the poor,
and delivereth my
body to be burned,
and have not love,
it profiteth me nothing.
Miss Sophie!
Mrs. Williamson,
if you please.
Your eye!
l ran into a door.
Adoor?
Yes, it was dark.
Well, you really should put
a piece of beefsteak on it,
it is a proven cure.
Thank you.
Do you have something
to say, sir?
Yes.
lt's about your
absences at communion.
lt is a most serious matter,
neglecting your religious
duty in that manner.
(Miss Sophie) l have been busy.
lt has gone on so long
that l must require that
you meet with me privately
before you may take
communion again,
so that l am assured of
your genuine repentance.
My repentance?
(John) Yes, it's required
by Church law.
Thank you Mr. Wesley.
l shall take yourwords
under careful advisement.
Good day, Mrs. Williamson.
Good day.
The body and blood of Christ.
The body and blood of--
Mrs. Williamson, l told you that
you must speak to me privately
before you could
partake of the Eucharist again.
l must refuse you.
Fine!
We'll just see
who'll be repentant,
Mr. John Wesley!
Excuse me.
Constable Harris, good morning!
l'm sorry, Mr. Wesley, but l
must place you under arrest.
Under arrest?
For what?
Yes.
Mr. Williamson is suing you for
defamation of the character
of his wife.
l'm sorry, sir, you'll
have to come with me.
Defamation.
Mr. Williamson, what are
the damages sought?
Athousand pounds sterling.
Why, it's a king's ransom!
Mr. Wesley only earns
twenty- eight pounds a year.
He could never afford it.
Mr. Wesley, what say you?
That this court has no powerto
interrogate me on these matters.
Every part of the incident
concerns ecclesiastical law.
That may be your
opinion Mr. Wesley,
but this court finds that it
does indeed have jurisdiction,
and shall proceed to trial as
soon as we can empanel a jury
to hearthe case.
Case continued.
Listen to me, you arrogant....
You have insulted me
and my entire family!
l have drawn my sword, sir,
and l shall not sheathe it
until l have had satisfaction!
Now get out!
But make sure you are here
Tuesday next to face a jury.
This is getting ridiculous!
How much longer are we
going to go on like this?
Seven trial sessions,
and not a bit of progress!
Please listen to me.
Herr Causton is out to ruin you.
He and his wife are doing
everything they can
to turn the people against you.
He waits until the jurors
are sufficiently coached
in their hatred.
(Delamotte) John, he's right.
You know that.
l'll not sneak away
like a guilty coward!
l'll not do it.
But you can't stay here and
be convicted unfairly.
As much as it
pains me to say it,
l think you must
return to England.
Your ministry here has ended.
You should put him in jail.
l can't, unless he actually
leaves the jurisdiction.
He's the apple of
Oglethorpe's eye.
l'm flirting with
trouble as it is.
Then l know how to handle it.
Yes, l'll pay a gold sovereign
to anyone who catches
Mr. Wesley leaving Savannah!
Cor!
Asovereign!
l came to bring
Christ to the lndians!
And what have l accomplished?
That l didn't even know
myself what salvation is!
They're still out there,
just like every other night.
Harker has the best view.
He'd kill his
motherfortuppence,
much less a sovereign.
ls everything ready?
(Delamotte) We're to wait
for Mr. Locke's signal.
(Harker) Where did he go?
(Locke) He took a dinghy
from the south landing
mor'n a 'aar hour ago.
Ye'll no catch 'em now.
Yer all set, sir.
Ol' Jenson was
watching the rear 'ere,
but now he's sleeping
orf the rum l gave 'im.
Mr. Locke, you know that
spirituous liquors are...
Now, Mr. Wesley, don't
a-go lookin' a gift horse
in the mouth.
Asides, it were for
medicinal purposes.
Now, Mr. Coates is
upstream by the point.
Okay.
Good luck, Mr. Wesley!
Mr. Locke, l thank you for
your kindness and your help.
Stay in the shadows!
(John) They followed our
decoy downssteam
whilst l made my way upssteam
and crossed the mud flats
to get to Port Royal
where l obtained passage on the
HMS Samuel with Captain Percy.
Gentlemen, l have brought
discredit on the cloth.
And on you.
And forthat you have
my deepest apology.
That is not the opinion of
the Trustees, Mr. Wesley.
Looking overthe reports we have
for yourtwo years in Georgia,
we see that the church
was better attended,
and according to our inspectors,
the working people have
taken a more energetic role
in the life of the settlement.
We do not feel you
have failed at all.
We feel you have
ably prepared the way,
and your successorwill be able
to make even greater progress.
My successor?
Who shall that be, sir?
Mr. Whitefield.
Mr. George Whitefield?
Even so.
He's on his way this
very moment to Savannah.
With his very, entertaining
and popular style,
he will be able to build upon
the legacy that you have begun.
We congratulate you,
Mr. Wesley
and we thank you
for your service.
Thank you.
What will you do
now, Mr. Wesley?
l don't know.
Mr. Bray is a
compassionate landlord.
He has charged me to see
to your brother's comfort.
Wait a moment, his comfort?
He has been quite ill.
No need to worry.
He is in good hands.
Jackie!
Oh, heavens,
you are burning up.
lt's nothing.
l'm better.
Not so much.
You need to rest.
Are you Herr Wesley?
l am Peter.
My brothers in Savannah
speak highly of you.
They were most kind to me.
l shall miss their guidance.
Jackie!
l am so very, very
happy you are home.
How long has he been like this?
Perhaps you have
some more of that...
He is betterthan he
was two weeks ago.
His body will heal with
time and God's blessing.
l have no concern
for his spirit.
The Holy Spirit
truly resides in him.
Brother Boehler,
may l speak with you?
l simply feel that my
affections for her
were taking away from
my focus on....
This woman was not the problem.
lt is your heart
that is the problem.
You are confused.
Yes. l am.
To be honest Brother Boehler,
lately l've been feeling
more and more that
my faith is a lie.
Do you know in your
heart that you are saved?
That is the very question
Mr. Spangenburg asked me,
and l told him yes.
But l lied.
You must not lie to yourself.
Tonight, everything has
come to this one moment,
everything has led you here,
to realize that you
cannot earn salvation.
Yes, but everything
l have learned,
everything that l
have been taught,
is that by good works and proper
living one shall attain heaven.
Where is that in the Bible?
lf you, by your goodness,
shall be saved,
why did Christ die?
Tonight the Saviour offers you
everything you have sought for
so long, as a free gift,
if you will but take it!
When you do, you will know
what we call Heart Religion.
l don't know what l
believe any more.
l just feel so -- pulled -- in
so many different directions.
Come with me tonight,
we have a meeting.
Mr. Bray will be there.
My grace is
sufficient for thee:
for my strength is made
perfect in weakness.
This here is true, for l was
as weak as any God ever made.
So often l used to
gamble away my money
while the kiddies
had naught to eat.
ln my cups,
l used to beat my dearwife.
But the gracious Lord has saved
me with his wonderful grace.
And now, today,
my heart is at peace.
How can it be
that a man like that,
who has led a life of sin,
can be in such peace while
l am in such turmoil?
Are you not a sinner, too?
Oh, l hope you're not
comparing me with him...
Yes, Peter.
l am just as much
a sinner as he.
But you speak of this
instantaneous conversion that...
l cannot accept that a man
can just be instantly saved,
someone like that,
where someone who has lived a
righteous and careful life --
John!
Do you hope to be saved?
Yes, of course!
Why do you hope it?
Because l have used my
best endeavors to serve God.
You, see, you see.
Again, yourwill.
Yourworks.
My brother, this
philosophy of yours,
it must be entirely
purged away.
l have been looking
through the Scriptures
for instances of conversion,
and indeed Peter is right.
Every one an instantaneous
transformation,
not because of deeds
but because of Grace.
That is what we have been
trying to tell you, John.
Look at you Charlie!
You're so content, so
at peace with the world.
l feel that no matter
how hard l look,
l'm never going to find
such comfort.
John.
Perhaps you should
return to Epworth.
Mother would be most happy.
That's out of the question.
What?
No, nothing.
l have good news
from Savannah.
You have been acquitted!
lt seems Mr. Causton has been
removed from his post as well.
He had some issues
with his accounting,
among other things.
Are you not pleased?
lt doesn't really
solve my problem -- me.
l've been thinking l
should stop preaching.
But why would you do that?
How can l preach to others
something l don't have myself?
My brother, do not
stop preaching.
Preach faith
until you have faith.
Then you will preach
faith because you have faith.
For all have sinned and fallen
short of the glory of God.
How often have we heard
that comment from Paul
and ignored its true meaning?
Awoman dead drunk on gin we
might hold to be worthless.
But l am of no more worth.
And neither are you!
We have all sinned and fallen
short of the glory of God.
But at least a woman who is dead
drunk on gin is not a hypocrite.
Mr. Wesley...
lf l may, please, it is my
belief that your parishioners,
and in fact the majority of the
parishioners all across England
have been coddled into thinking
they may believe whatever
Scriptures they like...
Mr. Wesley, no matter
what our friendship of old,
what you said in
there was inexcusable.
l'm sorry, John.
You are no longer
welcome in my pulpit.
Mr. White.
Mr. White!
l trust that your
missionary work in Georgia
will be more
blessed than mine.
As do l!
My ship is waiting.
Thank you for everything, Peter.
Godspeed.
And with you Herr Wesley.
John!
ln here.
Jackie!
Did you see Peter off?
l did indeed.
And l trust that his
experience in Georgia
will be more blessed than mine.
And mine!
John, l must tell you.
l've written a poem, a hymn.
l'll read it for you.
Where shall my
wand'ring soul begin,
How shall l to
heaven aspire?
Aslave redeemed
from death and sin,
a brand plucked
from eternal fire...
Let me make you some
tar-waterforthe cough.
No, Jackie, l'm fine.
You have a cure for everything.
Jackie, stop!
lt's always so that
you're in control.
Don't you understand,
sometimes you must just rest,
rest in the will of God?
No!
No, Charles, l don't understand.
l feel so alone.
Peter has left, and
you're writing hymns
about an experience
that l cannot share.
l feel as if God
has abandoned me.
Look at me.
Go to the meeting
tonight with Mr. Bray.
Open your heart.
Forthe first time in your
life, let yourself go.
l don't know what
that means, Charles.
They are hypocrites still,
who live virtuous lives but
without eagerness and love;
in their heart they are
enemies of God's law
and like to judge other people.
What is he reading?
l believe it's
Martin Luther's introduction
to the Book of Romans.
lt's an excellent commentary on
how we are saved through faith
and not...works.
That is why faith alone
makes someone just
and fulfills the law; faith it
is that brings the Holy Spirit
through the merits of Christ.
The Spirit, in turn renders
the heart glad and free,
as the law demands.
Then good works
proceed from faith itself.
You've found it?
No!
lt has found me.
My heart is
strangelywarmed!
Oh, l have prayed
daily for you.
Where shall my
wondering soul begin, ,
how shall l all
to heaven aspire? ,
Aslave redeemed
from death and sin, ,
Abrand plucked
from eternal fire,
(Voice) 'Ere, quiet!
How shall l equal
triumphs raise,
(Man) Quiet!
(Man 2) l'm stying' to sleep!
What is this, you say?
Mercyfor all?
Yes, yes, that is the truth!
Mercy for Zacheaus,
a public robber!
Mercy for Mary Magdalene,
a common harlot!
Then l hear you say,
you sinner, and you,
''Why, perhaps maybe
there is even mercyfor me!''
Don't ever darken the
door of this church again!
(Man) l'll speak
to the Archbishop!
The man should be defrocked...
(Samuel) What is this l hear?
That my younger brother
has been barred
from nearly every
pulpit in London?
Have you taken
leave of your senses?
No, Brother,
l've just come to them.
Rather like the
Prodigal Son, in fact.
You have intentionally
offended some of the wealthiest
and most respected supporters
of church work in England.
You don't see a
problem with that?
lf what l said offended them,
then perhaps they were
in need of offending.
lt was nothing but
the truth, Samuel.
The truth!
The truth as you see it!
The truth as l have
it from Scripture.
Jackie.
You say that you're
different now.
But l don't see the difference.
You've always
visited the prisons,
you've always helped the poor.
Why is doing that
now so different?
l do it for a different
reason now, Samuel.
Before, l did good
works out of fear of Hell,
out of desperation
to save myself.
No matter how
noble my deeds seemed,
they were all for me.
And now they're not?
No. No, now they're not.
Now l don't fear Hell--
l know that l am saved Samuel.
When l visit the prisons and
bring food to the hungry
because l understand what it
means to love thy neighbor.
l don't see any difference.
The l shall pray
that one day you will.
You and Charles have
clearly lost your minds.
lf you wish to act the
fool, that is your affair.
But please don't
drag my good name
down into the
gutterwith yours.
lt sounds as if your
ministry in Georgia
was a wonderful success.
Aye, but l'm making
myself useful preaching here.
l wish l could
say the same.
l've been barred from
nearly every pulpit in London.
Then you must do as l do!
Forget the pulpits
and the parishes!
There are no
churches where l preach.
New mines, new mills,
new manufactories,
all have all been built
outside the old parishes.
All of them are filled
with needy souls.
The bishops will not
build them churches.
They think ...
Well, you know what they think.
Yes, they are strangers,
outsiders.
Animals, more like.
Yes, but it goes
against the grain,
to preach outside the church.
l have always
believed in proper order,
in maintaining the traditions.
Order?
Open your eyes, man!
There's no orderto it.
And what's wrong
with field preaching?
What do you think
the Lord himself did?
He often spoke in
the synagogues.
Afew times, John, a few times.
Look at the Bible!
Where do you think he preached
the Sermon on the Mount?
Where did He preach before
the Loaves and the Fishes?
ln the fields.
Come with me to Bristol, John!
Come and see what l mean.
Thousands come
to hear me preach.
Gin shops close,
magistrates' offices empty.
These people are
desperate forthe Gospel.
l need your help.
They need your help!
Do you know why so many
congregations are dead?
Because they have dead
men preaching to them!
Today, my brothers
and sisters in the Lord,
John Wesley, a man
whose heart is alive,
shall preach to you!
Thank you.
Good morning.
How a sinner may be
justified before God,
the Lord and Judge of all.
You must look to Jesus!
There is the Lamb of God,
who takes away your sins.
And you who feel
just as fit for hell,
are just as fit
to advance his glory;
the glory of his free grace.
Come quickly!
Believe in the Lord Jesus;
and thou, even thou,
art reconciled to God.
Now, who shall open their
hearts to the Lord today?
Well?
What did l tell you?
John!
Have you lost your mind?!
Just a few repairs,
and we can have the
printing press overthere,
the chapel over here!
Areal place for us
to work and live.
And a home for Mother.
Ahome for Mother?
Here?
Yes, trust me!
That thou my God
should'st die for me.
Amazing Love,
how can it be,
that thou my God
should'st die for me.
Hear what comfortable words our
Saviour Christ saith unto all
who truly turn unto him.
''Come unto me all
that travail...
and-- and l will refresh you.''
You should
have seen them.
An entire pew of
filthy beggars.
They are all Christians now,
and that is their parish church.
Nevertheless, Mr. Wesley,
you will not bring them again.
And why not?
Because l've commanded it.
You are interfering
with the governance
of one of my parishes, bringing
offense to the good worshippers
by bringing these...
strangers among us.
l would ask however,
why you believe you have
the right to interfere so?
l believe it is God's will
that l should revive the
Church of England.
You believe it's God's will!
What if l believe it isn't?
Pretending
extraordinary revelations
and gifts of the Holy Spirit
is a horrid thing!
Avery horrid thing!
You have no license but to
preach in your own parish.
And since you
have no parish...
My Lord, l look upon the
whole world as my parish.
Good day.
Bloody Hell!
Dear! Language!
The Gentleman's Magazine says
that this upstart preacher
could upset the supply of coal
and push prices to the sky!
But what can preaching have
to do with the price of coal?
All the colliers go to hear
him bythe thousands.
They're not working.
He gives them
ideas above their station.
Here, he tells them,
these dirty, vulgar miners,
that they are just
as good as we are!
Oh! How horrid!
Amen.
Mr. Furniss, how are
you feel today?.
Well, sir, you talk
straight with me before
like no one else has so
l'll talk straight back.
Sitting here saying
prayers l feel right daft.
And what of your drinking?
Well, l stayed
off it forthree days now,
that's bad, eh?
ln fact, me old wife
think it's quite a miracle.
Morning, my lord.
Ah! Baker, do you recall that
arrangement we had last year
when a gentleman caused
trouble forthe mine?
l, that l do my lord.
We took care of him
good an' proper...
Have you heard of
this preacher, Wesley?.
Aye, my lord.
He is causing a
bit of trouble...
Let me know when my
troubles are over,
theres' a good chap.
Aye, my lord.
l would like to thank you
all for your kindness.
Oh, tis no trouble, Mr Wesley.
We are delighted to
have you at our table.
...And the vicar says
this man Wesley
is a threat to the Church!
The good folk around here
they are in such need of
hearing your message.
...And l say we should
go out and get him!
l believe that the
folk everywhere
are in need of hearing
about God's love.
'Ere, what's that?
Oh, blessed Lord, it's a
mob, and they're comin' here!
Alright, you heard him,
children, let's hold hands,
let's pray.
[praying]
Oh, Mr. Wesley,
they'll burn the place down!
What are we going to do?
lt's me they want.
Lock the door.
[crowd yelling]
l am John Wesley!
Why do you come out
against me with clubs
as if l were a criminal?
What wrong have l done you?
You preach heresy!
Heresy?
l preach the Bible,
l preach of God's love!
l have come here to help
you to improve your lives.
What wrong is there in that?
Yer given' folk ideas
above their station!
Above their station?
Each one of you
is a child of God,
each one of you has the
chance to become a great soul.
What station is
there better than that?
Heresy!
What station higher?
[crowd yelling]
Will you hear me speak?
Kill him!
Let him speak!
l know that some of
you are here tonight
because you've been
paid to do so.
But l would ask you this:
Did they ask you to do this
because they care for
yourwives, your children?
Or do they simply
look to use you?
And how often would you
allow them to do that?
l have come to tell you
how you may be free
of the sin that binds you.
l'e come to help you!
The mine owners,
they do not want me to speak
the plain truth to you.
They would rather hold you
in ignorance of the truth:
that you too may be saved.
They would rather
treat you like animals,
that you would work yourselves
to death in the mines
without a glimmer of hope.
But l am come here to
preach hope to you,
the hope of God's saving faith!
Now, l know that
there are those here
who are bound to
the slavery of gin.
And you wake each
morning to the gin-sickness,
to realize that the night before
you have beaten your wives.
And you swear that you
will never do it again,
but evening comes around
and you are once again
falling into the slavery.
Many of you have been
told all your lives
that you are marked
to burn in hell,
and that there is nothing
that you can do about it.
But l am here to
tell you that is a lie,
you are as much a child of
God as the gentry orthe vicar.
God is waiting, He is waiting
for you to give Him your hearts.
And if you would but do
that, you all would be saved.
l came here tonight
to kill you, Wesley.
But now l will spend
my life to protect you.
Truly, l shouldn't be here.
l must have had a
guardian angel on my shoulder.
The opposition we face
may be a terrible trial
but more and more letters come
in for you to preach every day.
Surely we are
winning this battle?
Look, John.
You're not ordained!
lt's true, sir, we don't have
the learning you gentlemen do,
but we know the Word.
And we believe.
We know God's word.
l'm absolutely
opposed to the idea.
Send out lay preachers
and you'll be seen
as ordaining priests.
lt's just the opening
our enemies need
to say we have started
an illegal sect.
l'll not hear of it.
l completely agree
with Charles on this.
l am sorry but...
Mr. Wesley, with all
respect, sir--
the people, they're desperate.
Thousands of souls
need encouragement,
and you're only one man.
You've let us speak
before the societies,
you've even let women speak!
The societies in Bristol
need guidance, sir.
With your permission,
we'd both like to help.
Jackie, l have heard you preach
that all are equal
in the sight of God,
that faith is given
to simple souls...
You won't find many simpler
than us, Mr. Wesley!
lt's against my
better judgment.
But l will allow you to preach
for a time, gentlemen,
and we shall see how it goes.
Shall l tell Epworth
you are coming.
No. No.
My lord.
Yes, what is it?
l found this at the door, sir.
Let's liken it to a square,
where each side is
supported by the others.
And everything that we do is
interpreted using four criteria:
The Bible first of course,
and then reason, tradition,
and of course ending with
our own personal experience.
Ho, Mr. Wesley, you'll have
more people mad at you now,
if you say reason
and personal experience
must be applied to the Bible!
What did Jesus saywas the
first and greatest commandment?
Love the Lord your God
with all your heart,
with all your soul and...
with all your mind.
And with all your mind,
absolutely.
God would not have
given us wits
if He did not intend
us to use them!
These Methodies seek only to
destroy the Church of England,
to tear it down
stone by stone...
Gracious heavens!
They are allowing women
to speak in their meetings!
Several disorderly persons,
styling themselves as
Methodist preachers go about...
...And against the
peace of the King.
All are commanded
to search after
the said Methodist preachers
and bring them before
the magistrates.
Our Father, which art in
heaven, hallowed be thy name.
Thy Kingdom come,
thy will be done
on earth as it is in heaven.
Give us this day--
You don't sound like a
Church of England preacher.
Ay?
And how does a Christian
sound to your ear, sir?
You preach forgiveness?
Yah, l forgive you.
Forgive this!
This would not have happened if
we'd not allowed him to preach.
We haven't done
anything, Charles.
We haven't.
We have only
preached the truth.
Dear Mr. Seward
only preached the truth.
We are opposed because
we speak the truth!
lt could have been
you or me Charles.
Oh, no-- no, no!
(John) We will persevere.
His death will not be in vain.
l have a favorite story.
lt's about ''Little Bo Peep''
who lost her sheep.
God wants you to know He
does not play Bo Peep with us.
When He lost His sheep, He sent
His only Son to find them.
For the Kingdom of Heaven
is as a man traveling
to a far country,
who called his own servants and
delivered to them his goods.
To one he gave five talents...
What do you think
of Mr. Wesley?.
We ain't welcome
in the big church.
Mr. Wesley comes to us in
the fields to preach to us,
and we 'as meetings in our
'omes to study the Scriptures.
'E's been wonderful
to us, Mr. Wesley has.
And he that had received the one
went and digged into the earth
and hid his master's money.
Brother!
Charlie!
Good to see you.
You've just about
worn that horse out,
haven't you?
James, if you would please,
take good care of him.
Brother!
lt's good to be back.
How did it go
in Manchester?
Oh, very well.
But l must say that l'm a
bit worried about something.
What?
l realized while riding back
that l hadn't offended anyone
for at least three days.
l must be slipping!
l have no doubt you'll
make up for in the next week!
lndeed!
Do you know what
Mr. lngham figured out?
ln the last year,
you rode over 5,000 miles
preaching around England.
5,000?
Yes.
When you put it that way,
it sounds like a lot!
We've come up with a
new nickname for you...
Yes?
Yes!
Old Leatherbreeches!
This man is a
menace to the Church,
and must be defrocked
and excommunicated!
What do the rest of you think?
Yes, definitely yes.
Yes.
Yes l would think so.
Bishop Ryder?
How many of you men have
heard this man preach?
We have heard many reports!
l have.
Outside of Manchester in
a field a fortnight ago.
And gentlemen, l must tell you
l was unable to lay hands
on anything that he said
that was not Scriptural
or in keeping with the teachings
of the Church of England.
He is rude to people of quality
and does not care
who he offends!
lt's true -- he speaks
with great bluntness,
and offends many, no doubt.
But if we are offended
by truth bluntly spoken,
we must have a good deal of
house-keeping to do ourselves.
The truth is, gentlemen,
that as irritating as he is,
he has created a most
remarkable ministry to the poor
in places that we have ignored.
Ratherthan defrocking him, l
think we should be thanking him!
Very good.
So, what of the
other correspondence?
We have several more requests.
One from Leeds,
another from Aberstwyth.
This one's from Epworth.
Ah.
l'm simply not
ready for Epworth.
Jack--
Oh!
[screams]
Do you know that the thought
of preaching in Epworth
fills me with a sense
of dread, of doom.
Like the feeling
that l can't breathe.
For heaven's sake,
why, John?
Everything, Charles.
The fire, the rejection.
They hate us!
What if they will not hearthe
message because of who l am?
Because of who Fatherwas?
He was convinced that a
farm worker set the fire.
Oh nonsense!
There wasn't a whit
of evidence forthat.
lt was more likely just a
spark from the chimney
on the thatch roof.
Yes, but Father said --
William Seward died
preaching the truth.
Where is yourfaith,
John Wesley?
lt hasn't changed.
Let's go, brother.
Good day.
l am John Wesley and this is --
Yes l know who you are.
Yes, well, l have had letters
from some of your parishioners
they've been asking that
l come here to preach.
Not from my pulpit, sir!
Be so kind as to remove
yourself from this parish ...
and see to it that
you never return!
That's exactly what l expected.
Shall we see about
the people who matter.
Aye.
Mr. Wesley is preaching
tonight at six o'clock -
Mr. Wesley will be preaching
here, tonight at six o'clock.
Mr. Wesley is preaching over by
the church, do you want to go?
Thomas - down by church --
six o'clock -
(John) Do you know
it's been eight years
since l was here last?
What are we doing here,
Charles?
This is ridiculous, do you
really think anyone will come?
Yes, l do.
(Charles) You see, Jackie?
Yourfears were in vain.
(John) l didn't know there were
that many people in Epworth.
John, lt's time for you to
preach to the good people
of Epworth.
The seeds you've
planted now bear fruit...
My friends, l am John Wesley
and l am come to tell you
about the Kingdom of Heaven.
Faith is not found
in outward actions,
or rites and ceremonies.
Not even of the
most excellent kind.
No, the religion of Christ
rises infinitely higher
and immensely deeper
than all of these.
lt is a kingdom not
of meat and drink,
or of outward ritual,
neither is it in right
doctrine or intellectual belief.
No!
Christ is found in a heart
transformed by love.
Thou shalt love thy God
with all thy heart
and with all thy mind
and with all thy soul
and with all thy strength
and thy neighbor as thyself.