Falllng ln love ls beautlful
We do it forone reason: nothlng
ln the world makes us feel so good
-Don't!
-''Don't!''
-That hurts!
-Poor Kate Let me make it better
You're ugly You're ugly!
Flrst love ls the most powerful
because no one's been hurt yet
My flrst love was Bobby Norton
Everythlng he dld
had a sort of maglc to it
The way he smlled, talked
the way he walked llke my
favorite actor,Bllly Jack
Bobby was a movle star
You okay?
Maybe you shouldn't
shove so hard the next time
My heart just got bigger
When l do like this it looks like
you only have one eye
Thank you
One of the dlfferences between men
and women when it comes to love
ls the need to tell the world
every little detall
lf you choose to splll your guts
to someone
just make sure
it lsn't Becky Sussman
Bobby, are you okay?
-How could you do it?
-What did l do?
You told everybody
How could you do that?
All my friends are making fun of me
And now it 's over
lt 's over!
Bobby!
l'll tell you friends l was lying!
l'll let you hit me harder!
Bobby!
Love ls a mlnefleld We take
a step,get blown to pleces
put yourself back together agaln
and stupldly take anotherstep
l guess that's human nature
It hurts so much to be alone that
we'd rather blow up than be slngle
Hey, Frank
That doesn't make the elevator
go any faster, Kate
l know, but it makes me feel
more involved
-Are you angry?
-No Why?
l just heard single women
tend to be 8 times angrier
than married women
Maybe you should write an article
about it, since you're not married
l would, but
l'm writing about married bald guys
who can't get hard without Viagra
-You're late
-l know
-Not a good day to be late
-Why not?
Because the Anti-Christ
is really pissed at you
She wants to see you
in her office right now
-God Why?
-l'm not supposed to say
-Do you have any stretch marks?
-Not yet
Damn! l have a deadline
on my Vitamin E piece
That bitch in accounting won't talk
Anybody here have stretch marks?
Sit down
God!
Don't get old, Kate
Old is ugly, ugly is death
-You're fired
-What?
Get me Leo Was this a joke? Were
you planning to turn in this thing?
You said l should make
the article my own, so l did
Kate, this is a step-by-step
description of sucking cock
-Yeah, l called it ''Blow by Blow''
-Very clever
''When life sucks, so should you
Oral sex can cure depression''
What the fuck were you thinking?
Maybe the title is a little harsh
But l found a great hook, no?
l meant you should draw from your
own experiences and relationships
That 's what l did
l know ten times more about blow
jobs than l do about relationships
l failed at every relationship
l've ever been in
l don't know about your personal
life, and l don't give a shit
The point is,
our readers still have hope
This is called Monique Magazine
My name is at stake here
lt is not called ''Tired Old
Jaded Dicksucker Review''
What if Mary writes the piece
on perfect relationships
and l do the thing on stretch marks?
l know tons of people with them
l'm gonna be completely
honest with you
l can't cope with being fired
This is the only thing in my
entire life l haven't failed at
l can do the assignment,
l know l can
Can you finish 2,5OO happy,
perky words by deadline tonight?
-Absolutely
-Then you are temporarily unfired
Now get the fuck out of here
Shit! Shit!
So were you fired?
Not yet
Somebody made a copy
of your article and circulated it
Pretty good
So you use your hands?
Happy, perky notes
on how to find and keep
that perfect man
We allwant to be loved
It doesn't matter by whom,as long
as they make us feel less alone
What makes a relatlonshlp
last forever?
lf l knew the answer,lwouldn't
be llvlng alone with my fourcats
They say you have to klss
a lot of frogs to get to the prlnce
Rlchard MlItnerwas the most
borlng frog l ever dated
But sometlmes you just
have to get out of the house
You know,
masculine and feminine
We lucked out pretty good
My mother's corns
aren't usually this bad
Lucky for us she wasn't able to walk
well enough to come to the show
lt 's haunting, don't you think?
What?
The paintings
They're pretty disturbing
-You think?
-lf l had a kid
l definitely wouldn't put
one of these up his bedroom
Unless l hated him
My father would've hung
stuff like that from my ceilings
He hated me
My mother hated me too
She used to tell me l was dying
of cancer when l was four
lt always sent me in depressions,
which is exactly what she wanted
because then l wouldn't ask her
to make me lunch
She hated it when l bugged her
for food or stuff
-Would you like a champagne?
-What?
A champagne, would you like one?
Yeah, absolutely
Are you looking for me?
l wasn't really looking for anyone
Do you mind if l talk to you
for a minute?
Sure
ln the corner
-ln the corner?
-l don't like the middle of rooms
Just come with me to the corner
No one's behind you in the corner
-Who's the guy you're with?
-What guy?
Richard? He's a stand-up comedian
He seems funny
ls he your boyfriend?
Richard? No He's 3O years old
and lives with his mother
So what do you think
of the paintings?
l love the style, but l think
they're a little immature
lmmature? What makes you say that?
Look at that one over there
-What the hell does it mean?
-That?
That means there's a woman pulling
a severed head out of her ass
What 's the point?
What do l learn from it?
Maybe that 's it There's no point
You don't have to learn anything
l wonder what the artist looks like
He must be scary to make this shit
Maybe he has a highly developed
dark side you don't understand
So how long did it take you
to paint that one?
Gosh, there you are
l've been looking all over for you
You are a doll
Look at this! Thank you
Richard, Adam Levy
-You're the artist
-You're the lucky guy
We were just getting around
to discussing our future children
Right, but l don't think you're
gonna have a future together
-l'm sorry Excuse me?
-You'd need to see the person again
You're not gonna be seeing her
anymore 'cause she's my girlfriend
-What?
When we laid eyes on each other
we had this spark Right?
-Kate
-lsn't that right, Kate?
No, actually
ls this some kind of joke?
No, but this is:
two guys walk into a bar
One guy is a 3O-year-old stand-up
comedian who lives with his mother
Could we go now, please?
You know, it is women like you
who turn men into weirdoes
Don't bother Once l've been hurt,
there's no turning back
That wasn't cool l made it weird
-You shouldn't have done that
-l know
So where should we eat?
You are without a doubt the tallest
woman l've ever met in my life
Really?
l've been noticing you have
these
long ET fingers
Like a tree frog
My God! How big?
-Size 11
-Size 11?
-Yeah, size 11
-Woman's size 11?
ls this some kind of artist thing?
Focusing on people's flaws?
l don't see them as flaws,
but as God's artistic choices
l guess God decided to give you
this abnormally large head
You know what 's different?
You're being shitty and mean
And l was celebrating
your body, who you are
-You were celebrating my body?
-l was
-l like this part normally
-What part is that?
When it 's new, you know
You can ask all the fun questions
-Right
-Let me first
What 's you relationship like
with your dad?
My dad's dead
He was hit by a car in front of me
when l was six
God l'm so sorry
Just kidding We get along great
-Any brothers and sisters?
-lt 's my turn
l took your turn away
Any brothers or sisters?
Three older brothers How many
women have you slept with?
-Excuse me?
-l know you've counted How many?
-How many men have you slept with?
-Not that many 13
13?
As like 13 different guys?
Spread out over the years,
that 's not so many
Aren't you gonna
answer the question?
2 Okay?
-2? That 's it?
-That 's it
Some of us actually believe
in having full relationships
l believe in relationships
Mine just happen to be short ones
l'm sorry you're like a whore
-Excuse me?
-13! Jesus Christ!
Give me a break!
-Were you popular in high school?
-What do you think?
-l guess that 's a no
-l don't need this shit
l was very popular in high school
l was an artist, l used to draw all
the pretty girls, made them better
They all loved me
They didn't sleep with me,
but they loved me
How about you?
You must 've been
real popular with that attitude
No, l had huge buck teeth
and bony knees
And l slouched to hide the fact
l hadn't grown any boobs yet
And my hair was all stringy
and everybody called me Horseface
Horseface? lt suits you
-You think so?
-l like it
-You like it?
-What was your longest kiss?
The longest kiss?
Don't, it 'll just make me jealous
Just make sure this one's longer
Adam was unllke
any guy I'd ever know
We were lnstant best frlends
Two people who understood each
other without havlng to say a word
It wasn't llke that at all
ln my flrst relatlonshlp
lwas a bad ldea to glve up my
vlrglnity to my French teacher
lf two people want to be
a couple of them
it is good when they are making love
with each other, they feel nice
-What?
-Let 's make love
We will, Mr Bossard
l promise
l don't think l can tonight though
l'm not really ready yet
Because you feel we don't have
the quality of life together
-l am sad for this
-What?
Let 's make love, cheri, please
l am waiting for so long
-Will it hurt?
-Do not be scary
-l am there for you needing me
-What?
Mr Bossard
are you doing it?
l can't believe it lt 's supposed to hurt
Maybe it 's because l've ridden
horses all my life
Are you smaller than most guys?
My older man daddy phase
contlnued on rlght lnto college
lwas not a very evolved person
by the tlme l ran lnto Erlc
-Are you okay?
-Are you blind? Out of your mind?
What is wrong with you?
This is a brand new car!
You could've killed me!
What are you doing?
-l said l'm sorry, alright?
-This is a US$ 5OO shirt!
-l didn't see you
-You didn't see me?
-Were you painting you toenails?
-Listen, fuckface! l didn't see you!
l didn't wake up this morning
and go
''Today is the day l'm gonna crash
into some fucking uptight yuppie!''
You know what, lady? Fuck you!
Fuck you!
Shit! Fuck!
-There! You see that?
-How's that?
-Take that!
-Okay, break it up!
-Officer, l
-Shut up! Hands behind your back!
-Hit him with your big stick!
-You! Get up there!
-We got off on the wrong foot
-What?
You just destroyed my car!
l'm sorry about that
Maybe we could start over again
You got any plans for dinner
tonight after we make bail?
So this is where writers hang out?
What do you write about?
l'm working on a novel between
my journalism classes at UCLA
A novel?
-What 's it about?
-Death
That sounds interesting
So what do you do?
l work a lot with
Big Red-Ass Monkeys
lt 's a band You know, the band?
''Big Red-Ass Monkeys are here''
l direct music videos
lsn't that the one where the naked
girl swims with a chimp?
Ape Great ape
Right l guess chimps don't have
those big red asses
l don't know, l never checked
Do you think
maybe l could kiss you?
-Maybe later
-Maybe later when?
Maybe later like 5 seconds
5, 4, 3, 2
l hate when that happens
A toast to our
three-week anniversary
l think this is the longest
relationship l've ever been in
Well, not counting Mr Bossard,
which lasted one semester
-Did l ever tell you?
-Don't mention your French teacher
lt really disturbs me
-Good
-And your last relationship?
-God What about it?
-How long was it again?
-Five miserable years
-What did you have in common?
Nothing
What do we have in common?
-We have a lot in common
-Like what?
Like, how many people do you know
who have sex in public places?
Every guy l've ever met
Good morning You know
what day today is, don't you?
Sunday morning My turn
-l thought it was my turn
-Nope lt 's my turn
You know what?
This game is idiotic
-lt 's not spontaneous
-That 's not true
Scheduled spontaneity is the key
to long-term love
Don't look so happy
l like Sundays
Careful, careful
l'm not getting that
They can wait Come on
-Get it or you're not getting it
-l can't get it
Alright
l'll be back
Don't lose your
concentration, okay?
Where you going?
Now you want some, don't you?
Hold that thought, okay?
Daddy!
-Guess what l did at Kiddieland?
-We're gonna go Come with Mommy
lt 's not what it looks like,
l'll explain Nell, wait! Nell!
Kate, l can explain!
Will you come back?
Will you stop? Stop!
-What are you?
-l understand how you feel
You have no idea how anyone feels
You're a social climber!
-l'm planning on getting a divorce
-Don't ever touch me again!
-Kate!
-Daddy!
Even when bad relatlonshlps end
the paln can be severe enough
to screw you up foryears
We all plck up a little baggage
afterevery breakup
The hope ls that when the bags
start to accumulate
we're stlll able to drag them
lnto the next relatlonshlp
Fortunately when Adam and l
moved ln together
my carry-on baggage
was falrly llght
-Let 's put that one in the bedroom
-l was gonna put ''Paul's Entrails''
lt 's better for the bathroom
lf you want to be obvious
Okay, whatever you want
-l love you, Horseface
-l love you too
l mean l love you more than
l've ever loved anybody ever
in my life
Where are you going?
God
-Say it
-Why do you want me to say it again?
Because it was cute And l want
that cute moment saved forever
lt 's gonna sound forced
And l'm irritated Could we just?
-Just say it
-l love you
-Horseface!
-l love you, Horseface
l love you too Now strip
-Strip?
-Strip
-Put the toy away and we'll
-Come on
-Don't poke the bear in the zoo
-Take it off Come on
-Whip it out
When you flnally share your lonely
bed with the one you love
llfe just doesn't get any better
-That was not me
-Stop Stop it
That was the first time you
That was your first fart
You do love me
Don't blame it on me
That was so cute
You're embarrassed
Come here No woman has ever
farted in front of me before
Hi
-Hi
-What?
-Why are you smiling like that?
lt 's our one-year anniversary
You should be smiling too
l guess so
Come here Come on
No, come here
Are you a grouchy little bunny?
l'm taking you to some place
very special today
-Where?
-lt 's a surprise
Go fill me the tub
and l'll take you
-Now, in the middle of the day?
-l feel very dirty l need a tub
Forget it
Can you just fill me a tub?
Come on, you big grouch, just go
My God, it 's like pulling teeth
with you to get anything
My God!
Are you insane? What are we
gonna do with all these kittens?
l don't know
Make stew, l figured
What are they doing in there?
They like you, obviously
This one's Louie,
this one's Murray
This is Steve and
this is Mordecai
l got them from
the Chinese restaurant
Hi, Mommy
Hello Aren't l cute?
Hi You are my new mommy now
Bet the other 13 guys you slept with
didn't get you a litter of kitties
l'm pregnant
-You're really?
-l took a test and it turned pink
Pink? lsn't it supposed
to be like a plus sign?
Believe me, l know how to pee
on a stick and read directions
-l thought we were being safe
-Yeah, not safe enough
-God, we hardly know each other
-We know each other
l just don't know if l'm ready
to be a mother, Adam
l'm too confused, too immature,
too messy
What about abortion? Did you ever
think about that
possibility?
l just never thought this
would happen to me
-l don't know what to do
-Here, come here
Don't worry A lot of people think
it 's the world's greatest present
-What do you think?
-l'll tell you what l think:
that our baby would be the cutest
thing walking in poo-poo pants
Are you scared?
Of what? Of doing the most
natural thing in the world?
Of bringing a gorgeous little
brilliant genius into the world?
No l wouldn't be scared
What if it wasn't a gorgeous genius?
What if it was an ugly little troll?
l guess we just have to pray to God
that the baby takes after me
We could name it Ned,
after my grandfather
-What if it 's a little girl?
-Nedina, we'll call it
This one needs to be changed l want
you to practice to be a good mommy
God, my stomach is huge!
l look like Buddha
You're the same as always
So l've always had a Buddha gut?
Calm down You've been pregnant
a month The baby's too small
-Soon you'll look like a Volkswagen
-You have an abnormally large head
Come on, Horseface, get over here
Come on
Let 's see what we got here
Ned wants a womb with a view
Ned's not very funny
Well, Ned's just a fetus
We should cut Ned a little slack
And l think you're
more beautiful than ever
Are you okay, baby?
Are you okay?
What 's wrong?
l'm bleeding
Something's wrong
Something is going wrong
Get up Get up
Where's your robe, baby?
-Where's your robe?
-l don't know
Do you think it 's possible
to love the same person forever?
-Sure Don't you?
-l don't know
l haven't seen a relationship that
didn't end one way or another
What about your parents?
They've been together for 35 years
They live together, but they haven't
said ''l love you'' for 2O years
Maybe that 's human nature You spend
that much time around a person
saying ''l love you'' is probably like
saying ''cheese sandwich''
God, l hope not
Katie
-l cheese sandwich you
-l cheese sandwich you too
The longeryou're with someone,
the more annoylng they'll become
You'll become annoylng too So lf
you want perfectlon all the tlme
don't bother havlng
a relatlonshlp
Did you see that little old lady?
-Didn't she look sad and lonely?
-l didn't look l need some shoes
Her eyes were so hollow
Old people have hollow eyes
Especially old women
-What?
-Can we go in here?
What do you mean,
especially old women?
-Women don't age as well as men
-How could you say that?
How many 5O-year-old women
do you see with 2O-year-old guys?
That 's a societal double standard
lt 's got nothing to do with facts
Who looks better,
Sean Connery or Shelley Winters?
lt 's nature Men have thicker skin
That 's why women wrinkle more
-Shut up
-You're afraid to become obsolete
At a certain age men start to notice
younger girls lt freaks you out
Well, you're going bald!
l have the keys!
Where are you going?
l've got one What do you have?
This with topless female ninjas
Let 's just get one 'Cause
we'll forget to return them
and it will be 8OO dollars
for two movies
-And which one do you want?
-''Nosferatu''
You've seen it 5O times,
and every time you get depressed
l like being depressed lt makes
me feel deep and introspective
Wanna see what this is about?
Maybe you might like it
''Nasty naked ninjettes infiltrates
the mob and take over little ltaly
nunchacking their way to Mafia
Don Guido Mantucci''
That sounds incredible
Why do you have to do it?
You think l wanna go home
and snuggle
and read subtitles and
watch in black and white?
Can't we ever go to a goddamn
video store and not argue?
Not as long as you have
such shitty taste in movies
lt 's not true! How can you not
appreciate German Expressionism?
-l love German Expressionism
-Right
What l don't like is what you turn
into when you watch that movie
You get all fixated on death
''l'm gonna die, you're gonna die''
Fine You watch your stupid titty
movie, l'll watch my death movie
-You return yours, l'll return mine
-Fine
lt 's her birthday
One of these should be free
Romance
The most lmportant part of keeplng
a good relatlonshlp golng
Be sure to treasure each one of
those moments together ln bed
We haven't had sex in a while
We haven't had sex
in like three weeks
You're not even listening to me
No, l wasn't
l said we haven't had sex
in like three weeks
Maybe it 's because you clip
your toenails in our bed
What 's the real reason?
l don't know
Do you want to have sex right now?
No Do you?
No
-ls there something wrong with us?
-l don't know
Maybe we should force ourselves
-What? Like mutual rape?
-lt might turn us on
-l'm tired
-Me too
-Love you
-Love you too
Don't do that You don't know
how much that bugs me
l said don't!
lf you do that one more time,
l'm gonna scream
l think it 's over
What 's over?
Us l think we're done
What are you saying?
l think l need to break up
What did you just say?
l said l think we should break up
No You said you need to break up
-What 's the difference?
-There's a huge difference
Saying ''we'' implies it is mutual
Otherwise it means you're ending it
-Are you ending it?
-l don't know l guess so
Have you met someone else?
Nothing like that lt 's just we're
becoming this old married couple
God lt 's the 13 guys thing,
isn't it?
That 's what it is
You've been obsessed with my past,
now you want to make it even
Shut up about that
lt 's not the 13 guys
l'm over that, l've dealt with that
lt 's a non-issue, l promise you
Then why now?
lt 's that l've never been single
l've spent my whole life going
from one relationship to another
And l've never been alone
Do you realize what you're saying?
Do you realize what this means?
What does this mean?
lt means this is it, the end
And once it 's over, it 's over
Yeah, l guess so
But it 's not like
we won't still be friends
Who said anything
about being friends?
We love each other
l don't wanna lose you from my life
Know that when you get to number 13
l won't be here waiting for you
Give that up, it 's not about that
lt isn't working for either of us
-You're not happy, are you?
-No, l'm not happy
-So neither of us are happy
-You're right l'm miserable
Could you stop?
You're packing my laundry now
Breaking up would be
the best thing for me!
You know what?
-l feel good No, l feel great
-Come back to bed
Already it 's like a weight
has been lifted off my head
-Can't this wait?
-l can breathe, l can think
All of a sudden life is clear
lt 's amazing!
l am so happy!
When l look back
at the love l had with Adam
l see a pathetlc potted plant
nobody bothered to water
It started out green and lush, then
eventually became a drled up stlck
Breaklng up ls llke dylng,slowly
with nobody around
That's why ls so lmportant
durlng that dark perlod
to keep yourself busy dolng
the thlngs that don't depress you
Fuck me! Jesus! Kate!
l can't believe it
Our relationship hasn't even
started decomposing yet
-Who's this?
-My friend Kate
Kate, this is my friend
Peaches
This must be the friend
you just broke up with
And this must be the friend
you just started fucking!
Wait, wait
Peaches? My God!
What the fuck
is that thing on your face?
-Keep your voice down
-What are you doing here?
This is my movie! You came to make
out with someone called Peaches?
-How dare you?
-l wanna call you Can l call you?
No l'm gonna get over you
And when l do, l'll call you
That could take days
Okay, let 's see here
That 's hideous
Here you go Kate, how about this?
No That makes me look
like a drug addicted hooker
l wanna look great
Like a drug addicted model
l don't see what the big deal is
lt 's just a birthday party
Adam's gonna be there
-Aren't you over him yet?
-Of course l am
l just want him to feel jealous
when he sees me with Jerome Davis
Jerome Davis? Wait a minute
The perverted basketball player
who was obsessed with your ass?
He was?
You got a great ass
You're a big woman
but your ass is small and compact
to fit your size
And yet if you take that ass and
put it on your little friend here
it would be fucking huge
That 's it, l'm gone
God!
Thought it was you
l didn't expect to see you here
l didn't know Sam invited you
-No Mary invited me
-Mary? Of course
That 's great
lt 's nice to see you
l haven't seen you in a while
l've missed you
lt 's been a long time
-l'm sorry Hi, l'm Adam
-What 's up, Ad? Jerome
lt 's not Ad, it 's Adam
What 's up, Jer?
-Why don't l call you tomorrow?
-Don't make this a weird thing
-l'll give you a call tomorrow
-Give me a call
Give me a call or page me,
'cause my shit 's blowing up now
-Why don't you call me?
-l will
l'm running around a lot Star 82
so l now it 's you, l'm screening
-That was really weird last night
-l know, that was really weird
-So you're in love?
-l should be asking you that
-Why should you ask me that?
-You kept kissing that Lolita!
Come on, Michael Jordan
was sucking your tonsils out
Where did you find
that guy anyway?
-Let 's not get into that
-You're bringing it up
-l'm ready to be mature
-Me too Absolutely
-How could you go with that freak?
-How could you go with that bimbo?
Savannah is not a bimbo
She happens to play the harp
Excuse me A bimbo savant
At least l'm not having a fucking
hot tub party with Dennis Rodman
-l can't believe you're jealous
-l'm not jealous Stop
l don't like her, l don't love her
l'll probably never see her again
-l was waiting for you
-Noon lt was supposed to be
My harp lesson ended a little early
l bought myself some new underwear
-l'm Savannah
-Kate
-Adam told me all about you
-Really?
Go back to the coffee shop and
wait for me l'll be there at noon
-And get me a mochaccino
-Okay Nice meeting you, Cynthia
lt 's Kate
l meant Kate
Noon
-That felt really bad
-l know, l'm sorry
Don't be, we have to get used to it
l have to go and throw up now
Kate, l miss you so much
You're my best friend
-l only feel normal around you
-l know
Hopefully over time
this is all gonna work out
lt will We just have to let go
of those old feelings we had
Fine
So this Jerome guy,
was he just like huge?
l just wanna know as a friend
ls that bad for a friend?
Was it like, nice surprise big or
you better take me home now big?
Was it like l'm in over my head?
Was it l'm in over my head big?
As you move on
ln your search for love
sex ls the fastest way
to erase the past
Promise you'll never leave me
l promise
What are you doing?
Great
The only sex l've had in months
and it 's with you
Belng slngle agaln can be dlfflcuIt,
but it can also be empowerlng
After my breakup l got out
of the house as often as l could
golng to places that took my mlnd
off my lonellness
Excuse me l'm looking for
a joke gift for a friend's birthday
-What 's the kinkiest stuff you have?
-Depends
Do you mean kinky up the butt
or just white bread kinky?
Just white bread kinky, please
-Third aisle
-Thank you
lt 's a butt plug
Some guys like to put it
up their butts
Great Thanks
So what 's a nice girl like you
doing at Earl's Pornorama?
l'm here to buy a joke gift
for a friend of mine
-l'm not here to talk to strangers
-Why are you so nervous?
Are you attracted to me?
God, that is so arrogant!
l feel uncomfortable picking up
plastic dicks
with some guy
Wait a minute
Don't l know you?
-Could be
-God
Aren't you that guy in movies
with the topless ninja girls?
Yeah l've done a lot since then
That was some earlier stuff
l'm
-l'm Joey Santino
-l know
My ex-boyfriend forced me
to watch all your movies
Forced you to?
Well he loves you
Well, not after we fall in love,
he won't
l don't date actors
Joey wasn't very brlght
But l loved hls lnnocence
lwas golng through
my non-judgmental phase
and dldn't want to push people
away just for saylng stupld thlngs
l love you
-You've only known me for 14 hours!
-l know
l loved you in the first hour,
but l waited 13 more to tell you
You just think you're in love 'cause
we've been having sex non-stop
How can you be so cynical?
l've never felt this way
in my entire life
You're the most wonderful thing
that 's ever happened to me
You see?
That 's why l don't date actors
And you don't have to say
you love me back Because
l just want you
to know how l feel
that 's all
Unless you want to
l won't stop you from saying
that you love me, if you want to
l like you a lot though
-Hello
-lt 's me
Hey,Adam What's up?
Nothing much l haven't seen you for
weeks Wanna grab dinner tomorrow?
That 's so sweet, but l can't
l'm going out
What about Frlday?
Wanna see a movle on Frlday?
No, l can't l'm going to Malibu
for the weekend
Malibu? What 's in Malibu?
A big beach
l saw that ln a Thomas Gulde
once Who are you golngwith?
Some guy, you don't know him
He's got a house over there
-You like him?
-What's with all the questlons?
No reason l just want to know
if you like this rich Malibu guy
Yeah, l like him
-Do you like him a lot?
-Yeah,he's nlce
-Hello?
-Do you love him?
l think so, yeah
We've been togetherevery day
forthe last couple of weeks
That 's great for you
You know what? l gotta run
'Cause l got a date
with an actress You know
-l'll call you when l get back
-Sure, great
-l can't take it
-What?
l cannot
-l can't take it
-Just get in here
l thought l was over you
l thought l was done
God, this is horrible!
-Please, don't go to Malibu
-Are you crazy? lt 's a joke, right?
This is not a joke This is not
What 's wrong? You've been dating
nonstop This is the first guy
l've even gotten close to
-l know l was wrong, l was silly
l was stupid l didn't know how
l felt about you until right now
-What about the actress?
-lt 's cancelled, it 's over
-You shouldn't Joey's on his way
-Joey?
His name is Joey? How could
you date a guy named Joey?
Let 's get back together again
l love you Let 's have babies
Stop acting like an insane person!
Go home and relax or something
-l love you
-Go on your date, you'll be fine
-Could you just tell me one thing?
-What?
What 's his last name?
Just tell me his last name
Santino
Santino That 's perfect Joey
Joey Santino, the actor?
My the titty ninja?
You fucking hate him!
Actually he's a very good actor
Clearly you haven't seen
any of his later work
What, his later work?
Motherfucker!
My God! You're kidding me!
How could you?
Adam, you have to go
-You shouldn't fall in love
-Quit being such a hypocrite
l'm a guy! l fuck!
l don't fall in love!
-Maybe you don't
-You think Mr ltalian fucking
he's fucking you, he loves you?
l don't think so!
-Whatever
-l'm fucking out of here, alright?
This is fucking horseshit!
Don't fucking call!
-Are you Miss Kate Wells?
-Yeah
l have a message for you
from Adam Levy
Even though we're only pals
Only pals,only pals
l don't llke the other gals
You're my baby
Don't go out with that dumb guy
That dumb guy, that dumb guy
lf you do I'll start to cry
You're my baby
Mr Levy would like you to have
an autographed picture
of himself
and this
Hold on, it gets better
-Cheese sandwich
-Thank you
-Hello
-Dld the little guy slng?
What do you think?
-You got my picture up?
-Adam?
Next to the boys?
Yes, l got the sandwich
and l got your picture
-Could you stop torturlng me?
-Come over
Get rid of him We'll sport,
we'll spoon, we'll do it all
-We'll lay around all day
-Adam
What are you wearing?
God, it 's beautiful here
Are you talking to me?
There's nobody else here
Who the fuck do you think
you're talking to?
-De Niro!
-Right
De Niro is the best
l swear, l love him He's
De Niro
Yeah He's a good actor
Good?
Good? l mean, we're talking
about Robert De Niro here
Good? Come on He's a
Peanut butter and jelly sandwiches
are good Asparagus is good
De Niro, he's not
l mean, like ''Cape Fear''
Counselor
Come out,
come out wherever you are
l know you, you piece of shit!
l'm better than you all!
l can outlearn you,
l can outread you
l can outthink you
and l can outphilosophize you
And l'm gonna outlast you!
That 's good, right?
And ''Raging Bull'', which is
the greatest performance
of all time
You're gonna get me down, Ray
You're gonna get me down
Are you alright?
l know the Heimlich
-You wanna ruin my relationship?
-Your nose is so cute
You never tried to get me back
before What ego trip are you on?
-Can l kiss it?
-What?
-Your nose
-Stop screwing up my life
l'm involved with somebody else
Marry me? Please
-Are you listening to me?
-l get it, don't worry
l broke up with you
'cause l was inexperienced
You were my third girlfriend
How was l supposed to know better?
You had it so easy compared to me
l was your 14th You were my 3rd
-Look, you can't
-Just marry me
l'm sorry, l screwed up l can't
live with this kind of mistake
Don't you see?
This is really bad timing
You can't just wait until l'm
involved with somebody else
then suddenly propose marriage
or profess you love for me
l'll change How does that sound?
We're gonna make up a contract
everything you don't like about me
l'm gonna change
Death penalty You're against it,
l'm for it l'm against it now
We're gonna go do candlelight
vigils at the prison
-l don't want you to change
-You know what? l won't change
l'm enough l learned that from you
We're gonna fly, take trips
l'll go to therapy, l'll get over my
fear of planes and we'll travel
Adam, stop it
Stop it right now
Alright Let me just ask you then
Straight out, all kidding aside
Katie will you marry me?
No
l won't torture anymore then
lf you're happy,
l'm happy you're happy
l made you miserable and l'm sorry
-l just want you to know something
-What?
l can't be friends
l'm just too weak
-Adam
-l can't even be around you
You're here like this incredibly
juicy ham sandwich
that l wanna eat, and l can't
because my lips are sewn shut
-That 's a pretty analogy
-You know what l mean
Have a nice life
Don't say that You know
we'll see each other again
Yeah, right
ls lnfatuatlon love?
No But it feels llke it ls
All those chemlcals ln your braln
turn every word he says lnto poetry
Did l ever tell you what l used
to do with my little brother?
Whenever he did something wrong,
l'd put dog shit under his pillow
l'd say ''Jimmy, go put you head
under the pillow and count to 2O''
Half the time he'd get to 1O
before he realized what happened
That was pretty stupid
Jimmy? No
He's a lawyer now
He's the smartest of all of us
Now you remember me?
Relatlons based entlrely on sex
end the mlnute the sex gets borlng
So lf you want it to last
beyond borlng sex
You'd bettertry to connect
on a deeper level
l brought us some cheese sandwich
Thanks
Do you think people can stay
passionate about each other forever?
Yeah As long as they work
on the relationship
and don't get fat
l wonder
l'm not sure it 's natural l'd like
to think it 's possible though
l think that, over time, we'll come
to take each other for granted
And after the years
of staying together saying
''l love you'' is like saying
''cheese sandwich'', you know?
Do you know that Robert De Niro
is lactose intolerant?
Afterthe lnfatuatlon chemlcals
ln my braln stopped muItlplylng
l began to get over
my non-judgmental phase
Joey and lwere gonna have
a real conversatlon soon
l'm gonna die
-Are you listening to me?
-What?
l'm gonna die
When?
Someday
We're all gonna die
Watch the movie
Doesn't that bother you?
-l don't think about these things
-Why not?
Look, we're in the middle
of a movie
That 's when l think
about death the most
All these people staring into
the darkness freaks me out
-Don't you get that?
-No Okay? l don't get that
Why should l get that?
l don't wanna get that
That 's the problem
We are supposed to get each other
You don't get me, l don't get you
What? What the fuck
are you talking about?
You know what my problem is?
l'm a floater
l float through life like
a corpse on a river
bumping into rocks and logs
l don't choose my path
-Shut up!
-l just bump into stuff, like you
l bump into you in a porno shop,
Boom! l have sex with you
Boom! l'm in a relationship with
you l don't think, l just boom!
-Shut the fuck up!
-So that 's what l am to you?
l'm just some goddamn log
you bumped into in a porno store?
You're wearing sunglasses
in a movie theater
-They're subscription
-That 's prescription, you idiot!
Okay, Mrs Thesaurus l'm an idiot
You know, that 's it
Hasta la vista, baby Here is a man
who will no take it anymore
You're all gonna die
Think about it
And nobody will remember you
because they'll all be dead too!
Excuse me
Hl, thls ls Adam I'm not home,so
leave your message afterthe beep
Hl,Adam It's me
Adam,are you there?
l dldn't wanna call anybody else
Are you okay?
-What 's wrong, baby?
-We broke up
-God
-l broke upwith Joey
That 's horrible
-l'm such a failure
-You're not a failure
l am l am a relationship leper
Not true You have more relationship
potential than anybody l know
Fuck potential
Anyone can have potential
Are you kidding?
Your only problem is bad timing
Two people could be perfect, and if
the timing's wrong, it won't work
Bad timing is the reason that most
normal people end up single
Normal people?
Weirdoes are single because
they're weird
but people like us
we're single because
we're victims of bad timing
Since when did you have things
so figured out?
Since you fell in love and l've lain in
bed awake every night and wonder
if l'd ever find anybody
who l feel as normal with
No Bad timing, Adam
lf the timing's ever right,
you just let me know, okay?
How about now? You think?
Okay, that 's cool
Take as much time as you want
Love ls ecstasy and agony
freedom and lmprlsonment
longlng and lonellness
lt 's what keeps us together
when life tears us apart
So, when you find that perfect man,
hold on tight
And then call me so l can see
what he looks like and laugh
because he doesn't exist,
you sad, perky
little optimistic suckers
l quit
l couldn't do the assignment
l've always felt like a fraud here
Everything l wrote was crap
And l'm a total sellout,
l can't do it anymore
And honestly l'm sorry
if l've caused you any problems
Wait a minute
She's way too fat
Everything you've written here
has been bullshit?
-Nothing has had a grain of truth?
-Nothing
So your research on blow job
being able to cure depression
is completely made up
No, actually, that one was true
But it only works for the suckee
The sucker always stays depressed
l told you that
l'm here
Actually, could l ask you
a few questions if it 's okay?
Sure Go ahead
-Are you married?
-No
-Do you have any children around?
Do you feel the need to have sex
with a lot of different women?
-No
-Are you a liar?
Yes
Just kidding
Good You've got a sense of humor
That was my next question
Can you listen?
l'm sorry, what?
-You see how l?
-l get it Just one more, l promise
Do you have a problem
with complicated women?
Great Let 's go
May l ask you one question?
Of course l'm sorry,
ask anything you want
Have you allowed Jesus Christ
into your heart?
-God!
-lf l could have one moment
-No Get out!
-May l?
-lf the next knock is the devil
-Go!
-Listen, have you allowed
-Go! Now!
Thank you
Hi, are you Kate Wells?
-Yeah And you're Rob, right?
-That 's right
Thank you
-Thanks for coming
-Nice to meet you
-You're good
-Thank you
And nasty
l like my men good and nasty
Thank you
-You got a girlfriend?
-Yeah, l do
She's on a date now however
So where's your blind date?
-l told him l was sick
-Yeah, you're sick alright
Yeah, from wanting you back
That was incredible
l'm very proud of myself
-l did good, right?
-Yeah, you did alright
-lt was different
-l surprised you, l know it
-You seemed scared
-l wonder where you learned that
We should break up more often
We should
-l love you
-Me too
Get out
-So with Joey, was is it now? 16?
-Shut up
No, seriously
15 l was 14
What about Peaches?
Tell me about Peaches
-l don't wanna know about her
-No, you do
Where do you think
l learned that thing l did?