WOMAN: Once there was a girl
who walked straight,
yet she was truly lame.
She walked upright
in new boots,
yet I tell you,
her feet were bare.
She lives forever,
yet she lies buried
in a vault of fertile air.
And if she's shaken
from her torpor,
she'd rise to write.
What would she write?
[SPLAT]
[LIGHTS CLICK ON]
DR. MURRAY:
How are you feeling?
Still feeling crappy.
The biopsy
doesn't look good.
Melody,
I'm very sorry, but...
it's cancer, laryngeal...
and it's inoperable.
The tumor is malignant
and it's growing rapidly.
It's causing an obstruction
in your trachea and larynx.
[HEART POUNDING]
What will happen?
Most likely you'll
lose your voice first,
and then,
as the cancer progresses,
you will find it increasingly
more difficult to breathe.
How much time?
I would say from
the looks of things,
you have perhaps
a month or two.
Is there anything--
You need to go home,
get your affairs in order,
and then you come
back here tomorrow,
and we're gonna set you up
with a counselor, okay?
I'm sorry.
Thank you.
[WHEEZES SOFTLY]
[CHATTER]
[CHILD LAUGHS]
[WOMEN SPEAKING CHINESE]
[ELEVATOR DINGS]
[SPEAKING CHINESE]
[LAUGHING]
"Driving me nuts"!
[ELEVATOR DINGS]
[DINGS]
[WOMEN CHATTERING]
[DISTANT PHONE RINGING]
Hi, Melanie.
Mr. Faddis,
I'm sorry I'm late.
Listen.
You're being downsized.
- What?
- Fired.
In that envelope
is your severance pay.
I've been here
for four years.
Four weeks' severance pay.
That's one week for each year
you've been with the company.
I don't understand.
Four weeks is plenty of time
to find a new job
in this environment.
Good luck.
[SHOCKED PANTING]
[ELEVATOR DINGS]
[LAUGHING HYSTERICALLY]
[CONTINUES PANTING]
WOMAN: Oh, my God,
can you believe the nerve?
On their first date,
all he wanted was oral sex...
[YELLS]
[DISTANT, LOUD HAMMERING]
[CAR HORN HONKING]
[COUGHS]
I'd like to make
a collect call, please...
[PANTS, COUGHS]
...to Brett White.
My name is Mel Wilder.
Hey, Brett, it's me.
Y-yeah.
You know, I don't
have a cell phone.
Well, yeah.
No, I think they're
a big waste of money.
Listen, listen,
I need to see you.
I can't tell you
on the phone.
Brett, please.
Please.
Listen, I have to see you.
Later is kind of tough.
[CHUCKLES]
Twenty minutes, bye.
Hey.
I--I--I--
Mel.
I'm glad you called.
I've been thinking.
If I really,
truly loved you...
[ANGUISHED SIGH]
My therapist said--
Um, okay. Okay.
I need some time alone.
I need some space.
I'm feeling suffocated.
I mean, not me personally,
but my life force.
Do you understand?
[AUDIO BEGINS FADING OUT]
Honey, I--
I think we need
to take some time apart.
It's time for me to look
for my inner child,
to discover
who I really am.
I mean, it's been
a hell of a day...
[AUDIO FADES OUT
COMPLETELY]
[COUGHS]
TAP WATER RUNNING]
[KEYS CLATTER]
Thank you.
But why would you
call Richard?
Because he's pathological!
Listen, I'll call Jiggy,
and I'll get back to you.
Because I'm with someone.
Okay, I'll see
you later. Bye.
Miss Wilder.
Miss Wilder?
Mel Wilder.
Ah, Manny Laffs.
What's wrong
with your voice?
Laryngitis.
Well, now, you understand
this is a short-term rental.
Short, long
are relative.
Yes, yes,
but this one is short.
It's actually
kind of a unique sort
of New York-style
situation--
short term, as-is,
leave the place
as you found it.
Pretty unique.
And you don't
wanna see the loft?
It's perfect.
All right.
[WHEEZING]
[FOGHORN BLOWS]
[ELECTRIC GUITAR PLAYS
SUSTAINED, DISTORTED NOTE]
[KNOCKING AT DOOR]
MAN: Hello!
Anybody home?
Just a minute.
[KNOCKING]
Hello?
[WHEEZING]
Who is it?
Phone man!
[KNOCKING]
Hi.
Melanie Wilder?
May I come in?
Just moved
in here, huh?
Melanie...
Melanie Wilder, right?
- It's Melody.
- [LAUGHS] Oh.
Mr. Laffs, we saw
him the other day
and he told me that
you just moved in,
so I figured
I'd save some time
'cause I was doing
an installation
And I figured...
usually it takes
four to six weeks
for a residential.
Get you set up today
and you luck out.
Uhh...
You just moved in,
right?
Ma'am, are you okay?
All right, look,
you're gonna get
a new phone number,
so that's good.
You want call waiting?
Call waiting's
a good thing.
I don't--
We also have
a DSL special if you want,
or you can get
call-forwarding or--
- No, no.
- Caller ID, or...
No? Okay.
I'm gonna leave you with
this, uh, phone we have.
It's a promotion.
You get a free one.
[LAUGHING] It's a--
Don't ask me.
Corporate sends
it out and--
but, you know,
if you don't like it,
you can always just set up
your own phone there.
[SIGHS] What are you,
just waiting for
the furniture today or...
[BARELY AUDIBLE]
Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah?
Yeah.
Okay.
You know what?
I'm just gonna leave you
with these phonebooks,
just put them
right there.
And, uh, if I can just
get you to sign this,
I'll be--
I'll be on my way.
Just, uh...
I--I want
an unlisted number.
Yeah. That's
no problem.
All right, look, why don't
you just, uh, take this?
Take care of yourself,
all right?
Have a good day.
[DIAL TONE]
[CLEARS THROAT]
Hi. I'd like a delivery.
What are your specials?
Golden Beef Happy Family?
Actually, I'm vege--
you know what?
I'll go for
the Golden Beef Happy Family.
Oh, what does
that come with?
Spare ribs? Okay.
Hi.
I'd like to order
a bed, please.
Mm-hmm.
What's the best
you carry?
Vera Wang?
Okay, I'm gonna trust
you on that.
Um, what size...
Um, I don't know.
I think... a king?
Yeah, I'll go for a king.
Okay, I'm just gonna
get my card.
"Return to the womb"?
I could do with that.
[CHUCKLES]
The card is 70262437.
[PANTING]
Ah!
[ELECTRIC GUITAR PLAYING]
Hey.
MOM: Next time, he's
not gonna let us put--
DAD: That hound
is a psycho.
If we'd stayed
in our old place--
It was a room,
one room.
Honey, it was a room
we could afford.
Dad, Mom, can you get me
that red guitar for Christmas?
- Christmas...honey!
- The guitar, again.
MOM: Christmas isn't something
to indulge in right now.
DAD: Now it's gonna take
that crap to make her happy.
[SIGHS] Don't start.
- Did you put
tarragon in this?
- This is overcooked.
- No, it's not.
[SQUEAKS, FLOPS]
[GASPS]
Hi. Um, I'd like
to make an order, please,
um, of your linens.
I'd like--I'm just gonna
go to the catalogue--
three sets from the Bed, Bath
& Beyond Hotel Collection,
the ivory color,
king size.
Uh, a dozen of your towels,
your bath towels,
the softest ones
you have in white
and a dozen in silver.
[COUGHS] Hi. Uh...
Could I please have
your six foot by nine foot rug,
the Mums in Silk rug,
and then the Camilla Blue,
uh, twelve foot
by nine foot rug...
the Camille.
Yes, please, a delivery...
Space 107?
I need to order
the Milo Baughman coffee table,
the pair of Karl Springer
Lucite lamps,
and the 1950s wire chaise.
The lantern vase
from the Jonathan Adler
and also the thistle vase
from the Relief Collection
on page 15.
Uh, five of those,
that's right.
You have my card number?
Okay, maybe you
could store that.
My card number is 9437--
Yeah, next day is fine...
5202780...
Yeah, I know
it's expensive.
I have the money
but I don't have the time,
if you know what I mean.
No, you don't know.
Of course.
[ITEMS DROP
THROUGH MAIL SLOT]
[WHISPERS] Pizza.
Pizza delivery!
Just a minute.
Ma'am, your pie's
getting cold!
Okay, hang on.
Don't come in, please.
Just slide the box
on the floor.
Where's all
your stuff?
You're still gonna have
to sign for the pie!
[PANTING]
You're still gonna have
to sign for the pie.
[CLATTERS]
No need to tip.
Sorry, I have no cash.
Don't worry about it.
Sorry.
[ELECTRIC GUITAR PLAYING]
The, uh, 62975...
[KNOCKING AT DOOR]
Page 18.
Yeah.
[KNOCKING]
Coming.
Hold on.
You know, there's
somebody at the door.
I'm gonna call you back.
Ahem, okay.
[KNOCKING]
Yeah?
Parcel delivery,
ma'am.
Who?
I have some packages
for you.
Great.
Uh, yeah.
Just a sec.
Ma'am?
Hello.
Holy cow!
It's Christmas!
Just move in?
Uh-huh.
Nice.
Lots of room.
Yeah.
[CLEARS THROAT]
What's your name?
Me?
Yeah.
What's your name?
Roscoe.
Roscoe?
Really?
Is that funny?
I just--no, I just
never met anybody,
you know,
named Roscoe.
Will you sign
this, please?
Melody Wilder.
Never met anybody
named Melody, either.
It means "graceful"
in, uh, Hawaiian.
Your parents,
they Hawaiian?
No.
No, no, no.
They're from Tonawanda,
upstate.
No way.
That's a freaking
coincidence!
My parents
named me for a town
Get out of here!
Serious.
Roscoe, New York.
That's where they met,
in a diner.
I'm glad my parents
didn't name me Tonawanda.
Tonawanda Wilder?
[LAUGHS]
You got more
big orders like this?
I'm ordering
lots of stuff.
Well...then
I'll be seeing you.
Nice dress.
Fuckin' crazy bitch!
Pizza delivery.
[GASPING]
You need a hand
with that?
Sure.
You know, you could
have killed somebody
throwing all that shit
out of the window.
Uh, thanks...Tony?
Ah, no, it's
my brother's shirt.
What does he
think about that?
He probably
wears my underwear
My name's Cookie.
Cookie Clemenza.
Yours is
Melanie Wilder.
I've seen it
on your card.
Melody, Mel.
Mel.
What's the matter
with your voice?
I...
I'm sorry,
I don't mean to get up
Okay. The tip
is on the slip.
Thanks.
Oh, the best pizza
to get is the special--
dandelion greens,
double cheese,
The sausage
is homemade--
Thanks.
Thanks for that.
- Yeah.
- See you.
Yeah, cool ring.
Oh, yeah,
yeah, yeah!
- Real diamonds.
- Three carats.
- Holy Hanna.
- Yeah.
Oh, before I forget,
we give these out
for free.
Uh-huh.
My dad picked
out the picture.
It's different photos of
the Leaning Tower of Pisa.
Actually,
it's the same photo
but a different
color background.
Ah, this month,
it's green.
All right, well,
see you around.
Nice.
[CHUCKLES]
[BUBBLE WRAP
POPS UNDERFOOT]
[INDISTINCT MUTTERING]
[INAUDIBLE]
- [PARENTS ARGUING, MUFFLED]
- # It's a hard way we travel #
# A long road we came #
# From a dark fall
we wandered #
# No one calls our name #
# We crossed
through cold mountains #
# And wound
through the trees #
# We ran
with your rivers... #
[INDISTINCT ARGUMENT
CONTINUES]
[ELECTRIC GUITAR PLAYS]
DAD: It's not my fault.
MOM: We've
apologized to her.
It's over.
It's over, Nick.
Come on.
MOM: Come on, honey.
Let's go home.
Hi. Do you take
credit cards?
Good.
I'd like to buy a guitar.
Electric.
Uh-huh.
To deliver today?
What do you recommend?
Money's not really
the issue.
A '63 Fender Strat?
- Uh-huh.
- [KNOCKING]
Reissue?
Color? Red,
it's gotta be red.
Amps?
I--I don't know.
My place is pretty large.
- All stringed? Yeah.
- Oh, hey.
Yeah, sounds good.
Marshall?
A Marshall--
two Marshalls.
Great. Um...
Where do you want this?
Triple stack?
Sure.
Cords? I need long cords,
the longer the better.
Yeah.
Picks? A hundred.
Yeah, a hundred.
Simple black strap.
Wah-wah pedals?
Pedals, wah-wah.
Humbucking pickup?
Sure.
You know,
whatever's right,
'cause I'm a beginner,
so whatever I can do
in two months.
It's a long story.
Card number's,
uh, 94728075230599.
Expiration 09-09.
Wilder, 295 West Street,
penthouse.
Yeah, I'll be here.
Be here all the time.
Okay.
You're welcome.
You have a nice day, too.
I just bought a guitar.
That's great.
And then I have to get,
you know, amps and stuff
for the guitar.
What?
You're spending money
like there's no tomorrow.
There is no tomorrow.
All my tomorrows
are yesterday.
Anyway, I'm charging it.
- But when they come
for the minimum due--
You're leaving?
Yep, splitting...
splitting into atoms.
Big bang.
Whatever you say.
Oh, oh what,
the customer's
On this job,
I see a lot of people
Plastic get so hot,
they stick 'em in the freezer
just to cool them down.
You think I got a fever?
Miss Wilder.
You wanna feel
my forehead?
Please, sign here.
You're married.
Yeah, going on
seven years.
I was just thinking.
Thinking?
Some girls
get all the luck.
I'm not sure
my wife would agree.
But thanks.
[AMPLIFIER HUMMING]
[FEEDBACK]
[OPEN STRINGS SOUNDING]
[PLAYS OPEN STRINGS]
[SILENCES STRINGS]
[FEEDBACK]
[PLAYS LOW NOTE]
[NOTE DISTORTS]
[SCRATCHES]
[OPEN STRINGS VIBRATING]
[KNOCKING]
ROSCOE: Hello?
Anybody home?
Jeez.
Who is it?
Roscoe.
Oh, hi, Roscoe.
Did I catch you
at a bad time?
I thought I got
everything I ordered.
It's been a while
since I delivered anything,
but I thought I'd check
to see that you are okay.
I had a funny feeling
after that little rap
What's behind your back?
Oh, these?
I was walking by
my aunt's flower stand
over on Bleecker.
She gave me these.
They reminded me of you.
Not your wife?
Roscoe...
If you come back,
just come back
for the moment.
It's all there is.
MAN: As you play Exercise 24
and marvel at
how great you sound,
please remember--
you learned this lead
a section at a time.
And don't forget
that this is the secret
-  A lead when viewed
in its entirety...
...looks impossible.
When you break it down
into small sections...
- Hang on a second.
- ...it becomes manageable.
That's the way you learn
the five pentatonic--
COOKIE:
Yo, Melody!
You haven't
ordered in days.
I thought you might
be starving to death.
[QUIETLY]
Hold your horses.
Hi.
- Are you busy?
- Oh, no, it's fine.
Am I interrupting
something?
'Cause I could go.
No, no. Yeah, come in.
You're looking good.
Fuckin' A.
You're looking
good, too.
Yeah, I joined a gym.
I haven't gone yet,
but I joined.
Where do you want me
to put the pie?
Oh, on the rug's fine.
One second.
So, who gave
you the ring?
Vito.
Vito?
Katana.
Vito the Cat.
He hates it.
Hates what?
He thinks when you
call him the Cat
you're dissing him.
You know, it's like a--
it's like you're
calling him a pussy.
What does Vito do?
I'm not really sure.
Deals with the money.
Money?
He's connected.
Connected to what?
You know, connected.
Leather couch!
Ha, fucking awesome!
Genuine.
And look at the bed.
And the TV.
What are you watching?
Oh, I'm learning
how to play guitar.
No shit.
Uh-huh.
Are you serious?
As cancer.
I brought Chianti.
That's nice.
Um, I'll find
some glasses.
I can't--I can't believe
all this shit you got in here.
What in freaking hell
inspired you, huh?
Why are you here, Cookie?
I don't know.
They speak to me...
the objects.
They speak to you?
They whisper.
In a strange language.
What language?
The language of objects.
They give me hope
by whispering rumors
of my redemption.
It's like poetry.
I only wish I could
have collected them
more slowly,
individually, but...
But?
I don't have time.
Why not?
I just don't.
You going somewhere?
Yeah.
Where?
Where are you going?
I'm-- I'm leaving.
You're serious,
aren't you?
Yes, yes.
Cancer.
[MELODY STRUMMING
SINGLE CHORD]
[STRUMMING C CHORD]
[STRUMMING D MINOR CHORD]
[DISTORTION]
[NO AUDIBLE DIALOGUE]
[MELODY PLAYING
MORE COMPETENTLY]
[KNOCKING LOUDLY]
[FEEDBACK]
[CONTINUES SONG]
COOKIE: Let me
see your ears.
- My ears?
- Yeah.
Why do you wanna
see my ears?
Because they're
beautiful.
[SCOFFS] Stop!
They're gorgeous.
Jeez.
Yeah.
[LAUGHING]
Mwah!
Watch out,
I'm ticklish.
You ever hear of
a Chinese musician
Mm-hmm.
What about him?
Why would somebody
give their son
two first names
like that, huh?
What about
John-John Kennedy?
Who's that?
You don't know who
John-John Kennedy is?
Yeah, yeah.
He's the president
Uh, never mind.
- So what about--
- I wasn't even born.
Oh, you weren't
even born.
Nah.
What about Cookie?
What about the name
Cookie? Cookie?
It's really Constance.
Get out of here.
Yeah.
[LAUGHS]
Serious?
Yeah.
Constance.
Okay, I'm gonna call you
Constance from now on.
No, don't call
me Constance.
I like Constance.
We should get a--
Don't.
You should have a shirt
with Constance on it.
No, no.
It's Cookie to you.
Constance.
I like Constance.
Yeah?
[NO AUDIBLE DIALOGUE]
[WHISPERS]
Oh, jeez. Oh, Jesus.
[MISPRONOUNCES]
Hi, is that Gusto?
[CORRECTS HERSELF]
Gus-Gusto.
Gusto. Yeah, yeah.
Uh, what are
your specials tonight?
Artichoke.
Yeah. Grilled octopus,
I'd like very much,
and the focaccia
with apples.
Let's see here
on the menu....
[MISPRONOUNCES]
And the gnocchi
[CORRECTS HERSELF]
Gnocchi. Okay.
Uh-huh. With
the mushroom, very good.
And I'd like the chicken
as well, please.
Heirloom chicken.
I like the sound of that.
And, uh,
tiramisu times two.
Uh, cappuccino, maybe.
Bottle of Chianti. Yeah.
And the cannoli dessert
that you mention there.
Uh-huh. Okay.
Oh, it's for
one person. Yes.
I've never been
so hungry in my life.
The name is Wilder.
I'll just get my card.
THE EVERYOTHERS:
# When Lana's pregnant
# Enjoys awful strong
and bettin' your life
Hello!
# You know I need some lovin' #
# Would you touch me? #
[GIGGLES]
# John #
# Well, I'm only dancing #
# She turns me on #
# Well, don't get me wrong #
# I'm only dancing #
[BOTH CHUCKLE]
- [RASPBERRIES]
- Oh!
[LAUGHING]
Fuck me, all right?
[GRUNTS]
Whoo!
# You know I need some lovin' #
# Oh, baby, touch me #
# John #
# Well, I'm only dancing #
# She turns me on #
[FALSETTO]
I'm going away! Oh!
Yeah! I love you!
Holy shit!
What happened?
We had a lovers' spat.
Spat?
He wanted me to tell him
who I was seeing up here.
And when I wouldn't,
he, uh... he...
Anyways, I
finally told him,
and, uh, he
called me a dyke.
Mel, what are you doing?
Hang the fuck up!
- But--
- But nothing.
I fucking stabbed him
in the cheek with a fork.
Nobody calls me a dyke
and leaves with all
their wisdom teeth.
I told him
to leave you alone,
but just in case
he does show up...
just let it ride, okay?
I like you.
I do.
And Vito?
He's not all that bad.
The wedding's
in a few weeks.
I can't invite you,
you understand?
Bye, Mel.
[KNOCKING]
ROSCOE:
Hello, ma'am?
Mel?
Hi.
So, what's up?
Nothing.
It's nothing.
Well, I was just...
Roscoe, what do
you wanna tell me?
My wife and I
have been trying
to have a kid
for a while.
She's hearing
the ticking clock,
but it didn't look like
it was in the cards.
She was so depressed.
It didn't have
anything to do with me,
you know... till recently.
She went to see the doctor.
She's...
Congratulations.
Thank you.
You bet.
[PLAYING GUITAR]
Hey, Blue Hill?
Daniel?
It's Mel Wilder here.
Yep, I'm starved.
I would like to order
the salmon steak,
country salad--
broiled salmon.
A red wine, a merlot.
Yeah. Use my card.
Add a $10 tip,
of course.
Thanks.
[PHONE RINGS]
[RINGS]
Hello?
Daniel.
Okay, um...
I don't know why,
'cause there should be
6,000 in there.
I'm gonna give you
another one.
Take my... Vista Bank.
8532084364218049.
Expiration 09-08.
Yeah.
It's gonna be fine.
Oh, uh...
[CHUCKLING]
This is--
this is strange,
but I'll...
I'll give you another card,
if you don't mind.
Um, my Mission Bank.
I have here is--
Ready for the number? Okay.
807531000240837,
and the expiration
is 11-09.
Okay. Uh... you know,
I'm gonna shoot for one more.
Third time lucky, right?
Fourth--fourth time lucky.
It's, um, I'll give you
the Vista Bank--
it's an ATM card.
It's 8532084364218049.
That's expiration 07-09.
Daniel, what day is it?
What month?
[PANTING]
[SNIFFLES]
Ah. Ah.
[LOWER] Ah.
[GASPING]
Ah, ah!
Ahhhhhh.
[CRYING]
Ahhhhhh...
[KEYBOARD CLACKING]
[PHONE RINGING]
Hi, I'd like to see
Dr. Murray, please.
- Name?
- Wilder, Melody.
Do you have an appointment,
Miss Wilder?
You know, I think she's
gonna want to see me.
Okay.
[QUIETLY] Okay, um,
let's see here.
Okay, yeah.
Okay. Um...
[HANGS UP PHONE]
She'll be with you
in just a minute.
[PHONE RINGS]
[WOMAN PAGES DOCTOR OVER P.A.]
What's up?
What Dr. August was saying
and what we are all saying
is the tumor's gone.
What?
How could you
do this to me?
We didn't do anything.
The question is
what did you do?
- Do?
- What did you change?
In your life,
what did you change,
what habits,
your diet, anything?
What did I change?
I changed everything.
I've heard of
something similar,
a type of remission wherein
the person changes so much
that the tumor no longer
recognizes the body as host.
Medically,
scientifically speaking,
Statistically, you're one
in a million billion.
Melody,
you don't have cancer.
[SCREAMS]
[TIRES SQUEAL; HONKS]
[YELLS IN FOREIGN LANGUAGE]
[MAN CONTINUES YELLING]
Crazy New Yorker.
Wake up!
But, uh, I think
all in all it's--
I'm sorry, would you
excuse me, please?
One second. Miss Wilder.
Miss Wilder!
I've been trying
to reach you.
Here I am.
You were supposed to be
out of here in two months.
Yeah.
That was our deal.
[SIGHS]
I know, I know.
It's three months now.
I'll get you the money.
You don't understand.
The reason we did
a short-term lease
is because I'm in the process
of selling the building.
Now, these people seem
very interested, okay,
but I gotta get inside
and show the loft.
- But--
- I need you to vacate.
Can you just give me
a couple more weeks?
Please, I swear
I'll be out.
It's just
I didn't count on--
What? You didn't
count on what?
I didn't count on
being alive.
Well, I su--
I suppose I could use
the security deposit
as this month's rent.
Then you're gonna have
to be out, okay?
[CHUCKLES UNCOMFORTABLY]
[INAUDIBLE]
# Call upon my soul
within my house #
[RECITING] I cannot live
with you, it would be life
And life is over there,
behind the door
I could not die
with you...
For one must wait
to shut the other's gaze down
I cannot live with you
[CHUCKLES]
It would be life...
And life is over there
Behind the door
Hi.
Hey, how you doin'?
- Good.
- What's up?
How much will you
give me for this?
Fifty bucks.
- Fifty bucks?
- Yeah.
I paid $425 for this.
My mommy didn't love
me either. $50.
It's not that great.
- Fine.
- All right.
And what
about this?
Twenty bucks on that.
This is
a very fancy chair.
It's all right.
[SIGHS] Okay.
Jeez Louise.
Billy?
So, what do you think?
Thirty bucks.
[SCHOOLCHILDREN YELLING]
[GIGGLING]
BOY: Over there!
Run, run, run!
[MELODY PLAYING GUITAR]
Miss Wilder?
Miss Wilder,
I know you're in there.
You need to read this!
[MELODY PLAYING GUITAR]
[TRUCK BEEPING]
[SIGHS]
[CAN RATTLES]
[RAT SQUEAKING]
And so is offered
in these optimistic,
though viral times,
a souvenir of another time
with this added prayer:
In art and dream,
may you proceed with abandon;
in life, may you proceed
with balance and stealth.
[ACOUSTIC GUITAR PLAYS]
[COINS CLICK]
[PLAYING WITHOUT AMP]
Oi, girl.
What's up?
Hi.
What, you, uh...
you making coin?
Nickels and dimes.
Think you've got
a few quarters
Nah, I'm just funning you.
Just funning you.
Listen, babe,
why don't you
All right?
There you go.
- Uh--
- No, no.
I'm just gonna run
after the old Rasta dudes,
score some dime bag,
but I'll be right back.
Roll us a fatty,
we'll fire her up
and we can jam,
yeah, all right?
You know,
I-I don't think so.
I, uh...
Uh, wait, mister?
[INDISTINCT]
Oh, fuck off!
- Can't believe it--
- COP: Hey!
BUM: All right,
all right, all right!
[OPEN STRINGS SOUND]
[INDISTINCT CHATTERING]
[LAUGHING]
[PLAYING STOPS]
[MUSIC PLAYING]
# I'm getting tired #
# Yeah, and I'm blue too
hanging on me #
# I took tomorrow over here #
# No one to follow #
# Well, I waited
all this time #
# Well, I'm on your side #
Hey!
# You gotta move it #
# Keep your eyes
or something moving #
# I'm in the mood
to sing a sad song #
# Sad song #
# Well, I need
to let you know #
# That I'm on your side #
Hey!
# I want to take
a dive with you #
# I need to take
# I want to take
a dive with you #
# Yeah, I think that
I could dive with you, yeah #
# Well, take a dive,
take a dive, yeah yeah #
# Take a dive,
# I'll take a dive #
# I been around for a long time
in the shadows #
# I've been thinkin' 'bout
the daytime in the hollow #
# I need to let you know #
# I'm on your side #
# A-hey #
# I'm on the brink #
# Of a solution #
# I wanna show you #
# It's a danger
like a handgun #
# It's gonna blow you #
# Yeah, please
don't read my mind #
# I'm on your side #
Hey!
# And I wanna take
a dive with you #
# Wanna take
# I need to take
a dive with you #
# I wanna take
# Yeah, I think that
I could dive with you #
# Well, take a dive,
take a dive, yeah yeah #
# Take a dive,
# I wanna dive with you #
Hey!
- [CROWD CHEERING]
- Thank you!
Thank you very much.
You guys have been great.
Appreciate it very much.
Thank you.
[EXULTANT LAUGHTER]
[DEB MONTGOMERY'S
"FLY FREE" PLAYS]
# I want to fly free
but I'm scared what I'll see #
# I want to fly high
but I'm still scared to die #
# I want you to love me
but where will I be #
but will I be free? #
# I want you to love me
Subtitles by LeapinLar