Everything worth anything
is both terrifying and beautiful.
Like the first time you do something
that you know is wrong.
You know it's wrong
and yet you do it anyway.
There was a ladybug
crawling around my ankle
when I saw Victoria let her
grandmother's bird escape from its cage.
I watched the bird disappear
into the endless sky like a lonely balloon.
It was so sad.
That image left a scar
that never completely healed,
because until then
I thought that bad things
could only happen by accident,
never on purpose.
It was Victoria who first
made me confront
that danger existed
on the inside of everybody.
Now she's coming to my school.
Mom, that's so much worse.
Every year my mother hopes
this five-hour drive to school
will be something that it never is.
What I share
with my mother is silence.
My heart exists within
the stone walls of that building.
That's where I live.
Tanner Hall is majestic
but crumbling.
It's just a fact,
as true as the uncertainty
of the year ahead.
- Fernie!
- Oh!
- Hello!
- Fernie!
- Get up here right now!
- I'm coming!
Fernie!
- Hello!
- I missed you so much!
Oh my God, you look so good!
You're so clumsy, Victoria.
It's not my fault.
He didn't leave me
enough room to get out.
This can't possibly be the school.
It looks like the pictures
in the orientation packet.
There was an orientation packet?
I never saw it.
Oh, I spared you, Vicky.
It was boring.
It's not supposed
to read like a magazine.
No wonder Daddy
has a girlfriend.
You're such a moron.
Would you just relax?
You're getting yourself
worked up over nothing.
Olga, hi!
Ah! Roxanne!
It's so good to see you.
I've been thinking about
when we were in school together.
The jerk driver forgot
to load my bags into the trunk!
I have jack shit to wear!
Hey, you know what?
They'll find your bag, you know.
In the meantime you could
maybe borrow some of Fern's clothes.
Fernanda, look at you.
Fern, you remember Victoria, right?
- You knew each other when you were little.
- Yeah, sort of.
You forgot to introduce your friends.
Right, sorry.
- This is Lucasta and this is Kate.
- Hello.
Let's go check in.
Would you two mind
showing me around the school?
Yeah, no problem.
I wanted to smoke a cigarette.
How do you know Fern?
So this will allow my friends
to be able to take her off campus
- and out to dinner and-- thank you.
- Precisely.
- Please sign here.
- Mom, I really don't want
to spend my weekends
with your friends.
It might be nice
to get off campus for a weekend.
- What's in the bag?
- Oh, I borrowed it from my roommate.
It stinks.
Uh, what are you doing?
Borrowing clothes, remember?
Oh, right. Uh, let me help you.
- No, that's okay.
- Okay.
Mr. Middlewood, hurry!
Mr. Middlewood,
we need your help!
Kate fell in the shower!
Mr. Middlewood, help!
We need you!
Kate fell in the sho--
Kate fell in the shower.
- She needs you.
- Everybody out of my way.
Kate? Sorry.
Kate!
Sorry. Kate!
Sorry! God!
Oh my God. Sorry.
- Kate.
- Oh God. Mr. Middlewood.
Oh my God.
Oh my God. Are you all right?
Yes, it's just my leg.
Does that hurt?
Does it hurt when I do this?
A little bit higher.
- Higher?
- Higher.
- Does it hurt?
- Oh, it just tingles.
Higher. Higher. Higher.
Oh, this is a new feeling to me.
Higher.
Shh!
Can we have
some privacy, please?
Is that all right?
Does that feel okay?
- It's stinging through my pelvic bone.
- What? Am I--
Oh my God.
Mr. Middlewood,
it hurts so bad.
Can't you do something for the pain?
What's going on?
You, this isn't your floor.
Get back to your dorm.
Everyone get back to their rooms.
Go!
Hey.
Fern, are you going to eat all that?
Breakfast is
the most important meal of the day.
Maybe, but do you have
the metabolism for it?
I'm gonna go get ready for class.
Save me a seat.
Who's that boy?
Oh, that's Peter,
the headmistress's son.
He's cute.
What's he doing here?
- He goes to school here.
- He does?
Miss Wallace is too cheap
to pay tuition to another school,
so she makes him go to ours.
To be a boy at an all-girls school.
Yeah, you would think
he would know how to have fun
in his situation.
Why would you even waste
your vision on him?
- Hello.
- Because he has so much access.
- To what?
- His mother's files,
her stationery,
the key to the front door.
Hey, can you help?
Can you hold this straight for me?
- Mm-hmm.
- Just so that the under part
- doesn't go into this. Yeah.
- Is this my shirt?
- No.
- What are you doing to it?
Victoria found these
from the lost and found.
She said they were too plain,
so I'm restyling them for her.
No, these are my shirts.
She borrowed them from me.
Oh shit. Sorry, Fern.
It's not your fault. it's hers.
- Who?
- I'll take it off.
- Victoria.
- Oh, she's awesome.
Hey, Fern Fern,
can you help me with my homework?
At least she's not in our dorm.
Right?
Victoria, you know we have
no empty beds upstairs.
Listen, we're negotiating right now.
Let's try to come up with a solution.
I agree!
Get me out of this room
and the problem is solved.
Why should I have to sleep in a pisspot
when I am not the bedwetter?
Bedwetting is not that unusual.
It happens to deep sleepers.
I'm going to be ill.
My recommendation would he
that you wake Margaret up
and take her
to the toilet every three hours.
- It sounds like a plan.
- You must be kidding!
Every three hours.
No.
I don't have to go.
Okay, look up.
Oh my God.
You're not putting that blue on me.
Fern, you have a very tough palate.
I'm just trying to make you
brighten up a little bit.
Thanks, no. it's blue.
We'll do-- well, first put this on.
You're welcome.
I can't believe I let my mom talk me
into hanging out with her loser friends.
- That is such a drag.
- I think the blue looks nice, actually.
Victoria, what are you doing today?
- Today is the day.
- What day?
- The day I get Peter to hand over the key.
- To sneak out?
He's never gonna give you the key.
It's not gonna happen.
Do you always have
such little faith in your friends?
No, I have
a lot of faith in my friends.
- I just don't want to get in trouble.
- I fixed it.
Thank you.
We're just gonna have a bit of fun.
Besides, who sits around
boarding school obeying every rule?
What?
- Jesus.
- Kind of you.
Kate, it's your last year.
Don't you finally want
to have some real fun?
Hmm?
- Yeah yeah. If you get the key...
- We'll sneak out. Totally.
- Yes.
- Consider it done.
Oh my God.
- She's amazing, right?
- She's so cool.
I can't even believe it.
Fernanda?
Yeah?
I'm Gio, Gwen's husband.
Gwen, your mother's friend?
Really?
You wanna get in the car?
Okay.
# Your tongue, your transfer #
# Your hand, your answer,
on the bus... #
You like this song?
I've never heard it before.
Really?
You like music, don't you?
Yeah. it's not my life
or anything though.
Okay, that's it.
How about we make
a detour into town?
Isn't Gwen expecting us?
She's doing her own thing anyway.
- And what's that?
- Decorating the baby's room.
I didn't know you guys had a baby.
We will in a month or thereabouts.
That's exciting.
When did you move here?
A better question is
why did we move here?
Why did you move here?
Oh, uh, well, you're not supposed
to ask 'cause it's a better question,
- but...
- But?
...I wanted you to ask me
that 'cause-- yeah.
- No, I'm just kidding. No.
- # Watching us #
# Kiss me on the bus... #
George.
George, why don't you put
your book down
so we can spend some quality time
together while the girls are in town?
What?
Hmm?
Oh.
Maggie, not-- not now.
I'm-- I'm really not in the mood.
Sometimes you have to push yourself
over the threshold
to get into the mood, okay?
Why don't we try some of the tools
that we've been learning in therapy?
Let's get in the cricket stance.
Feel that stretch?
- Um, yeah.
- You're so tight right there.
- You feel that right there?
- Yeah.
- That feel nice?
There's a smile I like right there.
- Maggie, what are-- what are you doing?
- Shh.
- Mmm.
- That's--
- That's nice. Mmm.
- Maggie, what are you doing?
George, I just love the way
your hair smells like tobacco.
It's nice. Mmm.
Yeah. Oh, there.
Oh, thank you.
Mmm. Ah.
Counterclockwise, George.
- Okay.
- Mmm.
Now let's do
some positive affirmations, all right?
- Your turn.
- Umm,
- Yesterday...
- Yesterday.
...The way you looked was so--
- you were so committed...
- Mm-hmm.
...And very--
you were very pretty.
Go on.
That's-- that's it,
or-- yeah.
Uh-huh. Really good.
That was nice, George.
I think it's working. Feel that?
Okay.
Maggie, this is--
this isn't working for me.
Okay. Shh. it's all right.
- It happens to a lot of men your age.
- Okay.
Okay? Just give me a minute.
I'm gonna go get something, okay?
- No, Maggie, I'm just not--
- Shh!
- I just don't think this is the kind--
- I'll be right back.
- It just isn't working for me.
- Be right back. Just relax.
# It's harder than they say
to try to settle down #
# You see it in her line,
you look it up and down #
# You see it end to end,
you read it like a book #
# And then for what it is
you take a look #
# And when it rains, when it rains,
oh, the sun comes out again #
# Crown of age, crown of age,
it's like it's always been #
# And you know and you know,
oh, what you've gotta do #
# Crown of age, crown of age,
yeah, it's all up to you #
- # It's harder than you know... #
- Come on, let's go inside.
# To get where you belong,
somehow you're always there... #
So isn't there anything
you like about living up here?
Not one thing.
Well, I just haven't
figured it out yet.
I don't know. it's nothing like
my old neighborhood.
It's not important.
It's crazy to get
so attached to a place.
Yeah, I get that.
Don't you have any friends
up here, though?
No, not really.
But it could be
turning around for me.
- Thanks.
- Yeah.
These are precious moments.
Oh, Maggie, we talked about that.
That doesn't work. We know that.
How many have you been taking?
- Well, if I take--
- Shh.
- If I take more than one, I get a headache.
- Okay, well, let's take two.
- No. No no no, that's more than one.
- Here. Shh.
Okay, Just take these.
Here you go.
- My head is gonna--
- Just take 'em, George.
Okay, here's some shiitaki tea.
Come on, let's go.
There you go. That's nice.
Okay, there you go.
- Here we go. Is that nice?
- Yeah, let me-- let me get my hand up.
There you go. Oh, okay.
That's better.
It's gonna take
at least 30 minutes to kick in.
I'm gonna wait
for the pills to rescue us, okay?
So I want to start with some visualization
that Dr. Adler taught us, okay?
Now I want you to name a country.
Uh, Botswana.
- Germany.
- Okay, I can work with Germany.
Home of the sausage, huh?
- Maggie.
- You are a navy BMW 750. You like that?
- Okay, George close your eyes.
- Yeah.
All right, we've got a full tank of gas.
- I am-- okay.
- Close your eyes. God, I'm so moist.
You're gliding
through the smooth pavement
of the Autobahn, hugging...
...every curve. Okay?
You surge forward
like a powerful bullet,
- searching for its target.
- Mr. Middlewood,
- my pelvis tingles.
- You find it? A dark tiny black hole.
Right there, George.
Come on, give it to me.
Come on, George.
What is going on down there?
- Maggie, I just--
- It's like boiled shrimp.
I need at least 30 minutes
for it to kick in.
We don't have 30 minutes, George.
I'm not waiting 30 minutes.
All right, I'm gonna
show you something, okay?
- You see this, George?
- Yeah, I do.
- You see this? This is a hole.
- Yeah.
Oh, all right.
- I can't--
- Let me see who's at the door.
- Just give me 30 minutes.
- Don't move, all right? Just get it up.
30 minutes.
What happened?
I tripped and fell
into the emergency glass case.
- Are you all right?
- It really hurts, actually.
Oh. Well, I guess I should take you
to go see the nurse, right?
Yes, okay.
First I wanted to give you this.
To the front door I think.
Oh. Well, we wouldn't want this
to get into the wrong hands.
Thank you.
No, don't thank me.
George, I'll be back in five.
I was checking for moles.
It's just-- I couldn't view 'em.
I'm so sorry you hurt yourself.
Let's go.
See, Margaret,
the urine comes down here,
it goes through the bladder
and the pee comes out
through the urethra
and it goes, swoosh,
down the toilet.
Oh God.
Okay, let's go out in the hall.
it's not that difficult.
You can understand that, can't you?
Oh gosh, let's see.
- Oh yeah, that's a gash.
- Mmm.
Victoria, would you consider
sleeping on a rollaway cot
on my floor this semester?
Ow! You mean
the high school dorm?
Oh yes yes.
Fight it, fight it, fight it.
Yeah. I just think our little Margaret
there is a little upset.
I think she's painfully embarrassed
about her situation.
Mmm, poor Margaret.
Yeah, poor thing. it's tough.
You know, Victoria, I'll look forward
to having a girl like you on my floor.
- Huh.
- It'll be nice.
# Playing me what I want to hear... #
Thanks.
# Don't make me
have to come down there... #
I kinda have to pee.
# I wanna hear,
a few minutes, a few minutes... #
- I should get back to school.
- Now?
We have time to visit Gwen,
don't we?
No, you guys didn't sign me out
for the weekend,
- just through dinner.
- Oh shit. Really?
She's gonna be so upset.
Get in the car.
- Okay?
- Okay.
All right,
this should be all right for you.
Here you go.
Hey, Lu, how come you never put
any male characters in your comics?
I don't know.
Girls are more fun to draw, I guess.
Hey, Fern.
I-- I really like this drawing.
- You can have it if you want.
- Really?
I will add it to my collection
of Lucasta originals.
Hank, why are you always here?
Oh. I'm sorry.
- I was actually just leaving.
- No.
He's just delivering a pizza.
Mind your own business.
Well, I was just returning your jacket.
It's dirty.
You can't return my things dirty.
It was already like that.
No, it wasn't.
What is that anyway, dried blood?
I have no idea.
Looks like chocolate.
I can clean it.
There we go.
Crisis solved.
You know,
I've got to go back to work.
- Bye, Hank.
- Bye.
Hey, by the by,
I got the key from Peter,
so you me and Kate
next Saturday night. That'll be great.
Oh, and I'm just down the hall now.
- What room?
- They gave me the student lounge.
No way. As your bedroom?
What's the big deal?
It's like having your own apartment.
Well, why don't you come now
and we'll watch a film?
You are so lucky.
You have a TV.
Actually, you know what?
I'm just gonna stay here.
I just started a drawing
that I'd like to finish. You know?
Well, just bring along
your sketch book.
Another time.
Thanks, though.
I didn't want to tell anyone about Gio.
I wanted to keep him for myself.
As it turns out, the nights were
keeping Victoria's secrets too.
I didn't know what to do.
The loneliness of Victoria's pain
was unreachable,
so I did nothing.
Oh!
- Sorry. I'm really sorry, Kate.
- It's okay.
It- it's okay.
Here. Are these yours?
Oh. Yeah, the nurse gave them
to me for my ankle injury.
Well, you'd better keep up that limp.
Hey, why don't you just take one?
I don't think
a pill would help, somehow.
I think it will. I'm working
a pretty good buzz right now.
Come on.
A really good book can be an escape
and transport the reader
even out of his own life.
You're late.
Oh.
Kate, could you sit there, please?
Is this gonna be my seat
for the entire semester?
Yes.
That applies-
applies to all of you.
Wherever you are seated today
is where you'll be seated
for the remainder of the term.
- We're so close.
- Yes.
We are.
Are you wearing cologne?
It's witch hazel, actually.
Okay, moving along.
Our reading assignments this term
will be decided by you guys.
So what books would you
recommend to one another?
- Kate?
- "Lolita."
Nabokov.
That's a very rich choice.
Thank you.
Ugh, cl-- class dismissed.
- Hey, Fern?
- Yeah.
I was wondering
if you could help me write something.
Yeah, sure.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
This is in first.
- You're gonna ease off the clutch.
- Right.
- Fuck! Okay, that was really bad.
- No no no, you're doing great.
I love your style.
I want you to put it back into neutral.
- Where's that? Okay.
- Right here. All right?
Now-- good-- start it again.
Ready?
Are you ready?
Ease it--
no. Whoa! Whoa!
Sorry. I think
we should switch now.
Here you go.
Mmm! I'm sorry.
Sorry.
- I'm sorry.
- It's all right.
Okay.
All right.
- It's just not cool.
- What's not cool
is the fact that
we're not going out tonight
and tonight is the fair.
This is the only night we can do this.
Guys, what are you doing?
You're taking forever.
What's going on?
Um, apparently we're not going.
What? why?
Because you can't exclude Fern.
She's our best friend.
Huh.
Where is she anyway?
She's with Peter right now.
Really? Why?
She's helping him write
an essay or something.
I thought you said
Peter kept to himself.
He did, I thought.
Obviously I don't know
anything about Peter.
I mean I never would've imagined
that he'd help us sneak out.
Yeah, how did
you manage that anyway?
Let's go get Fern.
- Do you think she'd come with us still?
- Yes.
You guys are right.
I feel really bad.
- Can we--
- Yeah.
- Yes, let's go.
- Can we still go? Okay, cool.
So, um, Victoria wants you to go.
- Who cares?
- We care.
It won't be any fun without you, Fern.
I can't anyway.
I told Peter I'd help him write something.
- Where is he?
- I don't know.
He should be here any minute.
Well, you guys figure out
what you wanna do
and I'm going to go use the toilet.
- Peter.
- Yeah?
Hi. Fern asked me to come say
she can't make it.
- What? Why?
- Period. Blech.
Sorry.
- Bye.
- I don't want to get expelled.
We're not gonna get expelled, okay?
God! Peter gave Victoria the key.
Yeah, even if we do get caught,
Miss Wallace is not gonna expel her son.
Please.
Well, he's not coming,
so can we go?
- Hmm?
- Fine.
- So?
- We're going.
Come on. Come on.
Shh!
Is it really gonna work?
- Hmm?
- Shh shh shh. Shh.
Shh shh!
Okay, are you ready?
Okay. One two-- go!
# I don't know where I've been going... #
# Or where I have come from #
# Everything here looks the same... #
Oh my God.
I totally kick ass at this game,
so I am buying for everyone.
- Whoo!
- Gimme gimme gimme.
I rule!
Whoo!
- A pig.
- One more throw.
Well, I am completely offended.
- May I please have the cock?
- The what?
- The cock.
- The rooster.
Go ahead and look at it.
Look at it. Here we go.
- Yay!
- Yes! You did it! You did it!
Whoo!
Look! I won! I won!
- You won?!
- Hey! No, you didn't!
- Yes, I did.
- That was my dart.
- No, it wasn't. What did I win?
- But I popped that balloon.
What are you, nuts? I saw the whole thing.
My daughter popped that balloon.
Are you calling me a liar?
Is he calling me a liar?
Okay okay.
We're all here to have fun.
Thank you.
I do hope you've come to kill me.
I have a terribly painful-- oh!
--painful painful malady.
Yes. How would you like to die?
Poisons?
Dagger through the heart?
Strangulation?
Shotgun?
Okay, I'm bored. Let's roll.
I want to stay
and watch how she dies.
The bone crush--
a wise choice, my dear.
I'm gonna get this.
I get this all the time, guys.
I've got the eye of the tiger,
eye of the tiger, eye of the tiger.
I won!
- Don't look.
- What? What?
- The Middlewoods are right behind us.
- Oh my God.
- Don't look!
- Stop it!
Okay, we have to run away.
One two three.
Whoo!
- Surprise!
- Whoa.
- What are you doing here?
- We escaped.
I wish we hadn't run into these guys.
Yeah, pick it up.
I have a surprise for you.
- A surprise?
- It's a cock hat,
Mr. Cock.
Come on, let's go get high
on the Ferris wheel.
- Yes!
- I guess it's off to the Ferris wheel.
Yeah. Umm...
Yeah, actually, I think I'm gonna
catch up with you guys later.
Wait. Where are you going?
Yeah, I just really don't wanna spend
the night babysitting.
- Slices, anyone?
- No thanks, Kenny.
Thanks, Ken.
- Where's Kate?
- Getting into trouble on the Ferris wheel.
Should probably go look for her.
- Oh. Well, I'll come with you.
- Perfect.
- Good. All right.
- Okay.
- You guys have fun.
- Bye.
- Bye. Don't be mad. Love you.
- Okay.
I think I'm gonna go
check out the produce.
- Do you wanna come?
- Uh, no.
- Come on.
- No no no, I'm just--
- Okay. I'll see you later
- Okay.
- Hi.
- Hey, what are you doing here?
Are you here by yourself?
No.
I'm with my friends.
We snuck out.
I used to sneak out
of my parents' house all the time.
- Really?
- Mm-hmm.
What would happen
when you got caught?
The threat of boarding school.
So basically my life
is your worst-case scenario.
No, actually, my life right now
is my worst-case scenario.
Gio, you wouldn't believe the selection
of cheddars they have here.
They even have one
that's marbleized with beer.
- Is that Fernanda?
- Hi.
You look just like your mother.
- Hello.
What's your name?
- # Cherry lives with a man in Queens... #
- Light it up.
# She wants to get lit
in a limousine #
# She locked herself
in the girls' bathroom... #
I'm a dragon!
What you looking at?
Aren't you supposed
to be keeping a low profile?
Lu!
- You're my best friend!
- Kate doesn't know how to lay low.
She's gonna get us all expelled.
I love you!
Look at the stars. They--
- Come up here! it's amazing.
- They look so close, don't they?
When I was little I used to get freckles
on my face every summer
and my brother would tell me
that they were a map of the stars.
So I would sit in front of the mirror
and search for the Big Dipper endlessly.
Stupid.
Are-- are-- are they still there?
Maybe.
There might be traces
of a sun-kissed seven-year-old.
Oh. I'm-- I'm-- I'm sorry.
No, it's fine.
It's fine. it's okay.
Whoa.
Whoo!
Harvest Fest!
Are they gonna let us off?
So how much for one of these?
Oh, well, that depends.
- On what?
- Well, lots of things, actually.
The wood finish, the hardware,
the size, the bedding,
the pillow insert, you know.
- Oh. Interesting.
- Yeah. Mm-hmm.
Well, I really love
this chrome hardware.
- Yes.
- Looks almost nautical.
I love this cherry wood.
- Is this satin?
- Yeah.
Can you have it in different colors?
- Mm-hmm.
- What would look best against my skin,
red or navy blue?
Oh, well, I'd say the red.
It's more festive. Yeah.
I wonder what it must feel like
to lie in one of these.
Gio, the arches.
So I take this great Italian cooking class
on Saturday mornings.
When you come over for the weekend,
you're gonna have to join me.
- We can do it together.
- Yeah, it'll be fun.
Hey, isn't this song
on one of the albums you got me?
- Yes, it is.
- I like this song.
You bought records?
I thought Fernanda couldn't hang out
'cause she had a paper due.
- Are you kidding me?
- No, I lent-- I lent her records
- from the trunk of my car.
- Where have you been?
Where is everyone?
Oh, did you know
it was hunting season?
Victoria, this is Gwen and Gio.
- Hi.
- Actually, you probably know her mom.
She's friends with my mom.
They went to school together.
It's Olga, right?
Wait. Olga de Monet?
- Sadly yes.
- You'll have to come over
and spend the weekend
at our house as well.
That would be great.
So, Gio, do you collect vinyls?
I saw you guys clear the shelves
at the record store the other day.