Queen to the king,
possible straight going there.
Eight on the eight.
And the jack gets a boss.
Eights open.
Aren't you guys afraid of an officer
coming down here or something?
Trust me.
Nobody ever comes down here but us.
- That thing always do that?
- Do what?
Whatever that thing is under the tarp.
I thought I just saw it move,
or do something...
Probably the only thing
it ever did was cost money.
I'm telling you, the thing is moving!
If you don't have the straight, just fold.
What are you doing?
Hold your fire!
This is Area C.
We're under heavy fire down here.
We need...
To the gate room!
Go, go, go! Move it!
Hold your fire!
I thought I saw someone on
the roof when we came up the drive, sir.
There's a ladder over there.
- Colonel Jack O'Neill?
- Retired.
I'm Major Samuels.
Want a little piece of advice, Major?
Get re-assed to NASA.
That's where all the action's gonna be.
Out there.
I'm... I'm under orders to bring you
to see General Hammond, sir.
- Never heard of him.
- He replaced General West.
- I'm a busy man, Major.
- I can see that, sir.
He says it's important.
Has to do with the stargate.
We have to take a second elevator
the rest of the way, sir.
It's a long way down.
Yeah, I know. I've been here before.
Of course.
This way, sir.
Come.
General Hammond, Colonel Jack O'Neill.
Retired.
I can see that. I envy you, Colonel.
Major Samuels mentioned something
about the stargate.
Down to business. I can do that.
This way...
Anyone you know, Colonel?
They're not human.
You think?
Best we can tell,
these slits are actually a pouch,
similar to that found in a marsupial.
- Like a kangaroo.
- Mmm.
Except...
In both sexes.
These people, or aliens,
whatever you wanna call them,
came through, killed four of my people
and kidnapped another,
using advanced weapons.
Airman?
Weapons?
Seen one before, I take it?
Yes, sir.
But there are no creatures like this
on Abydos.
Those people were human.
They were from Earth.
Ra brought 'em there
thousands of years ago.
I know all about that.
But your report said this Ra was in fact
some kind of alien that lived
inside a human body.
His eyes glowed. That was our first clue.
Are you sure he's dead, Colonel?
Unless he could survive a tactical
nuclear warhead
blowing up in his face, I'm positive. Why?
Well, Colonel, these people,
or whatever they are,
were guarding another man
who retreated back through the stargate.
I got a good look at his eyes, Colonel.
They glowed.
How do you feel about the Stargate
mission after all this time, Colonel?
How do you mean?
Well, it's been over a year.
Has your perspective changed?
Well, sir, I...
Kawalsky and Ferretti? Yes.
Served under your command
on the first Stargate mission.
Have a seat, Colonel.
Tell me about Daniel Jackson, Colonel.
Why are they questioning my men?
They're not your men anymore, Colonel.
You retired.
Daniel Jackson?
- You read the report?
- Yes.
- It's all there.
- Is it?
What's this all about, General?
You didn't like Daniel Jackson, did you?
Basically, he was a geek, sir.
So you didn't have a lot of time for him?
I didn't say that.
He also saved my life and found
the way home for my men and me.
A little thing like that can kind of
make a person grow on you.
According to the mission brief,
your orders were to
go through the stargate,
to detect any possible threat to Earth,
and if found, to detonate a nuclear device
and destroy the gate on the other side.
Yes.
But that's
not what you did, is it?
Not right away.
Ra's forces overpowered my team
and took the weapon before I could arm it.
But, with Dr. Jackson's help,
you eventually regained control,
- and did, in fact, detonate the weapon?
- Yes.
So, to the best of your knowledge,
Daniel Jackson and everyone else
you knew on Abydos is dead, correct?
That's correct.
Good.
Then you won't mind if I authorize
a go-ahead on our plan.
This quartz material
the stargates are made of,
it must be tough stuff
if it can withstand a Mark 3.
Well, we sent a robot probe through
after we got back, sir.
It was flattened on the other end.
Obviously, the Abydos stargate
had been buried in the rubble.
But somehow, it got unburied.
Oh, my God!
You're sending another bomb?
A Mark 5 this time.
Unless you have something to add.
General Hammond, sir.
I regret to inform you that my report
was not entirely accurate.
You didn't detonate the bomb.
I did detonate the bomb, sir,
and it was aboard Ra's spacecraft,
so it did kill him
and eliminate the risk to Earth.
- However...
Ra's ship was in orbit
above the planet at the time.
Neither the gate nor anything else
on the planet was destroyed.
Daniel Jackson is alive
and living with the people on Abydos.
You violated direct orders. Why?
Because the people of Abydos
are no threat to us.
They deserve to be left alone.
That's not up to you...
If I'd come back here and reported the gate
on the other side was still intact,
we would've sent another bomb,
just like you were about to.
It wasn't necessary to let those people die.
The threat from Ra was gone.
What about the probe we sent through?
It was crushed instantly.
After we came home,
Daniel buried the gate in rocks,
making my return
or anybody else's impossible.
Those four bodies lying in the infirmary
say otherwise.
Take Colonel O'Neill to the holding room.
Give him a little time to think about
things while I decide what to do with him.
Sergeant.
Colonel O'Neill, sir.
I'm retired, Kawalsky. Lose the salute.
Me and Ferretti didn't tell them anything.
I appreciate that.
Hey, those kids on Abydos
saved my life, too.
Yeah. Those kids...
I mean, they're the whole reason
we kept it secret.
Right?
That one kid idolized you. Remember him?
Weird name... What was it?
Skaara.
Right.
Remember how he was
always saluting you?
Yeah.
My kid used to do that when he was little.
Skaara kind of reminded me of him.
How many people did you say
are on Abydos?
That we saw? Maybe 5,000.
Does this mean you're reconsidering
sending the bomb, sir?
It means I'm open to suggestions.
General, let me take a team
through that gate.
We'll find out who those aliens are.
Kawalsky and I have been there before.
We know the lay of the land.
We know the people.
You think you know them.
Jackson could be dead.
You don't know
what you'd be walking into.
There is one way to find out, sir.
We'll have the prototype probe
shipped from MIT.
No, sir. We don't need that probe.
- We don't?
- Nope. This'll do.
Chevron one encoded.
Chevron two encoded.
Care to explain this concept?
Chevron three encoded.
Jackson has allergies.
I get it.
Chevron four encoded.
He'll know this came from me
and not from someone like...
Yourself.
Chevron five encoded.
Why not just send a note?
- Anyone could send a note.
Chevron six encoded.
Chevron seven locked.
Now what?
If Jackson's still around,
he'll know what the message means.
What if the aliens got it?
Well, they could be blowing
their noses right now.
They could be planning an attack.
Come on, Samuels.
Let me be the cynic around here, huh?
General, this could take some time.
Incoming wormhole.
Permission to take a team through
the stargate, sir?
Assuming I get
the President's authorization,
the mission briefing will be at 0800 hours.
Consider yourself recalled
to active duty, Colonel.
Gentlemen, take your seats.
Where's Captain Carter?
Just arriving, sir.
Carter?
I'm assigning Sam Carter to this mission.
I'd prefer to put together
my own team, sir.
I'm sorry. Not on this mission.
Carter's our expert on the stargate.
Where is he transferring from?
She is transferring
from the Pentagon.
I take it you're Colonel O'Neill.
Captain Samantha Carter reporting, sir.
But, of course, you go by Sam.
Let's get started.
- Colonel?
- All right.
For those of you on your first trip
through the gate,
you should be prepared
for what to expect.
Well, I've practically memorized
your report from the first mission, sir.
I'd like to think I've been
preparing for this all my life.
I think what the Colonel is saying is,
have you ever pulled out of a simulated
bombing run in an F-16 at eight-plus Gs?
Yes.
Well, it's way worse than that.
By the time you get to the other side,
you're frozen stiff,
like you've just been through a blizzard.
That's a result of the compression
your molecules undergo
during the millisecond required
for reconstitution.
Here we go. Another scientist.
General, please.
Theoretical astrophysicist.
Which means?
Means she's smarter than you are, Colonel.
Especially in matters
related to the stargate.
Well, you can believe me, this has nothing
to do with you being a woman.
I like women.
I've just got a little problem
with scientists.
Well, Colonel, I logged over 100 hours
in enemy airspace during the Gulf War.
Is that tough enough for you?
Or are we gonna have to arm wrestle?
I don't mean to throw a damper
on your enthusiasm,
but I still say the safest
and most logical way
is to bury the stargate,
just like the ancient Egyptians did,
make it impossible for the aliens to return.
It's the only way to eliminate the threat.
- Except it won't work.
- It worked before.
How do you all think the stargate
got to Earth in the first place?
Good question.
They've got ships, General.
Ra had one as big as the great pyramids.
They don't need the stargate to get here.
They can do it the old-fashioned way.
Now, with all due respect
to Mr. Glass-ls-Half-Empty over here,
don't you think maybe
we should use the stargate
to do a little reconnaissance
before they decide to show up again?
I'll give you exactly 24 hours to either
return or send a message through.
No Kleenex boxes, please.
Otherwise, I will assume the worst,
and send a bomb through.
Understood.
- Try to follow orders this time, Colonel.
- Sir?
This time, you bring Daniel Jackson back.
Is that clear?
Move out!
My God! Look at this!
You can actually see the fluctuations
in the event horizon.
Lower your guns.
Hello, Jack. Welcome back.
- Skaara.
- O'Neer.
I did not think to be seeing you again.
How are you, Daniel?
Good. You?
Much better, now that I know
everybody's okay.
Greetings from Earth, Dr. Jackson.
Hello, Ferretti.
Brought you a little something, Daniel.
Kawalsky.
Sha're, don't be shy.
It's good to see you again.
So, I figured it was only a matter of time
before you had to tell the truth
about us still being here.
Yeah.
Why the militia?
Something else come through?
- No, we're just taking precautions. Why?
- Amazing.
This is what was missing
from the dig at Giza.
This is how they controlled it.
It took us 15 years
and three supercomputers
to jury-rig a control system
for the gate on Earth!
- Captain.
- Look how small it is!
Captain!
Oh.
Right.
Dr. Jackson, I presume.
I'm Dr. Samantha Carter.
Hi.
What's going on, Jack?
Six hostile aliens came through
the stargate on Earth.
Four people are dead, one's missing.
One of them looked like Ra, Daniel.
Well,
they didn't come from here.
I mean, the boys take shifts guarding it,
36 hours a day, every day.
We'd know if they came through here.
Well, they came from somewhere, Daniel.
I'm gonna have to look around.
I think I can help you find out who it was,
but it's going to have to wait
till the sandstorm is over.
We were about to have our evening meal.
Why don't you join us?
I'm sure the folks at MIT would be happy
to know their million-dollar probe
also makes fine cookware.
Well, it got pretty banged up when it came
through the gate into our barricade,
so we made use, and...
Well, it is non-stick titanium, so it...
Very good. Perfect.
Beanaa wa. Everybody try this.
This too.
What's this?
Drink.
Moonshine? Did you make this?
Moonshine?
Yeah, moonshine. As in booze.
Daniel, what are you teaching these kids?
Our little soldiers
are all grown up, Colonel.
Try it.
All right. Skaara's moonshine.
Let's give it a shot.
Oh, God!
Smooth. Very smooth.
Moonshine.
I'm so proud.
Wow!
O'Neer...
No. It's yours.
I gave that to you to keep. Remember?
Thank you.
You know, he's never had that out of his
sight the whole time you were gone.
Yeah?
So this man who looked like Ra,
he must've come through another gate.
- What other gate?
- Another stargate?
- The stargate only goes here.
- No. No. I think you're wrong about that.
I was there.
We ran hundreds of permutations.
But you didn't have what you need.
Daniel, what are you talking about?
Daniel, the storm has passed.
I'll show you.
Sha're, ben qua ri Jack and his
friends to see the vili tao an.
No, no, I won't be long.
Goodbye, my Daniel.
Goodbye.
Bye.
- I can't say I missed this place.
- Come on.
- This is just incredible.
- You ain't seen nothing yet.
Let go of me!
Where the hell are you taking me?
Come.
Let go of me.
Lovely. Full of life.
You could be the vessel
for my future queen.
Yes. Very nice, indeed.
But I am not the one
you must finally please.
A shame.
So, I figured that
there had to be
more to this place, so I started exploring.
Just the area around the town
and the pyramid, at first.
Then after about a month,
I found this place.
Doctor, you're gonna love this.
Oh, my God!
This is the archeological find
of the century. There must be...
Thousands of lines of hieroglyphs.
So, Daniel, have you had a chance
to translate this yet?
- I think so.
- What's it say?
Well, it doesn't say anything.
Actually, it's sort of a chart,
more of a map.
A map?
Of?
Well, I haven't been able
to analyze all of it.
I mean, look at it.
It would take my whole life.
Well, Daniel, we don't have
that much time.
What's it a map of?
Well, the cartouches seem to be
separated clearly into groupings.
Each grouping is attached to the others
with a series of lines.
And each grouping of glyphs
contain seven symbols.
So you can see where
this is going, of course.
Why don't you tell us anyway?
All the symbols are on
the stargate in the Abydos chamber.
I've also managed to chart
some of them in the Abydos night sky,
or at least pretty close.
I think that this is a map of
a vast network of stargates.
Stargates that are all over the galaxy!
I don't think that can be, Doctor.
Why not?
Well, because after Colonel O'Neill
and his team came back,
my team ran hundreds
of symbol permutations,
using Earth as the point of origin,
and it never worked.
Then where did your Ra lookalike
come from?
Look, I don't pretend to know
anything about astrophysics,
but couldn't the planets change?
I mean, drift apart or something
like that to throw this map off?
- I knew I'd like you.
- Really?
I mean... You mean, I'm right?
The galaxy is a vortex.
All the stars are constantly moving
in relation to one another.
So in the thousands of years
since the stargate was built...
All the coordinates could've changed.
But why does it still work
between Abydos and Earth?
Well, Abydos is probably the closest
planet in the network to Earth.
I mean, the closer they are, the less
the difference in relative position.
The further away,
the greater the difference.
In a few thousand more years, it won't
work between Earth and Abydos either.
Unless you can adjust
for the displacement.
Right. Now, with this map as a base,
that should be easy.
All we have to do is correct
for stellar drift.
Then, I should be able to arrive
at a computer model
that will predict the adjustments
necessary to get the gate working again.
So the stargate can go other places?
- Well, yes. Yes, it could.
- Probably.
Sir, with your permission, I'd like to put
this entire cartouche on digital video.
Then, when we get back to Earth,
I can download it into the computer
and get faster results.
Yeah, go ahead.
Man, you gotta give Daniel credit.
She is one beautiful woman.
Go, go, go.
This is not your weapon.
Where did you get it?
A good choice, Teal'c.
A perfect specimen.
You may be the one.
Sha're!
Hey, what's up, guys?
I wonder if he saw the symbols.
Bolaa!
It's all right. Just tell me what happened.
It was Ra.
Okay. Okay.
Hang in there, Ferretti.
- What's going on?
- Ra is dead.
No... Ra, I saw... He took Sha're.
He took Skaara into the chaapa 'ai.
Where? Did you see?
Show me the pictures.
Did you see?
Come on.
What's going on, Daniel?
Could there be another Ra?
How in the hell should I know?
I should have left the barricade up.
This is my fault.
Colonel, Ferretti needs
medical attention now!
Go! Help him. I can send you back.
You're coming with us this time, Daniel.
I've got orders.
I don't care about your orders, Colonel.
My wife is out there. So is Skaara.
And the only way we're gonna get 'em
back is for you to come home with us.
Ferretti might have
seen those coordinates.
I've got everything I need.
After we go through the chaapa 'ai,
you have to bury it like we did before,
and then leave this place.
- You come back?
- No.
No, I can't. Nobody can.
That's what I'm telling you.
Not for a long time.
Now, as soon as we're gone,
I want you to close it. Bury it.
Put a big, heavy cover stone over it.
Nothing good can ever
come through this gate.
Do you understand?
You came through it, Daniel.
Do you remember the story I told you?
How the ancient Egyptians back on Earth
cut themselves off from Ra?
Well, that is exactly what you have to do.
Then, in one year, one year from this day,
you take the cover stone away.
I will try to bring Sha're home
with me on that day.
But if I don't make it back, if I don't...
If I don't return, then you must
bury the gate again forever, joa qua?
Promise me.
- Yes.
We promise, Daniel.
You tell Sha're's father, in one year...
Incoming wormhole.
Stand by for arrival.
Close the iris! Close the iris!
What the hell's that, sir?
That's our insurance against
any more surprises.
What happened, Colonel?
Base camp was hit while
we were on recon, sir.
Ferretti's hurt,
Currin and Swope are down.
Same hostiles who attacked us?
That's a fair guess.
Jackson's wife and one of our kids
was kidnapped.
General, hi. I'm Daniel Jackson.
We've never met.
I'd like to be on the team
that goes after them.
You're not in any position
to make demands, Jackson.
Ferretti might have seen
the sequence of symbols
they used to go through the stargate.
That should tell us where they went.
General, Dr. Jackson found
an entire cartouche on Abydos
with 1,000 possible coordinates,
maybe more.
That's 1,000 new worlds, General.
And our stargate can take us
to these worlds?
With this new data, as long as we make
the appropriate allowances
for alignment in the targeting computer...
Yes or no?
I think so, sir. Yes.
Request permission to upload the symbols
into the base supercomputer for analysis.
And, sir, I'd like to lead the rescue mission
once we find out where these hostiles are.
We'll discuss that request in a briefing
at 0800 hours.
Captain Carter, the base computer
is at your disposal.
In the meantime, get this man
some clean clothing. He stinks.
Your death cannot help her.
I am not afraid of you!
No!
Doc says he's gonna make it.
Yes, sir.
- You gonna stay here all night?
- Yes, sir.
Hey.
They don't know what to do with me.
And I don't know what to do with myself.
Come on. Let's get out of here.
- Nice catch.
- Thank you.
Sorry. Gate travel always seems
to make my allergies...
- Sorry.
- So, you were saying...
Anyway...
As soon as you were gone
and they realized they were free,
I mean, Abydos was
their world for the taking.
- Had a little party, did you?
- Yeah. Yeah, big, big party.
They treated me like their savior.
It was embarrassing.
Savior of Abydos? Doesn't sound so bad.
Yeah, I spent the first year having to stop
everyone I saw from bowing all the time.
It's amazing you turned out so normal.
Well, if it wasn't for Sha're, I probably...
She was the complete opposite
of everyone else.
She practically fell on the floor
laughing every time
I tried to do some chore
they all took for granted.
Like, grinding yaphetta flour.
I mean, have you ever tried
to grind your own flour?
I'm trying to kick the flour thing.
This is going straight to my head.
What time is it anyway?
I must have gate-lag or something.
Daniel, for crying out loud,
you've had one beer.
You're a cheaper date than my wife was.
Yes, when am I going to meet your wife?
Probably never.
After I came back from Abydos
the first time, she'd already left.
- I'm sorry.
- Yeah. So was I.
I think in her heart she forgave me
for what happened to our kid.
She just couldn't forget.
And what about you?
I'm the opposite. I'll never forgive myself.
But sometimes, I can forget.
People, what is spoken of in this room
is classified as SCI, top secret.
Colonel, what do we know about
these hostiles we didn't yesterday?
Not a hell of a lot, General.
The Abydon boys who survived the attack
on base camp thought it was Ra.
I thought he was dead.
Gentlemen, which is it?
He's dead. He's definitely dead.
I mean, the bomb...
I mean, he's gotta be dead, right?
- Then who's coming through the stargate?
- Gods.
- What?
- Not as in "God" god.
Ra played a god, the sun god.
He borrowed the religion and culture
of the ancient Egyptians
he brought through the gate,
and then he used it to enslave them.
You see, he wanted the people of Abydos
to believe that he was the only one.
You're saying
Ra's not the last of his race, after all?
- Maybe he's got a brother, Ray.
- That's what we need.
Wait a minute.
The legend goes, Ra's race was dying.
He survived by taking over the body
of his human host, an Egyptian boy.
But who's to say more of his kind
couldn't do the same thing?
I mean, this could have happened
at any time, anywhere there's a gate.
I mean, this could be happening right now.
Colonel, you've had the most experience
in fighting this hostile.
Assuming you have to defend yourself
in the field, are you up to it?
- We beat 'em once.
- I'll take that as a maybe.
Captain Carter, you're confident
that the stargate will take us
where we want to go
with this new information?
Well, the computer's feeding
the revised coordinates
into the targeting computer right now.
It'll take time to calculate,
but it should spit out
two or three destinations a month.
Let's not fool ourselves here, people.
This thing is both vast and dangerous,
and we are in so far over our heads
we can barely see daylight.
These hostiles we are up against possess
technology so far superior to our own,
we don't have the faintest idea
how it works.
We would all be much better off
if the stargate had been left in the ground.
With respect, sir, we can't bury
our heads in the sand.
I mean, think of how much we could learn.
Think of what we could bring back.
What you could bring back is precisely
what I'm afraid of, Captain.
However, the President of the
United States happens to agree with you.
In the event your theories pan out, he
has ordered the formation of nine teams,
whose duties will be to perform
reconnaissance, determine threats,
and if possible, to make peaceful contact
with the peoples of these worlds.
Now, these teams will operate
on a covert, top-secret basis.
No one will know of their existence,
except the President and the joint chiefs.
- Colonel O'Neill.
- Sir?
Your team will be designated SG-1.
The team will consist of yourself,
Captain Carter...
And me?
Dr. Jackson, we need you
to work as a consultant
with the other SG teams from here.
Your expertise in ancient cultures
and languages are far too valuable...
I really have to be on their team.
My wife is out there, General. I need to go.
I'll take that under consideration.
Major Kawalsky, you will head SG-2.
I will?
Colonel O'Neill keeps telling me
it's about time you had a command.
I had a moment of weakness.
Ferretti is conscious, sir.
Dismissed.
I'll take over. Thanks.
- Ferretti.
- Hey.
Listen, Ferretti.
I know you're probably not feeling so hot,
but we need something from you.
Looks like
he's way ahead of you, Colonel.
You saw all seven symbols?
This is where they went? You sure?
Colonel, I'd like to remind you,
in the event that you fail to notify
base camp within 24 hours,
SG-2 will scrub the mission,
and return without you.
Understood!
Not gonna happen, Colonel.
SG-2 won't leave without you.
All right, let's confirm transmitter codes.
Remember, only the right code
will open the iris,
and if you lose the transmitter,
you cannot get home.
Understood, sir.
Chevron seven unlocked.
Let's move out.
Kind of wish I was going with you.
Yeah?
I'm kind of glad you're staying behind.
Damn.
Dammit, it's cold!
Okay, people, let's get the gear out!
Let's move!
Does anybody have a Kleenex?
Come.
No! No!
No!
This one has spirit.
Does she please you, my love?
It must be some sort
of ceremonial place.
The gate is, has to be, an integral
part of their spiritual culture.
See, this place was built for worshippers.
Well, let's just try to be on our way
before the worshippees show up, huh?
You figure out yet how to align
this gate to get back home?
Yeah.
The device is the same as on Abydos.
- This symbol represents...
- Brief Kawalsky's team yet?
- Yes. This symbol represents...
- Good job.
We'll have to set up camp where
there's better cover, Colonel.
Sirs, I found what looks like a trail
down the mountain.
Looks like it's seen traffic
in the last couple of days.
Thank you, Airman. Carter?
I set up a line of Claymores along
that ridge at 10 meter intervals.
That sound about right, Kawalsky?
Yeah. That'll work.
This looks like a good spot right up here!
- All right. If we're not back in 20 hours...
- We'll come rescue your sorry asses.
Negative.
You'll go back through the gate
with the combination Daniel just gave you,
- as you were ordered.
- Yes, sir.
If we don't make it back,
it's 'cause we got our butts kicked,
- and that means you're out of here.
- Yes, sir.
- Hold down the fort.
- Pick me up a T-shirt.
So, Dr. Jackson,
tell me more about Sha're.
- How did you meet?
- Sha're? Well, she's...
She was a gift.
She was, actually, from the elders
of Abydos the first night we were there.
- And you accepted?
- Hold up!
What?
- See any weapons?
- No, sir.
They're worshippers.
All right, Captain,
take a position 50 yards...
For crying out loud.
The man has not changed.
Hi.
We just came through the stargate...
The chaapa 'ai?
No, please don't do that.
- Friends of yours?
- No.
Unless we want to get ourselves
a really bad reputation,
I just think we should avoid shooting
the first people we meet on a new planet.
Please, you don't have to do this.
"Choose." They want to know
if we're here to choose.
Sure. We can choose. Choosing is good.
It's a derivation of Arabic, combined with...
Yeah, yeah, all right, whatever.
Just ask them to take us
to the nearest village or town.
Would you take us to...
Chulak. Chulak.
Chulak, eh?
Chulak.
Chulak. Sounds good.
I hear it's nice this time of year.
- Why are they treating us like this?
- They think we're gods.
Incredible.
This is a feast of some kind.
Apparently, someone's been expected.
Okay. We're gods. Now what?
I have no idea.
Maybe you should tell them
we want to look around, Daniel.
When in Rome...
Behold,
your queen.
Sha're?
- Sha're, thank God, I thought we'd never...
- Kneel before your queen!
Sha're, it's me!
Daniel. Daniel.
- Sha're!
- Easy.
- You've been unconscious for hours.
- No. I saw her.
- I know. We all did.
- I saw Sha're.
- Where are we?
- Some sort of prison.
Come on, sit down. Sit down. Easy.
It all happened so fast.
I mean, Ra sent you flying across
the room, a guard zapped the colonel.
Next thing I remember, we're all here.
No, it wasn't Ra. It was Apophis.
Who?
It's from Egyptian mythology.
Ra was the sun god who ruled the day.
Apophis was the serpent god,
Ra's rival, who ruled the night.
It's right out of The Book of the Dead.
They're living it.
What's he done to Sha're?
I've got to find her.
We can't.
- If I could just...
- Daniel, you saw her eyes.
- Well, maybe it's some kind of drug...
- These hostiles are parasites.
They use human beings as hosts.
That's what Ra did. That...
No, I don't believe that.
I'm sorry, I just... I can't.
If there's a way out of here,
I haven't found it yet.
But look what I did find.
- Daniel! You're okay!
- I think so.
Easy, big guy.
Welcome back
to the land of the conscious.
O'Neer told me about Sha're.
- Jack, help me. We can find her again.
- Daniel.
Don't.
Look, get some rest.
By all rights, you should be dead.
- You still got that transmitter?
- Yeah.
All right, we may have to destroy it.
If we can't find a way out of here,
the mission's a bust anyway,
and we don't want Apockhead or whatever
his name is to get his hands on that thing.
Well, he still wouldn't know the code.
There's half a billion permutations.
Don't take this personally, but
they're way smarter than we are.
Come on, Skaara,
let's find a way out of here.
What is this?
It's a watch. It tells me the time.
Where are you from?
Earth. Chicago, if you wanna be...
Your words mean nothing.
Where are you from?
Excuse me.
This is where we're from.
Friendly fellow.
What do you think that was about?
I don't know.
Come on, Skaara.
Warren, let's go! Rise and shine!
The sun is... The suns are coming up.
We're gonna be all right.
We can't go through another night
like that, Major.
Yeah. Gets a little chilly
on this planet at night.
The Colonel should've sent us
a message by now.
When do you have to make the decision
whether or not to go back
to the stargate?
That'll be about when hell freezes over.
I think that pretty much describes
our current situation.
We are not leaving here
without the Colonel.
Is that understood?
General, the warhead is armed
and ready for you to give the word, sir.
How much time have we got left?
Just under five hours.
Let's keep our fingers off the trigger
until the time comes, shall we?
Yes, sir.
- Sha're is dead?
- Yeah.
No.
- Know what, Skaara? I don't know.
- We will save her.
I can't promise you anything
at the moment.
But you are a great warrior!
We defeated Ra together!
Yeah, I know, but look around here.
Look what we're up against.
We'll try.
Come on.
What did he say?
They're going to choose.
Choose what?
Who will be the children of the gods.
Sha're.
Jack, help me, please.
- Daniel!
- Daniel! Don't! Don't!
Kneel before your masters!
Skaara.
Daniel!
This one is passionate.
How much would I remember
if you chose me?
- Daniel, what are you doing?
- Tell me.
Something of the host must survive.
Nothing.
Him.
Skaara!
O'Neer! O'Neer! O'Neer!
Kill the rest.
I can save these people!
Help me.
Many have said that.
But you are the first I believe could do it!
Get out of the way!
Come on, let's move!
Let's go, let's go, come on!
You gonna be okay?
Hey! Come on!
I have nowhere to go.
For this, you can stay at my place!
Let's go!
What's your name?
Teal'c.
Teal'c, where will they
take Skaara, the boy?
To the stargate.
After they've selected hosts for
their children, they will return home.
Sir, they have just under an hour
until the deadline.
We should've heard from them by now.
A lot can happen in an hour, Major.
Okay, come on, people!
We're almost there! Let's go!
We've got less than an hour.
How're we doing?
We lost a few when we reached the forest.
They will be hunted down and killed.
Anyone who does not exist
to serve the gods is their enemy.
And that makes you...
I am a Jaffa.
Bred to serve, that they may live.
I don't understand.
Man!
What the hell is that?
It is an infant Goa'uld,
the larval form of the gods.
I have carried one since I was a child,
as all Jaffa carry one.
This is the twelfth I have carried.
Well, get it out of there!
In exchange for carrying
the infant Goa'uld until maturity,
a Jaffa receives perfect health
and long life.
If I were to remove it,
I would eventually die.
Well, if I were you, I'd take my chances.
Why did you do this?
The Goa'uld are conquerors, nothing more.
Not worthy of worship or sacrifice.
You are the first to come along
with powers that approach theirs.
Powers?
You are strong,
perhaps strong enough to destroy them.
All right, people! Let's go! Let's move!
The boy you seek is no longer who he was.
I don't wanna hear that.
Take cover! Take cover!
Colonel, we're sitting ducks here!
Hold on.
Now, fire!
- Kawalsky?
- Kawalsky.
Yeah!
- Come on, folks!
- Come on, people!
Up the hill!
Great shot.
- How many are there?
- A dozen, maybe more.
They're going back through the gate.
What about Skaara?
He's with them.
Warren! Casey! On my right!
- No.
- Wait, sir.
Skaara!
Skaara.
- Did you see the symbols?
- No.
Sir, we got hostiles
coming out of the trees!
Okay, people,
we're going on a little fieldtrip!
Daniel, get busy on that stargate.
We got company.
Captain, arm your Claymores.
Me and Casey and Warren'll be
the last men out.
Negative. That's my job.
Captain, help Daniel.
Once you've sent the signal,
I want you to go through.
Tell 'em we're bringing company.
Let's go, move, move, move! Let's go!
We can't hold 'em, sir!
Pull 'em out!
Fall back, fall back. Now.
- Daniel.
- It's here.
Go! Go!
Come on!
Send the signal
as soon as it opens, Captain.
- Check the coordinates.
- Looking at 'em now.
- No signal yet, General.
- Stand by.
Wait! There it is.
- Is it working?
- Let's hope so.
Hit the Claymores!
Captain, let's get these people
out of here now! Move!
Give me a few seconds,
then start sending them through.
Stand fast!
Hold your fire! They're refugees!
I hope you know
what you're doing, Captain.
Go, go, go! Please!
Go, go, go. Stop, stop, stop.
Now, okay. Come on! Come on!
Nice!
That's it!
Go!
Casey, Warren, fall back!
- They behind you?
- I hope so.
Go! Go!
Casey!
Man down!
Move! Come on, move your ass!
- Hold your fire! Hold your fire!
They're with us!
Now! Lock it up! Lock it up!
Got it. I got it. He's not breathing.
Let's go. Get him breathing.
Sir?
Colonel O'Neill, care to explain?
We can use the stargate
to send these people home, sir.
What's he doing here?
General Hammond, this is Teal'c.
He can help us.
Do you know what he is?
Yes sir, I do.
He's the man who saved our lives.
And if you accept my recommendation, sir,
he'll join SG-1.
That decision may not be up to you.
Let's go, man down. Stand back!
Stand back!
All right, troop, get him off the ramp!
Let's get him off the ramp.
Colonel O'Neill, Major Kawalsky.
The sure-to-be-very-interesting debriefing
of SG units 1 and 2 will be at 0730.
- Yes, sir.
All right, let's get these people situated.
This way.
She's out there somewhere, Jack.
I know. So's Skaara.
So what do we do?
We find 'em.