My father used to say, "Life is a road,
"and every day is a mile marker.
"If you don't slow down occasionally,
you'll miss what each mile has to offer."
But there's also a flip side to that.
Sometimes you can take a wrong turn
and find yourself on the most God-awful
stretch of road imaginable,
spinning your wheels,
praying it's not a dead end.
How you doing back there, Joshua?
I'm in too much pain to be dead.
- How you hanging in there, boss?
- I'm all right.
I've lost more blood from a bad shave.
Damn. I think one of my lungs
just collapsed.
That's all right. You only need one.
My old man lost a lung to Joe Camel
when he was 53 years old,
and he lived to be 67.
Still running a pack a day
through the other lung.
Of course, out of spite,
he switched to Marlboro.
I'm dying, Vincent.
Hey! That is bullshit. I don't let you die.
I told you I was leaving.
All right, you gotta stay with me.
We're half an hour
from the doc's house.
I'll have us there in 20 minutes.
Love, honor, power,
fear of death,
people live for all kinds of reasons.
Some are more noble than others.
When all you have to live for is revenge,
it can really bone your quality of life.
Come on in, Donnie.
I don't see
why we have to talk in the garage
when I've got a perfectly nice house.
Why don't I...
Get in there!
Donnie. Stop being such a pussy, huh?
- Hey, Mickey.
- What?
Try to maintain
some level of professionalism.
- What are you talking about?
- The pushing, the name-calling,
- it's not necessary.
- Hey, I'm sorry, Donnie.
See, I thought that we work
for this big crime boss
and we're here
to collect some money for him,
but obviously
we're a couple of Avon ladies.
See, that's what I'm talking about.
Not everything's black and white.
- I mean, Donnie here's a good guy.
- Get over there.
But this isn't a social call, is it, Donnie?
This is business.
This is nothing personal.
We're here to collect the money
or impose a penalty.
There's no need to add insult to injury,
now, is there?
No.
Joshua, what kind of injury
are we talking about?
So you don't have Vincent's money.
- Well, not all of it.
- Well, how much do you have?
None of it.
Donnie.
You put me in a very bad place.
Please, have a seat.
- You don't have to do this.
- It's for your own safety.
- What?
- Hold him.
No!
Come on, Joshua.
Can't you tell Vincent I wasn't home?
Tell him I'm out of town on business
or something.
You want me to lie to Vincent?
Betray his trust because
you can't stay away from the ponies?
I can have the dough next week!
Vincent's been more than patient
with you.
- Now he wants his pound of flesh.
- Hey! Maybe we take his thumbs off.
No, nothing permanent.
What are you talking about?
They can reattach them these days.
Hey, I think I found something.
How about we give him
a little snip-snip Bobbitt?
Yeah, then there'd be two loose pricks
in the room.
- That's funny?
- A little bit.
I've got a joke for you,
and it starts like this.
That's enough, Mickey.
Grab that stool and prop his legs up.
- What?
- Take his shoes off.
- Get your fucking feet up.
- The socks, too.
Get your feet up here, you fuck.
- Why? Don't! Why?
- Shut the fuck up!
- Grab his legs.
- What? Why?
Joshua. Please.
No! Please! Joshua, please, no!
Don't you find it ironic, Mickey,
that the black culture has become
so influential in this country
that even the Italians
are trying to identify with it?
What the fuck are you talking about?
If your grandfather knew
that you had a lifetime membership
to the tanning salon...
Tanning salon?
You're out of your fucking mind.
This is natural. This is my natural color.
Orange.
That's your natural color, orange?
Orange? Do I look orange to you?
This is olive.
- Which one? The green or the black?
- The green and the black.
- Who is it?
- It's Joshua.
- Password, please.
- You're a douche! That's the password.
Hey, why the fuck do you...
Come on! Who is it?
- Jeff, it's me, Joshua.
- Bullshit. Joshua knows the password.
Majestic 12, Jeff.
"Majestic 12, Majestic 12."
What a fucking snatch.
What the fuck is Majestic 12?
It's a secret committee
formed in the '40s to investigate UFOs.
- You believe that shit?
- There are two kinds of truths, Mickey.
There's the obvious truth.
The sky is blue.
The grass is green. You're a dick.
And then there's the intangible.
The kind that requires one's faith
to be true.
Can't be conclusively proven or refuted.
This is the truth of religion
and conspiracy theories.
My faith in God mandates
that I stay open-minded to all truths.
Otherwise I risk becoming a hypocrite,
and that ain't cool.
Hey. Come in.
- How you doing, buddy?
- Okay.
- Wow. New wallpaper?
- It's aluminum foil.
It's nice. I gotta get the number
of your interior decorator.
Can I get you guys something to drink?
I have triple-filtered water, no fluoride.
Triple-filtered water, huh? Nah.
What was it about Vincent
you wanted to tell me?
You've heard of Frankie Tahoe, right?
- Why don't you tell me about him?
- Hey, Jeff.
Did you really get abducted by aliens?
- Yeah, I was.
- Wow. That's fucking crazy.
Can you put those down, please?
- These?
- Please.
- Mickey, put them down.
- Okay.
Thank you.
Okay, Frankie Tahoe
is this Puerto Rican small-time punk.
Drug dealer, right?
And he knows
I'm good friends with Vincent.
All of a sudden
he starts asking me all kinds of shit.
"Where does he live?
How many guys he got?" Okay?
But I didn't...
I didn't... I didn't tell him nothing.
I swear to God.
Look what he did to me.
Stop messing with this stuff.
This is cute.
See, now, I'm ignorant
on the whole abduction thing,
you know what I'm saying?
So, is it true that when they bring you up
in their spaceship, that they roll around
your fucking prostate and your anal?
- They get in there?
- Yeah, that's part of the exam.
Why the fuck would they put it
in your ass? I don't understand.
There's things they want to find out
about us human beings, you know.
- Through your ass?
- Yeah. Body temperature, you know?
Parasites.
I know, I know.
But I'm gonna be there this time.
I will.
Okay. Okay.
You know what I think?
I think that all the aliens
must be fucking gay
and they just want to shove it right
in your corn, you know what I mean?
They just want to come down here
and abuse humans
and fucking give it to you
right in your ass. Is that true?
Do you refuse to believe 'cause
you believe this to be impossible?
Or maybe it's just impossible
for your limited wit to comprehend.
Excuse me.
You know, that's a good point.
You know, my limited wit might...
Might stop me from believing that aliens
don't fuck you in your fucking ass!
- Now listen to me. Listen to me!
- Get off of me.
- Look at me, look at me!
- Joshua!
- Get off my...
- Fuck!
Put your fucking arms down.
Put your fucking arms down, now!
- Okay, okay. They're down.
- Okay, thank you.
- Thank you.
- Why didn't you go to Vincent directly?
- Why come to me?
- 'Cause you know how he would get
if he saw what they did to me.
You're his main guy, right?
Do what you gotta do
to this lying piece of shit.
Wait! Wait. Okay. Wait. Stop! Joshua!
- Hey, what the fuck?
- Stop, stop. Okay, okay, okay, okay.
- Okay, see?
- Okay, okay.
Joshua, all I was trying to do
is make a few bucks
selling his stuff, and he starts
talking to me about all this shit!
Just don't tell Vincent, please.
He'll be so fucking mad at me.
I am telling you the truth now.
I swear to God.
- You better be, you fucking junkie.
- Fuck!
- Vincent.
- Come on in.
Sorry to wake you.
I thought it might be important.
Actually, I wasn't sleeping.
I was fucking,
and if you think it's important
then it probably is.
Joshua, I want to thank you
for having the good sense and courtesy
to remove your shoes, so as not
to track in the filth of the outside world.
Take your shoes off, Mickey.
Shit, I'm sorry.
The good news is,
I didn't track anything in.
Can you detect things that exist
on a microscopic level?
In the future,
when you come to my home,
I want you to take off your shoes.
I don't want to tell you again,
'cause if I do,
you won't need shoes anyway,
'cause I'll cut off your fucking feet.
- Got it, Vince.
- Vincent.
Say my whole name
or don't say it at all, please.
Yes, sir, Vincent.
Let's sit down, shall we?
Well?
Apparently, a cat by the name
of Frankie Tahoe wants you dead.
That's not exactly what you want to hear
at 1:00 in the morning.
Is there any time of day
you want to hear that shit?
Who the fuck is Frankie Tahoe,
and where'd you hear this?
He's a Puerto Rican drug dealer.
Jeff told me.
Why didn't Jeff call me himself?
- Vincent?
- Yeah, baby.
- Did you offer the boys any coffee?
- No.
- Why not?
- 'Cause they don't want any.
Well, how do you know that
if you didn't offer?
Because when they're working for me
I make decisions for them,
and I've decided
they don't want any fucking coffee.
Jesus Christ, you are the worst host.
- Would you please watch your mouth?
- Look who's talking.
Do not take the name of my savior
in vain.
You know, you wouldn't even offer him
a cup of coffee.
He doesn't drink coffee.
Would you please do me a favor
and go back to bed?
I'll be up in a minute.
Go back to bed.
Like what you're seeing, Mick?
What?
Come on. There's a...
I mean, she's beautiful, but...
- I would never do that.
- Go wait outside.
- It's fucking freezing outside.
- Get the fuck out of here.
So, Jeff's been selling this dude's dope
on the side.
Okay, that's why he didn't call me.
What do you make of it?
It's not the first drug dealer
that wanted you dead.
- Yeah.
- But I don't know that I trust Jeff.
He's from my old neighborhood.
I trust him.
- Guy thinks he was abducted by aliens...
- I know, I know.
All right, here's what I want you to do.
Find out exactly
where this guy is right now.
I'm gonna go get dressed.
Hey, Vincent? There is one other thing.
What is it? What's the problem?
You need money? What is it?
- No, no. It's not that.
- Where do you think you're going?
I'm going to Disneyland.
It's 3:00 in the morning.
Isn't that when everybody
goes to Disneyland?
- Give me a fucking break.
- What a smartass.
And you know what?
I don't like you talking to me like that.
All right, all right, all right.
We'll talk about it later.
Hey.
- Jeffrey, how's things?
- They're fine. They're great, Vincent.
- So, how's Katie?
- What?
- Katie? How is she?
- She's good, yeah.
She's starting high school soon.
We're gonna take care of her,
you know that, right?
- You get enough visitation?
- Yeah, yeah, yeah.
So, Jeff, tell me about this Puerto Rican.
Frankie. Yeah, Frankie Tahoe.
You in trouble with this guy
or something?
Why?
Look at me.
I need to be 100% sure that what
you're telling me is on the level.
Yeah, Vincent. I wouldn't lie to you.
You know that.
- He do this to your face?
- Yeah.
- I wouldn't tell him nothing.
- Okay.
No, Vincent. No.
You don't have to sell dope
for these scumbags.
You need money, you come to me.
I know. I know.
Thanks, Vincent. Sorry, Vincent.
Jeffrey.
This is fucking unbelievable.
This fucking guy.
Fucking respects him
more than he respects me.
- This guy's a fucking lowlife junkie.
- He's got history with this cat.
- Come here!
- Fuck!
Shit.
- Where's your piece?
- Easy.
It's cute.
My grandmother's got one just like it.
- You know who I am?
- Yeah.
- You know why I'm here?
- No.
Interesting.
How long have you worked
for Mr. Tahoe?
A few months.
Now, here's the most
important question.
In that time,
do you think you've developed
a relationship worth dying for?
No. Fuck that.
Good answer.
- Give me your driver's license.
- What?
Fuck.
Easy, big boy. Easy.
Looks like
you've lost some weight, Gregory.
Yeah, I've been cutting back
on the carbs.
What the fuck, man?
- Put your hands behind your back, B.
- For your own safety.
- Okay, well, in that case, all right.
- Yeah, good.
Yeah, I'll play with you guys
for a little while.
- Turn that music down.
- Yes, sir.
Okay, we can talk.
I got a couple questions for you.
That's good, man.
'Cause I got a couple questions for you
my damn self,
you know what I'm saying? First one is,
which one of these two little bitches
right here
gonna give me a lap dance?
Joshua, you wanna give him
a lap dance?
Trip, man. Got chocolate over here.
- How was that?
- Shit.
Fuck. That's not really
what I had in mind, but...
Okay. Okay.
Listen, before we begin,
I want to give you some advice.
When you're dealing with me,
there are two things
that will always save your ass.
Honesty and respect.
Now, those are your cigarettes.
You mind if I have one?
Yeah, yeah, go ahead, man.
Help yourself, man.
Why don't we all have one,
you know what I'm saying?
Got a light?
You're a good little bitch, huh?
Lighting him up like that.
You know,
I can't smoke in my own home.
My wife won't let me.
She's 110 pounds soaking wet,
but she's got the heart of a drill sergeant
and the mouth of a sailor.
But, fuck, I married her, right?
Do what you do, man,
you know what I'm saying?
I married her, so I have to answer to her.
Everybody's gotta answer to somebody.
I answer to my wife. I answer to God.
Who do you answer to, Franklin?
Well, first of all,
I don't answer to Franklin.
You know what I'm saying?
I didn't like it much
when my mother called me that,
and it sure as hell don't sound
any sweeter coming from your ass.
- Fair enough.
- And the whole married thing,
too much pussy out there in the world,
man, to be married, right, right?
You feel me? And God,
he went right out
the motherfucking door, homie,
once I was old enough
to think for my damn self.
Now, that says a lot about you.
- Is that right?
- Yeah, it does.
You have a problem with authority.
By being an atheist,
you reject the existence
of the ultimate authority.
What the fuck is this? Inquisition?
Now let me tell you something, man,
this is the 20th century, homeboy,
you know that, right?
I stopped believing in fairytales, man,
a long time ago.
God, Santa Claus, all that shit
went out the motherfucking door, man.
Hey, come on, come on, come on, man!
Is this really what you ladies
came down here for?
Is this what you girls
Ask some stupid-ass questions?
I get it, I get it, I get it.
You guys want me to make a donation
to the church, right?
You really think you can kill me,
you piece of shit?
What the fuck you talking about, man?
You slap my people around.
You disrespect my lord and savior.
Hey, hey, my man, is this guy serious?
Hey! Talking to you!
What's this guy talking about, man?
Hey, look, hold on, hold on, let me just...
Let me just think about this
for a quick second, all right?
What the fuck are you talking about,
man? Your people?
What are you... Fuck! God damn...
I've had enough
of your Puerto Rican ass!
That shows how fucking stupid you are,
white boy!
I'm a motherfucking Mexican!
What the fuck is this place?
Who the fuck is that? Is he the cargo?
No, cargo's dead in the trunk.
He's with me.
- Just one?
- Yep.
All right, go straight, to the left.
Fuck this guy, huh?
Fuck. This guy's fucking heavy.
- Straight back. Yeah.
- Right here?
I swear to God, I think he's breathing!
No, I think I'm bugging out.
That was fucking scary.
Fucking goombah zombies,
'cause I hate that shit.
What the... What the fuck?
I'm sorry, Mick.
This thing's got a hair-trigger.
Tell you what,
use these to stop the bleeding.
Some panties.
You should recognize those.
You've been in them enough.
- What the fuck are you talking about?
- This asshole's fucking my wife.
Come on, Vincent.
Do you think I'm stupid?
I think you're stupid enough
to lie to me about it
- when you know I know you're lying.
- I'm not lying to you. Joshua, please.
Tell him I'm not lying to him.
I had her followed.
They saw him coming out of my house.
What the fuck were you doing
in my house?
- I wasn't in your house. I swear to God.
- Hope she rocked your world, Mick.
You got me confused with somebody
else, Vincent, I swear to God.
Joshua, please. We've been together
the whole time I've been on this crew.
Please tell him I'm not lying.
I swear to God, on my mother's life,
- I swear to God, Vincent.
- Shut up, Mickey.
Vincent?
Vincent! I swear to God,
on my mother's life,
I never fucked your wife! I swear to God.
All right, Mickey. I just had to be sure.
You scared the shit out of me.
Thank you, doll.
That's unbelievable.
That looks even worse than it sounded.
It's good for you. You should try it.
You're supposed to enjoy what you eat.
That shit's got no flavor.
It's utility food.
Excuse me, more decaf, please.
Thank you.
You see, that's what I'm talking about.
Decaf. What's the point?
It's like drinking non-alcoholic beer,
getting knobbed from some fat chick,
it's pointless.
You ever had your dick sucked
by a fat chick, Vincent?
No.
Don't knock it till you tried it.
Not only are they extremely
appreciative lovers,
but they're incredibly talented
when it comes to oral gratification.
- No shit.
- I shit you not, my friend.
You see, I would... I would
be worried the bitch would get hungry
and just start gnawing on the bone,
you know?
I'm leaving, Vincent.
What, are you going on a vacation
or something?
- More like retirement.
- Retirement.
You're gonna retire before me?
With what?
- With who?
- With no one.
Are you starting your own crew?
How long have you been planning this?
- This isn't me anymore.
- All right, listen.
If this is about Mickey,
the guy was fucking my wife, okay?
What am I supposed to do?
What would you do?
- It's not just him.
- Well, then what?
- What about the drug dealer?
- What about him?
Or the way we came down
on that sweatshop three weeks ago.
What about it?
Or that mark you pulled out of the car
on the freeway.
What are you saying to me?
I lose it sometimes. What do you want,
an apology? What the fuck do you want?
You all right, Vincent?
No, I'm not all right, Vincent.
Fuck you.
You owe me.
You owe me your life,
and you're out when I say you're out.
I am sick of this shit, Joshua.
- When is it going to end?
- He killed Mickey tonight.
- Oh, Jesus Christ.
- Thought you were sleeping with him.
Were you?
Fuck you, Joshua.
Wow, really?
Eight points, huh?
That's great, buddy.
And you packed already?
Okay. Me, too.
Vincent. Baby,
I don't want you to go outside.
- I don't want you to go out there.
- What?
Why don't you call Joshua?
Wait for Joshua.
Joshua's down the road, okay?
Joshua's not here anymore.
Joshua's gone.
I'm not gonna call Joshua.
- Listen to me. I'm fine.
- I know.
I'm gonna talk to these guys,
and I'm gonna come right back.
All right?
This coffee sucks. Shit!
- What the hell? What the hell was that?
- Christ almighty!
- You okay?
- Yeah, I'm fine.
Like I fucking need this...
Hey, Paulie,
there's no one in the fucking car here.
- What?
- There's nobody in the car.
- What are you talking about?
- You all right, fellas?
Yeah, we're fine, pal.
We got it under control. Thank you.
'Cause, you know, I saw the whole thing.
It was clearly the other car's fault.
Hey, pal, I think I already told you,
we have everything under control.
- You got that, right?
- Stephen.
- No, please, Paulie.
- No, no, no, Stephen.
You, please, shut the fuck up.
- What's the matter?
- This is our guy.
This guy? How do you know?
He has what appears to be
a very large weapon sticking in my ribs.
Okay. Okay.
Come on.
You know the deal.
We're just the messengers here.
Okay, my doorbell works.
And if it doesn't,
there's a big-ass knocker on the door.
When were you two
gonna deliver the message?
Quite honestly, when our boss called.
How's that for timing?
Hello?
Paulie's busy right now.
Can I take a message?
Yeah, that's me.
No, they were quite obvious.
Okay.
All right, I'll see you soon.
He wants you to take me to the house.
Let's go.
- Vincent?
- No.
Don't worry about it.
Go enjoy your retirement.
- Let's go, boys.
- Get in the car, Vincent.
This is Nino Bollino's house.
And how do you know that?
- Trust me, I know.
- Interesting.
Come on.
I used to work for his father
back in the day.
He wants to have a little talk.
Welcome to the top of the food chain,
gentlemen.
By the way,
naturally we'll have to pat you down.
Well, you can certainly try.
That's right. Let's have a look at that
gun you stuck in the back of my head.
- Fuck!
- You ever seen a compound fracture?
'Cause if you wanna continue
this little pissing contest,
I could have Joshua
rip this fucker's arm off
- and beat him with it.
- Hey. Just trying to do my job.
I understand,
but we didn't crash this party.
We were invited.
So, if your boss doesn't want us
to exercise
our Second Amendment rights,
we'll just be on our way. Joshua?
Hey, please. Please. Yes, sir, Mr. Nino.
- I was this close to having you.
- Yes, I felt it.
Yes, sir. Right away, sir.
Mr. Nino will see you right now.
Jupiter once commanded all the birds
of the Earth to appear before him,
so that he might choose
the most beautiful to be their king.
The ugly black crow
collected all the colorful feathers
which had fallen from the other birds,
attached them to his own body
and appeared looking very beautiful.
But the other birds
recognized their own plumage
and began to strip him.
"Stop what you're doing," said Jupiter.
"This self-made bird
has more sense than any of you.
"He shall be your king."
- Can I get either of you a drink?
- No, thanks.
Prendi un prosecco.
Have a seat.
- There are plenty of chairs.
- Thank you, but he prefers to stand.
You're a real guard dog, ain't you?
You found yourself a pit-bull.
- More loyal and can be twice as vicious.
- I like that.
Could probably teach some of my guys
a few things.
Quality over quantity.
In some things.
- You know, we've met before.
- Really?
I don't think so.
I'd remember a guy like you.
Well, this was a long time ago,
before I became a guy like me.
Your father was Benny Bollino, right?
I worked a paper route for him
when I was a kid.
- Paper route?
- Yeah, that's what he used to call it.
I ran bribes, picked up extortion money.
Shit like that.
I'll bet it paid better
than peddling The Sunday Times.
Yeah, yeah.
Your father was quite a guy, you know?
Loved by his friends,
respected by his enemies.
To accomplish everything he did
and still cross the finish line
due to natural causes, it's amazing.
You think so?
My father was a doddering old bag
of bones the last six years of his life.
When he wasn't pissing his pants,
he was wandering around his house
trying to figure out who
and where the fuck he was.
I kept him propped up on a throne,
but I was the one running things.
You know what I'm saying, Joshua?
And as for crossing the finish line
of natural causes,
at least with a bullet
he could have checked out
with some fucking dignity.
I'm sorry you feel that way.
- God rest his soul, I loved him.
- I'll bet you did.
So, tell me,
why'd you kill Frankie Tahoe?
- Who?
- Frankie Tahoe.
Drug dealer. Scumbag. About yea tall.
You accosted his bodyguard
outside of one of my clubs last night.
Sent the little pussy home
with his tail between his legs.
All we found of Frankie this morning
was a puddle of blood
and a couple of teeth.
And what makes you think
that I had anything to do with it?
I know you had everything to do with it.
Bodyguard knew your name,
and that stripper knows your face.
And yours.
She was staying late to give Frankie
his own private show last night.
She had slipped away to grab a rubber
when you and your boys
interrupted the festivities.
Bitch-ass motherfucker! Fuck you!
She saw the whole thing.
That was quite
the Perry Mason moment, Counselor.
- It was, wasn't it?
- Yeah, let's see.
I'm ID'ed by a dead chicken-shit
bodyguard and a strung-out stripper.
- Yeah.
- What are you gonna do for an encore?
Pull the murder weapon out of her ass?
Well, as entertaining as that might be,
I don't think it's necessary.
The verdict is already in.
What do you want to do?
You owe me for the life of my employee.
Well, since drug dealers are pretty
much a dime a dozen in this town,
you got change for a penny?
Frankie Tahoe may have been worthless
in the eyes of God and society,
but he was an exceptional drug dealer.
You all right?
You're looking a little pale.
Richie, un bicchiere d'acqua.
You gotta be careful.
The stress will kill you.
I know how you feel.
I don't want any water.
- You all right?
- I'm fine.
Looked like you were having
a heart attack.
You scared me for a second there.
Okay, so, the way I figure,
your little batting practice
cost me at least 100 grand a year.
Profit.
Maybe you can write if off on your taxes.
All right, smartass.
The only reason you and your boy Friday
aren't lying inside
a couple of chalk outlines right now
is because I'm a little curious.
If your actions were justified,
maybe we could work something out.
So, what did Frankie do?
Kill your mother? Fuck your father?
I have it on a good source
that he was out to kill me.
I'd check that source if I were you.
Frankie didn't wipe his ass
without getting the go-ahead from me.
If he was planning on killing anyone,
I would have known about it,
'cause I would've had to okay it.
The way I see it,
there are several options to consider.
Option A, you pay off the debt.
We'll say,
100 grand for the next five years.
Option B, you work off the debt.
I could always use
a couple of good leg breakers.
Then, of course,
there's the unpleasant option C.
That would be
the aforementioned chalk outline?
If there's enough of you left to chalk.
You know, there is an option D.
Might be a long shot, but it does exist.
Are you fucking serious?
You can't be serious.
You're a little fish.
Splash, splash, splash.
I'm a shark.
Bank account, body count,
I got you beat on all counts.
I am the ever-present threat
lurking just out of sight.
By the time you realize I'm there,
it'll be too late.
I will drag you down.
- Like that bitch at the beginning of Jaws.
- Okay.
Nino, let me explain something to you.
I ain't no bitch.
I'm Roy Scheider.
We all know what happened to Jaws
when he messed with Roy Scheider.
- The shark got blowed up.
- He got blowed the fuck up.
You listen to me.
I don't give a fuck who you are,
what you have or who you fucking killed!
Fuck this shit.
Vincent?
Honey?
So you wanna tell me
how Bollino knew your name?
- What?
- You think I'm fucking stupid?
I asked you a question.
Do you think I'm stupid?
- Son of a bitch!
- What's the matter?
That's the guy I saw outside
of the bodyguard's apartment building.
- You sure?
- Yeah, I'm positive.
Marisa? Fuck. It's going to voicemail.
Motherfucker! Go, go!
Marisa!
Just give me a minute, will you?
Give me a minute.
Listen, I need you to take Julian
over to your mother's.
No, no. Nothing's gonna happen.
Just do it, okay? Please?
Nice wallpaper, Jeff. Really works.
Charlie, now,
what did you have to do that for?
Our employer would like to have
a little talk with you,
ask you some questions.
Think of it as a little chit-chat,
a tête-à-tête, as it were.
Should you try to hinder us
from transporting you to said employer,
we have been instructed
to shoot you on the spot.
So, for now, just relax.
Breathe.
Think happy thoughts.
Easy. Hey, easy with him, huh?
Now, if you stay calm,
cool and cooperative,
you may even live to see tomorrow.
Come on, hurry up. Move.
Jesus Christ!
Hey, man. You know it.
You know, I'm only doing my job.
You know what'll happen to you
if you kill me, right?
Your boss set the pace.
I'm just trying to keep up.
That was for blasphemy.
What are we doing here, Vincent?
What's going on?
Don't worry about it.
That backpack looks heavy.
Joshua, take Jeff's backpack for him,
would you, please?
- It's not that heavy.
- Let go of the bag, Jeff.
Let's all sit down.
Let's see if we can answer
each other's questions.
You go first.
Why are we here?
'Cause it's a safe place to talk.
Joshua, you're up.
- Vincent?
- How much did you owe Frankie Tahoe?
No.
Jeff.
- Back on the shit, Jeff?
- Nope.
No, Vincent, I was... Oh, God.
All right, let me guess.
Frankie Tahoe gave you a line of credit,
and you got in over your head.
Am I right?
Yeah.
I imagine Frankie was the kind of guy
that didn't mind pushing pretty hard
when it came to collecting a debt.
Probably looked forward
to bills coming due.
Katie.
And I imagine
he considered working people over
to be one of the perks
of being a drug dealer.
What up, Jeff?
You know, little Katie
really starting to blossom, right?
There is nothing sweeter
than some untapped pussy.
I like that little bald shit,
you know what I'm saying?
Fresh, right out of the oven.
That's some grade-A cherry shit, man.
You wanna take a little sniff?
Are you kidding me right now?
I can't believe you just did that, dawg.
We're practically family, homeboy.
I just fucked your daughter.
You're a dead man.
- What? Come again?
- I'm gonna fucking kill you.
You got no right to be pissed off
at anyone but your damned self, man.
You owe me a lot of money, homie.
I'm gonna tell you right now, dawg,
the way I see it,
you're fucking lucky
Katie was in town visiting, man,
'cause she just bought you some time
and saved you some broken bones,
homie.
I'd rather you broke
every bone in my body.
I would rather you killed me.
No, Jeff, you don't get it, man.
You see this here?
This is a lot more fun, homeboy.
Lot more fun.
How much did you owe him?
3 grand.
You lied to me over 3 grand?
You fucking serious?
You manipulated and you betrayed me
for $3,000?
You could have come to me.
You could have told me the truth.
I would have taken care of it.
You could have come to me.
I know.
It wasn't about money, Vincent.
It wasn't about money.
All right.
How long's it been since your last taste?
Last night.
You want Joshua to cook you up a hit?
Yeah.
Did you ever hear the story
of the scorpion and the frog, Jeff?
There's this scorpion.
He's sitting on a rock in the middle
of the river and the water's rising,
and he knows he's gonna drown.
And he sees this frog swim by
and he says,
"Hey, man, give me... Give me a lift
to the other side of the river."
Frog says,
"You kidding me? You're a scorpion.
"You're gonna sting me."
Scorpion says, "No, I just want a ride.
"I'm not going to sting you, I promise."
So the frog says "Okay,"
and they start off across the river.
Sure enough, the frog looks back,
the scorpion's bitten him
right in the ass.
Frog says, "What did you do that for?
Now we're both gonna die."
Scorpion says, "I know.
"I'm sorry, but it's in my nature."
Hey, soup's on, huh?
You're gonna hurt yourself.
Give me the needle.
Hold still.
- Makes all the difference, huh?
- Yeah.
It's the only thing
that stops the nightmares.
You still get the nightmares, Vincent?
Can't dream if you don't sleep.
- I'm sorry I lied to you, Vincent.
- Yeah, me too.
But it's not about the lie anymore.
It's about the avalanche of shit
that's come down on me
because of that lie.
What do you mean?
Frankie Tahoe
wasn't a private vendor, Jeff.
He was employee of the month
for the Donald Trump of the underworld.
We pissed off the biggest junkyard dog
on the East Coast.
He's been shitting in our backyard
all day.
- Is that who sent those guys for me?
- Yeah.
Thank God you showed up
when you did.
The poor bastards
didn't know what hit them.
It was just like when we were teenagers
and you dry-gulched
those fucking Grays, remember?
Yeah, I do.
Remember what I used to say about you
after that?
You put the "Vince" in invincible.
I don't... I don't know who this big dog is,
- but my money's still on you, hoss.
- They killed Marisa.
No. No.
Yeah, they killed her.
They tied her up,
and they butchered her like an animal
because of your lie and my actions.
Oh, God, Vincent. Oh, God, no,
Vincent, please. No. Please.
Jeffrey. Jeffrey.
You don't have to explain anything.
You're like a brother to me.
- There's a reason, Vincent.
- I know.
There's a reason.
Vincent, you gotta let me explain.
Please, Vincent.
- I know.
- Oh, God.
Oh, shit, it's the guy's kid.
Close your eyes, motherfucker.
This is 50 grand.
It's called severance pay.
It's time for you
to get the hell out of Dodge.
What are you talking about?
I'm coming with you.
No.
This morning I owe you my life, and
I can't be trusted. Now I'm in your will?
I ain't dead yet. Just take the money.
Yeah, but here's the problem.
Nino's not gonna be happy
until he kills us both
and everybody we care about.
I can't let that happen.
I'm coming with you.
That's not everything.
- Get in the car.
- Damn right I'm getting in the car.
- You fully loaded?
- Yeah.
Work your way around the pool
and find a way in.
- I'll see you inside.
- How are you going in?
Front door.
Twenty-four, and I got 19.
I gotta go to work.
- You need anything?
- I already got what I needed.
Three times.
That was amazing, wasn't it?
- They got Doc Holliday with them.
- Holliday, huh?
Cotton, you get over with the horses.
Ike, I can't take this kind
of gunplay anymore. Cut me out.
Get over there.
Hey, Richie, Nino's looking for you,
and he's pissed.
I think he's looking for Paulie.
Paulie? Paulie Looch?
- That's not a word.
- Of course it's a word. It's foreshadow.
- Ignorant motherfucker.
- What the fuck is a foreshadow?
- Foreshadow!
- "Verb.
"To show or indicate beforehand.
Prefigure."
- There you go.
- Yeah, you know,
it's like a sign
that something's gonna happen.
Hey! Any of you jerkoffs
seen Paulie around?
No.
Fucking pansy.
- Hello.
- Hey, Paulie, Richie.
- Where the hell have you been?
- Who's Paulie?
- What?
- Who is this?
- Detective Miller, Homicide. Who's this?
What happened to Paulie?
Somebody shot him.
Was he a friend of yours?
Hey, Paulie! Where you been?
Nino's looking all over for you.
Hey!
Paulie's dead.
Seven of them are with Cotton.
I only see six.
- Mr. Nino!
- In the kitchen.
We got a problem.
The police answered Paulie's phone.
Somebody shot him.
Hey, Vincent, is that you?
I was just making myself
a protein shake. You want one?
- I'll have yours!
- Okay.
A salute, motherfucker!
Hey, Mr. Nino, what's going on?
It's an old-fashioned
mobsters ball, Larry.
- You ready to dance with the devil?
- What?
Just watch the fucking stairs.
Jesus...
I'm gonna go upstairs
and get that son of a bitch.
I'll take care of things down here.
Nino? Nino? Should I call the polizia?
Baby, this is no time to make jokes.
Go hide.
Fuck!
Come on, you cocksucker!
I'm gonna go grab another beer.
You want one?
- You got it, Johnny.
- Cotton,
you chicken-livered, miserable...
Well, I'm a little surprised.
I was unaware that Nino went
and hired us a house nigger.
That's impressive.
You want to see impressive?
Let's do this old-school.
- Are you wearing a vest, Nino?
- Yeah!
Ain't you?
Fuck, that hurts.
I know I nailed you with the shotgun.
How bad is it?
I've had worse.
Well, we ain't done yet, Vinnie!
Motherfucker.
Change for a penny.
That's too bad.
He was gonna get me a beer.
Is this the piece of shit
that killed Marisa?
Yeah, that's him.
Sometimes you can take a wrong turn
and find yourself on the most
God-awful stretch of road imaginable,
spinning your wheels,
praying it's not a dead end.
- Tell me about my father.
- What?
My father, Vincent.
Your father was a junkie.
He never did anything for you.
I saved you from that. I raised you.
You owe me.
How many times
do you want me to tell you?
He was a dope dealer.
He owed a lot of money
to a lot of people.
You owe me the truth.
You know the truth.
He was dead before I got there.
Love, honor, power,
fear of death,
people live for all kinds of reasons.
Some are more noble than others.
When all you have to live for is revenge,
it can really bone your quality of life.
You think you can kill me because of it?
Well, you can't. You're too loyal.
It's in my nature.
Subtitles by LeapinLar