Welcome back, everybody,
to the 1997 World Series of Poker,
where Stu "The Kid" Ungar
is attempting to make one of
the greatest comebacks in poker history
by winning the no-limit
Texas Hold-em Championship
a record third time.
And Al,
the amazing thing about this
is that Stuey would be
achieving that feat
after 16 years
of personal struggle
where victories were really
few and far between.
And standing
between Stuey and history
is John Stremp,
a local casino executive
who's shown remarkable fortitude,
actually, in making it to this point.
And here it is--Stu is raising enough
to put Stremp all in.
This could be it, Al. If Stremp wins,
it'll change the tide of the tournament.
If Stuey wins, he's got the championship
again after 16 long years.
You're not sure?
I thought you're supposed to be
some freaking genius or something.
Yeah? Well, fuck you, then.
Come on, Stuey.
You could do better than that.
Do better than what?
I wake up,
you're in my goddamn hotel room
wanting to know
if I seen you before.
What kind
of fucked-up game is that?
I thought you liked games.
Cards, horses, football...
I heard you play golf, even.
You got a good swing, Stuey?
So that's what this is about?
What do you think it's about?
Oh, man. Look...
stop screwing with me.
You do what you gotta do.
You in a hurry?
Got a hot date?
What are the odds, Stuey?
You're good with that stuff, right?
Maybe you can get to that blade before
I even figured out what you were up to.
You know...
cut and run.
Me? I'd say I'm a 20-1 favorite
to slice your fucking heart out
before you're off the bed.
That about right?
Hey, I know people, man.
I know important people.
Don't get all lathered up, Stuey.
You wanna know
what the game is?
I hear you're
a worthless piece of Vegas shit,
which is what you kind of look like
at this point, if you don't mind me saying.
No offense.
But then I hear other things.
Like...you're a--a God
or a legend or something.
A bona fide fucking legend.
Yeah?
That's interesting.
And my job
isn't usually real interesting.
So tell me a story.
A story?
Yeah.
About you.
Why the fuck would I?
Because then you might figure out
why I'm here.
And if you do that...
I'll go.
You'll go?
On my father's eyes.
Get off me!
Give us the money, Ungar!
Don't give us that crap.
Punch him again, Flesh!
No, wait! All right!
Hi, Leon.
Yeah, Franky. Stupid, I said 1 8.
Yes, 1 8. I don't make the line.
You want it or not? I don't wanna hear
a joke. Franky, I don't wanna hear--
I don't...
Are you a lonely person?
What's the matter with you?
Hey, Pop.
Oh, Christ.
What happened to you?
No, sorry. Call me back.
Who did this, Stuey?
That Sheinberg kid again?
I'll speak to his father.
No, no, no. It's okay.
Yeah, it's okay.
You mean that move
we talked about?
How?
I dropped some change.
It worked perfect.
Where'd you get him?
Solly, Stuey got that fat-ass bully
Sheinberg kid right in the chatchkes!
Congratulations.
I love it, ah! Beautiful!
That's it, kid.
That's how you're gonna do it.
You're smarter than all of 'em.
You don't have to be big
when you're smart, right?
- Yeah.
You don't need
any of this nonsense, do you?
Here's what we're gonna do.
We're all gonna go out of town
this weekend and celebrate.
Some place fancy. Sound good?
- Sure.
- All right. Go get washed up.
I'll have Jimmy pour you something
to take the sting away. Go on.
Hey, Stuey...
This was special.
But you don't come down here
unless I bring you, okay? I mean it.
Yeah, no,
I'm talking to my kid.
My kid. My kid. He just kicked
the Sheinberg kid in the balls.
Yeah, you hope he don't kick
you in the balls.
Oh, you don't have any balls.
Yeah, I knew that.
You should know.
He's a good boy.
Sure you wanna do that?
You talk too much, shrimp.
Okay...just asking.
Gin.
Woo!
It's like I already knew
how to play.
My mom stanted to teach me.
she let me watch. but I knew.
I knew how they fit...
how they felt.
More like a mouth.
You know cards
were invented in China?
First they invented paper,
then cards right after.
Not these, though.
These came from England later.
That's why there's a Queen,
you know.
Four suits of 1 3 cards.
It's just...
...magic. It's perfect.
The Devil's work.
Yeah. Yeah.
But God, too.
Let's go to work.
Hello, everybody. I brought
my twin brother from Jersey.
We'll see you inside.
I wasn't really allowed
to go to the club.
But sometimes. when Ma was visiting
her sister or something. I got to go.
At night...
there was no place like it.
Hi, folks. Everything okay?
The martinis good?
God bless you.
Nice to see you.
Welcome. Welcome.
This is Stuey, my son.
Senator, how are you?
So nice to see you...
Pop was a big man there.
Everyone shook his hand--
Jews and Italians.
Brooklyn Moe Weinstein.
Big Anthony Tontolla.
Jackie Nose.
Bad Phillie Broma.
even celebrities
that came down sometimes--everybody.
Most of the time there.
I felt dizzy. I couldn't breathe.
It was so much...
bigger than everything else.
He's my bodyguard.
I brought him along.
I mean. broads. booze.
gambling--all of it.
But they never got sloppy. Ever.
And they took exactly zero shit
from nobody.
None of this corporate
political bullshit.
If they liked you. you were in.
If not. you were fucked.
Not like now.
Like you company muscle guys. right?
Not my style.
Martini time
I'm lining up my straws
So they liked you ?
Shit. yeah.
They saw I could play cards.
so I played for them.
The fish never saw me coming.
Never forgot me. either.
I razzed them so bad.
they always came back.
Vince and the other guys--
they respected me for my talent.
Don't work that way no more.
It's not so different now. Stuey.
When I was bar mitzvah'd in '66.
they all came. Every one.
They all gave me cash--
three grand. Out of respect.
You gonna tell me
it happens that way now?
Yeah. You give respect.
you get respect.
I gave respect.
What'd you do
with the money. Stuey?
I don't remember.
Yeah. you do.
No, Maxwell!
You're gonna kill him!
That's what I should do, Flo,
after what he did!
That was your bar mitzvah money,
you little shit!
- You spit on tradition!
- No!
I'm sorry, Pop.
I didn't mean--!
You didn't mean?
You didn't mean?!
Let me tell you what I mean.
From now on, no more club,
no more cards, no more track,
no more nothing,
you understand?!
You go to school,
you come home.
You use that big brain of yours
to do something other than
embarrass me and your mother,
you understand me?!
Vincent wants me to--
That's right, run away, you little shit.
Don't let me catch you!
What?!
He-Hey! There's my little genius.
Jesus Christ.
Who did this to you?
It's in your religion.
You understand my emphasis?
You really
wanna play cards, Stuey?
Yeah. More than anything.
All right.
I'll take care of it.
Let's go get a steak
for that shiner.
Good. 'Cause this credit thing...
it's for losers.
Stuey. Come here, son.
I'm sorry I was late, Pop.
Ralph's dad got a new color TV,
and we were watching, um...
My son the doctor,
driving up in his new Cadillac,
visiting us
from his house in Connecticut.
You think I wouldn't do it
another way if I could?!
I'm not smart enough!
I hate school.
It's boring!
And you don't like baseball,
you don't like football,
- Leave mom out of this!
- She doesn't see!
What--that you sit down at the club
and take these guys' money and respect
and then you spit on them
behind their backs?
No, she doesn't see!
Or someone did.
Everyone needs partners, man.
Where you been, Stuey?
I've been waiting for two fucking hours.
Jesus Christ.
Your dick is gonna fall off
if you keep going to them places.
- Where this time?
- Dolly's.
Skanks.
Victoria's is better.
You wanna go?
Nah, I don't wanna go.
Vince is gonna be mad as it is.
The game was supposed
to start an hour ago.
So? We still gotta eat, though,
don't we?
I guess so.
Whose is this?
Teddy's.
Teddy's?
And they look forward
to the trip.
Unbelievable.
Listen...
Vincent wanted me
to speak to you.
Tommy Spinotti,
Carmine Frangine--
Carmine's a prick.
and then you'll run off to the track or find
some asshole bookie to take your bet.
Okay, Anthony. Okay.
Flaming Christ, Anthony!
Absolutely, Mr. Leo.
Hi, it's a pleasure
to meet you, Mr. Leo.
So, shall we begin?
I believe knock rummy is the game?
What would you like
to play for, kid?
Anything you want.
Two bucks a point,
500 a game too much?
I'm rolling the dice
Feeling pretty good
Nice run of luck there, kid.
Oh, it ain't luck.
What, then?
I know you.
You know me?
Yeah, but I know now.
After four discards?
Impossible.
Well, I know you got
a pretty decent hand
'cause you always lean a little forward
when the cards look good on the deal.
Since I got the queen of diamonds,
you got kings.
until you hit something else
and you move 'em over.
Now, that's interesting, right?
No.
No, I don't think so, Mr. Leo.
Oh.
Oh, and, uh...
if you ever get to Vegas,
look me up.
So you're laying ten Gs
against 66 hundred to make that call.
Yeah, but I had him.
I call right, he's destroyed.
If you could take a man out,
you do it.
What'd he do to you?
Nothing.
Yeah.
- Well--
- No, they don't. 'Cause they got class.
Look at that jacket.
Like you've never been
in one before.
No, sir.
Good.
Because they spread disease.
Give young Stu here my food.
He's going to be
a millionaire, you know.
Don't let him near Funzi Giacomo
or the other families.
Gratzi.
Just another $2 whore,
eh, Stuey?
Gimme a dime.
...six--I don't have change.
Seven...eight...
Give me a fucking dime, Anthony.
four...five...six...
Sixteen...
Yeah.
Oh, it's okay. Don't worry about it.
Yeah?
Okay. Uh, great. Um...
Friday?
7:30?
Great. Okay.
Okay, great.
I'll see you then.
All right, bye.
A king.
Now he's smiling real big,
he's relaxing, lights a cigar.
- The whole place goes berserk.
- No! What did he do?
He turned white as a sheet,
He died right there.
Oh, my God. Really?
Um, sir, about the wine,
my manager...
Do you possibly have
any identification?
A driver's license, perhaps?
Well, I don't drive,
You think?
Bad day.
You know, people coming and going,
winning, losing...
Yeah, exactly.
This is me.
Yeah, I talked to fucking Vincent,
you Jew bastard.
Carmine, let's go.
One of these days...
and with you,
it's just a matter of time.
There ain't gonna be
no Vincent...no Gus.
...we're gonna have
a nice long dance.
Oh, yeah.
We will.
Want some coffee?
And they lived
happily ever after.
But it wasn't enough?
Hey, nobody gets everything they need
from one person.
So why'd she ask?
So he could tell her
what she wanted to hear.
And she could be with him.
Okay, good. Here.
Hold on one second.
Yeah, it's Stuey.
Uh, could you set us up with a couple
of spaghetti and meatballs--two orders.
What was that?
- Joey's. I ordered for us.
- You ordered?
Maybe I'll be there
when you get back.
We'll do it tomorrow,
I promise. Okay?
Just you and me.
Real romantic-like. I promise.
I don't like this, Stuey.
This ain't like usual.
He wouldn't give it to me.
He said you owe him.
Rosco, then?
No.
Freddie.
No!
Who, then?
Gus won't cover us if we lose.
I should've told you.
Why don't you get out of here.
They broke Anthony's arm.
- You think this is a fucking game?
- Jesus.
Yes, you will.
You're going
to Las Vegas tonight.
Tonight?
But Angela--
Fuck Angela.
You don't even know when your life's
being saved, so shut the fuck up.
Every penny comes back here,
you understand?
Every fucking penny.
Come on, Gino.
Please.
Okay, Stuey. Sure.
Shit.
You have a wonderful evening, sir.
And if you wanna go anywhere,
ask for Gerald.
Okay, Gerry. I'll do that.
Welcome to Las Vegas, sir.
Thank you.
Me and Frank.
Best in the business--best in the world,
as far as I'm concerned.
They got a couple of guys making
some noise now up and down the strip,
but...it won't be the same.
Some kind of player,
this boy.
Listen, Stu...
if I even hear you're near
any one of them before the tournament...
ladies and gentlemen,
put your hands together
and welcome little Stuey Ungar!
You sure you're old enough
to win this, kid?
Anthony. Jeez, man.
- Hello?
- Um.
Sondra.
Yeah, Sondra, listen. I gotta take care
of some business, okay?
They're like fucking sharks around here.
They smell blood in the water.
Cops came....firemen.
Everything.
Big scene.
You could do this, Stuey.
I'm funny?
gone back to New York,
gotten a job as an accountant
or some shit, made my apologies.
No! No!
For leaving the goddamn table!
This was what I was meant to do.
This was where I
was supposed to be.
Movie stars in Hollywood,
politicians in Washington.
I promised myself I wasn't
gonna gamble no more, and I didn't.
I really didn't.
For a long time, I didn't.
and the casinos edge on the game
just whittles it away.
Sometimes it's just a tiny edge.
but it's always there.
so they buy you your room
and your dinner.
and they smile and wait for you
to lay your money down again
And that's what we did. too.
Just waited forya.
You get two private cards.
five others are dealt up.
'Cause these donkeys never figured out
that the game wasn't about cards.
It was about people.
Re-raise.
I gotta bet you 5,000, Mario.
That one.
This one?
You lucky bastard.
Nice draw.
Hey!
In golf. you could do that.
He's got about 1 80 yards
to the pin.
And this certainly is anywhere.
You'll drown!
He hits the ball off this huge tee
three feet from the fucking cup.
Five fucking months!
People stood six-deep to watch.
It was the fuckin'
World Series of Poker.
and either you had the chops
to win a bracelet. or you didn't.
Tell me I'm learning
I call.
But I don't walk on water
and I don't read minds
Yeah, it's just
a matter of time
When you made
the final table...
Listen, I'm gonna go
to my room and lie down.
Okay. I'll--
Stuey.
Hand-made.
You and those cards.
We all knew it.
I have to get home.
change is good.
It looks like.
I need to wash these windows.
He's, uh...really smart.
Tall.
I got a million bucks
in a vault at the Dunes.
Anything.
In Vegas?
For Vegas, it was a normal life.
- Thank you.
- I'll be downstairs.
I'm gonna go look at this house.
- Glass of wine.
- Okay.
You get married,
you get soft.
But there is a matter
of a down payment.
Yeah, 40K, right?
Here you go.
Stu.
What? What?
Everything okay?
Yeah.
Yeah?
Salmon or Hunter Green?
What?
I think Salmon.
Stuey, you haven't spent
one second in the new house,
and I have made
every decision, all right?
So paint the fucking thing
Day-Glo Purple, for all I care.
Just leave me
the fuck alone, all right?
I'm gonna put it in the bank
and give it to my kid--what else?
Then why'd you say that?
I was kidding.
Great house, cars, vacations...
And Nicky.
Your daughter.
No.
It's the most amazing thing.
You don't sound amazed.
Yeah.
See, a kid is you...
perfect.
Stuey!
- How ya doing?
- Good.
Listen, go see if Scout
has enough water, okay?
- Okay.
- All right.
- I don't know.
- How 'bout raw? Think he'll like that?
How 'bout Susan?
And now they have to come back over
and turn it on--again.
And I have to call Susan
and make something up.
No! That's not the way it works!
We could put it on a credit card,
but we don't have a credit card.
You know, sometimes you can be
a real cunt, Angie.
Sometimes you make me
fucking sick.
You should've seen that fucking guy's
face, man. He was scared shit.
Aren't we havin'
a fucking party, or what?
Yeah!
Look, I gotta go, okay?
Oh, come on.
We're just getting started here, DJ.
No, man. I'm done.
So, Stu--can I call you Stu?
Yeah, sure.
So, Stu, have you met
the lovely Sondra?
We could settle up later,
okay, Stu?
Yeah, sure.
Thanks, Tony.
No fun at all.
What, home?! Oh...
Like you'd think she had a shitty life
or something like that.
Like she didn't live in a fucking mansion
that I bought for her. She's like--
- Ungrateful.
- Yes. Yes. Exactly that.
She's fucking ungrateful. Here.
Here. Look.
- Stuey.
- Right there.
- You're happy, right?
You're thrilled, right?
Why should you?
You got 30 grand right there.
With her, it's fucking different
'cause that shit is not important.
Not that she hasn't smacked me.
No, that's okay, I guess. I don't know.
There's a different standard.
There's a double standard there. Why?
Angie wouldn't
even touch me by then.
But you didn't really mind.
You had two new mistresses.
But I don't wanna talk
about this no more.
Go on, Stuey.
We need this.
Oh, Bob, go fuck yourself, okay?
Security!
Get him out.
Why don't you just fucking kiss me, okay,
because you've been
fucking me all night, anyway.
Who the fuck you think you are...
Angie?
What the fuck is going on?
Don't fucking tell me this.
Don't you fucking tell me this.
Motherfucker!
You motherfucker!
Huh?!
Huh? You fucking miserable cunt!
That's what you're gonna do?!
Yes, it's me.
I know. I know.
I'm sorry, okay? I'm sorry.
Okay.
Yeah.
You miserable cunt bitch!
Fuck it!
I don't remember, DJ.
I don't.
Hey ,fuck you, man, okay?
I don't need any lectures right now.
You like that, Stuey? Huh?
Well, you better get used
to it, man.
Well, I haven't been in this room
since, uh, Susan left.
Yeah, one thing at a time,
okay, DJ?
Yeah. Yeah, sure. Okay.
These okay?
Oh, yeah. Sure.
Wait a minute. Hold on. I...
Susan always, uh...
She thought of everything, huh?
Yeah, she did.
Not today, brother.
Not today.
Good morning!
Tonight I kinda lost myself
in a moment of a year
To take away
yesterday's sorrow
Send them angels
It's good!
No shit.
It's really good!
But I'll get to see Nicky.
We sure fucked it up,
didn't we?
You know...if I'd have known
about corned beef earlier,
Come on, kid.
Get in.
Where's your competitive spirit?
I know, I know, I know.
You're worried about the money.
No, you wouldn't do that.
Of course not.
You're my player, all right?
I gotta think about that.
And he wanna think about it?
Well, thanks for the ride.
Oh...my pleasure.
Those are for me, huh?
You used to try and get me
to come out here, remember?
Yeah.
She's a lot like you.
- Oh, shit.
- No.
In a good way.
We're, uh...we're gonna be
moving back, Stuey. I got a job.
Doesn't change anything.
Well...
See ya.
I don't know.
It'll bring you luck at the series.
Bye.
Nicky.
You can't lose--
not with me around.
And as aggressive
as Stuey has been throughout,
here he comes again--
he raises $40,000.
Stu raised seven times in a row
with no one calling him?
Is he bluffing?
No one was willing to be the one
to pay to find out if Stu was bluffing.
Well, that's no help for Stu,
because he needs a four
or a deuce on the final card
But wherever you are.
you gotta consider all your outs.
See. sometimes they save you...
you really ain't got no outs at all.
Again.
A bona fide legend.
Oh, yeah.
Everybody's hero.
Uh-huh.
Oh, all the time, man.
They're always keeping me straight.
See, that's the great thing
about Vegas.
Is--is people are always
doing favors for each other.
So you got where you've seen me?
You did good anyway.
Really?
We could play a couple of hands
for, you know...