Somebody get me a beer,
please.
You gonna be my girlfriend!
I said...
- You gonna be my girlfriend!
- Get off me!
Get off me!
You hurting me!
Stop it!
Texas.
True love. Two words
I never quite understood.
Where was this place in the world
and how could it be found?
Have faith. That's something
I understood even less.
Could you change it, or we just blindly
following the natural order of life?
When I was a baby,
my mother died in a car crash,
leaving my father and I alone.
He never spoke of it, I assumed
that he carried the grief...
nightly inside himself.
At bedtime, he'd always point out
at the night sky, and said...
"there's your moon, Amy",
isn't it beautiful?
That's where your dreams
come from.
But, as I grew older,
the words "true love and faith...
seams illusive
as my dream.
Until one day, they all collided
against my shot to life.
And for me,
it all began right about...
here.
Someone's in trouble.
Where?
I just pull over and look
if anyone's inside.
All right.
I don't know, man,
I don't see anybody.
Well, I'll go check it out.
You stay here.
- Holy shit, Earl!
- What?
- You gotta see this.
- What is that?
Car-load of shit
everywhere!
Yeah, what is it?
Viagra I tell you, is the greatest
fucking thing in the world.
Yeah, that's if you needed.
If you don't need it,
who gives a shit.
I'm gonna tell you something, this...
this Viagra is a wonder potion.
You have a great big boner
that does the "Deep Down".
Hello, Deb.
Two sugars today, yeah.
I need some
sweetin' up.
Thanks Deb.
Hey, speakin' of heart,
take a look over there.
Leave the lady alone, alright?
John, you sure
you don't want some of this Viagra?
No, I told you,
that you guys work our asses off.
Alright, you guys finish up here. Somebody's
gotta do some work around this town.
Yeah, uh...
you'll be working on that.
- That's for the sheriffs, uh... coffee.
- You got it.
Hi, Sam.
Let me take a look at you.
Well, you look the same.
Thank God.
I saw your news this morning,
what was that all about?
Yeah, well, there should never been
any news at all.
I don't how the media
get's a hold of that.
- Mh-hm.
- Hm...
- Well, what a surprise.
Oh, I gotta go back to work.
You know, I make my living here.
- Good seeing you.
- Same here, you mind if I walk you out?
Yeah, why not?
How's the ranch going?
Well, we're hanging in there,
gettin' by on the skin of our teeth,
you know.
You look great, Sam.
- You too, John.
- Thanks.
How's Amy?
She's nearly a woman now.
I can imagin', yeah.
- Long time.
- Yeah, long time.
Well...
- See you around.
- Keep your other side down.
- Always do.
Sweetie, my dear...
I miss you so much.
Maybe I'll just join you.
Hm?
Oh, I could now put this silver bullet
in my own head.
Oh...
Oh, I know,
oh, I know.
You think I got parts for all this.
Look at the work, mister.
Guys, you know what I hate,
I hate my job.
- Hard day at the offfice?
- Ah, samo, samo. Give me a cigarette.
Sure.
Walla.
Never loose it, sister.
Hey...
Honey alert!
I dare you,
to go make contact.
- I'm okay.
- Come on.
- Just do it, don't be scared.
- I don't want to, I'm not scared, I just...
I'm a little more selective
then you guys.
- So selective, you haven't been laid yet.
- Yeah.
So?
Come on,
chicken-shit.
- Just do it. Come on, little lady.
- Do it, do it.
- Come on... Go.
- Go! Come on, go!
I just talked to him
the other day.
Can Amy pick up an ass-hole...
- you think?
- I don't think so.
Hey.
Can I help you with sometin'?
Hey, you live here.
Right?
Yeah, I know.
I saw you driving that little car
the other day. Is that yours?
Yep.
Hey!
What you think you're doing?
Smoking.
Yeah, you can't smoke here.
Oh, I'm sorry,
sorry.
That's a beautiful car.
What is it?
It's a 68 AMX.
- Do you do all the work on this...
- Look, kid...
if I sit here and talk you,
I never would get any work done.
So, why don't go
play somewhere else.
See you around.
Whatever.
See you guys later,
I'm gonna go home.
Jesus Christ, mother...
Would you like to ride?
- Not today
- Come on?
Look, I'm sorry.
- It's windy out.
- I like the wind.
Look, I'm sorry about that earlier.
I only been working here a week, kid,
the boss is kind of brick.
I guess there's a lotta
bricks in that shop.
Yeah, I guess so.
Wait here for one second.
I'm sorry.
It's a fucking cactus!
Well, use your imagination.
It could be a flower.
Okay.
I'm Amy.
- Dan.
- Nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you too.
I had that thing purring
like a chick in an hour.
I swear to God, the old mans' jaw,
about hit the ground.
That's why
you got the job, huh?
Yep.
So...
Will I see you again?
I don't know. Maybe.
My dad's real protective.
Well, I can live with maybe.
Why don't you drop
by the shop sometime?
I promise
I won't be such a brick.
Alright.
As long as you promise.
- Thank you.
- Any time.
Oh...
Don't forget your flowers.
I don't wanna forget that.
Bye.
Jack on the rocks.
You live around here?
No, man, I'm just visiting.
I'm fom L.A.
You?
Heading towards Nevada.
Just slummin' a little.
Drink pioson...
take a look at some titties,
and see what bites.
Nevada,
titties and ass bites.
Yeah, I remember back
in the day...
Hey, gorgeous.
I been watching you
all night...
What's your sign?
Stop, that's my sign.
Oh, come on...
You don't believe in astrologie?
What's your rising sign?
I don't know.
I think it's stupid.
Can I see your hand?
You know what that says?
Rosie Palmer.
You're a fucking ass-hole!
Wasn't that sometin'?
Well, you take it easy now, Rosie.
- Have a good night.
- Likewise.
- Bartender.
- One second, be right with you.
What can I do for you?
Gimlet for one of your fancy girls.
The girl over by the pool table.
Do you want it
sweet or dry,
- ripe or fruity?
- Fruity.
You got it, buddy.
- You see that guy over there?
- I don't know him.
He just bought you a drink.
Who got next game?
Hey...
So... how'd you know
what I like?
I be damned! I know a lot more,
we're going out tonight.
Besides...
you looked like you needed rescuing
from those beers uptown.
"Wankers only".
- I like a girl with experience.
- I'm not a hooker.
- Not here.
- Let's go in my truck outside, alright?
- Let me see your ass!
- You sure are a wild one!
Get outta the truck!
you ass-hole!
Come here you fuck
you here to fuck us up!
Stop! No! Stop it!
Get the fuck back in the truck,
you old whore!
Yeah!
You like that?
You want more, huh?
Stay the fuck
right there!
No...
See that, huh?
This is your boyfriend!
Hey!
Give me the shovel, ass-hole!
I asked you for the fucking shovel.
Hey...
Keep the fuck away.
I'm busy right here.
There's so many rich people
they're just out there...
waiting for the perfect
Miss Fabulous to come along.
They're coming here lining up,
and all I have to say is please.
Give me a break.
Okay, fine. Then I'll just take 'em off
until they're 3 inches longer.
You would.
Quit your smoking.
Hey, ladies.
You wouldn't happen to be
Johns daughter?
Hm?
Would you?
Yeah, I am.
I... I was just...
I was in the neighborhood,
and thought I stop by.
Is your dad around?
He actually just left,
but he'll be right back.
Hm...
Is there anything
I can do for you, sheriff?
Um... no,
no, just, um...
just... tell him
I... I stopped by, okay?
Who do I tell him?
Sam's the name.
Your father and I...
Yeah, my dad,
he...
- he told me about you.
- Oh, good.
Good things,
I would think.
Good.
Good, um...
I tell you what, just...
- tell him that I was here.
- Sure thing.
Been great to...
to be hanging out, do nothing.
Sure be nice,
to see you again.
- You too.
- Okay... bye you all.
Bye.
Where are you?
Oh, here you are.
- Hi.
- Hi-ah.
- Hey.
- Hi.
Come on, come on.
Hey...
How are you?
Thank you.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
- Cheers.
Why walk,
when you can ride?
Uh... I'm alright,
thank you, though.
I wouldn't feel right, if I was gonna
let you walk over there all by yourself.
Relax. I know your dad,
big John over at the ranch.
He wouldn't want me
to leave you here.
You know my dad?
Yeah.
Alright.
Get in the car.
It is kind of cold.
- Where we going?
- Rustig aan. This will just take a second.
I wanna go home now.
We have to have
some fun first.
Fuckin' bitch.
- Get off me!
- Yeah.
Fuckin' bitch!
- Get off me!
- Yeah, you fucking like that?
Help me!
Get outta the car!
- Chicken-shit!
- Where the fuck did you come for?
You brick.
Stay away from her.
Amy, let's go.
Are you okay?
It's alright.
- Are you okay?
- Mh-hm.
Yeah.
- Are you?
- Yeah, I'm fine.
Where are you from originally?
Well...
I moved around a lot.
Guess you could say,
I am from...
everywhere and anywhere.
So, what you doing
out here tonight?
I don't wanna freak you out,
but...
I've been following you
ever since the first day we met.
So, you're a stalker?
No, it's nothin' like that.
You seam different.
Sorta like the outsider like me.
I'm really glad,
you were there tonight.
That guy told me he's...
friends with my dad.
This... certainly never happened
to me before.
It's okay.
Did you have a good night?
Hey, dad.
Yeah, it was fun.
You didn't have to wait for up,
though.
Evidently I do.
Who drove you home?
Just a friend.
A friend?
He's no friend, Amy.
It's not like that, dad.
I'm going to sleep.
Good night, dad.
- Don't give me that face.
- Good night, dad.
Good night.
Son of a bitch!
What you doing out here, Sam?
- Oh, you think you're fast, huh?
- But I believe, the slowest got it.
You should?
- Look at that slicin' moon up there, girl.
- It's magical.
I like it out here.
Jesus Christ!
My God!
What's wrong?
Amy! Over here!
I love you!
Oh, my God!
- Amy, you gotta come in!
- You're crazy.
- You'll enjoy it.
- What you waiting for, let's go.
- Is it cold?
- Huh?
- Come on, take your clothes off.
- No...
Come and join me.
It's great!
It isn't cold.
Go ahead!
Watch your step.
The water is cold!
I got an idea.
What are you doing?
I'm lettin' you take the wheel.
Come on, slide over!
You shift her in first,
it's a four speed and let it go.
I know how to drive, Mario.
Let me just see
if you got that.
- You got your seat-belt on?
- I'm no dummy.
Are you ready?
- If you go a little faster, it's fine.
- Oooh...
Okay.
- Not bad for a rookie.
- Wanna see what this car can do?
Oh, I know
what this car can do, trust me.
I didn't realize it at the time
that this small thing...
the memoires I was collectin'
would sustain me...
now I carry them with me forever.
No, it's not out there yet...
Dear, I know you like this,
but this sure gives me the creeps.
Then why come back to that
anyway, Linda?
Oh, it's nothing.
Look, Floyd!
Oh... oh... oh...
Go get him, Norman!
You son of a bitch!
You mother-fucker!
Shit! What a crazy fuck!
I'm gonna kill the fucker!
Get your ass back here,
I'll kill you!
Why?
Why me?
Why!
What did I do?
Why?
Hey, what in the world
happened to you?
Got the motor runnin' here,
get in the truck
and I'll take you to town.
- It's about fucking time, Sam.
- What is going on, Louie?
Well, I was hopin'
you could tell me.
- Come here.
- Let's see.
Fuckin' pretty, ain't it?
It's some bad shit, I tell you!
Mother-fuckers are pissin' me off!
- Come over here.
- Louie, I'm coming.
- Come on, over here.
- Coming, Louie.
Take a look at this shit!
- God.
- Yeah.
I took a shot at the mother-fucker!
I don't know if I hit anything.
To fuckin' dark.
I don't know what the fuck's over here?
But... that's a dog lying here.
The other half is in there.
What I wanna know is what the fuck
you gonna do about this Sam!
Goddamn it, I don't need anymore
of your crap Louie!
I'm sick and tired
of your bull-shit.
Go down to my truck
and bring me my camera...
It's on the seat,
I... need to take picture.
I swear to God, I'm getting
sick and tired of this shit!
The best fucking dog I ever had!
Some mother-fucker's gonna die,
behind this shit, I tell you!
As soon as I can get,
this mother-fucker.
I waited for hours last night.
Where were you?
Hell, Amy.
I was in hell.
Those will kill you,
you know?
Is this a fucking joke?
This it least a choice.
What is it, Dan?
You know you can tell me
anything, right?
Anything Amy?
- Yeah.
- Yeah?
Anything? What makes you
sure with everything?
Huh?
What makes you so sure?
Because I'm in love with you.
Okay.
Okay!
I've become the wolf, Amy.
I know you are.
Listen to me!
I'm a fucking werewolf!
Those slayings at the farm?
That was me.
Well, what are you saying?
It's true, Amy.
It's real.
Remember
what you promised me...
I scream,
you drive away.
You never told me about
when you were a kid.
It's not much to tell...
I don't remember much.
Sometime I...
see my mother...
she's running through a forest,
with somethin' chasing her.
I think it's me, but...
I never quite remember.
I have this memory,
this vision of her...
holding me.
which is just so real.
When I reach out to touch her,
she just fades away.
And your father?
Yeah...
good old dad.
I never even knew my father.
Amy, it's happenin'!
Get outta here!
- Are you okay?
- Amy, go!
Goddamn it, Amy.
There's this kid...
a drifter...
he seams to be hangin' around Amy
and I thought...
Wait a minute, you're talking about
the kid at the auto-shop?
- Nice car he's got.
- Oh, come on, Sam.
There's somthin' creepy about him.
He's... he's strange.
I don't want him
anywhere near Amy.
Okay, lets...
lets get this straight.
You want me to maybe arrest him,
because your daughter like him?
No, well I thought...
you know, you could... scare him off.
Or shoot him or hang him.
Well I... I don't kow
if I can do that, John.
He ain't broken any laws.
Oh, Jesus Christ, Sam!
Come on, that's ridicules!
I don't want that son of a bitch
around my daughter.
I mean, do I have to beg you
to do someting?
Funny...
that's exatly how my dad...
God rest his soul,
felt about us back then.
Didn't make a bid of differnce,
did it?
Okay, I get it laud and clear,
but I'm telling you, he's trouble.
I mean please, could you just...
just check him out?
Why is it people
who have never raised kids...
always have an opinion
of how it should done?
Stop! Woa, wait... wait a minute,
you... you're right,
I... I have no experience
raising kids.
I'm not giving you any advise,
on how to do any of if.
I'm not speaking as a parent,
I am speaking as a law-man.
As a law-man I'm telling you,
Amy needs to learn a few things on her own.
Come on, Sam.
- Come on.
- I see what I can do.
Thanks.
You sure about this?
It costs you dollar.
- I got it.
- He's the man. He's got the money.
Thank you.
Okay...
let's begin.
We were wondering if you...
knew anything about, um...
people that
change in their life?
Hm...
Things that are...
kind of crazy
and unimaginable.
Hm.
Like, uh...
Like vampires?
Gablets?
Werewolves?
The werewolves?
Sometimes called
"Skin-shifters".
"Windigowak".
"Glabligouk".
The things our minds can conject
can be very real.
The problem we're talking about,
is yours, isn't it?
Yes.
Give me hand.
Close your eyes.
Take a deep breath and focus.
You are...
you are c... cursed.
You one of them...
Exuse me...
Mother in haven!
Mother in haven...
What's that?
This will...
this will protect you from...
From me?
No.
From the curse...
and its origin.
- How did this happen?
- This was...
It started...
with your father.
- My father?
- And was passed on to you.
I don't even know who my father is,
not alone know, if he's even alive.
Oh, he's alive...
I can feel him...
Okay, what do you do,
when you have problem?
What do mean?
If... if he didn't exist,
the curse would not be upon you.
You see this werewolf?
Right here?
He got cursed
to a sorcery.
His was the first...
the first hated blood.
That's your daddy...
he brought this down on you...
Your are his descendent.
You are his beta.
Is there any... hope?
Can we...
I think there still is hope, because
you have not tasted the human blood.
But, look at me.
Look at me!
Once you have it,
your soul...
Not from being within you,
except become... that what you already are.
How do you know
I haven't killed a human?
Because I feel it.
Because I...
I know... I...
I feel it.
No lies in your eyes...
You're... you're... you're save with him.
You're save with him.
So, it's okay?
It's your father...
He cherishes the curse...
and he can kill... anytime,
anywhere, that he wants.
And retain human intelligent...
clear knowledge
and mind of his acts.
He's more dangerous...
then you'll ever know.
Is there anything
I can do about this?
My guees is...
you gotta kill your daddy.
Good bye.
- Thank you.
Please don't let out the kiddy.
Thank you.
When everything else fails,
you've got your instincts.
It sounds
really, really weird...
what's going on around guys,
I don't know, at this moment.
My instincts are screaming.