Translation: Ang3l
- Hi Katie.
- Ryan!
What are you doing here?
Your mother left me to go.
I have a surprise for you.
I love Katie.
I always loved ...
and we always to love you.
You are my soul mate.
Ryan.
You are so good.
- It's new game Defcon 4?
- Yes.
- Package with sound?
- Come on. What?
- No, you must do so a. Look.
You can make you a. Right here.
Get up to this point.
There a catch!
Yes!
Yes ...
Spencer, I have a crazy party
to have sex with you.
I'm thinking about you all day
over me
trãgându me that so strongly
until you make þip.
Katie.
Ryan.
Katie. Baby ...
It's time to wake you up.
Last day of school.
You want to get the latest.
What about you?
You are okay?
- Yes.
- I know ...
Still you're sorry that you were not
best in class.
I do not want to worry
for this.
You grant that I, the rest
not matter.
Yes, my dear?
Honey ...
You are hot and sweaty ...
have fever?
No, I'm fine.
Well.
And his oricelul Cleo.
Never where you
go
and saliveazã everywhere.
Agreed. Get up.
Rose will be here any moment.
It's the last day.
Do not come late. It is very
emoþionant.
Hey, it seems that you're the last
exits, as usual.
I had to take leave from
d-l Warren, and I thank you for lecþiile
the literature on which we gave.
Come on, come with me in the center
commercial.
Rose, can not go with you to
shopping. You must go home,
I need to fix, the family comes
in another city.
I did not need new clothes,
but you.
What? No, I do not.
Katie, when we are good friends?
From kindergarten.
Joni, cãþea crazy!
Pull it with a rocker in Spain
for me when you get there!
And all this time ...
I advised him ever bad?
Yes.
Katie, look at me. We are
point to enter the world of evil.
We are about to exit the limits
this vieþi suburban.
We will make serious changes,
from your clothes.
Dress like a librarian,
not sexy.
I like my clothes.
You want to exit the world your stories and your
of books, study and boredom
and to join reality?
Ryan Lambert liked you for five years
and except for this Halloween
centuries
did not kiss him or
nor anybody.
Ryan Lambert is my soul mate.
I have to hold him.
We first.
I told you that if we arrive on time
will not be anyone.
God ... that was surprising.
- Who was that?
- I do not know.
But whoever it was, I think that was
my soul mate.
Ryan, playing Goldeneye lately?
Yes, I like guns. It is amazing.
It was Ryan Lambert. I knew.
I knew that we are one fãcuþi
for another.
Even if I disgust you think that ...
must go to that bastion
which is surprising center
and I'll get some
cool clothes
and today the party going
after him.
Genius. Tonight will be great.
What use to buy sexy clothes
if you cover the sweater?
- It's cold.
- There are 32 degrees out.
God ... wait.
Congratulations, gentlemen?
And why? The person who wrote it
love the Spanish ...
Let us not inquire ...
And we will not correct spelling
anyone!
- No?
- God, is trying!
Try really.
Everyone listen!
The party will not do.
He canceled the party.
Please exit to I all.
Please out. Stop it!
Staþi! Staþi!
Listen
My grandfather just out of it
hospital. It is up in a coma.
I want to with all plecaþi.
Rose, come on, you should
go.
Grandpa's just out of it
hospital. It is in a coma.
And why. Not to wake him.
Hey, show me breasts. It is for my movie
"Memories of High School.
Come on, you receive a t-shirt gift
if you do.
I have never done such a thing,
and do not you write that word, Seth.
Virgin ...
Come on ...
Rose, how's that still are tiut
virgin?
As all know bãieþii status
sex of pretty girls.
Katie Powers is still a virgin?
Who?
Yes, all virgin.
But you do not ...
to go to look for Ryan.
Here it is.
Go talk to you with him.
First I need a shower that.
Let's go to a drink.
I need two.
What to say, what'll I do?
Be yourself only. Just yourself.
- Really?
- Yes ...
No. Be sexy and beautiful.
Make it feel smart.
And not to correct grammar.
He just looked at me.
Go and you talk to him.
No, I need a minute.
At least you know where?
Sit here and wait to come.
Good gentlemen, and gentlemen and there.
I think you're the only person
and that he realized that.
Beer? But you wish you beer.
Okay, I'm sorry.
You saw the show on channel ...?
Spencer, you were here. You need to talk.
Katie ... you came.
I thought that you will not come that
you out of it first class.
And why would you mind if you like tigat
Award and scholarship, slut?
That do not know. Still have not counted
votes
Don 't you, Spencer?
No.
But Katie is the only nominated,
so that ...
One word, folks.
A walk.
In fact, there are two words.
Anyway, I go for a walk
in your car ta us?
Sure.
Great.
Please, she thinks that if flirteazã
with you
tri you and you will give him the prize.
Award of Katie.
Okay, go get beer.
Want?
Yes, more beer.
More beer?
Do not look now
but Ryan comes.
Okay, îndrãzneaþã but not aggressive.
Willing, but not vulgar.
Go.
- Hi Katie.
- I'm sorry.
It's okay.
It is a zoo.
I do not worry.
I wanted to thank you for
that helped me in all the years and people ã
in high school, and you know?
- It's finished.
- No!
No! Yes!
If you need anything tell me,
agree?
Thanks.
Ryan, I was wondering if you can, you ...
You want ... you know you ...
To exit from here.
What? I have not heard.
I'm sorry.
I wanted to know if you ...
You want a beer.
No, I have a beer.
And you just ... you two beers.
Yes, you e.
Tomorrow I leave with my father
summer,
so that if you see ...
Tomorrow?
Do not stay for graduation?
No.
Actually my friends I wait,
so that ...
Excuse me, I ...
I'd like to know if Ryan ...
I always had this relationship client-guardian
and you may want to know if you
be willing to something more ...
- No you're a virgin?
- Yes.
Now while I had an experience
with a virgin, and was ...
Susan Enright ...
Yes.
Anyway ...
was too much drama and I can not.
But will not you be with me. I promise.
Frankly I'm sorry.
I did not promise that
I make sex with a virgin.
No virgins.
It is a shame, because ...
In other conditions ...
Hey, what did he say?
Not like me.
He said that?
He said that I do with a virgin
after all disaster Susan Enright.
Why a virgin he broke for
other in November?
What?
Katie! Hey!
Katie!
Katiekins, Katiekins.
Tiut and I always think ...
in one way or another, Ryan
and I will be together.
Now it is too late.
If in any way I could snap
of fingers
.. and ready to stop being a virgin.
I'm sorry.
Hey, haideþi to climb, and
make nonsense?
Okay, go and vomit.
I know that is a form in which
you could still have it on Ryan.
But you do not never.
Rose, I do anything.
All you need to do
is to lose your virginity.
But Ryan will not sleep with me.
Someone at a party in
tonight.
Rose!
You asked.
I think I can go.
- Well ...
- No!
You stay, have fun.
I need some time myself.
Okay.
Come here Katie. I love you.
Katie!
Rose, I can do.
You can do anything to him
a chance and love.
I am so proud of you.
Let's get the facts ...
Who do we need to do?
Spencer!
No.
- I think not.
- Is perfect.
I know you are in kindergarten. It is nice.
It is safe.
And I think that it will take a minute.
I'm sorry that it took both.
Queue was ridiculously high, and
world away.
- You are well? You seem ...
- All right, Spencer.
Actually ...
Actually I said that I want to ...
I'm like what?
To do with you.
Let him hit it ... can penetrate.
In any form.
Yeah, so is Katie?
Really?
I can not let a girl escape Spencer ...
Yes or no?
Yes.
Yes, the final answer.
- Really?
- Sure.
I mean, sure did.
When?
Right now.
If not now, when?
Agreed.
Just think ... you must go to the bathroom.
I can not believe you do this.
- I can not.
- Katie, come on, sure you can.
- Better to say they look.
- Katie ...
Wait and Tita lines, no big deal.
All you need to do is, well ...
Nothing! Just stretch it.
- To lie down ...
- Spencer And you put in a ...
Spencer and I put it on ... ...
- His penis.
- God!
Spencer has a penis!
Rose ...
I always assume that the tiut this
but never ...
- Katie.
- Rose, I can not.
I think ...
Do not look.
- Really?
- Yes!
But I think we need to see!
Should not see and can
nor have you felt.
Yes?
Okay, I will hurt bad.
I thought that I feel good.
Like you have some meddle in sauce
ear, how good are you to ...
God.
And then blood.
Blood?
Katie, wait lines and Tita. Oh I like you.
Maybe not the first time, and no second
and neither can the third ...
Why do I need to do this?
Well, get this. Think it over,
is as if you go to the dentist.
I like to go to the dentist, right?
Yes.
Because I have cavities
and I always periazã dinþii.
Well, neither Spencer will not find holes,
except this.
You must remember that when you
when this
you have something better than
a dental brush
I'll have Ryan Lambert!
Yes.
Okay, okay.
Can do.
He and they just added ...
and then wait a minute or two
- And ends.
- Like going to the dentist.
Yes.
- Can!
- You can.
- I can!
- Seriously, I can!
- You can.
Come on, go and do it.
I can not.
How to do this? They have încolþit me.
Is not correct.
It's too much pressure.
I need time to prepare me.
Hey, you ready for
18.
Yes.
Yeah, right.
I have to be okay.
I just can not come too soon.
What?
Girls take the time to ...
And you know ...
How do you know?
Believe me, you know.
Just go and pull it and not
will have lasting problems.
What? No!
Can not do that.
You have another alternative.
Good.
Here?
I can not believe I do.
Well, you must concentrate.
- I gotta go to the bathroom.
- Yes.
One moment.
I can not.
I need something for ...
That he left to do.
Katie ...
Yes.
I asked to leave, but did not want.
But not approaching this room.
You can fill it with water?
Fill it in the bathroom.
God!
What about you? My grandfather is together.
I'm sorry.
God.
No, it is not what it seems.
Only that we did not find anything else.
Really?
I saw it.
I swear!
Honestly I love this thing.
In fact, keep.
I want to masturbate with it.
You are a pervert.
And?
Great advice. I almost gave me
out of the party.
I just wanted to help.
Look what I got.
- What are you using?
- Believe me, making sex ...
something very hard.
How do you know?
I know it.
Okay, can do.
The best thing you can
to do is ...
to do it as soon as possible.
Well.
Well ... I suppose ...
you must use your car my
the new.
Your father bought you your car
that for graduation?
- Yes.
- It's nice.
Thanks.
Then, I suppose ...
- First, it's more secure.
- Yes.
Is important.
Then I go to my place him.
Only if you want ...
No, thank you.
Well.
I do not ... you know ...
I mean that there is enormous.
Okay.
Actually, that's probably good.
It's your right.
I mean that's not small.
It is only normal. 15.8 cm.
That if a measure of peak
not the basis.
He's one of the most measured,
I think that is a way to tri and a.
I mean ... perhaps.
Well ...
Well.
Then ...
You are ready?
Yes.
I let you back.
God.
A to fire some fireworks
fireworks.
Go!
What the hell is going on with this shit?
Okay, just ...
You are okay?
Yeah, just that ...
Spencer Yeah, come on!
I know you?
No.
It was weird.
I'm sorry.
I do not knew that you do.
Frankly I'm sorry.
I think we should go for
external interference ...
with kissing.
Well.
Great.
Just wait.
- Damn.
- What? What happens?
- I did something?
- No, it's good.
Okay?
- Close your eyes, right?
- I agree.
Spencer ...
- You can quickly insert?
- Yes.
You need only to focus.
Okay, now.
What? What are you doing?
Get away!
Damn, she înþepenit!
Think you are on another woman
with a great ass while I
penetrate?
- No one does.
- No.
Katie, wait.
Please, Katie!
I know that most are not nice
of school
But you need help
vision to penetrate me?
I imagine that you're a
woman with big ass?
No, Katie, I imagine that you are.
Has no meaning.
Just watch.
I can find someone else.
Anyone else?
To do, slut.
One, two ...
Good luck, fucker!
Katie, how you went?
No, not function.
Very drunk?
Not only are you not like him.
God!
Spencer is gay!
I always tiut and that.
It was in sight all the time.
Do not you was up because of beer?
You could not?
No.
You just can 't explain.
Hold.
Please urinaþi in the bathroom.
Hey ...
Take, relax.
Damn! Cheers.
Up your ass!
I do not know, Rose. Maybe we can
go home.
What?
No.
I had only a small contretemps.
May have to find someone
and skip the dentist sexy!
And if me sui a horse
and he wants the water ...
and water has a big butt ..
Okay, that's fine.
Not understand anything. You are drunk.
Katie ...
Tonight I lose virginity.
This virgin bitch.
The wait to find Chelsea.
Chelsea!
Very good, a little contretemps.
You get reorganized.
Sweater flies.
You know, I never thought I would be so difficult.
It happens.
Katie, you're here?
I sign annual album?
I'm going to join the group
the dialogue and debate, for
And a head next year.
Everything you need is a
female model on which to follow him
and happens to be one up.
My model is followed?
Yes.
Look good, because that is what
and what do you want a man.
That is what they want and the one
man?
Well.
Let's see what it is.
You did that?
No.
Good?
Mandy said that before and to make
48D implants
regular and switch to fill and bra
with chicken cutlet.
But we have such a thing.
But can not find something that
to be useful.
Plan:
I can look in the refrigerator
and you go and you makeup
more
combs and I laugh at you.
- But I laughed the morning.
- The legs do not.
And chestiuþa you, right?
You said that it is an emergency. Why are
a razor?
Shave emergency. Health.
Is not so bad.
It feels good.
It was locked.
Chicken ... chicken ... chicken.
We got something. Super.
Finally it's a little bit.
You are man. You can rub one out.
Not clean.
You are very lucky.
They take me everywhere.
You are ready?
Take it off.
Mommy has care, right?
Yes, I eat.
Really?
Well, the mind controls matter.
Do it, please. And now put your stuff.
But it is chicken.
Do not be so sensitive, okay?
Want big breasts or not?
Marina?
Is what I found, right?
Ask them, I a.
Extraordinary!
For me, it works.
Hey, do not get.
What do?
Want to get and to make a
and private session?
What are you doing?
Chelsea told me that you planned
you lose your ...
Busy!
No, Wait.
- You can do this.
- And why not?
If you can not with her, does not mean
that no one can.
Ia. You are Kathy, right?
Katie.
Yes.
You were with me in class to
French, no?
I think the show differently.
I want to say, into good.
Thanks.
- You are here much?
- What?
- I hear you.
- I said
maybe you should get, and
stam de vorba
in a camera or something.
No girlfriend?
Who? Rachel? You see here? No!
No, no, no, no.
Maybe you should get.
- I agree.
- Really?
- Yes!
- Okay, come on.
I scuzaþi.
A mad.
Give a Damn! Forget it.
You meriþi something better.
Hey. hey.
What happens?
To go in camera.
Will happen at any time.
Okay, I can tell you that you see
a penis, right?
Yeah, you know.
You're right. This time
are ready.
And you should ...
Just try.
Just need to do, right?
Petardele you tried?
Hey, excuse me, are you ready?
- Come on.
- Goodbye.
Goodbye.
God, give it off.
Will be fine. You are so cool.
Yes?
Is there ...
form to make love
or sex?
Look, I like French.
Sure, we can not do sex.
But first you must want to suck.
It will be very good. You are ready?
God, come on.
Come on.
What happens? What?
Nothing, just ...
All you show?
No way!
Some are ugly.
Come on, you can sãruþi.
I have to answer the phone.
I heard you calling.
And answer me back in a minute.
It will not be ready all day
and not talk to me.
Just a second.
I have not heard to call.
What happened?
It is assumed that you have to be in.
Tell me if you need to show you a.
Yes, more or less.
You are sure?
Forget you.
I am a lesbian.
No you're lesbian.
You need only to regular and nuiele you.
Looks like a wild mushroom.
That has veins.
And it is purple.
And I want to put your mouth on it.
- When to come ...
- To come?
Launch sperm.
I can, really can not.
You must go.
- Katie!
- I can not.
All these are like a movie
horror.
And do not even like
mushrooms.
Trevor! Where are you?
Kathy, you came back.
Katie.
What happens? You seem nervous.
Come on.
Let gu are a bit of that ...
you felt better.
- Yes?
- Yes. Course.
Shoot, so, okay.
Now it's time to make you fly.
Well. I just need ...
to suck a little one minutes
and then we can do sex.
Okay?
I do not think you can. I want to vomit.
Katie relax.
What?
I did not say anything.
Katie, yes, closer-up.
Katie Yes, yes.
Mr Mushrooms?
Yes Katie, love. Now kiss me.
No.
Katie, please, is for your sake.
You know why men do not look at you?
Because of the lack of "do not know what"
that have experience with women.
Yes.
Katie, listen to me. Men are
some wrap and empty sites.
Mind, brain.
Soul men is here.
Yes, penis.
I is.
So I Katie, you must
you know dick.
Yes Katie, it sucks.
You are here Trevor?
- It's my friend!
- I thought I did not have friends.
- Trevor, I can get!
- Okay!
There you are!
Well.
Do not you do that if I would
in your place.
Ta thing smells like cherries and a.
Yes.
Okay, okay.
Katie, hey.
- What happened?
- I want to talk about it.
Rose, the whole thing with the sex
was more annoying than me waiting.
I will be happy if I have to
see a penis again.
Just that you have not found that indicated.
When you see Ryan's,
will be gratified.
Rose, I do not think ...
I'm sorry Rose, I'm sorry virgino.
And what's worse to be a virgin?
Nothing!
I'm sick of you and form
stupid to tell me.
I am president of the club ah!
I am the captain of the debate!
And best of class!
Almost.
Yes.
Can I do this.
Can I do if I proposed.
Yes!
Rose, I will end with this ...
quickly.
Wonderful. Very good.
Well, him.
Cisco? Is completely gay.
No, it is surprising to bed.
He has a great tool.
What color is it?
Hey Cisco ...
It is a rumor that you do
in a way surprising.
- Katie wants to persuade.
- Rose!
No, it is true, but ...
for me means not only
to have sex.
Is to use my sexual energy
forces to release "Cunnilingi"
and to unite with this energy
energy that our bodies emit.
Dad! And why not give it to Katie
a lecþie?
Normally I do not lose time
girls with no experience
but can be very interesting.
God once again!
- You are a real bitch.
- It is not.
Maybe we should call it to
I feel really.
Yeah, totally.
You should say that it felt
it is
a true bitch!
The train leaves the staþie love.
All aboard!
That is perfect.
Feel the power.
Get your body to release
and your spirit ...
I can run through the veins.
Feel good and do not forget to breathe.
Respiraþia is important.
Let down your clothes and go to bed with me.
Come here.
Yes.
Cari move slow.
In and out.
Your body to be a recipient
for love.
Now to begin,
with the presentation.
That is lingum "is my name is Rama.
Hi Rama.
What is the name of Yoni yours?
Yoni mine?
Listen, why not ask?
Yoni ...
How you name?
I said nothing.
Breathe.
Now ask her.
Yoni ... how do you name?
Says that her name is Joni.
Joni.
Joni!
His name is Yoni Joni yours?
You know Katie, I thought that is something
particular, that you are you can better
but not take it seriously.
What?
I can not reveal if I learn.
No, I just think it only ...
is nervous, and make bad jokes
when angry.
Tell them you're sorry.
Okay, you convinced me.
We start with the cow?
No, I like my colon.
Muy bien, wheelbarrow.
Well.
Plate.
Pizza?
I a.
Well.
Cisco, I quickly put it?
No need to do this?
I feel the energy when passing
Lingum from the Yoni.
Excuse me.
I wonder how long you can do that.
Well, once took ten hours.
I have for ten hours. I have a deadline.
I love you.
I always loved.
I'm always thinking about you.
And i. ..
just love you.
No, I was ...
No, it is okay.
Is love.
Love is sweet.
It is a perfect union, and it is beautiful.
Well. It is available.
No, what?
You can be my grandfather. You can
I buy gifts for Christmas.
I want a Playstation 3.
Katie.
- You did it?
- No! He wanted to do 10 hours.
Hey.
I do not worry.
I have a plan.
Katie.
Here you are.
- I want to talk to you.
- Not now, Spencer.
Please let me out.
Katie.
But what, what you did on the exam
chemistry final?
I passed.
Rose, please, let me out.
I know that we can help with that,
if you want?
No, I'm sorry. There was ...
Girls, concentraþi sure.
Either stay here or leave.
Katie, please stay with us.
We'll be more fun.
Yes.
You mean we do sex?
That can work.
I suppose that we must present.
I'm Katie.
I do not think a lesbian.
God! What is this?
I don 't want.
Well, Katie is the faeces.
It fits!
No, wait! It's mine!
It's okay. Not I
worry.
You over?
No. It was the fourth time in an hour.
You must go, then.
Great. My father will reach about
in half an hour
so you have time.
Come on.
Half an hour?
Hey ...
I know you are on Todd.
I think it was in our school,
but I did not see any.
We?
- I do not know what to do with it.
- Love you and me.
Make me your bitch, right?
I promise you that after a fire.
But now I need it.
You were at our school?
No, my sister was.
Love you me.
Well.
You are my bitch.
I'm sorry, do not even know
what to say.
Say what you want, only to be filthy
Maltrateazã me, ugly.
Modificatoarele mixture.
There are better uses modificatoarele.
As in, "said an ugly"
or you love me hard. "
- Who cares?
Who cares? I'm sick of people
not interested to talk
good English.
The first time Rose and penis and
now you!
Do not you understand English correctly
is the civilized society?
Yes, Mrs. teacher.
I so tepþi to triumph without
you know grammar?
- Yes.
- Really?
How will you observe if you
English words are correct?
I love you and your brain,
goes astray.
You did it again. I hit the brain?
No.
So tell correctly.
When I love you, my brain
goes astray.
Accurate.
I have to use it to
My lecþiile private.
I'm sorry, Miss, I was
a very bad boy
and must be punished.
Now you can hit me?
You have a penis, so you hit me too.
Speaking of changes ...
Someone coming!
Haideþi children out.
Out!
What the hell?
I do not think you deserve the award for
best citizen
because today was a slut here.
Katie.
God.
Seth needs to see this.
Seth!
Katie!
Jeremy
I love you.
You are beautiful.
Figure ta ...
and tai breasts.
Your penis.
Katie, I never told you
I have a big penis.
Not so!
God.
It is a big penis!
Where?
How did I forget?
Yes, crabs.
It ... yes.
It's good.
How crazy!
Film. No! You stop it!
What are you doing? Please do not shoot.
Please, stop it up.
No go.
We can transform you into a star.
What are you talking?
10.85 bucks for a porno film.
That's a lot.
Take care, leave.
Do not be stupid Seth.
Look, give me the tape.
I have to pay for it.
Under any circumstances.
Why do this? Wanted to do
serious stuff.
It's fun. And then not
scandals here, or yes?
Spencer! Your fault.
I know.
Katie ...
Hey.
Here you are.
You are okay?
Katie ...
Nothing. No one and will
remembers nothing morning.
Well, it is something that will
all talk
all the time, and why? Who cares?
However, all are bad.
Now that you're so close
not applicable to renunþi.
What?
Yes. Had to renunþ three hours.
I can not do this.
That was the ugliest night
of my life.
You saw what happened there?
Yeah, I heard.
Not only that.
Everything! Everything!
What I?
Yet we can go back and to
to make this happen.
No, we can.
I do not want something you never.
I have to wait until we can reach
40 years to lose my virginity,
if necessary.
Rose ...
Thanks a lot for everything
your help, but ...
I think it's time to go.
And Ryan?
I do not know.
Katie ...
Damn.
Spencer Really, you think that Katie deserves
award for the best citizen?
No ...
I mean ... No, it does not.
It is my fault. What I did before,
she makes it.
Think about that and they lose
virginity?
I do not like to sleep with Ryan Lambert.
And everyone and you do not think Ryan
would not do it with a virgin.
What? No!
-Where did you hear that?
- We all know ...
less you.
Damn.
I'm so stupid.
Of course it is for Ryan.
Always was and a.
I knew. I knew that Ryan was the soul
My pair.
Kiss That proved it.
He will be the first.
Let's go after some punch.
- Spencer, are you okay?
- Yes.
Spencer ...
If you want to go back to her,
know good shape.
What?
Just fudge the votes in my favor
and I have to do what you want.
Whatever.
And nobody should want to tie.
Shit ... Katie?
I'm sorry, I only came
after my bag.
Why are you naked?
I changed clothes for
I have puke on me.
- Where you going?
- I'm going after my bag.
Do not go home. I want to do it now.
We do now.
But you said ...
I've said before and, not forget.
What?
Nice tits, Katie.
- What þâþe beautiful.
- Ryan.
Ryan.
I always thought at the time
this.
Yeah, and me.
A quick felaþie.
- Yes, it's good.
- I gotta go to the bathroom.
Well.
- I need the bathroom.
- Sure.
If we abandon an island
I have no problems with it.
- Really?
- You are a good boy.
I came back.
Not understand.
Chelsea and everybody.
Ryan, I'm sorry, not even
I do not like it.
Well, Friday.
Where were we? A blow job.
Today was the most crazy night
of my life.
I swear. I do not know what it could
happen.
Shit.
Heart monitor is the grandfather.
Damn, sunaþi 911.
God, what the hell!
I suck her grandfather.
Kill him!
God!
Katie, you came back.
You must go. I need
my bag.
What happens? Where were we?
Only ... it's time.
No.
What happens?
May I not love you?
Yes, sure.
Just ...
Make love to me now.
Now.
Ryan ... Ryan.
What happens?
I do not know.
I'm sorry. I thought that would
be different.
That that kiss.
Kiss?
That kiss of class and ASEA.
It was surprising.
So passionate.
Mean that we will be together
forever.
I do not remember.
I'm sorry.
You must go.
Goodbye Ryan.
Goodbye, Katie. Have a nice summer.
My bag.
You are gay?
No ... yes.
Well, technically are bisexual.
You are gay.
Forgive me for not told you. I
to know all.
Ryan, I would not tell anyone.
Damn. Hey, you have to say
anyone, right?
Katie, Katie!
Rose, I am. Are out in front.
I need a minute.
To be two.
Here you are.
- You must speak with you.
- Hi Spencer.
Katie, listen.
I should not say. I know.
I behaved like a madman
tonight.
Yes, but ...
All the shit that I did!
I can not believe I've killed
bãtrânelul on that.
It was very bad.
Yesterday I was not upset about that
I was the best in class.
Not even we appreciated what we had.
I mean ...
sure we lost scholarship and everything.
Very good.
Morality clause.
Yes.
I so worry about that.
This box of Seth,
"Memories of High School.
Katie Powers.
How did you get it?
I negotiated with Seth.
Can not believe it.
Best scenes are with me and Chelsea
bedroom.
Thanks.
Yes.
You!
You suck it my grandfather.
Jeremy, I'm sorry. It was a
accident.
I wanted to kill him.
Do not you killed.
Do not you killed grandfather.
You healed. You woke up.
- To exit from the coma it.
- Yes?
Yes, it's a new chance.
It is the Good Sam, room 1321,
if you want to visit.
Katie, listen.
Tonight I realized that ...
not want to be your friend.
Spencer.
I mean ...
It was you.
Yes.
Why never ...?
Ryan and I used
same costumaþie that day
and I saw that you were so happy
when you saw that he ...
I am gone.
- Spencer!
- Should I have to say.
I love you.
I always loved.
Spencer ...
But Chelsea and you, tonight ...
Keep it. A to appear on CNN with this.
Seth, wait. A to do what you want.
Look.
Chelsea, about what you said
May now ..
How can be sure that the directory
we will catch?
Spencer, I can not.
I sucked it last year.
How do you think I was the best?
To my notes?
Chelsea, I do not think that you're in
still the best in class.
Seth, what are you doing?
Let's go!
You are sure that you're ready?
Yes.
And me.
What the hell?
- I'm sorry.
- No, Spencer. It's okay.
I mean, after so long
of waiting, an hour in addition there is nothing.
Katie ...
What?
You gre it's qualification.
God, yes.
Yes.
- Katie.
- Tell me Spencer.
I do not think that will have to
wait an hour.
It is beautiful.
I did it.
Translation: Ang3l