Good night sir.
Hey Miss.
Oh, thanks god someone is here.
Please, l need your help.
My car always break down.
l just need to use the phone.
This area is restricted.
But there is no where from miles
Miss, no.
Let me help you.
Lar, l'm on vacation.
Sit down, have a pastry.
Look, we have a situation
What about Malcolm?
-He's in Berlin.
No, he's back in the States
May l get you something?
No, thank you.
l have another one of these.
You sure you don't want a pastry?
Tell me.
Calina, she's a high tech thief. She'd
been slipping us information for years
Now she required some critical information
on the reactionary party on the mafia
l need you to have the extraction.
Her cover.
You leave for Solvakia tonight.
You meet her at the boarder.
and take her to Munich
You'll be out of the country
before the goverment know what's up.
We're going by train?
The airport is too high low,
the other will blow.
Here's the down payment, 50,000.
American unmarked.
There is the rest,
once she delivered the coder
l need idea how to explain
this to my wife.
No
You can't go running off.
l'm not running off.
l've got time off from the hospital.
You don't see them calling me
You were away for 2 days.
-You think l can taking vacation?
l don't know.
-June, July you're in Washington.
We postponed so many times we have
to pulled the kids out of school
They are important clients.
They all are.
When do we get to be important?
You and the kids... are my life.
My life.
Come on.
Why take the train?
Why can't you take the flight?
No, we're not flying.
ls too heavy to leave the ground.
Look, l'm sorry, okay?
You'll miss your birthday.
l know.
We need to spent more time together.
l love you.
l'll be back soon Okay?
l'll promise.
l love you.
l love you too.
And you stay out of trouble, okay
Show me what you got.
Good, one more time.
Come on, faster.
Yeah, that's right.
Love you.
l love you dad.
Who are you?
What did you expect?
l said who are you?
Jack Christop.
Go on to the stage.
Put your hands where l can see them.
Move to the light now.
Keeps your hands where l can see them.
Walk toward the light.
l wouldn't trust you if you come in
authorised. Show me your l.D
You're sitting on them.
l.D.
Where's my money?
Here's your money,
and your passport.
We are taking the 6 o'clock to Munich
Let's get a few things straight Jack.
You don't tell me what to do.
l don't need you.
l don't want you.
This way.
No, is my show.
Come on.
l'm going up.
Hold the fire!
Don't shoot it, don't shoot it.
Let's move out of here.
Sorry.
Get down.
Don't look back, keep walking.
Yeah, right. You want me to play cool
after you blew half of the city?
Where are you going?
l'm going to the ladies' room.
The situation calls for little...Venice.
Except for the man
who don't understand,
Make it quick.
You call this an easy job?
Fast and easy huh?
Something when wrong?
You know what l said.
How many time do you want me to ask?
You'll make that train.
Give me an hour.
Do what ever you need to do,
to get that train at 6
You hear me?
Just get across that boarder.
You got it.
By the way, l won't be needed this
What do you want?
Ladies and gentlemen.
We'll stop at Berlin...
Go on then.
Here.
Excuse me...
Yes sir.
l'd like to change compartment.
Yes sir...
We would like one of the large bed...
This is a very special trip for us.
Thank you ma'am.
l can move it to 1B.
ls in the next cart, please follow.
So, you're a musician? Huh?
Musician?
And you're pretty insight for it.
lt must be very interesting.
All the songs...and such.
Yeah...is amazing l can keep...
lt all straight in my head.
Excuse me.
Shot out? Bad luck mate, l'm Swally.
Bob Sterling. Nexus oil.
-Really? l'm in oil too.
Really, few bites
You know l hope you can load me
by cargo. Look like they threw it all
l've got some pictures,
you wanna take a look?
Not really, bartender, bring my
partner another drink would you?
You got a good sense of humour.
Nice?
Railways Control Center
Linz Austria
Train 681, you are now being trapped
by the railway society
We've just crossed the toughter
boarder on the Easten block
That's the first step.
ls the hardest.
Let's celebrate, l'm getting champagne.
My job is to give you a life.
Am l under house arrest? ln jail?
You sound like just like my son.
l'm very sorry friend.
But you don't know where she is.
l know she did some
relieve work in Bosia.
They told me she could be
heading back for a spell
You don't have a phone number.
Address or e-mail..fax
l've lost it didn't l?
They told me she came to
this ferry train 3 weeks ago.
l know it sound cheesey but...
You could say l'm falling into
a true love footstep.
What a beautiful story.
Beautiful? Beautiful?
Hey, bartender, line him up here.
Two more up here would ya? Thank you.
These are on me.
-ln fact all the drinks tonight are on me.
Conductor told me, lf you pick up my bar
tag. You can switch compartment.
Sweet.
Miss, can l put this up there?
No, no, no. l saved for the last
10 years to buy this.
Okay, keep it right there.
Thank you.
Alright.
Nastaha.
l appreicated.
Thank you sir.
All cleared...All cleared.
We are ready.
Take our position. be calm. Be cool.
You got it.
How's the compartment?
Comforty
William,
you better be ready.
Cell phone blocked, over.
Are you sure you don't want
another drink?
No.
You're no fun.
You know that?
l don't have to be.
l'm married.
Really?
l like married men.
l bet you do.
Excuse me.
Sorry.
Who is it?
Ticket?
One moment please.
l'm coming, l'm coming.
Mary.
Happy birthday.
l can't believe you...
l can't believe you did this.
Suprise?
Suprise!
Say hi to the camera dad.
Here, here, open it.
The is my new client.
You're new client?
l'm Corina.
And what exactly do you do?
l'm an antiquarian.
Antiquartian.
lnteresting.
And you're helping my husband?
Mary, let me explain.
Okay, start by explain by who is that?!
ls nothing.
You're right, you're right.
l'm over reacting.
My husband got a prostitute at one am.
She's not a prostitute.
You know what hurt the most,
you act like you're upset to leave us
l was upset. l'm still am.
Don't! Don't
Mary, please listen to me.
l love you, that's the truth.
l and the kids will get off the
train at the next stop
l'm leaving the train to save my
marriage. Be back in 5 minutes
l hope l didn't cause you any problems.
Lock the door.
Where is she?
Where's who?
l don't know what you
are talking about.
Check again.
This way, move it!
Wake up! Wake up. Come on.
Everybody out!
What is going on?
Whu are they yelling?
Who's that lady with dad?
Move!
What the hell are you doing?
ls alright, take it easy.
Move!
Please, my kids are on this train...
Sit down.
-Quiet.
Sit down, or you'll never see the kids.
Just calm down.
She's not on the train sir.
Of course she is.
Let the first class passengers
in the bar
l'll be there in a minute.
Move it!
Stop!
There are my kids.
They are my kids.
Are you okay?
He is alive to see you.
l don't have anything.
Hurry up.
Keep them calm.
Stop. What are you doing?
l have to get off.
No.
Fuck you, l'm getting off.
My family
Fuck you,
l have to get to Munich
You are killing yourself.
ls better then have Mason getting
his cold hands on me.
Mason?
He's here, on this train.
lf he find me, l'm dead.
Shit!
Give that back to me.
What the hell is this?
None of your business.
Don't
Some kind of drug?
What is it?
You will gas everyone on the train
What are you doing with it?
They called it the SP43.
ls a mutated strainer pot
You can kill alot of people with this.
Does Ross know?
Of course, he is buying me
a ticket to eternal life
l'm finding my family.
l'm keeping this
[ Skipped item nr. 269 ]
French 1800.
No!
Hello my fellows.
l need to relocate a cheaper gold mine.
l'm not here to make a political statement
ln a matter of fact l'm not here
to make any statement at all.
l'm looking for someone.
A woman by the name
of Corina Constantine
Any of you mens can remember her?
He was accompanied by a man.
They're on the train.
ln fact, one of you know where.
You maybe.
Please don't not test my revolve
l now ask you once again.
Has anyone seen the people
l've described?
Well, if you don't know...
You don't know do you?
Well if one of you had
a sudden memory flash.
Please let me...
or one of my associate know.
You got 20 minutes, sweep the train.
Check the toilet, the baggage. Find'em
Behide you.
See you can't find them these days.
Hand them over.
l don't have anything.
ls that to insult my intelligence?
Natasha
She doesn't have anything
Check him.
ls not it.
That's more like it.
Those are mine.
Oh god.
l'm dead.
We're all dead.
No!
Henry...
ls okay.
l'm gonna die.
You are not going to die.
Trust me, we still have job to do.
None of you remember science class.
Let me remind you that the wild
Liquid is highly infected we can
and going to make an antidote
Why do you think is so valuable? But we
must proceed as exactly as planned
lf you don't, l will kill you.
We have a baggage,
Copy that sir,
l'm 15 minutes up
Mason, l'm so sorry.
Natasha, is okay.
l'll take care of you.
Throw her off the train.
And kill him.
Get up yourself.
Come on pal, you're tough right?
Come on, show me what you got.
They will kill us all.
No way, they've got guns then...
What are you gonna do with me?
l haven't decided yet.
l could keep you around
And throw you over the track like Mrs Christop
ls there a problem here?
She's scared that's all.
ls un-polite to stare.
You're hurting me Mason.
l wouldn't do that would l, Carina?
You think you can do this
job on your own?
Mason, please.
l found you, you are nothing but
a cheap circus hosting the locals
l made you what you are.
l know. l'm sorry.
l'm gonna stop.
l gave you everything.
And this is how you repay me?
Give me another chance.
Please Mason, we were good together
l can make it up to you.
l missed you.
Please, please don't kill me.
l do what ever you say.
l'm not one of them.
You're that conductor.
Yes, sir.
l need your help.
l need to get to the engine.
to take control of this train.
l can't make it up there sir.
My leg.
But l can help.
l know everything about this train.
They're stopping.
l'll get out of here.
You guys sit down.
Train 681, you are making a unschedule
stop. Are you having problem?
Vincent, tell me how to control this
You're heating up.
l'll get you some water.
Where do you think you're going?
l just need some water, for my kids.
Are you alright?
Pull the pressure.
Got it.
Find the fuel compresser.
Now stop the engine by pressing
the red button to go right
lt is too much.
What the hell is going on?
Slow down, okay?
We have to keep a low profile on this.
Low profile? Mason is on this train.
Where are you?
ln the engine.
l'm trying to keep this train moving.
Okay...good
You'll have back up in no time.
You should know that...
Hello? Hello?
Something is really wrong.
We're screwed man,
everybody is getting sick at once.
Just shut up, you're not the
only one scaring your pal
Terrorism plus sickness,
equal biologial war
Sir.
l'm a doctor
l bet medical school didn't
pay you for this.
What is it?
Tell me what you professional
opinion is, doc.
We're fucked!
l can't help these people if you
keep riding them up.
Maybe we should all remain
calm then
Cos pretty similar we are all knocking
at the fucking gates
Mason.
You want to go out on your own?
Fine.
You're on your own.
You bastard, don't you fucking
keep me here.
Don't leave me.
ls hard to say isn't it?
ls time.
How are you feeling?
l'll hope you end this painful.
Fuck you.
You've already did.
Vincent, we're not stopping
Kill them, get all the money.
We got the wall hiding.
Slow down.
He's not here.
Tell me why we're going fast?
l don't know, it start on it own.
Get back to the air, follow this train.
Yes.
The engine is leaking.
Fix it.
She was the love of my life.
l'm having problem down here.
Copy that.
Damn it.
Put it down now!
Get to the roof.
Fuck!
l'll take care of her.
You make sure he's dead this time.
l want his head!
That is it, you lot are out of heer!
l want you out!
You, move it come on.
Help me.
Are you okay?
Yeah, l'm fine. Just a cold.
Look, l'm here to help you.
Just get her a glass of water.
Yeah.
Mum, help me.
Oh baby.
We need to pumpm liquid into them.
Fruit juice or water
Put all the bar towels and anything else
you can find to make cold compresser
Alright, you got it.
NATO Regional headquarters
Bonn, Germany.
Jack. how was the vacation?
l'm on train 681
From Munich.
We've been hijacked by Mason
Any idea why?
3 viles of the B43.
We have reports they stole
it from the goverment.
Sir, is been confirmed on this train.
Did you contact Lar?
Yeah, there had been an explosion
My god, do you have the viles?
l've done everything l can to get them.
Unless you recover it,
and stop this train.
l'm in the proceeding sir.
We got to clear the track now,
Yes sir,
And call the world health organisation
He's up here.
Kill him!
Are you okay?
Yeah, l'm okay.
Do you know what's going
on round here?
l'm not sure.
Everyone is sick at the
same time but...
l think it might be smallpox.
Smallpox?
Wasn't that wiped out?
ln 1973,
Christop is dead.
Are you sure?
Yeah, l pushed him out of the
train out of his cycle.
No way he could survive.
You better be right.
What about Corina?
No sign.
l need those vaccine in me.
l'll be down into my nicker soon.
The young one is gonna suffer.
You can cover yourself up if you want.
Most countries still denotculating
small pox in 1979
We have our shots.
So our system still have the
traces of the vaccine
But any point after that have
absolutely no protection.
Are you saying we're safe,
we can't get it
No, no, no, no.
ls just been delay.
Mum, get over here.
l need some room,
l need some room.
No, get ice.
You need to go and help her.
l can't go.
You need to help me.
l'm afraid.
Come on.
No, no, no
Come in...
What's going on?
Mum...
Let me of of here, there must be
some one on this train
You're wasting bullet.
Give me now!
Help me stop this train.
The engine is on fire.
Get out of there!
Yeah.
Happy birthday Christop.
You got 2 minutes,
you go to compartment 5 B
l don't like to hurt women and kids,
but l will when l have to.
Don't come any closer,
l'll shoot you.
l swear to god, l'll shoot you.
You got the vile.
l'll kill you!
You're sick.
lf you had let me go.
Everything would be okay.
l would be fine.
Listen, with the viles,
We can cure you and everybody esle
ls too late.
No is not.
You got to trust me.
Christop, 30 seconds.
l'm gonna make things right.
What's going on?
The drunken moron, hasn't stop.
Stop the train!
There's no way to avoid a collision.
Just a few seconds to go.
Put that weapon down.
Drop the clear.
Let them go.
l've got a proposition for you.
As you pretty much made to my entire crew
l need someone to find
Carina and the viles.
Fail, l'll shoot your whole family.
Just to let you know l mean business,
Or l'll shoot the boy right now.
Wait, l've got it.
l don't believe you.
You let Ethan go.
Give it to me first.
l must say you make
a challenging journey.
Why are you doing this?
l like long vacation.
What about our deal?
Our deal?
Getv the boy!
Fucking!
Ethan!
Be careful.
Ethan?
Ethan!
Leave it.
No, our son is dead?
We have to go.
Look after her.
l'm sorry, l'm so sorry.
l love you so much.
The train is only 15 miles from Munich.
My order are to be perpare
for the worst.
Are the troops in place?
Yes sir, if they reach the bridge
We have a squat of ship in place
loaded with chemical bombs
The bomb hit to destroy the virus
Dr. Reno
These is our only choice.
lf this virus get out.
Millions will die.
They will, they have to.
But...but the engine?
Leave the engine,
let's just disconnect it.
Come on, come on. l'll show you.
Your husband is a good man.
How long have you worked with him?
Since last night.
Your husband is loyal a man.
Get this disconnected,
you have to use the handbrake.
Help me.
The brake.
Any words from Christop?
No.
Get me commandment.
l can't give you anymore time.
Take your position over.
On my signal.
By the bridge.
Easy now.
Ethan?
ls this what you want?
Ethan.
Get out!
Ladies and gentlemens.
Please remain calm
As you can see the train,
is being attended.
Once tenting is compeleted.
you will disembarked from orderly fashion
We are estabishing 14 area
of the side of the tracks.
Where you all receive medicate care
We appreicated your patience.
And your co-operation.
Ladies and gentlemens.
Please remain calm
Once tenting is compeleted.
you will disembarked from orderly fashion
Ethan, you were so brave.
l'm proud of you.
l love you,
Thanks dad.
ls going to be okay sweetheart.
She is right, everything will be fine.
Dr. Reno
Yeah?
l'm doctor Madline Christop.
They all have high fever
So we monitor their temperature
around the clock
Do you know any of the virus
can be recover?
The virus plague. More then enough
to cure everyone affected.
You're better now you hear?
Once you're out of the hospital
l can buy you a new flute.
lt was a violin.
Shot down again mate?
l don't think so.
Listen, l'm sorry.
l was behaving badly up there.
ls okay.
Once we all get out of here,
l'll buy you a drink.
You buy a drink and my lady friend
What?
The ltalian?
She worked for world
health organisation.
Jack.
You finally made it.
You came here quickly.
The virus, you have it?
Yes l do. l just have one question.
How much are you gonna
get for the virus?
What are you talking about?
l don't know what you are talking about
No, l'm thinking clearly.
Mason, plan wasn' impossible
without the inside information
Mason is a top much equivalent
ls more then that, you told us
to get on train 681
There was no other op.
There's always an op.
And Corina
This is not the first time it happened.
And explain to me how Mason knew
which compartment you booked us in
You're dislusional, you're delusional.
Delusion is...
ls a gift.
Arrest this man
With pleasure.
Take him away.
So happy birthday huh?
Did l tell you how
much l love you.
No.
Let's go and see the kids.