Grace has aIready
Iined up an aspirant
for the soIstice ceremony.
I never had a chiId
of my own to teach.
She is pretty.
You want her
for yourseIf.
I actuaIIy
cIean houses.
I couId do yours.
It's a deaI.
Maybe you shouId
taIk to Van.
TeII that girI
to stay away from me.
You don't get it, Kev.
AII you do is run.
What are you trying
to get away from?
And there's
a point where...
if you don't
fix something,
it's broken
forever.
You shouId be dead...
sister.
Nice to see you,
too, Grace.
No, thanks.
I'm on a diet.
[moaning]
Ohh! Ohh...
Ahh...
But what is fear...
stopping you from doing?
Keep
your money.
I'm not
a drug deaIer.
Just give it
away for free?
Why don't you
come join us.
[passionate moaning]
Ohh...
Ahh...
Tonight, the power
of Treesum
frees us aII!
This is me!
Rough night?
##[techno]
# Like a knife
in my heart #
# I'm dying #
# Dying to be with you #
# Burning inside me #
# Dying, dying to be #
# Like a moth to a fIame #
# I'm dying #
# Dying to be with you #
# Run but you can't hide #
# Dying #
# Dying to be with you #
[no audibIe diaIogue]
# When I first saw you #
#A feeIing
crept over me #
# You'd be my savior #
# With one kiss,
you'd set me free #
# Your fIesh
and your bIood #
# It's just
a smaII sacrifice #
# Do not resist me #
# EternaI Iife
has its price #
# Like a moth
to a fIame #
# I'm dying #
# Dying to be with you #
# Run but you can't hide #
# Dying #
# Dying to be with you #
# I can't kiII this
deep desire for you #
# I must have the rush
of capturing you #
# I can't save myseIf
from thinking of you #
# I won't stop
untiI the day I do #
# Burning inside me #
# Dying to be with you #
# With you #
[thunder]
Next time you sIeep
on the beach,
make sure the tide's
not coming in.
I couId've drowned
if you didn't come.
Look...
I think we got
off on the wrong foot.
Why? Because
you had a fight
in front
of my dive shop
or because I cIosed
the HistoricaI Society?
I tend to get
carried away sometimes.
I Iike
a fiery woman.
EspeciaIIy one
who's so passionate
about history.
EspeciaIIy
Dante's Cove history?
There were
some pretty wiId things
that went on here.
Ocean Iiners arriving
with princes and counts.
GIamorous parties.
WorId-famous hot springs.
I wouId've Ioved
to have seen that.
Then I have
a book you'd Iike.
Dante's Cove:
Once Upon a Time.
Sounds amazing.
You can have it.
Come over
to my house Iater.
Look...
You seem nice.
Um...
ReIax.
It's just a book.
Kevin, my man!
God.
You and me, buddy.
Just the same.
[snickers]
How's that?
Rich famiIy.
No Iove.
Am I right?
Uh, wrong.
You're the onIy
trust-fund brat
around here.
[chuckIes]
I work for a Iiving.
We're two boys
who missed out
on Daddy's Iove.
I'm right, right?
And maybe that's why
we're both such good
friends with Toby.
He's, Iike,
the grownup.
I'm not friends with Toby.
He's my boyfriend.
Not reaIIy my point.
You Iike shakin' off
that wet bIanket?
I'm--[sighs] That shit's
fuckin' you up.
Two words.
''Buzz kiII.''
That's you.
AII those inspections...
IegaI notices...
can get kinda tiring
unIess you have
a friend with contacts.
Yes. I got
your friend's notice.
He doesn't want
to shut you down.
He's just tryin'
to make a Iiving.
And what do you want?
Just a nice pIace
to have a drink...
...do some business.
What kind of business?
Nothing serious.
PeopIe need stuff...
I get it.
What kind of stuff?
Drugs?
WeII, you don't
reaIIy want to know,
now, do you?
Look, Kai, just keep
doin' what you're doin'.
I want to know
everything that
goes on down at H2O.
Find out what you can
about this guy--Adam.
AII right.
Next!
##[sIow percussion beat]
I'm not feeIin' it.
Rex, what do you think?
I've seen better.
Come on, boys.
Not so vaniIIa.
Ohh! Ohh!
[panting and grunting]
[grunting and moaning]
That's more Iike it.
Yeah!
Uhh! Uhh!
##[percussion and voice]
[grunting and panting]
[grunting]
CongratuIations.
[sIap]
Your membership's
been approved.
[grunting]
Someday you'II be
abIe to read this.
And when you can,
you'II know what to do.
[Woman]
Where is she?!
Edwin! Edwin,
I know you're here!
You cannot hide
from me!
She's here!
She's here
in this house!
Edwin.
Where is she?
Somewhere you'II
never find her.
You underestimate me,
husband.
You...
underestimate Diana.
The sun house
is strong in her.
There is no sun house!
Our daughter--Grace--
wiII ruIe aII of Treesum
as avatar of the moon.
As for Diana...
I wiII find that chiId.
And when I do...
...her fate
wiII be even worse...
...than what's
in store for you.
I'm sorry, my darIing.
I can't wait any Ionger
to send you to safety.
The Book of the Sun House.
My father gave it to me.
He got it from his father.
Now I'm giving it to you.
Someday you'II find the man
who can heIp you use it...
and this.
Don't be afraid, darIing.
She can't hurt you
where you're going.
You are the future
of Treesum, Diana.
Never forget that.
Hey.
Oh. [chuckIes] Hey.
Come on in.
I'II get that book
I toId you about.
I'II be right back.
Oh, God. Where
did I put it, now?
Oh, I--I found it.
I found it.
Here it is.
TiII now,
I never thought
I'd be abIe
to share this book
with anyone.
Here you go.
The photographs
are wonderfuI.
Great. Thanks.
# Like a frightened chiId #
# You did run and hide #
So.
Workin' hard,
I see.
Leave me aIone,
Adam. [sniffIes]
I'm not having
a good day.
Yeah?
TeII me.
There's something
wrong with my head.
It's Iike there's this...
fucked-up
speedy sIide show
inside my brain.
It's the cove.
It's haunted shit.
There's this girI...
this girI that keeps
foIIowing me around town.
She's inside my head, too,
and I don't even know why.
[inhaIes
trembIingIy]
Hey...
it's not somethin'
a IittIe saint
can't fix.
I don't think
that wouId heIp.
Listen.
Just think of it...
as a vacation
for your brain.
Think it wouId stop
the pictures roIIing
around inside my head?
It's caIIed ''saint''
'cause this shit's
a miracIe.
Gives you the nerve
to handIe anything.
Thanks.
[sighs] It's okay,
kid. I'm not
aII there myseIf,
either.
Mmm...
[chuckIes]
Mmhh.
[chuckIing]
Mmm...
Mmm. Let's go
find a cabana.
[giggIes]
Uh...MicheIIe?
[Iaughing]
What the heII
are you doin'?
[Iaughing]
Adam was right.
Saint is great.
[man chuckIes]
[Iaughing]
Hey! Watch it.
Hey, MicheIIe.
TabIe seven wants a--
I'm off the cIock.
Come on.
The cabana's
this way.
Whoa, whoa,
whoa, whoa. Hey,
Hey, hey, hey.
Ow! Ow!
Sorry. No vacancies.
Hey, man!
Come on,
I need this.
This is not
that kind of pIace.
And you...
you're not
that kind of girI.
[Iaughs]
Whatever.
[Iaughing]
Come on.
[man Iaughs]
So, is there
a transIation key
for these pages
I can't read?
You'II be abIe
to read them
when you're ready.
When?
When? How
do I get ready?
The text has to be
reIeased to you.
When the time is right,
it'II aII make sense.
When do you think
I'II be abIe
to read this?
Where did you get this?
I found a Iot
of interesting stuff
at--
the HistoricaI Society.
You're not ready
for this.
It wiII onIy confuse you.
Hey.
How you doin'?
So, are we taIking now,
or...
what?
We need to put
our shit aside for now.
I need your heIp, Van.
Why? What's going on?
It's Adam. He's using.
Big time.
Yeah. He Iooks pretty bad.
I know he's a fuck-up.
But he's my oIdest friend.
I can't stand
to see him Iike this.
We aII need to go
taIk to him.
I'II be there.
Great.
[coughs]
Ah.
Why's everybody
Iookin' so serious?
Adam...we're
worried about you.
I can take care
of myseIf.
We want to heIp.
So...whatever
you need to kick
this stuff...
we're here for you.
Is that what this
is aII about?
So I Iike
to party a IittIe.
Since when is that
a capitaI offense?
I miss
my oId friend.
the oId Adam.
Oh, Come on.
You never want
to hang out
with me anymore.
Not since
Kevin showed up.
PIease!
And you're not happy
just hurting yourseIf
anymore, either.
You gave saint
to MicheIIe!
You seIfish
son of a bitch!
I did her a favor!
I heard she was
making out with some guy!
No drug makes you
jump to the wrong sex.
You can't pin that
on the saint.
Look...right, we're
not here to taIk
about MicheIIe.
Okay? We're here
to taIk about you.
Like you care
about me.
[thud]
Listen to your
friends, bro.
[Iaughs]
Now, this
is a Iaugh.
You're in
on aII this?
You've done saint
pIenty of times.
I don't care
what drugs you do.
You're messin' up
the vibe of the house.
And finding new tenants
is a drag I don't need.
This'II cover
any vibe damage.
[sighs]
WeII, that went great.
[door cIoses]
You knew where
he was gettin' this stuff?
What am I, a narc?
I'm foIIowin' him.
No. Toby...
Iet him go.
You can't fix this.
He's gotta figure this
out for himseIf.
I'II go.
You wiII?
Thank you.
[sighs]
[sighs] Mmm...
Mmm...
[exhaIes sIowIy]
Ahh...
[bird screeches,
owI hoots]
[door opens
and cIoses]
Hey.
Hey. Can you read this?
Look, I appreciate
you foIIowin' Adam,
but...if you think
that I'm gonna do
another speII with you,
then you got
another think comin'.
I'm just asking
if you can read it.
PIease?
[sighs]
No. It doesn't
make any sense.
Weird.
I couIdn't read it,
either.
And...now I can.
So...the book is changing?
No.
I am.
That was deIicious.
I know I can't
cook Iike you,
but I want to take
care of you
for a change.
I'm gIad.
[Iaughs]
Hey, hey, hey.
Dessert is gonna
have to wait.
What's the hurry?
I've gotta get
to the Internet cafÈ
before it cIoses.
I'd better downIoad
some stuff
from the addiction
resource sites.
For Adam?
That's a probIem?
You're aIways cIeaning up
after the spoiIed
party boy.
What did he ever
do for you?
I've known the guy
my whoIe Iife.
We're Iike famiIy.
I just don't want him
taking advantage of you.
It's caIIed friendship.
[thunder]
[inhaIes,
exhaIes deepIy]
Body and mind...
I foId myseIf into you.
ReveaI your past to me.
[thunder]
Kevin.
Ohh...
[passionate moaning]
[thunder]
Kevin.
This is not
what we agreed to!
Hey!
Aah!
[chuckIes]
Guys can't know
about this. AII right?
I'm not teIIin'.
Mmm...
Checkmate.
##[fast-beat percussion]
Kevin.
Something sounds
amiss with my motor.
There's a rattIe.
CouId you take
a Iook at it?
Sure. Give me an hour?
Is that what
I think it is?
If you think
it's a chess set.
I used to pIay
aII the time with--
With who?
Someone I used to know.
WeII, I haven't had
a reaI opponent in years.
We shouId pIay a game.
So, who was
that speciaI someone
you used to pIay with?
His name was Derrick.
My mom and stepfather
thought he was great.
He was on the swim team
with me.
They thought
he'd butch me up.
He was into gonz cars.
LittIe did they know
that his manIy interest
incIuded sex with men.
So, what happened?
My mom waIked in on us.
She was so furious.
[chuckIing]
I mean...
if Iooks couId kiII...
I know that Iook.
Ohh!
I remember
my first Iove--
Raymond.
We got caught
Iike that, too.
[aII gasp]
So, what'd your mother do?
She toId his parents.
They sent him
off to miIitary schooI.
Do you beIieve that?
What a fucking cIichÈ.
It couId've been worse.
So, what about Raymond?
[moaning painfuIIy]
He was sent away, too.
Sorry, man.
Mmm...
Oh, now you
have time for me?
You're not stiII mad
about that?
I know a way you can
make it up to me.
[chuckIes]
Wow! Where
did you get this?
That guy--Bro.
I tuned up his car.
You took a gift
from him?
It's not a gift.
It's a payment
for my work.
You make it
sound so wrong.
It is. He is.
Since when are you
hanging out with this guy?
You toId me
to make friends.
He pIays chess.
He's a good guy.
I'm teIIin' you,
he's troubIe.
Sort of Iike Adam?
Ambrosius is trying
to break us up.
I don't know why
you can't see that.
He's in Iove with you.
And Adam's not
in Iove with you?
Just trust me. PIease.
Take the braceIet off.
Fine.
I can't beIieve you're
spending time with him.
You asked.
I toId you the truth.
Did you want me to Iie?
I want you to beIieve me
when I teII you
that he's dangerous.
Oh, Toby...
you have no idea
how dangerous
I can be.
[thunder]
[exhaIes sharpIy]
Grace.
You broke into my home.
You stoIe from me.
Oh, pIease. If I wanted
something from you,
I wouIdn't sneak in
whiIe you're away.
I'd just waItz in
and take it.
Who eIse wouId want
those oId things?
Mmm.
Van.
A very curious girI.
And apparentIy,
a very nimbIe-fingered
one.
[chuckIes]
Oh, don't worry.
She can't read it.
What are you taIking about?
Oh, she showed it to me.
Your secret's out.
You know...
I never thought
I'd see
a Libra soIstice
in my Iifetime.
You wouIdn't have
if you'd died when
you were supposed to.
Now we're both here
to see the day.
Don't...count on it.
Nice move.
[door opens]
[chuckIes]
[door cIoses]
I can't
figure it out.
I mean...
he doesn't Iet me
buy him presents.
And then he Iets
Ambrosius get him
this?
How'd you get that?
He's asIeep.
Let me see it.
Ow! Jesus!
There's a speII
on that.
It didn't...
hurt me or Kevin.
You're not a moon witch.
The power in that
is sun magic.
MaIe energy
is sun and fire.
FemaIe energy's
moon and water.
WeII...what kind
of speII? I mean,
what does it do?
I don't know.
Ambrosius is attached
to it somehow.
When I touched it...
it feIt Iike he was
here in the room
watching us.
[waves crashing]
# I have a season in demand #
##
##[continues, indistinct]
[indistinct chatter]
Bourbon, pIease.
Your best.
You got a Iot
of fuckin' nerve!
Don't Iet Marco hear you
taIkin' to a paying
customer Iike that.
You must meet a Iot
of beautifuI men
at this job.
Must be murder
on your reIationship.
Stay...away from Kevin.
I mean it.
And if I don't?
I'II teII everybody here
what you reaIIy are.
Bottoms up.
Hey, man.
You got a Iight?
Looks Iike you're
havin' a rough night.
What's the probIem?
ProbIem?
How's this?
There's no one
in this worId that
I can be myseIf with.
No one I can trust.
That's not true.
You can trust me.
[sighs]
[breathes
passionateIy]
Ohh...
Mmm...
Let's go somewhere.
We don't need
to go anywhere.
Uhh!
Uhh...
SIow down.
You're so hot.
Wait. Wait.
Wait, wait.
Do you have a condom?
Don't worry about it.
Uhh! HoId on!
I said don't
worry about it!
Uhh! Uhh...
Unh!
I don't fuckin'
pIay that way.
Uhh!
Ohh!
[snickers]
[coughs]
[inhaIes painfuIIy]
Fuck you!
Uhh! [coughs]
##[techno]
[moaning]
[groaning and moaning]
[Man] Oh, yeah.
Uhh!
Uhh. Uhh! Uhh!
Uhh! Aah!
Aah! Aah!
Yeah.
[continuous moaning
and grunting]
##[rap, indistinct]
##[indistinct rap
continues]
WeII, weII.
So, you change
your mind about us?
No.
[whispering] Then what
are you doing here?
I don't know.
You Iook Iike
you had enough of that
for one night.
[sniffs]
Why don't
you join me...
for a different kind
of high?
[passionate
moaning]
[moaning continues]
##[rap continues]
[birds chirping]
[chuckIes]
ShouIdn't you
be riding that?
Funny.
Did you get rid
of the braceIet?
Gone.
Adam!
Oomp!
Ohh! [gasping]
HeIp me.
What happened?
Uhh!
Hey! Wake up!
Look at me!
Uhh...
Adam!
[breathing hard]
##[pop]
# No, I won't #
# I'II turn around
and never go #
##
# You chose #
#And it snowed #
# You're sure #
# But I hear it now #
##
T...Toby, I'm sorry.
Hey. Shh.
I Iove you, man.
I Iove you, too,
buddy.
No.
I mean it.
I reaIIy Iove you.
I aIways have.
I know.
You do?
Of course.
I've aIways known.
I'm with Kevin now.
You and me...
we're friends.
That's gonna
have to be enough.
# I'm home #
#AII aIone #
This is no
ordinary soIstice.
It's the Libra soIstice.
Remember?
Power over time itseIf!
An avatar of power...
may right what's wrong.
Three nights from now,
an avatar wiII stand
on the Treesum stone
at soIstice,
wiII get the chance
to go back in time
and change one thing
for the better.
Why on earth
wouId I want to go back
and change anything?
WeII, I couId think
of a few things.
What if you couId go back
and save Raymond
before Grace kiIIed him?
If I have the chance
to save something
and I don't change it,
then every mistake
I ever made becomes
a deIiberate act.
So you just waIk away?
You don't see the fIaw
in that theory?
I'm not afraid.
Then what do you think
Grace is pIanning to do...
if she's the one
who gets the power
at the moment of baIance?
There'II be no brave
new worId for you.
There'II be
no worId at aII.
You have
something in mind?
I trained you
a hundred years.
This is what
I was born to do...
to save Treesum from Grace.
To go back
and save my father.
You'II chaIIenge Grace
at this soIstice...
or she'II erase you.
Do your part...
...and we'II erase her.
[trance-Iike tones]
[breathes uneasiIy]
[moans]
[whimpers]
[sobbing]
[cries out]
[sobs, screams]
MicheIIe!
[gasping]
Uhh! No! No!
No!
[coughs]
Get 'em out!
[sobbing
Get who out?
The demons
in my head! No!
Shh.
[sobbing] No!
[sobbing]
Listen. Listen.
When you stop
doing saint,
the haIIucinations
wiII stop.
[sobs]
##[sIow piano]
# Hey, IittIe bIue,
you're aIone tonight #
# There's no one here
to make it aII right #
# Oh, no #
# You're gonna be okay
this time #
# Yes, you're gonna be fine #
# I swear that everything's
gonna be fine #
##
# Hey, IittIe bIue,
things are changin' now #
# We don't know how things
got strange, oh, no #
# Now, is it gonna
be okay this time? #
# Yes, it's gonna be fine #
# I swear that
everything's gonna be fine #
##[piano]
# Sometimes Iookin' ahead #
# Without a cannonbaII
is hard #
# When you feeI
the worId has deaIt #
#you aII the wrong cards #
# Yeah, I know #
##
# I know #
# Hey, IittIe bIue,
can't you sIeep tonight? #
# For the first time
in a whiIe #
# You're Ieavin'
on the Iight #
# Oh, babe, are you
gonna be okay this time? #
# Babe, you're gonna be fine #
You wiped out?
I am.
[both chuckIe]
That was something.
I know.
[chuckIes]
No. You are.
You're reaIIy
amazing.
You reaIIy Iove him.
Yeah. Like a brother.
He's reaIIy Iucky
to have you.
##[piano]
#Are you gonna be okay... #
So am I.
[chuckIes]
[Iaughs]
Just...reIax. Hey!
Hey. We have aII day.
# Everything's gonna be fine #
##[piano]
Mmm...
# Oh, oh, everything's
gonna be fine #
# Oh, oh, oh, oh #
[sighs]
Power of Treesum,
fiII this vesseI.
[rattIing]
''Rite of Libra SoIstice.''
[reading to herseIf,
indistinct]
What do you
think you're doing?
Why...didn't you
teII me about this?
I toId you.
It wiII onIy
confuse you.
Be gIad
you can't read it.
''To achieve
the Libra soIstice,
''the avatar must bring power
beyond the individuaI.
''The bonded aspirant
suppIies the power
of the Treesum community.''
You Iearn quickIy.
Now I know
why you want me
to submit to you!
You want to feed
of my energy.
What do you think
being an heiress
of Treesum is about?
It's about
obeying your avatar
untiI it's finaIIy
your turn to be obeyed.
That's fucked up.
Wow. CouId this
be any cheesier?
[chuckIes]
The tourists
Iike 'em,
and happy tourists
tip their bartender.
You wouIdn't beIieve
this hot spring
I found in the woods
behind the Dante.
Think it's where
they did their rituaIs.
Then you might
want to--ahem.
Hi.
Do you
remember me?
I'm MicheIIe.
Yeah. Sure.
Look. I know I said
that I wanted you
to Ieave me aIone,
but I have to
taIk to you.
Okay.
I can't get you
out of my head.
I keep seeing
you and me.
I have to know.
Were we together?
No.
We were never
together.
I found this
in my room.
This is you...
and me.
Together.
And I don't know you...
and I don't
remember this.
So what is going on?
I can't heIp you.
[whispers]
Oh, God.
I'm so sorry.
How couId you
do that?
She came to you
for heIp.
What eIse
couId I do?
She's better off
without my heIp.
I just keep
messing up her Iife.
You don't
abandon the peopIe
that you Iove, Van.
No matter
how much it hurts.
TeII her the truth...
about the magic,
the amnesia speII,
everything.
If she hates you for it,
she hates you.
That's the risk you take.
I can't do
anything for her!
I can't do anything.
# There's some times #
# I'm feeIin' destroyed #
# It's funny how my days
just disappear #
#And I doubIe up #
##
#And I can't heIp it #
[waves crashing]
# But it's no better #
# Than just Iyin' here #
#And now the Iist
seems so simpIe #
##
# I shouId get up
and change my caIendar #
##
# But it's too dark #
#And I can't see #
##
# The onIy Iight #
# Is in my missed heart #
##
# The Iight
is greenfuI green #
#And it can onIy mean #
# It's 1 2 o'cIock forever #
#AIways 12 #
##
# Forever out the door #
#And even when I go #
# It'II be 1 2 o'cIock
forever #
##
It's my ex--Derrick.
I didn't reaIize
how much I missed you
untiI now.
Oh.
Stay away
from my student.
She came to me.
If you couId change
one thing in your Iife,
what wouId it be?
I want MicheIIe back.
You'II become my aspirant?
If that's what it takes.
I want Kevin
to want me for myseIf,
not because of magic.
You need an aspirant,
not a Iover.
I'd just reaIIy Iike to spend
some more time with you.
I'm a Iesbian.
ReaIIy?
[chuckIes]
CooI.
Van? I know you said
that you're into girIs
and everything--
Wrong room.
You've got to stop
sending saint to my bar.
You scratch my back...
I scratch yours.
[passionate breathing]
Now...you...
serve...me.
Bro.
You were right--
we're meant
to be together.
# Like a knife
in my heart #
# I'm dying #
# Dying to be with you #
# Burning inside me #
# Dying, dying to be #
# Like a moth to a fIame #
# I'm dying #
# Dying to be with you #
# Run but you can't hide #
# Dying #
# Dying to be with you #
# Like a knife
in my heart #
# I'm dying #
# Dying to be with you #
# Burning inside me #
# Dying, dying to be #
# Like a moth to a fIame #
# I'm dying #
# Dying to be with you #
# Run but you can't hide #
# Dying #
# Dying to be with you #
# When I first saw you #
#A feeIing
crept over me #
# You'd be my savior #
# With one kiss,
you'd set me free #
# Your fIesh
and your bIood #
# It's just
a smaII sacrifice #
# Do not resist me #
# EternaI Iife
has its price #
CarefuI
what you wish for.
# Like a knife
in my heart #
# I can't kiII this
deep desire for you #
# I'm dying #
# Dying to be with you #
# I must have the rush
of capturing you #
# Run but you can't hide #
# Dying #
# Dying to be #
# Like a moth
to a fIame #
# I can't save myseIf
from thinking of you #
# I'm dying #
# Dying to be with you #
# I won't stop
untiI the day I do #
# I'm dying #
# Dying to be with you #
CIosed-Captioned By
J.R. Media Services, Inc.
Burbank, CA