- It's undignified.
- Bollocks.
It's one of the reasons
our sperm counts are plummeting.
- More bollocks.
- It's against nature.
If a man and a woman are in a car,
the man should drive.
- Is this it?
- I think so.
You can drive back
if it makes you feel better.
Yes.
All right, lads?
Is your mum or dad about?
We don't have mums and dads.
We have elders.
Please go away.
- I have to present you with this.
- You have no jurisdiction here.
- Your authority is not recognised.
- I've got a job to do.
With regard to
the non-attendance of minors...
You don't exist. wait here.
This is Rossborough. 7312.
We have a... Oh, God.
Shooting. we have a man wounded.
Stony... Shit.
- 'What is the message?
- 'Rosie? '
- No,
'This is control. Over. what's going on? '
- Please don't.
'Hello? Rosie? Hello?
'Come in please. Rosie, come in please.'
And the Lord said,
"I will destroy man whom I have created
from the face of the earth."
'The Stonyhurst siege
moves into its second week
'with no immediate prospect
of resolution.
'Negotiators have failed
to establish rapport... '
- What are you doing?
- What does it look like?
Pete, why don't you...
These pans look like they haven't
been cleaned in ten years. Look at this.
Pete, it's me. Please, will you stop this?
I can't bear it any more.
Then keep the pans clean.
I do my side of things. You do yours.
Will you listen? I said I can't stand it!
Then leave.
Pete.
- This is... storage stuff.
- Not bad.
You'd get a wife and three kids in there.
- It's your room for when you stay.
- That's your doorbell.
- Yeah. Should get that changed.
You'll want to.
Hello.
Hello. I'm Beth. Jamie's sister.
Are you going to let 'em in or what?
It was at the crematorium.
There were a few people there.
- And some flowers.
- We missed you.
- Yeah, well, you know...
- Who wants milk?
Who wants it black?
- Conrad made us leave Mum's house.
- He was waiting for Mum to pass away.
Look, Beth, there's room...
- Peter, I told you!
- Show him yours!
What's he done to you?
Beth, has he hurt you?
- Let it go. And you.
- I can't let it go.
He's gone.
- He's not gone.
- That part of our life is over. Let it go.
With a deadlock in the siege,
the Home Office want us down there.
Our role is to consult,
support and prepare.
We'd be mad to get involved.
There are children in there.
Nobody's asking us to blow the place up
and slaughter the innocents.
Why else would they call us in?
What else can prepare me?
There's nothing to discuss. It's an order.
Comes as an order to me and that damn
well means it's an order from me to you.
And if you use your considerable
diplomatic skills to avoid any bloodshed,
nobody will be more delighted than me.
With regard to Pete,
I'm wondering if you were right
to block his return to Ops after Bosnia.
You must keep an eye on him.
Sir.
We never talked.
About what?
About me and you.
What about me and you?
- When we were having a...
- Sex.
Yeah.
And then you were shot.
And now we're not.
Henno found out. Said we should stop.
You agreed, so we stopped.
End of story. Lesson learned.
No cover for attackers
Within 60 metres of the building.
Power was cut, but they have
their own electricity generation,
water supply and appear
to have large reserves of food.
Security lighting, CCTV cameras
and lookouts covering all the angles,
posted 24/7.
This is their leader.
He calls himself Omega. We've
identified him as Donald Klissman, 38,
Gulf war veteran.
Probably came back with
Gulf war Syndrome, PTSD and God.
This is the sort of thing
he's been saying to our negotiator.
'Babylon the great, the mother of harlots
and abominations of the earth,
'has become the habitation of devils
for all nations.
'For all nations have drunk
the wine of her fornication.
'Kings have fornicated with her
and merchants have waxed rich
'through her abundant delicacies.'
'His small community of disciples
comprises eight children,
'from 16 down to six months,
'nine adult females
and at least 11 adult males.
'There are probably more.
A few have been identified.
'Misfits looking for answers, convinced
they've found them with Klissman.'
- 'Weapons? '
'we've seen assault
and sniper rifles and shotguns.
'They have purchased materials
from filling stations
'and hardware stores,
adequate to produce fire bombs
'and homemade PE4 and napalm.'
- 'We'll set up a DPA... '
- 'Any hostages? '
'Not that we're aware of.'
- Good, well, that...
- And negotiations?
- Sorry, sir. Go ahead.
- No, please.
Have negotiations thrown up
any demands or objectives?
Negotiations are indefinitely stalemated.
He just rants.
He doesn't seem to want anything.
Our position is we'll give them as long
as it takes for a peaceful resolution.
- What's your real position?
- We'd like it sorted ASAP.
The children are at risk,
not least from sanitary conditions.
The siege is affecting air traffic.
It's bad PR.
Minority groups say we're doing this
because they're Christians.
I prefer your first position. Starve them
out or let them blow themselves up.
- Let's not be crude.
- I'm being practical.
He's trying to recreate waco.
We shouldn't help him.
The brief is to examine
and prepare a range of options,
up to and including armed assault.
Why are there no armoured vehicles,
even if it's just to retrieve dead bodies,
seeing as they're shooting
at everything?
Looks very bad, armour against civilians.
It may look bad, but it sure as hell feels
a lot better when you're being shot at.
We need to take five guys
round the back. Five round the front...
Sergeant Garvie.
- That was outrageous.
- Yes, I know, but you'll improve.
- What?
- You heard.
Your insubordination is unsupportable.
That was a discussion.
That's how we operate.
- You behaved appallingly.
- You are very keen suddenly for a fight.
Like you have something to prove.
Just take a breath and think.
I haven't finished.
Never use force
unless you are certain you will win.
You're a very silly boy.
- Don't know what you mean.
- Sister Beth said to forget about him.
She's right.
I don't know what you're talking about.
There are cameras all the way
up to Manchester and all the way back.
It will take plod
five minutes to suss you.
If it's murder or GBH,
it's the end of you, young man.
(Grievous Bodily Harm)
Am I right?
You're right.
Thanks.
- Anything useful?
- Could be.
'You said they had a water supply? '
'Artesian spring in the courtyard.'
'And drains connect to main drainage.'
This culvert was used to bring
spring water out into the fields.
We may be able to use it
to gain access to the courtyard.
- You've got to be kidding.
- Forget it.
We need eyes and ears in the
stronghold. This could be the answer.
Forget it.
It's going to get too tight
for breathing apparatus.
It's a balls job.
You're sick.
Like he said, it's a balls job.
The man's attitude is intolerable.
The man's attitude
is a large part of the man.
And the man is the best soldier
in the best regiment
in the best army in the world.
You'd be better advised trying to learn
from him, rather than dominate him.
- You'd gas yourself.
- Yeah. Boss.
- Morning.
- Boss.
A kango wouldn't be that funny either.
A controlled explosion.
With the emphasis on control,
or you bring down the culvert.
And attract the attention
of the Jesus mob.
- I'll deal with that.
- Caroline, bung me the keys.
I need some plastic and detonators.
Find me the biggest skip lorry you can
lay your hands on and get it here ASAP.
Sir, we found a culvert.
Runs from here to here. We're getting
Pete to clear a concrete collar inside.
We should be clear
all the way to the courtyard.
- Wouldn't it be better to do it at night?
- No. Essential we do it by day.
- Well... Excuse me.
What are you looking at?
Freedom.
The real world.
What do you mean?
You know.
No, I don't.
I wish it were different.
I wish I could take you out to a film or...
We're all afraid, Michael,
but we're all God's children.
We offer him our unquestioning faith
and he chooses
whether to accept our sacrifice
or leave us to fight again another day.
Don't be afraid of the fear.
Savour it.
What's that?
- A skip.
- Skip.
"Thunder and hail and fire
ran along the ground.
"And hell and death
were cast into the fire."
For God's sake.
It was just a skip.
For whose sake, Michael?
Oh, it's a boy.
- Well?
- It's clear.
All right, we're stood down until 0500.
We'll take another look then.
A hotel in town
for anyone wanting a bath.
Mobile phones and bleepers on
at all times. It's a 30-minute standby.
Stood to at 0500.
There's a good Indian in town.
Fancy a curry?
Yeah, why not?
- Hello.
- What are you doing here?
There are people from the regiment
staying here. Jamie...
What are you doing here?
- I knew you'd be here. I had to see you.
- I can't believe you drove down.
It didn't take long.
Are you all right?
No, not really.
You kissed me in Hereford.
Yes.
Like you meant it.
Well, I did.
Do you want me?
- What about Pete?
- Forget Pete.
He's no angel.
You're quite shy.
- I wasn't expecting that.
- I'm...
Come on. It's fine.
No one's giving marks out of ten.
- Go away.
- What is it?
- No, I...
Hey, hey. Have you been to see Pete?
You mustn't tell him you've seen me
here. Jamie, I think I'm going mad.
Jamie, please don't tell anyone
you've seen me here.
- Tell them what?
- Just promise.
- Ah, Pru.
- Pete.
- Have you seen Jamie?
- No, aren't you staying here?
I wish. A B&B down the road.
Me and Jamie are going for an Indian.
- Do you want to join us?
- No. I don't think...
Ah, the wee man.
- Where have you been?
- Checking the garden.
Another hidden talent.
I'm starving. Are you sure?
Absolutely. Stuff to do.
You two have a good time.
- Everything all right, sir?
- Yeah, fine.
- You're very quiet.
- Just tired, mate.
- We should get an early one.
- I'm getting banana fritters.
Excuse me. Do you have banana fritters?
Just the one fritters, please.
What are you looking at?
Whoa, Pete. Take it easy, mate.
- What?
- Are you all right?
- Why? Because I've ordered fritters?
- You're not your usual self.
- What are you on about?
- Mate, is something bothering you?
What do you mean? It's like
having dinner with my bloody wife.
I'm in high spirits
and you want an encounter group.
All right.
You don't mind putting this
on your gold card, do you?
I'm busted.
Piss off, Conrad. Go home.
Night, Tony.
Wanker. Stick your pub up your arse.
Why aren't you in town with the others?
Why aren't you?
Are you married?
I'm separated.
- You?
- Mm-mm.
Why do you ask?
Interested.
- There's no sugar in that.
- I know.
What, interested in me?
Well, yes, actually.
Good. Cos I'm interested in you.
I know.
When I first saw you, I wondered
What you did in your spare time.
Eat takeaways and watch
Sex And The City. what did you imagine?
- Wagner, Chablis.
- How flattering.
I...
- All right, Sean, any news?
- Been to the end of the culvert.
There's a grille,
but you can get through it.
- Good.
- Nice find, that. Gold star for Red Troop.
- Cheers, mate.
- Not taking advantage of the hotels?
I'm preparing to clear up the mess
Blue Troop leave behind after their shift.
- Cheers.
- Night, mate.
- Which is the problem.
- Yes.
- Golden rule. Never at work.
- And with me.
So when do you knock off?
Whenever we finish here
and after the debrief at Hereford.
Can I ask you something,
in confidence and off the record?
Yeah, sure.
Would Pete bring his wife down
When there's an operation on?
- Never. Not in a million years. why?
- No, no, I saw her just now in town.
I'm pretty sure
Pete didn't know she was here.
What, is that it?
Look, if it's something else,
then you have to tell me.
She was with Jamie.
- In the car park at the hotel.
- Jamie?
- They were...
- Sergeant, something's happening.
- That's promising.
- Yes, sir.
Michael!
Don't betray the Lord.
Run, you fool. Run.
Weave. For Christ's sake, weave.
- Argh!
- Don't. You'll kick it all off.
We're not prepared for that. Not yet.
Hold your fire, everyone.
I repeat, hold your fire.
I want Red Troop stood to ASAP. Over.
'Got that.'
- You told them not to give covering fire?
- Yes.
He could have told us who was in there,
what weapons they were using...
- Yes, sir.
- How are people going to view this?
I don't really care. We were in no position
to respond or to control the situation.
- It was still a police investigation.
- Sir, we have work to do. Where's Ricky?
Isn't he back? I sent him to the late-night
garage to get Vaseline for detonators.
Henno, Ian, there's been
a possible development.
You were right about dispositions
within the stronghold.
- Maybe now we can get them.
- What do you mean?
We put someone through the culvert
and try and get her out.
What if she puts up a fight or screams?
We just have to make sure she doesn't.
Got a job for you.
Louis, you're in support.
- Where's...
- Wally.
Pete. I reckon that'll get you through
a few more games of gay before bed.
They love it. They do. They love it.
We've got an X-ray needs snatching.
Jamie and Louis to the culvert.
The rest of us and Blue Troop
in support. we go in five.
I'm going to take my hand away.
If you scream, I will shoot you
in the head. Do you understand?
Got that.
They're on their way back.
Stage three.
That lad certainly has a way with women.
"His eyes were as a flame of fire
and on his head he had many crowns,
"And he had a name written
that no man knew, but himself."
I don't think there's any answer to that.
Your mother met Klissman
nine years ago, when you were ten.
So that means Klissman's
not the father of your two brothers.
Jonathan and Thomas.
They were in there with you.
You know he intends to blow you all up?
He means for you all to die.
"And God shall wipe away
all tears from their eyes,
"And there shall be no more death.
Neither shall there be any more pain."
You don't think he'll give up?
So you came out and left your two little
brothers in there with that creep?
"And there will be no more death."
You see, I too love the Lord Jesus.
But I wouldn't gamble my brothers' lives
on a random passage from the Bible.
It says Abraham,
although 600 years old, still managed
to get his sister Sarah pregnant.
Genesis, chapter 20.
It also says, after his wife turned to salt,
that Lot managed to shag
his young daughters.
But this was OK because he got
the nod from a passing angel.
I think these days, if that came to court,
the judges would find these visits from
passing angels a little bit convenient
and lock the dirty bastards up
for a couple of years, don't you?
Now my tea's cold.
That's very good.
The brothers are definitely the key.
We don't have any time to waste.
I think we're going to
need shock treatment.
- Henno, can I have a word?
- Yeah. Sure.
Is that your brother Thomas?
Actually, it's not.
At the moment, your brother is still alive.
This kid, the one with half his face
and stomach missing,
lived for two days
after this photograph was taken.
Now, when we go in, if we know where
people are, where the weapons are,
where the firebombs have been placed,
there's a good chance of bringing
your brothers out alive.
If we go in blind, everyone will die.
You have 20 minutes.
Hello?
I'll go call my bosses.
After the original shooting,
three cars left the stronghold,
carrying between them four men
and two women.
Susannah says these pairs are teams
called Earth, Air and Water.
Which suggests that Klissman is Fire.
She confirmed the stronghold
is one giant bomb.
- Petrol cans in every corner.
- The other three are sleeper cells.
Waiting for him to give his word.
Which he seems likely to do
when he finds out the girl is gone.
We're at the point where an immediate attack
is inevitable.
There are still good reasons for not
going in. Eight of the kids are under 16.
Catch him alive and expose him
for abusing minors.
Right. We will prepare
a direct plan of action.
Then assess what's possible
and make a decision. Light by seven.
Last chance for a go would be 0600.
It's now 0240.
DPA by 0340.
Right, bombs here, here
and possibly here. Wires there and there.
On the outside of the building in
the courtyard. Will it be OK to cut them?
He won't have them on a live circuit.
So we can cut away.
I'll get bomb disposal
to send some of their ECM boys.
(Electronic CounterMeasures)
Good. Right. Our five smallest through
the culvert. Jamie, on wire-cutting duty.
- Have that.
- No, me. why waste him on wires?
Pru knows what she's doing on comms.
Put me in.
I don't have a problem with that.
All right. Bring Pru up to speed
with call signs.
'Team One to wires.
All other teams to FMPs.'
'X-ray down in side entrance.'
All in position now.
And... stage one.
'Stand by.
'Stand by. Go.'
Stage two. Stand by. Stand by.
'Go.'
'Romeo Four Zero Bravo.
Team A and B into building by door 1-5.'
'Have that.'
Hey. we're making sandwiches.
Do you want cheese and pickle?
No pickle. Just cheese and ham.
'Two X-rays down in 1-3.'
'Have that.'
'Romeo Four Zero Bravo.
X-ray down in 1-2.'
'Have that.'
'Romeo Two, Zero, Bravo,
X-ray secured in two-alpha.'
Go, go, go.
Sod that.
Romeo Four Zero Bravo.
Four X-rays in 2-7. Secured door. Out.
They're coming in the back.
Into thy hands, Lord.
No!
Move it!
Go.
This is Romeo One Zero Bravo.
We are pinned down at the base
of the stairs in 1-1 by X-ray Two
at the top of the stairs.
Need support. Over.
I'm on it.
Hey, boy, you drop it.
Right, we need X-ray One alive.
On three, I move right,
you take out his hands.
On three. One, two...
"To him that overcometh,
I will give a white stone,
"And in that stone a name written
that no man knoweth,
"saving he that receiveth it."
Shut up.
You, back in the car with me.
I need a piss.
Let's get cleared up, cleaned up
and back to OH. Debrief 1300.
- Yeah. Good work, guys.
- Well done, yourself.
Sorry to bother you, mate.
Do you know where James Dow is?
James Dow?
- Could I have a word?
- What about?
Conrad Boyd.
You know who I mean.
- What about him?
- He were killed last night.
Good.
- Was there any trouble between you?
- I hated him. How did he die?
- Beaten to death with a brick.
- Nice one.
I hope it hurt.
Someone saved me the trouble.
Would you have any idea where you
Were at 11:30 last night?
Yeah, I was...
I was at an Indian restaurant
here in town.
- Would there be witnesses to that?
- Yeah. Yeah. Plenty of witnesses.
Thanks. We may have
to come back to you on that.
- Yeah, whatever mate. Good luck.
- Cheers.
- Nice job in there. well done.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry. I was afraid. I'm sick.
I'll take counselling.
Marriage guidance.
I'll dye my hair.
Whatever it takes to make it up to you.
The immersion's on.
Get out.
I've a pretty good idea what your mate
did for you last night.
I wonder if he'd been so keen if he knew
you were sleeping with Pete's wife.
- What?
- You were seen in the hotel car park.
You've got it wrong. Aah!
- Now, was she there or wasn't she?
- Yeah, but...
- So why was she there?
- I can't say.
Listen to me. I can't say!
Who is it?
I can't say.
www.subtitleonline.com