I need a drink.
Here you go.
Okay, all right.
Katie Cumming?
Shaved.
-Very bad.
-Nice.
What about Molly Simmons?
Trimmed neatly.
I like it. I like that.
Holly fucking Dwyer?
Full bush, with a little treasure trail.
Fucking treasure turn pike.
Fucking treasure freeway
with a car pool lane.
-Here we go.
-Yes.
Who invited you freaks?
So he walks up to her,
he goes, "Open the vagina."
Come on. I never said that.
No, no wait.
She slaps the shit out of him,
and so he says,
"Open the vagina, please."
Sarah Voizon?
Shaved.
Timmerman's sister?
Dude, she's seven.
Timmerman's mom?
Buckwheat in a scissor lock.
Janie Smith?
Trimmed.
You study for that history exam?
No.
Dude, that scared the shit out of me.
SECONDS APART
I can't see.
Popular kids,
from what we're getting upstairs.
Jocks.
Football or basketball?
Football.
They had a game tomorrow.
Nobody heard the gun shots?
They had music cranked up pretty good.
-Who found them?
-Pizza guy.
Pizza guy? They ordered pizza?
Two.
Pizza guy strolled in at 11 :05.
So they commit suicide en masse,
the night before the big game
and they ordered pizza.
-En masse?
-My vocabulary is expanding.
Must be the literature.
Here's what I think happened.
Junior got a hold of papa's gun,
started to have a friendly game
of Russian roulette.
Things just got out of hand.
First kid commits suicide,
blows his brains out.
That'd bring the game to
a screeching halt, don't you think?
Can you feel it?
-But all the elements are there.
-Trimmed.
Then why can't we feel it?
The project takes time.
But everyone else feels it.
I feel it.
-Liar.
-Seriously.
There, the way he tilts his head.
No. It's in his eyes.
Bedtime, boys.
Five more minutes.
You heard your mother.
That scared the shit out of me.
Well, maybe next time.
I didn't feel it.
I know.
Trial and error,
that's the nature of the project.
It's the genius of the project.
Exactly.
-Goodnight.
Now I got to run. Booked all morning.
You'll be home in time for dinner?
Word of honor.
Do you know how much I love you?
This much?
Not even close.
It is with great regret
that I've summoned you here today.
The loss of these four fine young men
has come as an abrupt
and unexpected shock.
They were friends, scholars, athletes.
But above all, they were the embodiment
of the phrase, "Men for others."
Let us pray.
"Our father, who art in heaven.
Hallowed be thy name.
"Thy kingdom come, thy will be done."
Detective Lampkin.
Sorry to have kept you waiting.
Good book?
Yes, well, it does have its moments.
Poetics?
You mind if I...
Of course, for as long as you like.
Please.
Well, so far,
most of the guests at the party
don't remember a goddamn thing.
I was wondering if I could
open it up a little bit.
Interview some friends,
girlfriends, that sort of thing.
They were very popular boys.
I always wondered what that was like.
You heard anything?
Just a lot of teenage gossip.
That they were in a suicide club.
Some sort of satanic ritual, drugs.
Were they on drugs?
One of them tested positive for weed
and that's about it.
Who?
Yes, well, I just hope
that you can help us understand
why they would kill themselves.
If, in fact, they did kill themselves.
What are you saying? That someone...
Suicide and homicide.
One can be made to resemble the other.
My uncle has diabetes.
He never takes care of it, though.
He's always losing toes.
-I'm new. What's your excuse?
-Reactive hypoglycemia.
-I'm Eve.
-Jonah.
Jonah, I'm looking for room 408A.
I had no trouble finding 401 through 407.
It's in the Dorsey Annex.
And where might that be?
Far from here.
You know, you strike me
as a New Testament kind of guy.
Are you familiar with The Parable
of the Good Samaritan?
Luke 10, verses 30 to 37.
Great.
Let's pretend that you are
the Good Samaritan
and I'm on the side of the road.
Show me a little mercy,
it's my first day.
All right, follow me.
Pencils down.
They didn't even ask about
the Great Western Schism.
So, should we focus on the next project?
Who?
The one who made you late.
No.
We should stick to the program.
Lay low for a while and then...
Feed the birds?
Yeah. Feed the birds.
All right, Vargo. Back to class.
Ms. Dunn.
Ms. Dunn, I know this must be
real difficult for you.
Lots of people.
Lots of people what?
You're gonna ask me the same thing
that you've asked everybody else.
Do I know anybody
who would wanna hurt those boys?
I know lots of people. They're jerks.
-Including Derek?
-Especially Derek.
How long did you two date?
I saw them kill a dog once.
Derek and his friends?
A chow chow.
They look like lions, don't they?
They do that to your arm, too?
No, I was in a movie once.
They like making movies.
Who likes making movies?
Were they at the party?
Even if they were,
nobody would remember them.
Twins with the camera.
How do you forget something like that?
Jonah Trimble?
Seth.
Good enough.
Let's say we talk for a little while?
Is this seat taken?
-Gum?
-It's not allowed.
That's a keeper.
It's a shame what happened to them boys,
ain't it?
Friends of yours?
We don't have any friends.
You know Elvis had a twin?
I didn't.
Brother was stillborn.
Elvis was the first,
then came the dead one.
You imagine that? Two Elvises.
Wow.
What do you want?
So my real name is Kristen,
but if you ever call me that,
I'll have to kill you.
-I'm from Salem.
-Massachusetts?
Oregon. Vancouver before that.
British Columbia?
Washington.
Before that, Hollywood.
California?
Florida.
-My mom relocates a lot.
-For work?
For love.
I mean she thinks it's love.
It looks like love on paper,
but it never really works out.
I'm just trying to make sense
of this tragedy.
Maybe you should see
one of the grief counselors.
Maybe you should.
I'm not experiencing any grief.
Really?
Not even...
What's it called when you
question God and what not?
-Existential.
-Right.
Not even that. That a crime?
Not in this state.
Good. So I guess we're through.
Now, withholding evidence,
that's a crime.
We've known each other
ever since we were eight.
She was the only other kid
on my block, besides me,
who knew the words to American Pie.
-Where?
-Kansas City.
Missouri?
Kansas.
Now, neighbor lady says
she saw twin boys, about your age,
head into the party,
with the video camera rolling.
Now what I can't figure out
is how come none of the guests
recall you being there.
When you're not popular in high school,
you might as well be invisible.
So you were there.
Never said I wasn't.
But we left before anything happened.
I think we gonna have to let
the video camera speak for itself.
I'm sorry but there is no video.
I mean, there would have been,
but my brother, dumbass,
forgot to put the memory card
in the camera.
Seems like a real simple mistake for boys
with such high SAT scores, don't it?
I'm gonna have to talk to your parents.
They're out of town.
-Where?
-They're in Aspen.
Your brother says Vail.
My brother wouldn't say that.
Why not?
Because they're in Aspen.
My God.
It is uncanny.
How far apart?
Ninety-three seconds.
-You're the older one, I bet, right?
-Younger.
Taller by a few inches, though.
Shorter by less than one.
What can you tell me
about the video camera?
Your brother says that you, dumbass,
forgot to load the memory card
in the camera.
There you have it.
Don't get mad at me.
-I'm just repeating what he said.
-I'm not mad.
No?
You're the sensitive one.
Gum?
I'm diabetic.
Not so funny second time around.
Dumbass?
Cops dig the vernacular.
-Puts them at ease.
-How considerate of you.
Come on.
You know what they're trying to do.
He was smart to keep us apart.
Just lucky.
Lying about the neighbor,
that was kind of clever.
Are you worried?
Not at all.
We covered our tracks. He's fishing.
Yeah.
But somebody told him something.
So let's find out who.
What in God's name
are you two doing here?
You said you had an open door policy.
It's after 8:00.
How the hell did you get in here?
You said if anyone had a problem
they can come to you.
Anytime, 24/7.
Not now. No...
-I thought I saw...
-Rats?
You're more likely to find those
among the student body.
-What are you talking about?
-Who ratted us out, Frank?
How dare you?
In Africa,
they get to be the size of small dogs.
Is that why you left?
I'm gonna have you
little bastards expelled, you hear me?
Now get out.
Out!
You were just hitting your stride
as a missionary.
Why'd you leave?
I got...
I got sick.
With what?
-Dracu...
-Dracunculus.
The Guinea worm.
I find parasites
much more interesting than rats.
Did you know we spent a whole week
on parasites in biology class?
-The Guinea worm is our favorite.
-By far.
Infection can be caused by drinking
contaminated water.
The worm matures in the host's body,
growing up to six feet long.
After about a year,
it migrates towards the surface.
In 90% of the cases...
The worm will emerge
from the leg or the foot.
The worm needs to be rolled out
onto a small stick.
Caution must be exercised during removal,
Frank.
If it breaks...
What happens if it breaks?
Crippled.
Right, you can lose a leg.
Or worse.
Now back to my original question, Frank.
Who ratted us out?
I can't hear you.
Katie.
Really?
Guess we didn't make
enough of an impression on her.
Please, please.
No.
Looks like you'll have
to dig it out yourself.
Dig out? No!
I found this in the contraband drawer.
He cut an artery. Bled out in minutes.
You get a shot of this?
Maybe he was trying to get to the phone.
Maybe he was trying to tell us
something else.
How you doing, Lampkin?
Larry, I want you to be the first to know,
this is my last pack of cigarettes.
Yeah, I heard that one before.
Oh, man. Seriously, my wife says
she's gonna divorce me if I don't quit.
Figure I'm gonna
have two on the ride home,
park a block away, have one in the car
and two on the porch. Shit, maybe three.
How many that make?
Fuck 'em all but nine.
-Come again.
-We used to say that back in Nam.
Six for pallbearers.
Two for the road guards.
One to count cadence.
Fuck 'em all but nine.
Maybel?
Maybel!
I can't see. I can't see.
That wasn't so bad, was it?
Welcome to pain management
for the new millennium, Detective.
Distract the mind from what's happening
to the body.
Send you on a little trip,
while we scrub you down.
We need to escalate.
Haven't we done enough lately?
They're just trying to make sense
out of this tragedy.
-We need to talk about Katie.
-No.
Morning, Katie.
She's a loose end.
The quicker we take care of her, the
quicker we can get back to the project.
I think we should take a break for a while.
Why? What about feeding the birds?
Holy shit.
-I can tell the difference.
-You can?
You have a scar by your eye.
And you have a squiggly thing on your iris.
I do?
It's kind of cool.
I'm Seth.
Eve.
Nice to meet you, Eve.
You know, Jonah and I have been
working on this little project.
-Seth.
-What kind of project?
It's a movie.
-You wanna be in it?
-No.
Sure.
I mean, how do we even know she can act?
Audition me.
Sounds pretty reasonable to me.
Don't we have someone else in mind?
Do we?
Yes. We do.
-I want her.
-Good, let's have her.
No, just me.
-All to yourself?
-Yes.
-You wouldn't know what to do with her.
-I know what not to do with her.
I've learned from our mistakes.
Katie.
Daddy?
Yes, Katie, it's me.
How's my little angel?
Daddy, I miss you so much.
I miss you, too.
How's my little girl?
It's okay.
I know about the abortion.
How you can't have children.
I'm so sorry. I'm so sorry.
Sweetheart, do you know where I am?
Heaven.
Would you like to be with me?
Yes, I would.
I wanna see you.
Daddy?
Katie?
Stay the fuck away from me.
Put the glass down.
No!
-Another suicide.
-And you believe that?
This time, we got a bunch of witnesses.
Including our boys?
Trimble, Jonah and Seth,
they were sitting right there.
What makes you think they're witnesses?
What's your point?
My point is maybe
they had something to do with it.
Well, your point is moot.
Moot?
I'm expanding my vocabulary.
Books?
Books on tape.
Look, Detective, I got 15 witnesses says
those boys never laid a finger on her.
Maybe they didn't have to.
She's as same as the others.
No. She's better.
I feel it.
Liar.
Maybe it's your blood sugar.
I'll make you a sandwich.
I'm not hungry.
Where's Jonah?
I don't know.
Not your brother's keeper, huh?
You know the game Hacky Sack?
Me and my buddies
used to play it in college.
I remember this one time we were
playing and this feeling came over me.
Sadness.
Found out my father died that day.
While you were playing Hacky Sack?
I've been reading up
the last couple of nights about twins.
And a lot of people say
that twins have a special connection.
Started to think you and your brother
have a special connection.
Like you and your wife?
My wife?
What were you doing when she died?
Playing canasta?
Don't talk about my wife.
Were you freaked out?
Not really.
What about the blood?
There wasn't that much blood.
You know what I mean.
Someone offs themselves in front of you,
there's an effect, right?
There's supposed to be.
I've been to five schools in three years
and I can honestly say,
I've never met anyone like you.
Really?
Well, well, well.
I need to borrow
your boyfriend for a minute.
I'm not her boyfriend.
She didn't seem to mind the label much.
Seth, on the other hand,
did not look happy
because he felt left out.
God with the football team this year?
God was always with our football team.
Not so much the water polo team.
I was never much into sports myself.
Too much like you.
Too damn sensitive.
Your interrogation technique sucks.
See that's not you talking. That's Seth.
Seth must have really gotten to you.
He said some hurtful things about my wife.
I lost control.
Hell, I think any man would.
I think you would have stood up
for somebody that you care about.
She met your parents yet?
No.
Think it's about time I did.
May I help you?
Excuse me. I...
I knocked loud, twice,
and no one came to the door.
I'm Detective Lampkin.
Detective Lampkin.
Our sons told us about you.
I'm sure they did.
Nice home.
You know, my mama, she used to...
She used to work as a housekeeper
in a beautiful home.
Like this.
How long you've been living here?
This house has been in my family
for many years.
You mind if I...
No.
You know, I couldn't afford this place
with my salary and my pension.
What kind of square footage
are you looking at?
About 4,000.
You know, my house right here,
I'm standing in my kitchenette,
and I take two steps, little steps,
I'm in the alley way.
Sounds claustrophobic.
Like a jail cell.
-Where are your boys?
-Upstairs.
I am sure that they have informed you
about the recent tragedies.
We're still in shock.
I'm advising all the parents
to communicate with their children.
Help us sort out this mess.
We did and we have.
We have great communication
with our boys.
They mention the video?
Unfortunately there is no video,
Detective Lampkin.
I wish there had been.
Perhaps it could have helped you
make sense of things.
They ever talked to you about their gift?
I should hope they have more than one gift.
Gift I'm referring to is
less conventional.
I'm not sure I'm following you.
How was Aspen?
I don't see what this has to do with it.
We stayed at a little bed and breakfast.
Which one?
I'm sure you've never heard of it.
Try me.
Elsa's Landing.
Honeymoon suite.
Do you know it?
We even brought back a little souvenir.
Right over there.
My wife and I used to go there.
It's lovely, isn't it?
Yeah.
Anything else, Detective?
No.
Thank you for your time.
Ma'am.
Oh, and Detective.
You lay a hand on one of my boys again
and you can kiss that little pension
of yours goodbye, understood?
Yes, ma'am.
You're on work study?
I just needed to get away.
The police asked me about you.
I know.
Should I be worried?
Maybe.
Do you play?
No.
Here.
That's good.
-Good job.
-Yeah?
So where do you live?
Santa Maria, by Dunham.
Fancy.
Do you want to hang out there?
I'm not allowed to have guests over.
Then we'll go to my house.
I can't see.
Excuse me, so sorry to bother you.
-Can you help us out?
-We are kind of stranded here.
I...
I just parked my wheels right over there.
Thought I was seeing double
back there for a second.
I guess you guys get that a lot, huh?
Twin jokes?
Less than you think.
So, Kirby, do you?
-What?
-You know, feed the birds.
Did I say my name was Kirby?
This isn't the way to Grandma's house.
Yeah, we blew past that
like three miles ago.
Don't worry.
I know a way.
You ever hold a little bird in your hand?
It's so light.
Deceptively light.
It's an aerodynamic thing, I guess.
Well, boys at your age
are like little birds.
I guess you realize I do
at the carnival, but you pick one up...
Mother?
It's okay.
Mother.
Kirby, help.
Mommy.
Mom!
Here it comes.
Hey!
-Why did you get in the car?
-We needed a ride.
-You needed a ride where?
-The mall.
We told him to stop
but he just kept going.
Jonah grabbed the wheel
and the car started swerving.
Then I pulled the emergency brake.
And the rest is on video. Why?
Evidence.
Figured we could show it to the police
when we got away.
We didn't see the truck coming
until it was too late.
The driver says,
he's been taking that same route
every Saturday morning
for the last five years.
Company log says he ain't lying.
Neither are we.
I think you knew that truck was coming.
I think you tricked that man
into giving you a ride.
And I think you used
your unique talents to kill him.
Right, you think we have
these weird powers.
You know, my dad
called his lawyer last night.
Not because you hit me.
It's no big deal.
You were upset.
It was just to see what our rights are.
He says what you're doing is harassment.
This is not Salem.
It's what he said.
Wormwood wants you.
What the hell are you doing in there?
Interviewing suspects.
We have our suspect, right here.
Kirby LeFleur.
Busted in '91 for indecent exposure.
Graduated to criminal misconduct
with a minor in '94.
Did a seven-year stretch
for accosting a child.
As far as I'm concerned, those kids
were abducted by a sexual predator
who should have invested
in a AAA membership.
That's what they want you to think.
They can get inside of people's heads.
I've seen them.
Did I bring you back too soon?
Let them go, Detective.
This isn't Salem.
This time he deserved it.
He's a goddamn pedophile.
Then why didn't it make a difference?
Why didn't we feel a fucking thing?
It's the nature of the project,
all right? Trial and error.
It's the genius of the project.
It's just not working.
Come on.
You know we have it in us, all right.
Remember when we were little
before the babysitter?
-I think that part of us is broken.
-Why?
I'm done wasting my time.
It's her, isn't it?
No.
You can't abandon the project.
I just did.
He just doesn't get it. I can't do this.
-Do what?
-The project.
We're not the same anymore.
-I'm not making any sense.
-No, it's okay.
You're just upset.
I'm glad you called me.
-Hi, honey.
-Hi.
Who's your friend?
Jonah Trimble.
Hi, Jonah Trimble. I'm Brenda.
Nice to meet you.
-Thank you.
-Okay, Mom.
All right, honey, I'm gonna go lay down.
I'm sorry about my mom.
She's much more interesting
when she's sober.
I liked her.
-Not too much, I hope.
-No.
I bet you have the perfect parents.
I used to think so as a kid.
What does your dad do?
He was a doctor.
What does he do now?
He's a doctor.
You said "was."
-I wasn't. I was just...
-I don't wear thongs.
I mean, I know most girls do
but I don't like the way they feel.
Do you know, one time,
a boy broke up with me
just because I didn't wear one.
Can you believe that?
I bet you wear boxers.
Ask me another question.
-I didn't ask you anything.
-On a boat.
-What?
-My first time was on a boat.
On the Lake of Ozarks.
You know where that is?
Ask me another question.
-I can't think of any.
-Some football player, some jerk.
What was it like?
It hurt.
Here.
That's what I like to listen to.
-How old were you?
-Fourteen.
Listen.
It's beautiful.
-What's wrong?
-I should go home.
-You're not into me?
-No. I am.
-It's just I...
-Wanna take things slow?
Yeah.
You're weird.
I know.
I'll see you later?
Here.
So I can tell you apart.
I know you feel it with her.
Of course not.
It's why you don't need
the project anymore.
I need some protein.
Maybe I should go see her.
Stay away from her.
Nice ring.
What's going on up there?
Nothing.
Hold me.
I can't see.
Linda, I need to go back there.
I don't see any fresh burns
on you, Detective.
Anyway, we're done for today.
Please, I just need to escape.
I'm sorry it's just...
My wife and I used to go here.
Yeah.
-Happy birthday, Jonah.
-Happy birthday, you two!
Happy birthday, my two sweet boys.
That's the way, boys. Good job.
It's about a girl, isn't it?
At your age, it's always about a girl.
Or God.
I don't believe in God.
You were always my favorite.
Really?
Is she beautiful?
Yeah.
I used to be beautiful, too.
You still are.
You're the most beautiful mother
in the entire world.
Having twins,
it ruined me.
See the stretch marks?
I'm sorry.
Touch it.
It's okay.
You sucked the life out of me.
Look, the babysitter.
She's so beautiful.
Remember the babysitter?
Things really seem to be falling apart.
Yes.
It's strange.
Time for your shot.
Dr. Elder?
Dr. Elder is dead.
-I'm Detective Lampkin.
-I'm Dr. Houska.
We used to be partners.
Well, they came here to get pregnant.
That's what we do.
Or it's what we did.
How does that work? Drug?
Well, it depends on the patient.
Depends on the couple.
I'm asking about the Trimbles.
Can I see your credentials again,
please, Detective?
-About that time, isn't it?
-Excuse me?
I don't mean to compare you
with the local street addict
but a jones is a jones, ain't it though?
Listen, I have a consultation I have to make.
So please. Hey! Hey! Get your hands...
I'm not asking you to compromise
your high ethical standards.
Just allow me to compromise mine, okay?
All right, Detective,
you're on your own.
What happened?
You went to instant shock
because you've been eating like shit.
Come on, time for school.
Sorry about last night.
Catholic guilt?
I fell asleep.
Me, too. I was out like a light.
Why did you leave again?
-What?
-You could have stayed the night.
My mom's cool.
What's wrong?
I never do that.
I mean,
I try to get to know the guy first.
Listen,
if some of the stuff that I said...
I hope I didn't scare you away.
I haven't been scared since I was little.
-I take it you're pissed.
-Fuck you! Why?
To keep you in your place.
Shut up!
We're the same!
Jonah!
Couldn't tell the difference,
you fucking idiot!
Well, I'll be damned.
...color of television and radio
as well as stereo recording.
This fabulous home entertainment center
will be yours
if The Price Is Right, priced authority.
Thank you, Don. And thank you, ladies.
Mr. Ritner, we begin with you.
Minimum is 50. You may start anywhere.
Oh, my God.
Did Seth do that?
No. I did it.
Owen.
Does it hurt?
Now they'll be able to tell us apart.
...Fifty, that's the minimum. $1500.
Mr. Ritner,
you're picking up where you left off.
-Thank you. Thank you.
-You're welcome.
I'm your favorite right?
Sweetie, I love you both just the same.
No. No.
You said I was your favorite.
Did I?
I can't remember.
He says we're just the same,
but I'm not like him, right?
We're all special in God's eyes.
I've got the scar. I've got the scar.
Sweetie, it's just a tiny little scar.
He fucked my girl!
Poor thing.
His heart's broken.
Son.
It'll all come out in the wash.
What kind of parents are you?
Good question.
It's okay, Jonah.
It's gonna be okay.
You're not like him.
Mommy. Make him leave.
Mommy's not too talkative right now.
Especially when Seth's not around.
Where is he?
I don't know.
It's harder to do when he's not around,
isn't it?
Get out.
It's harder to pull the wool
over your own eyes.
Daddy?
Make him leave.
I see what's happening.
You know what's happening, Jonah?
I remember now.
It started with the babysitter.
Open your eyes. Open your eyes.
What is this?
I did this to protect us.
Excuse me.
I had knocked loud twice,
but no one answered so...
I'm Detective Lampkin.
Nice home.
You killed them?
No.
I'm sorry.
Listen.
They're ruling this as suicide.
We know differently.
They killed her.
We just need to keep them apart.
It's just the house.
I'm scared of them.
They wouldn't hurt us.
Then why are we whispering?
Do you remember
how badly we wanted a child?
How we prayed?
I went to those doctors...
It's not our fault.
It's my fault.
I let them put those drugs in me.
We just need to keep them apart.
Do you know how much I love you?
This much?
Not even close.
I can make things right, now. Trust me.
I can protect us.
Like the way I always have.
No. It needs to end. Right now.
I don't need you anymore.
What are you doing?
Stop!
Stop it!
You fucking need me.
You need me.
Get away from him.
Wow.
Where was that enthusiasm last night?
'Cause I thought I was fucking a glass
of water but, hey, I'm willing...
-Please get up.
-Seth.
Get up.
Stay away!
This is your fault! You fucking whore.
I'm gonna make you watch.
Help!
I can't see.
Can you feel it?
Yeah.
Finally.
It's beautiful.
I'm scared.
Me, too.
Subrip & sync: easytobeaman