Poppy!
Come on, let's get going.
Where are you?
Oh, for heaven's sakes.
Poppy, get dressed.
Zeb will be here
any minute.
Oh. What's all that for?
The picnic for Nono and Barry--
their engagement.
You have known about this
for weeks.
Well, I can't remember
every wingding you...
you got going around here.
It isn't a wingding.
It's for Nono.
You're going to have
lots of fun today, Peter.
You know, my family throws
parties for a living.
My stepmother--
your soon-to-be
step-grandmother--
well, nobody throws
a party like Beck.
(phone rings)
Open Arms-- for all of...
Oh, Zeb, where are you?
Sorry. I had an emergency.
I'm going to be a little late.
Want me to meet you at the park?
All right.
I'll wrangle up Poppy.
See you there.
Oh. Come on.
Help me get this stuff
in the car.
Okay.
Oh, boy, this is heavy.
Oh, yeah?
Too heavy?
Well, uh, I can make it.
Oh, good.
I'll get the door.
Ah.
You all right?
(glass clinking)
Oh, Poppy, careful.
There's crystal in there.
Crystal? At a picnic?
Well, what
better occasion
than for my nearest
and dearest?
Oh.
Well, how can you have a picnic
without food?
Biddy's making the food.
As always.
Oh.
Mmm-- snails in phyllo dough.
Mom, can't we ever have
hamburgers and hot dogs
like normal people?
Which?
Uh, sneakers.
Beck says she wants to organize
a family baseball game.
Oh, there it is.
Ow! Oh!
(chuckling)
(horn honks)
Hey. Come on, I'm starving.
All right, all right.
(chuckling)
Is there any food in there?
No. It's for the champagne.
Oh.
I hope Patch
remembered the bats and balls.
So, where is everybody?
Beck did say everybody
was supposed to be here by 3:30.
Uh... Well, I guess
we'll go for a jog then.
Oh, go ahead-- just run away.
Just like every other
family gathering.
Poppy, those
are for Min Foo.
Oh. Is she going
to eat the whole jar?
(chuckling)
Well, when I
was pregnant
with Min Foo,
I used to crave dills
all the time.
Mmm.
(slurping)
Oh, Poppy!
Love it!
Oh, I want more.
(chuckling)
Hey, Min Foo, I came...
So, where is my mother?
Oh, there she is.
Oh.
Let me get your bag.
I'm fine. I'm fine.
Hi!
Hi.
Oh, see?
She doesn't want
to be here either.
I don't know why we have to
celebrate Nono's engagement
to that... that
corporate lawyer.
Because she's your sister.
Oh, come on.
Help me set up
before Nono and Barry get here.
And here they are.
Hi, Barry.
Oh. Hi, sweetheart.
Hi.
And you
have got to be Peter.
I'm Rebecca.
Hey, you want
to come with me
and meet
your new cousins?
No.
Oh, come on.
Okay, a toast, everybody,
a toast.
To all of us
gathered together
in this glorious
spring weather.
Here she goes.
To Zeb
for scoping
out the site.
Cheers.
Thank you very much.
To Biddy,
for cooking
with all of
her might,
and Troy for helping
her get it right.
Um, to Patch
and Jeep for suggesting
the bats and the balls,
even though we never
use them at all.
To Hakim and Min Foo.
In August, they're due.
But most of all,
to Nono and Barry.
Oh.
We are so delighted
that they are going to marry.
(laughter)
Oh, and last
but not least,
a toast to Peter.
Someone new
in our family.
Oh, what
could be sweeter?
ALL:
To Peter.
I'm not in your family.
Oh. Better go get him
before he jumps
in the river.
BARRY:
Peter, get back here right now!
(people murmuring)
Peter, come on!
REBECCA:
Did you ever
have the feeling
you turned into
the wrong person?
ZEB:
Mmm... well, no.
I mean look at me--
after 20 years,
still a widow
planning other people's parties.
Don't read no more,
discuss important issues,
don't got no friends.
You've got friends.
You got the girls.
You've got me.
Yeah, relatives.
And everybody else I know
is some kind of repairman.
Relatives can be friends.
Repairmen,
I'm not so sure about.
Listen, I'm serious, Zeb.
What, what happened
to the friends
I knew in college
or in high school?
I mean, for instance,
Amy Darrow,
the girl
who had her engagement party
the day I met Joe right here.
Oh. I didn't even get
to her wedding.
Of course, I was married myself
by then,
and all three girls
had chicken pox, but still.
Okay, okay, to be continued.
I'm gonna make rounds
at the hospital tomorrow.
Okay. 'Night.
'Night.
(train whistle
and wind chimes)
(bell clanging)
REBECCA:
I had the oddest dream
last night.
Were there any numbers in it?
What?
If you can recall any numbers,
my friend Al is always after me
for numbers
to play the
lottery with.
He wants the numbers
from my dreams,
but I don't have
any dreams anymore.
No, this was a,
this was a dream about a boy.
And he seemed to be... my son.
I was on a train,
and I couldn't quite
see his face, but...
it seems that he was
very handsome... and confident.
Do you recall
what number train it was?
No. And I don't know
where we were going either.
(chuckling):
Well, I'd call that a dream
that was lacking in plot.
In fact,
it's sort of uninteresting.
So, I'd like
to switch
the subject to my birthday.
Your birthday's not
till December, Poppy.
December 11th.
I'm going to be100years old.
Well, I know
that, Poppy.
I suppose you're planning
some big wingding for me.
I mean,
I mean bigger than usual, huh?
Well, we'll see. Maybe.
(phone rings)
(chuckles):
Yes.
But it's still
pretty far away.
And when we get
a little closer...
Open Arms-- for all
of life's occasions.
Oh, yes, hi, Melinda.
Here's a list.
The guest list
for my birthday party.
REBECCA:
Oh, certainly.
Oh, he... yeah,
he's a very good DJ.
Yup, he brings his
own sound system.
Oh, I'm sure he can play
whatever anyone would like.
Mom, it's me!
Not to worry.
Hi, Poppy!
Hi, Min Foo.
If you dreamed
you had a son
and not daughters,
and the boy was blonde
and not dark,
then you might
have been dreaming
how your life could be
if you had chosen
a different fork in the road--
if you'd decided on some
different kind of life.
Or, it probably means
my baby's going to be a boy.
No, Min Foo,
this is not about you.
And besides, he didn't have
your coloring.
He was blonde.
I could have
a blonde baby.
Half my genes are
yours, remember?
Well, yeah, maybe
with Joey's father.
But I seriously doubt
that you could hope
to have blonde genes with Hakim.
I know where this is going.
Before we start talking
about my choices in husbands,
I have an obstetrician to see.
Oh, honey, come on.
I wasn't implying anything
about your various husbands.
Yeah, right.
I got to go.
Bye, guys.
Bye, Mom.
Let's use these.
Oh, honey.
This is a graduation party.
Those are wedding bells.
Aw.
Hey, why don't we pretend
they're school bells?
Yay!
Okay.
Let's just make sure
they all work.
Ooh, pretty.
Nice.
Yeah.
You know that these
were strung across the room
the first time I ever came here?
? Hey, little woman,
please make up your mind ?
? You've got
to come into my world ?
? And leave your world behind ?
? Come on, now ?
? Na-na-na-na-na-na... ?
(laughing)
MAN:
I see you're having
a wonderful time.
Hi.
I'm Joe Davich.
That guy you're laughing at,
that's, uh,
my kid brother, Zeb.
I'm Rebecca Holmes.
I'm Amy's roommate.
Are you a friend
of Artie's?
Oh, no, no,
my family owns this place.
Oh.
Can I get you some champagne?
Oh. no, thank you,
I don't drink.
Well, we'll
have to find you
some ginger ale, then.
Oh! I am so sorry.
Come in the kitchen with me.
Joe, get the ham.
Wish I would
have known
you were coming.
Joe so seldom brings
his dates home.
I'm not his...
Of course,
you know Joe's children.
Children?
This is Nono
and Patch and Biddy.
And you've probably heard
the story.
Their mother Tina
escapes to New York City
and dumps the whole crew on me.
Mommy's going to be a
famous nightclub singer.
So some would have us believe.
Here, Mother.
A little soap and water,
and no one
will ever know.
Right.
Let's clean off
those shoes, huh?
Okay.
Mommy has
this beautiful dress
where the straps
are made of diamonds.
Really?
There. Good as new.
Thanks.
Come on.
MOTHER:
Where are you
taking her?
Don't worry,
we'll see her again.
Okay, guys.
Oh, sweetie, that-that,
that's really
a lot of raisins.
Uh...
we will be seeing you, won't we?
I'm gonna have love
at first sight, too.
Oh, I hope
you do, dear.
We finished just
a few hours ago.
Well...
Isn't that
lovely?
Oh, yeah.
Here's the problem.
Katie didn't graduate.
She didn't graduate?
No.
I was laying out
her clothes this morning
and suddenly Katie
turned to me
and she said,
"Oh, did I mention
I flunked chemistry?"
At the time, I failed
to understand
that flunking chemistry would
keep her from graduating,
but it-it did and...
Well, listen.
Isn't it fortunate that you
already planned this party?
It sends such a message.
A message?
Yeah, a message--
that you love
and you support
your daughter in spite
of her failure.
Oh.
But my friends.
How will I face them?
Oh, did-did you read that report
a few years ago?
Oh, my, it was, um...
Scientists actually discovered
that if you fake a smile
that your, uh, smile muscles,
they just somehow trigger
a signal to your brain,
and you start to feel
the way you pretended to feel.
Yeah, really. Happy.
(chuckles)
Well, I suppose it
is kind of difficult
to cancel at this late date.
But I-I-I thought maybe...
You know, Katie's
such a lucky girl.
ZEB:
Nice save, Beck.
How do you manage
to pull these things off?
Well, it's not like
I ever had a choice.
What is that supposed to mean?
Oh, never mind.
You know, maybe I should
get myself a dog.
I mean, if I had
a dog to walk,
it would be easier
to meet people, right?
Maybe you should just get away
from the Open Arms
for a while.
Go somewhere,
visit someone.
Yeah, well that's my point.
Who would I visit?
Surely you can
think of someone.
REBECCA:
Mother, I have to leave
first thing in the morning.
But you just got here.
Yeah, but I
have a big
anniversary party
at the Open Arms.
Oh, that place.
Oh, darling, no.
That place is how
I make my money.
What little there is of it.
That's the Daviches' business.
No, actually
it's mine.
And there's Poppy
to think about.
Oh, that old man.
Is he still
alive?
Yes, he's still alive.
Exactly how are you related?
He's Joe's father's
twin brother.
You know that, Mother.
Darling.
You could have done
so much better.
Like how?
Oh, you were such
a brilliant
student, Rebecca.
Do you remember that
paper on Robert E. Lee?
Didn't the professor say
that you could expand it
into an honors project?
Well, he suggested
that I...
And before you got started,
bang, here comes Joe Davich and
puts you to work.
Mother...
And poor
Will Allenby.
He didn't
know
what hit him.
One day you were
as good as engaged,
and the next you up
and married a man
that nobody knew from Adam.
I made a choice.
Well, it was
the wrong choice.
You and Will Allenby
were soul mates.
You've been a different woman
ever since you jilted Will.
(bell tolling)
POPPY:
Rebecca!
Where were you?
(phone ringing)
You knew where I was, Poppy.
I was at
my mother's.
Oh, is she
still alive?
Is that Biddy?
It's not like I wasn't
gonna tell you.
Why doesn't anybody
answer this? Hello?
Uh, uh, Open Arms, for
all of life's occasions.
You've always
hated my cooking.
Yeah?
That's not true.
Tomorrow night at 8:00.
Besides, we just
want you
That's right
to be able to enjoy
the wedding.
All right, well, we'll be very
happy to see you then.
Oh, please.
Yes. Bye-bye.
What was that all about?
Oh, she's mad
because
I don't want her
to do the food.
Barry and I just want
a more
straightforward menu.
And besides, Biddy's never done
a garden wedding before.
Who's having
a garden wedding?
We are. Here.
Mother suggested it.
I think it's
a great idea.
Oh, Tina suggested it.
Oh, is Tina doing
the landscaping?
Of course not--
Mother doesn't arrive
until two days
before the wedding.
Aha. I see.
We can do
it, Beck.
I am a florist,
after all.
(horn honks)
(car doors slam)
(several people talking
at once)
Mother's here!
(all talking at once)
Oh, Rachel. Dear!
Rebecca.
Mother brought us
gifts from London.
Oh. Nice.
Oh, Mother,
please.
Oh, Mother, I love them.
For your chignon.
Oh.
Oh, thank you so much.
It's about 1812.
All that tea with
this instant family.
Mother, this
is perfect.
Oh, do you like it?
I found it in Capri.
Mother, I love it.
Min Foo, she's
not your mother.
Oh, I-I just...
Oh, Minerva, I've
always thought of you
as my fourth daughter,
haven't I?
Rebecca, come,
come, come.
You haven't opened
your present yet.
Oh. Okay.
Oh. An apron.
I thought something useful.
Thank you.
Now, Barry, tell me all
about the wedding plans.
Well, we finally
found a minister.
Nono and I were
at a restaurant
the other night
Mm-hmm.
wondering who we
could get to marry us,
and our waitress said,
"Well, I can do that."
So, what'll it be?
Do you, like, take
this woman here
to be your lawfully
wedded wife?
Oh, you're
joking.
Turns out she has
some kind
of certificate
she sent away for
through
the mail.
You didn't
tell me this.
It's...
Perfectly legal,
and she said
she'd do it
for free.
Oh, well.
Why not?
It's all a big
charade,
anyhow, I mean, my singing
teacher was devastated
when I married
Joe, I mean,
"My dear, you
are throwing away
a God-given talent."
I mean, marriage may be useful
during those little
child-bearing years,
but, all that, "My darling,
aren't you amazing?"
gives away to blood
pressure monitoring
and hand holding when
the man retires
and he can't think what
to do with themselves.
And the wives, meanwhile, start
longing to get free
from this institution
invented by males
for their own benefit.
It's all a primitive
tribal ritual,
meant to make us forget
we're merely propagating
the species.
(man clearing throat)
She certainly knows
the right thing to say
to a bride and groom.
(phone dialing)
Oh, hello.
Is this Alumni Records?
This is Rebecca
Holmes Davich.
I'm looking for
a, um, an address of
a classmate, Allenby.
Will Allenby. Yeah.
Oh, Dr.Allenby.
He teaches there?
Ah. Okay.
Oh, good.
All right.
Thanks very much.
Okay, bye-bye.
(sighs)
I can't believe
Uncle Poppy's
still here.
He was always such a bore.
I mean, all the Daviches,
a bunch of mopers.
How ironic
their profession
was throwing
parties.
I mean, just
because your house
has 14 foot ceilings
doesn't automatically
turn you into
a social butterfly.
I don't know how you've managed
all these years.
I just put one foot
in front of the other.
You don't have any,
shall we say,
man friends, I suppose.
No.
Well, of
course not.
After baby-sitting
Joe Davich,
why would you want one?
Yes, why would I?
Oh. Ah.
This place is like
a time machine.
Same old sink.
Same sticky wooden cabinets.
Same scummy little
drinking glasses.
Same rusty screen door.
Why, how American.
Instant lawn!
I knew we could
create a garden here.
Very impressive.
Thanks a lot.
Been working out every day.
Oh.
(playing traditional
introduction)
(piano continues over monitor)
She's so cute.
("Wedding March"
plays on piano)
Oh...
Today we are gathered here
to witness
a celebration
of the human
family.
The uniting
of two people
in marriage.
Nono and Barry come
before us here today
to...
be united in marriage.
Theirs is a love
that springs from
the affection
of those who loved
them into being.
And to that source,
let us all turn and ask,
who gives this woman?
Oh.
Me.
(chuckles)
London, well...
Our mother's
actually flirting
with her new
son-in-law.
Nono's about to kill her.
She was telling Barry
they ought to take Peter
on their honeymoon.
Every time, you
girls can't wait
for your mother
to get here.
Now you can't wait
for her to leave.
Oh, I told Nono
that Peter could stay here.
Is that cake a little slanted?
What do you mean?
Well, look.
Hmm.
Well, what do you expect?
First Nono doesn't even want me
to cater the wedding,
then she does.
I mean, she's lucky
there's a cake at all.
Oh, honey,
it's a lovely cake.
It just needs a little...
Peter, I have
a job for you.
No. I can't.
Oh, yes, of
course you can.
You just-just
be creative.
And we're smiling,
and we're smiling.
Yes, and we're smiling.
Um...
Sir, um, you're-you're
in the shot.
Can you...?
Yeah, okay.
Oh.
Thank you.
You did a great job
with those strawberries.
PHOTOGRAPHER:
We're smiling
and we're smiling.
Nice.
(whistling)
Okay, everyone.
Everyone, group
photo, group photo.
Yes, group photo. Okay.
That's right.
Okay, um, will the people
who are not related
by blood-- can you move
to the sides, please?
I can't get you all
into the picture.
That'd be us.
We'll just...
Oh, Beck, Peter, come on.
Come on, Beck.
Oh, all right.
PHOTOGRAPHER:
We're smiling, and...
Quickly.
PHOTOGRAPHER:
Okay.
Smiles, and we're smiling,
and we're smiling.
(crickets chirping)
(phone rings)
Dr. Allenby.
Will.
Laura?
Who?
Will, this is, uh,
Rebecca Holmes Davich.
Rebecca?
Oh, gosh, I... I hope
you weren't asleep.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
I know it's...
I know it's late, uh...
Oh, my, I didn't realize
how late.
You know, um, in fact,
I think that I'll just call back
another time.
B-B-Bye-bye.
Ay-yi-yi. Oh, no.
(phone rings)
Open Arms,
for all of life's occasions.
Yes, yes, that's right.
The Tea Dance starts
at 4:30 tomorrow.
You're welcome.
Who's he?
It's Peter Sanborn, Poppy.
He's staying
here with us
while Nono and Barry
are on their honeymoon.
Oh...
Remember?
Mm. Do you remember
Nono's wedding cake?
Yeah, I remember.
You know how it kind of...
it kind of...
it-it kind of tilted?
Mm, yeah.
Well, I don't feel that cakes
are Biddy's strong point,
so I'd like you to find
somebody else
to make my birthday cake.
I'll be 100 years old.
(chuckling):
December 11.
Mm...
Taking that to
your room, huh?
Yeah, I think I will.
Hey, how about you and I
go out for some ice cream, huh?
Get some fresh air?
No thanks.
How 'bout a game?
Uh, Clue, Checkers,
Monopoly, Scrabble, huh?
We can't tell your dad
you didn't do one thing
the whole time
you were here.
I don't care.
Well, I do. Come on.
I wish I hadn't promised Poppy
this party.
He'll forget it before
the balloons have shriveled...
...maybe the instant
it's over.
He could enjoy
the party
while it's
happening, though,
even if he did
forget it later.
Yeah.
Well, you're right
about that.
Hmm.
Guess this
is about all I can do.
Whoa. Ho, ho, ho.
60 points.
Hey, I suspect
you might be a hustler.
(phone ringing)
Open Arms, for all
of life's occasions.
Rebecca speaking.
This is Will Allenby.
Will.
H-How'd you get my number?
I looked at my caller ID.
Anyway, Rebecca...
...what did you call me for?
Oh, gosh, I, you know,
I just h-happened to be home--
I mean, at... at Mom's,
and-and she and I
just got talking
about old times,
and I thought to myself,
"Gee, wonder whatever happened
to... Will Allenby?
Wonder where he got to."
Oh. Well, I'm...
right here, where you left me...
at MacAdam, that is.
Well, no, I haven't been here
the whole time.
I... I did go away
for my doctorate.
Um, I teach here now.
Oh, that's wonderful, Will.
I'm the head
of the Physics Department.
Well, that's really wonderful.
Well, you know, it's been
such a long time.
Maybe-maybe you and I
should just get together,
you know, catch up, or...
I... I happen to be free
this evening.
Oh, this evening?
Oh, no, I-I couldn't do that,
'cause I've got a tea dance,
and then...
Oh, boy. This weekend,
I got a funeral,
and I got, uh,
an engagement party, but, um...
Well, what about Monday,
uh, um, at that place?
Is it still there?
The, um...
What is it, the Maple Tree?
It's here. I-I don't know
if it's still good, uh...
Well, why don't we just say
7:00, the Maple Tree?
All right.
Okay, good.
See you then.
That was my very first
boyfriend.
Well, my only
boyfriend,
besides Joe Davich.
(bell tolls)
(birds chirping)
Oh, good.
That's right.
Well, thanks for
watching him, honey.
That's okay.
He didn't play
with the kids at all.
He just sat reading a book
the whole time.
There's nothing wrong with that.
Why the sudden urge
to go shopping?
Oh, nothing, I'm
just sick of the
same old clothes.
Time for some
new ones.
Well, I'd better
get back.
(engine starts)
Bye, Peter.
Bye.
I decided not to tell
Min Foo about my date.
It's none of
her business.
Besides, it's not
really a date.
I used to love to read
when I was young.
I was quite an
intellectual,
like you.
If you were offered a trip
on a time machine,
would you take it?
Oh, I sure would.
I'd be crazy not to.
Would you go into the past
or the future?
The future.
Absolutely the future,
'cause I want to know
what's going to happen.
Yeah, me too.
(doorbell rings)
MAN:
Hello? Rebecca!
Oh, J.J.
Rebecca!
Oh, J.J., I'm so happy
you're here.
Boy, that ceiling
really needs to be patched.
Well, we'll do that.
REBECCA:
Yeah.
Mm. Oh.
Yeah, well, I-I'm
having dinner
with my old high school
sweetheart on Monday,
and I'm-I'm just as
nervous as a cat on a...
(chuckles):
You know, Tanya was my, uh,
high school sweetheart.
Really? My gosh.
You two really made
a go of it, huh?
Yeah.
Well, not that you haven't
had to... work at it.
Ain't that the truth?
Will you just give
it a little...?
Sure.
Yeah. No good, huh?
Well... the color's nice.
Mm.
W-w-w-what about those, uh,
harem pants you had on
the-the time I was patching
the bathroom?
Oh, no, no, no.
I-I don't want to wear
pants to a restaurant,
and, besides,
they didn't make...
(whispering):
Weren't good
for my derriere.
(laughing)
But... the color's nice.
Oh, Poppy, your tapioca's
in the fridge.
Uh-huh.
And don't forget
your penguin
program's on at 9:00.
Okay. I won't forget.
Night-night.
Yeah.
Have fun.
Okay.
Uh-huh. Mm. Yum.
Good evening.
Oh. Hi.
I'm meeting someone here.
I don't suppose...
Would that be him?
Uh, no.
Oh... I... William.
Hello, Will.
Hi.
Oh.
What happened to your
long golden braid?
My what? Oh, my gosh.
I got... I cut that off
long ago.
It was too much trouble.
May I tell Marvin
what you're having to drink?
Who's Marvin?
Iced tea, please.
Oh. I'll just have, um...
w-water, thank you.
Sparkling or still?
Pardon?
Tap, I think. Right?
Yes, tap.
It is so good to see you, Will.
Me too.
I mean, it's good for me
to see you, too.
Except for the braid,
you... you look
just the same.
Oh, no, no, I haven't
changed a bit. Ha, ha.
So, decided what you're having?
Well, not quite.
Oh, I-I-I'm sorry.
I'll see what I should be
having here.
Oh, you should go first,
Rebecca.
Oh. All right. Yes. Oops.
Oh, dear. Well, salmon's...
Uh, you have salmon,
I'm sure, don't you?
I always liked that.
That's it.
Thank you very much.
Okay, uh, salmon,
veal, rib roast...
Uh, maybe the rib roast?
And how would you like that
cooked?
Well done.
Thank you very much. Yeah.
Well done it is.
Or, uh, you know...
how 'bout the award, uh,
winning, uh, swordfish?
Swordfish.
U-unless...
would it actually be
the award-winning swordfish
if it didn't have
the sauce?
(laughs)
So, the swordfish,
no sauce,
and salad, no dressing,
thank you.
(clears throat)
Sorry, uh, I don't
eat out often.
I-I cook for myself.
Oh.
I make my
famous chili.
You remember my chili.
Oh, your chili.
Yes, right, of course.
The way I
prepare it
is, every Sunday,
I mix up two batches and then
divide them up into
seven containers.
And that's what
I'd eat each night for the week.
For the whole week?
Mm-hmm.
All week?
Yeah.
Of course, now I have
an extra container,
because of tonight.
I don't know how I'll
deal with that yet.
My, my.
Well, it sure sounds
like you've adjusted
to-to living by yourself.
I mean... since your divorce.
I can't complain.
I mean,
I-I rent a very nice apartment.
Mm-hmm.
It's even got a little s-study
that could be made
into a guest room,
and if my...
if my daughter ever wanted
to spend the night over.
Oh, well, you have a daughter?
Yes, a 17-year-old
high school senior.
Oh.
Beatrice.
Of course that...
That's nothing
compared to you.
Uh-uh.
No, that's right.
(laughing):
I... I'm way ahead of you.
I've got five grandchildren.
Hmm.
But that's
because my husband's
three girls are older,
from a previous marriage.
H-How did he pass away,
if-if you don't mind my asking?
No.
In a car wreck.
Ha. Oh, boy.
It was really sudden.
Well, of course,
a car wreck is a-always sudden.
It was just...
I was just so unprepared,
you know.
Mm. 26 years old.
And his girls had just adjusted
to the fact that I even existed.
(laughs)
Oh. Well, I'm not sure
I'd know how to deal with that.
I managed all right.
We... We were fine.
Thank you.
It seems so long ago,
doesn't it?
You broke my heart, Rebecca.
I mean, no warning.
I mean, I thought
everything was fine,
and then, you just
said good-bye
without a
reason why.
I had to hear
that you got married
two weeks later, from my mother.
Yeah. I'm... I'm...
I'm sorry.
You know, I-I...
I know I didn't handle that
very well, but, uh...
Everything
to your liking, folks?
Yes, uh,
everything's fine,
thank you.
Yeah.
I-I know
that I should have written,
but, uh, everything was just
moving so fast, you know.
And I just seemed
to be getting farther
and farther away
from my original self.
And then, this summer,
I just sort of...
I don't know.
I just sort of woke up,
and I thought,
"Who have you turned into?"
(sighs)
And that's why
I called you. I...
Oh, yeah.
Figured you could just
waltz right on back as if
you'd never
even left?
No, I never thought that.
Thought I'd
say, "Oh,
"sure, Rebecca.
"I forgive you for everything.
"Let's go back
to, uh, the
good old days."
No, no, no.
I never thought that at all.
I trusted you.
I'm really sorry...
I can see
this has been a mistake.
MAN (on television):
Preening can be a part
of the breeding behavior.
Among couples,
it is sign of love
when they clean each other's
feathers.
(sighs)
(snoring)
As soon as penguins
are out of the water,
they start cleaning
and combing their feathers.
Unlike his Antarctic neighbors,
the penguin mates for life.
The pains are five minutes
apart.
Oh.
Oh, honey.
Just remind yourself
that you're gonna get
a baby out of this.
Bye, Mommy.
I bet that you are gonna have
a brand new brother
or sister before lunchtime.
Min Foo is having a baby?
I thought she was divorced.
Poppy, she divorced
Professor Drake.
And then she divorced LaVon.
And then she married Hakim.
Hakim?
(laughing):
Oh, good God.
An-An Arab?
(phone ringing)
Poppy.
Open Arms. F-for...
O-Oh. Hi. Yes, yes, J.J.
Yeah, well, I'm afraid
that faucet still is leaky,
but listen, J.J.,
Min Foo's having
her baby today.
Yeah. So, I got to...
Oh, oh, your-your
daughter-in-law, too.
Oh, that's great.
Well, then you can understand
why I got to keep the line free.
All right. Bye, bye, thanks.
Ooh.
You said
we'd have a
new brother
or sister before
lunchtime.
Is Mommy okay?
Oh, yes.
Of course she is.
And, you know,
sometimes...
Just move your little drawings,
kids, for me.
Sometimes it just takes
a little bit longer.
Oh, you did a lovely job
on those candles.
Let's light 'em up.
Razzle dazzle time. Whoo!
(phone ringing)
If I could undo one
modern invention,
it would be the telephone.
I would choose the zipper.
(laughs)
(laughter)
Open...
WILL:
Rebecca? It's Will.
Oh, Will.
Uh, I really... I... I'm...
I don't know
why you rushed off like that.
The-The waiter was wondering
if anything was wrong.
And I... I'm worried
that you might have
misunderstood me.
Oh, Will, listen, thank you
so much for calling me.
Listen, my daughter's
about to have a baby,
and I really can't talk.
Uh, thanks.
Okay. I...
(dial tone)
Oh, boy.
(phone rings)
(groans)
Open Ar... Hakim?
Yes?Whoo!
Yes, I think Abdul's
a wonderful name for a boy.
Yay!
Oh.
Come over here.
(baby coos)
Oh, handsome boy.
Look at you.
You're so beautiful.
Welcome to
the world, Abdul.
Say hi to Grandma.
(laughter)
(keys jangling)
(door creaking)
(beep)
Rebecca, it's Will Allenby
again.
I trust everything's fine
with your daughter's baby.
I, uh... I just wanted
to apologize
for the other evening.
Lately, it's been all I can do
to just get up in the morning.
I look in the mirror and think,
"Gosh, same old me."
(beep)
Lord in heaven,
tell me everything.
Well, Will has been divorced
about two years now.
Perfect.
If a man is divorced,
he's always angry
at his ex-wife.
But if he's widowed,
he always feels guilty
about remarrying.
Mother, who said anything
about remarrying?
We're just having
a meal together.
That should put us back here
about 9:30 or 10:00.
Is that enough time?
Oh, yeah, that's-that's
plenty of time.
Thanks, Zeb.
Oh, Beck, so,
is this a...
Is this an actual
date you're having?
No. I'm much too old
to be dating.
(laughter)
Okay, Poppy.
Oh.
Mm. Don't you two get
into any trouble.
Okay.
Too old to be dating...
(laughter)
(doorbell rings)
Oh.
Whoa.
Oh, you shouldn't have.
I know I'm early.
I allowed a little extra time,
in case I got lost.
Come on in.
Oh. My goodness.
Let's see.
Um, why don't
we set it down
right over here.
Whoo. Here you go.
Ah.
(laughs)
My, isn't that...
Isn't that unusual.
Yeah.
And what's it called?
I don't know.
They said it
was impossible
to kill, is all.
(laughs):
Oh, good.
Well, I guess
I should have dressed
up a little more, huh?
Oh, no. I'm not so dressed up.
Oh, this is,
uh, very...
Well, this is quite a place
you have.
Well, don't
let it fool ya.
I expect the ceiling
to fall down any...
any minute now.
Well, I mean, it's...
it's really impressive.
It must have quite a...
(doorbell rings)
Yeah?
Uh, quite a history to it.
Mm-hmm.
Um, I...
I believe your doorbell rang.
Oh, yes, right.
Well, just make
yourself at home.
Hi, J.J.
Hi.
I just wanted to let you know
that we're gonna be out
in the back,
uh, planting those a... azal...
Okay. Fine.
Wha-What is that?
(whispering):
You know, I'm not sure exactly.
I-I-I've never seen anything
like it.
Thanks, J.J.
Hey, you-you want
to take a peek at them
before we start planting?
No, it's fine, it's fine.
How about I fetch you one
of those,
uh, hang tags
with a color photo?
You know,
I really don't care, J.J.
I've got company.
Oh.
High school sweetheart.
(chuckles)
Was this your husband?
(laughs)
N-No, no.
We got that at
a garage sale.
Oh.
Come on, I'll show you
what my husband looked like.
Oh, uh... Oh, here.
(phone rings)
I'll-I'll just
let the...
the machine get that.
Now, he's here
somewhere, but...
Oh, well here's my
newest grandson, Abdul.
And here he is with his mother,
Min Foo, my daughter.
(phone continues ringing)
And this is my eldest
stepdaughter, Biddy,
standing next
to Min Foo's ex, LaVon.
And that's Nono.
Oh, doesn't she make
a beautiful bride?
And let's see.
This is Patch.
She's celebrating
the girls lacrosse team
winning State.
And, uh...
Oh. There's Joe.
Yes. Well, you
always did want
to have a lot of children.
I did?
Mm-hmm.
Gosh, I don't
remember that.
Would you bring the
biscuits in, please?
Sure.
(men talking outside)
What's going on
in your backyard?
Oh, they're putting in
some azaleas.
Oh.
(phone rings)
This is like running
a plantation.
The, uh, divorce
was Laura's idea.
One day, she
just announced
that she wanted
me to move out.
Of course,
she kept our daughter.
Laura's always had a better
understanding of Beatrice.
It's only natural, I guess.
She's... so much younger than I.
Not like you.
Excuse me?
I, I mean
you were always
so mature for your age,
so involved with your
studies, so... serious.
I always regret
that I didn't finish
my education.
Mmm. Do you remember
this new theory
that I had of,
of why Robert E. Lee
decided to cast his lot
with the South?
Lee?
Mmm.
Maybe I should finish
that research.
Th-there are other things
you can do, too, uh...
Museums could be
particularly edifying.
Gosh, I can't remember
the last time I was in a museum.
Perhaps we could
go together.
I'm going down to Washington
on Friday.
Maybe you could join me.
Wonderful museums there.
Oh, I'd love to do that, Will.
(phone rings)
Friday, then.
Good.
Your phone sure does ring a lot.
Can we go
in the other room?
Rebecca...
It's occurred to me
that this was very providential.
What?
When you telephoned me
the first time,
I had just hit rock bottom.
I mean, it's
so incredibly
providential
that you called me
when you did, Rebecca.
In the old days,
ice cream places
offered unlimited samples.
Egg nog, pistachio,
rum raisin--
any flavor.
Well, hi.
What are you doing here?
We stopped
for ice cream,
but Poppy was
so displeased
with the service,
he said he'd just as soon
have his dessert at home.
Hi, I'm, I'm Will Allenby.
Hi, I'm Zeb, Rebecca's
brother-in-law.
This is my uncle,
Paul Davich.
Sorry to barge
in like this.
I thought
you were going to the movies.
After that
smart aleck
in the, in the
ice cream parlor,
I, I didn't have the heart
for it.
Wh-What's for dessert?
Well, I remembered
that Will
didn't care for sweets,
so I didn't make
a dessert.
POPPY:
Oh.
Well, I'm going to take
a look.
So...
you knew our Rebecca
in high school.
"Our Rebecca"?
Well, actually, um...
kindergarten.
Beck! Are you home?
(sighing)
He-here.
Where have you been?
I've been phoning
and phoning you
all evening.
Uh, Will, this is
my stepdaughter, Nono,
and this
is her stepson, Peter.
This is Will Allenby,
my old
high school sweetheart.
Really? Nice
to meet you.
Go ahead, Peter,
tell Rebecca
what you wanted
to ask her.
What, honey?
Um... at
my school,
they have this exhibit
of these projects.
And they have us
invite our grandparents.
It's on Friday.
Is it this Friday?
Uh-huh.
And, I know you're
not really my grandma,
but since my dad's parents
are dead,
I was wondering if...
I'd be honored to.
Ice cream--
who wants ice cream?
Super Chunky Chango ice cream.
(laughter)
I'm so sorry about Friday,
but, you know, I just,
I just couldn't
disappoint him.
No, of course not.
The museums will
always be there.
Yeah.
Well, you still have
quite a drive, right?
Yes.
I'll call you.
I'll call you tomorrow.
(clanging)
(chuckling)
Yikes.
Thanks for supper.
REBECCA:
Toast! To Abdul Abdulazim.
His arrival
makes us beam.
It's such a pleasure
to have a new boy.
Let's hope he's as nice
as Lateesha and Joey.
(screaming)
Joey got stung
by a bee!
Oh, my Lord.
He's allergic!
Well, how did a bee get in here?
It'll be okay.
Let's just go to the hospital.
I'll get some ice.
I've got Abdul.
Dixon, you and Emmy
take Lateesha to the backyard.
Wait, I'm coming.
I've got the ice.
Beck?
Oh, Poppy, please, not now.
Beck, I... I don't feel so good.
Here's a list
of all of his medicines.
He's allergic
to, uh,
to penicillin and tomatoes.
Is this a heart attack?
I didn't have my,
my 100th birthday party yet.
You'll have your
party, Poppy,
I promise you.
I'll call you.
PARAMEDIC:
Watch your step.
(monitor beeping)
It's okay.
It's going to be okay.
How are we doing?
Well, he's not feeling so...
Zeb... they're trying
to finish me off.
Nope, they're
letting you go.
Turns out
it was indigestion.
(chuckling):
Oh.
Indigestion?
I spoke with the resident.
He said you had three cupcakes
at the baby welcoming.
Well, what if I did?
I've eaten far more many a time.
We should let them know
at home.
Poppy...
They must be
pretty worried.
Yeah. Did Joey get his shot?
He's already
back at the party,
making up for lost time.
I'll go call.
Oh, God, I am so relieved
that it was only indigestion.
Yeah, well,
I don't know
what the world is coming to
if a man can't eat
three measly cupcakes
without folks
calling an ambulance.
(laughter)
REBECCA:
Oh, I forgot
the dessert.
You do like dessert,
now, don't you, monsieur?
Whoa.
(laughing)
Thank you.
How's your father-in-law?
My father-in-law?
Mm-hmm.
Oh, you mean Poppy.
Uh, he's not
my father-in-law.
He's Joe's uncle.
Want this one?
And you still live with him,
even though
you're barely related.
Well, I sort of
inherited him.
He came with the house.
(chuckles)
For a while
I resented
having to take
care of him,
but when I thought
he might die, I...
I realized
how much he means to me.
Don't mind
my asking, but...
how come
after your husband died
you never remarried?
I don't know.
I, I think what you look
for in a person changes.
You know, when I was young,
I wanted somebody "other."
The most wildly other person.
Not... well, that's why
I was drawn to Joe, I guess.
But now I just,
uh, think the idea
of being with
somebody different
would just...
be exhausting.
Well, look at you and me.
We're totally different,
Rebecca.
We are?
Oh, well it might seem so now,
but...
well, I think of the old days,
the things that interested us...
well, I think,
yeah, that was back...
that was back
when we were grownups.
'Course, you still are
a grownup, but me, I...
I feel like I've been
traveling
in reverse.
(chuckling)
WILL:
Robert E. Lee.
Boy, things sure
have changed
since we were
at MacAdam, huh?
WILL:
Go.
REBECCA:
Oh, wow!
This was such a good idea,
Will.
Well, you said you wanted to
continue on with your research.
This might be interesting.
Uh-huh.
This one might be good.
On special order.
Oh, dear.
No, no, it's all right.
Hmm? Won't take long?
Uh-uh.
No problem.
Okay. Come on.
(beeping)
We'll call you when it comes in.
Great, thanks;
you're done.
Let me grab these.
I'll take some of those.
No, no, no; here we go.
Oh, well.
Chivalry is not dead.
(chuckling)
Thank you.
(phone rings)
Hello.
ZEB:
Hey, Beck.
Oh, hi, Zeb.
What you doing?
Ooh, I'm reading
a fascinating book.
Me, too.
The Harmful Effects
of Nightlights on Children.
Nightlights?
Children who've been raised
with nightlights
end up with vision problems.
Their eyes
don't get enough rest.
They should read this book--
that'd put them to sleep.
Well, from now on,
I am going to read
two books a week-- serious ones.
And I am going to join a gym,
'cause I'm going
to get into shape.
You're fine the way you are.
I am not.
I'm a slug.
You of all people-- a doctor.
No, from now on,
I am concentrating on me.
You're right.
Good night.
(sighs)
Hi, nice to meet you.
How's that?
Good.
Oh, that's great.
(devices buzzing and clicking)
Oh, where's your project?
It's over here.
REBECCA:
This is yours?
PETER:
Uh-huh.
Oh, my gosh.
(laughing)
(gasping and chuckling)
This is wonderful!
I don't know
how you did this.
What do...
what do
your teachers say?
I think they kind
of liked it.
Oh, I bet they do.
Is there a motor?
(chuckling):
That's a secret.
Oh.
Oh, then don't tell me.
Don't tell me.
I will just view this
as a miracle.
You want to see
the other projects?
No. No, I...
I just want to stay here
and admire this one.
Oh, no, no.
That boy is brilliant.
Yes. Everybody keeps telling me
how bright he is.
I just...
I wish he could drive.
Honey, did you
see his project?
I don't know if it was
music or art or science,
but it is astounding.
I was the one
who had to ferry him
to the back of beyond
for supplies.
Barry was away
attending a conference,
wouldn't you know?
I know it's hard.
But I so wish
that you could enjoy this boy,
because he is going
to be grown and gone in a flash.
Easy for you to say.
You don't have
the slightest idea
what it's like being saddled
with somebody else's kid
when you're still
practically on your honeymoon.
GIRL:
No, no, no, no!
I thought maybe you'd like
to meet my daughter.
Oh, Will, I would love
to meet your daughter.
Oh, mm. Something I can bring?
No, just yourself.
What shall I wear?
Anything...
or-or maybe...
no... just anything.
No, Will, you can tell me.
I mean, is there
something special
you want me to wear or not wear?
Well, I...
I-I-I don't know, um...
(clears throat)
Maybe... something
not too... hippie.
Hippie?
Well, it's-it's just
that some of your clothes
tend to be a bit... exotic.
Oh.
And-and I want Beatrice to focus
on you more as a person.
Oh, oh, oh, I see. Okay.
(doorbell rings)
Ta-da.
Oh. Well, you
look great.
Thank you.
Hi. Come on
in, come in.
My, this is wonderful.
Come in here.
Here, ha-have a seat.
All right. Thank you.
I keep feeling I should get
a cleaning service in.
Oh. Uh, Beatrice
isn't here yet, huh?
No, but I expect her.
Aw...
What?
Everything's going
to be just fine.
You don't know Beatrice.
We are going to
have such fun.
I'm serving this nutritious,
all-grain dish.
She's a vegetarian.
(doorbell rings)
Oh, boy.
Excuse me.
I used chicken stock,
but don't say a word.
Oh. My lips are sealed.
Hi, Beatrice.
Hello, Beatrice.
So, you told me to
come here at 6:00.
Here I am.
Well, thank you, Bea.
I'm very glad you came.
Are we eating
supper or not?
Oh, oh, don't you want
to sit around a while
and talk? I...
Talk? About what?
And who is this lady, anyhow?
Oh. I'm, um... I'm, um,
a very old, old friend
of your father's.
We grew up together.
Oh, so I guess next,
you're going to tell me
that you guys have fallen
madly in love or something.
Beatrice...
Oh! Oh, my goodness.
Well, I guess we've
fallen in fond,
but really, I came here
to meet you tonight.
Your father's told me
so much about you.
Yeah? Well, I'm not here
'cause I want to be.
I'm here because
he promised me
my own cell
phone if I came.
Oh.
Okay, we've met.
Can I go now?
You-you-you haven't eaten.
All right, if you insist,
let's eat.
Oh.
(clears throat)
This is a complete,
in one dish, whole grain meal.
Oh.
Entirely vegetarian.
Actually, I eat meat now.
You do?
Well, we can all stand
to eat some grain
from time to time.
Beatrice, pass me
your plate.
I'm afraid
I'm not much of a chef.
Oh, I think you were wonderful
to make the effort.
Thanks.
(groans)
(scoffs)
So... do many men
have you to supper, Rebecca?
Oh. Well, I don't... No.
'Cause, actually, you seem
pretty normal on the surface.
I'm just wondering
if you realize
what kind of guy
you're eating with, here.
Uh, he's a pretty nice guy.
The guy who
kidnapped our dog
when Mom asked
him for a divorce.
Your dog?
Our little dog, Flopsie.
I did not kidnap
Flopsie Doodle.
I borrowed her.
He stole her
while we were out,
and we came home,
and we called, "Flopsie."
No Flopsie.
So my mom phoned my dad.
We knew it was him.
And she said that she
was calling the police.
Do you know what he did?
He lied, and he said,
oh, he had no idea what
she was talking about.
Then he opened up his door
and let Flopsie run out
all by herself,
when everybody knows
what a terrible sense
of direction she has.
It's lucky she wasn't killed.
I was feeling sad, okay?
I was having
a difficult time.
Like it wasn't difficult
for Mom and me?
I went looking for her
in the rainstorm.
I was out half the night,
and when I found her,
all covered with mud,
I-I put her
in my brand-new car,
and I brought
her home.
How many times
can I apologize?
Well, just so you know,
you're boyfriend's a total perv.
You're getting me
a cell phone tomorrow.
(door opens)
(door slams)
Well, I guess this
wasn't very successful.
Oh, well, it's...
You know what?
Now that I've met your family,
I want you to meet mine.
I mean, I already...
Well, three or four
you bumped into,
but I... but I mean
a proper dinner party
with everybody there.
Okay?
That'd be great.
Good.
Oh...
Gracious.
(chuckles)
Well, hey, thank you.
Thanks for dinner.
Thanks very much.
If I'd known that Beatrice
was back eating meat,
I would have served my chili.
Hmm. Mm-hmm.
All right. Bye-bye.
Bye.
Hmm.
(crickets chirping)
ZEB:
He kidnapped their dog?
REBECCA:
Oh, yeah.
Oh, boy. Well, in a way,
I think he's still, um,
in mourning for his marriage.
You know, he's been going
through a really difficult time.
He's kind of an odd guy,
and I just thought a party
where he could meet
all of you would...
Rebecca, I've met Will
on a couple of occasions.
Yeah, I know, but I-I'd like him
to meet everybody,
all together, you know--
a more formal atmosphere.
Formal?
Yeah, just not some typical
Davich free-for-all potluck
where Will could be overwhelmed,
but something... sedate
and organized.
You know, everybody arriving
at a pre-arranged time,
talking about civilized topics,
you know?
Why can't we bring children?
It's a grown-up affair.
I want you to meet
the man in my life.
You have a man in your life?
You never told me that.
Oh, you know Will has been
coming around now and then.
I thought he was just a friend.
(baby cooing)
Why are you springing this
on me now?
I am not springing
anything on you.
This is not about you.
Saturday night?
You're never free on Saturdays.
Is the Open Arms going under?
No more than usual.
Well, haven't I already met
this person?
Yes, but-but I
want this to be
a more official
introduction
to the family
as a whole.
Okay, look, whatever.
I'm running late, okay?
Okay. Bye.
(phone rings)
(sighs)
Open Arms.
How come you invited Min Foo
to dinner and not me?
Patch, I was just going to...
Is this because
she's your real daughter?
I hate you.
You're not my mother.
(gasps)
Patch, for heaven's sakes,
I'm inviting all of you.
Oh, Beck, this
is so exciting.
A man in your life.
I am making
something fabulous.
What is that
you're wearing?
Oh, just something
different
than my usual
hippie dippie
color crazy
thing, you know?
Call it flight attendant
casual.
(laughs)
(doorbell rings)
Well, fasten your seat
belts, me merry crew.
Hi, Will.
Am I late
or early or... okay?
Oh, you're... you're
right on time. Come on.
Okay.
Yeah.
WILL:
Thanks.
I trust you have nothing
against hearts of palm.
That what that is?
I thought it'd
be a nice...
symbolic touch.
Hearts, romance, you know?
Hmm. Palm trees
are cut up for that?
(grunts)
Broccoli plants are cut up.
Asparagus shoots are cut up.
Don't tell me you're one
of those food avoiders.
No, no, no, I'm...
not that much into experiment.
Sea urchins are an experiment.
Hearts of palm is just a salad.
So, you and Rebecca
have-have known each other
since you were kids?
50 years.
Oh! Can I really have
been alive that long?
And now you're reunited.
That's, uh...
Must be complicated, though,
living in separate towns.
WILL:
Oh, that's exactly it.
My odometer's taken a huge leap,
and my engine's developed
a cough, uh...
Oh, well, you-you should give
J.J. a call.
WILL:
J.J.?
Yeah, J.J. does a lot of,
uh, odd jobs around here,
but, oh, he is
a gifted mechanic.
He's the only one
that can coax my Chevy along.
J.J.'s great.
Yeah. Oh, you know,
he is forever bragging
about his wife, Tanya.
Look, see, um, they had, uh,
themselves made up
to look like Bonnie and Clyde,
and then they had
their picture taken.
(Rebecca laughs)
That's your mechanic?
Mm. Well,
lately, though,
Tanya's had to increase
her medication.
Poor thing, you know,
she's just given to these sort
of demented delusions, and, uh,
oh, gosh, one day,
she was walking
across somebody's front porch;
she was wildly
flinging a-a souvenir
Japanese sword.
Ay-yi-yi. And, uh...
J.J. said that that's not
the real true Tanya.
He just still thinks
that his wife is... amazing.
That's the man
that repairs your cars.
(door opening)
Oh.
Hello. We're in here.
MIN FOO:
I told you,
she's not gonna be...
Hi.
I know you said
adults only...
Hi.
but I'm still
breast-feeding.
What do you expect?
It's all right.
Hi.
Hey.
Don't put him there.
Someone's gonna
step on him.
This man is hopeless.
At 7:00 in
the morning,
he's asking me to
brew him coffee.
I only asked if coffee
had been made, Min Foo.
You could have
seen for yourself
that it wasn't made.
Shh. It's all right,
it's all right.
What is that
you're wearing?
PATCH:
It's us.
Hi.
Sorry we're late.
What is that you're wearing?
It is my brand-new suit
that I bought on Thursday,
and I like it,
so don't
say a word.
Ah, everyone,
I would like
you to meet
Will Allenby,
the person
I invited you here to meet.
(silence)
(silverware clattering)
(baby cooing)
(all talking quietly)
Min Foo, do that
in the other room.
MIN FOO:
I'm decently
covered.
I'm not sitting
here naked.
We have company.
What must he think?
I'm sure you've
seen a woman
nursing a
baby before.
Well, yes.
I mean, of course.
(baby fussing)
Though, not
at a dinner table, but...
(sighs)
(baby crying)
Oh, boy.
Patch, go
after her.
I will not.
MIN FOO:
Hakim!
I shall go.
A toast.
Oh, yes, a toast.
Yeah.
POPPY:
A toast.
Good.
POPPY:
I propose a toast to...
a toast to me and my birthday.
(laughter)
Oh, Poppy.
It is not your birthday.
POPPY:
Oh.
(whispering):
This is a toast
to Will, welcome.
Oh, yeah, a toast to Will.
To-To welcome Will.
ALL:
To Will.
POPPY:
Here's to Will.
Here, here.
(all talking at once)
WILL:
Thank you.
Ah.
Um... maybe a toast
to... Rebecca.
Oh.
To Rebecca for being so lovely,
so gracious,
and cheering up my life.
Thank you.
To Becky!
Rebecca.
ZEB:
Can't imagine where
we'd all be if
Rebecca hadn't
shown up.
She turned out
to be awfully
good for business.
(laughs):
Not at first.
I'm sure that Zeb remembers
the first time
I helped out at a party.
(laughs):
Oh, God.
I let fly a champagne cork...
(laughter)
...straight
into a woman's bosom.
(laughter)
ZEB:
Right.
Rebecca crumples to the floor
in mortification,
like she's the one who got hit,
and this women just
keeps right on talking,
completely unaware.
Falsies was my
considered opinion.
(laughter)
Then she bends down
and she says,
"Are you all right, dear?"
And then I just popped right up,
and I...
(laughs):
I poured the
champagne...
(sighs)
...like nothing
happened.
(laughs)
Hmm.
(low chatter)
(clears throat)
(chatter,
silverware clattering)
HAKIM:
? Oh Abdul, boy ?
? The pipes,
the pipes are calling ?
Here.
? From glen to glen ?
Oh.
? And down the mountainside... ?
Sweet.
I didn't know he was Irish.
I can't believe
that she brought
the baby here.
(chatter, soft laughter,
singing continues)
? Oh, Abdul, boy ?
? Oh, Abdul, boy,
I love you so. ?
WOMAN:
I'll call you tomorrow.
Nice to see
you again, Will.
REBECCA:
I loved that.
Thank you, bye, bye.
We'll see
you again.
Thanks, Beck.
Thank you, Rebecca.
Bye, bye. All right.
It was nice to
meet you, Will.
Bye, Will.
Thanks. Bye.
Yeah. Frankly, I'm
having a hard time
sorting them all out.
(laughs)
I mean, why-why
is that one,
uh, stepdaughter,
uh, Chinese?
And... and the
fella, uh, Troy--
is he Biddy's
husband?
No, no. Fir-First of all,
Min Foo is my daughter,
not my stepdaughter.
I named her Minerva.
But Joe took one look
at her paintbrush hair
and her sleepy eyes--
no wider than slits-- and...
Hey there,
little Min Foo.
REBECCA:
As for Troy,
he's the brother
of Biddy's fianc?, Roland,
who died suddenly.
Troy is gay.
REBECCA:
And then,
after Roland died,
Biddy discovered
she was pregnant with Dixon,
so Troy moved back in
and helped raise him.
And he's been with them
every step of the way.
So, Dixon was conceived,
uh, before...
I'll get the family album.
Oh, but Poppy,
your milk's almost ready.
And anyway, Will has already
more or lessseen
the family album.
I'll get the family album.
REBECCA:
Oh, boy.
Now you're in for it.
So,
how'd you like my family?
Well, um...
(clears throat)
they're... they're
ver-very interesting.
Yeah, well.
Ah, you didn't see Min Foo
at her best.
I'm afraid
she's beginning an old pattern.
Uh, have a baby,
ditch the husband.
Oh, they all are
pretty outspoken...
It's-It's kind
of like those nature programs,
you know, where the female
does away with the male
after he donates his sperm?
Pardon?
So many parties.
POPPY:
Yeah. Isn't
that the truth.
I mean, everywhere I look.
Well.
On the refrigerator,
in this album.
Everybody's celebrating.
I mean, we just drank a toast
in there.
And now you've brought me
in here,
and you've got me looking
at photos of toasts.
Years of toasts.
Oh, they're
photographs.
I mean, you don't
usually take pictures
of people reading a
book or playing chess.
Chess?
(laughs):
We-We don't play chess.
WILL:
Well, I
mean you...
You do have an unusual amount
of parties,
you'll have to admit.
Every time we try
to get together, we have
to work
around your social events.
Social events.
WILL:
Well, I mean, I understand
you're a social type.
But consorting
with your mechanic?
Sharing marital secrets
with a stranger?
J.J.'s not a stranger.
Well, from what
you've told me,
his attitude about his wife
shows a total lack
of responsibility.
Piffle.
Oh. Oh.
Here's my Joycie.
(chuckles)
She was a cutie
all right. Ooh.
Yeah.
I better haul myself off to bed.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, I-I
think I'm, uh...
I'm gonna go
to bed, too.
Oh. All right.
Oh.
Don't forget
my birthday party.
Oh, I wouldn't miss it.
Oh, yeah.
When is his birthday?
It's in December.
What date in December?
I don't think
we'll be seeing
each other in
December, Will.
What-What...
What do you mean?
Or before
that, either.
Was it something that I did?
You didn't do anything, Will.
Was it your family? Didn't...
I mean, didn't they like me?
I'm sure they liked you.
Zeb?
Well, obviously,
he's my competition,
although, I...
No, the fact
of the matter is, this...
It just won't work, Will.
It won't.
I'm sorry to do this to you.
Again.
(sighs)
Good-bye, Will.
Well...
all right then.
Good-bye, Rebecca.
WOMAN:
Practically as old
as Robert E. Lee himself.
Sorry it took so long
to come in.
Oh... no, that's-that's, uh...
that's all right.
Thank you.
No, really, really,
my life is finished.
It finished
when the girls got grown...
so here I am, just, you know,
hanging around,
marking time, waiting
for things to wind down.
ZEB:
Rebecca, are you all right?
Well, yeah. Define "all right."
Where's Will in all this?
Gone.
You ditched him?
(chuckles):
Yep, but that's not the problem.
The problem is just I've...
I've outlived myself.
Well... remember
what George Eliot said.
What did George Eliot say?
It's never too late
to do what you want to do.
Well, you know, that's just...
that is just plain wrong.
I mean, what if I wanted to--
I don't know--
what if I wanted
to get pregnant?
I mean, Zeb,
that's just ridiculous.
(dial tone buzzes)
(phone rings)
Sorry.
I just remembered; it wasn't
do what you want to do,
it's be what you want to be,
I think.
I guess I'm just so tired.
I'm not even sure
it's George Eliot.
Thanks for trying, Zeb.
Night.
Good night.
(water running)
(sighs)
There you are, Joe.
Ready for another
glorious day,
helping other people
celebrate life.
(birds chirping)
Happy birthday, Poppy.
Oh, thank you, Beck.
(chuckles)
Ooh, I got it, I got it.
Ooh. Do you know that
100 years ago today,
you were just the
tiniest bundle
nestled in your cradle?
I don't even know who
was president then.
Oh, beats me.
(chuckles)
No cars, probably
no phones.
Mm.
I wonder from time to time
if the years Joycie didn't get
to use in her life
got added onto mine.
Oh, oh, she
would've been glad
to see you enjoy it.
Ah... Joycie... Joyce was
a naturally happy person,
not like us Daviches.
Some people just have
a harder time being happy.
Oh, boy. The night
that I met Joe,
oh, he... he was laughin',
and then, when I saw him
a few days later,
through the
library window...
oh, I saw that life in his eyes,
and I knew right at that moment
that I wanted to marry him.
You know, I think
you might be right, though,
about the Daviches,
because deep down,
I-I-I'm not sure
he was really happy.
He never thought of party-giving
as his true life.
Face it, Beck,
there is no true life.
Your true life is the one you
end up with, whatever it may be.
You just do the best
with what you've got.
This isn't my party,
is it?
(laughing):
Oh, no...
No, no, Poppy.
Your party is going to be
everything you dreamed
it would be.
(band playing jazzy music)
Oh, Mother, come here.
I want you to meet Tanya.
Oh, no, thank you.
J.J.J.
How do you do?
And J.J. Barrow.
Hi.
How do you do?
J.J.'s our,
uh, handyman.
Oh. Are you here
as guests?
Yes.
Yes, we are.
Hey, Poppy,
how you doing?
Oh.
(kids laughing)
Happy birthday, Poppy.
Birthday, Poppy.
Whoa, for me?
(laughs):
Oh.
Whoa, how
'bout that?
President Theodore
Roosevelt.
He was president
the year you were born.
That's beautiful. Look.
President Theodore Roosevelt.
He was a great president.
Are you really 100?
Yes, but don't tell
anybody, huh?
"Pick up dry cleaning,
"make dental appointment
for Peter,
"find someone
to clean the gutters,
buy my bro
a birthday gift."
These are the things I was
supposed to do last week.
So?
Beck, when you and Dad
got married, did you...?
And-and-and don't take this
the wrong way,
but did you ever wonder
if he'd married you
just so that he would have help
with us kids?
I mean, I...
I am trying
not to think that of Barry,
but I mean, these lists.
Oh, what are you saying,
that you don't think
that Barry loves you?
He says he does, but, I mean,
the PTA meetings, the carpool...
It's like... I'm so useful.
Well, don't you think
that all of us,
I mean, love people,
you know, partly
because of their usefulness?
Beck, love has nothing
to do with it.
There's no use.
Hakim is hopeless.
Thanks. I can always rely on
my family for emotional support.
Oh, Min Foo...
please, could you please
just once try to resist
dumping a husband
once you've had
his baby?
I gave you the name
of Patch's marriage counselor.
Patch, you're going to
a marriage counselor?
Thanks a lot, Biddy.
Why does everybody
in this family seem so unhappy?
Thank goodness
for you and Troy.
Troy is gay,
but we still argue
just like every
other couple, okay?
How reassuring to hear that.
Hey, everybody,
Hakim took all of Poppy's
homemade movies
and turned them
into a tape.
They only go up
to 1971, but...
Shh.
"Celebrating Paul Davich."
(laughing)
ZEB:
Ah, your famous
hamburgers, Poppy.
God, I was always good
with my barbecue.
Hey, there's my Joycie.
(laughs)
ZEB:
She looks great.
POPPY:
She's my girl.
She looks happy.
Oh, man.
Oh, I loved that dog.
That was Molly.
POPPY:
Oh, that old train set.
Oh, there's Uncle Zeb.
POPPY:
I gave him that train.
ZEB:
And there's Joe.
Dad...
Yeah, he looks good.
GIRL:
Real bright lights.
Uh-huh.
(kids laughing)
ZEB:
Oh, that's a
sweet shot.
Look at that.
(scoffs)
ZEB:
Now, that's dancing.
I should've
been arrested.
That's some
nice moves.
Our Easter egg hunt.
Oh, there's me.
I remember
that dress.
Well, we all wore it.
(laughter)
Would you look at us?
GIRL:
That looks like fun.
POPPY:
Ooh, what a...
what a bath she's getting.
(all laughing)
Weren't we the
perfect family?
GIRL:
Where are you, Mommy?
I wasn't born yet.
And here you are,
Min Foo.
MIN FOO:
Oh, there I am.
There you are, Mommy.
ZEB:
Yahoo, Min Foo.
MIN FOO:
Dad didn't have a chance.
Four girls.
(laughing)
Look at him.
He was so handsome.
Wow.
POPPY:
Oh, that's a good movie.
It was beautiful, yeah!
MIN FOO:
Good job, Hakim.
All right, cake
is in the dining room.
Yay.
MIN FOO:
Yeah, more
champagne.
%% For he's a jolly good fellow %%
%% For he's
a jolly good fellow %%
%% For he's a jolly good fellow %%
%% Which nobody can deny. %%
What's wrong?
Oh, it's the video.
It's as if I never existed.
As if what?
(applause and cheering)
(cheering)
Beck. A toast.
Poppy.
To Poppy.
He's beginning to seem
perennial.
We're observing
his centennial,
so shout it
from the chandeliers.
We wish him another 100 years.
(cheering)
Happy birthday.
Another one of those
everlasting rhymes of hers.
POPPY:
I could eat
all of this myself.
Let me take the baby.
I'll deal with him.
(baby crying)
(sighs)
Oh, look at you.
I know what you're thinking.
What kind of people
have I ended up with?
How am I ever going
to live
on this planet?
Come over here.
Look, look, look.
(dings)
Miserable day?
Yeah.
Beck, you know that was
just Patch being Patch.
Oh, listen,
what do I care?
Before that, Nono asked me
if Joe had married me
for my usefulness.
Oh, believe me,
over the years, uh,
that crossed my mind, too,
especially after he just...
up and died,
leaving me to cope
with all this.
What are you
talking about?
Oh...
You know, when I first
met him right here,
he said, uh,
"Oh, you look
like you're having
a wonderful time."
Well, you know, I wasn't having
a wonderful time.
I should've just said that
to him right then.
I was here,
too, you know,
and I remember you
walking into the
Open Arms that day,
and you were having
a wonderful time,
and my brother saw in
you this gift of joy.
Joy?
Yeah, joy.
I'm sure you know
that's something
the Davich gene
pool sorely lacks.
Believe me, you give
all of us such joy.
Oh, well, it's not enough.
It's more than enough;
how can we survive
without it?
You'd survive.
Not a chance.
I don't know.
I know.
I know you hold
all of us together
with your love,
with your parties,
with your funny
Rebecca toasts.
Mm.
We need you, Rebecca.
(baby crying)
Abdul's hungry, I think.
Hmm... well, it wouldn't be
a family celebration
if Min Foo wasn't
breast feeding.
Well, I guess we
should go find her.
Yeah.
You're so young.
He's hungry, honey.
Beck, where you been?
Champagne?
Yes, thanks.
Mom, I've run
out of diapers.
Oh, honey, I think
there's an extra package
underneath the sink.
Why aren't you in the video?
Well, I guess
I was busy planning
some happening or other.
(sound of train moving)
Peter?
Do you know I had a dream
about us?
Really?
What'd you dream about?
Well, it was
a beautiful, sunny day...
and you and I were on a train.
Where were we going?
Well, we were traveling to...
to right here, I guess.
We were coming home.
Peter, can you
come here
for a second?
I see you're having
a wonderful time.
Yes, Joe... I really am.
BOY:
Poppy, what
did you wish for
when you blew out
the candles?
Oh, for an even
bigger party
next year.
GUESTS:
Here, here.
Absolutely.
Yeah, yeah,
all right, let's go.
(loud ding)
---the end---