Shared by http://DJJ.HOME.SAPO.PT/
And now, the conclusion of
Judgment From Outer Space.
One of the primitives is trying
to activate Andros' key control.
Let her, Gorel.
If the correct signal isn't sent...
the satellite would automatically
destroy their planet.
We won't have to bother.
General, I just received a report
of an unidentified submarine.
A PBY spotted it this morning.
I checked AtCom
and none of our subs are in that area.
It could be the way of getting Andros
out of the country.
Red alert the anti-sub patrol
immediately...
and get every available PBY in the air.
I want that craft identified and seized.
We've got to get Andros back.
The Nazi humans
now have Andros prisoner...
and are taking him to their homeland.
How much more must we see
before the judgment is made?
Please, if you hear me...
wherever you are...
Andros has been captured by the Nazis...
and he needs whatever strength
and powers that you can give him.
He told me about his mission
here on Earth.
There are good people here,
people worth saving.
People who right now
are risking their lives...
to try to save a stranger like Andros.
If you can hear me...
please help.
I still say all humans are alike
and not worth saving.
It is Andros' mission to decide that.
We cannot leave him without hope
as you would wish it.
Then leave him the spacecraft.
If he can gain his freedom...
and if his humans are civilized enough
to help him...
why, then, he's proved his point.
Otherwise...
Let him die? Alone, among savages?
Andros chose the test.
I call a vote.
As the Council has decided.
We've been searching all sections
of the north and south Atlantic...
for two weeks now.
We have to assume
that they've gotten away with Andros.
I think we should proceed immediately
on the information...
Prime Minister Churchill gave you.
Yes, Mr. President.
I'll implement the plan immediately.
Churchill has told the President
that British Intelligence...
knows of a heavily secured
enemy intelligence interrogation center.
We feel sure that's
where they'll take Andros.
It's heavily guarded
and extremely difficult to penetrate.
But not impossible.
I'd like to volunteer to try.
- How soon can you leave for London?
- Tonight.
Diana can look after the office
while I'm gone.
Of course, sir.
I'll secure full cooperation
from the British.
This interrogation center, what's it called?
Schloss Markheim.
- I trust you will be comfortable.
- No matter, Mr. Bjornsen.
If you like you may wash, change clothes.
Dinner will be black tie in one hour.
And I'm invited?
You are the honored guest, Doctor.
Guest, of course.
Even given me a black tie.
- General Clewes.
- Yes.
You're admirably prompt, Major Trevor.
I had a good flight, sir.
Yes, and God willing, an equally good one
over the Schwarzwald.
I'd like to have you meet Evan Mallory.
- Steve Trevor.
- My pleasure.
Thank you.
Mallory is going to guide you
to the Nazi Interrogation Center...
Located at Schloss Markheim.
You see, I have a very solid
false identity...
as a Nazi officer just returned
from the Russian front.
You'll have papers identifying you
as a technical aide on the mission.
Sounds like you've got everything set up.
- British efficiency.
- British!
Dear, no, my friend.
I'm Welsh.
It's a temporary alliance
against the Nazis, eh?
Welsh madman. But then, all the Welsh
are a bit mad.
That's possibly why
he's a most efficient secret agent.
- You're in good hands.
- I'm sure of it.
- When do we leave?
- Now. Within the hour.
- Good luck, sir.
- Thank you, General.
You're the busy one.
Got a lot of things to clear up
before this weekend.
That's what I wanted to talk to you about.
The weekend. I thought maybe we could...
go down to the beach
and splash in the water...
lie on the sand...
maybe drum up a little interest.
I'd love to, but I've already
made plans for the weekend.
Really? What're you gonna do?
Well, you might say I'm going hunting.
Hunting? Diana, you couldn't hurt a fly.
I'm not going hunting to hurt anything.
I'm going to find something.
Hopefully.
You have no idea
of how this mechanism works?
Only that it connects
to some power source, sir.
I trust Dr. Graebner will soon tell us more.
We will begin analysis at once.
Question: This Andros will cooperate?
I think I can persuade him.
And if you cannot...
I have experts who can.
"Lieutenant Felzer. " Good papers.
The best.
There really is a Lieutenant Felzer.
He's on the Eastern front.
He'd better stay there.
If he comes back, we will both be shot.
Dr. Andros, welcome to Markheim!
May I introduce Colonel-General
Heinrich Von Dreiberg.
- Dr. Andros.
- No "Doctor," please. Just Andros.
On my planet, we've given up
the custom of using titles.
I'm Professor Graebner
of the Ministry of Science.
And you, Dr. Andros, are you...
an alien from outer space?
I'm precisely what I claim to be.
But you are involved in atom research?
No, we completed
our atomic research long ago.
Now our children learn
atomic and sub-atomic physics...
in primary school much as
your children learn primitive fire making.
Very interesting, Doctor.
But let us leave serious talk for later.
Now, dinner.
May I introduce Fräulein Engel.
Shall we go in?
Bjornsen.
He is impertinent.
And the ridiculous cover story
about an alien from outer space.
Gentlemen, he has already admitted
his connection to atom research.
We are convinced he is a key scientist
in the Allied scientific establishment...
but like many scientists, he is naive.
I think I can persuade him
to join our cause.
And if you can't?
Sir, perhaps Fräulein Engel can.
I promised you, Andros...
that we'd have a chance
to talk more privately.
And more pleasantly.
Well, I'm flattered.
Thank you.
Prosit.
It's beautiful, bubbly.
It's alive.
It's too bad the sparkle
is so short-lived...
and then it's dead.
Tell me something.
Why do you let yourself be used like this?
A charming object...
sent off to seduce a stranger.
Love isn't a commodity.
It is at least, a gift...
at best, a sharing.
You remember when you were a little girl?
The ocean sunrises over Wesermunde.
The golden dreams
of a knight come riding.
How did you know?
And the girl who knew she was beautiful.
No!
Touching.
I see you've decided
to communicate with me again.
You do have faith
in these primitives, Andros.
It is a quality the Council needs.
I'm exercising my privilege.
I'm canceling the Judgment's survey
and bringing you back.
And this planet Earth?
Destroyed, of course.
No.
Andros, you must realize...
your romantic faith
in these humans is false.
They've captured you. They will kill you.
No, they're not all savages.
I'm an anachronism, Gorel.
I'm a romantic. I still have faith.
You're wrong.
These people are savages.
And if they kill you, Andros...
I will lose a friend.
And their planet will be destroyed
in any case.
You have quite a remarkable collection
of artworks.
An example
of our historic culture, Andros.
Seize her!
Come on, I'll get you out.
No, wait!
Wonder Woman, I can't leave yet.
There's much to learn here
before I make a judgment.
They're holding you prisoner!
They are Nazis.
Yes, they are Nazis.
Your friends
are Republicans and Democrats.
The Russians are Communists.
All different, all human.
I told you, I intend to meet
the leaders of humankind.
- Including the Nazis?
- Yes.
You brought me here by force...
but I would stay
of my own will and necessity...
- if you do not harm Wonder Woman.
- Of course.
We'll make you a good Nazi yet, Andros!
At the very least,
you are an honored guest.
And you are quite a different kind of guest.
Take them away.
There is no doubt she is an Allied agent,
this Wonder Woman.
So why do we play games, Bjornsen?
Take her below and have her questioned.
Questioned scientifically.
With all due respect, I disagree.
This Wonder Woman has been involved...
in some very curious episodes in the past.
There are reports
of extraordinary physical strength...
- speed...
- Utter nonsense.
She is a woman!
An unusual woman?
I suspect an experimental agent.
Perhaps the result of scientific processing.
Connected with this Dr. Andros?
Very possibly.
So I have arranged to leave them together.
Privately...
so to speak.
I don't understand...
how you can be friendly with the Nazis
when they've taken you prisoner!
So did the Americans.
But that was different,
for temporary security.
Americans don't make arbitrary arrests
or use concentration camps.
I think you better explain that
to Americans of Japanese descent.
Democracies are not perfect.
I mean, there are...
mistakes made
but not warfare against civilians.
Not deliberate torture.
Distinctions, not necessarily differences.
I'm not interested in national squabbles.
I am here to study humanity.
Or inhumanity.
And you have no feelings,
one way or the other?
I have very strong feelings.
That's why I cannot indulge them,
believe me.
I'm as vulnerable as you are.
No.
You're a guest of Bjornsen,
and his Nazi masters!
Bjornsen is a Nazi
but all Germans are not Nazis.
I cannot judge him, or his beliefs
until I understand them both.
I am a prisoner, and thanks to you,
they have my Belt and my Lasso...
so I am as helpless as you.
Or else you would be
trying to tear this castle to pieces.
Yes.
Who would be waging warfare then?
A few more days,
and he will be on our side.
Good.
I will need his help. I must confess...
as of yet I don't understand the scientific
principles behind his mechanism...
or the devices of that woman agent.
Andros will cooperate.
As for Wonder Woman...
No.
Nothing...
will happen to her.
Until she gives us
the information we want.
I'll be careful.
All in order, Captain Braun.
But your case is slightly different,
Lieutenant Felzer.
In what way?
Your papers indicate you have recently
served on the Eastern front...
- von Paulus' command.
- Yes. So?
As it happens, we have another man
just back from the Eastern front...
Lieutenant Berghoff, also served
under von Paulus, also in headquarters.
You two must have known each other.
Of course, it's possible, Captain Grau.
I'd like to meet him.
- Lieutenant Felzer.
- Sir?
You have forgotten,
your social life must wait...
until after we have delivered
the dispatches.
Your General von Dreiberg
is waiting for them personally.
If they are delayed...
Lieutenant Felzer will undoubtedly
return to the Eastern front.
- And we will accompany him.
- I apologize, sir!
Of course we can't have delays...
but I had Berghoff notified,
he was eager to meet an old comrade.
Some other time.
Dispatches for General von Dreiberg.
Thank you, Captain.
I'm only asking
for a few simple explanations.
We realize, of course,
that these devices are connected...
to your American atom research.
Nonsense.
I expected you to be stubborn.
But you, Dr. Andros,
I'm sure you can give us some details?
Do the Americans
have an atom bomb yet?
Herr Bjornsen, I'm here
to meet with your leaders.
Not discuss dangerous toys.
You call the most powerful
explosive device...
known to scientific theory a toy?
I'm sorry,
I don't mean to be condescending.
But my people discovered basic atomics...
some thousands of your years ago and...
we experimented with it...
and then outgrew
the uses of such power, such weapons.
We developed other uses: More effective,
less clumsy and polluting.
- Enough of this other-world nonsense!
- Please.
Let him continue.
We know planets where
atomic explosives were discovered...
leading to war and destruction...
and the planets did not survive.
Earth is entering the atomic age...
and if you do not outgrow
your emotional primitivism...
you'll destroy yourselves, and others.
It is that we cannot allow.
Where's Felzer? Sorry.
I'm Lieutenant Berghoff. Felzer and I
were pretty close on the Eastern front.
Berghoff, too bad!
You just missed him.
He just went through a few minutes ago.
Then, perhaps, I can see him
when he comes out.
He still has a uniform of mine
that he borrowed...
and I'd like to get it back.
It must have been
a very loose fit on you, Lieutenant.
No, as a matter of fact...
it's just about the best-fitting
uniform I own.
But you can't be more than 5'9", 5'10"...
Felzer's at least 6'2", 6'3".
Georg Felzer?
Impossible. He and I are
exactly the same height!
- Are you sure?
- Positive.
Whoever he is, that man's an imposter.
Get me Oberst Bjornsen at once.
Emergency!
I see.
Thank you, Captain Grau. We'll handle it.
General Von Dreiberg.
Major Trevor, how nice to see you again.
Disarm them!
Wonder Woman, you, too?
I came to free Andros.
But he doesn't want to be freed.
Dr. Andros has become friendly.
But I think, Doctor, the time has come...
for you to give us a concrete
demonstration of that friendship.
To be specific:
We know you're a key scientist
in the American atom program.
We've been patient.
Those colorful stories of alien space.
But now: Facts.
- I told you.
- You told us charming fairytales!
The Third Reich is at war.
We need weapons. Atomic weapons.
No.
I think you're confused, Doctor.
I'm not asking you politely.
I have the top American female agent...
the head of
an American Intelligence operation...
and the leading British spy
in the Third Reich!
I have them! And you will see them die!
- You don't understand! Why don't you...
- It is you who does not understand.
The talk is over!
Take them down. For questioning.
I'd get nightmares like this.
But I wasn't lucky enough
to have you in them, Princess.
This leads to the wine cellar,
which we have enlarged.
This whole section of the foundation
was carved out of living rock.
It took us a year
and a good deal of forced labor.
The ultimate plague:
Man's inhumanity to man.
Rather the strong's use of the weak.
Not pretty, Dr. Andros,
but the truth behind...
all power, all governments: Strength.
The strength of a frightened, evil child...
too terrified to trust in gentleness.
Only in paradise, Wonder Woman.
I hope not.
You will see we have modernized it a bit.
Have them cover all exits.
Put them in there.
We'll go to the laboratory.
Get your hands off...
Don't confuse heroism with stupidity.
You are a hundred meters down in
the heart of the mountain.
You have very few options.
He's right, Steve, for now.
Look, you, the war isn't over yet.
But don't worry, Colonel.
I'll notify you when we've won.
If you're still alive.
Professor Graebner has been
examining your devices.
And I must admit, up till now
I've made very little progress.
This is clearly a control mechanism
of some kind...
operating on electronic principles.
These artifacts...
They are gifts.
But what do they do?
How do they function?
I want detailed technical data.
There are none.
- You're being stubborn.
- And stupid!
Let us start with your device,
Dr. Andros. You will explain it.
Even if I were willing,
it would be impossible.
You don't have the scientific knowledge.
It's not a machine.
It's part of my mind,
perhaps, part of my soul.
That is mystic nonsense, and I want facts!
I'm sorry. No.
I'm disappointed, Andros.
Let me be clear.
If you refuse to cooperate...
- You'll use force on me?
- No.
On her.
While you watch.
They are savages.
They have convinced me.
You are right.
I am a terrible threat to your planet,
and yet you are here...
at risk of life, to help me...
and so is Major Trevor, and Evan Mallory.
The Americans, the Allies...
they have human virtues, human flaws...
- but the Nazis...
- I don't need a lecture on ethics!
Nor would you understand it.
You spoke to me
of your cultural inheritance.
Your inheritance is in a direct line
with Genghis Khan, Attila.
You celebrate the darkness
in the human soul.
Start on her!
Gorel!
Stop her!
If we could break up this bunk
we could use it as a battering ram.
Lock all the exits, stop Wonder Woman.
Whatever happened, my dear princess...
your coming here to help me
has renewed my faith in humankind.
I'm stripped of my powers.
The only way I can return to my spacecraft
safely is with human help.
And I will have made a point.
If I'm killed...
Then it would prove we aren't civilized.
And then Earth...
Would end.
And you have risked your life for us.
No, for what I believe in.
I don't risk my life:
My life is what I believe in.
Too bloody well-made,
bloody perfectionists.
Go after them.
That way!
Go on.
No, she's here to help us.
- How do you know you can trust her?
- Andros knows.
I don't care about the rest of you
but I won't see him killed!
This way.
A secret exit. In case of heavy bombing.
You can break the door, there's a
tunnel that leads past the security points.
Thank you.
- Thank you, Lisa.
- Don't.
- I don't even know why.
- I do.
And when that knight comes riding
he'll know, too.
I'm no longer important...
but Wonder Woman is. Surely
by now you've seen the potential...
for good in humans.
Wonder Woman is the hope
of the human race.
The hope of this entire misguided planet.
Grant me back my powers
that I may help her.
Do you have your powers back?
Yes, because of you.
- Has the decision been reached, Andros?
- Yes.
We found war, violence...
injustice and torture.
Your planet is troubled.
Humankind is flawed with self-destruction.
But that is only a flaw.
It's the disease of racial childhood.
I found a balance.
And I remember how you gave me back
my power:
Freely, ethically.
Then the Earth won't be destroyed?
No, the spirit be thanked.
I won a vote in the Council.
Fifty of your years, Princess.
I am empowered to grant you that:
50 years.
And you'll have atomic power...
you'll begin to explore space...
- I hope you discover answers.
- We will.
No, we may.
It's a question.
Perhaps the next 50 years
will give us something of an answer.
I can answer in regards to you, Princess.
And I can offer you an invitation.
Come with me.
- Into space?
- Yes, to the real world.
A planet of water,
and a civilization of dolphins...
a planet of gardens,
where you can meet plant intelligences...
a planet where
the gravity allows you to fly.
There are thousands of worlds...
you can see them,
you can even taste them if you wish.
Then spend some time with me.
Us.
On my home.
I can't. Andros, I'm pledged as well...
to my Earth...
humanity and my destiny.
Of course.
It's only 50 years.
In 1992, I'll be back and renew my offer.
Hi, Diana.
The General still in with Steve?
I know that look.
Who's the fella?
I'm sorry, I didn't hear what you said.
I said you were thinking about a guy.
And I want to hear all about it,
in minute detail.
As a matter of fact,
I was thinking about someone...
- but by this time he is very far away.
- Overseas?
You might say so.
Don't worry, he'll be back.
I'm not worried. He'll come back,
I know, he promised.
And he seems to be a man of his word.
The White House just called. The President
wants your final report on Andros.
Final report?
The man's vanished
from the face of the earth...
that's about the only final report
I can make.
The General's right.
How do we know it's a final report
if we can't find a trace of Andros?
From what you told me, Andros was
the most honest man you'd ever met...
he said he was going back
to his own planet, why doubt him?
I don't.
I guess I'm just a little jealous,
that's all.
I saw the way Wonder Woman
looked at him...
and just wanted to make 100% sure
he is gone.
I don't think you have
anything to worry about.
No matter how much Andros
would have wanted...
Wonder Woman to go back with him...
I'm sure she'd rather stay here with you.
With us.
English
Shared by http://DJJ.HOME.SAPO.PT/