('d "Niri" by Paul Nabor)
('dogs bark)
('mn shout)
('hlicoptr vvhirrs.)
('man. In English.)
Are you coming or not?
- ('banging on door)
- ('mn shout)
Where's the rest?
('banging continus.)
Don't go telling anyone you're short.
('spaks Spanish.)
Where are they taking us?
- ('spaks Spanish.) New York.
- New York?
New York, huh?
('spaks Spanish.) Get in.
('plan flis ovrhad)
('ngin starts.)
('boy.) I could use a little milk myself.
Oh, dear. Yummy!
Hungry?
- No, I can't. It's your last.
- No, I have more.
It's a long trip.
Go on.
It was my father's.
It's beautiful.
Yeah.
I'm going to see my father tomorrow.
In New York?
Then you know the city?
No. And you?
('radio plays livly Latin music.)
('spaks Spanish.) Goddammit!
Hey. The plunger.
The plunger!
Fuck man, move your ass!
You old bastard!
Hey! Pass me that.
Pass me that, dammit!
Partied a little
too hard last night, eh?
Dancing, dancing, dancing,
all damn night.
Move your ass like last night.
Watch it, old man.
('Spanish program on tlvision.)
What's wrong?
You don't feel so good?
You're disgusting!
('man laughs.)
Leave him alone.
You pig.
Here.
- You're from the south, no?
- From Puebla.
You must be tired.
I'll rest when I see my father.
Where does he live?
Here.
What's it say?
You can't read?
But I can read numbers.
"Five, four, one..."
"541, 12th Street, Brooklyn."
Brooklyn.
Why write him a letter
if you're about to see him?
No, it's not mine.
It's from my mother.
She's dead.
I've never met my father.
This is my introduction.
- Do you want me to read it to you?
- No!
I promised to deliver it sealed.
Just trying to help.
Hey.
('spaks Spanish.) It's Santa Claus.
Fuck off.
Look at the craftsmanship.
- When do I get to meet your wife?
- She's busy.
She does better work
than any of my ladies.
A real feminine touch.
50 pieces at a dollar per piece.
That's $50.
All these years we do business
and I never once cheated you,
and still you stand there and count
like I've taken your last cent.
- You're five short.
- Huh?
Gotcha. ('chuckls.)
You asshole.
Bastard.
- ('boy.) Is that your old man?
- With my mom.
17 years is a long time.
Yes, but he's a good man.
Before they split,
he sent my mother $ 200 every week.
Now he's a chef and owns the place.
He'll help me.
What if he doesn't?
Then...
Well, you were lucky to have
someone who cared for you.
My old man left me with two things -
the knife...
and the hole that he left with it.
- Your father did that?
- Yes.
You should have seen my mother.
But, hey,
we're going to New York, no?
That's all in the past.
You mean like those guys
back in the garage?
That?
Yeah, I can't go back to that shit.
We have only the future now.
And luck. I can feel it.
Thanks for the help.
No, thanks for the food.
And the jacket.
I'm Pedro.
And I'm Juan.
Here, let me give you a lift.
You go first.
One, two...
You ate a lot of tamales.
('spaks English.) We're here.
Let's go. Hurry up.
Hurry up, hurry up.
Come on.
('spaks Spanish.) Let's go. Let's go.
('spaks English.)
Let's go. Wake up. Come on.
Hey, come on.
Let's go. Let's go.
Hey, wake up.
Let's go.
All right. Let's go.
('spaks Spanish.) Let's go.
('spaks English.) Oh, man.
Hey. Wake up, kid.
Wake up.
Come on.
('spaks Spanish.) Are we here?
('spaks English.) Come on.
Hop out. Trip's over. Let's go.
And Juan?
- I only agreed to go to Brooklyn.
- Brooklyn?
My bag!
Where's my bag?
- Hey, get out of my truck.
- My bag! My bag!
Goddammit.
Sir...
They stole my bag.
Get your fucking hands off me.
Where's Juan? Sir?
Urgh!
('horn blars.)
('knocks.)
('knocking continus.)
I'm coming.
Yes?
Sir?
Papa?
What'd you say?
I'm Pedro Gonzalez Martinez.
Lupe Martinez was my mother.
- ('spaks Polish.)
- Hello.
I'm looking for Diego Gonzalez.
('spaks Polish.)
No, I'm looking for my father.
I mean no harm.
If he doesn't live here, please tell me,
or he's gone somewhere else...
('spaks Polish.)
('vvoman continus shouting.)
('rustling.)
('unlocks door)
And the locket?
The locket?
Here, at the top of the letter
it says you have the locket I gave her.
It was stolen from me on my journey.
Someone took my confidence
and robbed me.
- You're not my son.
- But I am.
- How old are you?
- 17.
It's been 20 years since I left Mexico.
How could you be my son?
You didn't read the letter?
When you came to visit in '90...
She was already engaged to another man.
But for five years I sent her money.
She probably had five other idiots like me
hidden beneath her apron.
- But that night...
- That night was a mistake.
Besides, look at you.
You don't even look like me.
- You don't even look like her either.
- Please, I have no one...
You know who you look like?
That asshole Pepe.
That's who you look like.
I can't help how I look.
You're even kind of pretty, aren't you?
Please, my mother's last wish is...
was that we meet.
We've met.
But...
What?
What the fuck are you looking at?
So she bends him over the table
and starts humping him,
and then she says,
"How do you like it, bitch?"
('Digo.) What, we're not working today?
What's wrong, old man?
You don't look so good.
Long night with the ladies?
No, not at all.
Your wife was too busy
taking care of my kids.
- ('mn. Laughing.) Ooh!
- He's being funny.
One second, fellas.
- Diego doesn't need a woman.
- Why?
He has too much fun making love
to his little piles of money.
('man #2.) That was a good one.
At least I'm not out blowing it every night
like you assholes.
('radio blasts out music.)
('bustl.)
Get out. Come on!
What do you want, huh?
You're the dishwasher?
- I thought you owned the place.
- Of course I'm the dishwasher, idiot.
- But Mama...
- Don't speak of that woman to me!
Go on, leave.
Get the fuck out of here!
Why are you
treating me this way, Papa?
Don't call me that.
Maybe one of your friends would help me.
Sir?
It's all right.
Here, take this
and get something to eat.
But go.
- ('English.) What the fuck is going on?
- ('English.) Coming, coming. Coming.
('Spanish.) You got the money,
what else do you want? Go.
I'll just wait for you to get off work.
- We could walk home together.
- You can't stay here.
No, no. Now that I found you,
I don't want to lose sight of you.
Pedro, please.
Please leave, OK?
We can meet later, OK?
Just meet at my place, OK?
At your place?
Yes.
OK. I'll see you there.
OK.
At your place.
Bye, Papa.
('man talks on phon
in Indian languag.)
Excuse me, sir.
('English.) 4.75.
- I was hoping you could help me.
- 4.75, please.
I don't have any money,
and I'm not one to ask for favors...
('spaks Indian languag.)
English?
I don't have any money.
Sorry, man.
('continus convrsation
in Indian languag.)
Look.
- I'll work really hard.
- No, no, no.
You want sandwich,
you must be paying cash.
('English.) One cigarette.
Yo, man.
What's the deal?
I don't know.
He doesn't speak English.
('Spanish.) What's up, little brother?
Thank God. You have to help me.
('English.) Get the fuck off me, man.
I came here to find my father, but he
doesn't live where he's supposed to,
and they stole my bag
that had everything in it...
OK...
I had to sleep on the street,
and I haven't eaten for so long...
('Spanish.) It's OK, relax.
I'm very hungry.
Listen, this guy
isn't going to give you shit.
('English.) Yo, man.
This kid's fucking crazy.
('continus convrsation
in Indian languag.)
('Spanish.) But maybe I can help you.
What's your dad's name?
Diego Gonzalez.
- He's from Puebla.
- Diego Gonzalez?
- Do you know him?
- Do I know him?
Of course I know him.
I should have seen the resemblance.
It's amazing.
('English.) Yo, man, I think you might
wanna call the cops on this kid.
('Spanish.) The son of Diego Gonzalez,
huh? I can't believe it.
- Your dad practically runs this town.
- Really?
Go ahead, take a sandwich.
I'll buy it for you.
('English.) Yo, man. I tried.
He's just gonna eat it now.
('shouts in Indian languag.)
If I take you to him,
can I meet him?
- Hey, I told you, no cash, no sandwich.
- No, my friend here is paying.
You don't understand.
I told you, no cash, no sandwich.
('man shouts in Indian languag.)
('vvoman on phon. English.) Is somthing
happning thr? Rajiv? Who's thr?
What is happning?
('vvoman continus faintly.)
What's up, old man?
Have you been hiding something from us,
my friend?
Fuck off, OK?
Come on, man, cut the bullshit.
You're hurting my feelings, man.
Who is he?
I thought we were your only family.
There aren't any assholes in my family.
He's cute.
Pedro, no?
He's my nephew.
He must be confused to call you "Papa"!
Hm?
('childish voic.) Papa. ('laughs.)
C'mon, don't get angry.
- Papa.
- ('smashs plat.)
Don't touch me, motherfucker.
Papa.
It wasn't me, it was Papa.
('door opns.)
('toilt flushs.)
Papa.
Don't call me that.
OK, then, "old man."
- I know this isn't easy for you, but...
- What?
- You already spent the money?
- Not a cent. How could I?
- It wasn't enough, then.
- I'm not after your money.
No?
Then I'll take it back.
What are you doing?
- I'm coming in.
- You think I'm letting you in?
- But you told me to meet you.
- And?
I just thought maybe that...
You thought wrong.
- But where will I sleep?
- That's your problem.
But you took my money.
My money.
Couldn't you at least give it back
so I could find a place to stay?
- Just like your mother.
- How else will I get by?
Why not be a man
and do a little honest work?
- I am a man.
- ('laughs.)
I can work for you.
- What can you do?
- What can I do?
- Do you have a trade?
- A trade?
Do you have any special skill?
What do you think?
That everything's free?
It all just falls from the sky?
Just like that damn woman.
What can you do with that, huh?
Join the circus?
Please, don't do this to me.
('Juan coughs.)
Hey, my knife!
Give me back my knife!
('kicks door)
Give me back my knife.
I'm talking to you.
Goddammit!
Give me back my knife!
('dog barks.)
('imitats ngin.)
Papa Rooster calling Pedro.
This is Pedro, where are you?
I'm at kilometer 78,
headed for New York.
('imitats ngin.)
Hey.
Hey. Get up.
You can't lay around here
like some lazy bum.
Hey! Hey!
What's your problem?
- You son of a bitch.
- Hey, hey!
Come on.
- ('Juan.) Where are we going?
- We are not going anywhere.
I'm not going to work with you?
You think you can
just work wherever you want?
Besides, it's hard work for a little girl.
- Don't call me a little boy.
- I said "little girl."
You think that's funny, huh?
I'm talking to you.
Quit your whining.
You're lucky.
When I came here
there was no one to help me.
Wait here.
When the men in trucks come, be quick.
Just follow the others. OK?
I knew you would take care of me.
Don't get any ideas.
This is just so
you can get a place of your own.
Of course, Papi.
Stop calling me that.
- ('vvoman. In Spanish.) They're delicious.
- ('man. In Spanish.) Thank you.
- How much did that cost?
- Nothing today. She gives credit.
- Hello.
- I have no money, but a gentleman said...
- No, no. Sorry.
- Don't you give credit?
- To those I can trust.
- You can trust me.
- And I never trust anyone who says that.
I wasn't hungry anyway.
So why are you wasting my time?
Excuse me, sir.
I'm looking for my father,
Diego Gonzalez.
From Puebla.
Did you just get off the boat
or what?
('horn.)
('man. In Spanish.) Seven men,
$50 a head.
('mn clamor)
That's it! That's all!
('vvoman.) Hey!
('English.) What the fuck, man?
Nice push, Torito.
('English.) I hope you guys
are ready for some dirty work.
('drilling.)
Hey, Torito, over here.
So, you're looking
for your father, eh?
What's his name again?
Diego Gonzalez.
Anyone know a Diego Gonzalez?
He's from Puebla.
From Puebla.
I'm sorry.
But I'm sure you'll find him.
('Juan.) Hello.
Calm down,
I'm a paying customer.
- How much?
- You like to read?
I don't want your trash.
How much for you?
I don't know what you're talking about.
You don't have to play with me.
- How much?
- ('English.) Fuck off, man.
No, I don't want "focos."
I want you.
Look.
('Spanish.) Go back to Mexico -
there you can get something for your $5.
- You think I don't have more?
- Yes.
Yes?
No. There's plenty more
where that came from.
- Bitch.
- Loser.
How much for the heater?
Wake up, old man.
What are you laughing at, assholes?
Stop, stop!
('English.) Fuck, man!
- You robbed me.
- I could've got 20 bucks for that.
- Don't fucking touch me again.
My locket.
('Spanish.) I don't know
what you're talking about.
The locket you took from me
at the store.
- I already sold that, man.
- What?
- How could you?
- Easy.
- It was all I had left.
- That's not my problem.
- You're going to help me find it right now.
- ('English.) Don't fucking touch me again.
- I'll call the police.
- ('Spanish.) Shut up, idiot.
I'll call.
Then you'll just be sending yourself
back to your little shithole in Mexico.
- Don't walk away from me.
- Shut up.
You're the one they're going to deport.
I was born here, you little bitch.
Look, get off my back, kid.
No. You owe me,
and now you have to help me.
I don't have to do shit for you.
I'll pay you.
Huh?
I'll pay you to help me.
- Do what?
- Find my father.
Shit, kid, that could take forever.
Then just for tonight.
You'll pay me just for tonight?
- ('English.) 50 bucks.
- What?
('Spanish.) You want to make it in this world
you gotta learn to speak its language, kid.
Can you say...
('English.)..."50 bucks"?
('Spanish.) $50.
But that's all I have.
OK.
Half now, half later.
Shit, you can trust me.
- I tried that once.
- All right, fine.
Where does he live?
I mean,
where was he supposed to live?
- 541, 12th Street.
- Which 12th Street?
There's more than one?
('English.) You don't know anything,
do you?
('Spanish.) South 12th Street's
over there.
North 12th Street is
about 20 blocks that way.
There's plain 12th Street in Park Slope.
That's just Brooklyn.
In Manhattan there are two,
and in Queens...
I can't even figure out Queens.
Let's go.
Old man?
('Iock pops.)
What's the rush?
Don't touch me!
I thought we came to an understanding
about you touching me.
I'm sorry, but can you please hurry?
If he's been there for 15 years,
he'll still be there in five minutes, no?
What makes you
so sure he's even there?
My mother said he would be.
Well, if your mother said it, then...
('Pdro.) 541?
I should go alone.
Good idea.
('door craks.)
('knocking.)
('footstps fad.)
- Magda?
- Just a sec.
Does he live here?
No.
My father owns a restaurant.
He doesn't live here.
So pay me and I'll go.
You said there's another
12th Street in Brooklyn.
Yeah, but that's too far from here.
Hey, what are you doing?
Give me my bag!
I need you to write something for me.
Just in case.
Put that I'll come back later.
- It's late.
- So?
And cold. Listen, you can go tomorrow,
I'll even go with you,
- but right now I gotta go meet somebody.
- I paid you for the whole night.
Then let's take the train, at least.
('toilt flushs.)
Hey, old man.
What's happening?
If you don't eat,
why do you do so much shit?
Look what I found.
I thought you were gonna find a place.
I tried but I was too busy working.
Look, I can pay you rent.
There wasn't much to do and the pay
wasn't so good, but this should do.
You really would charge
your own son rent?
No. I wouldn't charge my son.
You can stay.
But I'm not running
a boarding house here.
- Yes. Thank you, Papa.
- Don't call me that.
OK, old man.
You can put your things on the bed.
I'll sleep on the chair.
No, no. The floor is fine for me.
It's OK, I'm used to it.
Really?
('turns on TV)
Black and white?
Even at home everyone has color.
Is there anything else you'd like, sir?
- I imagined something nicer than this.
- What did you expect?
I don't know...
I mean, after 17 years, you'd think you
could've fixed the place up a little.
This is worse than Puebla.
Perhaps the street would suit you better.
No, no, it's perfect.
Just a little joke.
Soap operas?
What do I know?
I don't watch that crap.
If you have so much money,
why can't you help me a little?
- You want some help?
- Yes.
OK.
Help yourself.
- What's this?
- Work.
- What kind of work?
- Sewing.
Sewing?
That's woman's work.
Then it should suit you just fine.
- I told you...
- Oh, yeah, you're a big man.
I've had a lot more women
than you, old fart.
You think sticking your prick
in some hole makes you a man?
Yeah. Seven times.
Almost eight, except the last one got a little
complicated. But I was almost there.
Hey, at least I'm not sewing.
Then you're not making any money either.
I could try.
You could?
Toss me the thread.
You'll see.
Let me show you how it's done.
How much do we get for these things,
anyway?
50 cents.
50 cents?
Fine.
50 cents.
Fucking American Dream.
('Pdro.) This is it. This feels right.