resynchronization:
"R. Celeste"
SMALL INVADERS
RESTRICTED
- My God, Stewart!
- What?
Notes Tom finally
were posted.
- Look.
- Great.
- No A or B.
- No.
Even in
Health Program
- What is ...?
- It was a D.
How are they changing?
A word and die.
Are you crazy?
- If your dad catches you, kill you.
- He will not catch me.
I do not understand. What you see
this guy?
Besides being beautiful, sweet,
sensitive, romantic,
funny and
absurdly athletic?
- Santa is coming and is angry.
- With whom?
- Tom!
- What?
- If you're so smart
to hack the school site,
then you can pass in mathematics.
Do you think Bethany was accepted at
Michigan by carousing around?
Of course not. She entered
because it is perfect.
No, his sister worked hard
and that is what I expect from you.
You're right, Dad.
I do not deserve a family vacation.
I stay home tomorrow.
Learn.
I will not fall for it, kid.
This is not you.
This attitude, these notes.
- What is happening?
- Nothing.
I blame it all,
up between this right here.
Vacation antiquated
without technology
with close family
is exactly what we need.
Go to sleep. Hit the road
early tomorrow.
And you too.
Hannah, please
next time
you go in the middle, right?
- I'm going to throw up in the middle, remember?
... other news, it seems that there
more than fireworks night
since a meteor shower
adds excitement
- To our area this holiday.
- Legal. We will have a great show.
- It will be beautiful, people.
- Better wear hats tonight!
We do not want our heads
fire!
Wow. Your doll
is a complete idiot.
Ricky is not a doll.
We are in a serious relationship.
Talk a few years,
when you know what dating.
Type ... Ricky knows?
One more word about Ricky
and I swear I'll kill you.
Sure. No more fighting. Can stop.
We're almost there!
And there is the pool.
Bye!
Let's see Uncle Nate!
Yes!
Let me, Tom
Do not worry.
- Cool, huh?
- Very cool! He took it.
Had to book the discount
most boring place in the country?
We pertinho at least
a 6 fishing lakes in first!
We have the machine to go back 5 years
in time, when fishing was legal?
I bought a new reels,
technology antirreverso!
Pathetic.
Very pathetic ...
- Bela "landing", Nate!
- I said I could skid.
Nice try, little by
did not take my children.
But almost killed his mother
heart. Again!
- Grandma!
- Hi, Mom.
- Hi, honey.
- Grandma!
Sweetie!
- I brought something for you.
- I brought?
Brought, yes. Here it is!
- Thank you.
- It's so good to see you.
- I missed you.
- Hey, we.
Well, one of the brothers Pearson
come have fun.
- This is at least legalized?
- No!
- Come on, Stu.
- Let's get him!
- Nate, stop! What!
- Get him!
- Take his shirt.
- Mom
Whats up Stu is calling
a yummy mummy!
- Gemini, here.
- Hi, everybody.
- Put my bags on the bed.
- Yes, sir.
- Is it a wise guy?
- No! Definitely not.
- Not the cause.
- Good
Now take it from here.
Wait. Why is
with the best room?
- I came here first.
- I'm here now.
- I'm older.
- But I'm bigger.
- You have grown since Christmas?
- 5 centimeters, cousin.
I can get a card
Stop in without jumping.
- And the Mathematics Olympiad?
- Do not participate more.
Tired of being defeated?
Tom, come down here and help us
downloading. Fast.
Close my door to leave.
- Surprise, Princess!
- Ricky, what are you doing here?
I just came to spend the afternoon.
Or perhaps the night!
- What is it?
- What is what?
Ricky!
- Beware of the car.
- I do not believe you're here.
Is my girlfriend now,
then do everything for you.
Take a care for Dad!
Bethany! Please do not give
"affection for Dad!"
- Mr. and Mrs. P.!
- Ricky, what a surprise.
- I brought a gift.
- What love! He is not a love?
- Yes! They are beautiful.
- They are wonderful!
Well patriotic, too.
Let's put the flags
the water and see if they grow!
- Want to eat or drink something?
- That's very kind, I ...
like much, but my parents
have a house on the lake and
gotta get back before dark
if my car breaks down again.
- Problems with the car.
- Why not check for Ricky?
I do not care
your hands dirty.
Try again, Ricky.
It should be obvious, Dad.
I have to be honest, mechanical
cars is not my forte.
If it were a spreadsheet or a book
accounting, I set off.
Why not stay here tonight
and take the car to the shop tomorrow?
- Mr. P. Very kind of you.
- Well ..
- Really? He can stay?
- Yes, in the office. On the couch.
- Sure.
- Not ready.
- Father!
- What slicker.
Yeah. Since no one sees it?
Man, parents have
"connections" different.
Their brains
are old. Moles.
Fried so
bad music of the 80s.
It is with you, Thomas. Must
defend the honor of your family.
As a man.
I call
"The Justiceira.
- Your father bought it?
- Profits of divorce.
Never underestimate the power of
feeling of guilt of a man.
Just the mention of the mother
already takes us straight to the mall.
It is all yours. Not
a coward forever.
I do not know, no, man.
Take a look at that face.
Really want to brother?
- No way.
- We prune the family tree.
This is quite funny,
is not, Ricky?
It? Well ..
You know, it's just the beginning.
Wow, the sun beating
water e. ..
This cotton shirt
is ...
- Suffocating.
- I hate cotton.
Want to help pass
the sunscreen, baby?
I think I hit her boyfriend
with this is not the best idea.
It is not ideas,
but action.
Do not think. Do.
I can not believe I'm listening to you.
Is dressed in bush.
- Now, spread on my chest.
- Target is in action.
Bring it before
he goes further.
I think not ...
- What? It caca head?
- Will compromise our position!
My God, she saw us.
What do we do?
She is coming.
Get down and stay hidden.
- Sorry, sorry.
- You shot my boyfriend.
Apology not even close.
When will grow
and stop being a shame?
- That's why we use camouflage.
- Shut up, Jake.
I do not know what you
I was thinking.
- Yes I'll be okay ...
- A paintball gun?
Do not know what is dangerous?
And what next?
Bola? Pellet? Shock?
What will I do? What do you think?
I do not know what to do!
Leave it in the fourth
the rest of the week?
- But neither was I!
- Right.
It was lucky he did not stay
seriously injured.
All right, Mr. P.,
has also been a child.
What kind, Ricky. Thank you.
He is a nice guy.
But do not feel well
that.
We are here to fish, not to
hunt her boyfriend.
You could have him blinded,
would have been funny?
I think not.
Let's start from scratch.
Tomorrow, we fish.
- Seven o'clock.
- At seven?
- Are you kidding!
- I'm out. Nate!
Yeah, Stu. Is not that
a little early?
How about this: 10 hours
the boat, without discussion?
Good way to solve, Nate.
Hey, Stu?
- The TV blew up.
- Stu, the TV blew up.
Mother, stop it.
Must be the antenna.
After the rain
climb the roof and repair.
Wait, Mr. P.,
let me fix it.
It's the least I can do
for their hospitality.
- No, you're hurt.
- That was nothing.
No, dear, he is okay. Go there
Richard. Show your energy.
Absolutely.
But I need help.
What do you say, brother?
Our chance to bury
old hurts.
If hit with Ricky,
or not get off that roof.
Ladies first.
Seems horror movie.
Sure. Let's go.
Look on the paintball ...
No questions asked.
Took! Too slow!
You know, thanks to his shot
I mean with their parents
and his sister is dying to be
my private nurse.
So thank you, champ.
It was a maneuver support perfect!
Come on, stop fooling around. Go on
and make me the hero of Grandma.
But I told my father
you to fix it.
He said a lot of things to him.
Like, my car broke ...
My parents have
a house on the lake ...
I'm 18 ...
You are not forming?
Not high school.
Now, go.
Go.
Hello?
- Dude, you make too!
- Not funny!
What the hell happened
with the antenna?
I can not stand one weeks
no TV here.
here and point.
Hello, human!
Please say it is
saw it too!
- Not that I want, but yes.
- We came from up there.
- I take care of human contact.
- Yes, sir. Noted. Yes
Hello, human.
No need to call the army.
We come in "folders".
- In "peace." Repeat after me: "peace.
- What? What are you talking about?
Book idiot. Forget the book!
Attack humans! Attack!
With pleasure!
Human.
Submit yourselves!
- Why are they taking so long?
- No, come ...
Ricky!
- What is wrong with him?
- Now the fun begins.
Testing! Testing ...
Testing.
Subjects insignificant.
We are the kind Zirconian.
And by this we demand
its lush planet like ours.
You have the choice between
servitude or ...
instantaneous death.
- Run?
- For me is good!
You chose
instantaneous death.
- They are falling!
- It's locked!
Not escape me.
- And now?
- Get down!
Unbelievable!
- Razor, go!
- Yes, sir!
- Can I play too?
- Thank God! Open! Fast!
Fast!
- Bichinhos disgusting!
- No! Back!
Care!
Hey, little toad!
What noise is that?
Open the window!
- Open there.
- Open you.
- No, you open!
- Fast! Get them!
Someone open!
Let's right there.
They have to open ...
Fast!
Run, twins!
Fall everyone! Now!
- What?
- Come on!
Pets disgusting.
- Disgusting ...
- Go, go!
Down!
Move! Fast!
- Commander, be careful.
- What's up with that?
- Beware!
- Fix.
I'll fix it!
This is very ...
- Are you a zombie?
- No.
- You?
- Prove it.
- What do you mean?
- I mean, prove!
- He wet the bed up to 10 years.
- A zombie would not know it.
- There they are!
- Beware!
- Human ugly.
A rope!
- Tom, tie!
- I'm trying. Push strong!
God! God!
She scratched
with his claw.
Get out, idiot!
- He cut her nails!
- We gotta call 190!
- I can not sign.
- Me neither.
Mine too is dead.
Dwarves are Martians
be interfering.
It is never a good sign.
Working.
You do not have keys.
What is that thing?
It is a rotary phone.
You turn it.
What happened there? "Get them"
was not clear enough?
Someone was
obviously distracted.
I was following
plan.
You kidding
with his toy.
- This is a deadly weapon.
- No.
- Yes.
- Those are deadly weapons.
Listen to what they say. So not
had success in the previous mission.
Not wanting to blame,
but it was the fault of the Razor.
- What? It was you ...
- If we fail this time,
I lose my command.
Will learn
work together
or we all end up together,
collecting manure in Sector 7.
We will not disappoint you, sir.
Come enslave some humans!
In fact, about that ...
I'm sure that enslave
is fun,
- But because humans?
- What?
They do not seem so bad.
- Beginners ...
- "They do not seem so bad."
Funny, that's what our
former engineer said.
- Former engineer?
- Well before the creature
"there seemed
bad "to eat it!
Humans are evil.
Peace is not an option.
Here is the sheriff.
There is an alien invasion
in our house.
Human small, short,
and violent.
- Baixinhos? Type ... a hobbit?
- No. Real.
I know it sounds crazy
but have to understand ...
Listen son, do you know that a
false accusation is federal offense?
- Is punishable ...
- Hello?
Technical decent ...
for a female.
How about this technique?
Hello?
We must rely
our parents.
Do you think he still
alien is a zombie?
You are useless. Because pins
mind control does not work?
You are the engineer,
discover. Fast.
Fast. Fix it.
He is not talking
with us, right?
I think you're getting the conversation
them. As a "bluetooth".
Are you telling me that the pins
work only in mature subjects?
Why not plan it?
You failed me.
Your incompetent piece of ...
"Translation Unavailable".
These humans will pay.
- Did you hear that?
- It seems that Ricky was the guy.
No. That they shot at us.
Control pins are mental.
Not work in children. Is like
said. We have "connections" different.
And Ricky? They got
and he has the age of Bethany.
He lied. Idiot
in college.
If you do not work in children,
means that we are saved.
- It means that we can fight.
- It means that our country will take up.
- They are walking targets.
- We have to tell them. Now!
Hold on.
Think.
Se nossos pais chegarem perto,
will be caught and will turn zombies.
- Our fathers in the attack.
- We need the police.
- And a firepower heavy.
- Zombies armed. Better.
We lost.
Game over.
End game for adults.
But we can still fight.
Expected to prevent a
alien invasion alone?
He's right.
We are the only option.
But we can not
tell anyone.
No police, no parents,
no exceptions, understood?
Hannah?
They are there in the attic. Now
same. Small aliens.
They are loud, are
scary and very bad.
- There are no aliens.
- There is. I saw them.
They broke the antenna and tried
break down the attic stairs.
I hope not,
for their own good.
We pay a large deposit on the house.
It's good to keep in one piece.
You heard Tom,
No more problems.
It was just a video game.
We should not have let her see.
- Yes, video game.
- Scary.
Tommy, I'm afraid.
I do not like the evil aliens.
Do not worry, Hannah.
Pretend it's a great game.
A game that we win.
Think about how they are small.
Small and deadly.
What we do now?
Found
their weakness.
They came from outer space
really think they have a weakness?
First rule
code warrior ...
"All enemies
have a weakness. "
Sparks, because my map locator
not working yet?
I told you, I
parts to fix it.
Even on Earth
the male is dominant.
- Wait ...
- But the female always wins.
But what ...
Those rings Zirkon!
- It makes no sense!
- They were fighting ...
Now your lips are
is stroking?
- I never ... Never!
- Never.
License, can I bring something?
Cold drinks or a snack?
Or would prefer to help me
to invade the planet?
Sure, there goes my
specialty. I rise.
- I'm with you.
- Tom, be careful.
Enemy ... seized.
I asked him.
- Gross.
- What? Seriously, what?
- Browser enabled, sir.
- Excellent, secure the goal.
Take a zoom.
Zoom!
- Zoom, zoom ...
- No need to be saying zoom.
- Zoom e. .. run.
- They're after something in the house.
- Running.
- Good
- Let me see better.
- Stop.
- Turn, turn ... The basement!
- Tom, help me.
Must have hurt.
Basement. We have to go
to the basement.
Ricky?
Ricky!
Personal expected.
Have you seen Ricky?
Should be here,
somewhere.
- Beth ...
- He was not though, was it?
No. Him ..
said he was going to the lake,
tanning your abdominals.
He wants to see you there.
Hold on.
Talked about what
the roof?
- He said something about me?
- No.
No. He talked about
his car. E. ..
Almost exclusively on
his car.
- But you should go to the lake.
- It is the lake.
- It is there.
- The lake is there.
I'm saying, map them
led to down here.
- Are you sure?
- Did you hear that?
Sound of cornflakes ...
What is this?
They.
Something down here
is shooting it.
Whatever it is, we can not
let them be.
Everyone, get ready.
- Come to my command.
- Wait a minute ...
If we go up there with a lot of
any crap we are screwed.
- We can do better.
- We are in the middle of a battle
and wants to play
science fair?
Hardly.
Let's go back there now.
Before our parents
see zombies aliens.
You're not thinking.
We need a plan.
I already have a great idea
for a weapon.
It? Come on.
Now!
Hannah, give me that tape.
- So?
- Hi, everybody!
Who wants a cupcake?
Wow, that's a lot of tool
to try to fix the TV.
They are trying to get out. Code
Warrior says "attack first".
Art, cover me.
With the rake?
How do you feel now?
Idiots.
Mission accomplished.
Damn!
Failed.
But what ...
- What's going on?
- We are floating.
They turned off the gravity,
as in "Halo".
This is not an Xbox, Lee
It's real. As the Wii.
- What do we do now?
- I do not know.
Stay behind me.
- No. No!
- No, again ...
- Hello, humans.
- Enjoying the ride?
- They have gravity boots.
- Why do not we?
- "Boots of gravity" ...
- The door. Prevent them.
Use your gun, Tom
- Go for it, meat sack.
- Today!
A potato gun?
This is your big idea?
- My plan is working.
- My plan. That is my plan.
Quick, Tommy.
- You okay?
- I'm fine.
- The door.
- I'm going.
Jake, get the grenade.
Fast.
Fast. Play here.
What?
Monkey luck!
You little ...
- Go. Stand back.
- Take them.
- Shoot them.
- Go. will.
Shoot them.
- Venha!
- Okay.
My ass is on fire!
This is the thing that use
to control Ricky.
Cool. Let me see.
Good action buttons.
What is this?
Let me see.
I got first.
Return.
Folks, this is not
a toy. It's real.
- Ricky?
- Yeah.
Get it before someone else thinks.
I'll be watching the aliens.
I think that
will come out easy.
- Where will he go?
- I'll find it.
Cool, then these are the floor.
And these ...
Control arms.
Speaking of
gameboy supreme ...
What does the big button?
But what ...
Car!
It would be the button
on or off.
Press again.
- Who did this to my car?
- You did, you big idiot.
Ricky!
Where have you been?
Shut up, you little ...
Bethany?
What?
- Why are you hitting me?
- Why is it so lame?
Revenge
is so sweet.
I spent the last hour running
the lake. Where were you?
- I thought so.
- No, I do not know.
- You want to take you back?
- I do not know ...
Let him suffer.
Where's Ricky?
- The aliens got him?
- No, worse ... my sister.
Some action up here?
It has been quiet.
Too quiet.
Understand?
- Understand?
- Yes, sir.
What are you doing
ventilation?
The map of them. Thus
will arrive to the basement.
What do we do?
I hope that
work, Einstein.
I never got to thank
for having saved me there.
Why not needed
to do so.
- That makes no sense.
- I do not like you.
- Cut the conversation.
- Right.
I'm sweating?
It's hot.
Hottest ...
Run!
Back!
Sounds good ...
Good work.
I think it's working.
Children. Come down here,
now.
Who turned on the heater?
I called.
We need it on.
- Are you crazy? It's July.
- Yeah, but is freezing here.
- Wow. Arctic.
- I think Han is getting sick.
- Han, what's going on?
- We are fighting aliens.
'm Pretending
is make-believe.
Quero dizer,
Sure, but I'm not doing
account. Do not touch the thermostat.
- Tom, I'm not kidding.
- Me neither.
Tom, really. Want to spend the rest
the week in your room?
Why not trust that there
a reason to do this?
One reason for melting
the boiler in the summer holidays?
To shoot the boyfriend
your sister?
To discuss with me
this attitude?
To get low grades?
So that's it.
I took grades
purpose.
It is my fucked
notes, okay?
I'm tired of being AZUCRINADO
to be a skull.
I was, it worked
me.
Not want to be like you.
I want to be cool.
Do not touch the thermostat.
Really? Are taking
grades on purpose?
Nobody likes a
Athlete of Mathematics.
We can not fight them
with our parents here.
We can not simply
get rid of them.
Maybe we can.
I want to do
the following ...
Send it.
I hate when we fight.
I can not fight with someone
as beautiful as you.
'm Glad
which made up.
Are not peace officers
without the kiss.
- Calm down, my family is there.
- And they are crazy for me.
- And you?
- You know I like you.
And we have all summer
before us.
Perhaps we need not
go so fast.
What?
This is a no?
Ricky!
Caution, do not break.
- Ricky!
- Do you get the shirt.
Ricky!
Still no sign of them.
- Where are they?
- Two options ...
We are dealing with a recession
or a surprise attack.
NO SIGNAL
Surprise attack.
Where's Tom?
I thought I'd help you.
- Me too.
- Bad news.
The estate called.
They need to return there before
to close for the holiday.
- Really?
- Problems with the contract.
They insisted.
Ricky, are you okay?
It's just allergies, Mr. P.
But actually said
it is urgent.
Sure. I'll call
and will resolve it.
What a strange thing.
This is strange, Stu.
I think the phone
muted.
They cut our energy?
They will hear what I have
say! Come on
- We are going there right now.
- Hey, guys ...
We need more beer,
Snacks ...
Pass the market and I
light the barbecue.
- And take care of children?
- All right, whatever.
No!
I mean, all you
have to go. They ...
They said that all their
names are on the list.
- I'll take care of children.
- I do not know if it's a good idea.
Well, I think
could go driving.
- Okay, okay.
- And, Mr. P.,
as it will go, can I bring
some adult diapers?
Mine is almost full ...
- What is a bad allergy.
- Superabsorbent!
Look!
Fog deadly alien!
- Do not breathe.
- Put it on pause.
Happy 4th of July
worms space.
Jake, have smoke
ventilation.
I did. They were moving
I have tracked down and amazed.
- Legal.
- Parents?
- If you have been.
- Legal.
Now we can take this
to a level above.
This could get ugly.
Hannah, go into hiding.
- Yes
- Indo ...
You do not.
- It's coming!
- Move! Go!
Swallow it, idiots!
- Ai ...
- Damn!
- Go! Run!
- Run!
I'm beginning to see
because the last engineer ...
I see you put traps
in your room.
I got, got ...
I could not.
Trap human
despicable ...
I laugh a lot with you!
- It's okay, do not worry.
- We come in peace ...
It's okay,
I'll help you.
Do not worry.
It's okay.
It has a Machucadinho.
Do not move.
- All right?
- Thank you.
Tazer. Razor.
Sparks ...
Sparks!
It is essential
to our mission.
- Beautiful sounds.
- It's music!
- Music! I try?
- Sure!
Definitely the delay, but
those worms adapt fast.
We enter
the big guns.
Hissing black cat
or Fire Dragon?
That it would not set fire
the house?
He is armed ...
Enemy armed!
Hannah, stay away
the alien.
No.
No! Leave him alone!
He is my friend.
He was pointing a gun
rays to his head.
It's my bubble blower.
He fixed it for me.
He is not
others. Look!
At the first sign of
aggression, I will drop.
- With extreme damage.
- I have no training for it.
- Training all.
- It's okay, Mr. Snugglelump.
- Snugglelump?
- It was the name I gave to him.
- My name is Sparks.
- It's not your pet, Hannah.
It is an alien weirdo.
He's my alien.
Hi ..
I mean ... yuck!
Maybe she's right.
Look what his belt ...
It is to carry tools.
Okay, friend. Just want
talk to you.
Come, Snuggs.
Back.
Look.
Amazing!
How does he do it?
What was that?
Talking about feelings is
part of having a girlfriend.
Had no reason
for that.
Sure. Okay, understood. It will
talk while I scream.
Sorry, is ...
immature yelled.
Look, I'm so happy
to be his girlfriend.
But if you really care about me
like I care about you.
It should not be a problem
give me the time I need.
You may need to think about it.
I respect that, right?
Take the time you want.
I'll be here,
ready to talk.
You.
So is this? I get the
silent treatment?
Who is in
school now?
- Why are they trying to kill us?
- What is the plan of invasion?
- What is your weakness?
- Water?
- Earthworms?
- Women?
- There are more of you coming from?
- We need the information.
- Do not be evil ...
- Hannah, we have to ask him.
Whether the world ends?
Want?
No. ..
Home here.
Purpose of the mission here.
What they seek is not in the basement,
is beneath him.
- Yes
- What to steal the planet?
This is not our planet.
Look at that, seems alien.
Should be of their planet.
Is. The planet "Blossom."
Whatever it is, is huge.
How does he do it?
So this is what is in the capsule.
Some kind of giant machine?
Great. A huge
alien killing machine.
- No one said anything about death.
- I doubt it is a copier.
What! We can not rely
4 of this weird arms.
- He is one of them!
- It is not.
This guy does not match
others.
He is ...
else.
- Great. An alien "geek".
- Jake, he is not a "geek".
It's better than one
alien assassin.
"Buenas Noches"
enrugadinha.
ESTATE
CREEK LANDING
DESCULPEM,
ARE CLOSED
This is ridiculous!
What a mess!
Modified!
Beauty.
Beauty ...
Sorry.
- It's the strip. Hold up.
- Stay ... cold?
Open up!
- Damn, forget Grandma.
- Wait. Hannah, fast.
- Hide your alien.
- Open the door now!
Snuggs, enter here!
- Wait a minute.
- Children of my children ...
entry requirement.
I have sweets!
- Do not open. This is not Grandma.
- Are you sure?
Yeah, sure.
Hand over the engineer
Sparks now!
- Engineer? I do not know ...
- Move over, son of Earth.
- Move.
- Grandma ...
Do not make me hurt you.
Grandma ... I ...
- Return it to me.
- Tom, do something!
Human disgusting.
- Someone has to answer.
- Not to be, is dangerous.
- Here comes Grandma!
- Let my grandma alone!
Silence project
tiny human ...
I picked up the controller
Grandma!
Set me free! Or face
consequences ...
- In here.
- You will not catch me. I got you!
You ...
Shake all you want,
we got him.
The suitcase. Go!
It got me!
Stand still,
bastards of the earth.
- Got it! Let.
- Do not stop taking the Snuggles!
Art, fast.
- Shoot it.
- Shoot the humans!
- Shoot 'em up!
- Get down!
- You lost!
- It's ours forever!
I, Han. Sorry
that got him.
- Beauty, eh?
- Very cool.
Here is the Sheriff's Department
of Creek Landing,
open this door immediately
will initiate or forced entry.
- In 10, 9 ...
- Right.
You get rid of the strip,
I go after the aliens.
- 5, 4 ...
- We can not leave it here.
Um ..
I do not know how much they know about
criminal codes,
but make phone calls with the intent
to annoy or disturb
is a serious offense.
Attention is criminal damage and may
mean 6 months in jail.
The 190 is only called
emergency
and any misuse of this system
compromises our line of defense.
And this defense is me.
Around here, I am the law.
Literally, I'm the only one. My
boss is on maternity leave.
Look, Sheriff, we apologize.
It will not happen again.
Seriously ... You can go now
we behave.
I "can" go?
Sure, we solve everything then.
- What have you got?
- Squadron answer!
- They are the Sparks?
- No!
Do you have a job
you two do not go bad?
Answer. I'm sorry, I
excuses. That was unnecessary.
Still stuck in that
box, right?
Yes, I am.
- Get away, young man.
- No need.
It's just the robot dog
my sister.
It is activated by sound.
- Okay, Han?
- Right! There is an alien.
You know what? I'll take a look
inside. Please stay away.
It is the strip. Hold up.
One hour. We were out for 1 hour.
What was, what they did?
Hi, I'm Nina Pearson
You all right?
- It's all right?
- No, ma'am.
I would have to call the 190
about an alien invasion
- Nothing is sure.
- They called the 190?
Come on, buddy. Certainly can
release them with a warning.
Look at them.
Um, I'm not your buddy.
Two, I noticed that his vehicle
is no license plate.
- Three, that this will give you a fine?
- That it would not give?
Nate, stop talking.
You tend to leave their children
so, without supervision?
No. No way.
We had to go to the estate.
They cut our electricity.
For me, it seems
be all right.
Sheriff, I know that is something
difficult to explain.
But honestly
there is nothing wrong here.
Why do not you and see for yourself?
Let's have a barbecue.
- Stay with us.
- Mother ..
Thank you, ma'am, I would.
But I'm on duty.
The boys committed
a big mistake.
And I guarantee that the
Tom will be punished.
But she's right. Have good
food. Why do not you?
I know it's service. But
no law against home cooking.
We have a lot of
hot dogs,
burgers, steaks ...
You'll love it.
Sure.
A decent meal.
I have not been as one.
- Okay, convinced me.
- Great.
I think one hour apart
not kill anyone.
Of course not.
- Gotcha.
- Hey!
What was that?
- What was what?
- Something clicked.
- Come on, everybody. Dinner.
- We have dinner.
Come.
I take dessert.
- I'll get you, bastard.
- I said it.
- Stop it.
Fell in trivia!
Live the Zirkonianos!
Sure. Wait Mom, do not
I understand. What happened?
One minute was cleaning
denture, the other was here.
You know, may have a moment
those in their age.
Sorry, I forgot.
Want cheese on a burger?
No.
I think whoever invented love
and smash him with a hatchet.
- Problems with boys.
- You and me both.
I do not know what to do about
the problem of Tom
We have a guest.
Put a smile.
- Nate, where's Jake?
- No idea.
Dinner is almost ready.
How about going for him?
Jake is an adult.
If you want to eat, come check.
- Sorry.
- That was bad.
- No, I'm asking.
Oops Care
with his head.
There is nothing more American
a piece of meat in the stomach.
- I bought the pickles.
- Really?
If you think this will
rid it of that fine ...
No way, sir.
It's my stomach.
I'm starving.
- Any news of Jake?
- Still no sign.
- Where is he?
- Boys, none of the table.
- All right, Nate?
- Okay what?
- They are playing with the phones.
- Yes, that is. Hit it.
- Can someone pass the mustard?
- Hey, Hannah?
Ate all
hot dogs?
No.
I mean, yes.
I say, walk by eating only
pasta, the police car.
Every day, alone.
- Are you comfortable up there?
- I hope so.
Enjoy a little
land on your face.
Attention, everyone.
Resistance is futile.
- I deem I need.
- Honey.
- I knew you would.
- Back off, female hormone.
Wait. Are you
hormone calling?
Get away. You irrelevant
for my mission.
Irrelevant?
I do not care about your age.
Can not talk to me like that.
- What is happening?
- Drama teenager. Think.
The teen drama,
right, Ricky?
Snuggles!
- Turn it off.
- Not me.
Let. Bring Grandma.
Stopped.
You have not
are released.
Let them go.
're Playing
a game, Uncle Stu ...
I mean, Stu.
Are on vacation.
I'm getting younger?
I think not.
Do you really want to deprive me
of my time with the children?
Guilt is never tired.
Well, go ahead.
I think we should leave
Mom away from the wine ...
You lost!
And now the invasion
begin.
Invasion? There are
of you coming from?
More. And we
crush them like insects.
Do not crush them
first.
I will not be defeated
by children.
More signs of resistance
and that they call
Jake will be deleted.
I want Snugglelump
back!
Basta. It's time to die.
Richard
remember Grandma?
- The game began.
- The game is over.
- What a blow was that?
- Coup Samurai with twisted twist.
Grandma, get up!
He is in the buff.
Have her get it!
- Grandma!
- Lee, flying is their specialty!
- Get him, Lee
- I can not!
Give me!
- Ricky?
- What the ...
Grandma?
This, human cry, for his
species no longer exist today.
What the hell was
that thing?
An alien from space.
It's a long story.
We think they are here
to destroy the planet.
Come on, if not get down there
will be trouble.
I would say this is the
phrase of the century.
Mother?
You okay?
What happened?
How do I ... arrived ...
I need a glass of water.
Sure. Somebody better
start talking.
- Apparently it was a battle here.
- And there was.
- Grandma against Ricky.
- Not now, Hannah.
- Father, is not what it seems ...
- All of you up there.
- Now!
- Uncle Stu, it was not our fault.
Now!
If you want to join them,
better cough up.
What the hell
happened here?
I have no idea what
happened.
But for years I did not feel
my column so good.
Mother? Mother?
Where are you going?
Aliens.
- Build a machine! Now!
- No!
My bad, guys.
- It's all over.
- Finished?
As that is not finished.
Ricky're down with that ...
- Rodent space.
- You do not understand.
An entire fleet that faces
is to invade.
So be a man and
Deal with it.
I'm dealing with it ...
all day.
If he is afraid,
you can help me.
Not without Tom
- Why?
- Because he is our leader.
Let. Not only is Ricky,
Jake also needs help.
- And Snuggles.
- And all the earth.
Even our parents.
Okay.
Let's save the planet.
And her boyfriend silly.
You want the monkey?
He is lucky.
I'm fine.
Stay close. They can
be anywhere.
It's Jake!
He tied me up and Zirconian
Snuggles dragged out.
- God damn vacation!
- He saw the machine?
Yeah, you were right.
Sent here for years.
Some idiot built
this on top of it.
Personally, I found the first show.
- He is waking up.
- Where the hell am I?
Love, I'm glad
is well.
Do not touch me!
- Stop!
- Okay.
I know it has been a strange day,
but have to let me explain.
Okay.
Sure.
I explain why
keep deleting,
because I'm bleeding and because
his grandmother gave me a kick ninja.
Sure.
We are fighting against
aliens from space.
Yeah, they are small but
dangerous and very frightening.
Bright. I believe in you.
Why do not they?
Why waste time playing
hide and seek and kill aliens
with his brother and stupid
their cousins stupid?
Do not talk of
my family
Well, look no further
worry about it.
Because we.
Should have stayed home and
out with Annie Filkins,
is really good and not like
of talking about ...
"feelings" all the time!
I'm going straight to
home of Annie.
I'm so sorry.
Do not.
Was right all along.
If it's any consolation ...
he goes straight to
home of Annie
or anywhere
for a while.
Personally, this comes
"union brothers"
are on alert
up here.
My God.
- The forced to build it.
- Building what?
How will dominate the
world with that thing?
I do not want to find out.
We must stop them before
the fleet arrives.
- Fleet?
- This is just the advance team.
We need to rescue
Snugglelump.
- Snuggle what?
- Lump.
The guy abroad.
He is on our side.
The other three,
not so.
- This is not happening.
- We have to go there. Come!
Not so fast.
I have a plan.
Help me here!
Someone has Mentos?
- Why?
- Pass here!
- What? We shoot them?
- No.
We will projetinho
science.
Bomb Mentos.
You're a genius.
They should not do that.
Humans are friends ...
It's coming!
In my eyes!
- Let's get them! Move!
- Come on. Go, go!
- Snuggles!
- Traitor!
- Let me go!
- The powerful just been bagged!
He is unconscious.
- You!
- Get off my planet
your child's blue ...
- How do you feel now?
- We did it! We ended up with him!
- How did it?
- Too bad ...
Nothing beauty
Beauty is nothing ...
Hey, human ...
machine ... expanded o. ..
Machine made Grand Commander ...
Who is small now,
your worms of the earth?
- Pretty cool, huh?
- We need a larger potato.
Over. I won.
- Where is he going?
- Where he wants.
How so?
And Mom and Dad?
Guys, listen.
Not have much time.
Sparks, anything
can go on that machine?
- Theoretically.
- Art, Lee, I control it.
Bethany, I need to keep
the other prisoners.
Sure.
Jake, come on. This
battle is not over.
Others.
Ali!
Cool! It was also higher.
You are an alien
ugly.
It can be ugly
but mine.
You do not know when
give up, you know?
We need a shot
clean his neck.
I rise.
- Broke my nail!
- I do not care!
My God, are signs!
He is calling
for the invasion.
- My Madonna.
- Look at that ...
- God bless America.
- What is a patriotic act.
Not bad. But it is
nothing compared to this.
These fireworks are there
Category 3!
Think will win
another fine.
Light them. Make that
there to shame.
Got it.
Tom, come on, I thought.
Make him turn around.
Hey, down here, your
prehistoric garbage space.
- Very good, Nate.
- It was great!
They cost only U $ 1.99,
can you believe it?
- I guess it was not you, Nate.
- What is it?
They.
They will arrive soon.
Open your eyes, folks.
There is only one answer.
- Rain of meteors.
- Really ...
- You are right.
- It's ... bright.
That's all you got?
- Oops!
- Come on ...
Tom shoots.
Shoot!
The collar it
remains disturbing.
Care! The ugly
was great!
Hurry! Shoot, Tom!
45 meters ... the aliens have an arc
of 20 with a volume of the square ...
45 degrees.
What was that?
Moved to the athlete
math wrong.
- Yes!
- Get it closely ...
- Comandante?
- Wait a minute!
Human unfortunate.
That's all you have?
That's good.
- See that?
- Sparks, revert the machine.
Very easy.
- Nothing is working.
- Give it to me!
- Cruel, but effective.
- It was too much.
- Reversed.
- Tommy, it's time!
You came back for me.
Let. We cherish
the lips Zirkon.
- Bethany!
- Han, okay?
- We are here.
- Bethany!
- Have you seen?
- Good work.
- Snuggs was great. You too.
- Tom, and others?
Many.
Backward. Back!
The machine is destroyed.
We were overwhelmed
by humans.
The invasion failed! Back
to Zirkon immediately!
Backward. Back!
Disappeared.
Over.
It's all over.
We won.
Thanks Snuggs.
Everything.
You're a fine, for a
worm space. To miss.
Saudades? He will be here.
With us.
Please do not go.
Can be part of our family.
Han, I think he
already have a family.
My family.
Goodbye, Hannah.
- Look over your notes ...
- Father, I'll spare you the sermon.
You were right.
And I was wrong.
In the end, there are advantages
to be smart.
Sorry.
Had a great sermon preparation.
Even trained in front of the mirror.
- Did you see the meteor shower?
- Yes, it was revealing.
Beautiful shot, Grandma!
I got one!
It touches here!
- Annie!
- Ricky ...
- I was at the lake house?
- The vacation ended early.
- This is for you.
- You are so cute ...
Is my girlfriend now,
then do everything for you.
Now take a caring
for pa ...
- Girls ...
- It's the night the girls.
But, you should come.
If you like to dance.
Dance?
- You did not see what is dance ...
- Until I saw the Funky Ricky.
Moment of underwear.
- Ball bouncing ...
- I think that impressed.
Turn it off.
Ricky, is acting
strange.
What are you talking about?
Will turn it on again.
I even get it!
Translation: Hasitha Tharinda
(htharinda@GMAIL.COM)