You'll pay me $10,000 up front
and another ten grand
when the job's done.
On the day
I finish our contract,
a dozen white roses will be sent
to your office.
Don't attempt to contact me.
If you need to communicate,
go to the steps
at the main entrance
of the Central Post Office.
3:00 in the afternoon,
I'll find you.
This meeting will be
the last time you'll see me.
Once you pay me,
changing your mind is
a complication
that's going to cost you.
So I got to ask you
one more time.
Are you sure you want him dead?
All right, let's go.
Come on, keep it moving.
Buy you a cup of
coffee, Mr. Neville?
Do I know you?
Detective Mac Taylor.
I was called to the
scene of the accident.
I don't remember.
I've tried to contact you
several times since then.
You refused my calls,
wouldn't allow me to visit,
so you left me no choice
but to be here today.
And now you're here?
I was wondering
if we could talk.
Why?
Because you just spent 18 months in prison
for a crime you didn't commit.
-==破烂熊乐园倾情奉献==-
本字幕仅供学习交流，严禁用于商业用途
-==http://www.ragbear.com==-
犯罪现场调查纽约篇 第5季第23集
-=破烂熊字幕组=-
翻译：ID
校对：ID
时间轴：panda
Adam,have you seen Danny?
He left about 20 minutes ago with Doc to
a crime scene on the Upper West Side.
What about, uh,
Stella or Mac?
Stella's in court
and the boss took a day off.
Yeah, can you believe it?
Mac never takes
a day off.
I don't think
there's been one day
since I've worked here
that he hasn't showed up.
He's like,
"Hey, I'm not coming in,"
you know,although he did go to London
that one time, but I don't...
-Adam, okay, enough.
-What?
I just got back
from Montana.
I-I'm not ready
to deal with you.
-Okay.
-This is not how I imagined it.
What?
-I need you to focus, Adam.
-Okay.
Go get a set of keys
to a car, any car.
Meet me in the garage
in five minutes.
My water just broke.
I'm about to go into labor
and you are taking me to the hospital.
Go!
-Okay.
Adam...
Yeah, wrong way,
sorry, j-just relax.
Everything's
going to be okay.
Here you go.
Thanks very much.
So it was your fault?
What do you mean?
I just spent 18 months
in Riker
You show up
on the day I get out
and tell me I shouldn't have
been there in the first place?
Two years ago your vehicle struck
and killed Maris Donovan.
You claimed
that you were behind the wheel,
but I believe someone
else was driving.
So, I'm just curious,
why would you take responsibility
for something you didn't do?
You think that's what happened?
Yes, I do.
Unfortunately, all I've got is circumstantial forensic evidence
and a gut feeling.
None of which the DA will pay any attention to without
the truth from you.
Why would I lie about something
like that?
Why would I sentence myself
to prison?
Because you didn't think you'd
go to prison, Talmadge.
Or if you did go to prison,
you'd get three months, tops.
Or maybe you'd just get slapped
with a fine.
But instead, a very unsympathetic judge
made an example of you,
and there was no way
you could have predicted that would happen.
And there was no way
you could get out of it once you took the blame.
A detective
chasing theories,
What I'm chasing is the truth.
Someone committed a crime
and got away with it.
There was no one else
in that car.
Well, that's what we believed that night
because that's what you told us,
but I have evidence that
suggests otherwise.
Circumstantial evidence?
Thanks for the coffee.
Oh, no! No! No! Oh, no!
No, I-I can't... I can't tell
if she's breathing!
I don't know if she's alive!
Somebody help!
I'm a doctor.
I might be able to help.
Somebody call 911.
Please be okay.
Call an ambulance!
It's a terrible accident.
It's just awful, Mac.
She's so young.
Her name is Maris Donovan.
The deli ownerays
she comes in occasionally.
Thinks she lives
around the block.
Was he the one driving the car?
Talmadge Neville.
Said he didn't see her
until it was too late
and did everything he could
to avoid the collision.
He swerved, and his car
slammed into the lamppost.
Is he okay?
Paramedics
checked him out.
Despite the damage
to the car,
he appears to be
physically fine.
Emotionally,
he's struggling to hold it together.
-Intoxicated?
-No. Passed the sobriety.
This is a bad one.
Any witnesses?
No one that can help.
Most of these folks
just heard the noise.
A passerby tried to revive her
before ESU got here, but...
Was there anyone else
in the car?
No, he was alone.
What'd you find?
********
Looks like he was
texting while driving.
Maris! Where's my daughter?
Maris!
Ma'am, I'm sorry, you
can't toh the body.
Oh, no!
Mrs. Donovan.
No, no!
Listen, listen, listen, I'm...
-Did you do this?
-I am so sorry. It was an accident.
Look what you've done
to my daughter!
Look what you did to her!
Give her back...
-Mrs. Donovan, please! Mrs. Donovan!
Oh, no!
Why isn't she answering her phone?
Doc, take 57th right there.
It'll be faster.
Danny, I got this, I got this.
l right.
Voicemail again.
Baby, it's me.
We're close, okay?
Hold on till I get there, okay?
I don't want to miss this.
I love you. I love you, okay?
Hey! Watch out, man!
Okay, right here, Doc, Doc,
Doc, okay, right there.
Make a right, go around the
corner and pull into Emergency.
Hey, Danny,
congrats, brother.
Thanks, Doc.
Hi.
Okay, here's what
you're looking for.
Talmadge Neville's parole
officer is Jerome Addison.
Condition of his parole is that he check in
within four hours of his release.
I've got an address
up on East 59th Street.
Hey, I thought you were
taking the day off.
Just looking into some
unfinished business.
Neville. It's the, uh,
car accident, right?
He was texting?
thought that case was
pretty cutnd dry.
He did 18 months.
Got out this morning.
Hey, Mac, most people on their
days off take in a museum,
a matinee,
catch up on some sleep.
Here you are digging up
a closed case.
Our lab didn't analyze the
evidence collected at the scene
because at the time Neville took
full responsibility.
Well, makes sense.
He was driving the car.
Maybe not.
Okay.
So you've processed
that evidence.
And now you have
a different theory?
Nothing definitive,
but certainly enough to have reasonable doubt.
You were that kid
in school
who did all the extra credit
projects, weren't you?
You made all the rest
of us look bad.
Three months ago
I slammed on the brakes
in my car
to avoid a collision with the
vehicle in front of me.
My shoulder restraint jolted
back.
And I was, I was sore within an hour
and for a few days afterwards.
My left shoulder was bruised
from where the restraint tightened.
That moment triggered a memory.
The night of Talmadge
Neville's accident,
I remember quite clearly he was
rubbing his right shoulder.
Which would put him
in the passenger seat.
And suggests someone else
was driving.
I suppose I could
just let this go.
But Don, I can't forget the look
on Katherine Donovan's face
when she saw her daughter
lying lifeless in that street.
I remember thinking,
"I'm so glad this
isn't a hit and run."
That this man took
full responsibility for what he'd done.
He didn't claim
the brakes didn't work,
he didn't point the
finger at the victim.
There was something so tragic
yet decent about it all.
And now I believe
someone else is involved.
And that someone
thinks they got away with it?
No.
That's not how
this is going to end.
Thanks for this.
Mr. Neville, get in.
What the hell do you
want, Detective?
The truth, a name.
I have nothing to say.
All right, then I'll dothe talking. come on.
I heard it already.
Look, Talmadge,
I'm not going away.
I could call your
parole officer.
He might wonder why a detective
from the crime lab is asking so many questions.
That would definitely
complicate things for you.
Come on, get in.
Start telling your story.
My lab recovered your vehicle
from the impound yard.
I recreated the reported
speed of the car
and simulated the
object of impact
and placement of the phone
and not once did the cell land
on the front passenger side
floor where u recovered it.
And in Neville's vehicle,
the power adjustment
gears under the seat
are too bulky for an object
just to slide forward.
But that doesn't definitively eliminate the possibility
that the driver was holding the phone.
But it makes it more plausible
Which brings us to the prints.
passenger seat was
Now, Neville's left thumb print
was on both the driver
and passenger seat belt
release button.
Well, he certainly could've been
a passenger in his own car
at another time
other than the accident.
Yes, he could and I thought
about that but...
This is Talmadge Neville's thumb print
lifted from the driver's side release button.
Now, based on the position of the apex
and the delta points,
it appears that Neville released the belt
from the passenger seat.
But there is another
possibility.
He could have used his left
hand from the driver's seat.
Doc, I thought about that,
too. But why would he reach
all the way across his body and turn his thumb
180 degrees to release the button?
I mean, it's an
unnatural action.
But easily accomplished
from the passenger seat.
Leads me to conclude
that Neville released
that belt to let
someone else out.
There was no one else
in that car.
I struggled with
my seat belt.
I panicked, couldn't get out.
The evidence doesn't
suggest that.
Your thumb pressed that
button once and lifted.
You had no problem
releasing the belt.
And the direction of the print implies that you weren't
in the driver's seat.
Why would I lie?
What would I gain?
I am now and forever an ex-con.
Unemployable,
unreliable, unworthy.
It doesn't sound like something a man
chooses if he's got an ounce of common sense.
You see that vendor there?
That was my life before
all this happened.
I was a single father,
working 10, 12 hours a day,
seven days a week,
peddling dogs and pretzels,
earning an honest
living for my kids.
My son, Joe, is now a professor.
And my daughter, Karita,
she's a surgeon.
And wouldn't you like
them to know the truth?
Were you in the car with someone you
shouldn't have been?
Were you or your family threatened
if you didn't keep this secret, Talmadge?
When you were in Rikers,
you refused to have any
other visitors except one.
Nick Donley.
He's head of the Local 515,
the City Sidewalk Cart Union.
I wanted to know what would
happen to my business.
He's also a pretty tough guy
who shakes down vendors for a cut.
Haven't seen you in
a while, Talmadge.
I been busy.
What do you say
we take a ride?
Hey, look, Nick,
I'm really tired, now.
You know, I've had a long day.
I'll tell you what.
I'll drive.
You listen.
Nick was not in the car.
Then who was?
You weren't behind the wheel of the car that hit
Maris Donovan.
The right person should
be punished for the crime.
The debt has been paid.
Unfortunately, Talmadge,
that's not a decision you get to make.
Yeah, I need to order
a dozen roses.
Delivered tonight after 5:00.
White.
Do they really think that I'm just going to
walk this baby right out of me?
Why can't I be one of those women
who just sneezes and before you can say,
"God bless you,"
she's had the baby?
Think of what
you'd miss out on.
Reminding your
child of all those long,
painful hours of labor
that you endured to bring them into this world.
I guess I could get
some mileage out of that.
I'm kinda scared, Stella.
That's normal, Lindsay.
Just remember, you're
healthy and strong.
You and Danny went
through all the courses.
Yeah, no, I don't mean
about having the baby.
About being a mom.
I mean, what if
I stink at it?
And the worse part is I won't
know until it's too late.
She'll come home, she'll
scream that she hates me,
then in rebellion she'll get some part
of her body pierced that's inappropriate.
And she'll get
an infection,
and she'll wind up
on antibiotics
which we find out 12 years later
they cause an eating disorder
and pretty soon
I'm in therapy trying to save my whole family.
I mean, what if some people just
aren't cut out to be parents?
Well, the fact that you already
thought about all this,
tells me that you're gonna
do just fine, Linds.
I'm losing it, huh?
Yeah.
Oh, contraction.
What if she has twins, Adam?
I mean, you hear stories about people
being completely surprised.
And you've seen Lindsay, right?
I mean, she's huge.
She knows it.
Relax, you got the ultrasound.
It's not twins, all right?
You gonna be okay?
No, no, I'm not.
Feel like I might go into cardiac arrest
while she's giving birth.
Mac, you're here.
No, no, she hasn't yet.
Oh, we're on
the fourth floor.
All right, I'll be right there.
ANNOUNCER (over P.A.): Dr. Karita Neville, please report
to the second floor nurses station, Tower Two.
My daughter, Karita,
she's a surgeon.
Dr. Karita Neville, please report
to the second floor nurses station, Tower Two.
Is that a picture
for your grandma?
Beautiful,
I like that.
Okay, well, I'll
see you later.
she was driving in the car.
You're sure
it was Dr. Neville?
Positive,
I remember her face.
She was at the accident scene.
That's who Talmadge Neville
was protecting, his daughter.
She had to be the one dring
the car, not him.
And then she just
blended into the crowd
and watched  he
took the fall?
Why would she do that?
It's possible that
they traded places
because she had more to lose
if she was behind the wheel of the car.
I remember Flack saying
that someone tried to revive the victim
before the paramedics arrived.
Is it possible that it
was Karita Neville?
I mean, she is a doctor.
Maybe there's something in Sid'autopsy report
of Maris Donovan that can confirm that.
Well, we know she was there.
You can ID her.
Yeah, but we need something
that puts her at the scene
very close to the
time of the accident.
Something that says
there was no other place
she could have been
except in that car.
We should go, Mrs. Donovan.
How much time will he get?
Talmadge Neville.
Most likely he'll be charged
with second degree manslaughter.
Time he serves will be
up to the judge.
Meaning he could simply get
probation and his license revoked?
Mr. Neville's been
very cooperative.
He's remorseful.
This whole thing--
Yes, I know, it was an accident.
Everybody keeps saying
it was an accident.
Just doesn't feel like that
on this side of the glass.
Oh, that man was stupid
and reckless.
In one split second,
he took my daughter's life.
And he has to live with that.
Unfortunately, so do I.
Mac.
Did you need something?
Uh, I was wondering
if you could pull an old autopsy file.
Maris Donovan.
Came in here
about two years ago.
You working
on your day off?
Why is it that everyone is so concerned
with what I do on my day off?
Are you kidding?
I mean, come on,
you never take a day off.
Yes, all right.
The file?
It's taking a minute to come up.
You looking
for something specific?
Maris Donovan.
Car accident victim,
16 years old.
Two years ago.
Was there anything to suggest that she was alive
for even a few minutes at the scene of the car accident?
I don't recall.
However...
different monitor,
different equipment.
I have a database
of CT scans...
and I'm quite sure I have one
for Maris Donovan.
Yeah, it's coming back
to me now.
I believe I noted that the bruises here
were inconsistent with the accident injuries.
But...
because they are red
in color, I can conclude
that they occurred
very close to death.
Placement on the body and the size
are consistent with compression marks?
Yes, someone could have
attempted CPR,
but they must have been there
right after impact,
because, based on these other injuries,
Maris Donovan didn't live very long
after the accident.
Karita Neville is a doctor.
She may be the one
who assisted the victim at the crime scene,
and your time line
just might put her in the car.
All right, autopsy report.
Strange.
Yours is the second request
for this particular case this week.
That rarely happens
for one this old.
Who made the first request?
Usually, it includes a name,
but this says "Confidential."
My father was in that accident.
And so were you,
Dr. Neville.
You switched places.
There was much more risk
for you to be behind the wheel than your father,
because eight years ago,
you were charged with a DWI.
With one more conviction,
you could face 15 years.
Detective, I'm going
to say this one last time.
I wasn't in that car.
Now, I have patients.
I'm in awe of your unwavering
commitment to the lie.
Can't imagine what it was like
to watch your father cuffed and later locked up,
knowing the whole time
that it should have been you.
15 months were added to his sentence
for being accused of texting while driving,
only he was texting
from the passenger seat.
I'm just curious.
Was there a moment
that you ever felt guilty?
The debt has been paid.
No, Dr. Neville.
No debt is paid when
the wrong person is convicted.
I don't want you
to forget my name.
You're going
to be seeing me again.
Mrs. Donovan, we believe
it was Karita Neville
who was behind the wheel of the
car that killed your daughter
and not her father
Talmadge Neville.
I'm sorry, I don't understand.
How do you explain this?
And why didn't
you know this then?
Well, I'd like to discuss the details
of our investigation, but I'm...
You're starting
a new investigation?
Yes, yes.
That's why I'm
here.
I wanted totell you personally.
-It's been two years.
That man spent
18 months in prison.
I know that none of this
is easy to hear,
and revisiting what happened
all over again...
I won't do it.
I can't do it, Detective.
I'm still waiting for the morning when
I no longer believe I hear Maris
singing in the shower
down the hall.
Well, thanks for
the information.
I would prefer that you involve me
as little as possible.
I'm sorry to rush you out,
but I have a meeting.
Of course.
Flack, see if you can
track down Neville.
I think he'd be interested
in what we know.
Talmadge Neville, NYPD! go ahead.
-We're clear.ead.
We're clear over here.
Hey.
Hey, how's Lindsay?
7 hours counting.
She dilated past
one centimeter yet?
That's kind of a
personal question, Adam.
Oh, sorry.
I-I just have 18 hours and 15 minutes in the
hours of labor office pool.
600 bucks on the line, yo.
What's up with the bike pedal?
Flack found it
at Neville's apartment.
What was strange, though,
is that
it was wrapped in copies of
Maris Donovan's autopsy report,
and it was painted
completely white.
Analysis of the paint
says it's pretty heavy duty.
Yeah, it's something you would use to paint
the exterior of a house.
There's a void on the spindle threads.
Suggests that it was still
attached when it was painted.
But if that's the case,
there should be some kind of
wear pattern from a shoe.
But there's barely a scratch.
Means nobody rode it.
You said that Flack found this
at Talmadge Neville's apartment?
Yep.
Just the pedal, no bike.
Ghost riders.
Follow me.
Those bikes are
all over the city.
They're in memory of people
who lost their lives in bike accidents.
They're called
ghost riders.
Somebody died in
a bike accident down there?
Yeah.
And I'd be willing to be that t pedal in our lab
is from a bike in memory of Maris Donovan.
Somebody didn't want
Talmadge Neville to forget
why hepent the last
18 months in prison.
You asked to see us,
and we're here, so...?
You know this guy?
What about him?
He should be lying in an alley right now
with a blet between his eyes.
Excuse me?
And how do you
know that?
You were gonna do him,
weren't you?
So what's your beef
with Talmadge Neville?
Let's just say I'm a guy
with a specific skill set.
And I got the constitution to commit acts
that other people don't have the courage to.
You're a hit man.
I'm not familiar with that term.
Sorry, contract killer.
Is that what you prefer to put on your business cards?
I'm not interested in playing games,
Mr. Desoto.
What are you doing here?
-My client had a change of heart.
-Who's your client?
An hour ago, I received word
that the new beneficiary of my services
is supposed to be this girl right here.
Something tells me your client wasn't
the only one that had a change of heart.
No women, no children.
A hit man with a code of ethics.
How noble.
Who hired you, Mr. Desoto?
Don't know her name.
How about a description?
Female, late 40s.
I had a meeting with her once.
She was wearing sunglasses
and a wig.
If you find her,
don't go asking me to come
pick her out of a lineup,
'cause I pretty mh got
"I don't recall" down pat.
Thank you.
You've done
the right thing here.
Hey, look, I didn't come in here
for a pat on the back, Detective.
This woman's desperate.
I get the feeling,
with or without me,
she's gonna get this done.
Just checked with
the hospital.
Karita Neville finished
her shift two hours ago.
I left a message with
the swering service.
We've tried her cell
and home phone,
haven't gotten an answer.
-Just keep calling.
Flack has uniforms
at Neville's apartment.
We checked in
with his parole officer,
and Neville never indicated
what he had planned for the day
except to say
he would look for a job.
He used to be a
street vendor.
See if he's tried to contact
any of those companies or Nick Donley about work.
Let's also try to contact
his cell mate at Rikers.
See if Neville mentioned
any special plans.
Mac, female prints I lifted
on the photo of Karita Neville
didn't get any hits
in AFIS so no ID.
But they were a match
to the prints
I found on the autopsy report
recovered in Neville's apartment.
Easy to put
two and two together.
Only this time,
it adds up to one.
Are Talmadge and Karita Neville
alive, Mrs. Donovan?
That's an odd
question to ask me.
Are they safe?
Those flowers are from a friend.
He was supposed
to do me a favor.
But he couldn't.
Turns out, I didn't
need it done anyway.
I know about grief,
Katherine.
About losing someone
you care about.
I lost everything
when I lost her.
Make sure to get brown
and white rice in the bag.
And don't stop for any junk
food, Maris.
I got it, Mom.
Okay. Be careful. I love you.
Mom, I'm just going
around the corner.
It's been two years.
It still hurts so badly!
I lost my wife on 9/11.
Some days...
it seems like it
was so long ago.
Others...
like it was just yesterday.
I wish I could promise
that you'd stop missing Maris,
hearing her voice or imagining
she'll be there
when you get home, but...
I can't.
I'm so ashamed that I let
this consume me.
I'm so afraid that if I stop
thinking about it,
it'll be like I forgot her.
But you came here
for another reason.
So what now,
Detective?
Compassion.
Grief is an emotion that
can force a good and decent person
to make a very, very bad decision.
And knowing that,
I have a choice to make.
I can do everything I can to prove that
you were involved
in a conspiracy to commit murder.
Right now, I have no witness,
no paper trail, no confession.
Or...
I can show a little compassion.
Are you sure I deserve that
courtesy, Detective?
I believe Maris' mother
deserves it.
However, I want
to be clear.
If you violate the law
in any way,
I will, without hesitation,
gather all the proof I need to prosecute you for this offense
to the full letter of the law,
you understand?
That, Katherine, I can promise.
Thank you.
Still no Talmadge
Neville.
I was about to report the same thing
about his daughter, but...
I'll tell you everything
you want to know.
I'll tell you the truth.
Your brother even whines
in his text messages.
He says, "It was not fair."
Is he crazy?
You tell him I don't care
how much more money I make. He owes me.
He lost that Super Bowl bet.
-K, you good?
-Yeah, I think so.
We gotta get out of the car.
Dad, there's a girl in the street.
I think she's hurt.
Come on. Get out. Get out.
Come on. Get out of here.
Get out of here.
You gotta leave.
Oh, but Dad, she's hurt.
This is an accident that can
ruin everything you worked for!
Get out of here!
Get out of here now!
Go, go, go, now, now!
No, no! I-I can't, I can't tell
if she's breathing!
I don't know if she's alive!
It was so stupid,
I know.
But I was just doing
what my father asked.
I was scared. We both were.
But you were at the scene
when we arrived.
I just couldn't leave her there.
Your instincts
as a doctor took over.
Yeah.
Somebody help!
So I returned as if I hadn't
been there at all.
And I offered my help before
the paramedics arrived.
Somebody call 911.
And my father and I
just pretended
we didn't know each other.
Why? Why lie?
Why trade places, Karita?
We had spent the evening at this reaurant celebrating
the end of my residency.
You'd had a couple of drinks?
One glass of wine.
I swear to you, I wasn't drunk.
My father would never
have let me drive.
Despite that,
he just couldn't take the chance.
He was afraid your prior DWI
would influence the judge
and ultimately your conviction.
So he claimed to be driving the car.
He didn't have much
faith in the truth.
I begged him for days after just
let me take responsibility for what I'd done.
But he said we were in too deep.
He still believes to this day
that it was the right thing to do.
"Greater good, Karita," he says.
Greater good!
Dano, Dano, how's Lindsay doing?
You gotta be kidding me.
Is that her I hear screaming
in the background?
Yeah, yeah, all right.
All right, daddy.
I'll talk to you later.
Take care, bud, bye.
Detective Flack?
Mr. Neville.
I understand you have something
that belongs to me,
and I was wondering
if I could get it back.
Need some help?
I thought I was rid of you.
I wanted to say
I'm sorry.
For what?
That I can't give you back those
18 months you spent in jail.
I would have done it again
all the same if I had to.
Your daughter means
the world to you.
Oh, yeah.
And I'm sure Ms. Donovan felt
that way about Maris.
Karita told us
everything.
What was it about the
truth that scared you?
The odds.
My daughter made
a mistake.
DWI. One mistake.
No question she was wrong,
but sometimes
we're not too forgiving.
You can't tell me
that taking responsibility for that accident
wouldn't have changed things for her.
I wanted to preserve
what I had worked for all those years.
I wanted her to succeed.
And she's doing it.
Only one regret...
That this little girl lost
her life that night.
So what happens to Karita now?
It was an accident, Neville.
Now that we know
what really happened,
no DA with an ounce of common
sense will prosecute that case.
Greater good.
That's okay.
You're doing great.
-You can do it, baby. Good!
-Breath breathe.
-Good!
-There we go!
There we go!
-Come on. Come on. You're doing great.
You're doing great!
-Good job, Lindsay.
Good job.
keep it up.
Keep it up!
-Hey, that's it, baby!
That's it, sweetheart!
Go ahead! Come on!
-Breathe.
-Come on! Push one more. Push!
Here we go!
Come on!
-Good job, good job.
-There she is! There she is!
Way to push, Lindsay.
There she is!
Keep it going. Come on.
She's beautiful.
Here we go...
Oh, babe...
All right, you did it.
You did it.
Oh, hello.
Oh, hello, sweetheart.
Ah... Hi. Hello.
Oh, Danny,
I hate to admit it,
but she looks just
like you.
Yes, that's right,
she's a knockout.
How you holding up?
I'm great.
But she's gonna be an only child
'cause I am never doing that again.
Do you guys have a name?
-Lydia.
-Lucy.
Guess that's a no.
Mac, we did agree
on one thing.
We were hoping that you would
consider being the godfather.
Absolutely, yes.
Made him an offer
he can't refuse.
You know, "Godfather," that's
code word for diaper change,
you know that?
Whoa, whoa.
Do I get to spoil her?
I think Danny's got that
covered.
Oh, we forgot
about the oohs and ahs.
Okay, yes, yes,
ready, everybody?
And...
That's nice.
So cute.
破烂熊字幕组
-==http://www.ragbear.com==-
欢迎加入