Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
A hippie is someone who seems Tarzan,
runs as Jane and smells like Cheetah.
Put your right hand on your other arm.
Are you ready?
I swear allegiance to the flag
of the United States of America
Cries of pain.
Soldiers signed for life.
The devastation.
Maybe we become accustomed
to wars in which films are shown.
But here is the reality show, and
since you do not hear victory music.
There are no heroes. This is the reality
and we see only people suffering.
These wars are neither glamoureus,
nor romantic.
They are only memories,
the brutality of man.
And let there be no doubt about that,
that this war and perhaps all wars,
absolute "evil" represented.
Northern California 1967
I will give you half,
so you r still have tomorrow.
When my today's opinion
Governor Reagan asked ...
... 's proposal for the extension
's national park.
Was his answer, and I quote:
"A tree is just a tree."
"And there are enough trees."
Other news are ...
Hello?
I'm coming.
Come on son, we must leave.
What's going on, Burke?
They keep coming back.
How can we work?
Visit them go.
You heard him. Restart your machine.
You know why we fell trees?
In order to build houses.
For families. That I may not care.
My wife is sick. She needed medication.
And if they do not get, it will die.
You make it all possible
to be fair to earn his bread.
If your wife should die,
to save trees ...
... then is it so.
You ...
And who will you save?
Bastard!
Is everything okay?
If everyone wants to come to rest.
Give it here.
He has distributed the first battle.
He started it.
Can a man not even carry his job?
I got you caught in the act.
Everything is good, boy.
We stay here until we petition
to save these trees.
And where is that petition?
Paper, you idiot.
This is made of trees.
Not trees,
but 't body of Christ.
I kill you all.
I swear 't.
Papa!
Translation & Sync by DrakeDCX
www.ondertitel.com
Rome louder delicacy.
Should you not in the way 't mind?
No.
I will be driving.
The drugs keep Joey sharp.
Not, dude?
Thanks, but I have nothing.
Sam.
See that nest at the top of the tree?
Yes.
That 's nest' s American bald eagle.
I would not disturb you, but I want a pee break.
Me too.
Please, 't toilet of the bus.
This bowl is leaking.
With a little practice will 't you get it.
Joey, beware.
What was that?
I think that 't' n dog was.
Do you? I hate dogs.
Who hates dogs now?
He is likely to walk.
The girl toilet is on the right
big boy.
Chuck, come with me.
Sorry, I am also afraid of dogs.
You're such a chicken.
Someone is your 's buzz.
What?
Your cellphone rings. Who is it?
Nobody.
Is everything okay?
Yes, I think it does.
While Jimmy is not in my area.
You will love this trip.
Beware of traps.
Beware of what?
Traps.
What ... where?
What fall ...
I am concerned.
I am so clumsy.
There should be no glass still in it.
Who the hell were those guys?
I do not know, but we
be careful.
If these guys we get,
they cut our balls off ...
... and they use it as fertilizer
for their crocodiles.
Sounds like the perfect place
to a music festival there.
Jesus Christ, Samantha.
- That was not my intention.
It hurts.
I can 't stitch, if you want?
What?
I have a needle and thread.
I warm it up.
So it is sterile.
- No, thanks.
Let him do sissy.
Otherwise it will ignite.
- That is disgusting.
Don 't.
- I'm okay.
On his Rambo's.
The wound is too deep.
We must 't disinfection.
Give me the whiskey again.
Rambo!
Do it!
I'm Rambo.
I'm Rambo!
I can 't respect. I feel dizzy.
Value countrymen, many battles
are at end of the war in Iraq ...
He is not only
the best American president ever.
He is just ...
That will be a scar be.
Thanks, I get some medicine.
Who wants high?
What is wrong with her?
Like them a trauma has occurred.
Sam?
Yes.
She 's currently difficult.
- How are you?
Did Ivan 't you not told?
- No.
She was not always so shy.
She has had a bad relationship.
You are very much for your height.
My ex-boyfriend ...
... loved SM.
Also Ossy?
That liquid stuff
that we put our tongue ...
That was no toothpaste.
Jimmy was her last boyfriend.
A rich, spoiled kid
that it hated to be dumped.
He was accustomed to receive his sentence.
Samantha.
What are you doing here, Jimmy?
Jimmy, please.
Got t verkloot?
- I do not know.
Have you given her drugs?
Fuck you, Jimmy!
- You give me no orders, pig.
Show her a little respect.
- She has only a bad influence on you.
Fuck you, motherfucker!
- Why are you so angry?
Why am I evil?
Sammy was just a dagreis made ...
... and when Jimmy found out,
lost his pedals.
I had asked you to stay here ...
... and you did not.
I don 't understand.
I love you, damn.
I love you, Samantha.
You make yourself ridiculous.
Help us!
Everything you break, you buy.
Jodie Foster acted great in that movie.
Not Jodie Foster, but "The Blair"
played with in "The Exorcist".
Yes, with that priest and the demon possessed
was played by Reagan.
But it was not President Reagan.
I understand why you all wrong.
Beer.
Boose not everything.
Where is Sam?
In the shop.
- Get her out.
You heard him. Boose not everything.
Sam?
Calm down, slokop.
These are the guys.
Let's go.
- You are in a bad mood.
Those guys from that truck are just stopped.
What?
- The guys who threw that bottle.
What is your problem, dude?
Sit her down something in your vagina?
Yes, the dick your mother.
What does that mean now?
- I do not know.
Five's like coffee.
I want those guys murder.
- I would not do.
Why not. We are in the majority.
I am not a fighter, and they may have weapons.
That's the bastard
that my bottle has absorbed.
Pussy.
- I'm like a sissy.
Let's just leave.
Hey, motherfuckers, you find problems?
Because my friend asked 't away.
Are you big, lean kid?
- Will he fight?
Thanks for your help, Johny.
No problem.
I call a religious war on him.
Ivan.
What is wrong?
Tell them that we have no problems.
- But your boyfriend wants it.
What did you expect.
You have my head hurt.
I thought you were peace-loving hippies.
Friendship make no war.
Turn around and go out,
I hurt for you to do.
Stupid bastards, come on.
- As you wish.
Not "t knife, Muff.
Let's make some vegetarian burgers.
Come on, baby.
Never mind what to see.
Stay away from me!
Thank you, sir.
Hello?
Samantha?
I know that you are.
Say something.
I can not believe
you holding me.
Bitch you are.
Gus?
Damn, Gus, rep your ass inside.
And continue with your work.
I love violence.
Damn, I knew she 's aunt was hard.
He did not know what happened to him.
Who?
- Just Mr. T, Rocky.
Winnie the Pooh.
I never knew you had so much guts.
Why have I brought you,
because you know absolutely nothing.
Because I have good uitzie.
Gentlemen! There is a saying.
Rome was not built in a day.
But I have a saying.
Fuck you, Rome.
This is America!
We do what we sense in it.
So you need not have worried.
We will track here on Monday.
And your forest will remain untouched.
Mr. Baker, you have a great crew with him.
Call me Frank, please.
We have only ...
... a few concerns.
In connection with ...
- What? Admission tickets, revenues, ... ?
Fatalities.
There are a few spectators died,
last year.
I do not think we have met each other.
May I introduce you to agent Buzz Hall,
Mr. Baker.
Peace on the supervisors of the city.
Supervisors?
We do not have much money
to security spending.
Then you really do
the best agent in town.
Yes, he and his partner Cooper.
And there is also a large team of foresters
that regulate movement.
Fantastic.
But there are a few formalities,
not Buzz?
If I remember correctly.
Is there someone vertrappeld last year,
when my baseline could not reach.
Tragic.
But I have this year increased security.
They took care of last year still
for security.
But you are here this year,
to a loop in it to sail.
If supervisors, of course.
And what she regards ...
Which girl?
The girl who disappeared without trace.
You know how many young people in a night
even "The Grateful Dead" singer have been followed?
Jerry is dead.
What?
Jerry Garcia is dead.
"The Grateful Dead" singer her anymore.
Perhaps it is her
any rocker here?
Maybe she is "The Fish" went after.
Yes, "The Fish" are also split.
Hopefully, young people not only
come before him.
You are here to save the furniture,
not Frank?
Buzz, there is still work.
How are you doing, Buzz.
Not bad.
I know t.
And also that you are extra tough
the security of this festival
Extra tough?
What you see there?
I won 't even tell you.
I see jobs.
And that is what this timber town needs.
Maybe not.
Buzz.
Can I be assured that everything
will do to this town to help.
You can be assured
I will exercise my job.
As I always exercise my job.
'S mustache' s requirement that the job is,
Buzz?
Welcome to "t" Free Love Festival ", where the
best groups to come to America.
Freedom?
- Yes, the freedom to use drugs.
Now we 're talking about it ...
We have cocaine, speed, purple hydrobag ...
And a few pills that Jay
my mother has stolen.
And what have we here ...
... even a half sheet of "smilies".
- Is that all?
Is sometimes not enough?
We are experienced drug swallower, Samantha.
- Yes, you should not try this at home.
Sam, do not worry.
It is not just about drugs.
"Free Love Festival" is a great concert ..
... where peace loving people
meet ...
... to the bad things
of the Government to discuss.
It is fun.
- What are you talking about?
She is talking about Bush and the war in Iraq.
And that Bush dicks of his generals afzuigd.
Thanks for the explanation.
- Shut up, Bush is super.
At least that guy has guts.
He is the first president
who do not care about ...
... what the world thinks about his decisions.
They will not stop him.
George Bush is the worst president
this country has ever had.
You say that just because Bush hates blacks.
Make that the cat would.
What's that sound?
What was that?
There is a tree on the road.
Do you get out!
You are not welcome.
This is the last time
I warn you hippies.
Joey, stay here.
- That's the woodcutter in the newspaper.
Everybody stay calm.
Dylan Riggs, Jesus.
I stay calm. Do not worry.
- Stay there, please.
This maniac was trying to murder us.
Dylan, what the hell is your problem?
You had these children may shatter.
I have no problem.
But the hippies ...
It is the forest not, damn it!
It is also not yours.
I can arrest you for this, fool.
This tree is marked by the forester,
because he is infected by beetles.
And I'm engaged to him to decide.
And that had to happen today, eh?
Remove the tree here,
or should I arrest you?
Is anyone hurt?
Everything is fine, but go to him
just let go?
What kind of a policy shall be exercised?
I care for the safety, boy.
I wouldn 't appreciate if you
would show more respect ...
... for those who live here
and those who visit here.
Sir, do you want me a trouser suit for the show?
My father has never done
and I urgently needed some discipline.
Do you think this a joke?
Each year, four or five young people.
Youth against a tree to drive ...
... or they paralyze themselves
by nitrous oxide gases ...
... or they blow themselves during 't cook.
If you feel invincible to be ...
You are not.
Sorry that I have your job more difficult ...
... but can you tell me to
the nearest police car guide.
We will see if you
can dance without legs.
Why not leave you.
Or should I even search your van?
Would you like that?
Local problem?
Nothing for you to worry about it.
Prepare yourself but for Mr. Baker.
I will.
Mayor.
- Call me Hal.
This is a beautiful pin.
Can I also get one?
That you deserve, Frank.
It is a interesting weekend.
That water felt good on.
Water is wonderful.
I go a couple picking mushrooms.
You coming?
No, I go a little rest.
I will not stay away long.
Hello, mister rabbit.
Come here, knulletje.
Mr. Rabbit.
Come here.
What place is this?
It was formerly a timber company.
Until such radical hippies' t opbliezen.
When they are holding to it were built ...
... there are 200 Chinese workers killed
when a gas bubble became.
And they have them in a mass grave burial.
On that spot.
Mr. Rabbit.
Come here, Mr. Rabbit.
I can not hurt.
Who's there?
Is that you, Mr. Rabbit?
Champignonnen.
Look, Ivan!
It is that old guy, Oronomy.
He has a pimped coat.
Very nice.
What is your means of transportation?
It was not our intention
to harass you.
I have no objection.
This is not my woods.
Are you a hippie who is hardened ...
... that the nature of all
and nobody 's possession?
Yes, if you would 't able to.
But I would be careful but in these forests.
You never know what you may encounter.
You mean something like Bigfoot?
No, he is not dangerous.
They are traps that you should beware.
I got it anyway you said.
I have knowledge.
It is true.
There are people here disappear.
What do you mean? Why?
It is because of the weed.
The local residents find it not nice
if someone comes to their stock.
Look at that!
Hello!
Come down.
We are amidst a orgy.
Bring beer with us!
- Dude, that are assholes.
Bastards!
- Take cover!
Give it back, dog!
What?
I had said to you still from the forest to continue.
Do not use all my coke, my friend.
- I was' t word.
You are always' t word.
I am glad that everyone along.
This is strange trip started
but we are much fun.
You know what I like to find?
If someone cannabis plantation
to find where this guy talking about it.
It is these moments that 'make life beautiful.
I am pleased that her coke is
I can not.
There is also speed and other shit,
your appetite away.
Yes, she is on a cocaine diet.
- Go fuck yourself.
If I could, I would fuck me every day drowsy.
- That you would want.
First, did you talk about, and now
do you want to cannabis fields go?
No problem
like a paracommando I 'r through.
All vehicles and slog through the ground.
Everything for the cause.
You want some?
- No, thanks.
It is good speed. You, Ivan?
- No, I have nothing.
I am more.
You've already had more than enough.
- You can never have enough.
Stay away from me.
If that is
I look up that cannabis plantation.
Go for it, cowboy.
Are you tired? Sleepy?
- No.
You may take a bit, if you wish.
I just want you.
I hope he is not drunk.
If everyone is drunk,
can something bad happen.
You have less worry, Sam.
You're just scared,
because of your previous relationship with Jimmy.
You do not have to be afraid.
Be still not afraid kitty.
Anyway, it is pretty good.
And I will behave.
Only a little weed, and a few beers.
Nothing more.
Okay?
- Really?
Yes, I promise 't.
I got a surprise for you.
I am so back.
Ivan.
These are but grains.
Do you have someone in the rain to see it?
Yes, it is full of crazy people here.
He said he immediately came back.
- How long has he lost?
Since yesterday.
- Excuse me.
Hold on.
If after the presentation is still
missing, we will find him.
My friend is in the forest lost
and he wants nothing to do.
Easy.
He is probably ...
... somewhere intoxication 't sleep.
You know what drugs might
he has taken?
Go to Monday
- How they called me?
Why would you not help?
She says that he is lost.
I don 't care. All she thinks
that Mickey Mouse a cat is real.
I am not in the forest looking to
a hippie flowers to pick is.
He is probably one of those tents
another girl to fuck.
What can I do for you?
I think I will gestalkt.
I am so back. I promise 't.
Buzz?
- Yes, what is it?
We have you on the north side
the river necessary.
It is not pretty.
Apparently, the beetles become involved.
That must have been large beetles.
I will be a report.
It looks like an accident.
- Do you?
This was not his intention, Cooper.
Watch your step.
Where is Joey?
Follow me.
Beer?
Does anyone know where I can get beer?
Nitrous oxide?
- Nitrous oxide.
Nitrous oxide.
Watch your step girl.
- Sorry.
Where are you going?
We have some drugs needed.
What on earth are you doing?
Mayor.
How you doin '?
You should not start flatter, Buzz.
You just half of the forest closed.
And why?
Because some nudist
itself suspended?
The body was maimed.
It may be a mountain lion or a bear have been.
Or perhaps was it Bigfoot?
Now you gonna listen to me.
There is a file of 3.2 km.
And they want to the site 's festival.
So here are your instructions.
They let you go,
you take care of the security ...
... and you go into it.
You want me to remove the roadblock?
Come on. Go to a man
diploma without listening?
You still have no qualifications?
Let the roadblock stand, Cooper.
And please the forester,
to anyone willing to admit.
Buzz.
Do you think that t. ..
Bigfoot ... would be?
Yes, if Bigfoot black sweets hold.
You look funny from up close.
And not otherwise?
You look always funny.
It is weird.
I start 't feel.
Samantha is crazy if she finds out.
It 's soft, like XTC.
She owns you.
- I don 't.
It is not fun.
They will find out.
Do not worry, honey.
She loves you.
Really?
Does she love me?
Joey?
Sorry.
Have you seen Joey somewhere?
Here he is not,
and we will still be a while.
You know the golden rule or not?
'S shuttle back and forth,
then there gevreeën.
Do I look high from?
Yes.
How do you feel?
I feel super.
- That 's all that counts.
Linda.
Samantha.
I know t.
Linda, I can speak?
- Of course, sweetie.
Amateur you are.
See you.
That is simply beautiful.
I got a black car seen ...
- Jimmy is not here.
Yes it is.
- No, he is not here.
You gotta relax, right?
Linda.
Come here. Let me show you something.
I wonder what that might be?
Wait for me.
We were not in the woods?
Good afternoon, officer. What can I do for you?
I would like to speak.
There are a few problems,
I want to speak with you.
Take me in your leg?
- No, sir.
On the north side of the river
is a hippy in a graduated trap.
And thus ended up
it upside down on a tree.
Do you know who this fall has sometimes put?
Got a search warrant, Buzz?
- No, but I can acquire one.
I always wanted to know
where you are dealing.
I do not think you understand it, Buzz.
I hate hippies who do not, because they
here each year 's concert.
I hate them because they have destroyed my life.
Their debt people think that a tree
worth more than a lifetime.
And my wife have been arrested ...
... and my son.
I don 't.
But now I have that problem with that dead hippie.
And I do not want more victims.
- I have killed nobody.
That claim I do not.
But it is better if I lock you
to 't concert is over.
It is for your own good.
Whether you show me where the rest
of which are located?
I will show you their location.
But I think you still
protect the wrong people.
The government has yet laws
which trade unions protect.
And troublemakers.
But they are always behind the little man.
The government is always looking for the best solution
for the majority of the population.
That depends on who leads the government.
You know ...
Ronny Reagan, may he rest in peace,
had a theory about candy.
He had a big bowl of sweets
on his coffee table.
He studied those who have names.
- Why?
He said you two types of people
can distinguish.
Those who seize every opportunity that arises,
without them there.
And all those plans.
Those who see all tactical.
Let Cooper site
of the other fall show, right?
And stay here this weekend.
It is for you to realize.
- Until later.
Cooper.
Are you there?
I'm here.
I want you to fall Dylan collect.
And keep a eye in 't sail.
He will not be the location
of all the traps out.
I address you.
I will address you again.
That I mean now.
- They were indeed delicious girls.
You are all afraid of a big tit.
- As' t your mother.
My mom has nice tits.
That you have to admit.
Indeed.
What do you think of a game:
"Bang the hippy thing".
Linda.
Where are you girl?
Come here, kitty.
Kitty.
Come on, Linda.
Joey?
Joey, I'm here!
Joey!
Joey?
This is not fun anymore.
We 've found cannabis field.
You just have a weapon of mass destruction
found.
Shut up.
- Keep you up but again.
What is it?
I'm bleeding, fucking.
It is paint.
They are paintball guns' t shoot.
Perhaps it is his dick 's suction.
- Let 's look.
Damn.
I paint my balls drop.
Where the hell are they?
- Not here.
Really 't, Sherlock.
Someone like a game play.
Play with the big, bad wolf.
I got you, slut!
Get that fool of me!
Come on, motherfucker!
Do you like it?
What the hell is your problem?
Come to daddy, girl.
I can not hurt.
I just want to talk.
Help me!
This is for Nancy.
Today's youth ...
... have nothing respect.
Nancy!
What are you doing?
Get here.
Drug addict.
Faster, gatlekker.
Busted.
Give me one.
I feel there is not much of.
Perhaps the dose was too small?
- Stop whining.
Take everything. It's good stuff.
And it is not quickly developed.
You get a delicious feeling of.
- I do not know.
Did we drink?
No.
Come on, man. Create a little fun.
Swallow it now.
Sam.
I'm glad to see you.
Where are Linda and Joey?
- I do not know.
Maybe somewhere a party to it build?
Come on.
Starts it raining?
I want everyone leaving this place.
This access should remain accessible,
and I want you to that direction.
Jesus Christ!
I immediately needed body bags
on site.
What are you waiting for, get admitted Friday
The party is over.
I want you to reach the highway again makes.
That is dangerous.
Please Extinguish that fire on your head.
Sorry for the disruption.
There is no light upon it wood.
And keep your clothes on.
What on earth are you doing?
I close it off festival, Frank Baker.
- Rot op.
I have two bodies found
here there is a killer around.
Thanks for the party, but
I must now exercise my job.
So grab your belongings and get the hell outta here.
Very funny.
Joy.
It was nice to have you here.
Come on, guys.
Vogelman.
The party is over.
Take that costume off.
Maybe you know it yet. But r
has tonight 's event played.
And I have all ordered
to this country to leave.
A few hours ago.
If you do not want to leave, I
the power to call for reinforcements.
To you with brute force away.
And there is also 's army at.
You will be arrested.
Go home. The party is over!
Leave now!
And do your clothes on.
This is no joke. If you
not leave, you will die.
The sheriff believes that a security problem
is. Let him but to send army.
From me he may even call the Navy.
Should I have her sometimes to remember that
we 's contract, Mayor.
It is the basis of American civilization.
- That 's the problem, Mr. Baker.
We have indeed a contract ...
... look what it means ...
... you have a presentation to ...
... and the cost
you owe us ...
... you will then have to pay.
Excuse me?
- That was not against you.
You look me busy.
Talk to you later, okay?
Where do you go to?
The party is over.
The party is not over.
Unpack everything and make
you at that stage is.
What?
There are many people come
for a concert to see.
And I do not disappoint, because
any agent that forbid us.
And what do you want us to sing, Frank?
"Taps"?
That I do not care ass.
All of you sing "Kumbaja.
Make so that you are on stage.
We have a contract to come.
By the grace of George Washington, do 't.
Understood?
They can not forbid us to sing.
God, the American people
't given right to rock.
Have you come to party?
- Yes!
This is the forest.
I love 'forest.
It is the forest of God.
Where is that damn cell phone.
I have talked with Melody. Everything is fine.
And what did he say?
He said that it would take hours
to the highway to reach.
And Joey, the keys,
and who knows where he is.
Him you do not 't seen circus car?
- No, not Linda.
We need them to look.
Forget t.
Not until this killer is walking around.
We can not just wait?
- Easy, baby, sooner or later he comes back.
No, I'm not calm. We must do something.
Why not try the XTC?
It is a must.
Sam, stay here with me.
I do not want to wait
and I would not be high.
I would just get out.
I can under any circumstance
be high. With pleasure.
And the guy said it was not party.
Not officially.
What are you talking about?
Some guys like 'forest go
and a drum circle forms.
We're still down here,
we can also further celebrations.
Are you crazy?
What is the problem of your girlfriend, dude?
- My problem?
Got it sometimes noted,
that there are people dying.
And where should we go, baby?
- Anywhere.
Without Joey and Linda? Come here.
Let's just stick together.
Everything is good.
And we will Joey and Linda
's party somewhere else.
What?
You are also high.
That is not true. I'm just ...
I'm just ...
Come on, baby. Where are you going?
Sam?
Come on, Sam.
Ivan!
The problem is ...
... that people have no respect
for the authorities.
I respect you, Buzz.
You've misunderstood me.
Old Riggs, the police have
always claimed that he was crazy.
I had not thought
that he would murder people.
He's a frightening bastard.
Hold on.
The coast is clear.
Some people now
once sweets, my friend.
Get him off me!
- You are in the way.
I get him off me.
Shoot him!
Nice work.
- Sorry.
Dylan Riggs!
Turn the saw off,
and put your hands in the air.
You are not my son from me decline.
You are arrested.
Is everything okay?
- Yes, go after him.
Hang on!
Ivan!
Jack! Jade!
Call "No".
No!
Sam.
Ivan!
Jack and Jade are ...
What happened to your friend, Samantha?
He seems pretty high, right?
Bastard!
- I thought hippies were peaceful?
I'm not exactly welcome.
- How could you?
I love you, Sam!
- I hate you! You're sick!
How can you say now?
- Let him go.
I will let you go, slut?
- You can 't do not.
You are going nowhere!
What you see in this motherfucker?
How do you prefer him over me?
- You are crazy.
Why him you killed my friends?
You are a monster.
What?
What are you talking about?
I have not touched your friends.
He has killed Jack and Jade.
What?
I have killed nobody.
Why should I murder someone?
Because you have a weapon!
What should I say?
I am a big fan of Charlton Heston.
I am a Republican.
Sam, get the hell outta here are.
Get outta here!
Here we go again.
Linda?
Joey?
Wil someone help me?
Help!
What was that?
Something where you are on high.
Ronny?
Large improvement in occupied institutes
prepared itself for the release ...
... of 1000 mentally handicapped patients.
Many of them had a violent past.
By a lack of capital strength,
this is the only solution.
Critics across the world condemned
Governor Reagan for this decision.
Because these patients
showed the least positive evolution.
The latter was impaired
released in January.
Jesus!
You are safe.
You're safe, nobody will hurt you.
You can not stop him.
It is Reagan.
Nobody will hurt you.
It is all okay.
Everything is good.
Buzz won 't get.
- Nobody will hurt you.
It is time that these hippies some money.
Or sometimes we work for nothing?
Nobody works for nothing.
Cooper, is everything okay?
- Yes, I'm okay.
Did you get him arrested?
- He is dead.
And he was not the perpetrator.
I got a ambulance is needed.
And contact the forester.
I wait for you at the campsite.
This is a manhunt.
Briggs And Gus is our prey.
Let him.
I thought they took him years ago
were imprisoned.
Apparently he has Reagan
and thousands of other maniacs released.
And we 're lucky that he has returned.
What do you think his purpose is?
Hippies.
Brave dogs!
Is everything all right, Buzz?
Cooper,
I am near Matilda's farm.
And everything is not fine.
Linda?
Linda.
Everything will be fine, honey.
I am so glad to see you. I missed you.
Can you grab me?
No pity.
See what happened when you
deals with the wrong people?
My daughters will never
become addicted to drugs.
You want your mother's heart
do not break?
Nancy? Dexter? Sit!
The morning breaks in America.
As each day.
Gus Briggs, don 't!
You call this compassion and conservatism,
boy?
Miss, is everything okay?
Are you hurt?
- No.
Cooper, still live?
- I'm still here.
I'll have to treat, cooper.
What did you say?
I got it.
- No.
Do not shoot!
- Do not shoot.
These are creatures of God. They are our friends.
Shoot.
There is a wounded girl to me,
apparently under the influence of drugs.
And a fatal victim.
Leave me alone.
Let my leg go, miss.
You have been my release.
Easy.
Give me the gun. What are you doing?
Jesus.
View this mess out.
Someone goes deep into his wallet
may affect.
Jesus, what a stench.
Goddamn.
Nitrous oxide Boy, give me the balloon here.
Get this outta here.
Is everything okay?
Have you ever 't "triple effect" heard
cooper?
No.
It's like a big crazy bastard is
and the whole world goes to the sharks.
Hold on.
Is everything okay?
Yes.
Well.
What is it?
We went to the crime scene has been ...
... and we have Gus's body not found.
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org