The following is based
on true events.
I swear by God this sacred oath:
I am unconditionally obedient,
to Adolf Hitler,
Führer of the German Empire
and its people,
Chief
of the armed forces.
I am ready any time,
as a good soldier,
My life for this oath.
The promises of the Führer about
peace and prosperity are destroyed
and left nothin but destruction.
The nastiness Hitler broughed with his SS
are a shame to the German army.
In the officers choir
there is widespread disgust,
about the bad things the Nazis did.
The killing of civilians,
The torture and starving
of prisoners.
The mass execution of Jews.
My job as an officer,
is no longer to save my country,
but to save lives.
I think no general with the courage,
to have to confront Hitler.
Von Stauffenberg, sir,
the General is coming.
Thank you I want him to speak
once he has arrived.
I was surrounded with people,
who wanted to see the truth.
Hiltler is not only the arch-enemy,
of the whole world,
but the arch-enemy of Germany.
This must change.
Colonel, my orders are to tear
to Sidi Mansour and we do.
The British are coming from the south
Patton and approaching from the coast,
know that we have two days.
- No, Colonel, we continue to fight.
Until the final victory.
That is a big lie
and you know too.
We can Germany,
or Füher, not both simultaneously.
With that kind of statements,
you are sent through colonel.
What I said was much worse.
General.
I try only to these men
live here to get.
What do you want me to do?
Do the headquarters to the proposal for a
other route, with the 1st Panzer unit.
Then we at least have a chance.
And from the reports will show
Sidi Mansour that you will achieve?
That I guarantee.
Let's see what it is.
General.
Sit.
Hitler departs quickly.
- Yes, the igniter.
Colonel Brandt.
A gift for Colonel Stieff.
Thank you,
so we do not get thirsty on the way.
He has landed.
With General Tresckow, give me operations,
Colonel Brandt.
Colonel, in Tresckow.
I am glad you are safely arrived.
I'm sorry you hard to be covered
but you got the wrong bottle
for Colonel Stief.
Did you pack yet?
No, but I is expected in Berlin,
I'll fetch you in the morning.
Sorry for the inconvenience colonel.
Yes, thank you
Do you think that he has it?
There is only one way,
to find out.
We detected.
- Why do you think?
Oster is arrested
the Gestapo came to retrieve him.
The Gestapo, he may for all
and some have been arrested.
What's wrong?
- No idea.
The ignition temperature,
know, that thing has not exploded.
General Tresckow,
for Colonel Brandt.
The colonel expects you, sir.
Rust.
Sorry General, I have the whole day
write reports on a raid.
A raid?
Dissidents.
- Another conspiracy against the Führer.
Who are these people?
You would be stunned.
Is this where you come?
Maybe we should make it open.
Pardon?
You have a long trip,
you must be thirsty.
I do not know what the Führer thinks,
of a soldier who drink during his service.
Colonel Brandt.
I had you otherwise assessed, General.
And I am
We are still in business.
Search for Replacement Oster.
Here you can trust no one,
not in Berlin.
Stop searching in Berlin.
Frau von Stauffenberg.
Maybe we can first
talk in my office.
I go to my husband.
His right hand,
is amputated above the wrist.
He lacks the fourth and fifth finger
of his left hand.
And the left eye,
we could not survive.
Colonel.
Are you ready, sir?
I am a soldier, I serve my country.
But this is my country.
I was there, while I bled to death
and thought,
if I die,
I let my children nothing after.
I must find another way,
to Germany to serve.
If I do,
I am a traitor,
I accept that.
Tell me,
these men see it as?
We need to reorganize,
rethink our strategy,
recruit new men.
We want you
What happens to my wife and children,
if these men not see?
Come listen
what they have to say.
You know where you can find us.
Enough. I do not listen anymore.
You had your chance and you failed.
Your solution, failed.
The only way now,
Hilter to directly confront.
This is a military operation.
It is not a military operation,
it is a political organization,
and what happened,
is that the military too much power.
We must still consider,
with some errors.
Mistakes?
How about a complete fiasco?
Gentlemen, we have the facts
face.
The allies will come sooner or later,
I say, let's wait
and let them deal with the Nazis.
And every living soul in Europe,
the price to pay? Use your head.
Carl, please.
- Ludwig Sorry, I love me too long silent.
We must now confront Hitler.
Forcing him to leave.
And then what?
Pardon?
If Hilter away.
Excuse me, who is this?
Colonel Stauffenberg,
is the replacement for Oster.
He was transferred to my office,
the Ministry of War.
How is your uncle?
- Well sir, he do for me.
He speaks with praise for you
- About you, General.
What Oster good organizer made,
that his opinion is held.
I ask simply, what you do
as Hitler away.
You do not believe that you Reichskanzelarei
can walk,
the military orders,
the war to end?
Yes, we believe it.
You were close to these men,
from Hitler's immediate vicinity.
We refused that, colonel.
The people know that our principles,
top private places.
We have respect for people
and the army.
Then you do not need.
Gentlemen.
They confuse respect,
in popularity.
They have sworn an oath,
forget that they just do not.
What will you do with Goebbels,
Himmler and the SS?
They will delete you.
- Stauffenberg.
We must now do something,
before we lose the war.
Otherwise, it always
Hitler's Germany remain.
We must show the world,
that we can not all be like him.
That is not enough for me.
There should be a chance of success.
Then find a way.
Papa is home.
I thought we would see each other
in Bamberg.
The children could not wait.
The children?
Valkyrie.
We have already considered,
it is not appropriate.
I know, but the Colonel has an idea,
that we have to take.
Sorry, what is Valkyrie?
- Operation Valkyrie.
The reserve army of thousands of men,
all over Berlin.
Valkyrie is Hitler's plan, they are
mobilized by a national catastrophe.
With the aim of his government to protect
cut or if he is slain.
And what have we there?
Valkyrie is designed
Civil unrest.
But what if the SS consult a coup?
The security service would overthrow Hitler,
how will the highest command respond?
We, the military emergency
should cry.
Just start and Valkyrie.
- Hitler's reserve army against Hitler's own plan.
We have no other option
than the power in Berlin,
to prevent
that the SS is in power.
They think Hilter for government to fight
instead of against it.
While we quietly
a new government installed.
But only if he is dead.
That mean you right?
How do you convince people,
that the SS would seize power?
We must kill Hitler.
- I'm disappointed in you, colonel.
I thought that someone of your background,
a more honorable approach would choose.
Your plan includes a few obstacles colonel.
Valkyrie should be rewritten,
the SS off.
And I need your help,
to copy it.
A warrant rewriting is one thing.
The spread is something else.
In this case we disseminate evidence
high treason.
Proof that Hitler's signature required.
We can all his signature.
How about the Fromm?
- Who is Fromm?
The commander of the reserve army.
I can troops in reserve to preparedness,
only Fromm, Valkyrie can start.
Can you approach him?
Our time is running out,
Fromm you approach?
He is a carrièreman.
But how far is he willing to go
with Hitler's army?
It is no secret,
that he is not happy with it.
Offers him a key position
in the new government.
Let him see the light.
Colonel Stauffenberg,
for General Fromm.
Colonel Stauffenberg, sir. Welcome back.
It is an honor, sir.
I send you to the front,
for you to give as Montgomery's whore.
The General will now receive.
What do you want?
I wish our new husband.
Colonel Stauffenberg.
Right, from Africa.
I would like to give you my hand,
but I might not get him back.
I would say that the General has important
Cases lost this morning.
It was time that someone
with balls placed in this office.
Please sit, Colonel.
And you too, Olbricht, and certainly should.
They say that you are critical about the war,
you seem to have good reasons.
I am critical
certain decisions, General.
In the field?
- In Berlin.
So why are you here to ...
to make decisions.
I have my decision already taken.
I'm here to help others,
in taking their decisions.
They say that if there is no clear option,
it is best to do nothing.
We have war, we must do something.
Sometimes rational.
What rational action
you are a colonel?
That would be a decision,
of a chief, sir.
The chief?
The two men behind the Chancellor.
If I was that man ...
would this war are very different.
That thought so too.
I need you not to remember
that we have taken oath to the Führer.
That said,
I will call not made to consider
that means that the types of calls,
never more will take place.
Is that clear?
Tell your friends colonel
I always choose the right side.
And as long as the Führer lives
you know where that is.
You realize,
Hitler how close I am?
I can keep them away.
My partners do not know that we talk
if you are afraid of.
If you get the SS,
you get them apart.
It would be a crime,
you know it.
I warn you,
Take no more contact.
When I first approached,
had you on your oath to keep.
Now you're just as guilty as me.
- And why am I a sympathizer?
Ask a man his fellow officers
and the Führer to betray,
and you believe that his actions
I will show its true?
If it is not easy.
- Yes it is.
For the last time,
compelling me to take a decision.
I have no choice.
Without you, there is no hope of success.
You are like rats,
which leave a sinking ship,
why do you think,
otherwise you will be?
Why do you
you are stronger than the people,
now, at this moment in history.
- This will continue an action is inevitable,
as the consequences.
If they get me, I will do everything
to hide me, hold not kid yourself,
you did to this crime,
long before you met me.
There is still time for something to do.
Only God can judge you.
Hitler designed operation Valkyrie,
within six hours of his government to secure.
I Rewrite the orders, so we
the government can take over in three hours.
The orders are distributed
on all 19 German military districts.
including occupied cities,
such as Paris, Vienna and Prague.
Here are the main sources
because all these districts,
strictly follow orders from Berlin.
If you take Berlin, please Germany.
I Rewrite so that the strongest units,
fully focus on Berlin.
We surround the government buildings,
manage the S.S. and gray shirts.
If the government hands,
Close all the concentration camps.
Officers who refuse
be arrested.
I am transferred to the front.
It does not matter.
You know this better than anyone recommend.
Therefore I give you,
the command of the operation.
Beck agrees.
- Why not Olbricht?
No, it is your plan.
You're it.
Make sure that no
conflicting orders are issued.
Hitler dead, is not enough.
You should isolate its command structure
and direct closure of the outside world.
It is thought.
I have the right man to help.
- Who is that?
Maybe I better not tell.
God promised to Abraham,
that he would not destroy Sodom,
when ten
righteous men could find.
I have the feeling,
that Germany is a need.
Let us begin.
The Führer, Adolf Hitler,
is dead.
Heil Hiltler, General.
Would you excuse us?
You play a good bureaucrat.
- I hope so.
You are encouraged,
to chief of staff of the reserve army.
Pardon?
- Congratulations.
I am with other issues.
Unfortunately, your action has not
the merit of the 'Reich'.
I refuse.
- You can not do.
Tresckow you exercise leadership made
but I am higher in rank,
you accept that promotion.
You'll have access to Hitler,
his advisers, his agenda.
We need him to.
I have your changes in Valkyrie views.
I agree.
You must be signed Hitler.
There is a man,
that is your job as assistant.
It is highly recommended.
Close the door.
Sit down.
Do you know how the world
to its end, Lieutenant?
This portrait is removed,
and that man will be prosecuted.
I love me busy with high treason,
with all the resources but are available.
Do you?
In all, sir. With anything.
Come children.
Colonel Brandt, operations.
Colonel Stauffenberg, I want your presentation
the Führer gladly take.
That is normal.
Sir, the contents of the folder
are only intended for the Führer eyes.
I am the eyes of the Führer, Lieutenant.
The colonel is my staff at the Ministry
of war, he is not among you
They wait.
Along here.
My Führer, I present Colonel Stauffenberg,
our new chief of staff of the reserve army.
My Führer.
It is an honor for an officer to meet
which so many sacrifices made for Germany.
Waren but my men like you
Leave him an example for you.
He is the epitome of a German officer.
My Führer ...
Colonel Stauffenberg will inform us,
the mobilization
of the reserve army,
to drive back the invasion.
Invasion?
In Normandy, my Führer.
Right.
Normandy.
That will not be necessary.
Reich Marshall Göring, assures me,
that everything is under control.
Thank you Colonel.
My Führer, if I may, I have a copy
of Operation Valkyrie, for approval.
You know your Wagner colonel?
The Valkyrie, the help of the gods.
Those who decide on who will live
and who will die.
The most heroic save,
a painful death.
One can not understand socialism,
if Wagner does not understand.
I am sure,
that your changes are good.
You can go.
Send your men to the front.
If a fresh team, yes?
I do not know and would not know
what you are doing.
But when the music stops,
I no cent for those without a seat.
Every problem on this planet,
can be solved,
with a proper application
of explosives.
The only thing not in the neighborhood are
if they go off.
2 slices 975 grams of plastic explosives,
enough to cripple a tank.
The inflammation.
British ball points.
This acid capsule is the igniter.
You put everything in focus by the igniter
the ball to confirm.
So.
Put the ball in the explosive.
Break the acid capsule
and he is on edge.
If the wire in the acid dissolves the igniter,
you better nearby.
For you
- How much time do we have?
Theoretically, about 30 minutes,
but given the heat,
Wolves in the gap you need to rely on,
10 up to 15 minutes.
That is not very accurate.
This is the latest, you can small
or accurate will not both.
Maybe a little too small.
Hitler bunker strengthened the explosion.
It reinforced concrete,
with steel doors and without windows.
The pressure built
by an explosion in such a space,
everyone will get killed.
The second charge is unnecessary.
What do we as Hitler
by a miracle survive?
That we still Valkyrie export.
At that moment, we can not go back.
But we have an advantage.
We have an insider.
After the explosion, he breaks
communication with the outside world.
While Hitler's confidants will
struggling with regrouping,
we have the time,
to the control to take over in Berlin.
Himmler is also expected
do not
unless you can address them both.
Do not unless you both,
both Hitler and Himmler can address.
This is Goerdeler work, huh?
I do not
if the decision is unanimous,
but I want an additional member of the team.
And no politician.
- Who?
Him.
Well.
But remember,
this is a military operation.
Everything goes according to plan.
We bring the children to Bamberg.
If I fail ...
Do they get you.
All of you.
I know.
Gentlemen, good morning.
Hitler has scheduled an emergency meeting,
today for an hour.
Stauffenberg begins when everyone is present.
- They are.
For the calk will Stauffenberg
call for authorization.
After the explosion, will his inside man
Disconnect all communication.
If Fromm does not participate,
Olbricht will command
the reserve army to take over
Valkyrie and launch.
That tells you all district commanders,
that the SS want to take power.
The reserve army will all SS, Gestapo,
and Nazi leaders arrested.
By that time, Stauffenberg returned to Berlin
and take over the reserve army.
Witzleben and I take the role of
supreme commander,
and on state.
With a secured Berlin Dr. Goerdeler,
the people speak as new Chancellor.
With God's help ... can we go on peace
negotiate with the Allies
and Europe,
prevent a complete destruction.
This identifies you as a member of the operation,
nobody is without inwards.
Gentlemen.
This is the most important day,
of your life.
We are fighting for Germany.
What is it?
- A command of General Olbricht.
The reserve army in preparedness come
in all districts, including Berlin.
It will be an exercise.
Send more.
Preparedness Action, why?
- It's not.
Let the men taking.
Please let this one exercise.
The men took
and waiting for orders.
This is rather strange.
HITLER'S shelter.
Station.
You may pass.
Your husband?
Now.
Colonel.
Attention.
Gentlemen, the first item.
General Fromm will present plans,
for moving troops,
of the reserve army,
to the Eastern front.
As you know, the Russians
Army Group North Ukraine attacked,
in Poland's southern sector.
General Harmel Model has replaced
an end to this confrontation.
Himmler was not there.
- I have three divisions,
Harmel troops to reinforce.
These divisions are,
to a mobile defense plan
and are not used,
at a certain fixed position.
Give me the ministry of war,
the office of General Olbricht.
General Olbrichts office.
- Himmler is not at the meeting,
I call for approval,
to continue.
A moment.
Stauffenberg said Himmler is not there,
he wants to continue.
Call Beck.
Himmler was not there.
They say no.
What do you think?
I say continue.
You are a little lost, Colonel.
I hope that it was important.
Colonel, your bag.
This was an exercise, Dismissed.
How dare you reserve army in preparedness
it, without that I know?
That cost me my commission.
In God's name,
why do you think you have that power?
It was just an exercise.
- Don 't lie to me.
We both know that it was not a drill.
- General, if I may ...
No, Colonel, you can do nothing.
You are not only incompetent,
you made me a target.
If I even feel,
that you have the reserve army to do
I arrest you both.
I have expressed myself clearly enough?
I did not hear you say, Colonel.
The need to replace Hitler,
the peace negotiations.
I had hoped that the Allies
were prepared to negotiate,
before them, damn, Berlin reach.
Hitler did not kill sentence
if you do not kill Himmler.
Why remove a crazy,
if we have a crazy back.
This has nothing to do with this
and that you know
This is a military operation
and not political, nothing more.
What you suggest?
- I suggest nothing.
I mention the facts as I see them.
You have the courage not to kill Hitler.
So make the mission impossible.
Nothing seems to murder you and your command
to stop
to hand to do.
- I wish that you would be right back again.
I think I am not alone
if I gave your review in question.
I suggest to vote.
I propose that we Colonel Stauffenberg
relieve of his duties.
Carl, I can even speak in private?
- If you just want to say, say it.
Okay.
I heard the chief of police,
Himmler that you want to arrest.
You should have left Germany last night.
If we are successful,
get back as Chancellor.
Disappearing Carl
and you avoid any contact.
Good luck, Colonel.
From now on,
Stauffenberg has all powers of attorney.
I can not approach the Allies,
if we do not continue.
I accomplish my task,
take Berlin.
I can now connect.
- Thank you
Excuse me sir, there were bombs
in Emmingen, we paused.
Emmingen is not in that environment.
I am sure that your family is safe.
Welcome colonel.
- Can I change something, Major?
Come on.
Make it the reserve army in preparedness
- Not before I'm called by Stauffenberg.
Not before I have security.
- That is ...
No Colonel, thank you
The meeting,
is delayed until 12:30.
Mussolini comes this afternoon by train.
The Füher want to wait.
Will Mussolini to the meeting, sir?
This was only true
than was an ambitious officer
the opportunity,
for that bastard to pop.
Sorry General. I expect a call
do you want me to get
even though I am in the Führer.
But of course, Colonel.
- Thank you sir.
Colonel.
With Major Freyend.
They want you to make.
The meeting begins.
- One moment, Major.
Two minutes, two for the welcome,
one for the checkpoint.
Time enough.
Sorry, Colonel.
Sir, the Führer is already in the meeting.
The dresses to Colonel, Major.
This is tricky, with his disability.
- Sure.
Time enough.
Get the car.
I have everything I need.
I wear it.
Where are they going?
- It is too hot,
they go to the conference room.
Majoor by my accident, I hear bad
I would like to stand close to the Führer.
I will see what I can do.
They come not only from the east,
but also from the North and South of France.
As you can see, my Führer,
the critical situation in the east,
as if the enemy continues.
The lack of resources,
weakened our units.
And the reserves are incomplete.
My Führer,
you know Colonel Stauffenberg yet?
As you know,
is the 10th Army in Poland displaced
and the 14th Division back.
Army Group Central is 28
lost 40 of their divisions,
that nearly 350,000 men.
Since the attack of the Red,
about a month ago
our troops back
to the Polish border.
Together with the loss,
of the 4th Army in Minsk ...
Yes sir.
... Army Group North of Ukraine,
as well as the Romanian army.
... further losses.
Unless we use new divisions,
along the border of the Reich.
Army Groups are enclosed by the enemy,
in less than 14 days.
We risk losing all profit site,
that the last three years we have made.
The General, he said that it was urgent.
Yes General, Stauffenberg.
Russian air activities
are as determined as the ground troops.
Some parts are flooded ...
... the Italian front, I go for ...
One thing is certain, the Red Army
pulls aggressive westward on.
Even at the expense ...
To regroup ...
... all southwest of Lüneburg
and approaching army group ...
It will be a catastrophe.
Step into.
Ride.
For the future, driving.
To work.
Enter the ministry of war,
General Olbricht, it's urgent.
With General Olbrichts office.
- There was an explosion ... General ... Führer.
Staak all communication.
- Sir?
Do it.
What did Fellgiebel?
- It was not clear.
Get him back on the line.
The bomb went off, that was clear.
Fell Giebel next step
is breaking all communication.
Sorry, Colonel, but nobody out.
- We have a command of the Führer.
We need to operations,
Do the gate open.
Excuse me sir. I recommend ...
- I just gave you an order, Sergeant.
Excuse me.
Colonel Stauffenberg,
for Field Marshal Keitel.
Colonel Stauffenberg was clear.
We start Valyrie, despite ...
We need Fromm.
- The Führer is dead, arrest him now.
He should recommend to Valkyrie to start
this is our only ...
I do nothing, before I got a confirmation
of Fellgiebel. Call him.
Every second of discussion,
is a second lost.
The risks are too great.
Stauffenberg and then
What about its risks?
He did his part
and now let him down.
Veldmaarschalk,
Stauffenberg in here, Sergeant ...
Kolbe, sir.
Kolbe will not let me through the fence.
Yes, I explained.
Maybe you want him out, sir.
Everything is fine sir, thank you
Open the gate.
Then the reserve army in preparedness.
- Only when Stauffenberg back,
and confirms that Hiltler dead.
Then we go through.
Where are you going?
- Wherever you go.
Lunch.
Another preparedness order.
Send by and give me a copy.
Here was an ancient Greek to be slain.
Lucky for you,
we have developed.
Gather the men.
What is wrong?
I see where our driver.
The Colonel and I are at the airport,
there is no car, no one.
The command is only just given?
This is Stauffenberg,
give me General Olbricht.
What is this?
Explain me this once?
- We did something, while h. ..
We do not know whether Hitler is still alive.
- This is Germany, not u.
Office of General Olbricht.
- Colonel Stauffenberg, for you
It's been three hours ago Olbricht,
where were you doing?
We have no confirmation,
Hiltlers of death.
I have seen the explosion itself.
We have carried out.
- Oh dear.
Where is Fromm, does he?
There was nobody with him.
Listen to me.
Think not to Germany or Europe.
Your life is at stake,
if you want to survive, do what I say.
Once you have suspended,
start from Valkyrie Fromm name.
Give him the chance to do
otherwise you arrest him, understand?
Be about 50 minutes Fromm office.
Call Beck and others,
tell them that the time has come.
Connect me with communications.
This is General Olbricht.
I call on behalf of General Fromm,
commander of the reserve army.
The Führer Adolf Hitler is dead.
Radical elements within the SS,
try the government to take over.
Start Operation Valkyrie.
Give the orders through.
Battalion.
Attention.
Our Führer, Adolf Hitler ...
is dead.
Who told you,
that the Führer is dead?
General Fellgiebel,
Wolves from the Gorge.
You do not call
all communication lines are dead.
Give me the Wolves Gorge.
Yes, this is General Fromm,
for Field Marshal Keitel, urgent.
I am sorry to disturb you,
but can you tell what is going on?
There are terrible rumors rotation.
- What do you mean?
They say that the Führer was murdered.
Another failed attempt.
The Führer has never been in danger.
By the way.
Where is your husband, Stauffenberg?
Stauffenberg?
On return to Berlin, I think.
Let us know when he has arrived.
I want him to speak.
The Führer is unharmed.
- That is a lie
Hitler is dead,
Operation Valkyrie runs.
Only I can start Valkyrie.
- That you have done.
This is treason.
At present, the reserve army
control over Berlin.
If you are with us or not?
- Do you know what you have done?
The Führer is alive.
I have placed the bomb.
I saw the explosion, he is dead.
If you join us?
- I believe this. Is this a kind of ...
If you are with us or not?
Colonel, if this is true.
- Should you shoot yourself now.
The rest is under arrest.
- We do not u.
I do not know whether you know
which should lead.
Give me operations.
With Colonel Stauffenberg
leader of Operation Valkyrie.
Nobody goes in or out,
without command of General Olbricht.
Geral Beck.
You carry your uniform not, sir.
We need to see us,
as movement from the people.
Colonel Stauffenberg.
The chef has the full cooperation
the police of Berlin guaranteed.
My people, you will not suffer,
you have my word.
Thank you
Colonel Stauffenberg,
We report our service.
Thank you for coming.
Gentlemen.
About three hours we have the confirmation,
that we in government hands.
And SS command center is removed.
You know what needs to be done.
Tonight, the Hitler's Germany,
seen his last sunrise.
Yes sir, everybody is replaced.
In fact, everything is already commander.
He is correct participant
just think back to that party.
I get it, but this is an emergency.
- Can I's 11th district ...
I need a decision, Major.
- This is not revenge, for ...
Can I have your highest officer in Hanover ...
- To set up another government form.
Be careful with who
you say, loyalty is now different.
Yes, Paris, France.
It also said the Führer.
Thank you, you took the right decision.
District 13 of us.
I arrest you in command of the Field,
for crimes against the state.
This is Colonel Stauffenberg,
I want General Todt speak.
I spoke with battalion 134,
no difficulty in reporting.
Colonel Stauffenberg, will explain everything.
Excellent.
For my wife, she is in Bamberg,
with the children, would you call them?
Thank you
The General has declared
that the orders at the headquarters are.
Check every 20 minutes the radio,
until we have a confirmation.
With respect sir,
but you can not believe everything.
That's SS propaganda, he is dead.
- The whole army awaiting orders.
General.
The army, the communications centers
in their power.
They repeat the message.
He participates.
Call Postner, tell him that he
units under our management places.
We must find a way,
to control.
We have the government center
under control.
Berlin we have not.
What is it now sergeant?
- An arrest warrant.
A command of Colonel Stauffenberg,
of the Ministry of War
to Reich Minister Goebbels to arrest.
The other comes from the Wolf Gap,
to Colonel Stauffenberg arrested.
Send them both on.
We do not recommend to assess
we send them on.
That's all sergeant.
New arrest warrants sir.
For Stauffenberg and Goebbels,
them both arrested.
I would not like that,
to discover that I was abused.
Do you really think a coup is?
I'm afraid so.
I do not know,
which side we are.
Come on.
I just spoke with the colonel,
they have 1200 SS and Gestapo officers
in Paris were arrested.
Without one shot.
The first reports from Vienna and Poland,
look good.
I am ready to be connected.
Minister Goebbels?
What can I do for you, Major?
My battalion has a warrant,
your ministry to be filled and you arrested.
Are you a dedicated
national socialist, Major?
With Major Remer.
Hopefully you recognize my voice.
Yes sir.
- Then listen to me.
I want to live traitors in charge.
- Yes, my Führer.
You heard what he said.
The Führer wants to live traitors address.
Yes sir.
It is a coup.
We can no longer remain neutral.
You must decide.
If it is, we know
whether we have chosen the right direction.
Send all communication
Wolves of the gap by
stop all communication with Stauffenberg.
Let these men Friday
But why?
We now have orders Hiltler itself.
We were misled.
We lost contact with District 11.
The circuit panel is overloaded,
try again later.
Give me Fellgiebel General.
We still have ...
- Keep trying.
Where is General Fromm?
I command
not General Fromm.
What are you doing here? What happens here?
- The Führer is dead.
The SS was a coup to make,
Operation Valkyrie then,
to stop the riot.
To Hitler's government to protect.
You keep the command of your troops.
I do nothing,
until I have spoken with General Fromm.
You follow the orders on
or you are arrested.
This is treason.
Since I do not participate.
The Führer is not dead.
Listen to me,
you make a terrible mistake.
The Führer is not dead.
Try my wife
again achieved.
I can reach anyone.
Look what is happening.
Yes with Stauffenberg,
General would return your call.
I assume,
that everything in your district under control.
The General wants me to wait?
I recommend him to the phone to get.
You need the oath,
a liar, Hans ...
Hans, listen.
This operation is aborted.
Today was an attack
the Führer committed.
The Führer is not seriously injured ...
And he immediately picked up his work again.
Were seriously injured ...
Send this to all commanders.
"Broadcasting is incorrect, Führer is dead."
Operation Valkyrie run.
I saw the explosion.
Today was an attack,
on the life of the Führer.
The Führer is not seriously injured ...
What happens.
- I do not want to be caught.
Excuse me.
Go.
It is good, go ahead.
General, sir, you have here.
Stop.
- Reverse.
I said stop.
- I said back.
Stop shooting.
Colonel Stauffenberg.
You are under arrest,
by order of the Führer.
If you have something like, to your wives
and children, I am now happy.
Okay, the war,
represented by me,
in the absence of the Führer,
will pronounce the verdict.
Beck, you are under arrest.
Colonel Mertz von Quirnheim,
General Olbricht, Lieutenant Haeften
and the colonel, whose name I do not call,
to death.
General, according to my orders,
I have these guys live ...
No Major.
I would like a gun,
for personal reasons.
Continue.
- With all due respect sir ...
That was all, Major.
By us to kill
hide not your concern.
My involvement? What are you talking about?
You knew it. And did not.
- You are as guilty as we do.
Hold still lieutenant.
- No one is spared.
I think of times of yesteryear.
This is a disgrace.
This has never occurred
the Field Marshal and General
declare him dead,
him, the Füher all of us.
And you protest when I say this?
My German countrymen,
I speak to you, because of two things.
First, I want you to hear my voice,
so you know that I am unharmed.
Second:
I want to inform you about a crime,
which is unprecedented in German history.
A small group of malignant officers
stretched together in order to eliminate me.
Apart from a few bruises
and burns,
I was totally unharmed.
I see the hand of Providence,
I encourage,
to accomplish my work.
Look them in the eyes.
They will continue to remind you.
We must show the world,
Lest anyone forget us.
Fire.
The people will know
that our principles, our lives.
Targeting.
Halt. Stand still.
You can now send to the executioner,
but within three months
be honest people,
please leave
and you will live to the scaffold drag.
- Feed him away.
Men ready.
Targeting.
Fire.
The plan of June 20,
was the last of 15 known attempts
Germans,
for Adolf Hitler to murder.
Nine months later, Hitler committed,
surrounded in a Berlin, suicide.
Nina von Stauffenberg, and her children,
survived the war.
She died on April 2, 2006.
You could not shame,
you resisted.
you gave your life for freedom,
justice and honor.
From the memorial,
of the German Resistance, Berlin.