[ Birds chirping ]
[ Children shouting, laughing
in distance ]
[ Sighs ]
Come on.
Let's bring it in.
FREDDlE: Let's go, Blue Jays.
Everyone to third base!
Hustle up, guys.
Come on.
FREDDlE: Third base. Come on.
Thanks, people.
All right.
Gather around, boys and girls.
FREDDlE: Give Calvin
your undivided attention.
This is infield fundamentals.
FREDDlE:
Right there, Terry.
Back straight, butt down,
toes planted.
FREDDlE: Okay, Cal, watch
your lips. Here they come.
Soft, agile hands out front,
guys,
like you're fielding an egg.
There's no flinching.
A bloody lip will heal, but a
fielding error is irreparable.
Arms are fully extended
out here. Club head out.
Your right knee
should almost scrape the dirt.
Show me. Go ahead.
-[ Grunts ]
-Nice!
All right.
Come on, people.
Let's see some endurance.
The high knees!
Come on, lan.
High knees.
GlRL:
Have him sign a ball.
BOY:
Can l have one?
Thanks for giving back to the
kids again this season, Cal.
Oh, it's no worries, Freddie.
You know l love coming out here
with you guys.
Can l get an autograph, too?
SUSlE:
Coach Fred?
Can l have your autograph?
Sure, Susie.
How'd you get so good, Calvin?
Just gettin' my game on
at the crack of dawn, lan.
[ Alarm sounds ]
[ Grunts ]
[ lndistinct conversations ]
First base line!
Let's go, pantywaists!
Move it! Move it!
[ lndistinct conversations ]
All right. Shut up!
Gentlemen, in three days,
most of you will be cut
and humiliated.
Coach Dewey and l look forward
to supervising your weak-willed
attempt at this beautiful game.
Okay, this is your chance
to show us what you got,
so don't fuck it up!
Only 25 of you pip-squeaks
can become Bisons.
The rest of you might as well
quit, take up --
Coach, help me out.
-Badminton.
DEWEY:
Landscaping.
Any questions?
[ Whistle blows ]
l'll let this one slide.
When you hear that,
it means run!
[ Whistle blows rapidly ]
MAN:
Lead with those hands!
Yeah! Nice.
DEWEY:
Oh, no.
ls that...
Calvin Marshall?
Yeah.
Just cut him now
and get it over with.
Oh, not yet.
MAN:
Heads up! Oh!
[ Laughter ]
How about now?
LlTTLE:
Marshall!
What?
[ Grunts ]
You couldn't hit a bull
in the ass with a shovel.
What's wrong with you?
You look like shit!
My wrist is killing me today.
Just keeps acting up.
l'll be fine.
His wrist.
CALVlN: Easy stroke. Come on.
Bring it to me.
This is about bat control.
Hitting is not swinging
from your ass.
None of you
are fucking Mark McGwire.
You're scrawny, weak,
and unremarkable.
Caselli, get on the mound.
Heat it up.
Right now?
No, uh, next Tuesday.
Yeah, now! Go!
Don't ever lollygag on my field!
All right.
One at a time in the cage.
Move your asses!
Go.
MAN:
Nice. Nice rhythm.
[ Bat cracks ]
Yeah.
Let's see it.
Come on.
Let me get in the box, man.
Easy, Caselli.
Lighten up.
Ugh!
Nice, Marshall.
-CALVlN: [ Grunts ]
-[ Baseball hits fence ]
That it?
All right.
Asses and elbows!
MAN: Come on, man.
Yeah.
All right. That's it.
Go home.
Oh, hey.
lf your name
is not on the board,
do not show up
to tomorrow's session
or l will not hesitate
to drop-kick you off my field.
Oh, hey, Coach.
Hey, Cal.
Oh, l can lock up.
l...need to work through
a few bugs in my swing, so...
Uh, all right.
-l got keys.
-That's right.
l'll take care of your lights,
too.
Okay.
Man, Caselli's got a cannon,
huh?
Yeah, he does.
Yeah.
Hopefully he pulls his head
out of his ass.
Yeah.
We'll see, right?
Well, see ya, Coach.
All right.
See ya, Cal.
[ Door opens ]
[ Footsteps approaching ]
CALVlN:
[ Laughing ] Yes!
Oh!
[ Clang ]
Yeah!
Yes.
[ Dog barking in distance ]
[ Music playing inside ]
That's weird.
[ Door rattles ]
ERNlE:
Just a second!
Coming.
Just a second.
Hey, Cal.
Hey, Ernie.
What's going on?
Nothing, man.
Just watching TV.
What is it, man?
[ Laughing ]
Let me in.
ERNlE:
Cal's here.
Yeah, we were just kicking back,
watching "The X-Files."
JUNE:
That was a late one.
Just out practicing.
ERNlE: Actually,
really good episode tonight.
[ Chuckles ]
Oh, no way.
Cal, l want you to always
think of me as your pal, okay?
You know, your first baseman
on the softball team?
Yeah.
And just because l'm in love
with this fabulous woman
does not make me
your step-uncle, okay?
l don't want you to ever
think of me like that.
He's right. l'm not
your legal guardian anymore.
l'm still your Aunt June.
That goes without saying.
But l think you should think
of us more as roommates.
Okay.
Well, no, don't worry about me.
l love you guys.
l totally support this.
JUNE:
l love you.
-You're my hero, buddy.
-Yeah.
l knew you'd understand.
You want a coldie?
No, no, l'm cool.
You know, l got to catch
some Z's anyways.
l got the last day of tryouts
tomorrow.
How's it going?
-lt's going good.
-JUNE: Yeah?
Just kicking the rust off,
you know?
JUNE:
Good.
Yeah.
Good night, guys.
ERNlE:
Good night, Cal.
LlTTLE: And boom!
Slams him down to the ground!
l remember that game.
Coach coldcocked
one of their players.
Now, that little pansy was
pulling my third baseman's hair,
and you just don't do that
in baseball.
l just had to clock him.
[ Laughter ]
l was at that game.
Hey, Skeeter,
get the box going.
Didn't see you come in.
Beer? Come on.
Whiskeys, Carramae.
Rocks.
CARRAMAE: How about
some Knob Creek, Little?
Aged nine years. Smooth.
100 proof.
Knob Creek? Come on.
lt's just Karen.
Just give me whatever swill
you got in the well.
Yeah. Right.
You son of a bitch.
Come on. Drink up.
Game started an hour ago.
Mnh-mnh.
Karen.
Come on.
Are you insane?
l love you.
[ Laughs ]
God, l love this game.
Yeah, l know you do.
Come on.
We just gonna sit here like this
all night or what?
Hey.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Slow down. Come on.
Give a girl a minute.
l got to get in the mood.
ls it always gonna be like this?
Like what?
l thought you liked it out here.
Yeah, but how about
your bedroom sometime?
And when am l gonna see
your stupid apartment?
Uh, it's a condo.
Well, l wouldn't know that,
would l?
Hey, this is who l am.
You don't like it,
you can clear out.
Hell, l got players
with more sense than you.
What the fuck, Karen?!
Hey! Karen!
Where are you going?
l was a little out of line.
l'm sorry.
KAREN:
You fucking weirdo!
All right.
l'll show you my condo.
[ Scoffs ]
All right, Meat.
Bring it.
-[ Click ]
-[ Grunts ]
Ain't got shit.
Double.
Ooh!
Triple.
[ Grunts ]
All right.
Error -- shortstop.
Oh, that's out of here.
SlMON: Have a great show, Cal.
Let's do it.
Seat belts, everyone.
CALVlN: Welcome to the season
premiere of "Bison Brigade."
l'm your host, Calvin Marshall.
l hope Bison sports fans
everywhere had a lovely summer.
We'll be running a looser ship
this year for sure,
but still an extremely exciting,
entertaining show.
lsn't that right, Simon?
Moving on to baseball.
Former minor leaguer Doug Little
has quickly become
one of the best young coaches
in junior-college history.
This year, Little inherits
a young ball club,
forcing him to lean on
sophomores J.J. Caselli,
Grant Murphy,
and new faces like
Pete Vanos, Rick Viczorek,
and yours truly,
Calvin Marshall.
l'll see everyone
down at the ballyard.
DEWEY: Marshall's name
is still on the board.
Why don't you let me be
the bad guy?
You obviously can't get it done.
How about this, Dewey?
How about you let me worry about
who's on the fucking ball club
and who's not?
You guys are pathetic!
You smell like the garbage bins
behind the Hillbilly!
And some of you have beer-face!
-[ Laughter ]
-Caselli?
l don't have beer-face, Coach.
You have jowls.
l can smell you from here!
How many beers did you have
last night?
God damn it!
Let's get one thing straight!
You idiots aren't here to party!
"Hey, Coach, can l have
a couple beers?"
"Yeah, sure."
l'm a big fan of the barley pop,
in moderation.
"Hey, Coach, can l drag a
couple babes up to Bison Ridge?"
"Yes, you can."
The flesh is a useful thing
to indulge in from time to time,
especially during a long season.
But the only reason you monkeys
exist is to play baseball!
Now, some of you are gonna go
to four-year schools.
And some might even sign
a minor-league contract.
l seriously doubt it,
but you never know!
So the next time one of
you boneheads shows up
with beer-face,
l'm gonna assume that you forgot
why you're here to begin with.
Where the fuck is my...
Now, l'm cutting more of
you assholes today.
Let's get to it, gentlemen.
Pep in your step!
[ lndistinct conversations ]
[ Whistle chirping ]
[ Spoon's "Metal Detektor"
plays ]
# Metal detektor ringing as
l'm walking through the door #
# With every chance l take,
can feel it start to break #
# Oh, yeah #
# Start to break some more #
# lt's going down some more #
# l'm gonna break the bank
of Texas and walk out #
# lt's a lie no more #
All right. Next.
# l'm gonna break the bank
of Dakota and walk out #
Next.
Aw, turn inside!
lt won't hurt you.
lt's a tennis ball.
MAN:
Come on, Marshall!
LlTTLE:
There you go.
Next.
Murph, Murph, Murph.
You're kind of tying me up,
okay?
l need you to lead me.
-That's a good feed.
-l can't turn that.
# l'm going down some more #
# Not gonna fake it no more #
# Just gonna break the bank
of Texas and walk right out #
# Make the sound of getting
kicked when you're down #
# l'm gonna break the heart of
Chicago and walk right back #
# Metal detektor ringing as
l'm walking through the door #
# Ooh, ooh #
Coach, l'm gonna go grab
a locker.
Hey, hey, hey.
Show some respect.
Wait till the final cut is up.
-But l thought --
-No. Don't think.
Write that down on your glove
so you don't forget.
Right?
T-H-l-N-K.
Who -- Who are you?
Why are you still here?
Marshall?
CALVlN:
l'm right here, Coach.
My office in five.
[ lndistinct conversations ]
Cal, this is your third year
trying out for the team.
And, uh,
l thought that we agreed
that this year you would
focus on the TV show.
Don't you think l've made
some big strides in my game?
Yeah.
Yeah. No, l can tell
you've been practicing.
[ Sighs ]
Look, Cal, lot of ballplayers
need a little push
when their ship doesn't come in.
l'm not sure l heard you right.
Would you mind repeating that?
A lot of --
[ Sighs ]
Look, you need transcripts,
letter of recommendation --
l can do both for you.
Yeah, there's no way in hell
l'm transferring.
You need to do something else
with yourself, man.
Go to a good university.
End of story.
Look, Cal,
l know you want to be a Bison.
Hell, l want you to be one, too.
Coach, my wrist has really
slowed me down this year.
Seriously.
lt's...
Cal.
[ Sighs ]
Exactly.
Take your time.
Get healthy again.
Most importantly, don't
jeopardize the rest of your life
playing a game hurt.
Okay.
You know, Cal, you and Simon
do a kick-ass job
at sports information.
Thanks.
Speaking of which,
do you want to broadcast
women's volleyball this year?
Sure. Yeah.
l'll do it.
Awesome.
No, no.
Don't let the door hit you
in the ass on the way out.
Uh, hey, Coach?
Can l keep my locker?
Yeah.
Just...
That's great.
l'm just -- l'm gonna need
a place for my gear
while l'm rehabbing.
l'll see ya.
[ Spits ]
Good news.
You made the cut!
Yeah!
Oh, my God.
That is so great.
ERNlE:
Way to go, Cal.
Oh, that's so good!
Really proud of you.
Way to go.
JUNE:
l can't believe it.
Coach said l made some big
strides in my game, though.
So you are on the team, then.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, once l'm healthy.
What happened?
What's wrong?
Oh, l'm in pain.
No, no, just --
lt's cool.
lt's no big deal, really.
Did you break it?
No, no, no.
lt's just --
lt's just a sprain, really.
l wanted to play through it,
but Coach wouldn't let me.
So l got to wait
till l'm 100% again
then get back on the field.
Huge drag.
[ Sighs ]
lt's just a temporary setback,
Honus.
One week on the D.L., maybe two.
Just rolling with the punches,
right, Mom?
[ Thud, woman grunts ]
Point Foothill.
Time-out, Bisons.
7-12, game one.
l thought they were supposed to
have some sort of recruit
who turned down 30 scholarships.
That's Tori Jensen.
l'm interviewing her
for the paper after the game.
Number 21 .
She's not here.
Simon.
There she is.
[ The National's "Abel" plays ]
# Well, my mind's not right #
# My mind's not right #
-1 , 2, 3.
-Bisons!
[ Cheers and applause ]
# Abel, come on #
# Give me the keys, man #
[ Whistle blows ]
# Everything has all
gone down wrong #
# Abel, come on #
# Give me the keys, man #
# Everything has all
gone down wrong #
# l see water on the bridge #
# Well, you better hold my hand
through this #
# Turn around, turn around,
take me back #
# l can't calm down #
# Turn around, turn around,
take me back #
# l can't calm down #
# Well, my mind's not right #
# My mind's not right #
-[ Crowd groans ]
-Yes!
Whoo!
Tori!
Jensen!
Give it up for her, guys.
She tallied an amazing 31 kills,
15 blocks,
24 digs, and seven aces.
[ Feedback ]
l'm gonna do the Tori Jensen
interview, Simon.
What am l gonna do, then?
Here.
Take some pictures.
Excuse me.
You want to apologize?
Aah!
Hey, knock it off!
Have some class.
Come on, guys.
CALVlN:
Ms. Jensen!
Tori Jensen!
Ms. Jensen, please!
Whoa, whoa, whoa, Calvin.
Can't let you in the women's
locker room this year, bud.
Come on, man, Bryce.
Quick interview. l promise.
No, man. l mean it.
Wait outside.
Hey! Wait outside!
What's that?
Wow! Yeah!
Sweet move, Bryce.
Go, go, go, go, go!
[ lndistinct conversations ]
[ Gasps ]
Tori.
Excellent match.
Absolutely stunning.
-Calvin Marshall.
-TORl: Hi.
So, the voice
of the Lady Bisons.
Only for the interim.
Actually,
l'm on the baseball team,
but currently dealing with this.
l took the catcher out.
At first they were talking about
putting titanium pins into it.
Oh.
Well, good for you.
But l have to go now, so...
lt's two questions.
lt will only take a second,
sweet thing, l promise.
Why J.C., Tori?
l mean, you turned down
30 Division l scholarships.
You literally could have played
anywhere.
l need to be close to
my family right now.
Do you care to elaborate
on that?
No.
Okay.
l really have to go.
Just one last question.
l promise.
How fantastic does it feel
to dominate the game --
pounding kills, ripping aces,
laying out for digs like that?
lt feels like the world
fades away
and all that's left
is the court
and playing the game is the only
thing that ever mattered.
That's the most beautiful thing
l've ever heard.
SlMON: He's almost done
with the interview!
Uh, Tori, why don't we go ahead
and take this
to a more neutral --
-Calvin!
-Easy, Bryce!
Hey, Tori.
How's it going?
What are you thinking, man?
You're gonna get me fired, dog!
CALVlN:
Miraculous.
Believe me, people, the tape
just doesn't do it justice.
You had to be there in person.
Her kills sound like
shotgun blasts.
You do yourself a favor.
Go see Tori Jensen play.
SlMON: Enough Tori.
Moving on to baseball, Cal.
As you've probably
already heard,
Calvin Marshall suffered
an injury
during a violent collision
at home plate last week.
But it's not career-threatening,
as first suspected.
Only a matter of days before
Marshall rejoins the team.
-[ Bat pings ]
-Caselli, you loose yet?
Uh, no.
No, not yet.
You're pitching intersquad!
Caught in the middle of a crick
without a pot to piss in, l see!
Story of your fucking life!
Give me that.
Let's go.
Loosen up.
Hey! Run!
-Hey, Coach.
-Hey, Cal.
Thought l told you l didn't need
you hanging out at the field.
No, l know. l know.
l just, uh...
l need some advice about a girl.
lt's Tori Jensen.
You going out with her?
No.
All right.
Step up to the plate.
Anticipate her pitch.
What's she gonna throw you?
Look, l've seen her.
She's gonna come at you
with a fastball.
Trust me. She's gonna try to get
in your kitchen.
So get that club head out front.
And bam.
But, you know, looking at her,
she's probably got pretty decent
off-speed stuff.
So if she makes you look like
shit and gets ahead of you,
watch out.
She's gonna waste one
in the dirt,
maybe even throw one
at your head.
So try to get her
to a full count.
Put the bat on the ball,
foul off anything close.
Attaboy.
Hit her opposite field.
CALVlN:
This is great.
What's the best way to get
an A.B.?
Well, first you need
a scouting report.
Just follow her around.
So you want me to stalk her?
No, don't stalk her.
Just spy on her.
Find out what she's all about,
and then,
when the time is right,
take her up to Bison Ridge.
That ought to make things
interesting.
Bison Ridge.
Hey, thanks, Coach.
Yeah.
Hey!
What are you doing?!
Get over here!
Are you kidding me?
Does your sudden interest
in Japanese
have anything to do
with me taking the course?
l don't know.
l just decided to drop
my cooking class, you know?
l didn't really care for it.
Oh, so, then l suppose
you'll be adding
my child development as well.
No, but your astronomy l on
Tuesdays/Thursdays is tempting.
Hey.
Look, l'm not stalking you.
Geez, Jensen,
you're hard to keep up with.
TORl: l'm having a hard time
figuring you out.
CALVlN: l play baseball.
Host a talk show.
l'm an open book.
20 Questions. Go ahead.
Okay.
You have a girlfriend?
Negative.
l know.
lt's hard to believe.
What position do you play?
Shortstop.
Quarterback of the infield.
l got a rehab assignment
this weekend.
lt's a little city league.
God, l love the game.
Sweet smell of the grass,
crack of rock maple,
working hard with the team.
Well, Mr. Shortstop,
good luck with rehab.
l have to go.
You know,
l'm detecting a pattern.
We always start talking,
and you always have to go.
Oh, you're very...perceptive.
You were about to say
"irresistible."
[ Laughing ] Yeah.
Try resistible.
l'm the one who always
has to go, remember?
Hang on.
[ Engine stops ]
We have to change that.
How about this --
you and me swapping war stories
over a cold one.
Just one athlete talking shop
to another.
Hang out with a baseball player
and listen to him talk
about himself?
No, thanks.
You know, l did love what you
said to me the other night.
Oh, yeah?
What was that?
About how when you're in
the middle of a game,
you play like it's the only
thing that ever mattered.
Yeah.
Too bad we can't play
all the time, right?
l'm so pumped you're playing
with us tonight, man.
Already been through
two sorry shortstops this year.
They just couldn't
get the job done.
Make 'em chase your pitches,
Freddie.
Yeah.
No meatballs tonight, man.
[ lndistinct conversations ]
Let's go, Freddie!
Way to pick it.
Attaboy, Cal!
Come on, Calvin!
Come on, Cal!
Yeah!
Get it out!
Gun it!
Gun it! All the way!
Oh, yeah.
Nice shot, Cal.
Yeah, yeah!
Attaboy, Cal.
Way to turn it, baby.
[ Cheers and applause ]
Up!
-Yeah!
-[ Cheers and applause ]
Congratulations, people.
You played with some big-ass
moxie out there today.
So it gives Coach Deerfield
enormous pleasure
to present the game ball
to Calvin, my man!
All right!
Good job, Cal.
lt's a friggin' honor to have
the shortstop of the Bisons
out here with us little guys
for a rehab game.
We miss your bat and glove, Cal.
So your position's always open,
man.
-No offense, Bill.
-No, l agree.
Thank you, Freddie.
You guys, you really didn't
have to do this, you know?
Unfortunately, l won't be able
to join you at the Hillbilly,
but take care, guys.
l hope to see you all again
real soon.
Okay, cool.
Good job, everybody.
CALVlN:
How about giving me a sad look?
You're losing, and it hurts.
Losing more.
And more.
Yes.
lt's perfection.
Let me know if you need
any of these for the scouts,
by the way.
Now give me three of those
legendary jump serves.
Ooh, that was a beaut.
Nice!
Unbelievable.
Five rolls of film
is probably enough, right?
Hey, aren't you supposed to have
practice here right now?
No.
Coach gave us the day off today.
And l really don't feel like
going through my workout.
Never thought l'd see a force
like you pass up a workout.
TORl:
Yeah.
My mom is sick right now,
so it's been really difficult
lately.
She can't come to my games
anymore.
Do you feel like going
somewhere?
You want to clear your head
a little bit?
You're not gonna believe this.
This is one of the best places
to relax in the whole world.
We're going to a bar,
aren't we?
Uh, negative.
lt's one of my all-time
favorite spots
except for the ballyard.
You want to get going
pretty quick.
Oh, come on, man.
All right. You're up.
The fire buttons kind of stick
on this machine.
Okay, keep the throttle about
70% -- There you go --
so you can keep it going.
You see,
you want to keep it moving.
You're pretty good at this.
[ Puck rattling ]
Oh!
[ Laughing ] Oh, yeah.
Oww!
Yes!
Oh, man.
That's pretty good.
lt's pretty good.
Um, you know, you could stand
to get the club head out
a little bit more,
beat the pitcher to the spot,
but not bad.
Let's see how it's done.
-Oh, no, you know, l --
-Oh, come on.
l'd need 15 minutes or so
to get warm
before l could take
my big hacks anyways.
Coach Little would freak
if l got hurt again.
Blazing speed, stole 722 bases,
led the league five times
in RBls,
six times
in slugging percentage,
seven times in doubles.
When he retired in 191 7,
he led the league in hits, runs,
singles, doubles, and triples.
Who is this?
Guy was amazing.
What's his name again?
Honus Wagner.
Oh. Okay.
[ Cheers and applause ]
That kid has talent.
Fred has me teach these kids
fundamentals every year.
So when did you know
you loved baseball?
Oh, l remember the exact moment.
Yeah, l was 7 years old.
Saturday morning.
Not a cloud in the sky.
l got ahold of one.
Line drive to the wall.
l can still feel myself running
the bases
and the crowd going wild.
My mother was the team mom.
She brought oranges
to every game,
organized our parties for us.
So you got your enthusiasm
from her.
Yeah.
She was a kick.
She died when l was 10.
Oh.
That was 1 1 years ago.
Where's your dad?
He's...out of the picture.
So, what about you, though?
When did you learn you were
gonna dominate volleyball?
Uh, 7th grade.
My mom taught our team
the jump serve,
and l caught on pretty fast.
So it's in the genes, then.
My mother was a high-school
Ping-Pong champion.
l give her all the credit
for my hand-eye coordination.
Will you do me a favor and...
don't tell anyone
that my mom is sick.
Because not many people know
about it.
l won't say a word.
Okay.
Thanks.
Well, thanks for a fun day.
l had a great time.
Oh, sorry.
Bad call.
l'd invite you back home,
but, you know, my mom...
Oh, it's no worries, really.
l should get
a good night's sleep.
Tomorrow l come off the D.L.,
and it's gonna be
pretty serious.
Well, have a good night, Tori.
You too.
So great getting back
on the field, Murph.
lt's like getting out of jail.
LlTTLE:
Hey!
The fuck you doing out here,
Marshall?
l was just getting
some glove work in.
Well, who told you
you could do that?
You did.
You told me to take
my time and get healthy.
Diana cleared me this morning.
l'm officially off the D.L.
Come on.
Let's take a walk.
[ Laughter ]
l never said
you were on the team.
You gave me a locker.
What did you think l was gonna
use it for, my books?
Look, l don't --
Come on.
Let's go.
All right. Listen to me.
No, you listen to me!
You remember how it felt
after you got released?
LlTTLE: What does that
have to do with anything?
Some asshole prying you away
from the game that you love.
Yeah, l remember.
So what?
lt's a bit hypocritical,
isn't it?
LlTTLE:
That was different, Cal.
l was a professional player
back then!
Everything's relative.
You're gonna drive me
out of my fucking gourd!
Hold it, Coach.
Stop.
Just don't do it, okay?
Don't hold me down anymore.
ls there anybody out there
that's more dedicated than l am?
l know.
l'm not a superstar yet.
Just give me the chance to help
the team with my gifts.
l got soft hands, good speed,
quick bat.
Most importantly, l got this.
Now, l'm a force our team
can't afford to be without.
Spineless.
Shut up, Dewey.
Don't say a fucking word!
[ Clears throat ]
Sorry, Coach.
Maybe his attitude
will rub off on the team.
CALVlN:
[ Grunts ]
Man, l'm trying to get
the barrel out,
and you're painting corners.
What are you doing?
Dude, it was right there.
Look, l'm not asking you
to comprehend
the art of hitting, Caselli.
l just need you to get the ball
over the plate, okay?
Whatever, Calvin.
You can't even hit a piata
with a rake.
Come on, fellas!
Cool it!
-Caselli!
-Come on, Calvin, huh?
You moron. Get up.
Want some of this, bitch?!
Don't break it up, Dewey!
l was about to kick his ass!
Marshall!
Right-field foul pole.
Now.
DEWEY:
Get up there, Marshall!
Go!
You -- poles.
Run.
All right, you little candy-ass.
Stay up there.
Don't come down till l tell you.
No problem, Coach.
l take full responsibility
for punching Caselli.
Man's got to defend himself.
Yeah. Whatever, Cal.
# Salome #
# Uncross your heart #
# l know it's been overcast #
# lt's written
before it starts #
# Salome #
# Oh, stay right here #
# The full moon
might work magic, girl #
# But l won't disappear #
# And l'm tired
of making friends #
# And l'm tired of making time #
# And l'm sick to death
of love #
of trying #
# And it's easier for you #
# Yes, easier for you #
[ Applause ]
All right.
l got to take a break.
That's the fast part.
That was a good one.
We got another bit to go.
Okay. Mm.
Coach Little --
l like you, Coach Little.
You know what?
l got something to show you.
Okay.
lt's really cool.
All right. Anything.
l'll see it.
-Are you ready?
-Yeah. l'll go with you.
All right. Come on.
Shh. Be quiet.
-That's good.
-Just put them back there.
Carl will get them
in the morning.
-All right.
-Right.
-Here we go.
-SONDRA: Okay.
[ Buzzing ]
-LlTTLE: Give it time.
-SONDRA: Okay.
-Huh?
-Yeah, that's nice.
-Are you kidding me?
-[ Laughs ] lt's good.
That is a sight to behold
at night, isn't it?
lt's like a damn cathedral.
Kind of.
Well, yeah.
Okay.
That's pretty, Coach.
LlTTLE:
lt really is, you know?
Hey, one of your players
gonna join us?
No.
SONDRA:
Coach.
Marshall!
[ Grunting ]
-Hey.
-Sorry, Coach.
l should have stayed awake.
LlTTLE:
All right. Yeah.
Okay, Cal. You're good.
You can go home now.
Sondra and l need the field.
Hi, Sondra.
Calvin Marshall.
You play softball?
No, not really.
Coach said he's gonna teach me
a little bit about baseball,
though.
Yeah. Yeah.
Um, yeah, we're gonna run
through some drills together,
so...
You want me to shag some balls?
No, l don't need you
to shag balls, Cal.
You can go home now, all right?
Okay.
See ya later, Coach.
Hey, tomorrow l bring
my "A" game.
Yeah. All right.
Go.
Oh, my God.
[ Rock music plays ]
-l'll think about it.
-Hey!
You heard me!
Get out of here!
l'll put you jackasses in the
hospital if you bug her again.
Sorry about that.
What was that all about?
Ah, Division l scouts
are harassing Tori here,
and l told them
they had to go through me.
Yeah, or they could go
through me.
Why would they do that?
Just when you're busy,
they can go through me.
l know how to take care
of these guys.
Give me 20 minutes, okay?
Okay.
l'll see you soon, Tori.
And thank you.
You bet.
-TORl: l'll be in touch.
-Good to see you again.
WOMAN:
Are these free?
-No, the stickers aren't free.
-WOMAN: Temper.
LlTTLE:
Hey, Simon, what you got?
Hey.
CALVlN:
Show him the posters.
The jump-serve
is the best poster.
[ Whistles ] All right. Good.
l'll take one for my office.
Cool.
You also get a free
Tori Jensen bobblehead
or a Coach Little
Bisons pennant.
No. Give me a bobblehead.
SlMON:
Right. Totally. Um, okay.
l took these pictures, you know.
-Yeah?
-Yeah.
They're outstanding.
Yeah, l think
it's your best work.
Thank you.
Yeah. See ya later.
Oh!
Oh, shit.
Keep 'em coming, Carramae.
Don't let my ice go dry.
Shit.
Can l please get
some more peanuts, darlin'?
Thank you.
Coach Little?
What a surprise to see you here.
Hey, Coach.
LlTTLE:
Oh.
Well, how are you ladies
this evening?
Oh, we're doing just great.
Sondra and l have become close.
Well, that's awesome.
Yeah.
So maybe you both might
want some company tonight.
Maybe we can turn some double
plays down at the ballyard.
That's crazy, 'cause that's
what l was thinking, too.
Sounds like a good time,
Coach.
Except...
Yeah, we have that little
problem, don't we, Sondra?
Funny thing to find out
that you've been telling us
the same pitiful stories
about how you're ready
to settle down
and how we should meet
some of your celebrity friends,
like Nolan Ryan or --
or who else?
Willie Nelson.
-Willie, dude.
-Right.
That was the one that got me.
l'm a huge fan.
l wanted to meet him.
You can meet him.
SONDRA:
You know what, though? No.
Because, Coach, my favorite
was when you said,
"Oh, l haven't been with anyone
in a year and a half."
Yeah. Year and a half.
Did you mean maybe...
Okay, girls --
...a week and a half?
Look, let's not get
all worked up!
[ Murmuring, laughter ]
Here you go, Little.
Little wienie.
Thank you.
[ lndistinct conversations ]
[ Laughter ]
Oh!
Did you see that?
Oh, come on.
Come on. Come on.
l can't breathe, dude.
Oh, l think he broke his nose.
What?
Call an ambulance, dude.
Call an ambulance!
l can take him.
l got you.
Whoa. Come on.
Coach Little's gonna kill you,
man!
[ Chuckles ]
Hey, Jensen.
Sorry about that.
The boys need me on their team.
ls Caselli gonna be okay?
CALVlN: Oh, yeah.
He'll pitch tomorrow.
You know, Tori, you really
played like an MVP tonight.
You want to get out of here?
Sure. Yeah.
What do you want to do?
l have something in mind.
Okay.
Have you been up to Bison Ridge
before?
No.
But l heard it's a great place
to talk and enjoy the view.
[ Chuckles ] Calvin...
l didn't bring you up here
to talk.
Are you scared?
No. No, no.
l'm -- l'm just, uh...
Uh...
Have you been with a girl
before?
Yeah, yeah.
Just...not like --
not like this.
So you haven't.
Just not with somebody like you.
You're a goddess.
On and off the court.
This is a great album.
[ Rock music plays ]
Be still.
Hold still.
You've done this before.
So, how was it?
lncredible.
To be that close.
[ Chuckles ]
You can't get any closer.
CALVlN:
No, you can't, can you?
Nope.
So, was it everything
you wanted it to be?
Was it fun?
ls that, uh...
-ls that --
-What?
ls that what this is to you?
lt's just fun?
Well, uh...
Yeah.
Wasn't it?
Oh, definitely.
l don't know.
lt just...
feels like
there's something more to it.
That's all.
But...
That is not how it is, though.
Not -- Not how what is?
[ Sniffles ]
What?
Um...
Nothing.
l just had too much to drink.
Can you just take me home?
Are you mad?
No.
Um...
Are you?
See you tomorrow?
Yeah.
Sure.
Call me.
Here.
WOMAN:
Thank you.
[ Telephone rings ]
Hi. We're not here.
Leave a message.
[ Beep ]
CALVlN: Oh, l hope l didn't
wake you, Mrs. Jensen.
Tori, l had to call
and say sorry.
l can do this.
Tonight was like seeing
a 95-mile-an-hour fastball
for the first time.
Tomorrow night, we are going out
on the date of a lifetime,
so clear your schedule.
And, Mrs. Jensen,
you would have been so proud.
Tori had 45 kills tonight.
[ Beep ]
Sounds sweet.
l'm not sure l have the energy
for him right now.
[ Sniffles ]
Shh. Shh. Shh. Shh. Shh.
Shh. Shh. Shh. Shh.
Shh. Shh.
Fuckin' A-Rod and l
locked horns
more than once in the minors,
man.
Yeah, l know.
They took the training wheels
off that teenage punk,
and the next thing you know,
he's just a major-league
all-star.
lt's fucking unbelievable!
Coach, your -- your
minor-league career
ain't nothing to be ashamed of.
How many times
l got to tell you that?
LlTTLE: l love you.
You're all right.
Hit me, Carramae.
CARRAMAE:
No, no, no!
-l'm cutting you off, Little.
-What?
You been drinking whiskey
for six hours.
Go on!
Lift your little butt
off the stool and get.
Hey.
Maybe we better, uh,
call it a night, Coach.
l've just been sippin' these.
l just been sippin' these, man.
Come on.
Don't -- Don't turn on me now.
Come on!
Uh, Carramae...
[ Chuckles ]
You know, l think
l'll have me another.
l'll put you out on your ass,
too, Skeeter.
Now, get him out of here
before l call Mo.
l have been carrying this place
on my back for six years!
l'm tired of being treated
like a fucking tourist!
Hey!
Come on!
Come on, Mo!
[ Clattering ]
Don't do it, Mo!
Get out of here, Skeet!
Get out!
Hey, Mo.
Swear to God Mo will toss you
on your head again.
LlTTLE:
Oh, yeah?
Come on, Mo.
What you gonna do?
Aah!
Tweet!
-[ Whistles ]
-MO: Fuck you, Doug.
LlTTLE: Hey, you're lucky
l don't want to brawl!
l'd kick all three of your asses
up and down the street
like a fucking parade!
That's right.
[ Buzzing ]
Yeah, Mo!
You should have seen me
pick it out of here.
Yeah.
l was some kind of shortstop,
buddy.
l flat-out had wheels
in "A" ball.
[ Mumbling ]
[ Grunts ]
Backhanders...
Oh, God.
Whoo!
l had a cannon, too.
[ Grunts ]
Appleton, Wisconsin.
Crack!
[ Groans ]
[ Birds chirping ]
[ Engine rumbling ]
-[ Laughs ]
-Can't breathe, dude.
What the fuck happened to you?
Well, we were just, um...
Well, he got sucker-punched
last night.
The other team crashed
our party.
You're kidding.
By who?
lt was Tolkheim.
Tolkheim?
Please tell me
you can still pitch.
Yeah. Yeah, for sure.
LlTTLE:
Throw at Tolkheim.
You better fucking drill him.
What, am l boring you, Marshall?
Oh, no, Coach.
l just had a late night
last night.
Yeah. With Tori Jensen.
Well, l don't believe it.
Marshall went yard last night.
Boy, he's playing way above
his head this year, fellas.
[ Laughter ]
My God, we're not talking
about a slump-buster.
We're talking about Tori Jensen.
CALVlN:
Coach.
Who is...standing
right over there.
Oh, shit.
Hey, Tori.
What were you guys
talking about?
Oh, nothing.
l just hit one out
the other day.
Went yard.
LlTTLE:
Marshall!
What the fuck are you doing now?
Look, you stay out all night
before a double-header,
that's your business.
But on game day, you keep
your head on the field!
Sorry, Coach.
Right-field foul pole -- now.
Run!
[ Sighs ]
Oh, l'm just messing
with Marshall.
l mean, he's more or less
our team mascot.
What?
No, l thought he was
the shortstop.
[ Laughs ]
No.
We'd be in deep shit
if that were true.
Hey, good game last night.
Thanks, Coach.
l'm not your coach.
You can call me Doug.
Okay.
Now, schools are starting to
inquire about you,
so l want to be there.
A good A.D. like myself,
l can help you sift through
all the bullshit schools
and then squeeze the big one
for the money and perks.
You got the goods, Jensen.
Now make them beg for it.
You come talk to me
when you're ready, all right?
Maybe l will...Doug.
There you go.
SlMON:
Leading off the second inning,
White Oak's first baseman,
David Tolkheim.
[ Grunts ]
What?
Dude, go!
Bitch, come on!
Go, go, go!
l'm gonna kill you!
[ lndistinct shouting ]
ERNlE:
Get the hell off him, Coach!
What the hell, man?
Okay, okay, okay!
Uh-huh. Okay.
She's late.
lt's 4:15.
Well, Ernie won't be
at the trailhead until 5:00.
lt's about a 2-mile ride,
so we should get there
by sunset.
Ernie and Fred are gonna take
the horses back down,
and then after the picnic,
we'll four-wheel down the other
side of Bison Ridge in a Humvee.
Then we'll jump in a kayak and
go downriver for about a mile
just in time for dessert and
wine at Wildcat Creek Tavern.
We should be eating by 6:30.
Can you make it that long?
Yeah, l think so.
You want some sunflower seeds?
-No, thanks.
-Yeah?
[ Brakes squeak ]
Give us 15 minutes, okay?
All right.
No problem, guys.
You're right on time.
That's Ernie driving.
He's been seeing June
for a while now.
We should all get together
sometime -- have dinner.
-lt'll be great.
-Calvin!
He's a sweet guy.
Calvin!
Stop, okay?
Time-out.
Please.
And l'm supposed to pick
a university for next year,
and all l can think about
is my mom.
You know, it's a really
awful time right now.
Believe me, l know it is.
That's why l planned all this.
l want to help take your mind
off everything.
[ Sighs ] Calvin,
you're not listening to me.
l can't do this.
You know, we don't
have to ride horses
if you don't want to.
No. This!
You and me.
Why did you lie to me?
What do you mean?
About what?
About baseball.
CALVlN: l didn't lie to you.
l'm on the team.
So l'm not a starter yet.
l still have three years
of eligibility.
Yeah, but you misled me,
Calvin!
You made me think
you were some kind of phenom.
Doug says you're just
the team mascot.
Doug? Who's Doug?
Doug Little.
Coach Little?
TORl:
Yes.
Well, maybe you should have
watched me play first
before you got involved.
Yeah, maybe l should have.
[ Horse whinnies ]
Look, l'm sorry.
[ The Church's
"The Unguarded Moment" plays ]
# So deep #
# Deep without a meaning #
# l knew you'd find me leaving #
# Tell those friends
with cameras for eyes #
# That their hands #
# Don't make me hang #
# They only make me
feel like breathing #
# ln an unguarded moment #
Oh!
[ Laughing ]
# ln an unguarded moment #
[ Cheers and applause ]
You didn't scratch,
so that's good.
Hey, Cal.
l know you've been going through
a difficult time.
lf there's anything l can do,
l want you to let me know,
all right?
Okay, Ernie.
Thank you.
lf you feel like taking
a break from school,
l can get you a good job.
You know, you're
supervisor material, buddy.
You know that, don't you?
Yeah.
lt's not really what l want to
do, you know, but who knows?
Yeah, exactly.
Think about it.
Good salary.
Great benefits.
[ lndistinct conversations ]
FREDDlE:
Ernie, you're up, man.
Ooh!
Whoo-hoo!
Yee-haw!
All right.
l'm gonna carry you to second.
You carry me to third.
Wait! Whoa, whoa! Stop.
We can't cross second.
Why?
lt's tradition.
lt's a rule.
-l need a kiss.
-What?
l didn't make the rules.
lt's just the way it is.
Come on.
lt's got to happen. Sorry.
[ Chuckles ] No!
No!
[ Grunts ]
Oh, girl, you're hard.
lsn't this a little bizarre?
l mean, l thought you were gonna
show me your apartment.
lt's a condo.
Whatever.
Or we can go downtown.
Or anything.
Downtown?
You kidding me?
Look at this.
How many people --
[ Chain rattles ]
Who's there?
That you, Dewey?
Marshall?
You should be so ashamed.
Calvin, nothing happened.
No, l am not talking to you.
l loved her.
She's so out of your league,
it's not even funny.
Oh, and she's in yours?
You're 40 years old!
l'm 38.
Oh, yeah, a 38-year-old,
over-the-hill,
minor-league failure!
-Stop!
-No, no, no, no, no, no.
lt's only gonna get worse,
you know.
50 is right around the corner.
By then, the women won't be
so easy.
And you'll have to find a new
group of friends to harass,
'cause the guys at the
Hillbilly, they'll be dead!
Are you done?
[ Grunts ]
Stop it!
This is absurd!
You think you're in your prime,
but you're not.
You're not,
and you are so deluded.
l'm deluded?
CALVlN:
Yeah.
Do you know how bad you are?
-Doug, don't do this.
-What are you talking about?
Baseball!
You suck ass.
You're miserable.
You're the most delusional
player that l've ever met.
You're an embarrassment
to the sport.
l like you, Cal.
And that's why l put up with
your sorry-ass game for so long.
But the only way you're gonna
manage to stay in baseball
is if you umpire
or you cut the grass.
Or sell hot dogs and beer.
Yeah, that's it.
Just go home.
Get the fuck off my field!
You're cruel.
He needed to hear that,
and you know it.
[ Engine cranking ]
[ Breathing heavily ]
[ lndistinct conversations ]
MAN: Come on, guys.
Let's get out there.
ERNlE: So as soon as those guys
are done, get them cleared out,
because we got to pour
the concrete
in both these trenches by 3:00,
so you got to get the concrete
guy to move his truck.
When you tell him to move
his truck, he'll say no.
Tell him to do it anyway.
Hey, Cal. Good morning.
CALVlN:
Good morning, Freddie.
lt's Mr. Marshall to you,
buddy.
Your new supervisor.
Right, Ernie.
Yeah. Okay.
Don't forget your hard hat.
Yeah. Yeah.
So when the concrete
gets poured,
then the side joists
and the roof joists
will get delivered later on
in the afternoon.
We got to get all those up
by the end of the week.
And we also got to keep both
these access roads wet down,
because you can see
how dusty it gets.
[ Engine turns over ]
Be here at 7:00 a.m.
for that lumber delivery.
Oh, yeah.
See ya later!
Okay.
Freshman Tori Jensen is also,
uh, mulling over,
uh, scholarship offers
from many universities
all over the country.
All over the country.
She, uh --
Those schools include UCS --
USC, UCLA, U--
[ Television turns off ]
ERNlE:
That's a foul, Fred.
You're all over him.
-Ooh!
Who are you guarding, Cal?
-[ Thud ]
-Bricklayer.
Come on, Cal!
There you go, babe.
Yeah!
Nice stroke.
[ Chuckles ]
Why you do that to him?
Sportsman of the year.
Again.
Oh! Oh! Yeah!
21 .
-Good night.
-Good night, grandma!
That's the closest
you've been to making one, Fred.
[ Music playing ]
Ma'am, will you please give
Skeeter another
of whatever he's having,
and, uh, l'll take a stout.
Whatever you got on tap.
Go back to the mall
with your friends.
What are you -- 16?
l may not have my wallet
on me right now,
but l'm rolling in cash.
l work in construction,
and l have great benefits.
Give him a beer, Carramae.
l'll be responsible.
That really sets my mind
at ease, Little.
Thanks.
Doug Little.
Trying to come through
with the game on the line.
How are you, Doug?
Oh!
Psych!
[ Laughs ]
l'm not so sure
l want your charity, Doug.
That's fine.
l'll give it to Skeeter.
Yeah, or you could give it
to Tori.
Skeet, you want a beer?
SKEETER:
Yeah. Sure.
Oh, no, no, Skeeter.
l'll take it.
Hey, what happened with Tori,
that wasn't right.
Don't beat yourself up about it,
Doug.
l couldn't care less, really.
What can l say?
l got philandering genes.
Least l could have done was let
you know l was moving in on her.
Yeah, well...
You can have her.
Yeah, l wish l could.
Yeah, she strong-armed me.
Three hard sliders
off the plate.
That's exactly how l felt.
Hey, Skeeter,
you're breathing on me.
Will you get out of my face
for a second?
SKEETER:
Oh. Uh, yeah, yeah.
Sorry, Coach.
LlTTLE:
And another thing.
l didn't mean all those things
l said that night.
Yeah, you did.
Come on. You did.
And you're right.
l'm a miserable,
delusional disaster.
And l am an embarrassment
to the sport.
No.
lt's people like you
that make baseball
the greatest game in the world.
lt's always the talented
assholes out there
that disrespect and tarnish
the sport.
What the fuck are you doing here
all by yourself
on a Friday night?
What are you,
a Hillbilly regular now?
Maybe.
[ Scoffs ]
l can think of 10 or 15
better places to be.
A guy like you? Huh?
Well, might as well show you
the ropes.
This here's Carramae.
And she's a sweetheart.
She's always in a pleasant mood.
And there's Skeeter.
You met him.
And, uh, well, there's always
a colorful bunch of characters
in dumps like these.
l've seen hundreds
of these shitty bars
all over the country.
Always the same.
Bad food, unstable women.
Just enough meatheads to keep
these dumps in business.
Fuckin' losers.
Welcome.
[ Chuckles ]
Carramae?
[ Applause ]
Williams seems to be
falling apart.
[ Knock on door ]
He's had some personal issues
lately,
so it's a victory that
he's out here at all.
As we move into...
What happened?
MlNlSTER: ...a time
for every event under heaven.
A time to give birth
and a time to die.
A time to plant and a time
to uproot what is planted.
A time to search
and a time to give up as lost.
A time to keep...
Coach Little steps up,
says something to the umpire.
Oh, boy. Got to be careful
there. [ Chuckles ]
And here's the pitch.
Fly ball. That should do it.
Back to the warning track.
Makes the catch.
And Temple will score easily.
And the Bisons take a 3-2 lead
here in the 7th.
That was a great at-bat
by Murphy.
Make sure he gets
the go-ahead run.
Ground ball toward second.
And he's gonna beat it out.
l'll tell you,
Viczorek was hustling.
That's what Coach Little's
gonna want to see.
Reporting courtside with
Bison sensation Tori Jensen.
l'm Calvin Marshall.
How are you feeling tonight,
Tori?
Strong?
Ready to dominate?
You are looking gorgeous
tonight, by the way.
We're all expecting
a fantastic performance
from you on the volleyball court
tonight.
Why don't we go back
to the studio?
[ Cheers and applause ]
All right, this guy's throwing
watermelons, Freddie.
-He's looking for a double play.
-FREDDlE: Okay.
So just get a good swing on it
and send something
to the outfield, okay?
Use your wheels.
Get in scoring position.
Okay.
There are no arms
in the outfield whatsoever.
Okay.
[ Cheers and applause ]
WOMAN:
All right!
MAN:
Keep your eye on it!
[ lndistinct shouting ]
[ Cheers and applause ]
Go, Fred! Whoo!
Yes!
Calvin.
You got it. Line drive.
[ The Sound's "Monument" plays ]
MAN: Nice and easy!
Just get it out there!
# ls it fear? #
# ls it fear that you feel
inside of you? #
# ls it fear? #
# Shouting out, just fear
you feel inside of you? #
# ls it fear? #
# That you feel
when all eyes are on you? #
# ls it fear? #
# Surely not just fear you feel
when all eyes are on you #
Oh, that's so cold!
So, who told you
about the game?
Simon.
Great job.
Thanks.
[ Chuckles ]
So, who's the lucky
university?
l don't know.
Um...
l'm going on a recruiting trip
early tomorrow.
You'll pick the right school.
Just make sure
you like the coach
and they need an outside hitter.
You really don't want to get
stuck behind a returning player.
That's kind of what happened
to me here at Bayford.
l think l might head back east.
You know, l kind of need
a change of scenery.
Some excellent programs
out there.
Maryland, Notre Dame, Florida.
You'll be fine.
You came here to say goodbye.
No.
l came to see you play.
[ Both chuckle ]
[ Sighs ]
l loved watching you out there.
Thanks.
Do you want to come
to the party?
Mm.
l have to pack.
But l will call you
when l get back in two weeks.
See you later.
Bye.
FREDDlE:
What a friggin' finish, huh?
-Hey, Freddie!
-[ Laughs ]
Hey, so, Simon, you figured
out my ERA yet?
SlMON:
9.27.
That's not bad, Freddie.
Thanks, man. l'm definitely
coming into my own.
Yeah, especially after all
the meatballs you threw up
last year.
FREDDlE:
We're gonna win again next year.
l can feel it.
This club's a dynasty.
You know what, guys?
l don't think l'm gonna be here
next year.
What are you talking about,
man?
lt's time to move on.
l got bigger games out there
to call.
And you'll find somebody to host
the show, Simon.
Gonna miss you, man.
Guys, l'll be here all summer.
Excuse me, everybody.
l'd like to make a toast.
[ lndistinct conversations ]
[ Clears throat ]
To, uh -- to --
Excuse me.
Um, to a man who has been
a big-ass inspiration to me.
Uh, just found out he's gonna be
heading out of town,
on to bigger and better things.
Here's a man who gives
and gives and gives.
And you know what?
He gives more than l ever could.
And, uh, here's to a man whose
clutch base knock in the 7th
gave Ernie's Construction
another title,
so that was cool.
Here's to a man
we all care about.
Here's to Calvin Marshall.
-[ Cheers and applause ]
-Hear, hear!
-Calvin.
-Way to go, Cal.
Whoo-hoo!
JUNE:
l love you!
[ Clark's "Standing
in Your Silhouette" plays ]
# Standing in your silhouette #
# Whispered words connect #
# Golden light and reasons why #
# Oh, l hear you now #
# Sometimes l hear you speak
at night #
# When moons and stars do meet #
# ln your voice,
my heart rests #
# Oh, l hear you now #
# l want to see you look at me #
# The way you used to do #
# As constant as #
# The morning sun #
# Surely it will rise #
# l saw you fly,
a winter night #
# The angels held your breath #
# l want to know
the truth we had #
# Behind those days and nights #
# l want to see you look at me #
# The way you used to do #
# As constant as #
# The morning sun #
# Surely it will rise #
# As contant as #
# The morning sun #
# Surely it will rise #
# Help me with chemistry #
# Remember all the science #
# To be #
# Help me with chemicals #
# All the bio-altering #
# To see #
# All there is to see #
# To feel #
# All there is to feel #
# Help me have energy #
# Make the colander seem full #
# Found me with energy #
# Show me l've done nothing #
# To burn #
# All l've broken down #
# To spin #
# All over ground #