[SCREAMS]
[GRUNTS]
[GROWLING]
[DISH CLATTERS]
Hmm.
[SNIFFS]
[PANTING]
[SIGHS]
[GRUNTING]
[CRASH]
[TWO SHOES SNORING]
TWO SHOES:
Huh? W-What? Thomas.
Get out of my room, you crazy cat.
[IMITATING SHIP FLYING]
[IMITATING EXPLOSION]
[WHIMPERING]
[GRUNTING]
TWO SHOES:
Go back downstairs, Thomas.
[GASPS]
[SCREAMS]
[TWO SHOES GASPING]
TWO SHOES:
Thomas!
[TWO SHOES GRUNTING]
Get off me.
Don't teII me you're afraid
of that IittIe mouse.
Has your pea brain dropped
right out of your soft IittIe head?
Heavens, this cat's off his nut.
[CRASH]
[GRUNTS]
[SCREAMS]
[BUTTONS BEEPING]
TWO SHOES: CIose the door, Thomas.
You'II Iet the weirdoes in.
VAN HELSING: Come, Thomas,
there's much work to be done.
VAN HELSING: Be carefuI
with my monster-hunting equipment.
[TOM GRUNTS]
[BELL RINGS]
BELLHOP:
V-- V-- Van HeIsing.
The famous monster hunter.
What are you doing here
at the monster convention?
VAN HELSING:
Business and pIeasure.
[GRUNTS]
[BELLHOP YELLING]
BELLHOP:
I'm going to get you, Van HeIsing.
VAN HELSING:
Hmm.
Thomas, I forgot my siIver werewoIf trap.
Take the Iuggage upstairs.
Guard my equipment.
I'II be back before midnight.
[GRUNTS]
WeIcome to Monster Con. I am the count.
As one of the first guests to arrive,
aIIow me to get your ID badge...
...and to say--
[SCREAMS]
Fine, get your own badge.
[GROWLS]
[BARKS]
Hi, I'm Jasper, the sociaI ghost.
Wanna be my friend?
JASPER:
Guess not.
ALL:
What the--?
Hey, paI, we got this room tiII 3:30.
Yeah, the sign-up sheet is outside.
Uh-oh. Is that a ghost vac?
Oh, how rude.
I don't wanna go. I don't wanna go.
[GHOSTS GRUNTING]
GHOST:
HeIp. HeIp.
[GRUNTS]
[BELL RINGING]
MUMMY:
HeIIo? HeIIo?
Me Iove Monster Con.
[GRUNTING]
Mummy outfit ruined.
Me go home now.
Never win costume contest.
[DOOR OPENS]
[WHISTLES]
[GROWLING]
[TOM SCREAMS]
[GRUNTING]
[HOWLING]
[GROWLING]
[CHUCKLES]
[HORSE WHINNIES]
VAN HELSING:
What's going on here?
My word. Is that a werewoIf cat?
-Huh?
-I've never trapped one of those before.
I'II add it to my coIIection.
[SCREAMS]
[MONSTER GRUNTS]
[ENGINE SPUTTERING]
Ah. Battery bad.
Wha--? No.
[ENGINE STARTS]
[MONSTER GRO ANING]
VAN HELSING:
I've got you in my sights, werewoIf cat.
You can't escape from Van HeIsing.
[BIRDS CHIRPING]
[YAWNS]
[SNORING]
[TOM LAUGHING]
[SCREAMS]
[SCREAMING]
[YELLS]
[GRUNTS]
[MALE VOICE LAUGHING]
MALE VOICE: So we got a pair
of newcomers to the cursed forest.
FinaIIy, some entertainment.
Yeah, I got bat wings.
And it ain't poIite to stare.
That's just the way
things work around here.
Oh, boy, I guess I gotta expIain.
You see, this is a cursed forest,
and I'm, uh, sort of a bat now.
Listen, I don't make the ruIes,
I just foIIow them.
And here's the main one:
Anytime somebody enters the forest,
at Ieast one sucker has gotta stay behind.
But because there's two of you,
onIy one has gotta stay.
Forever.
[CHUCKLES]
Yeah, that forever bit aIways gets them.
Hey, wait a minute.
If I get out of here first, I can Ieave.
[LAUGHS]
Uh, ahem.
Oh, heIIo.
You weren't supposed to hear that.
So Iong, suckers.
Nuts. ExpIoding nuts.
You ain't seen the Iast of me.
[THUD]
[WHIMPERING]
Like I said,
one of us has gotta stay behind.
[GASPS]
The waterfaII?
That's our ticket out of here.
Oh, I'm sorry, did I say ''our''?
I meant my.
See you.
[GASPS]
[LAUGHING]
Yahoo! I'm the first one out.
Hey, no wings.
Wait a minute,
if I ain't got wings, I can't fIy.
[GROWLS]
[ENGLISH SDH]
[TOM SNORING]
[GROWLS]
[LAUGHS]
[LAUGHING]
[BONES HIT TOM]
[SCREAMS]
[MIMICS CAR HORN]
[MO ANS]
BIeh!
[SCREAMS]
[CHUCKLES]
[GRUNTS]
[DIRT BIKE APPRO ACHING]
[ENGINE REVVING]
[THUD]
[WHEEL SQUEAKING]
[FLIES BUZZING]
[CHOMPS]
[GULPS]
MAN: Now, I hope the both of you reaIize
that being a Iifeguard is serious business.
The requirements are very demanding.
So keep that in mind, Droopy.
Oh, and you too, Tom.
AIways remember,
a Iifeguard must be aIert.
What?
Where did everybody go?
A Iifeguard must be swift.
Oh, dear.
And a Iifeguard must be strong.
[DROOPY SPLASHES IN WATER]
I'm never going to get this job.
[LAUGHS]
Okay, boys.
Your first test
wiII be diving from this high board.
Now, you'II be judged on styIe,
form and grace.
My assistant, Miss ShapeIy,
wiII keep score.
She's very good at figures.
I shaII go first.
[WHIRRING]
Oh, dear.
[DROOPY SNEEZES]
[LAUGHS]
DROOPY:
Oh, my.
Sports Iovers, I'm ready.
Ta-da.
SIight advantage, Droopy.
Your next test wiII be to swim
across this debris-fiIIed pooI...
...over to Miss ShapeIy on the other side.
Good Iuck.
I shaII do my best to avoid
each and every obstacIe.
Who turned out the Iights?
On your mark, get set, go.
[INHALES DEEPLY]
[GROWLS]
GIug, gIug, gIug.
Ready, Droopy?
-Ready.
-On your mark.
Get set.
Go.
[BELCHES]
[GIGGLES]
Oh, I just can't make up my mind.
They're both exceIIent candidates.
So I want you to fake a ''reaI emergency''
so we can see how they respond.
Sounds smart.
HeIp! HeIp!
Uh, save me.
HeIp.
Whatever. I'm out of here.
[STOMACH RUMBLING]
[MO ANS]
Stomach cramps.
Somebody didn't wait 20 minutes
after eating before going in the water.
Hang on, Tom.
Everyone stand back.
I know just what to do.
One, two, three.
[SPUTTERING]
You know,
I aImost hope he doesn't wake up.
BIeh!
Yuck.
That was some rescue, Droopy.
You get the job.
Remember, a cIean pooI is a safe pooI.
[SLURPING]
DROOPY:
Keep scrubbing, Tom.
[GROWLS]
Oh, Thomas, I so enjoy
the peacefuI soIitude of a camping trip.
MAN [ON RADIO] : We interrupt
this broadcast for a special report.
Bigfoot has been sighted in the vicinity
of the Ootagootasolo Campground.
[CAMPERS SCREAMING]
TWO SHOES:
Bigfoot? Ha! What nonsense.
I don't beIieve in such things.
[HOWLING]
[HOWLS]
[CHUCKLES]
MAN [ON RADIO] :
Attention, campers.
The Zoological Society
is offering a $ 1-million reward...
...for conclusive proof
of Bigfoot's existence.
SHELDON:
I'm down here.
Yeah, I know, there's not much inventory
in the height department.
But the feet are gigantic.
The name's SheIdon. Nice to meet you.
I don't introduce myseIf
to many campers.
In fact, I hardIy ever come down
from the deep woods.
But I am starving.
No worries. I won't eat you.
I'm strictIy vegan. Grew the fur myseIf.
Yikes! Who's that?
I'II be captured and put in a zoo.
We gotta hide.
[WIND WHISTLES]
[SNIFFING]
Oh, no. He's picked up my scent.
This guy is good.
BIeh!
Okay, good, but not gifted.
We shouId stiII do something.
[WHISTLES]
[SNORING]
BEAR [YELLING] :
Quiet!
What's with aII that racket?
I want quiet!
Don't you know what quiet is?
What are you, some kind of ignoramus?
Now, get out!
I hate noise! I can't stand noise!
Bears are notoriousIy cranky
during hibernation.
[THUMPING O VER HEADPHONES]
He can hear my big feet. HeIp.
HeIp.
[HOWLS]
[ECHOES]
[SNAPPING]
[SCREAMS]
[JERRY HOWLING]
[PANTING]
[THUD]
Ouch.
Are you guys starving?
Because I am absoIuteIy famished....
[STAMMERS]
Berries.
[CHOMPING]
Oops.
SHELDON:
Too high. I'm down here.
[LAUGHING]
[SCREAMING]
[BUZZING]
[SCREAMS]
WeII, he won't be bothering me anymore.
And I got a bowI fuII of yummy berries.
Thanks, IittIe friends.
Come back and visit.
TWO SHOES:
Thomas, is--? Is that you?
I thought I heard a noise.
[TWO SHOES SCREAMS]
Oh, it's Bigfoot. Save me!
TWO SHOES:
I wonder whatever happened to Tom.
No matter.
I can buy a whoIe house fuII of cats
with $ 1 miIIion.
[BEES BUZZING]
[ENGLISH SDH]
[THUD]
TWO SHOES:
That's right, Thomas...
...you show those pesky birds
who's boss.
We've worked too hard
on this summer garden...
...to have it ransacked by riffraff.
Up, up.
Now, Iet's see how my prizewinning peas
are progressing.
[TWO SHOES SCREAMS]
Do you see that, Thomas?
Something's been nibbIing my pea pods.
No, sirree, we won't have any of that.
And you, Thomas,
are gonna make sure of it.
That's right, you.
You're gonna stand guard...
...and keep this garden
free of pests and poachers.
Do you understand me, Thomas?
Good.
Nobody's gonna mess with my garden.
[BELLOWS PUFFING]
[SQUEAKING]
[WHISTLING]
[SPLATS]
[THUD]
Huh?
[CHUCKLES]
JERRY:
Yoo-hoo!
[BLOWS RASPBERRY]
[GROWLS]
[CHOMPING]
[SIZZLES]
[GULPING]
[SCREAMS]
[CRASHING]
[TWO SHOES SCREAMS]
TWO SHOES:
Thomas!
What in the name of the heavenIy harvest
is going on here?
Just Iook at my prizewinning tomatoes.
This is horribIe.
[TWO SHOES SCREAMS]
My precious corn...
...my beIoved crops.
You good-for-nothing garden guardian.
I know just the thing
to keep you out of troubIe...
...and stiII do your job.
[CAR HORNS HONKING]
[BLOWS RASPBERRY]
[PANTING]
[MO ANS]
What a tired, oId cat-and-mouse routine.
Hey, tomcat.
Ain't you tired of never catching
that stinking mouse?
ProbIem is, you're going about
catching mice aII wrong.
You got no discipIine,
no game pIan, no dignity.
What you need, brother,
is to join me and the League of Cats.
The League of Cats
is a super-secret society.
Like, we got each other's backs, man.
Sign this card and you're in.
Attaboy.
[CHUCKLES]
Now, the quick initiation process.
And weIcome to the cIub.
Come to our secret meeting tonight.
[WHISPERING]
It's at....
[BUTCH SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY]
Now, Iisten up.
This is a mouse.
[GROWLS]
BUTCH:
No, no, a picture of a mouse.
This is a cat.
[CATS LAUGH AND CHEER]
BUTCH: Now, this is the oId-fashioned way
of catching a mouse.
The probIem: the IittIe guy just runs cycIes
around the Iikes of us cats.
This way and that way, over hiII and daIe,
backwards and forwards.
It's enough to make you sick.
Now then...
...same mouse...
...same cat.
OnIy this time, the cat whistIes for heIp
from the Ieague.
[WHISTLES]
By foIIowing this simpIe tactic,
we'II catch us more mice with Iess work.
This pIace'II be Ioaded with mice.
We'II aII be fat cats.
[BUTCH CHUCKLES]
So the next time one of youse cats
corners a mouse, just whistIe.
-Got it?
CATS: Got it.
[CLEARS THRO AT]
[WHISTLES]
[ALL PANTING]
You Iet him get away.
It wasn't me, it was him.
[CHUCKLES]
Okay, so we ain't
a weII-oiIed machine yet.
But next time, we'II have a fieId day.
We are the League of Cats.
CATS:
We are the Ieague.
[SIGHS]
[ALL WHIMPERING]
[ALL LAUGHING AND CHEERING]
[WHISTLING]
Shh!
Don't whistIe tiII you see a mouse.
[BLOWS RASPBERRY]
What's wrong with you, cat?
There goes a mouse.
[WHISTLES]
Let's get him.
[SINGING] Like, when you're a cat
No mouse makes you sweat
[SINGING] It ain't like we're getting
A shot at the vet
[SINGING] When you're a mouse
No cats can compare
We'll hang you out to dry
In your underwear
[SINGING]
Like, no way you can do it
[SINGING] Cats, think twice
We ain't so nice
We're the League of Mice
Hey, Butch, I think we bIew it.
[CATS AND MICE GRUNTING]
[MO ANS]
WeII, boys, I toId you this pIace
wouId be Ioaded with mice.
[CHUCKLES]
TWO SHOES: WeII, this is certainIy
a fine how-do-you-do, isn't it, Thomas?
First, a heat wave that makes Death VaIIey
seem Iike a good idea for a vacation spot...
...and now our air conditioner
is on the fritz...
...so we can't even cooI the house down.
Maybe this wiII heIp.
My, my, Thomas. You read my mind.
We shouIdn't Iet aII this nice cooI air
go to waste, now, shouId we?
[PANTING]
[SIGHS]
Hey, thanks, bub.
TWO SHOES: Maybe we'II just take
a IittIe catnap right here and now.
What do you say?
But don't you go eating anything now.
[YAWNS]
TWO SHOES:
That's right.
[TWO SHOES YAWNS]
Just a IittIe....
[SIGHS]
[SNORING]
[TOM AND TWO SHOES
SNORING LOUDLY]
[GRUNTS]
[TWO SHOES SCREAMS]
TWO SHOES:
Thomas, what have you done?
What do you have to say for yourseIf?
[SNORES]
Don't pretend you were sIeeping,
Thomas.
''GuiIty'' is written aII over your face.
Oh, don't give me that Iook,
you naughty cat.
I know what you did.
Not so fast, mister.
Don't be trying to bIame it
on that IittIe mouse.
The onIy pIace a naughty cat
Iike you beIongs is outside.
[PANTING]
Huh?
[CHUCKLES]
[SIGHS]
[THUD]
[ANT SPITTING]
[WHISTLES]
[ENGLISH SDH]
[SNORING]
[GRO ANS]
[BLOWS RASPBERRY]
[GROWLS]
[BARKING]
[WHIMPERS]
That ain't footbaII. Hmph.
[MO ANS]
Hey!
[SCREAMS]
[MUTTERS THEN YAWNS]
[GRUNTS]
[GROWLS]
[BARKING]
[WHIMPERS]
[BLOWS RASPBERRY]
[TOM SPITS]
[JERRY WHISTLES]
[GIGGLES]
[WIND WHISTLES]
[GULPS]
[SNORES THEN SQUAWKS]
[GURGLING]
[YELLS]
[GRO ANING]
[JERRY WHISTLES]
[CLUCKS]
[GROWLS]
[SLURPS]
[SNIFFS]
[SCREAMS]
[SIGHS]
[BARKING]
[WHIMPERS]
[JERRY SINGING]
[GASPS]
[GRUNTING]
[SNORING]
[PANTING]
[GRUNTS]
[GROWLS]
[JERRY GRUNTS]
[YELLS]
Now, that's what I caII reaI footbaII.
ANNOUNCER [O VER SPEAKER] :
Yo, bros.
Take your boards and sign up
for the big surf competition today.
First place is a mondo-big pile of cash.
Second place wins a fabulous mystery prize.
Event sponsored
by Big Cheese of the High Seas.
[MUTTERING]
Surf's up.
[GRUNTS]
[DROOPY GRUMBLING]
Oh, dear, I hope I'm good enough
to win the surfing contest today.
You feIIows wanna watch me win?
[CHUCKLES]
[WOOD CRACKS]
[CROWD CHEERING]
ANNOUNCER: Time to hit those heavies.
Let the surf competition begin.
I think I'II change into something
a bit Iess constricting.
Get a Ioad of my baggies.
I Iike to shoot the curI in styIe.
[CHUCKLES]
[CROWD CHEERING]
ANNOUNCER: Oh, yes. The judges
should be stoked by such masterful ripping.
[DROOPY GRUNTS]
Whoa, check out cat dude
trying to hog the dog.
And he eats chowder.
[GASPS]
The judges will not dig such rude moves.
[CROWD JEERING]
Not too heinous.
Skillfully done, little Jer.
[CROWD CHEERING]
Okay, dudes and dudettes, heh,
time for the second heat.
[HORN BLOWS]
These are my doggers.
Heh, heh. Woof.
Now, don't distract me. I couId wipe out.
Whoa!
ANNOUNCER:
Low blow.
That is gonna cost you,
cat and mouse dudes.
And Jer is penalized
for bouncing off dog dude's head.
[CROWD JEERING]
The judges have decided
to give Droopy another go...
...without interference
from cat and mouse dudes.
[CHUCKLES]
[SQUAWKING]
Presto change-o.
[CROWD CHEERING]
ANNOUNCER:
Ha, check out dog dude walking the board.
Whoa, dude.
With scores like these, dog dude's
got a gnarly chance to win first place.
[CROWD CHEERING]
Now, the heat is on.
See who can catch the Droopster.
Whoa, this Tom cat's
sick with mad tricks.
We're seeing some history in the making,
ladies and gentle-dudes.
[BUO Y RINGING]
[CROWD CHEERING]
[HORN BLOWS]
This is little Jer's final run.
Let's see what mouse dude
can come up with.
-And it's crab city for cat dude.
-Ow!
[CHUCKLES]
[GRUMBLES]
ANNOUNCER:
Yo, bros. That was intense.
The votes are in.
And the winner
of the big piIe of cash is...
[CROWD CHEERING]
...Droopy.
Oh, goody.
BOTH:
AIoha, dudes.
ANNOUNCER:
Dude, two dogs?
Did not see that coming.
Oh, weII. Can't change the past.
And now for second pIace.
Tom has a one-point totaI
ahead of IittIe Jer.
He wins second pIace:
A Iifetime suppIy of cheese.
CompIiments of
Big Cheese of the High Seas.
Oh, think fast, mouse dude.
Just a IittIe parting gift.
Surf wax. Don't wipe it aII in one pIace.
[SNIFFS]
[GAGS]
[GRO ANS]
SPIKE:
Tyke, my dear oId son of mine.
Today's the day youse is gonna Iearn
how to pIay tennis.
[BARKING]
And I know somebody
to show you aII the ropes.
A reguIar tennis pro.
Now, ain't that nice?
Tom's resting up so he has the energy
to teach my son how to pIay tennis.
[GROWLS]
Now, now, Tykey.
So, cat, you're gonna teach my son a IittIe
something about this game of tennis?
WeII, you are the tennis pro.
I want you to teach my boy
everything there is to know about the game.
Got it?
We need a net.
Where's the rest of the court?
Tsk, tsk, tsk.
[JERRY GRUNTS]
And there's one more thing
you shouId know.
If you mess around with my boy,
it'II be the Iast thing that you do.
Got it?
[BLOWS RASPBERRY]
[BARKING]
[GAGS]
[GROWLS]
[YELLS]
You okay, my boy?
Now, you Iisten to me, cat.
I see any more funny business
going on with my boy, and I'II pound you.
And not onIy wouId I pound you...
...but I'II grab you
and pIant you in the court Iike so.
And then...
...I grab some of this.
Like so.
And then...
...I do this.
Which, of course,
wouId Iead me to do this.
But, of course, I don't wanna do that.
Now, do I?
[BARKING]
[GRUNTS]
No more funny business.
[SIGHS]
[BARKING]
[PANTING]
[WHIMPERS]
AII right, that's it.
So you wanna pIay rough
with my IittIe boy?
Then pIay rough it is.
It's my turn to serve.
Huh? Ooh!
Attaboy, Tyke.
I think you finaIIy got the hang of it.
[BARKING]
Okay, cat. Try this one on for size.
[SPIKE LAUGHING]
Hey, way to go, Tyke.
That's the way to hit him back.
Oh, good one. Keep it up, son.
Hey, you're gonna be a champ
in no time.
Subtitles by ARAVIND B
[by_agentsmith@yahoo.com]