AMBITIOUS
If you want to know, had this
Hucklberry problem with Finn.
I mean,
Li, and is good at everything.
The trip to America and everything.
But that only made me stop.
I had literature in the 1st period.
And I should mention the river,
was when I thought about it ...
... In a way not to stand still.
Hey, man, ever stolen anything before?
Not really, not a car.
Wait.
It's random I suppose, like everything else.
Stealing a car from someone?
Yeah, I mean, there may be an exchange.
How is Mercer?
As my friend Jason said
I could not have done.
Can I borrow your shirt?
Shit!
Shit! Shit! Shit!
Hello?
You do not look much like a thief.
I talk to?
With whom? It is my car and my
phone you are talking about ...
... And do not try to be polite, right.
Try not know,
sound crazy or rude.
I do garden work.
- Garden?
- To compensate.
When returning the car,
after the trip.
It has a trip?
Oh, Jesus Christ!
I have no garden, have a car.
Not only is the garden, I can do
other works of their choice.
No. Tell me, think that life is
random or is there fate?
Because these are
the two explanations.
What? Two explanations for what?
For you, Mercer.
Oh, shit, espaquete
're at the point, I must go.
- Wait. What?
- No, it hurts my poscoço say so.
You see? Not everyone can see.
You are the brother of Arlen.
You do not even look like him.
I mean, he is more
old Mexican.
The Latin.
There are so many countries there to
down is crazy.
He is my half-brother.
Is he here?
Nick. Ask Nick.
Nick should know.
Nick, a good guy. Well,
so good, you know.
The furnace of Nick in the city.
Want Candy?
Nick needs to sweets.
Nick likes to say, sweet.
Jesus Christ.
Come with me?
- I?
- Yes, come.
You are the brother of Arlen?
Tell him that this is
for accessories.
- Fuck, fuck.
- What happened?
Hurt the fuck out of my hand.
- Ahh! Why did this?
- He is the brother of Arlen.
- I know. Honey, come here.
- Son of a bitch.
I'll bring ice. We have a
first aid kit.
Come. No.
Arlen stole ...
Arlen stole a toolbox
that belonged to my father ...
... Who had a game
accessories for 50 years.
Moreover, not finished
wood oven tunnel ...
... That was the reason I bring it here
and taught to burn the pots.
This is where Mary said
he is.
Reno?
You're doing a building,
Mary said.
Came a postcard last year.
Reno is near Fallon?
I know a girl
Fallon, Nevada.
When was the last time
who saw the Arlen?
I was five, he 23.
He is 18 years older than me.
So you do not know?
It is probably best
the long term.
I was Buddhist, but still
love everyone.
Except that's fucked Arlen.
Let's eat.
If you want, you can stay
here a little.
Working in Anagami,
earn some money.
We still have to dig
the damn thing.
There are some beautiful girls.
Mary makes paella.
Seriously, it's better to know
The Arlen, believe me.
My father said: "If you do not know where you are
going, you better stop where you are. "
- Never smoked marijuana.
- It's nice.
Does anyone know if Reno
Fallon is near?
I know a girl who studied the
secondary to me, in Fallon, Nevada.
Oh, God, it's nice to feel hungry.
Right? Hungry.
He is. It has a watermelon festival there ...
... Fallon is near Reno.
Melon has a delicious flavor.
Once we got to 50 ...
... Provo to Reno with my mom
camping in the Great Basin ...
... Where she got giardia,
which is not fun.
Thought it was going to shit all over the place.
She prayed to God!
Not funny.
Not funny. It was a
semester without teaching.
My mother was the
substitute teacher.
Really? Where is she now?
- Maybe he did not want to talk about this.
- Oh, no, okay.
Okay, my mother is ...
My mother competes in races
sled dogs in Fairbanks.
No way! With dogs and whips?
- Has its own brand of lashes.
- Really?
Oh, God!
No, no. In fact,
she is dead.
- Really it is.
- With the dogs running behind.
- Dead.
- No.
- No, it's a substitute teacher dead.
She's hot.
- Your mother?
The girl in Fallon. It would be perfect
take it to Reno.
If you ... If you ...
If you missed female companionship.
That is something ...
That is something I ...
Let me give you something that Arlen did.
- Maybe this old pot ..
- He is my half brother.
And I feel that he has stolen
the accessories of his father ...
... Especially if they were memories
of his father. I feel.
But take it easy with Arlen, right?
Why, I mean, he might
may be a thief,
but his mother, our mother,
he does not know yet.
Still do not know, and have passed
eight months and a half.
Already spent eight and a half months.
If I could tell him.
I do not know, I do not know,
'd be all over.
The bullet went through the nape of the
Sheriff knocking down the horse.
The blood ran down her lips
when Carlson took the Winchester.
End of tape 2.
Insert tape 3.
Chapter December
"A man must have his tricks
Cowboy "Leroy said,
"A pair of cowboy tricks
for when cooler breeze. "
"A wind colder than this?"
Carlson said.
Leroy Carlson liked.
Leroy was the only one not
was against him.
To the piano ...
Hello?
Yes, I know, sorry.
We were measuring the target
with coincidence
the meaning of life and had to
out because of the spaghetti.
- How do you know my name?
- Where are you?
- I do not know who you are.
- It's fine for now, Mercer.
You have the car.
You can read the road.
- You gave my name to the police?
- No, no police.
- What does it mean?
- I talked to my mother yesterday.
She thinks I should
call the police.
But I make a proposal. You turn
to me and tell me your trip.
This is the agreement that I propose.
For me it's fair enough.
Well now you're thinking:
Who is this girl?
What's wrong with her?
She must be crazy.
No, sorry. Sad in a chair ...
... With cats.
Cats? No, crosswords.
A crossword puzzle ...
crosswords and tea.
No, beer.
Beer, it is ... strong?
Think you are strong. But not so.
Imagine the young. No, older.
Imagine it with false teeth.
- Do you really know?
- Do you think about fate?
- How everyone.
- Do not like cooked spaghetti too.
- It's fun. Are you funny?
- I tend to be.
- When you call me, alone?
Hello?
Hi, this message is for Joely.
It's Mercer.
We studied together in
high school in Eugene.
And I'll be in Reno,
Fallon, in fact,
and you know, I'll tell you later.
I have a car.
Mom works with
real estate exposure.
So we pretend that we are sisters and
help when it is a single guy.
Not that something very serious happens.
Just to mess with them, but ends
selling many, many houses.
My cousin Buddy goes here.
We bought beer and see the cracks.
I used to read e-mails with Mom.
she said
"This market is ambitious."
"It's nice?" Just saying.
You're taller now.
- My fingers are swollen.
- What have to take the rings?
They gave me a lotion, I think.
- What was it?
- School Receptionist?
You will ... Will go to ...
School receptionist, in
next summer in Tucson.
Moby recommended this.
Moby.
Moby?
Mom and I were with her in
backstage at Tahoe Oakland.
She is a wonderful person.
As a person, you know?
You can read and know immediately.
Yes, it is a skill that has.
Then you will see your brother?
In Reno, it is.
- I was wondering ...
- So we go to Reno?
... If you want to come to Reno.
Sorry to move both.
I shaved down there and can burn.
Sorry. Oh, sorry.
Hey, what are you doing?
I'm not sure, ma'am.
Never done before?
What?
St. Ecstasys.
No, it tasted a lot.
Only marijuana and morphine.
- Wow, this thing is too ...
- It takes 90 minutes.
Yeah, he does.
- Do you have any lotion?
- What?
- Lotion?
- Or an ointment.
- What kind?
- What?
- What kind of ointment?
As a jelly. Something that uses
in marital relationships.
- Petroleum jelly?
- No, no, no. No, this.
- Yes, exactly, Vaseline.
- This helps you get the rings?
Yes, ask the nurse.
And ask for another pillow.
- Sure.
- Tell her.
Yes.
My ... My mother is ...
Mrs. White Room 28.
She's um ... is dead.
Needless to say, Joely,
how much I love you.
I mean the details
My love for you.
Starting with your kind heart,
Joely and her ass,
your ass so beautiful.
You're so brave,
but so brave.
- And I see where you shaved.
- Why not take an orange juice?
Do you think that would be fine if we
sex with each other?
- Definitely will.
- It would be my first time.
Should I say this?
Can not talk now.
So what should be that way.
Tomatoes, cherry tomatoes.
You should eat raw.
They say, fructose, fructose!
Washington, Adams, Jefferson.
Madison, Monroe, Adams,
Jackson, Van Buren.
Harrison, Tyler ... Tyler.
Fuck my pussy hot.
Fucked the Fillmore!
- Sorry.
- No.
No. ..
declined.
No, okay.
Okay.
You're so wonderful.
We can try again later.
I love you.
Where did you get the shirt
car washer?
My friend J, was in
test your bandwidth.
- You are not in the band?
- No.
Have you ever thought that people do
bands to feel like shit?
Yes Where are you now?
- Reno.
- Reno does not seem his style.
- How do you know?
- I just know.
Yeah, you're right, I guess.
- You're not playing?
- No.
I'm just looking for someone.
Hello, I'm Sergio Leone. It is not my
real name, obviously.
- I am here to ...
- I know.
Among please feel free.
You can wait in the living room.
Hear that?
- Do you think you begin?
- Shut up, shut up.
Friend, fuck, seriously.
His first time on this also?
Probably, yes.
Have you seen the masks?
- Masks?
- You know? I mean ...
- They taste at all, right?
- Shut the fuck that mouth.
Like to do anal?
Arlen has lived
here a year ago.
But honestly, the
pornography was his idea.
And the credit belongs to those who deserve credit.
I had a rebirth
spiritual underground.
Arlen said that would achieve a
camera, capturing the human connection.
And accept the rewards
as they pass ...
... Like bears and salmon.
Have you read Rumi? The human river
which never ceases,
you and I are one. For this thought
in rubber masks.
Will see, using a mask ...
A normal guy ...
face the camera ...
... And protect his identity.
And as the identity,
what consciousness is.
Can you give me the tape
adhesive. Just play.
Even boys who had
came to lose her virginity.
It powers.
But without masks
for women.
We need the groans.
Pain has its own energy.
So things are.
- What?
- Laurel.
Damn sleazy,
we had a deal.
Laurel!
Arlen never wanted to do
love with these girls.
I do not know why, I am not
owner of the mystery.
You do not look Mexican.
He is my half-brother.
I've seen him with this young
West Sacramento.
It has an animal house
she managed.
She is older than him too ...
... Which can be comfortable.
If you see Arlen, say no
I will complain.
I guess he needs the
more money than me.
I was angry,
was disappointed.
But so is America,
Our American River.
This lens holds the current
American eye.
I have to go help that
young people to relax.
What good is it,
weeping before the fuck.
Mr. Gorbachev,
tear down this wall.
It's a little disappointing
never be pursued.
It is officially a
crime spree?
If I knew what it was for this
camera, I think they stole.
- Whose?
- From a friend of my brother.
- Did your brother?
- I'm trying to find.
I do not know, it seems
is not the best.
Some things would have heard
killed my mother, if possible.
His mother died?
Yes.
That's what I have to tell him.
Sorry.
It's just you and your father?
My father? No, I do not know my father.
Who you are now?
A French teacher, and his
family. Put them nervous.
If you do not watch TV, put
people nervous.
You're in a swimming pool?
Yes, something like that.
What is your age?
I'm 19, but probably
already know this.
I saw your glasses for near,
know how old people.
I am an old person.
I hope you do not mind,
because I wear your glasses.
- Sometimes I think I need glasses.
- What's mine is yours.
Try the pepper spray.
Oh, well, I thought it was a
asthma inhaler.
I was worried about you.
Kind of you.
It's nice to know that someone
cares about you.
But I'm fine, Mercer.
I'm 24.
Hey, you.
Hey, you bring the food
in here, son.
Hey! Hey, Mercer.
This is my cousin Buddy and he is the Rid.
We were just waiting for you.
- This kid is going to lead us in Mojave?
- Getting where?
Reid and Buddy are building
a stock car for a long time ...
... In a junkyard in the Mojave that is
Reid's friend, so it is free.
They are euphoric and
're nice guys.
And it is basically ready,
then I said it would take
in Mojave to get it.
So let's go, shall we?
Yes Mojave is near Sacramento?
- Arlen maybe Sacramento.
- No, no, I mean is to the south.
Come on, is not it?
A short drive?
Do not want to try again?
We have to pack.
It was the best part of the west
Carlson heard them say.
Where can achieve
away from people.
You are more free than
had ever been.
In the west you could drop
things where they fell.
Where he got this camera?
I do not know, just a camera.
Has tea that shit?
It is a drug effect. All
camera has this shit?
It is tied into it, darling.
Someone should make a movie
long with this effect.
We will do our
own movie at the hotel.
Now drop this camera.
- Yes, fuck.
- Oh, shit, do it again.
It's great.
Let's look into what is done.
How's your mother?
It was always weird.
It is my mother ... it looks good.
Is doing his ritual walk.
His what?
She is the Australian desert,
doing ritual walk.
What is a ritual walk?
It's like a barmitzvah.
- Jewish?
- No.
You're not religious?
My mother was religious.
She was from Pointe Coupee Parish,
Louisiana. There are all Catholics.
She was kind of hippie.
With all the boyfriends, and I had
when he was older, by 45.
But went to church every week
St. Mary.
He spoke of it with you, in the end?
God, or things like that?
No. In the end I was unconscious.
All I could do was clean his
those with long mouth swabs.
I never said this to anyone.
People have deposit
calcium, tongue and mouth.
... When they are dying.
And the nurses gave me
swabs to clean,
like she cared,
anyway.
Not much fun, but you do.
What else could I do?
Smells ... Kate smells so bad,
could never tell you.
You know my name?
Yes, I found your gym bag,
and his YMCA card.
Found my bag
gym? Where were you?
It was behind where the
spare tire should be.
I'll be back with everything.
Can you show me the trip,
now that you have a camera.
Yes, I suppose I should
shooting things.
Scenario! Not within what.
If you could do a film if
all we could do a movie.
- What film would perhaps?
- A French film, my own.
Ends dancing, no
good reason, just for dancing.
There would be two dancing?
Three.
That sounds cool.
So I think one should do
movie with people dancing.
Yeah, I do not know.
I think people
dislike more.
What's happening?
Just got out of my way, I
finding my brother Arlen.
Hey, will not do it, buddy.
I got out of my way.
No.
Hey! Hey!
I must find my brother Arlen.
- What are you doing, drop it.
- We should go.
- I must find my brother.
- Bring him to the room?
- Stop, I must find my brother.
- Come in, motherfucker.
Everything will be alright,
her mother will return.
Australia.
I know how. Be different.
- No.
- By God.
- Fuck.
- I must find my brother.
- Okay.
- Can not get the car.
- It's not my car.
- Well, the car is whose?
It's my girlfriend.
You have a girlfriend?
Fuck.
Honey, go to the car.
You're so selfish.
Do not do it, kid.
Do not fuck with the heart of Buddy.
He is very strong,
but not like this.
Do not try to enter
contact with him. No.
Do you feel that sometimes too early
or too late for everything?
As my mom said that people
sing and chatter all the time.
Just because they want to. I
weird that.
Yeah, I had to leave
school last year ...
... To help my mother to die.
- All my friends graduated.
- You know the Irish song?
My mother used to
sing to me.
No, how?
Shit! Shit! I think
the battery is running low.
Plug it into the cigarette lighter.
Is in the car?
Kate, you should say something to you.
- You have a girlfriend?
- No, no.
It's just that I strayed a bit here e. ..
Hey? Hey?
Kate?
Not far away, you say?
Mojave?
80 kilometers.
I'll tell you something.
Someone who goes in my car arrives.
What's on your mind?
See my brother, Arlen.
- They are close?
- Yes
Good
When traveling either alone or
forget the people who have.
I am a seller of liquor.
And you?
No, I am employed.
Meet a man with his clothes
hanging in the back seat,
that can tell you two
things about the loneliness.
The first thing I can say is,
that does not result in anything.
This shit lone ranger,
is false as Christmas.
My blood turned into gasoline.
The other thing that can
say is, protection.
If you have to be on the road.
Arlen probably told you
about carrying weapons.
Traveling in your car,
probably has a pocket.
I mean, I think
prefer the same.
Do not want to meddle in
Arlen told you that, but ...
I have my own ideas ...
about protection
Use of weapons in almost
cost our country.
That's Protection!
Lord Jim Corbett. Type bull Mills
fists to fight.
Protection that was born with it.
Natural protection,
... As Jesus and globules
white blood.
You know what I have
pride in Mojave?
To take the bull by the tail
as before.
Before America forget how.
And who else would know
pride? His brother.
There were times when Carlson
wanted to ride alone.
Could use another shooter.
Carlson threw to first
his father taught IHE ...
... And went straight into the ear of the sheriff.
Someone attacked her from behind and Carlson
staggered, but it was unbreakable.
While Carlson staggered avoided
twice the sickle with his arm.
Give the boy his hat.
You actually do not
has a brother, do you?
No and yes.
Nobody taught you to fight?
I should have said. I never sent
a man to fight ...
... To see him lose his hat.
I have my ideas about fighting, but
need tools to live.
I can not give you this, would give.
My parents gave me the
my confirmation.
Get a knife for you ...
... To anyone
take off your hat.
Do you like novels
cowboys in particular?
He listened to the cd the book?
Yes, half. I
the tape two or three.
You can hear the rest when you return.
Right.
I was considering
something that I do not know.
Yes, I know, I mean ...
... I think people would like,
but really want to know ...
... What your dog and
your cat think?
- Yes, I did not want this power?
- No.
And if they were so disappointing
like humans ...
... And not think of anything.
And just think where they would
to college.
- And where would a second option.
- Once, I talked to a squirrel.
I was just walking alone
and saw a bush ...
... And I said:
Hey, how's it going?
And he said "Ee-ee-ee."
So I said, "Need
something like a juice or milk? "
And he said
"Aa-aa-aa".
What kind of ice cream do you like?
What kind of ice cream?
Yes, if I had to choose
a taste right now.
I do not know if I have one.
I'll let you think about it.
I go to bed now.
When you go back?
Very soon, I think.
I'm done with Joely.
Who is Joely?
Joely is a girl?
No. Well, yes.
I mean, yes.
It's a girl, but not so.
Forgiveness should not.
I in the west
Sacramento tomorrow.
Arlen meets a girl there that
Hal works in the shop's Pet.
I mean, it's not a girl,
is a woman.
Arlen is like me, like
older women.
Hello?
Wait a friend. I'm trying
Mangione catch the wave.
- Do you understand?
- Wait.
We have no public restroom
dear. Try the Winchells.
Oh, no. I'm looking for
Arlen White.
Oh fucked me!
There was Scott.
He heard the name of Arlen and
just thought the police.
... And this is what happens when
on parole, believe me.
Scott is a boy, anyway.
Hey, you sing?
- So Arlen is not here?
- Fuck! No.
Arlen it was when we were arrested.
Hi! Welcome to Hal's Pet.
Oh, there's a little problem with ...
... Filled with two checks
at odds with the law ...
... And some of us are free
conditional. Want to relax?
- No.
- Breakfast? It's important. Well
Arlen was nervous and went to L.A.
This is the number he gave me,
but I had left into it.
... Because it's so traditional that Arlen.
He likes it:
"One man, one woman."
And I: "Put that damn Holmes
and hands on my body. "
- Choose and then choose, right?
- Right.
Right? No seriously, my dear,
can sing?
- Because it is Arlen L.A. ..
- This is the deal.
The condition of our freedom is
make this community service
Christian songs and stories
idiots daycare.
And you just
scaring our singer.
- You want me in your band?
- No, not a band.
Yeah, you want the band.
- You know songs?
- I know some, yes.
Wait a minute, you do not
is a religious fanatic?
Because, well never mind. Forget it.
I can not choose.
- Dutch will give you a jacket.
- You are number 40?
- I have to ...
- Last chance.
- No, thanks.
- Right.
What?
I've never been in a band before.
There is a band are 140 hours
community service.
While this world.
Full of demons.
Threatens our faith.
Not fear
Because God wants.
His real triumph for us.
Wow, that was great.
Can you give me the jacket
and the drum? Um, guys?
Sure, what do we do?
Guys?
This part is not for you,
honey. Let there e. ..
... Is a thing of the band.
But there were great.
Gave people what they
wanted, God, cream cheese.
It was brilliant. Who are you?
It is my lifeline.
But it's over for you.
Hear me, tell Arlen ...
... You tell Arlen still
keep praying for him.
Hey!
Hey! This is my car!
Is it?
It's your car?
- How did you know where?
- Hal's Pet said ...
... In Sacramento, idiot.
Now give me the keys to the door.
- Already have the ignition.
- Sorry.
- Give me the keys.
- Kate, I'm sorry for the girl, Joely.
I do not care about that, just
I want my car back.
Damn thief, give me the keys.
- Give me that fucking key.
- Nothing happened really.
It will be my first time.
You lied to me e. ..
I thought I knew ...
one to the other e. ..
... And nobody knows
no one in the end?
I stink, my body.
No, you're not.
We just talk about
lies, just now.
Sure, you stink. I noticed.
You're an idiot, idiot. idiot.
But I liked the sound of your voice.
This person is a great explorer?
Oh, you're very bad at this game.
Fifteen questions and do not know if it is
a man or a woman, yet.
I have my methods that can
unless the methods of its staff
No, it's a great explorer.
Set me.
What?
It is the machine again.
Hi, this is a message
for Arlen.
It's your brother, I think, I left you ...
I called earlier and left
a cell phone number.
It might ask you to call me?
Thank you.
It was good.
What is this? It's horrible.
I do not know what it is.
It's not a Big Mac burger.
Can I prove it?
I'm divorced.
We were very young and
people lie to you ...
... And confuse everything.
Lied at the university and when
Cirillo worked in the kitchen.
It is a restaurant affiliate
the Humble Bagel.
Yeah, I used to go to Humble Bagel
always after school.
I know. I saw you.
So, when I stole your car?
You recognize me?
Yes, but not the whole story.
There's something not
I can tell you now.
Kate, you're not?
You're okay, right?
You're not sick or
dying or something?
No! No, I'm fine.
I used to go biking through the streets of
Amazon to work every day.
I love to cook.
Worked 1 to 12 hours with these
weird faces, faces criminal.
And I was, um ...
Tendonitis and smelled ...
rancid butter.
And was very happy
with it, too.
And my hands are like steel.
You can burn them and not feel anything.
All those knives and blood.
As we had no brain.
The kitchen looked like a brain.
And it was really nice.
It was the dream I had tonight.
Maybe you had too.
I could pass through
our feet.
Carlson left a little Brands
before he gets there,
... Back to the crossroads.
Rid never understood why
Carlson wanted to be alone.
Reid had never lost anyone before,
and it still had hope.
For Carlson was from
a shortcut and a shield.
The more you leave,
unless you lose.
Hi! Hi, I'm calling for Arlen.
With Arlen.
Could you please ...
No English?
Is he there?
Is calling.
Well, she seemed very angry.
I do not know, just be polite.
Do not yell, bitch! Let me know
White is Arlen is there.
It's not there.
He said he split his
older sister, hell!
He said he likes to fuck
older chickens.
Seriously, I need your help.
Try to be nice.
Love, not my dick
Whatever your age,
Can I help you down there.
Totally disgusted. Said
I have no dick.
- I dig this girl.
- Please.
Alright, alright.
Sure, my sky ... I'll call you
when this boy has gone,
So you know ...
when they come here.
But for now, tell me
Arlen is there?
Hotel Las Rosas.
The sister who was with Arlen
Aromatherapy makes this hotel.
Where?
Ensenada.
- Ensenada, Mexico?
- The hotel is in Ensenada, Mexico?
- Right.
- Mexico.
Call you in five minutes
have a conversation.
- Do you know where I can sell a camera?
- Now?
Passing MacArthur Park
Best Liquor opposite is true.
Need something else?
Why I call this chicken
soon, I need tea to ten.
Without offending his brother.
Who is it?
Someone else used the camera.
- Will you be selling?
- Yes,
Hey, we're talking
right now.
Actually, no.
It has something to say?
No, I thought maybe we could
play 20 questions.
Hey, kid, can not come here.
This is not a good hotel.
Go.
Arlen?
What?
No, no.
No, I ...
How'd you find me?
I have no money.
No, I. ..
Arlen, did not come for money.
Mom sent you here
for me to help.
- Arlen.
- What?
Raise you?
That bitch was crazy?
Where were you?
It did not take care of me.
Why should I care for you?
He's just a kid away from home
attempting to enter the hotel!
Do not want your hat, cowboy?
Hey, Cowboy!
His hat.
Cowboy.
Beats kid!
Bate. Bate.
Bate.
Okay. Chat!
Hey, you okay?
Feel, feel.
There's blood in the face ...
Need Help?
Coming.
The courtyard entrance is around the corner ...
here we have an infirmary.
Can I?
Cowboy.
You're so selfish.
There's something out there.
Think about it.
This is ...
Fructose.
Mercer.
No! I'll tell you.
Are you okay?
You found me.
Yes, the number still
was on the phone.
That girl told me
where you could be.
I thought we were
traveling together.
Jesus!
What is this thing?
Books e. .. Books and ash.
Want to disperse them here?
No.
Louisiana.
Two cousins ??who still have there,
in Pointe Coupee Parish,
The sister of my mother.
I thought ...
... If he found the Arlen,
maybe it was me there
but ...
If ...
What?
If it was not just because
I recognized you.
I let my take
car because I thought ...
... That could be a sign.
Because ...
I not only ...
... Used to see him at the restaurant.
I liked you.
And I had ...
... Had a ...
... Had this fantasy with you.
Dividiríamos that an ice cream.
We would ask for a double ice cream
mint chocolate and coffee ...
... And we would sit in Thugman ...
Dividiríamos ... and ice cream.
It's just that?
This is all a. ..
No, it was not. It was not
all fantasy.
But then, when I saw you
the car wash,
... And saw him sitting in my car
you seemed to fit him.
And I just ...
... Wanted to go out driving with you ...
the Dari Mart
or to wander.
Just someone to wander.
Kate wants to go to Louisiana with me?
This is my car.
I know. But even if it was not.
What did I do?
I just have to go to the bathroom.
You better take your clothes off.
It Fillmore, Fillmore, you bastard.
Pierce, Buchanan, Lincoln,
murder, emancipation.
Grant, Hayes, Garfield, Arthur.
What?
How did it happen?
He moved to the liver, but
began with lung cancer.
- Are you fucking me?
- No.
Spent eight and a half months,
almost nine.
Nine months.
Jesus.
I, you know.
Everything I said would not.
Sorry, I was an idiot.
It's funny, the things that
want to leave out. know?
Have you ever had a friend who
started a band e. ..
It was only his friend, and then began
a band and you were not there?
Yeah, always wanted to be in a band.
My friend Billy Kleinsasser,
started a band a year.
What if you could learn drums
I would be on it.
And I said to my mother, she had just
have you, and was with her boyfriend.
His father, what's his name?
- Ted something.
- Well, the old Ted fucked
Said it would be a lot of noise
for the baby.
What is a pile of manure, because
Babies do not care about anything.
It was just for him.
He never lived there, but Mom
I was in love with him.
It was not that.
I mean, I do not know.
She wanted to try something better
with you, you know.
You were a second chance.
Whenever someone tries to make a
band makes us feel like shit.
I have to return to the office.
- I have the ashes of the mother.
- No, no, no, no, no.
Do not take this fucking thing here,
Please. Could lose my job.
No, no.
I'll take them.
Kate and I will take them
Pointe Coupee Parish.
Just wanted to know if I wanted.
No, no.
I. ..
No, seriously, just let me know.
'll Buy one
Pay-per-view or something.
Hey, take care. Louisiana is like
a 3rd world country.
Okay, I have one.
It is your personal life?
Is it?
He is a man?
+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+
+ |T|h|e| |D|e|a|f| |B|o|y|s| |F|o|r| |B|o|y|s| |G|r|o|u|p|  +
E N J O Y   this   SRT   SUBTITLE   R e l e a s e
http://www.imdb.com/title/tt0479289
The Go-Getter (2007) English.srt
FPS: 23.976
+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+
+ |T|h|e| |D|e|a|f| |B|o|y|s| |F|o|r| |B|o|y|s| |G|r|o|u|p|  +
We want more subtitles right NOW!
1) All DVDs to be subtitled
2) All VIDEO GAMES to be subtitled
3) All videos/DVDs used in lessons at school to be subtitled
4) More pre-recorded & live subtitles on TV
____           __            ___   __              ___          __               __
/     /   _   /    )  _   _ (_     /  _)        _  (_      _     /  _)        _   / _   _
(     /)  (-   /(_ /  (-  ( /  /     /(_)  () (/ _)   /   () /      /(_)  () (/ _)   (__)  /  () (/  /)
/                                /                        /