Hey, let's order some clubs this weekend?
No club, Ace.
It is a hut in the middle of nowhere.
And do not forget this.
Sorry Jason.
I hope there is enough clean sheets.
Yeah. As if they stayed clean long.
I take a few more washed, just in case.
You will finally tell me who you invited?
Okay.
It's too late for you to affect the plans,
I invited a kind of my office
called Mac
It is a kind of computers.
Hot?
Warm.
A bit shy.
I think this will be good for him.
It will help you get out.
Your turn Coop.
I invited Kevin.
My yoga instructor.
You do yoga?
Yes, I do yoga.
I have to keep in shape for my boy.
So hurray for yoga.
Maybe he gives us a lesson this weekend weekend.
Yoga nudist.
What?
He teaches yoga nudist.
This is so exciting.
I think not.
Who will be your guest, kid?
It will be a surprise.
He continues to not tell me.
Neither Simon.
Idiot secretive, right?
No.
Simon is an open book.
Simon.
Yes
Are you sure you want me to go?
Again?
I'm serious.
What's the end of this weekend?
I told you...
All weekends are long weekends like this.
Jason and I are going with his friend,
Cooper and her boyfriend at the moment
the same place, the same conversations.
Blah... Blah... Blah...
It seems boring.
And it is!
Is why we decided to shake things up.
This end-of-week, four of us,
each invites a friend to go.
The matchmakers do?
Something.
It should be funny.
Or at least different.
God! I'm ready for different.
And are you sure you want me to be your guest?
Just do not tell Jason to the frequency with which you see.
You have the strangest in an open relationship I've ever seen.
Open is one thing, my dear Andrew.
You're another.
Wait.
These are the directions to get to the hut.
Do not be late.
Yes, sir.
This is for today.
E. .. ah...
This is the three days of the end-of-week.
It's a business can take pleasure.
END-OF-WEEK LONG
Fuck!
Do not worry,
I take the bag.
This is the most incredible site ever!
You think he likes?
I'm not sure.
Kids today are difficult to understand.
That door is my space.
Look, there's a fireplace!
My room usual?
Ready and waiting for you.
We stayed with the fourth corner.
What do you mean "we were"?
We were!
As if it were him and had taken?
Do not be ridiculous, I just said...
He'll think we were the best
quarter only because we have first.
We are always.
Is not the issue.
Hello Mac
Hello, this is Cooper.
Cooper this is the Mac, my colleague.
Nice to meet you.
You too.
This is my boyfriend, Ace.
Hello
I put my things in the room with double beds.
Can it be?
Are great.
But you'll have to share it with someone.
Okay.
The Cameroon snoring.
Who is Cameroon?
Is my friend.
Yet arrived. We were roommates in college.
And though he moved to the city.
I thought this would be fun for him.
But man... he snores like a fucking train.
He is in the small room.
And someone will have to sleep on the couch.
Share with whoever comes next.
I open.
Namaste, my friend.
There is tremendous energy here.
This will be a weekend of wonderful weekend and plainly in public.
Even if I do not know any of you.
We enjoy ourselves immensely.
Namaste.
I'm Kevin.
You have an amazing aura.
A haunting?
Well...
Roommates perfect.
So...
We met in freshmen over the course of art history.
History of Art?
Hey! I am a boy enduncado.
Once we went to an art exhibition,
It was so annoying.
Totally in the face.
He could not take the face of graphic images.
Did not believe what he saw, was going to vomit.
On what was the exposure?
Orchids, flowers binding of Georgia
So I ended up making fun of him outside the exhibition.
Best friends since then.
Is darling.
It helped a lot, know ourselves, when I came to town.
Despite being married.
"Married" can be a bit strong.
I do not think.
Look at the sky.
Can you feel this as strength to your back?
You say I say Cosmo Cosmos
and quickly.
This place reminds me of that movie.
"Friday 13th"?
Hopefully not.
Tell them what it is.
Native Americans have suffered so much.
"The Boys in the Band"?
No. It was a musical.
O God
"Love! Valor! Compassion"?
That's it!
Anything but that.
I will not use a tutu.
No. ..
a group of guys...
a cabin in the woods...
pass the end-to-week.
Yes A group of guys who do not like each other,
full of arrogance, sleeping around,
E. ..!
dying with AIDS.
We can not do this to this weekend?
I saw this movie was a classic product of its time.
Thank God that time is over.
I do not think you have said that.
Here we go again!
Accepts! We saw always the same in all movies gay.
They were either noble victims of AIDS, or angry
with AIDS, or friends of victims of AIDS.
Yes, because it was the main problem that our
community was facing at the time. Still is.
We really want our legacy
film are stories about death?
They always have the same discussion every six months.
At least there is a legacy, not better
a betrayal of the suffering of gays,
brought the total absence of gays in movies?
And Jason will respond with:
At least in the movies gay current
That suck!
That is not the point.
At least cover a wide range of topics in general.
No!
He's right!
I rent lots of movies. I mean...
Plenty of movies.
And it's true.
AIDS is a milestone in gay cinema for a long time.
But now we have gay romantic comedies, and.
documentaries about the struggle for equal rights...
and horror movies, and any other topic you like.
I think it's a good thing.
But it decreases where we, our history, and that includes...
films of the past, films about the
death and the struggles of our community.
What I say is that I prefer the "Longtime Companion"
this Ethan Green to make gay.
Everything I say...
do I need another beer.
Aid to the barbecue?
There was a request.
Never heard you speak so passionately
about an issue before.
You?
No.
Do not.
But thanks for asking.
When you reach a certain age, and is
with a particular aspect, assume all soon.
You have friends who are?
Too many.
The Daddy exercises even.
No. ..
... call him that!
Just me is that I can call it that.
Man still can not believe you are with an old man.
He is not old!
It...
mature.
This is your kind now?
He is not a "type".
It...
It makes me feel like...
Oh .. No!
You do not understand.
He is the one.
I've been to this before.
It was in college.
It was a stage, nothing more.
Why you do not expect the granddaddy go to sleep...
and sneak up to my room?
It is time to Mecca.
I do not think Cam
I never slept with anyone else since I met Cooper.
How long ago was this?
A year ago.
Are you monogamous now?
Do you like it?
I love it.
So... how do you know each other?
The Jason rented a room in my guesthouse.
When he moved to the city.
You have a guest house?
Easy!
It is rented.
A landlord.
So... mature.
I think your friend will not come.
I do not understand what happened.
I spoke with him this morning.
Already here it should be.
So what are the plans for tonight?
That's it.
How about a movie?
No!
A dip in the jacuzzi at night?
It's too cold!
I brought sunscreen creams and skin.
I was expecting a crazy night in the desert...
not...
Exactly.
Tranquility?
Whatever.
We chose this place to escape to the clubs and the crowds.
When you're a little older...
you will enjoy.
It reminds me of where I grew up.
And as I left.
Have you ever tried to do yoga?
No!
I thought about it...
but a bit intimidating when you do not know what you're doing.
Did not want anyone...
judge me.
I can teach you.
Without judging.
Seriously
Bright!
It's what I do.
Share with others, help them relax.
Relax.
I could use.
OK
Tomorrow.
You and I, private yoga class.
Deal.
It must be my friend.
How did you two meet, anyway?
It comes from a long time.
I hope he does not mind sleeping on the couch.
People...
this is...
André!
Andrew?
Hello everybody.
You convidaste a prostitute?
Jason!
For our cabin...
a whore!
A rent boy!
No one calls them that.
Not the subject, I know.
It was supposed that somebody knew what he does in life.
How could I guess that our friends...
They pay someone to fuck with them?!?
You sit for a moment?
We agreed early in our relationship,
we could sleep with others.
I know!
And we did it!
Both did.
We do not talk about it.
And do not bring them home. Never at home!
Technically, this is not our home.
It's as if you wanted to rub in my face...
or worse... show me what I am not!
It is not like that.
You do not understand.
Try it!
I do not have many friends...
even my friends...
those who have also interact,
and you know how my work
nothing but a group of women in middle age,
who just want to municipalities in their meetings Mach.com.
There was no one else to invite.
I had to pay someone to be my friend this weekend to weekend.
You could have told me.
I wish I had done so.
So... extent to which this well know Andrew?
It was a long time.
How long?
Before you being more likely.
He must have started early then.
How much does he charge?
We are neighbors is how long?
Three years?
Yes! I'm on top and below it.
In my building. He lives on top.
Sure.
All beds are occupied.
You'll have to sleep on the couch.
Okay.
I've slept in worse places.
Who wants another drink?
I think we are not allowed friends of lovers in the house.
Or boyfriends who do not bring me a drink are not my friends.
Wow
You are even comfortable with the history of nudity.
Thou?
Well!
Not really.
You should be. Everyone should.
Is what is most natural.
If you are not comfortable in your own skin
and waits to be with someone else?
Hello
We will....
look at the stars.
Goodbye.
You have everything you need?
Yes.
Thank you.
I. .. really regret it.
The fault is not yours.
Simon talks about you constantly.
Seriously?
Funny!
He never mentioned you.
I heard you.
What?
I heard you say the name of Andrew when he appeared.
This...
Not have to be ashamed.
I'm not.
Just...
well... I am mortified.
When I moved here, I...
not know where to meet people,
was not frequenter of clubs, e. ..
and most of the staff of the clubs was not interested in me.
Do not despise yourself.
Believed. I do not.
Is how things are.
So...
I... was watching one of those...
local gay magazines, e. ..
I saw the announcement of Andrew...
and thought it might be a good way to...
You understand.
Learn...
what they liked.
And you get it?
Largely.
Nothing of value judgments, remember?
'm Not doing.
What is it?
Your aura.
There is so much confidence in it.
But it has been pushed by fear.
Scared of what?
I'm not sure yet.
Yes?
Still awake?
Yes!
Busy?
A bit.
Do you need a hand?
Maybe.
But I must warn you...
I'm broke.
Okay.
The first time is on the house.
My God!
I wish I had their energy at this time of morning.
Someone is feeling her age today?
I did not sleep enough last.
Funny!
I slept well.
Jesus!
You are still arguing?
No. Of course not.
Do not be silly.
A bagel?
I'll see if Kevin and Mac have already agreed.
God! Give him a chance!
It was the worst thing he ever did.
But it is very close.
It seems that you two have more in common for someone besides me.
Do not be so obtuse.
I know your past remember?
Not the boy you have always been well behaved.
What is the story of these two?
Who?
Jason and Simon?
They are rich?
Why do you ask that?
They have this house, right?
I think so.
It's Jason.
Or... Simon.
One... the house is theirs.
Should be good.
Perhaps they need a house-boy.
Kevin!
They do not have that kind of relationship.
But sleep outside.
Obviously.
You probably know most of them rotten I am.
How long do you...
know... Simon?
A couple of years.
What is it like to do?
Confidentiality of clients.
So tell us?
That old pervert.
You want to talk?
We discussed a lot lately.
You have always argued,
but resolved things.
No.
Implicávamos with one another.
Never discussed, not so.
Seriously
Why do not you say something?
Continuous with hopes that things will improve.
What are the reasons for the discussions?
About anything...
about everything.
You know something...
let's take a walk this afternoon.
Just the two.
We talk to the setting sun.
How old?
As before.
Liked it.
Thank you.
Slice these bagles.
Correctly.
Are you awake?
So how are you going and Ace?
Great.
No reason to complain.
Glad you finally joined us.
Yes
He really likes this place,
I am sure you will want to return.
Looking at you now...
is difficult to imagine that you've already been to half a happy couple.
Kevin says I'm trying
rebuild my relationship with Sam.
There are worse things to emulate.
Sam was a great person.
There it was.
As is the Ace.
And if Kevin tells...
must be true!
I mean...
seriously...
Look to the skies, all that blue! Wow!
Namaste!
Stop it.
You should come to yoga with me sometimes.
To know him, he is...
enough inside.
No one wants to see me naked.
Especially during yoga.
Simon back with you.
Maybe you give the necessary spark.
And give Simon a chance to assess new prey?
It will not happen.
Seriously, you should take a chance on Kevin, you'll like it.
You will not be the only one!
Huh?
It seems that our Mac likes of Kevin too.
You're kidding!
You were not kidding!
I love this site even.
Not believe that never came here before.
I could live here.
It would be bad for business?
I like to be kept.
Speaking of which...
Good work with the Coop.
Wooff!
I'm not supported!
If this is what you are insinuating.
I work to live.
Doing what?
I am currently serving at the table.
But one day...
'll be an actor.
Well!
I used to say that.
Believe me, it's easier to do something else.
How do customers find you right?
Ads, Web pages, normal.
It was hard to get?
Not really.
And it pays well?
Why so many questions?
Are you interested in entering the business?
Maybe.
Man!
Seriously?
The work can be sanded.
Billy takes the minimum wage at this time.
I have no real skills
give me to make some money.
Ouch!
Can not be that bad.
Yes You!
Being a prostitute...
Escort!
Sorry.
Escort.
I get paid to do something I enjoy.
Not what career counselors
always told us to do?
Hey!
You receive more for bareback?
I have no idea!
And you shouldn 't think about it.
I'm serious.
Just asking.
Listen, do not fool yourself.
It's work.
You should see most of my clients.
They are not all like Cooper or Simon...
or even the Mac!
How are they?
Two words:
Hairs on the back!
Wow Is incredible!
The union of two souls is always a beautiful experience.
Not mine.
I'm not talking about sex, I am
speaking we see us both.
And we got it right?
I'm trying to talk seriously.
Sorry.
Sorry!
I'm not used to conversations in the morning after.
You are accustomed to what?
Uncomfortable conversations condition.
When the type looks much to me in the light of day,
and in no hurry to dress.
I'm not to rush into anything.
I do not know why.
You do not know me.
Not yet.
I know some things about you.
Tell me!
I know you got a sense of serenity that I never have;
I know you are much more cool than I;
e. ..
you are comfortable with your body
in a way that I never will be.
Come.
Tell me what time.
Christ!
Look at your body...
pretend that you are viewing for the first time.
I see a parvinho.
I see a boring, normal, parvinho.
You need to go to a gym.
Let me say what I see.
I see a beautiful eyes,
that have more than what others are capable.
I see a mouth capable of maintaining a
conversation with anyone.
A warm heart,
who cares more about others than you.
I see a very sexy body that I know better.
I see a strong man who needs it recognizes and accepts its strength.
See you!
I see what you see.
OK.
You have not promised me a private yoga lesson?
Yes
Let's start with my towel against your.
Missed breakfast.
I'm not hungry.
You eat at home.
Already eat.
It was expected!
You need something?
You have to avoid me, you know?
Do not avoid!
Yes You!
Mal spoke to me last night.
Yes ..
for consideration for the feelings of your partner.
Thank you.
I am sorry to put you in this situation.
You could not guess.
True.
I never realized that you were so popular.
Quality is rewarded.
Give me a hand.
Thank you.
The Jason will do a walk this afternoon with Cooper.
Must be absent for some time.
I'll be at your room.
What's the hurry?
Sorry madam,
forgot that he was going to walk this morning?
Fuck you!
How long have we to walk?
Ten minutes!
Seriously
Crap!
I do not like getting older.
It's better than the alternative.
I did a check-up this week...
and wants my cholesterol or my blood pressure is too high.
God! Really?
The curse of my family genetics are finally catching me.
I'll get a gun and end up with this agony.
Fuck you again!
When I was a kid...
heard my father...
talking with friends,
complain about this evil and that revenue.
Seemed so sad.
Know?
It seemed so old at the time.
Now I'm about to go through the same.
Do you miss him?
Will be two years next week.
He would have loved this place.
Yes I would.
Christ!
When you check for me I will be
complain about kids and rap music.
It's ridiculous!
Yes?
I present myself to the service, sir.
Stop it.
The boys were walking.
Must be absent for a good time.
Any idea in particular?
How do I read about it?
With what? Aging?
Yes
I accept the fact that it has to be.
I'm serious.
Me too.
Age is just a state of mind.
Says the guy with a boyfriend of 25 years.
I've been through enough.
Survived where others did not.
I refuse to feel or act
different just because I have 45 years.
You do not have 48 years?
And now it's my turn...
Fuck you!
I was fine until last year.
And suddenly I started getting that look in bars,
You know what?
The look of "who-is-the-old"?
Exactly!
And suddenly all seem young,
young and even younger.
Yes, but does it matter?
Are you Simon!
Fuck.
Well .. there is only one thing to do.
Whats up
Make room in a retirement home and learn to play bridge.
Mind if I go back earlier?
I would like to spend some time with Simon.
Okay.
I do not believe you have never had a massage.
Just the thought of someone touching me used to scare me.
"I used to?
Yes
Used.
It is a good way to relax.
Release toxins from your system.
My work is almost therapeutic.
It is true that matter.
Is there some kind of joke with a happy ending here?
I can not imagine that.
I am sure you will eventually get there.
You know, my mother would say that you are a bad influence.
I can give you a massage too.
This is wrong in so many ways...
I bet you're closer to your father, is not Mac?
Yes
I know it's not cool to say, but my parents are fantastic.
They know?
I'm gay?
Sim.
Already known for some time.
E. ..?
E.... And nothing.
They love me. They are my parents.
Should be good.
And about your family?
My family?
Lets see...
There's my brother
he joined his friends,
and beat me up when I knew I was gay.
My father
drove me home at 17.
And there's my mother,
that returned all my letters unopened.
After ten years finally gave up.
I very much Kevin.
Everything happens for a reason.
The past is the past.
And it led me here to meet someone with thoughts of love
and a loving family.
You're a lucky man Mac
Yes
I think I am.
I'll talk to the Ace for a while.
Enjoy.
You too.
A dollar and a half for your thoughts.
What happened to walking?
The Jason was not even order it.
He is quite old.
Care!
Something wrong?
No.
I got it because you are so fond of this place.
It's so peaceful.
It is a great place to think about things.
Like what?
Ahhh, you know...
Life...
the universe...
Everything.
So nothing serious, right?
How long have you come here?
God!
Seven years.
I want it.
I want to return here.
Back to you.
I want to be part of your group.
And not just your last achievement.
Thou shalt.
Thou.
What purpose does this come from?
It was something you said to Cameroon.
About getting to know Jason twenty years...
And?
You know I do not care about our age difference.
Except...
Except what?
Except when I think of the future.
Are you afraid to take care of me in my old age?
God! No!
I'm afraid to lose you!
Before we have time together.
I mean... I have twenty years to you?
Or you'll get sick of me long before that?
Nobody knows what the future will be.
But this I know...
I had the great fortune to really love two men in my life...
One when he was young...
And now you.
You're everything I need for the rest of my life.
And after that...
You'll find someone else.
No!
Okay!
It's something we will not have to think for a long, long time.
It's my turn!
Damn! I must have left me to sleep.
Where is everybody?
Hello?
You like?
I understand you see it.
And I know what I would like to see it now.
Seriously
Why do not you take a shower?
What?
Clean up.
Drink a glass.
Anything.
We were right.
Bullshit!
Thirteen?
Assumed you thirteen?
Hey! If you like wood, wood you like.
Truth!
What wood did you enjoy the 13?
From Gregory.
Do your cousin Gregory??
This is sexy.
It relays.
I met Gregory,
is definitely sexy.
He is also gay?
The florist in San Francisco.
What do you think?
I think you should invite to a trio.
No more groups for me.
I am a man of one man.
When will you marry?
So what is legal.
Well! As if that were to succeed in the near future.
It may not happen so fast...
but it will happen.
You are all so cynical.
Only realistic.
When you two make a
those commitment ceremonies?
Why? It means nothing legally.
It is symbolic.
The symbolism does not protect from nurses that homophobic
do not let you see your partner if he is in the hospital.
Or you protect your family back to your partner crazy.
That's what good are lawyers.
And a will.
And a will made in life.
And a good lawyer.
And hire a good lawyer.
So romantic!
Do you think that a ceremony makes you a couple?
Simon and I have spent thousands of dollars just to protect ourselves in case something...
in the event something happens.
And it is worth?
Sure.
I do not care if it is legal or not.
I want to marry me any day.
Maybe you cases.
Contigo!
I do not care if I ever marry.
That's good.
Has anyone seen Kevin or Mac today?
I have not seen...
but definitely heard them.
Seriously
Yes
You know what would meditate?
Well, "Namaste" means "I'll come" in yoga.
Good for them.
Yes, fine for them.
Going to sleep?
Obviously.
What is your problem?
None!
So why the fuck are you be so stupid to this weekend?
I??
What was it this afternoon?
What?
I join with you and your whore
for an afternoon of consensual sex?
Is not that what we do.
Maybe we should!
It's all very good, but...
second thought, you know it well!
We have a deal!
I did nothing wrong!
No.
You never doing anything wrong.
Not here, not at home. Never!
You are perfect!
I never said that was!
That is not the case!
So what is the case?
The case is...
I fuck if I know!
Are you not tired of discussing?
You're not sick of me cause?
Are you not tired of pretending you're better than me?
Away from me?
When it suits your purposes.
And then you ask excuse when you feel alone.
You're not tired of pretending that you love me?
As much as I love you?
Yes!
I!
Hello!
What is going on?
Nothing!
You have enough meat there?
Yes
Sure.
Kevin believes a diet of high protein value.
I sure hope so.
Thank you.
You know...
for inviting me.
This has been the best weekend ever weeks.
Glad you're going through a good bit.
Good?
"Good" or even used to describe it.
I mean, I feel a completely different person here.
As if he could do whatever I want.
Usually have that effect on people.
Can I ask you a question?
Strength
You....
What?
You arranged this?
I mean, you thought that Kevin and I...
Honestly...
had never met Kevin before the end of this weekend.
Cooper invited him.
But I have a feeling we'll see you more often.
Yes
Me too.
Remind me to send Cooper a thank you card.
Or a basket of cakes.
He likes to carp?
He prefers chicken.
Listen... I know that you are still in the closet at work.
No. Not in the closet...
But it is reality, right?
I always thought it was someone else's problem.
And it is not.
Actually I was a little surprised when you invited me,
always thought it was a bit macho.
Ok, maybe not. But...
I am grateful that you have asked me instead
the presumption to speak on my back.
It takes one to know another, right?
Yes, I think so.
Anyway...
for the week when we go back to the office,
You can rely on my discretion.
I'm not talking about you or this weekend the weekend.
Thank you.
But you know what?
What?
It's okay.
I will not think about them.
You can tell whoever you want.
Thank you.
I will never forget it.
Are you sure you're ready for this?
What did you say?
I have to face my fears.
Or your fears will face you.
So why...
this has to be my greatest fear?
Because we are taught since childhood to be ashamed of our bodies.
You must overcome this fear if you want to be at peace with yourself.
You are only vanities, do you know that?
Are you ready?
Yes.
Anybody want to go naked to the jacuzzi?
Anyone for a little jacuzzi morning?
Nobody?
Seems it's just us.
Farewell to face my fears.
I'm fine!
Seriously!
He returns.
If I had something to do with this sorry lot.
Of course you had not!
But thank you.
My name is Mac
It is a nickname.
E. .. me hate it.
Well!
But it's what everyone call you at work.
Yes
But... I never wanted to correct one before.
I think I will go to do.
You know my real name?
It....
Crap!
Sorry.
How's your name?
It Hamish!
And prefer it to Mac?
Hamish!
I like it.
So why do they call you Mac?
There was a TV series, a long time,
people loved to tell me.
Yet realized.
It is my full name.
It....
Hamish Wallace Gyver.
Like...
Mac .. Gyver?
MacGyver?
Still not got it!
Kids!
Your aura was not compatible with the name Mac
So what's the plan for today?
I thought that there were no plans.
Fuck that.
I need work...
and need friends.
Let's take a walk.
A walk is.
You come with us for a change?
Yes, do some exercise stand for a change.
We have done it.
Well!
In a 5 minutes all out there.
Who needs to change?
Sure. Come!
It's been 10 minutes.
You'll get old fart?
Shut up!
Give me water!
Are you sure that you can not run with the tenants?
I will work to Cooper.
Nature is so...
... Natural!
Do not you think?
I would not have said it better.
Yes .. this is fun!
Free the mind of all thoughts.
Concentrate on the noise made by wind in the trees.
Feel the presence of those around you.
Feel their energy.
Feel their love.
Stop it!
But I wanted to feel your love.
Let go.
Feel the negative energy out of each exhalation.
Feel the life force of these woods and penetrate you.
Concentrate!
Now a final inspiration.
Think of all the possibilities of life.
I know this is not easy.
Can I do anything?
'm Not in the mood.
I'm not talking about sex.
I'm talking about... talk.
I'm really an excellent listener.
Simon told you things... about me?
About us?
It would be strange to you?
No. Not at all.
Hearing both sides maybe I can help.
I'm not gonna pay.
At least now.
I do not want to reality.
The reality follows you where to go.
Not taught you anything?
I speak in fact real.
This site seems...
a hidden reality.
Are you saying that the cabin is like the Matrix?
Exactly!
I do not want to be presumptuous, but...
can ever again?
Absolutely.
You said "we"?
Yes, we.
Accept advice from an old...
You is not... so old!
So old?!?
You understand me.
My advice is...
enjoy these days.
You only have one opportunity...
in the beginning of a relationship.
Enjoy it!
We will do so.
Anything else?
Be honest.
Even if it hurts.
And when you find the right kind, will not let you escape.
Amen to that!
Any advice for us single people?
Depends if they want to remain single or not.
I'm fine.
I like to play open.
There is nothing wrong with that.
I personally do not feel the call to a relationship.
It seems that monogamy only leads to boredom.
There because you are in a relationship does not mean you have to be monogamous.
Yes
Love and sex are separate things.
Not for me!
I mean... have had sex without love.
But with love...
is much better.
Weird!
You said weird?
Fascism.
Do not do it.
Okay.
Are you saying that since you been in love?
Bright!
Surprises me!
What I do is my job.
It has nothing to do with my private life.
Are you in love now?
Definitely not!
But since you been?
And not long ago.
And he did not care what you do in life?
No! Did not care.
But you breaks?
Yes
For many reasons, least that.
Definitely not because of this.
I do not think Simon is gone.
They look good.
But if they end up...
Everything will be fine.
Promise?
I promise!
What are you doing here?
I was waiting for you.
Seriously
Looking for company?
Not tonight.
But I could use someone to talk to.
Really?
I was never friends with talk of anyone before.
Are you up to?
I!
If you were speaking seriously, call me this week.
I can give you some advice.
Are you sure you want to get into this line of work?
I!
I think.
We'll see.
So...
we see us soon?
We accompany you.
I told you that this would be an end-of-wonderful weeks.
There you said it.
But you know what?
We have to make the path.
We have dinner with my parents tonight.
Let?
Yes!
- Come on!
- Namaste!
Get a room!
See you at work.
The crazy yoga was right.
This was wonderful!
Except... the subject of the departure of Simon!
Well! Except for that.
I'm really glad I came to this weekend.
Me too.
Not have been the same without you kid.
Stop calling me kid!
Stop being a kid.
No, do not stop to be.
What they want.
You want to hit him or hit him I?
I beat him.
Later!
Not going to be the same.
You're wrong!
This will always be the same.
It will always be here for you.
Until a drought causes a
fire that destroys the entire mountain.
I'm trying to take a moment...
collaborates with me!
Okay.
- Has your time.
- Thank you.
This will always be here for you.
You can change the relationships may change, but...
Here you can ever forget
your problems and your own living.
And if you want me...
'll be here for you too.
That will never change.
I need you with the departure of Simon.
Do not talk like that, you'll solve everything.
No.
No more.
Not going to be the same.
No.
But it may be better!
Come!
It's annoying!
And it's all mine!
Are you ready?
Yes
I'm ready.
Translation and adaptation:
By SHANK
Visit
www.boyzforum.com
http://filmestemag.blogspot.com/