Listen, kid, i hate to tell you this,
but we gotta be off this mountain
in 20 minutes.
There`s a storm coming.
Ty,
i`m your eyes on this one, kid.
On three. One, two, three.
Ladies and gentlemen,
welcome to Beaver Creek, Colorado,
home of the Birds of Prey
Men`s World Cup Downhill.
Twelve in the chute. Twelve in the chute.
Here we go.
On five, four, three, two, one.
Tyler Crowe is in the start house.
He`s just... Just let him know
that down here the brink is deep.
it`s iced up. He`s gotta go easy.
Hey, Tyler,
this course doesn`t really begin
till you make it through the brink.
You overcook that turn and you`re toast.
You gotta conserve your strength
for the bottom section.
lt`s icing up pretty good.
lt`s way more rutted than it was
when you guys were training.
Remember to throttle back to hold your line.
Focus on that, understand? Understand?
Montana comes barreling over the jump.
And he`s 0. 7 ahead. Unbelievable.
-Hey, Coach.
-Yeah.
He`s one second ahead of the Austrians.
Nobody is one second ahead on this course.
Racer down. Racer down.
We have a course hold.
-How`s the knee?
-lt`s good.
Okay, Tyler, this one`s yours.
You know what do.
And now in the starting gate,
it`s American Tyler Crowe.
Who would have thought
after two knee surgeries,
the thoroughbred from Snow Basin
would bounce back
for yet another downhill World Cup season?
Look at the intensity in the start house.
-On five, four...
-Hold the line. Focus on it.
...three, two, one.
He`s really a cannonball, Chad.
Never a bad start with Crowe.
Wow, in perfect forms,
Crowe hits the first big air.
Oh, he`s doing awesome, Trace.
He`s flying, Chad. But let`s hope
he can keep it together through the brink
where most of the racers
are having trouble today.
He`s half a second ahead.
Just one last turn
separates Crowe from the lead,
in what will be a difficult time to beat.
Oh, he`s off balance. Oh, and he goes down.
Huge crash, Chad.
Tyler Crowe, what an unbelievable crash.
But, Trace, he`s moving.
lt looks like he`s gonna be okay.
lt`s not the type of air time you want
downhill racing, is it?
lt is not. And look at this.
The butt hits the snow.
The ski loads up and he gets high sided.
The full carcass huck upside down,
all the way around.
Tyler Crowe, what a maniac.
Once again, Chad,
Tyler Crowe has handed us yet another gem
for the highlight reel.
l can`t believe that crash.
l can`t believe you walked away
from that one. See, that was...
-Coach?
-Yeah.
Hey, guys, l need Tyler for a minute.
-What`s up, Coach?
-Apparently, that was a world-class digger.
Yeah. Well, the course was...
lt was pretty roughed up.
l wasn`t expecting it.
Do you wanna win, Tyler?
-Are you serious?
-You push too hard. You don`t listen.
-l caught an edge. lt happens.
-Bullshit.
You hit that turn at full throttle.
Well, you know what? With all due respect,
you have no idea what you`re talking about.
You`re off the team, Tyler.
-What?
-Yeah.
l think you need some time,
you know, to figure out what you want,
what you really want.
l know what l really want.
lf that were true,
the whole world would know it.
Ladies and gentlemen,
put your hands together
for the Birds of Prey champion,
Austrian Andre Meyer.
How good can i get at snowboarding?
i think the question is
how good can snowboarding get for me?
You saw that. You had to have seen that.
Dude.
-You don`t think it`s doable, do you?
-Anything`s doable.
-l broke my ass.
-More like you broke the mountain.
Just a sec, all right?
Shit!
Elisa Rider, when did you get old enough
to start serving booze?
What... What are you doing here?
l thought you were gone all winter.
You seem disappointed.
No, l`m... l`m just surprised, is all.
You know, you don`t look hurt
and Mark didn`t mention anything
about you coming home, so...
No, l haven`t talked to him yet.
Actually, l didn`t talk to anybody. lt was...
Kind of one those last-minute
kind of things, you know.
And you decided to come here first?
What can l say?
l thought a beer sounded pretty good.
Of course.
So, where is that old brother
of yours, anyway?
Mark.
-Hitting on my sister?
-Maybe l am.
Come here, man. lt`s good seeing you.
-How you been? lt`s been a long time.
-Too long, huh?
-Hey, beer`s on me, fellas.
-All right.
-Oh, great.
-These guys with you?
Oh, didn`t you hear? Your best friend here
is the subject of his own documentary.
What? You got a problem with that?
No, man, no problem. Just it seems kind of
like a waste of film, don`t you think?
Hey, don`t tell my investors that.
Stephan Weeks.
-l know who you are.
-You do? How come?
l guess it was a few years ago,
l believe in December,
you sent Mark here off the Nose
when there was less than 1 2 inches of snow
on the ground, just for a shot.
-That was sick, too.
-Dude, you broke your collarbone.
-Yeah, but it was still a hell of a shot.
-lt was a hell of a shot.
And because of that shot,
Mark here can go to any bar
in any ski town in the world
and drink for free, right?
Cheers. Made him a legend, that shot.
You hear that, sis? A legend.
lt`s on, bro, Meteorite.
Meteorite?
That`s what this is about?
You`re going to Alaska?
-Dude, you out of your mind?
-You know, she still hasn`t been ridden.
-Yeah, there`s a reason for that, Stephan...
-And the reason is because nobody`s tried.
-Not since Randy Klein in `92.
-You mean, not since he died.
This is fun.
Mark, dude, you`re out of your mind.
Everybody knows
that mountain`s not doable.
l already found a line on the north face.
lt`s totally doable, man.
-You think?
-CJ and l leave the day after tomorrow.
Meteorite with CJ?
Your ass is always busy chasing gates
and working for the man.
We`re doing dawn patrol on Zorba`s Ridge
tomorrow. Are you down?
-Yeah, l`m down.
-All right, cool.
lt`s good seeing you, man. Stay up.
-Later, Rider.
-Laters.
Must be a little weird having to carry
your own skis again, hey, Crowe?
-Should l get you a Sherpa?
-l think l can manage.
We`ll see.
-No place like home, huh?
-Oh, man.
l don`t think l have ever seen it like this.
Ever.
Been such an epic winter this year.
-Check out the Devil`s Coattails over there.
-Wow!
-Can you believe how filled in it is?
-Man, where have l been?
The racecourse.
Hey, Ty, l realize how awkward this must be
without that cute little spandex, huh?
So, if you want me to go first, man...
-You still got it.
-Yeah, Crowe.
What took you so long?
Just glad to see you still know how to ride
something without a starting gate.
Yeah, CJ.
Look at that, boys.
That`s what l`m talking about, cold smoke.
White gold. lt is, man.
That is all-time, right there.
Hey.
Oh, my God.
Where have you been? Where you been?
-l`ve been here.
-Awesome.
So, word on the street is
you got kicked off the ski team.
ls it?
lt was a little less dramatic than that.
lt`s funny, l just... l never thought l`d hear
the end of that drumbeat.
-Don`t.
-What?
-l know what you`re doing.
-What am l doing?
l`m just looking at you.
Yeah. And the last time you looked at me
like that we wound up back at your place.
And l seem to remember the words
``huge mistake``
and, oh, yeah, it gets better,
``Skiing out of bounds
with my best friend`s sister.``
-Okay, l would never have said...
-Oh?
-...``skiing out of bounds.``
-What?
You know, your brother would kill me
if he found out.
-You know what l think?
-What do you think?
l think that if l wasn`t Mark`s sister,
you wouldn`t be attracted to me at all.
Really? And why is that?
Because it`s safe.
And you know it`s never gonna happen.
You all wanna get a little bit of a taste
of what Rider and l are gonna do in Alaska?
Well, let`s get this party started.
CJ? CJ? Say something, man.
Well, thanks for driving me home.
-You wouldn`t wanna...
-No.
Okay. Right.
Still keep your trophies out?
Shut up. l know l`m a dork.
-You`re gonna miss it, aren`t you?
-l don`t know.
You know, l...
l`ve been racing my whole life.
l never even...
l never even considered
what l`d do if l wasn`t.
You`re a real loner, aren`t you, Tyler Crowe?
Yeah, l guess so. l have no choice.
Shit. lt`s your brother.
Ty!
Your truck is in the driveway.
He knows you`re here.
Oh, he`s gonna kill me.
-Ty!
-lt`s okay. l`ll talk to him.
-Are you out of your mind?
-He already knows l`m here.
We`ve got to come up with a story.
You were too drunk to drive
so l insisted you stay here.
And then we had mad,
passionate, animal sex.
No, listen.
-Yo, Ty?
-Then you slept on the couch,
and l slept on the bed or should you have
slept on the bed and l slept on the couch?
-Tyler.
-What?
-Your fly.
-Right.
-Ty, open up, man. Get your jacket.
-What?
Get your jacket. Let`s go.
-Come on.
-Wait up. Where are we going?
-Alaska.
-Alaska?
CJ broke his leg.
Be right with you, guys.
-So you wanna talk about this?
-Talk about what?
-Elisa.
-What about her?
Dude, come on.
You walked right past her truck.
l know you know she was at my house.
-Man, where is he?
-Who?
-Mark, come on. l wanna talk about this.
-What`s there to talk about?
You nailed my sister. Pretty cool, huh?
How was she?
-How was she?
-Stop. lt wasn`t like that.
You guys just sit up and talk
the whole night?
lf you got a problem with that,
l`d rather you just say that...
-Yo, Steph.
-Hey. Yeah,
l`ll keep you posted. Okay, great.
Ciao. Hey. Sorry, guys. lnvestors.
You gotta love them, huh?
-No worries. We just got here ourselves.
-Cool.
Can l have some coffee, hon?
-Thanks.
-Thank you.
Hey, Ty, l`m stoked you`re on board.
l can`t think of a better replacement for CJ.
Did Mark fill you in?
Mark hasn`t said much of anything
this morning.
-Dude, she`s not just another piece of ass.
-Did l say she was?
-Good, `cause she`s not.
-l know.
You guys in the middle of something here?
-No.
You know, it`s a better story, you know.
You guys,
you`ve been skiing together
since you could walk.
You go your own separate ways,
come back together,
ski the ultimate mountain.
Oh, it`s bloody great.
A contract?
Are you serious?
Look, we`re not just making
another ski flick here.
l wanna make a movie
that`s gonna set the benchmark
for all sports action films for years to come.
My commitment to this project, to Mark,
to both of your safety, is solid.
So how about it, bro?
Down for a shot at greatness?
What do you say?
-Give me a pen.
-Great.
More sugar.
-You will look out for him, won`t you?
-Of course, l will.
No, l`m serious, Ty, `cause, you know,
you`re the responsible one
and if something`s not safe
and it`s not doable,
-then you gotta make him back off.
-We`ll come back in one piece.
And what about...
-Us?
-Yeah.
He`ll get over it.
-l wasn`t talking about him.
-What?
Are you sure you want this?
l`m positive.
Hey, guys, this is Dean Bauer.
He`s gonna be your guide up here,
take care of us while we shoot this thing.
-Hey, Dean.
-What`s up? Mark.
l`m Tyler.
Welcome to Alaska.
Listen, the weather`s getting bad.
Load up your shit here.
We`ll get this show on the road.
Okay, let`s load up.
Welcome to the junk show.
This will be your home
for the next two weeks.
-Jesus. The place reeks.
-Yeah.
lt reeks like yo` mamma.
Dude, you love that joke. You smell that?
-What?
-Smells like... Smells like home.
-What`s up, guys?
-You`re just arriving now?
-You missed an epic day up there.
-Oh, yes. lt was super sick.
-We`ll catch it tomorrow.
-Oh, no.
Haven`t you heard the news?
There is big storm coming in.
Huge.
Just kidding.
See you.
l`m glad to see there`s not going to be
lack of entertainment.
-Do you have any idea who that was?
-Enlighten me.
Hubert Haddad. One of the best
big mountain boarders in the world.
No shit?
What do you think he`s doing here?
-Think he`s here for Meteorite?
-We`re here for Meteorite.
-Yes, we are, brother.
-Meteorite, man.
We`re doing it. We`re doing it!
Damn, that feels good.
Hey, guys. Dean`s office, five minutes.
Okay?
You guys better forget everything you`ve
ever heard about high-elevation snow.
This is Alaska.
8,000-foot conditions at sea level.
lt`s sticky and condensed
and it won`t crumble up
like that Sierra cement
or that soft Utah powder
that you guys are probably used to.
lt`ll bust loose and when it does, man,
it`ll fracture down 20, 25 foot
and take you with it and we`ll be digging
you out in the summertime.
We don`t want that to happen.
So l hope you got
fresh batteries in your transceivers
and shovels and whatnot.
We`re all set. We just need to know
the game plan for tomorrow, Dean.
Well, Fissile Peak,
the closest to Meteorite as l can get
in pitch, but it`s only one-tenth the size.
You better start picking your lines, boys.
it aii starts here. in just two weeks,
the US quest for the Worid Cup goid
carves its way to Chamonix, France
where the US ski team wiii attempt
to saivage a season rocked
with injury and heartbreak.
Can a young, inexperienced American team
beat the Austrian powerhouse?
Tune in to NTN,
your home for winter sports teievision.
Honestly, man, l don`t know
how you ever put up with them.
They weren`t so bad.
-You`re kidding me, right?
-What?
-They booted you off the team.
-Yeah, well,
l don`t know.
Everything happens for a reason, right?
l mean, l wouldn`t be here.
True that.
-No. You still have that?
-Yeah. lt looks after me.
-Dude, it`s a rock.
-lt`s a cool rock.
Remember that time up in Telluride
when l busted my leg?
-l left it at home that day.
-And?
So, as long as l`m 9,000 feet above sea level,
this baby is coming with me.
Don`t you think you can pick something
a little smaller,
like a bracelet, maybe an anklet?
-Something more along your style?
-Oh, an anklet is my style.
-Let me see it.
-No. What are you doing? Go sit down.
-Go write your letter.
-Dude, l just wanna see the rock.
-This is my rock, Ty. You`ll contaminate it.
-Are you serious?
-Ty, Ty. Don`t mess with my boulder...
-Come on, dude...
You`re crazy, man.
-So this is my backyard. What do you think?
-it is unbeiievabie.
There she is, boys, Meteorite.
Hoiy crap. Check it out right there, the peak.
We can drop in on that, definiteiy.
Take that iine down.
Hey, Dean, drop me off anywhere,
i`m serious.
-Yeah. Anywhere, huh?
-Anywhere. Come on.
Not today, cowboy.
You guys got some training to do.
Check it out. Looks like heaven, huh?
-lt`s great. Okay, Mark, you ready for us?
-Let`s do it.
-Camera one, set.
-Camera two, set.
Okay, Rider, iet`s see what you got.
Bottoms up.
All right. Easy, easy, easy. Take it easy now.
This is your first run.
That was sweet, brother.
Oh, yeah.
Okay, on three. Three, two, one.
l`m rolling. ls anybody going?
What are we doing here?
Hey, Tyler, we`re wasting fiim here, okay?
Damn you, Rider.
Get that latch.
-Happy now, cowboy?
-Very.
-l wish l could be there with you guys.
-Oh, l wish you could, too. l miss you.
-Call me tomorrow?
-Of course l will.
-Night.
-Good night.
Remember what i toid you, guys. Go easy.
Okay, not too fast.
Check it out, guy. Look over there.
Do it again, man!
When you`re ready, Tyler. Let`s do it.
Not too far. Keep your iine.
-You have a cig, brother?
-You`re right, he`s good.
Hello? Dean?
Hello?
lt was about this same time of year
that that storm finally broke.
-lt was deep winter.
-You were Randy Klein`s guide.
No, l was his partner.
Just like you and cowboy.
Yeah, conditions were great that day. Cold.
We weren`t even a quarter of the way
down that mountain
before all hell broke loose. Only thing
l could do was just stand there.
l watched the whole damn avi
just come down right past me with him in it.
l`ll tell you something,
there really hasn`t been a day that`s gone by
when l haven`t wondered,
why him and not me?
l`m sorry.
That`s easy for you to say.
l dug a lot of people out from up there.
Maybe one too many.
That is 76 points. Baby, read `em and weep.
``Jackball?`` That`s not a word.
-Yeah, it is.
-Dude.
-l think l found us a better line.
-Jackball, jackball. Like, ``You jackball.
``You jerk.`` Jackball. That`s 76 points.
-No way. You`re a cheat.
-And...
l quit, jackball.
Oh, no, you didn`t. You`re going
to your room? l`ll see you later.
Check this out. l don`t know
why l didn`t notice it before but...
Ty. We got our line.
Straight down the southwest shoulder,
-40 yards straight line...
-Then 100 feet to nowhere.
Dude, it`s a good line except to that area.
You just don`t know
where you`re gonna land.
Look, check it out. lt`s the same shoulder
but just a little bit to the left, right?
You cut half at least off that drop
and you know where you`re gonna land
and it`s not a postage stamp.
Dude, you don`t know
what you`re talking about.
Listen, l just ran it by Dean
and he thinks it`s solid.
You and Dean?
Whatever, man. Look, l didn`t come here
to play freaking patty cake.
My line is straight down the middle.
Yeah, there`s a good ianding zone
just up ahead.
Oh, shit. We got the Frenchies here.
Yeah, yeah. Bon bioody jour.
Those guys beat us to the top of Meteorite,
Dean can forget about his bonus.
Every aspect of these layers
is subject to conditions.
-Look at this rain crust.
-Here?
Yeah. A little bit up there,
but this is the big one.
Hey, guys. We`re burning dayiight here.
What`s the hoid up?
Jump with your feet flat.
-What are you doing, Dean?
-Listen, Dean,
l really think Stephan wants us to...
l just figured since he`s paying
for this expedition and all.
Right.
ls it safe?
l don`t know if l`d go that far.
-Let`s go.
-l think l got it, boss.
No, no, no.
We got this shot 100 times, guys.
l think up here. That`s the money shot.
-Let`s work, guys. i`m starting to tighten up.
-Hang tight.
Looks aii right to me.
Weii, it`s not. it`s just sitting there
waiting for some fooi to try it.
Yeah, yeah.
Don`t even think about it, Tyler.
l mean, that`s the money shot right there,
okay?
Get the door. Get the door.
What is he doing?
Okay. That`s it. Pack it in. You`re aii done.
lt was a nice call out there today.
You saved my ass.
-Just doing my job.
-Thank you.
Would`ve made
a hell of a shot though, huh?
That`s all you kids think about nowadays
is the shot, the shot, the shot, the shot.
Nobody even comes up here to ski anymore.
-That`s a little unfair.
-Why?
lt`s not like it`s a choice.
Do you think guys like me and Mark could
afford to come up here and do all this
if somebody wasn`t footing the bill?
l have no idea.
Besides, from what l understand,
you`re looking at a pretty fat bonus yourself
after Thursday.
-ls that what you heard?
-What, no bonus?
No Meteorite.
Everywhere you see orange is
an indication of low pressure.
Any time you see red on the top there,
you can bet we`re in
for about three to four foot of snow.
Great.
You might as well get comfy, guys,
`cause we`re in for a whiteout.
-How long, Dean?
-l don`t know, three to four days down.
Could be as much as a week.
And then again, once we get up there,
we gotta wait for the snow to stabilize.
-Jesus.
-lt`s not Jesus, it`s Mother Nature, son.
So, when do you think
this storm`s gonna hit?
l don`t know, maybe late morning.
Okay, cool. So, we get up there first thing,
we beat the storm, right?
Meteorite, baby.
l thought you guys said
that you wanted to do this right.
Yeah, we do. But we don`t have
the luxury of time, you know that.
Every day`s costing me thousands.
A week, two weeks? You`re kidding me.
We got nothing, we`re done. No movie.
Come on, you gotta take us up tomorrow.
-You ain`t ready.
-No, no. Are you kidding me?
These guys have completed
every training run you`ve thrown at them.
They`ve dug more ditches
than l wanna look at.
Trust me, they`re as ready
as they`re gonna be.
Oh, so, you want me to trust you?
lf l would have done that this morning,
he`d be dead.
Dean, come on. l know we`re ready.
-Ty, tell him.
-Yeah, tell me.
-Ty.
-You ain`t ready. Shut up.
-Ty?
-What? Yeah. l mean...
Okay, you guys.
Yeah, baby. Bring it on. Come on, man.
He knew.
Hey, Dean.
Dean.
l was wondering, you know.
You know, maybe, just maybe if, you know,
if we hadn`t been dicking around
for the last six days,
maybe we`d have the mountain in the can.
How do you feel about that, huh? Huh?
Great, this is bullshit.
This is bullshit, Dean.
Another? You go.
-Come on.
-l`m tired, man.
Let`s go!
lsn`t it a little early for that?
What`s one beer?
What`s one beer when it`s 1 1 :00 a.m.
and you spent
the whole night up drinking tequila?
Dude, we`re in Alaska and it`s
freaking nuking outside and l`m thirsty.
l don`t know.
l`d say it`s a tossup at this point.
Man, your head is as foggy as your lens is
half the time.
Look at Tyler here on Little Crooked.
And that straight line on Rayburn`s Peak?
You see that?
Tyler`s clearly got more style, man,
more flow.
Steph will definitely give him first descent.
Watch.
l still say it`s a tossup.
Man, that`s cabin fever talking, man.
Get back to work.
What are we gonna do with your footage?
Can`t find steeps like this
anywhere in the world.
No, l`m good. Thanks.
So, what`s the longest
you guys have ever been down for?
We arrived end of February.
We do not see sun until April.
-April?
-Yo, let me hit that, man.
Okay, he went...
-Dude, what are you doing?
-What does it look like l`m doing, man?
Taking a B with my boys here.
Got a problem with that, man?
You okay?
-Yeah, l`m okay. l`m fine.
-You don`t sound fine.
No, l`m just... l`m pulling my hair out.
l`m getting a little stir crazy, you know.
Well, if it`s any consolation,
the weather here has been sick
and l won`t even tell you about the snow.
Oh, great. l mean,
that does make me feel a lot better. Thanks.
You know, he hasn`t called or written
me once, not even to just say hello.
That`s weird,
`cause he talks about you all the time.
Oh, come on, Tyler,
please don`t stick up for him.
No. He hasn`t really been himself lately.
You know, since... Since you and l...
What?
Never mind, forget it. lt`s stupid.
So, what are we supposed to do?
Break up because of him?
l don`t know.
You don`t really wanna end this, do you?
l`ll call you later.
Man, you guys really do suck.
-Oh, come on. Come on.
-Yo!
Mr. Crowe, as always,
your timing is impeccable.
Come on, man. Why don`t you join me here?
-Dude, we gotta talk.
-Be my partner for a game.
-l got to talk to you now.
-Now is not a good time.
-Hey, what the hell are you doing?
-Come on.
What?
-Let`s go home, man.
-What? You crazy?
l just...
l don`t think we gave this enough thought
and l don`t think anybody`s gonna think
anything less of us if we leave now.
Ty, l came here for Meteorite, man.
l know you did.
But it`s not worth it. lt`s not worth this.
l see.
You`re trying to psych me out, is that it?
What are you talking about, psych you out?
Know what?
Don`t even try and deny it, all right?
Everybody knows.
Trying to steal my thunder,
my line, my mountain. Come on.
-Dude, you invited me here.
-Yeah.
Yeah, biggest mistake l ever made.
-You want first descent...
-Dude, you are out of your mind.
-Where is this all coming from?
-All right.
You`re a taker, dude. You always have been.
-Look how you`re handling my little sister.
-Handling your little sister.
l knew that`s what this was about.
You may think you can fool her, man,
but not me.
l see how you really are.
-l`m out of here, man.
-Don`t let the door hit you.
What happened to you, man?
lt`s good.
Yeah.
Tyler Crowe.
To what do l owe his honor?
l`ve been snowed in a while
and l`m itching to let them run.
Have a seat.
Looks like one hell of a training course
you got set up out there.
Yeah, it is.
lt`s about as technical as they get.
What would it take for a guy
to get a run down it?
Well, it`s not open to the public, Tyler.
Right.
Well, l guess...
You got one run.
That`s all l need, Coach.
Suit up.
Morning, sunshine. We got bluebird.
Come on, get up, kid.
Come on, get up, get up, get up, get up.
Coffee`s getting cold. Come on.
-You got to be kidding me.
-Meteorite awaits.
Three, two...
You`re not gonna beiieve it.
Tyler Crowe, 1.:38, 1.:38.
He just beat Jones by almost two seconds.
Book another ticket to Chamonix.
Mark.
Dean? Dean, do you have a visuai?
Mark? Do you hear me, Mark?
Oh, Jesus. Jesus. Mark!
You have two messages.
Tyler, where are you?
Something`s happened to Mark.
i don`t know what`s going on.
Will you just call me, please? Call me.
Hey, Tyler.
-Hey.
Sorry about your friend.
You gotta keep moving.
Mourn his loss, but don`t lose focus
on what you`re here for.
Today`s the best you`ve ever skied.
Listen, l appreciate that.
And l`ll catch up with you guys
just as soon as l can, all right?
l had to pull a lot of strings
to get you back on the team.
-l know you did.
-Okay.
You know, if you walk away now, that`s it.
There`s no coming back.
Father, we thank you for Mark`s life.
We thank you, God, and we celebrate
what`s happened in his life today.
We celebrate what we have had,
and again we thank you
that someday we shall see him again.
We say this in Jesus` name.
ln the name of the Father,
the Son and the Holy Spirit, amen.
Hi.
How could you leave him?
He wasn`t supposed to go.
Look, l don`t know what l wanna say to you
because, honestly, l don`t know
how l feel about anything anymore.
All l know is my brother is dead
and that you...
And that l what?
Say it, Elisa. l wanna hear you say it.
And that it`s my fault. Say it, Elisa.
Hello, Tyler.
-What do you want?
-Do you have a second?
Look, l know you think
l coaxed him up there too soon.
Truth is, he wanted to fly
first sign of bluebird.
You get four feet of fresh powder
with a storm.
-You know how Mark was.
-lf there`s a point, get to it.
You`re angry, l get it.
And if it helps blaming me, l understand.
l never should have left him.
You`re right, you shouldn`t have.
You turned your back on him.
-This project, your contract...
-My contract, is that why you`re here?
l need you up there.
l mean, you`re just sitting here.
Winter is almost over,
you`re just getting colder.
-Are you gonna let the mountain win?
-ls this some kind of game to you?
l`m not gonna let my best friend`s death be
some convenient plot twist in your movie.
-Okay.
-Get out of my house.
You know where to find me.
Tyler. Tyler.
Tyler! Tyler!
-Tyler!
-Mark?
-Tyler. Tyler!
-Mark!
Tyler!
Mark! Mark! Hold on!
God!
Glad you made it.
So, how much did you get?
What the hell is that supposed to mean?
What was the price tag
on my best friend`s life?
-There wasn`t a price tag.
-``There wasn`t a price tag``?
You told me you weren`t taking us up there.
You told me you weren`t ready...
Your bullshit stories about your best friend
dying and feeling guilty, and l believed you.
-And l left him here.
-He was gonna go with somebody else, man.
God damn it!
He had somebody else.
He was going with somebody else, man.
l was the best chance that he had, okay?
-He didn`t take his line?
-No, he took yours.
He took your line.
l wanna go there.
All right.
-Will you take me?
-Yeah.
When that mountain calls your name,
baby, you`re done. That`s it, man.
The way l see it,
he could have run off the end of a cliff
or tried to outrun an avalanche. Either way,
l guess it wasn`t meant to work out.
Your line was solid, Tyler.
lt wasn`t his.
That was the thing about Mark, you know?
He never would be told what to do
and it just kind of sucks
that the one time he listens to me...
There`s nothing anybody could have done,
short of not going up there.
l`m telling you, death is always
around the corner. Yes, it is, my friend.
Can l see those Polaroids?
-l`m not gonna show them to you.
-Why is that?
Because she`s not gonna look
nothing like that once you get up there.
lt`s gonna be
completely and totally different.
l`m gonna be your eyes, okay?
lf there`s any snow coming your way,
you`re gonna know where it`s coming from
and how to get out of the way.
l promise you that.
Man, l`m sorry about what happened.
-Hey.
-Yeah, l got your note.
He died the way he wanted to.
l miss him.
l miss him so much.
l miss him, too.
l`m sorry l left him.
This wasn`t your fault,
and you don`t have to do this.
-Please, just come home.
-Listen, l owe it to him.
l already lost a brother.
l cannot lose you, too. l won`t.
We made a pact
that we were gonna do Meteorite and...
And he`s still up there.
l gotta finish it.
l guess you`re gonna have to make room
for one more.
-Hey, Dean.
-Yeah.
-You share some poison?
-Okay.
Here you go.
So, how did it go today?
Pretty good. Pretty good.
A little preparation time.
Everything went fine.
l hate to tell you this,
but there`s another storm coming in.
You know l`m one run away
from finishing this movie, huh?
l need you to get Tyler up there
tomorrow morning.
You know,
l don`t wanna hear he`s not ready, either.
l`m not gonna say that `cause he is ready.
-But if the conditions aren`t right...
-Conditions?
ls that...
ls that what this is all about? Conditions?
`Cause you know what l think it`s about?
l think it`s about money. l think you flew him
out that day because you needed the cash.
l think it`s more about the decisions
that were made.
-A decision that cost Mark his life.
-That`s bullshit. Mark knew the risks.
He wasn`t ready.
You are under contract, Dean.
So, let`s conclude
our business tomorrow, okay?
Cheers.
See you at 7:00.
What?
What? Tell me.
Nothing.
l`m just happy you`re here, that`s all.
-Hey.
-What?
lt`s just you`re gonna need
your energy for tomorrow.
-All right.
-Keep packing.
-There`s been a change of plans.
-What?
Meet me outside in 15 minutes
and you`ll find out. All right?
Come on.
Okay.
-Where are they going?
-They ditched us, Steph.
Stay with me, buddy.
Listen, kid, i hate to teii you this,
but we gotta be off this mountain
in 20 minutes.
There`s a storm coming.
Ty, don`t forget,
i`m your eyes on this one, kid.
Let`s finish this.
Okay, kid. it`s aii yours.
On three. One, two, three.
Aii right, take it easy.
Hug the rib. Hug the rib.
We`ve got a iot of snow moving aiready.
Cut right.
Let your siough go by.
Get the hell out of there!
She`s coming apart!
Now, hang in there.
Where is he? Where did he go?
There.
Let the siough go by.
Tyler, are you all right?
-i`m fine.
-You`re done, pai.
-We`re coming in to get you.
-What?
it`s time to ball.
l thought you said you were
my eyes on this?
We`re coming in whether you like it or not.
l need you, Rider. What do l do, man?
What do l do?
Dean, is that Mark`s line directly below me?
Forget it, you`re done, we`re coming in.
-ls it or isn`t it?
-Yes.
Tyler, please don`t do something crazy.
You guys got to trust me on this one.
Don`t even think about it, Tyler.
What`s he doing?
Okay, kid. it`s aii yours.
You got a 15-foot drop dead ahead.
-Take your shot, kid.
-Please, baby, get it. Come on.
Sweet Jesus!
-You did it!
-We did it.
Nice job, kid.
Hey, kid. i`ve got a proposition for you.
Oh, yeah? What`s that?
You can forget everything you know
about high-elevation snow, boys.
This is Alaska.
8,000-foot conditions at sea level.
Game plan for tomorrow is Fissile Peak,
6:00 a.m. pending bluebird.
-What`s bluebird?
-Clear skies.
-Jesus.
-No, Mother Nature.