There is no chance.
no destiny...
no fate.
There's only
what you take from the world
and what
the world takes from you.
I miss you...
you know?
Sometimes I think about
the way you were,
the way
you treated me,
the good times,
the bad times.
And I just wish I could have
another chance at things.
Stop me if you've
heard this one before.
You will always be my girl.
Karl?
Sorry, I didn't mean
to interrupt.
No, I'm fine.
We've been
through all this before.
Are those for Mommy?
Yeah.
Did you pick them?
Mm-hmm.
They're pretty.
Nikky's bag's
in the car.
I can go grab it
if you two want to be alone.
Actually, I wanted to...
I meant to ask you,
do you think maybe you could
keep her till tomorrow?
But, Daddy,
you promised.
I got something
I need to take care of.
I know, baby.
Look, I'm sorry.
I'll make it up to you.
Please.
Just this once?
Oh, it's not a problem.
But can we.
Hey, Nikky,
did you want to play something?
Do you want to play
Marco Polo?
Yeah.
Go on.
So what's going on?
Is it something
at the hospital?
Something like that,
yeah.
I'm worried about you.
I'm doing better
and better
Daddy, I'm ready.
Marco.
Polo.
Yet we always seem
to find you here.
I like to come visit.
You know, I like to tell her
what I've been up to.
I just...
Nikky's been making
so much progress.
Come on, Daddy!
Marco.
Polo!
I feel like coming here
sets her back a little, you know?
Seeing you like this,
I think she worries,
after what
her mother did,
that you, if you got
depressed enough, might...
Never.
Look, I love Nikky
more than anything in the world.
Nothing's going
to happen to her.
Nothing.
I promise.
Marco.
Polo!
I'll bring her by
at 2:30 tomorrow.
Great.
Sharp.
Sure.
Boo!
See you tomorrow, okay?
Dr. Lewis, call ER stat.
Miss Matera?
I want to see her.
Yeah, Claudia,
you will.
I just think we should
have a word first.
Okay, tell me.
We did our best,
and the operation
was successful,
but with patients her age,
the body just can't
handle the stress.
I'm sorry.
At this point,
it's a matter of time.
Hey.
Hi, Karl.
Listen, just to confirm,
we do need you tonight.
What about Dr. Stark?
He asked for a day off.
Again?
Jesus Christ.
That guy takes more days off...
I know,
But we need you, Karl.
I know, but I can't.
I physically can't.
You know, I'm sorry,
but I'm not on call.
You're out of the city?
I've got something
I have to do.
Something you have to...
Yeah, something
for my daughter.
Yeah, okay, Karl.
Well, thanks anyway.
I'm sorry to bother you.
Okay, bye.
Oh, hello, ladies,
let me give you...
Here, let me help you
with some of that stuff.
Oh, thank you so much.
You heading away
for the 4th of July, Miss Maurie?
Oh, they're
turning us out again.
Units ready,
units not ready,
this building.
Okay.
Can you manage?
Good-bye, Lana.
Bye. Thank you.
Good-bye, Karl.
Chloe. Hey.
Thanks.
And stay out of the heat,
ladies.
Oh, I will.
That's comforting.
You know,
they don't always open.
I've seen
some nasty accidents.
Yeah,
I'll keep that in mind.
Okay, what did you hit, kid?
I didn't hit anything.
I'm kidding.
We'll be up and running
any second now.
Any second now.
Told you
it didn't sound good.
It could be a silent alarm.
We're not in a bank.
I have my phone.
There's no service.
Yeah, I probably shouldn't
use any more minutes anyhow.
That's clever.
Lighten up, kid.
Look, I got somewhere to be,
okay?
Well, I don't,
you know?
I was actually hoping
this might happen.
God, Christ,
my life is empty.
I have just captured
the perfect image of angst.
Erase the picture.
Why?
Just do it.
Just fuckin' do it.
Okay?
She needs it.
Hurry.
Claudia?
Claudia,
where did you put them?
Put what?
Oh, don't be
coy with me.
They were right here.
I don't go around
hiding your asthma inhaler.
My inhaler's not gonna kill me.
50 years from now,
who knows?
Mm, scientists.
There you go.
Aren't you going to join me?
No, I can't.
I have a to-do list
a mile long.
I should have never
gone to bed last night.
Are you going out
like that?
I left my black veil
at the cleaners.
I want more skin,
not less.
We live on the beach.
What are you, a nun?
Yes, Abuela,
I am a nun.
When I was your age,
I set this town on fire.
Let's go to the beach.
Uh-uh.
I can't.
Mid-terms
start next week.
Life is for living.
I know. I know.
I'm trying to do that.
I just...
have to take care
of some stuff first.
Listen, I love you,
so don't take this the wrong way,
but you
are starting to suck.
If you don't break,
you'll bend.
Isn't it, if you don't bend,
you'll break, I think?
No, no.
No, it's not.
I mean, if you don't start
taking breaks and breathe,
you'll mist
into someone really horrible.
Okay, we'll go
to the beach,
just for a little while.
Keep Calm.
You are not in danger.
Got any water
in here, dude?
In most cases,
the elevator mechanic
will arrive in 3O minutes.
O1:38
and counting.
Hey.
Where you going?
Where do you think?
The ladies bathroom.
You look good tonight.
I think your friends...
I think they're leaving.
I think
we're at floor level.
What do you think?
Yeah, it's worth a look.
Yeah.
Be careful.
Hey, can you
give us a hand?
What do you expect me to do?
My hands are sweaty too.
Maybe you'll let me see that.
Shit.
You always carry this
around with you, kid?
A lot of dangerous people
out there.
Oh, shit.
Somebody help!
Hello?
Help!
Can anybody hear us?
Shh. Do you hear something?
I don't hear
anything at all.
Hello?
Hello!
We need help
with the elevator.
Let it go on three.
One, two, three.
Shit.
Somebody must've heard us.
This building
is empty, man.
Even the freaking
Golden Girls are gone.
Wait.
Who else lives in the building?
There's got to be...
there's that couple, right?
They have a newborn baby.
People don't go
on vacations with babies.
Really?
Have you been
on an airplane lately?
Hey, we're
all in this together.
You don't have
to be an asshole.
So I can't even
disagree with you?
My God,
what a fascist.
That's not...
... Look!
Let's calm down, okay?
With this heat wave,
every air-conditioner
in the city's running.
It's a blackout.
Well, then, that means the power
should be back on soon.
Well, the one a few years ago
lasted almost mo days.
Someone died
in a fucking elevator.
They died?
It's not a blackout.
How do you explain
the emergency lights?
It's a back-up generator, genius.
My hospital
has a back-up generator.
Banks have
back-up generators.
Well, what if
the elevator's broken?
Huh?
Wait, wait, wait.
How many units have been rented?
I think it's,
like, half finished.
Half finished?
There's five.
Well, there's
okay, this is three.
You live with
your parents, right?
Where are they?
I don't know. Aruba.
Okay, Maurie sisters.
That makes four.
And the couple who are staying
with their relatives
while they're having
their plumbing redone.
They got a baby in tow.
That makes five.
This could be a while.
Shit.
It's a gateway drug.
You got to start somewhere.
Tom?
I wanted
to ask you something.
Someone told Olivia
at school that
last year, you were banging Eve,
among others.
Sometimes I just worry
that you do this with everyone,
that your promises,
things you say...
I don't think
it's an act, but...
Help us!
I need
to get out of here!
Don't yell!
Help!
Oh, God!
Tommy, calm
Hey, listen,
calm down.
Hey, calm down.
Calm down.
No, get off me!
Oh, my God.
Oh, shit.
You motherfucker.
I'm really sorry.
Oh, Jesus,
let me get a look at that.
Please.
You got to keep
pressure on the lip.
Without ice,
that's going to swell.
Get off me, man!
Hey, stop yelling.
Don't tell me what to do!
Calm down.
Look, I have got
somewhere to be, and if this
We all do!
Okay, the air is getting
really thin in here, okay?
We need to relax.
We need to think logically, okay?
Let me get that knife.
Okay.
The mountains it ain't,
but it's not bad.
I know I didn't know you then,
and I shouldn't care, but...
Look. Eve.
it was a drunk thing.
It was once.
And you...
You're pretty much
the only right choice
I've ever made
in my life.
And you know that l
Francesca!
Shh.
Francesca?
Fuck. It's early.
He must've lost.
He must've lost bad.
Lost at what?
Cards.
Get dressed.
You never told me
your father gambles.
Doesn't everyone?
Did you put it somewhere?
Where is the mail?
I mean,
are you going to be okay?
One fucking thing for me,
and you can't even do that.
Francesca!
You said your father
was an accountant.
You said he never drinks.
He's not,
and he does.
I'll tell you the rest
of the gory details later,
but right now,
you need to get out.
I'm the only one that can
calm him when he loses.
He can't stay mad
at his little girl.
Go.
Hey.
Hey, sorry
to sneak up on you.
Just
Who the fuck are you?
Dad, Dad,
this is my friend Tommy.
Hey, easy, easy.
No, Dad, just don't. Don't.
In my house?
Fuck!
What the hell?
Calm down.
It's cool.
It's okay.
You have a family?
I have a daughter,
yeah.
She's eight.
She's coming at 2:3O tomorrow.
I don't think I've ever
seen her around here.
We have a house
outside the city.
I bought this apartment
for nights I work late
at the hospital.
You have a wife?
She's, um...
she passed away,
unfortunately.
Yeah, she passed away,
Oh, I'm so sorry.
Yeah, well, it was hard.
It was hard
for a long time.
But, you know, when I look
at my daughter now,
I can still
I can still see my wife in her.
You know,
she's never really gone.
I think I can handle one more.
It's really so nice
to finally hang out with a guy
and not have to worry about...
not have to worry about,
you know?
Yeah, I know
what you mean.
Go on.
Okay, one, two, three.
What do you see
up there?
Is there a door?
The one back here is wall
but there's another
about 15 feet up there.
Maybe I can try
to open it.
Do you think
you can climb up there?
You need help up there?
No, no. It's all right. I can reach it.
Oh, thank God.
We're gonna be okay.
Shit.
Oh, God.
I'm sorry
about before,
when I hit him.
Oh, it's all right.
You had to do something.
I was afraid
it might upset you.
I'm fine.
Besides, he seems
to be over it.
I feel like I'm never going to graduate.
I wish your grandfather
could've seen you...
Worked in response...
Life is for living?
What does that
even mean?
I am living my life right now.
You were just wonderful.
Life is work.
That's what I have to do.
I want better things for you.
Maybe it'll change at some point.
Better and better.
As soon as we get out of here,
there's something I have to do
Something about...that?
I mean the blood.
Some kind of accident?
It's okay.
You don't have to.
I have something
I need to do too.
Does it have to do
with your daughter?
More like
for my daughter.
She's getting dropped off
here tomorrow, 2:30.
And I really need
to clean up.
She might not like
what she'd find.
Come here.
Sit down.
Would you like
some wine?
Yeah, I'd love some.
Red?
White?
Pink?
White sounds good.
Okay.
Thanks.
Come on.
Get loose.
Feel like you're at home.
Put your head back.
This place, it's kind of like
my bachelor pad, you know?
I usually use it for alone time.
What is it, porn?
Do I look
like that kind of guy?
Yes, porn.
Let yourself go.
Let go.
Lose it with me.
Uh!
Oh, my God.
Shit.
What the hell was that?
What the fuck
did you do up there?
Hey, are you okay up there?
Don't touch my leg.
Don't touch it.
Ugh.
It's that bad, huh?
What the fuck
did you do up there?
Karl, help me, please.
No, no, no!
No, no.
Hey.
Karl, please!
Please.
Oh, fuck.
Ah!
Grab that knife.
Oh, God.
Well, it's definitely broken.
Is he going to be okay?
If we get out of here soon, yes.
We don't
Wait. I don't want
to lose my leg.
Yeah, well
that's a long ways off.
But we can do something.
I have some pills,
some painkillers.
I have water. Here.
You could've
mentioned that sooner.
Sorry.
For the pain, Tommy.
I just don't drink it all, okay?
That's all we have.
That's it.
What does it say?
Your emerg…
Help!
We need medical attention in here.
Please help!
I think it only works
one way.
Please help us!
Please.
We're aware of your emergency.
Please stay calm.
An elevator mechanic
will be with you shortly.
And make it quick.
Thank God.
Any second now.
How do you think they're
going to pull us out of here?
Let them worry
about the logistics.
Right now, I just want
to get out of here.
We're aware of your emergency.
Please stay calm.
An elevator mechanic
will be with you shortly.
We're aware
of your emergency.
Please stay calm.
An elevator mechanic
will be with you shortly.
We're aware
of your emergency.
Please stay calm.
Almost 4:OO in the morning.
Been in here
nine hours.
Severe internal bleeding.
Her organs
are beyond repair.
If she wasn't such a fighter,
she'd be gone already.
Is she in pain?
She's sedated,
but she's conscious.
Does she know?
I was under explicit orders
not to feed her any bullshit.
Do you want me to call anyone,
parents, an aunt or uncle?
No, there's, um...
There's nobody.
It's always just been me
and my grandma, pretty much, so..
I'd like to see her now.
Help me!
Maybe we should sleep in shifts.
What's that going to do, kid?
If this elevator collapses,
it's going to do it whether
or not we're keeping guard.
Remember, it's going to be
daylight soon.
And if one of us hears something,
like people outside,
we should be able to yell.
Tommy's right.
Of course he's right.
He disagreed with me.
So you want to go first?
I can't take this anymore.
What are we going to do?
What can I do?
Let's run away.
After last night,
he'll come back.
And things are only
gonna get worse.
You know it.
That's crazy.
What's crazy
is staying here with him.
We don't have
the money for that.
No, but my father does.
And I know
where he keeps it.
My father...
He always keeps some cash
around the house for betting.
I found a wad yesterday.
Take it.
He owes you.
If he finds out it's missing
No, we'll be
at the airport.
Tonight?
Tonight.
We need to think about
rationing that water.
He needs it.
Yeah, well, he's going
to need it in six hours too.
And we'll need it
in six hours.
We weren't the ones
who tried to play superhero.
We're gonna be
out of here by then.
Yeah?
I hope so.
Hey.
No way.
Excuse me?
Please don't.
I have asthma.
I'll blow my smoke
out the opening.
Sorry. No.
Look, it's been a long time, lady.
I don't know if you've
ever had an addiction
Oh, I don't know
if you've ever had
your throat close up
on you before.
Well, you have
your inhaler, right?
Yeah, but that's
not he point
Well, you know,
you'll be fine.
I'm a doctor,
remember?
Tommy?
Tommy!
Tommy, I know you're in there.
I saw your motorcycle outside.
Thanks a lot,
asshole.
Put it out.
I have asthma.
I said, ''Cut it out.''
I asked you
to put it out, now.
I'm telling you
to put that thing out.
I'm almost done.
It's blowing back
in the room.
No, it isn't.
Stop fighting.
This isn't good
for any of us.
Jesus Christ,
calm down, Claudia.
Maybe you should have one.
Oh, okay, you want
to fucking pollute the air?
Go ahead. We'll just
close the fucking door.
Ow!
Sorry.
Fucking bitch!
And everything
for a fucking cigarette!
Great. Now we got
a regular gimp collection.
I said I'm sorry.
It's been five hours, and we're already
like lord of the flies.
I said I'm sorry, okay?
Just like a woman!
Look, this isn't helping.
And, you know,
it's true, kid.
You used to be able to smoke
anywhere, fucking anywhere:
movie theaters, airplanes,
hospitals, supermarkets.
Fucking moral majority's
taken over!
Calm down.
Oh, God,
I need to get out of here.
Let us out of here!
I hate this God damn
Let us the fuck out!
Oh, my God,
you have a temper.
God!
What, just like a woman?
Exactly, just like a woman
to set a guy off...
And then calmly criticize him
for blowing up!
What the fuck
is your problem?
This is it.
Nobody move.
Shit.
Don't fucking move.
Shh.
Tommy?
We were born in these lives,
Francesca.
We didn't have a choice.
But it's time that we take over
and do it for ourselves.
Help me!
Don't cry.
Abuela, I'm sorry.
When it's your turn,
it's your turn.
Shh, don't talk.
It's okay.
I have to.
Last chance
to piss you off.
Abuela,
it's not funny.
Remember.
you'll have to bend
Isn't it ''break''?
Whatever.
I just need you
to get me something.
The photograph
on my table.
I need him with me
when my time comes.
I'll get you
the photograph.
At this point, it's a matter of time.
How long?
Uh, maybe tomorrow,
maybe...
in a few hours.
Claudia.
Hurry.
I love you.
You've been holding out on us.
What?
first water.
Now candy?
Fucking convenience store
you got there.
Asshole.
What the
what are you doing?
Give it to me.
Give me
the candy bar.
No.
Don't.
Jesus, don't.
Here.
Give it back, please.
What the fuck?
That isn't cool, man.
Give it back to me, please.
I'd rather not.
Chill out, man.
Now, look...
We're not going
to get out of here
until we stop
yelling at each other
and start working together.
And we need one person, one,
to make all the decisions.
We need a strong leader.
Now, I'm just
strengthening my hand.
And don't worry.
I'll give you a hit
when you need one,
if you behave.
What kind of a monster are you?
Monster?
Don't you think you're being
a bit dramatic?
Maybe I'm just destined
for something else.
I don't know.
I'd like to think I'm meant
for higher things, though, you know?
Higher things.
My father always told me,
''To endure
is to conquer our fate.''
Fate?
Yeah.
Do you really believe
that shit?
I like your eyes.
Destiny sucks.
You'll be fine.
Yeah, you'll be fine.
There's no chance.
No destiny.
No fate.
There's only
what you take from the world
and what the world
takes from you.
You know that now,
don't you...
my darling?
What the hell are you doing, man?
Just making sure everything still works.
She's pretty good-looking, isn't she?
I got a girlfriend, man.
At least I did.
God, I hope
she's okay.
He's going to know by now.
Oh, boo-hoo.
My little girl sees
the mess I made upstairs,
let me just say,
her idea of me
as the perfect father
is going to be
severely tested.
2:3O.
She's going
to be up there at 2:3O.
And her lips
were trembling,
and I take this blade,
and I cut her up.
And it's beautiful.
It's fucking beautiful.
We were supposed
to run away to Paris.
Do people still run away?
I thought
we placated all you kids
with cell phones
and video games.
Shut up, man.
No, I'm just
kidding around.
Paris, it's a great city.
The food.
Some of the women there
are even more sexually
adventurous than I am,
and that's
saying something.
We're going to have
to get something on these cuts.
What do you think
she's like?
What do you mean?
Usually the hot ones,
they just lay there.
You're out of line, man.
It's true.
Bitches are so used
to getting there way.
And why?
Just 'cause
they look pretty.
Salt.
Up and down.
Last breaths.
She seems
like she likes this.
Salt.
They get all the jobs.
They get
all the attention.
But what about
the rest of us, Tommy?
What about us?
Sometimes I wonder
why was I born
in such a fucked-up era?
Yeah, man.
Fucked up.
Yeah.
Well, you'll see what I mean
someday, buddy.
Pills, man.
Please.
7:3O.
Hope.
Let's have
some fucking hope.
They're gonna find her.
Can you feel me now?
The building, man.
Do you think...
Do you think
it was terrorists?
Terrorists?
In the Bifrost Bridge Building?
Yeah.
You know what?
I'd say it was
definitely terrorists.
But how do you think
they made it past
all the security downstairs?
Maybe it was aliens, man.
Like in
The TwilightZone,
when the electricity goes out,
and everybody thinks
it was everyone else.
But really,
it was aliens.
Well.
I don't know
about that.
But there's one thing
I do know,
and that is that if I don't
get out of here soon,
I'm going to cut
your fucking throat...
and I'm going to rape
the shit out of that cunt.
What?
Oh, God, how many cigarettes
have you smoked?
Please give me my inhaler.
Give it to me.
Please give me
my inhaler.
Please.
God damn it.
You'll get over it.
I want to show you
something.
Look.
Come here.
Fire alarm.
You hold this
underneath the sensor
and we'll be hearing sirens
before you've even climbed down.
I'm having
a hard time breathing.
You want a hit?
- Please.
Okay.
- No.
And since you're going up there anyway...
Now, look, I really,
really need to excuse myself
from this elevator.
So don't you dream
of coming back here
without setting
that alarm off.
Come on.
You can do this.
What the.
Fuck.
Claudia?
My daughter
should be here by now.
Oh, you are dead,
you fucking cunt.
Claudia.
Claudia?
Hey.
I'm right here.
Are you okay?
Yeah, listen, I was on the top
of the elevator right now.
Jesus.
What's going on?
Karl.
Can you imagine how
she's going to react?
What?
My little girl,
Nikky.
Nobody should need
to see that kind of thing.
I protected her
the first time.
What are you talking about, Karl?
I did.
Why are you
You can plan
your whole life out.
You can plot
the most complex course.
But sooner or later
you're going to walk
into some piece-of-shit elevator.
Karl?
Listen to me.
Listen.
I was on top
of the elevator right now.
I looked over the side,
and I could see that
we're almost at floor level.
The optimism of youth.
It's remarkably enduring.
In fact.
it's usually
the last thing to go
when I cut some bitch up.
Fuck.
Their eyes pleading
and hoping to the end.
You can almost
hear them thinking,
''This isn't me.''
No, this isn't me.
Get the fuck
away from me.
''This isn't my life.
''I got class tonight.
I can't be late for class.''
Get the fuck
away from me.
Why do they always say that?
Stop it.
Hey, you want
to play something?
Marco.
Come on, guys.
Please stop.
The way it goes:
Marco.
You killed him.
Finally,
some privacy.
You killed him.
What's the point, Claudia?
We all know
how this ends.
Please.
You think the others
didn't say please?
I can get us out of here.
Give me the knife.
You have got
to be kidding me.
Okay, I won't tell anyone.
Please have a conscience.
Think about
your daughter.
Daddy.
What are you doing?
Please.
Daddy, you're not playing well.
What conscience?
She'll never learn!
So now learn!
Oh!
Get off!
Ah!
Uh!
Get fucking back here!
Hey, Claudia.
Claudia?
How is she?
My grandmother;
how is she?
We'll talk about it later.
Tell me now.
I'm sorry.
I didn't get her the photograph.
I tried.
Why do things
like this happen?
I used to think
about that too.
After working here
for a while.
I don't think
there is any reason,
no pattern.
Yeah.
You get some rest, okay?