[ Serena ]
Oh, I'm so excited.
[ Hercules Chuckling ]
Serena, we're only going
to the marketplace.
I know, but I could never
do this before,
not without fear
of being touched and
turning back into the Hind.
This is such
a great feeling
of freedom.
I'm glad
you're happy.
Are you?
Absolutely.
No regrets.
Well--
No. No regrets.
Hmm.
We could always
go in later.
Yeah, except Iolaus
is waiting for us,
and we stood him up
yesterday.
But it is
our honeymoon.
Good point.
[ Giggling ]
Wait! Wait, wait--
It would be rude.
Huh?
I mean-- Iolaus did help
with the house and--
Yeah.
Well, we can...
come back early.
I've created
a monster.
We'll come back early.
[ Giggles ]
[ Laughing ]
[ Chattering ]
I still can't believe it--
Hercules getting married!
And to a deer, no less.
Excuse me.
Did you say
Hercules got married?
To the Golden Hind--
last of her kind!
[ Laughing ]
Yeah, I heard he gave up
all his powers to marry her.
She must be something.
Yeah.
Come on, Gabrielle.
I can see it now.
He comes in and says,
"Deer, I'm home."
"Bought you a salt lick
for your birthday."
Salt lick!
[ Gabrielle ]
I know. It's that Hercules
didn't tell you.
That's what's
upsetting you.
Gabrielle.
Xena, you know, you shouldn't
bottle up your emotions.
Now, if there's some sort
of hurt or jealousy
operating here,
then get it out.
Gabrielle!
"Deer, I'm home!"
You're too much!
[ Gabrielle ]
Oh, great.
Just walk away from me.
What am I,
talking to myself here?
[ Bones Cracking ]
Strife,
I think you set
my little plan
in action.
Well done.
Get your fabric right here.
Come on. Step up.
[ Gasps ] Look.
Check that out.
Whoo-hoo!
[ Kissing Sounds ]
Let me take
a better look at you!
Let's just... keep moving.
Hey, baby,
how about a kiss?
[ Laughing ]
That's one prime piece
of venison.
Excuse me, but that's my wife
you're talking about.
Just ignore them, Hercules.
- Bet she's nice to snuggle
up to in the winter.
- [ Men Laughing ]
- All that soft deer fur.
- [ Chuckling ]
Ah, fellas,
look, I'm in
a good mood today,
so why don't you just
apologize, and we'll go on
our separate ways.
Now, why would we do that?
Especially since
you lost your strength.
Yeah, well, at least
I haven't lost my manners.
Let's just go find Iolaus.
I can handle this
myself.
[ Man Grunting ]
Hercules!
[ Grunting ]
You gotta rock
for a head?
Of course, he does.
[ Grunting ]
Oh.
[ Straining ]
- How's it feel to be like
the rest of us?
- [ Grunts ]
-[ Woman ] He shouldn't have
given up his strength.
- Which part of you...
shall I break first?
[ Man Narrating ]
This is the story
of a time long ago,
a time of myth and legend,
when the ancient gods
were petty and cruel,
and they plagued mankind
with suffering.
Only one man dared
to challenge their power--
Hercules.
Hercules possessed a strength
the world had never seen,
a strength surpassed
only by the power of his heart.
He journeyed the earth,
battling the minions
of his wicked stepmother, Hera,
the all-powerful
queen of the gods.
But wherever
there was evil,
wherever an innocent
would suffer,
there would be... Hercules.
- [ Screeching ]
- [ Roaring ]
Hail!
[ Chuckling ]
[ Grunting ]
-[ Woman ]
That's better.
- [ Screams ]
[ Man Groaning ]
Yaaah!
[ Shouting ]
Ow.
[ Groaning ]
Now, about that apology.
Sorry.
Are you all--
I said, I could take care
of this myself!
But--
You're welcome.
We were just trying--
When I say
I don't need any help,
I don't need any help!
Unless you two don't think
I'm up to this anymore!
I thought maybe--
I've never
seen him like that.
Herc, wait up!
[ Iolaus ]
Herc! Wait!
Ah! Don't you ever,
ever doubt me again!
I might not have all
my strength, but I'm not some
helpless, impotent old man...
who can't fight
his own battles!
What is wrong with you?
Nothing!
Nothing has changed!
[ Groans ]
Hercules,
are you all right?
I'm--
I don't know
what got into me. I--
I was worried about you.
I know.
I've never seen you
get so angry over--
I'm sorry.
I'm--
Oh, sweetheart.
It's okay.
And?
I got old Hercules
coming and going.
Good. Next step is to
get him going, going, gone.
No sweat.
I haven't even hit him
in dreamland yet.
Um, about... payment--
Hey, don't worry.
You'll be amply rewarded.
I-I-I mean, if I could
just get a hint.
I certainly don't expect
to get into your category,
but, uh, maybe,
you know, if I was, say,
"God of Skirmishes."
That was a joke. Dig?
[ Laughing ]
Dig Hercules's grave!
And learn how to talk
so I can understand you.
[ Sighs ]
You gotta learn
to relax more, Strife,
to savor the moments
of existence.
Example: This is the site of
one of my greatest triumphs,
the battle of Torrance.
10,000 corpses littered
the battleground.
The stench was...
[ Sniffs ]
invigorating!
So, who was the great general
responsible for this...
aroma?
No general.
It was a warrior--
Xena.
She led her army
through opponents' infantry
like flies.
Limbs were
scattered everywhere!
It was beautiful.
[ Sighs ]
You miss her,
don't you?
It's a shame
she decided to change sides.
I wouldn't give up
on her just yet.
Death's perfume
can be very...
addictive.
Let's just see
how my game plan unfolds.
Hercules, you need
your privacy, hmm?
I'm gonna go fishing
for a few days or at least
till your honeymoon's over.
Oh, you're gonna be gone
that long, are you?
[ Giggles ]
Well, you're not planning
a six-month honeymoon,
are you?
Mmm. We were thinking
more in terms of forever.
Okay. Well,
I got an early start tomorrow.
Why don't you stop by
for breakfast?
I mean, it's on the way.
- I'm leaving at dawn.
- That's all right.
We'll be up.
Come as early
as you like.
[ Sighs ]
- Iolaus.
- Okay, but only for
a quick visit, all right?
Okay.
[ Inhales Deeply ]
I want to remind all of you
to come to our town meeting
tomorrow night.
We'll be discussing
the formal dedication of our
new water cistern to Hercules.
Just a minute!
Don't you realize the trouble
you'll be bringing on
yourselves by doing that?
But Hercules is a friend
of ours. He helped us
build that cistern.
And what has he done
for you lately?
Married a creature
that is half human,
half animal!
That's right.
The gods can't be pleased
with that!
Hercules isn't
hurting anyone.
And nothing bad has happened
to any of us yet.
Oh? What happened
in the marketplace today?
Think that's the last incident
like that we'll see?
Every young punk
from here to Hellespont...
will be showing up
to challenge Hercules
to test his strength!
[ Man ]
Yeah! That's right!
[ Woman ] Yeah!
What do you suggest we do?
Go to him.
Tell him to leave.
Take our town back
before it's too late!
[ Crowd Chattering ]
- What do you think?
- He makes a good point.
Maybe he's right.
- We'll talk to Hercules
first thing in the morning.
-[ Man ] Yes!
[ Serena ]
You know--
[ Hercules ] Hmm?
If you want to go fishing
with Iolaus--
I'm a big girl.
I can take care of myself.
Hmm. Well, maybe
we should all go.
[ Giggling ]
You know what Iolaus says
about "three's a crowd."
So is two as far
as fishing and Iolaus
is concerned.
He'll have a better time
by himself.
Mm-hmm.
I just don't want you
to change your lifestyle
because of me.
I-I know how you help people,
the adventures you go on.
I don't want to
upset that.
You won't.
It's just a matter of balancing
what I do out there,
and what I do at home...
Hmm.
with my family.
Family?
[ Chuckles ]
Oh, yeah.
I love you so much.
Well, you're pretty
andsmart.
Mmm.
Aha.
dd Hey, Cousin Morpheus
throw Herc a dream dd
dd Shake up a wild one
Make him yell and scream dddd
Shake up a wild one.
Make him yell and scream.
[ Grunts ]
Oh-ohhh.
[ Hercules's Voice ]
Don't you ever,
ever doubt me again!
I might not have all
my strength, but I'm not some
helpless, impotent old man...
who can't fight
his own battles!
[ Serena's Voice ]
What is wrong with you?
Nothing!
- Nothing has changed!
- If nothing's changed,
then how come you let
that soldier back there
almost brain you?
- I can take care of myself!
- And me?
Can you take care of me
like you did
your first family?
- Don't talk about them.
- I gave up everything for you!
I was the last of my kind!
And now I can't protect myself!
And you gave up your strength.
You can't protect me!
- How am I supposed to feel?
- I am warning you!
- Oh, go ahead!
Hit me! Hit me!
- [ Shouts ]
- Oh, show me
what a strong man you are!
- [ Shouts ]
Blood.
Serena?
[ Pants ]
dddd [ Whistling ]
[ Chattering ]
Morning!
]
dddd [ Whistling
[ Hercules ]
No!
Herc! Herc?
Hercules?
Uh.
A pillow.
I, uh--
I-I need a pillow.
Sh-She's uncomfortable.
Hercules.
Huh?
- She's dead.
- No! She--
[ Panting ]
Murderer!
- You killed her!
- No!
Wait! Wait! Wait a minute!
Take it easy!
Get them out of here!
He doesn't know
what he's saying.
Go! Get 'em out!
Go on! Go!
Get out!
Go.
Go!
Ah, the Three Fates.
Clotho spins
the thread of life.
My dear Lachesis
measures it.
And my dearest Atropos...
cuts it.
That is Hercules's lifeline.
Another god can't kill him.
And he's protected by Zeus.
[ Clicks Tongue ]
Oh, no more.
He sinned against
the gods.
He's killed a mortal
in cold blood.
[ Man ]
Wait!
- Zeus.
- Who gave you permission?
This has already
been dealt with.
The other gods have voted.
And I wasn't informed?
You were unreachable.
Off on one of
your dalliances,
I suspect.
I can't believe my son
killed anyone in cold blood.
He's gone mad.
See for yourself.
[ Shouting ]
If he's guilty,
he'll be punished,
but not by you.
Bring him in
before the Olympians.
Shouldn't he be tried
among mortals,
now that he is one...
completely?
Then you'd better
make sure he lives
to see a fair trial.
It's out of my hands.
What if he refuses
to give himself up?
He's your son.
You know how stubborn
he can be.
What are you gonna do?
I have to find a magistrate,
tell him what happened.
Herc, I don't think
this is such a good idea.
I've just come from town,
and they're forming a lynch mob.
A lynch mob?
What, for me?
Yeah.
I know you didn't
kill her, but--
Maybe I did.
What?
I'm not sure what happened
in there, you see.
I've had these dreams.
I keep seeing myself--
[ Man ] There he is!
There's the murderer!
Listen, you better
get out of here.
He'll pay for what he's done!
I'll try and talk
some sense into them.
I'm not gonna--
Herc, you've got to go!
[ Mob Chattering ]
Okay l-let's take it easy,
fellas. Come on, let's think
about this for a second.
I mean--
Out of the way, shorty!
You can't defend a murderer!
[ Mob Chattering ]
Huh! Hyah!
Come on! Come on!
Come on! Giddyap!
Come on!
[ Mob Shouting ]
Hyah! Come on! Come on!
You'll pay for it!
He's going up in the trees.
You are
obstructing justice!
Out of our way!
Look, you can't just
hunt him down like
some common criminal.
This is Hercules
you're going after.
I'm afraid he's not
the Hercules we knew.
You saw with your own two eyes,
just like we did!
Step aside!
Hercules is a killer!
Hercules must be
brought to justice!
Psst. Hercules, over here.
- Who are you?
- My name is Veklos.
You might not remember,
but you once saved my life.
You can hide in here.
I've never hid from anything
before in my life.
I'm not about to start now.
Well, it was different then.
You had--
Look, those people
are out for blood.
Please, let me help you...
just until
things settle down.
[ Man ]
Let's check this way!
Thanks.
Let's check
the marketplace!
You saw the argument he had
with his wife, his anger!
Hercules is not himself
at the moment.
The gods could be
behind this!
Ah, that's my point!
Maybe they've driven him mad!
It doesn't matter
who's responsible!
He's become a danger
to the community!
Okay, I am going with you.
He'll listen to me.
If I talk to him, I can maybe
convince him to give himself up!
You're taking
a big chance helping me.
They think I'm a murderer.
[ Man ] Check all the houses!
[ Man #2 ] He's got to be
around here somewhere!
I don't know whether
you are or not. I only know
that once you helped me.
I'd like to
return the favor.
[ Knocking ]
Open up!
[ Woman ]
He's a murderer!
I'm looking for Hercules.
Have you seen him?
He ran by earlier,
and then headed back
toward the woods.
[ Woman ]
Get him!
Search everywhere!
Keep searching.
He couldn't have
disappeared into thin air.
Why?
With grief like that,
you couldn't have killed her.
Thank you.
I should get going.
But you're safe here.
I need to find out
who killed my wife.
Then go.
But trust no one.
[ Man ]
We must search
the town again.
He can't have gotten far.
There he goes!
Whoo!
[ Gasps ]
[ Man ]
Come on!
He went this way!
[ Grunts ]
We've got him now!
[ Grunting ]
Behind you!
He's getting away!
[ Grunts ]
[ Man ]
He's wounded!
Close in men!
- Surround him!
- Aaah!
- Hercules!
- What do you think
you're doing?
Hercules!
[ Xena Kiaiing ]
[ Kiaiing Continues ]
-[ Man ] It's Xena!
- It's the Warrior Princess!
[ Shouting ]
[ Cackling ]
[ Panting ]
Herc?
[ Groans ]
[ Iolaus ] He's in really
bad shape. I've never seen him
take a beating like this.
We need more water
and bandages. Hurry.
I'll be right back.
[ Sighs ]
The bleeding's stopped.
His other shoulder
is dislocated.
And he may have
fractured his skull.
He should not be moved.
It's a good thing
you came along
when you did.
I came as soon as I heard.
Is it true...
about him losing
his powers?
Yeah.
He must love her
very much.
- He did.
- Did?
Serena, his wife,
sh-she's dead.
And the townspeople
think he did it.
Serena, it's my fault.
I'm gonna go
and help Gabrielle.
I killed her.
Iolaus, are you okay?
Yeah.
Look, Iolaus--
[ Sighs ]
Hercules will be okay.
Xena is--
It's not that.
What is it?
Hercules thinks
he may have killed Serena.
I saw Hercules with a--
a bloody knife in his hand,
over the body.
I'm sorry
about Serena.
She was the most
beautiful woman.
I didn't think
I could ever love anyone
like that again.
I--
It's all right.
We're long past
the time when we
could've been together.
Tell me about
what happened.
I'm not sure. I--
When I woke up,
she was...
just lying next to me.
She was murdered in bed
right next to you,
and you didn't wake up?
It doesn't make sense.
It wasn't like any sleep
I ever had.
The dreams. I just--
What do you mean,
like nightmares?
No. It was worse.
It was violent.
It was so violent. It--
Like they were
from the gods.
Maybe they were.
But why?
I-I gave them my strength.
I gave them
what they asked for.
And they're
always known for keeping
their promises, right?
[ Whispering ]
Hey. Hey.
[ Groans ]
This smells of Ares.
It's my fault.
I never should have
trusted him to keep his word.
[ Straining ] I need to
find out what part Ares played
in this, what part I played.
You will.
But get well.
You still have time
to figure this out.
Yeah.
Xena.
What?
What's the matter?
It's Iolaus.
I've never seen him
like this before.
He-He's confused.
He's torn.
I'll go talk to him.
Keep an eye on him.
That head injury
still worries me.
What's in this goatskin?
Hopefully something
to save his life.
[ Xena ]
I never did thank you
for taking care of Gabrielle.
Thank you.
She's worried about you.
She says you seem upset.
My best friend falls in love,
breaks up our partnership,
and his wife gets killed,
and he's not sure
he didn't do it.
[ Scoffs ]
What's to be upset about?
It happens every day.
Have you ever considered
that the gods might be
behind this, all of it?
Yes, of course. So the gods
are behind it or are
responsible for it. So what?
What are you saying?
I know Hercules,
his sense of justice,
sense of honor.
If he thought there was
a remote chance
he killed Serena,
he would turn himself in
and spend the rest of his life
rotting in prison.
Yes, he would.
And?
And be remembered
throughout history,
not as a fighter for justice,
but as a--
as a wife killer.
And then everything
he stood for, everything
he fought for...
goes down the river
along with his reputation.
He doesn't deserve that.
No, he doesn't.
So what do you want
to do about it?
[ Clicks Tongue ]
I don't know.
I've tried to think
of... something.
[ Sighs ]
I've even considered confessing
to Serena's murder myself...
to spare him the shame
and humiliation of imprisonment.
He'd never
let you do that.
I know.
Unless--
Unless what?
Unless I kill him first.
You haven't got
the stomach for it.
He's your best friend.
You couldn't do it.
And you could?
If I had to.
If there was no other way.
I know you're confused.
But the gods are at work here.
All I'm asking is that
you hear me out.
And then...
you can do whatever
you think is right.
[ Gasps ]
[ Grunting ]
[ Gasping ]
Hercules, it's all right.
It's all right.
Just lie down.
It's okay.
If I did it,
I couldn't live with myself.
I'll get you
some water. Okay?
[ Groaning ]
Hercules?
Gabrielle,
where's Hercules?
I don't know.
I just went
to get some water.
I was afraid of this.
He's gonna turn himself in.
Xena, he took your sword.
To fall on?
No, he wouldn't do that.
But he might want to do
the next best thing--
charge into
overwhelming odds.
And die a warrior's death.
We've got to stop him.
[ Clicks Tongue ]
I gotta hand it
to you, Strife.
This has worked out better
than I could ever have imagined.
It's been fun.
Fun is good.
- So is dead.
- [ Twangs ]
dddd [ Hums ]
[ Chattering ]
[ Man ]
He's wounded!
He must be holed up
somewhere close.
If you're looking for me,
here I am!
It's him.
I wouldn't celebrate
just yet.
You got short memories.
Stay back unless you want more
of what we gave you before.
[ Man ]
Better do as she says.
No! Stop!
Out of my way, Iolaus.
I'm turning myself in.
I can't let you
do that, Hercules.
[ Man ]
Stay out of the way.
Get out of my way.
[ Sighs ]
Look, you're not listening
to reason. Why--
I'm warning you.
Don't try to stop me
from doing the right thing.
The right thing is to go back
with us till we find out
who really killed Serena.
We know who killed her!
Now step aside!
- Just put the sword down.
- [ Grunts ]
[ Fabric Tearing ]
[ Grunts ]
You've killed me.
[ Woman ]
Iolaus killed Hercules.
No! I-I didn't mean--
-[ Xena ] No!
- [ Panting ]
Get up! Get up!
[ Shouting ]
[ Grunting ]
[ Groaning ]
[ Groaning Continues ]
- You want to see
some more blood?
- [ Chattering ]
Bring it on.
Well done, Xena.
[ Snickering ]
Ares,
what are you doing here?
Let's just say
I have a vested interest
in all of this.
- You planned all of this.
- One must keep amused.
There is a way
to bring him back.
Come back to me...
where you belong.
How'd you do it?
How did you get someone
so noble and so strong
to kill his own wife?
I think I'll keep that
my little secret.
I think you're being
a little too modest
there, Uncle.
[ Strife Clears Throat ]
It was easy, you know.
A little
Morpheus-induced sleep,
and I just sort of...
slipped on by.
- You killed her.
- Yeah. Like I said,
it was easy.
What does it matter
who killed her?
[ Woman ] He's the one?
Hercules is dead,
and you're mine.
- It matters to me.
- [ Man ]
Hercules is alive.
Goatskin worked.
[ Shouting ]
Get up!
Help!
Fight him,
you pathetic little fool.
You're a god.
Use your powers!
Waaah!
Yeah!
- Take a hike!
- [ Shouting ]
- Even it up, Ares. Give
Hercules back his strength.
- No.
- I'm enjoying this too much.
-[ Blow Landing ]
You reneged
on your deal, Ares.
You said if he gave up
his powers, he'd be
happily married.
I lied.
So what?
Whoo!
[ Cackling ]
Ares, you heard them.
Play fair.
Father.
Strife, I'm back.
[ Screaming ]
[ Grunting ]
Uncle!
[ Cackles ]
Ares!
This isn't over yet!
No, it isn't.
[ Laughing ]
Zeus!
Don't you walk
away from me.
You handled yourself well.
Is that all you have
to say to me?
You have a strange way
of showing gratitude.
For what?
For saving you.
For giving you back
your powers!
[ Sighs ]
I would--
I would rather
have Serena back.
Son, you know I can't undo
what the gods have done.
I don't want to hear
about the other gods!
I mean, this is twice now
you've turned your back
on me and my family!
It's not that easy.
I have other responsibilities.
S-Since when have you been
responsible for anything?
When?
So, I don't even rate
a thank you.
Thanks.
But you're wrong
if you think that's gonna
change anything between us.
You give good scream.
[ Laughs ]
Well, let me
show you something.
Very nice.
You cut it
pretty close.
Well, it had to look real.
Another couple of centimeters,
it would've been real!
Yeah, but it wasn't.
Hercules?
[ Sighs ]
Don't ask.
Hey.
Glad you're okay.
I'm not okay.
Look, it isn't
much consolation,
but at least you know
you didn't kill Serena.
I did kill her.
If I hadn't fallen in love
and married her,
she'd be alive today.
dddd [ Xena Singing
In Foreign Language ]
dddd [ Singing Continues ]
[ Singing Stops ]
You weren't long
for this world, Serena.
At least not
in your mortal form.
[ Sighs ]
But you made the most
of your short life.
You loved,
and you were loved
in return.
That's the highest place
a mortal can aspire to.
And for that,
I am eternally grateful.
I--
[ Sighs ]
I will miss you.