My mother never told me
about her parents.
She regretted having to hide
such a pretty Russian name like Milla
between the ones
her foster family gave her.
But she told me the past
was another country now,
best forgotten.
It was in her nature to grow away
from the motherland,
just as it was in my nature
to grow away from her.
Sometimes I wish
I could go back myself,
to warn her that it wouldn't
be so easy, so simple...
that just because you're through
with your past
doesn't always mean
your past is ever
really through with you.
Yeah, what time is it over there?
No.
That's fine.
No. No, not yet.
Yeah, is Emily there?
Put her on, please.
Hey, sweetheart.
Yeah, Russia's...
Russia's beautiful...
kind of.
I'm... Well, I don't now just yet.
A couple of days.
What do you mean?
What, with Alex?
I thought...
No, I thought you weren't
seeing him anymore.
No, I don't have an...
I don't have an issue with him.
It's just...
Can you let me finish? Okay?
I don't have an issue with him.
It's just that I don't
want him staying over.
No, I don't care
what you guys do
in your own time,
just not in my house.
Hey, mind your language!
Yeah, because he's five
fucking years older than you!
Well, of course it's my business.
I'm your mother.
Yeah, l...
Can you just let me finish?
Emily?
Shit.
Mr. Misharin?
- I'm, uh, Marie...
- Marie Jones from America.
It's nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you, finally.
Make yourself at home.
Tea?
No, thanks.
- You produce movies, don't you?
- Yeah.
Big movies?
Well, probably big here.
You should see my daughter.
She's very pretty, you know?
Good for the movies.
I'm sure she's great.
You don't sound very American.
I was born in Russia,
raised in England,
and divorced in the States.
But your roots are here,
aren't they?
At least what's left of them.
Your mother's death certificate.
Can you read Russian?
No.
Her name was Olga.
Olga Kaidanovsky.
Apparently, she was murdered
just after you were born.
I tried to dig up everything I could,
as you requested.
You never knew about her?
No.
And my father?
Any brothers or sisters?
Sorry, no.
No records of anyone else.
Just the property you mentioned
on the phone, right?
Yeah, the Kaidanovsky place.
Now it belongs to you.
Look, I appreciate your efforts
on my behalf,
but it's been 40 years.
Forty-two.
Forty-one, if you insist on accuracy.
It's still another two days
till my birthday.
Yeah, so...
this is a present for you now.
Well...
Sign here, please.
Look, I didn't come
all the way out here
for the real estate, Mr. Misharin.
I've spent half my life
knee-deep in bureaucracy
trying to find my parents.
I've looked around, trust me,
but no one ever told me
a damn thing.
It was like
they never existed.
Our country has been
through a lot, Ms. Jones.
Governments change.
Things gets lost.
Sometimes people get lost.
So how did you find me?
I got your phone
from the Moscow office.
Took me six months.
You know, adoption was
a tricky business in the '60s.
Please.
I'm sorry.
I just... I don't...
I don't understand you.
You'll find this town
is not much good for postcards.
I didn't hear you pull up.
You must be Anatoliy.
You said 8:00 on the phone.
Right.
I can pay you now if you want.
It's impossible to go at night.
They think we'll die out there.
But I'd rather be dead
than live like them.
Is everyone is this country so friendly?
What?
Do you know anything
about my mother's place?
Kaidanovsky Farm.
They call it "The Island".
The only way to get there
is by a bridge.
A river surrounds it...
in a circle.
Great.
I can't even swim.
Hello? Anybody here?
We're almost there.
We already crossed the bridge.
I was dreaming.
No one has been here
for more than 40 years.
What do you expect
to find in those ruins?
I don't know.
Some clue perhaps,
something to make
sense of my life.
You really think so?
What are you doing?
You asked me to take you
to the Kaidanovsky Farm.
Well, here we are.
The house is just
behind those trees.
I'll go ahead
to make sure it's safe.
Hey, wait a minute.
The river is in flood.
You don't want to be
wandering around out there,
not if you can't swim.
Anatoliy?
Oh, no.
Shit.
Jesus, not now.
Come on.
Shit!
No...
Anatoliy?
Oh, for God's sake.
Hey, where the hell are you?
Kaidanovsky.
Anyone here?
Hello?
Who's there?
Hey.
I'm not going to hurt you.
Oh, shit!
Oh, shit.
Anatoliy.
Wait! Come back!
Shit.
Hey. Please, calm down.
Just stay the fuck away.
Who the hell are you?
My name is Nicolai.
What are you doing?
I got you out of there.
You almost drowned.
Listen.
Who are you?
I think we are here
for the same reason.
So what else did you find
in my bag?
She's my mother.
You were adopted, weren't you?
I've been trying to find
my birth parents for years,
but it was like my records
were erased or something.
Then a week ago,
I get a call from the notary Misharin.
He gave me that.
At first I thought
it was a joke.
But it wasn't, was it?
Look, if this is
about the property,
you can keep it;
I don't want it.
- I thought we've been through that.
- Right.
Do we look like brother
and sister to you?
Twins, actually.
We were born the same day
according to your driver's license.
Don't you want to know
what happened to her?
I've been here
for a couple of days now.
You were lucky I found you.
Another few minutes and that
would have been a different story.
I saw something here
when I first arrived.
What?
Hey.
Come on.
Are you okay?
Yeah.
Our mother was stabbed here.
Look. Old blood.
Did Misharin tell you
anything else?
About what?
Our father, maybe.
Look, I know about
as much as you do, okay?
There's men's clothes
in the other closet.
See?
Our father's clothes.
- Let go. Jesus...
- Sorry.
He didn't say anything
about any father, okay?
In fact, he didn't mention anything
about any brothers either,
so why should I trust you?
Have you seen the cribs?
No.
Look.
See the name?
It's the same as the one
on your medallion.
Mine is on the other one.
Milla.
What were you running from
when you fell in the river?
I saw my...
I don't know. No.
It's okay. I'm fine.
Maybe I really am
going crazy, you know?
I'm finally crazy
after all these years.
And twin brothers?
Fucking Russia.
Who's Emily?
You were calling her name
in your sleep.
What's it to you?
Where are you going?
There's a generator
in the basement.
We've still got
a few hours before dark.
I want to get it running.
Hey...
We've got to get out of here.
We've got to find
that truck I came in.
There are no vehicles here.
This is an island.
So what about the bridge?
The bridge is down.
If I hadn't pulled you
out of the river,
we wouldn't be talking.
How long was I out for?
Long enough to change your clothes
and dry your hair.
Nice tattoo, by the way.
Nothing creepy.
I had to get you out
of those wet things before...
I mean, we are brother
and sister, right?
- Come on.
- Hey.
You never said
how you got here.
I walked.
Took me a few days.
My unit trained in this area.
See that door?
I heard something moving
back there on the first night.
Where does that lead to?
I don't know.
Come on, Nicolai.
I don't like it down here.
Give me a minute.
What the hell is that?
Sounds like a truck.
- Jesus, it's him.
- Who?
Hey.
Hey, wait!
Wait! Marie!
It's Anatoliy.
Hey, I don't like this.
Wait a second!
Yeah, let my go, Nicolai.
I've had it with this shit.
The bridge is down, Marie.
Whoever that guy is,
he's part of it.
What do you mean?
You have a gun, don't you?
Wait!
Hey.
Anatoliy!
Damn.
- Hey.
Are you crazy?
Where the hell is it?
You...
You saw it too, right?
Is this what you were looking for?
This hasn't moved
anywhere for years.
This is the same truck
I came here in.
- It worked.
- Don't be silly.
It can't be the same one.
What was that?
Hey, these aren't animal bones.
Looks like a bullet wound.
A shotgun maybe.
Kaidanovsky.
I think we've just found
another member of the family.
What are you doing?
Move away.
Get behind me.
What the fuck are they?
Just shoot them!
Nicolai, shoot them!
What are you doing?
For God's sake,
Nicolai, shoot them!
Oh, God!
- Come on, Nicolai!
- The gun.
- Get the gun!
- Okay.
Come on.
Come on!
Shit.
Here.
- Shit.
- Where's our stuff?
The barricades.
Someone's been here.
Someone must have been here.
Look, you're bleeding real bad.
- You're bleeding real bad.
- I'm fine!
Jesus.
What were those things back there?
Who? Our friends?
I guess whatever...
whatever happened to them
happens to us.
Oh, shit.
It makes it hard
to kill them, doesn't it?
What are you talking about?
I saw your double
a couple of days ago.
When I saw the real you,
I didn't know what to believe.
Oh, my God.
Oh, shit.
Mine was soaked,
soaked through
like I fell in the river.
Shit!
So you will drown, then.
They're our deaths,
Marie, our futures.
Oh, God.
We are haunting ourselves.
Hey, what are you doing?
- If I die, I'm doing it my way.
- Stop! Don't!
- Don't leave me here!
- Let me go!
They caught you.
Fuck!
No.
No fucking way.
Come on.
Don't do this to me!
God!
Oh, shit. Okay.
This is not happening
to me, right?
This is not
happening to me.
What are you looking at,
you fucking bitch?
Nicolai! Is that you?
Are you there?
Nicolai, come on!
Son of a bitch.
Okay.
Come on.
The bridge.
Okay.
Nicolai?
Hey.
Is that you?
Oh, shit!
Shit.
Please.
Bitch!
Oh, fuck this.
Shit.
Oh, shit!
No.
I knew you would turn up.
Don't let the decorations bother you.
I found it like this.
You're dead, Nicolai.
You fell into a black hole.
I fell in the tunnel,
in the basement.
But it was black enough.
You tried to cross
the river, didn't you?
Don't tell me.
You didn't get far, right?
Just who are you?
You should be asking you
the same thing.
- I know who I am.
- Oh, no.
You have no idea
who you really are.
What happened to you?
The house wants us back.
What the hell happened here?
What did they do in this place?
You saw it, didn't you?
I saw someone upstairs,
a man, in our parents' room.
I saw what he did to her, Nicolai.
Like watching a fucking home movie.
We were never meant
to leave this place.
See the cake,
the decorations?
It's our homecoming.
We don't belong here anymore.
Jesus, that thing tried to kill me.
I don't think they can.
Not until midnight.
Why midnight?
What happens then?
It's our birthday.
They say when
you see yourself,
your doppelganger...
that it's time to die.
What happened to you down there?
I saw the past.
Mama.
Marie?
Marie.
Don't go any farther.
What is this place?
- Do you really want to know?
- Yes, I really want to know.
We were supposed to die
in this house in '66.
Now our father is going
to get his wish.
Our father?
Yeah, Kolya Kaidanovsky,
the man you saw upstairs.
At midnight everything
will be recreated as it was
on the night of the murders.
Only this time, we'll die
as we were always meant to.
We'll become our destinies,
our doppelgangers.
We don't have much time.
What is that?
Let's get out of here.
So, how do you want to spend
your last few minutes?
Ever been to Disneyland?
You have a daughter, don't you?
Yeah. Emily.
I guess I'm here
because of her.
What do you mean?
Well...
I watch her grow up every day
and...
I know that eventually
she'll walk away,
live a life of her own.
I'm frightened.
Of what?
Being alone.
Dying.
I thought it would
make me feel better,
but it doesn't.
Having a child, I mean.
How about you?
There must be someone out there.
Natalya.
I did a matching design
for her many years ago.
And now, I'm afraid
to touch another woman.
She said that she...
She said, "You have
come back from hell."
"I'll save you."
But she couldn't.
She left me.
I guess this is it.
It's not over.
It stopped.
What are you doing?
Mother of God.
It's her.
It's our mother.
It's all going to happen again.
- Just like before.
- Marie?
- What?
- You're back in '66.
The truck.
The truck in the pig sty.
It might work.
Hey.
Come on!
That's him.
That's our father.
Nicolai, we've got
to do something.
There's nothing we can do.
What do you mean?
We're just going to stand by...
Nicolai, we can't stand by
and let him go upstairs
- and fucking kill her.
- It's too late.
Hey, come on.
We can get the truck now.
- No!
- Come on!
Oh, shit.
Leave us alone,
you son of a bitch!
It's all been done.
You can't stop it.
Yeah, but maybe
we can change it!
It was all over
42 years ago!
- Stop hurting her!
- It's not real!
- Yeah, the fuck that isn't real!
- Stop. We've got to get the truck.
We've got to get the truck.
You must go if you want to live.
Go!
Go! Run!
Run!
Natalya.
Motherfucker!
Papa.
I'm so sorry this happened.
I gave your mother
everything I could...
a life...
a home.
When she tried to take
my children away from me,
to take you away...
to break the circle...
It wasn't easy
bringing us back together,
but it was worth it, you know,
just to see you again.
You belong with me
and the family...
at home.
No!
Why, God?
Mr. Misharin?
Please.
I thought your birthday
would be a suitable time.
You know...
I was your age
when she killed me.
Come on!
We're still missing
one member of the family.
Emily, your daughter.
Nicolai.
Don't be afraid.
Your brother is with us now.
I love all of you.
I always will.
Yes! Come on!
Yes!
Please let me go!
Where are you going, Milla?
I need you.
I need all of you.
Don't you think your mother
tried to leave before?
There's no way out of this.
Come back.
Shut up!
Shut the fuck up!
No matter where you go...
...will be with me together forever...
- Shut the fuck up!
- I've been waiting for you for so long.
Shut up!
Whatever happens to them happens to us.
Welcome to the family.
My mother never told me
about her parents.
When she left for Russia,
I knew in my heart
I would never see her again.
It's been a long time since she left,
but I will never go after her,
never try to find out what became
of her or her parents.
It's better that way.
Better not to know,
better still to forget,
best of all,
to be abandoned.
Subtitled By
J.R. Media Services, Inc. Burbank, CA