I wanted really good to my mother
She was drug addict
alcoholic
had become almost blind
was schizophrenic
But I never forgot that I loved
although even if you did
continuously,
continuously ...
continuously.
Give me the money!
Are mine!
Are mine, the state from them to me!
If you do not like us do not eat!
Do not touch me, touch me not!
Where are they, eh?
Where are they?
Leave me!
Damele now!
Give me, I said!
I have them given to you,
you have taken.
I ve data 100
When I arrived the check
I gave $ 100 to any one of you.
to keep them from,
you understand?
Those we serve to live!
Time enough,
every month the same fucking story
If you take them you shoot them in the vein
and we die of hunger!
They are my ...
Well I do not I have taken.
You are a liar
Give me now,
you my stuff!
Dangerous!
We are hungry!
Leave me!
Those we need to eat!
How you did it to have, eh?
You've given their lives.
Do you want me to go on the streets
a prostituitmi
E 'that eh?
And 'why do you want?
You know, I make the robe ...
I need ...
I need
A Medina?
It 'true, and you get to $ 15,200
at the end of the round of double jeopardy.
I wanted to see that smile,
Oh God, how I wanted it ...
I was pathetic ...
All'Acquedotto not go!
Mom!
Dad ...
Is going all'Acquedotto.
Accidentals What difference does it make ...
Robbery!
Who cares!
Help her father, does not see,
robbery!
It 'always the same old story ...
Seen, they repaired the lampposts
The robbers break them again
No, quiet
You see, your mother is sure,
the water goes down ...
There is no water
You are wrong,
you do not know what the aqueduct?
The aqueduct brought water to New York City
Well, for over 100 years
Then they closed but now open
and there is water just below
what drags your mother.
My father, you could sit on the couch
and speak with him for hours
But you could not speak at length
Hey Jane!
He knew many things,
always had the correct answers
to quiz jeopardy.
He knew all the answers
Hey, watch where you are going!
This is the way
Parents are of your
I see them as an example of what
that I found my long life
tended so little to my needs
and I feel that their needs
was so strong
that I was neither angry nor suffering
that is not me interessasero
In short, I said:
must be the human condition that has become so
Then came reality
I have taken the husband
Elisabeth I kill you!
No, Mom!
Did I understand you a favor, you are
only a sick slut!
Help me clean Liz, see if
this casino take away all of us!
No, noo!
Outside my house!
Do not stories!
I do not come with you,
you understand? Noo, noo!
The window is broken
I threw out the cat
Let me stay, let me stay!
Why not try to take your medicine?
No, take
Just get a little
Okay
E 'un vero schifo!
What have you done here?
He took a knife!
I fell!
Careful hoo hoo!
Where's the phone?
Non ce l'abbiamo.
This story must be solved
and now
You two have only one alternative:
give a cleaner to this post
and help your mother!
Tell our father!
No no, you are a feminist.
I can go away or send via your parents.
Continue to skip school
and here is a house that looks like a pigsty!
Where to go, come here, go back!
Go to school, you have idea how is done?
There are girls who beat you and that
you steal everything you have!
You can not have anything of yours!
We do clean the bathrooms,
does not work there if you do it here!
What happened?
Been back, been back!
There's nothing to watch
Mom!
mom
But I do not notice
and yet everyone could view it
who suffered so much ...
His efforts were so visible
but no one dreamed of understanding
It's not that if you rub it
or not that was a good mother
was that now she no longer had anything to lose
Fammi winds with you!
Here's the task, I hope you've finished.
Well, take your places!
Hey that stinks!
But what ...
I was always the one that stinks in the classroom
Lisa has many benefits
But Dad said that was supposed to marry
a doctor if he had so many expectations
on the contrary I did not have any expectations, so ...
I scratched for lice,
between the legs also mi prude
My teachers always told me
not to get excited
My laundry ...
I did not know what to do with the linen
the bore until it is torn
Forza ragazzi, come back to place,
the interval is over.
I had bad teeth,
I was hungry ...
The teachers are treating her not to touch me
And 'as if those words falling on the floor
Give me the test, it is unnecessary for you to do.
No, I want to do it.
But if you're almost never came to class!
I want to do it ...
does not seem difficult
OK ...
Liz, wait
Do you have a bad odor, Liz,
not your mother tells you to ..
No, no ...
it is my fault because I forgot
Well, tonight when you do shower
remember to wash behind here
I have put aside a few things
Here ...
And this, but how did you do?
We've never in school
I read a lot
really, and what?
Well Encyclopedia
The lady of the upstairs, Eva,
it was found in a box
is almost complete, in short ...
R apart from the S
if the test there were questions between the R and S
I have the wrong
Oh Liz, you have to come to school
OK
say seriously
you are too intelligent not to be here
I do not understand why we come.
There will come.
How did a tell you that the school made me sad?
I did not know how to speak,
I did not know how to talk to anyone.
My house was not a place where you can grow up
and be normal.
If too many absences will have to call the social worker
and is not a threat,
is a promise.
Eva, look what I got,
thanks to your encyclopedia!
Brava, you must always take votes bei!
Un'idiota not want to be ...
and keep hard, give me right
now that your mother is back
My mother has returned?
Ah, we passed a couple of quiet months,
is not it?
The good thing that my mother had been
in hospital was that when he returned was
my mother again
Cooked, slept, he began to study
shorthand for the company in a
while he was out of the community.
But then, the drugs appear ...
Mom ..
mom
Lizzy
Are you OK?
Yes, I'm good.
Sparrows,
just six beautiful, you know?
I am happy that you are here
.. and you are happy?
Well, see the hospital ...
was not all that bad.
No, it's not true,
the walls were high and also
the bars on the windows
I'm sorry, you know, you had to view it
Are accustomed
But now you are here
Look,
you see I took Mom 100
Ma. no ..
100 is a good vote, 100 is the highest.
Do not you ever taken, Mom?
No
I am not going to school
I ran that I was too young.
Do not ever run away from home, you understand?
No, I will not
I ... I will always here with you
I know, Mom
I will always be there ... remember
Sure, Mom
I am sick ...
are sick ... are sick, are sick ...
I have AIDS ...
No. .. no ...
No, no no ... You do not need to be afraid
They say that we must not be afraid
because I could say that well be able
to survive, you understand?
but not here ...
I have to go home ..
you're already home!
No, at home by my father,
and Lisa take you with me
No, no, you have to stay here
I have to stop drugs,
with your father and I can not close
But he will only
Liz, your sister has already left,
courage now
prepare your stuff and andiamocene
I do not want,
you have you said that you beat your father,
who had raped your sister
Now this is what I do
No, stay here
I can not ...
remains mum ..
Everything was in pieces
I thought that if I had stayed
I have stopped the destruction
or at least I would be able
to not make things worse.
Want to open the door?
E 'inutile, I know you're at home.
Your mother and your sister?
Left
and your father?
went to take food,
back immediately.
We called the school, continues to do away ...
never go there ..
We must do something, you understand?
Wanda has warned, I have warned you,
all the social workers have done
We have said to you in all ways
Please clean this place
and go to school,
clean and go to school,
but you have not done neither one nor the other ...
o sbaglio?
No
What do you mean?
I do not know
But I will
Go into an institution,
Come away with me
No! But things are better now,
dad buys me food all day
She does not pay the rent,
and not send to school
I tell him to go,
I said to you, is not it Liz?
but you think with your head,
is a silly feminist
Are not things that joke,
to prepare your suitcase ...
now!
No, no!
I swear I'll go to school, please!
Sorry, we need an adult
who is responsible
My grandfather was in charge!
I take my grandfather!
My sister was already by him
But Lisa goes to school there.
We'll go too!
I shall promise, please!
Not piagnucolare
Talk to your grandfather
and if you take him
will be out in 24 hours
Here's the bag
and if he does not?
You will have time to think about how to live life
Think about how to live life ...
how many people really do?
We think while sinking?
Intercom, and you put
it was like to visit my mother
Only now I was here in hospital
Now do you see!
Andiamo!
Not 24 hours after I left,
and even after 24 days,
nobody wanted me.
I just left them and
Why not go to school?
And 'This is the main problem,
why do not we go?
For me
your is a problem of discipline
Hello Liz!
Hello grandfather
You call your mother
Hey! Come out, came
Are late,
but first I wanted to see you
Thanks Lisa
Not all messed up,
we are well e. ..
you do not expect much, is dying
Lizzy!
Mom
Sparrows
When I think of my life,
this is the moment that I like to remember
when I went back into the life of my mother
was lucid
Do not take drugs anymore and so the drugs
schizophrenia were for effect
We went to the corner bar,
sedevamo us to speak
and ate hamburgher,
in short, we were together
even if he had weak eyes
I think we could see
ie could see my side dishes,
and for a while I had my mother again
I remember,
slide down the hill
the working board
as if it were a sled
We still remember?
Yes
And when you did the tickle
Of course I remember,
I do not remember precisely
Yeah, I was a good mother,
is not so?
Sure Mom, you were good
Right
You know, I am pleased that we are all together now
volio tell me, you and Lisa
Would not it be nice if Dad
stop to take drugs?
Maybe we could go back to University Avenue
Here, well the fact is that now your father
is at a shelter for homeless
I fear that we have
lost the apartment
I mean, he never paid the rent,
and so, you know ...
What happened to my stuff?
Been thrown
What?
Even my encyclopedia?
Feel sparrows, I am sorry to die, but
they put seals on doors and windows
In short, there was nothing we could do,
is that you know, bad luck is something that  happens
I want to say ...
Listen, I had almost dimanticata that I have to go
go around the corner to greet friends
We put only a minute okay?
You finschii Meanwhile the hamburger
I, I .. torno subito,
just stay away, promised
only a minute
It was just so,
no more return
I was not able to maintain anything,
I was only worsened things
at least if I were going to school ...
if only I had,
if only I had ...
and so that part of my life was over
had begun a new hope ...
Elisabeth Murray
She is the mother?
Yes Like
Ah, now I accompany you in your class
Thanks
A moment
Hello Mom
Hello
Can you get home?
Yes, step away from their friends and
I will help
Maybe I should be with you
No no, you stay in school you sennò
lead away again, go, go ...
Hello
and then there are the nouns, verbs,
adjectives and prepositions
Who is that, know?
Thank you
I was not the girl that stinks,
I had learned to get a shower every day
my clothes, even if they were
dell'usato me from the shop were good
but still I did not know how to stay in school
and how do I do to be accepted
Guys, if we quiet please,
Chris want to come to the blackboard?
No
Bobby?
This is fun
lady ... Elisabeth?
Do not call me so
And 'your name, according to these forms
Liz or Lizzy
Liz or Lizzy are diminutives
They are my names
No, I do not think so
Damn, the name with the name you prefer!
Elisabeth is a beautiful name, is the name of
a queen, the Elizabethan era was
Shakespeare
What that against that name?
My father calls me Elisabeth
lost when your head ...
Go to Liz
Bobby, the phrase
Where to go to school?
We went
And how did you do?
I was in an institution
A lunatic asylum ...
Already
but you are not crazy ..
No
Sin, I mean
I try my Birthday
Ah si? And when?
Ah, you'll see
I put the water to my father
Come to school wearing a pair of boots,
the water, and under no ...
Then open the front of the professors ...
Happy birthday ...
You do not believe me eh?
But you, instead
It is not true
It 'a fantastic place,
because you did not come before?
My grandfather is a little weirdo
By the way, we should be out at 6
Liz, where is your phone?
Make that TV game show
Lì
Do not ever win, Chris!
Is to see!
I just have to make the
first that I forget
Do you understand the theorem?
This test is not a week before!
Can I take a piece of bread in the fridge?
Sure
Hey, I'm already 6
No. 4 and a half
E 'un'ubriacona
acidente che schifo!
He vomited on the door
I go out the window
I do not feel good,
help me please
Courage, come
support me
strength
boys who suck!
go on ..
I am a good mother,
tell who is a good mother
Courage!
Oh my God!
That's it,
the whole six hours pulita
Could not make a normal life,
because I would have to wait due
to make a normal death?
Dying is not for everyone
the hardest thing
They left
except you ...
... already
Where to sleep your grandfather?
Here in bed
With his daughter?
But I do not think in that sense
Yeah, but do not know
Did things with the sister of my mother,
so I told her
With his sister and not her?
perhaps he did so with both ...
Even his sister is crazy?
Yes, and also their mother,
so do not want to come here
My mother is about to return with my father
I want it to do so even my
He does things with my sister
You do not have a sister
Good for you, no?
Have you told your mother?
Yes, I told
When he left,
and she cursed him
He said that would have called the police,
and you call him
I asked how it could do it,
and she told me that the missing
He missed ...
I was 7 years the first time I rapes
Chris, Chris, no!
Come and stay with me
What, to be here?
Yes
What .. what to tell your grandfather?
I do not know him ..
We will make sure that you do not ever see
insomma ..
There alzeremo fin that does not go out to go
to work you know, he is very precise,
leaves at eight
... and back to 6 ...
Off!
but not a place to stay!
Not a problem my
Leave me your hands!
Your mother is dying
asshole and your father is gone
fit with all of you
I lost in this old age?
Answer!
What do you do?
Do as you like,
both end up in hell
just like your parents
I went
You do, take your stuff or ..
Let me go out alone?
Who of us can predict
your life
not sure that there is only inside helmets
and then we must do our best
My mother was dying,
my father he had gone
but I believe that I had my way
I would have met
I was 15 years, I was doing ..
What is a house after all,
a roof, a bed
A place where if you did you
you do not take away
If so, then I had 15 years
when I became a homeless
You have a coin?
Go to work
Me something?
Bought food
You have some change left?
Sometimes I had the impression
that he never had a house
Roll the dice
Andiamo
Hey, stop!
At other times I knew
that was my mother anywhere
that was my house
Oddio ..
but over the months she disappeared
Liz ...
si ..
But where end?
Here I was with friends
I have six non -
Well grandpa has beaten me and I ..
I could not stay here
but sure ...
your sister told me that you
stopped going to school
is true, but we will come back
and when?
when starai better
all make fun of me
Liz thinks I make fun of
those of the bar, why tremble
and I can not stop shaking
I think it is the fault of too much alcohol, Mom
you should stop
Ok, ok ..
can you heal ..
I love you
mom
is resumed with pictures
dai, hurry!
I arrive first!
You are wrong, look
Boys expect,
we are after ok?
Vado a moment a..
Hello
mom
We made a collection
she no longer believes it
that you take all the fun
is dead ...
died yesterday morning
Sometimes I feel that there is
a kind of skin beneath
I wish that those who are born in us
can look through
but can not pass through
My mother was buried in 51
lot of the poor
My mother was inside them,
the strangers had put the
in the enclosure
was naked, scared ...
no, had died just
Hurry, let's go
No, a moment
What is the function,
there should be a priest,
is not that you use?
When one dies, the buried,
everything here
E 'una donna ...
And it is my mother
There is the priest?
Not in these cases, do not you know?
Ah so is dead,
put underground
Priest or a priest, that mattered,
if you had gone, and perhaps had
already begun to rot
I'm sorry
and I had to believe that he had found
Peace
Come with us?
Why do not you leave?
Hey, wait
Ok ..
So I leave here
Listen, the fact is that I can not
I .. non ce la faccio più ...
and then I leave here
Where?
In an institution
In a mental hospital ..
You know Lizzy, this is here,
this is the lunatic asylum!
Come with me
Ok, see you around
People died,
things are mixed up
everything that is apparently so solid
becomes devoid of meaning
there remain only
gestures we do
gestures in the air,
this is what remains
I remember racing to my mother
in the crowd,
I felt the warmth of his arms around me,
when I was little,
when she was good
but it was so long ago,
maybe it happened once
I was betrayed perhaps a hundred times
but it does not matter,
I have never been good at keeping accounts
them we choose our memories
Sign out of them!
Where do you put the tombstone?
No plaque, no space
Time a week
and there would have been more
track her
but that mattered,
that was not the reality,
the reality is only in our hearts
She lived in my heart,
but I am not living anywhere,
I was alone in the world
You have 16 years and the third media
and you are a prisoner of a spiral
all sinks in worst place
you have ever dreamed
There is nothing inside of you,
you've exhausted every possible
to be accepted
and all those who believe in you
you set them repinti
Eva?
I do not want to be an idiot,
I want to go to school
Yes
Hello, I am Liz Murray,
I have an appointment
at 9 and a half,
10 are the
Sorry, the Underground was ..
sorry to me, but now it's too late
The school started 2 weeks ago
and we have only boys that
come on time, dear
The brochure says: broad participation
Student Development
of a community calendar
I just need a chance
You can wait to talk to Daniel,
but a meeting immediately after
I understood at that moment that I had to make a choice:
I could surrender to what happened
creandomi living a life of excuses
or I could make an effort,
I could make an effort
and make my life better
We'll let you know Friday.
Ok, thanks
E 'stato un piacere
Elisabeth
Liz
Liz I am sorry, but those
were the last admissions
Oh, yes, but I can speak for a moment, 30 seconds?
You should make a request,
there is a questionnaire
E.. here I have already made
Give me a chance ...
There are no adults ever been
able to give me confidence, to feel
and then to give me an education ..
In short, I do not know how to talk to you, here is
still
My parents were, takes drugs,
I do not want to like them,
is as though I had lived their lives
Today is different, I feel confused
and I do not understand many things
including why
refused school
and I stop at the third media
What I see though your
results were good
I did see the last week
in time for exams,
that's how I was brought
So who are intelligent, I can do it,
.., I just need a chance
a chance to emerge
the world they were born, do you understand?
Those who live are so empty, tired,
and are left to survive
But I know that there is an outside world that ..
which is better, you see?
E. more developed.
And is what I want to live
Why only now?
My mother died of AIDS a couple of months ago
and for me was ...
beh ecco ..
a bad day
I always thought it would be healed
and it would be taken care of me ..
Bella nonsense ..
You have not dealt with me,
I worked for her ..
was my baby
hours if they have gone ..
and so I ...
It 'time for you take care
of yourself
ce la fai to get here
in time, Liz?
Sleep here, if necessary
Ok, you're eligible
But others said that
it would have known Friday
Tu ci sei
Thanks!
He changed my life!
Did you just enough
You must fill out other forms Liz,
the usual routine, peaceful
address, telephone number
hours we will have to talk to your father,
even for him
Take it here, and you can start
Dad
Lizzy!
I need your help, please ..
All this is absurd, I do not understand
I wanted to say, why do not you will stay here in the Bronx
and maybe you will go to Kennedy eh?
I can not do the normal school
Why, this is not a normal school?
Well, it is public, but it is as if it were private
Already
Dad, Dad!
I am able to do this school
Listen to me, I'm glad,
but I can not do anything
Yes you can, you ..
You could say that you're a trucker and
who travel a lot, and so do not
you will never
and maybe live with your companion
Already, a truck driver who travels,
and then I have a companion buckle
Here .. I can not,
is my mother
Listen I need ..
only one address, you understand?
A phone number that they can call
Please, please,
do not need to know that are homeless
or call the district
and I will be locked again
Ok ..
Yes
Ok
Mr Murray
I am Peter, Peter Fidelty,
in fact I never married the mother of Liz
Sit down, please
I am very grateful that recognize
My daughter, in short,
here is pretty good
And 'the beginning, but we have great ambitions
Liz also believe,
she's a feminist
but perhaps this already knows
you see, his mother was beautiful,
looked like a movie star
and she was also a kind of feminist
or stuff like
Anyway I thought it was just a little
lively, while she was completely crazy
We need to put a signature here.
Sure.
and we also provide an address
and a phone number
Yes, 3454 University Avenue
There are a number of apartment?
Yes, 2b
3b, 3b! Already 3b, right
It 'true, we will transfer
upstairs
Telephone number?
718 5 55 57 67
555 55 67
Excuse me, are somewhat out of phase
Well, all
why I have things to do
Sure, it's all
Thanks Peter
Thank you
Can I start now?
It 'good that you've really
want to come to school,
brava
Accompany him outside
Damn
oh that is just going to go single chip?
No, see, I found a job
You know Liz, I remember when you were small
and walked to the shops in Foren Road
near the station
How many years you had?
I am a lonely man,
you know
Yes
In short, they are not
a sociable person
I have nothing to do with you,
it is not a personal
But today you came ...
Already
I love you
oh do not do,
you would not well,
it is a waste of energy
You know, when I was young
me to you was the most interesting
In short, everyone was talking only
drug or sex
and get enough in the evening
You you have ever
had some ideas
it is thanks to you I know that there is
another way of being
Already ..
You're all right?
Yes, I'm good, you take care of me
down to the service center
In fact they are to me
my apartment everything,
and this way you can
come to find when you
An apartment your ...
Yes, you know they like to do so,
I mean, hold people like me
out of the dorms
understand it, patients,
people with AIDS here ...
Hey Listen, there is different from when
it happened to Jane,
there are a lot of medicine
I am clean, well survive
Ok, stay healthy,
I will live forever
Continue to study,
I have failed,
ma tu ce la puoi fare
The coup of Tonkin
I remember the Maine
Another? The Franco-Prussian War?
You took Bismark
Do not have taken Bismark
I have taken six
I thought that was a sandwich Bismark
Ma che dici!
Bismark Perhaps it was a rustic ..
Enough talk about food,
me be hungry
Daniel will book next year?
Why do not lose that, they
Books eh?
Why we do not use textbooks?
Someone knows?
Too heavy
Bsss they are, but it is not true
They cost too much,
the school does not have enough money
Bsss yet we have not kids
You, the new
Her name is Liz!
E 'here for a week, tries to Remember
Liz follow,
please ...
Textbook,
text ...
book ...
Up, open it,
what you see?
Words
What kind of words?
Those of
No, no,
it is important
and here we have?
Many words of other people
they prefer and why?
Why only one point of view
shows us a world-dimensional
Correct answer, here is the prize!
Bismarck, Marx, the guy who sold me
the tires that you do as a reward
do not be put in the borders
of his ... history, but history
David explained better, in short,
there is no official history?
New girl,
tell him what is the story
The soria is .. we ...
all our stories
It 's, take the handouts,
I will be in the room received
if you want to talk
Liz, this is your
Hello new girl
I have admitted and you
remember my name?
It would remind me that,
but I want the other
side by your side
You are very smart
Yes, you too
I see that I have put a A
Yes, it was a very good job
How come you have given me this vote?
Liz, if you have given to you is because you are deserved
This is your first task in the classroom
All Time eh?
If my job goes A
I want you to me the reasons
Okay
so ...
Oh!
What are you doing still here?
Algebra
Well, I am past the 11, I have to close
Sorry, but those who follow courses?
Ah, the regulatory cycles,
then the program on Saturday,
the evening course in French
and the laboratory sciences
after a
10 ...
Now you understand why I have to look
at this algebra?
It 'great!
I have 17 years,
I do not want to get to 21 without having finished high school
What would you do,
5 years in excess of 3?
In 2 ...
you should revise the mathematics
Yeah, but so is dying!
No. ..
that is to live
I knew the time, the line B
put us 70 minutes to do the whole race
back and forth 4 times
and I would be arrived at school just
a little in advance
Daniel and I would
be done
For the first time my life
had a place to which to refer
Chris?
Chris, that joy!
What surprise
What are you doing here?
I go out
You are not at school
I have skipped
Why not have you tried?
I did
I have sought for so long
just that ... Well, it's hard here
is the sound of this place, you understand?
Now I am free
and I go to a new school,
I see you
Hey ...
quiet
courage, it's all right, let us
The last to leave
and the first to arrive?
Well always arrive after you, Daniel
are you the king of punctuality
Well, it took me years to learn,
at school I was always late
Who are you, anyway?
My friend Chris,
my best friend
Chris hello
Hello
I want us to be you
Watch which is not a nightclub,
is a serious
se va bene a te,
will do to you too
What do you get in bacheca
We decided to send our 10
best students on a trip to Boston
Cool!
We've never been?
I've never been out of New York
Once we were in Queens
Well, there you go
Stop it,
I do not believe to be among the best
10 students
You're right,
you're not among the best,
you're the best ...
You had the votes
highest of the whole school
and so will you .. Boston
Fully charged
As
5 days
Va tutto bene?
Yes
It 's just that I am always
been a void ...
You are not a nullity
The tour serves to make you
think of the college
And as a college
It's not stuff for us, losing leaves
You could come too ..
Can?
Of course, if you be to do
But to me I could not care
a damn!
And from Chris
Be realistic,
what do you want to be great?
Why,
they do not seem
big enough?
Chris ...
I wanted to say after the above,
is Ok Liz
No, it is not Ok,
I am a Barbona, a prostitta
And then who cares if
what I will be
E 'fantastico
Welcome to Harvard
So, it's like you imagine it?
Better, definitely better
Liz, are just people
Yes, but are not like me
Why were not like me?
What is that made them so different?
The place where they were born?
Io ce la stave putting all
by not having to live as a
Barbona prostitute or worse
What if .. and if I had worked more?
Now I was so close to the skin of the world
that I could touch
It will be hard to get here,
but it is not impossible
Since there are other scholarships?
Yes, perhaps some
Write about 1500 words
the free market in the world
and will win $ 500
Well, I neservirebbero only 70
all years
Ah, there was an interesting article
on the New York Times,
ce maybe I still here
Here it is
$ 12,000
Each year for 4 years!
What should I do?
Include a short subject that describes
what do you think is the most
significant academic achievement
and how did you manage to overcome
the pitfalls and obstacles
I do a copy?
I want to stand beside the people
and not on the sidewalk for this
feel lower than their
I'd like to go to Harvard,
have a good education
e able to read all the books better
Then I think:
and if I were crazy?
If you work every crumb
my potential to succeed?
I have to do,
I have no choice
Are late?
No, it's me in advance
I made you coffee
sweetener, right?
Right!
Thanks
Can I have a stamp for this?
E 'for a scholarship
New York Times!
Not yet you have sent?
When the term expires?
Tomorrow
Io te l'ho on 4 months ago, Liz!
What do you expect?
To arrive at today,
and then to take 18 years
E 'il tuo compleanno?
Happy birthday!
I do not believe there was
an age limit
I know, thanks
Now I could tell the truth,
that I was a homeless
and no one could come and take me away
Lisa
Liz!
Yes
What are you doing here?
Will I be interviewed
I am a finalist for a scholarship
New York Times
But, here I am ...
I have nothing to put me
Would you like my clothes?
Well, nothing showy, just
ecco ... something to put
on this
Thank you
Once Mom
revenge my clothes ...
I could not go to school
I remember
How cried,
so I liked going to school
But there you've never gone
why give you a scholarship?
Why are homeless
I am going very well at school
You are not a homeless, Liz,
you could live here
I could not,
and you know ...
Grandfather's fault, eh?
I'm becoming blind
as the mother
and I have so much fear
Liz!
Liz, I was thrown out by
with all my stuff
They can not if you have not
yet 18 years
Were either Brooklin,
I do not want to go to Brooklin!
You must help me!
I have an interview
No! Liz!
I gotta go!
You can not leave
your friend
Chris!
Lasiami do this interview,
and then you can come to school with me
I do not care!
Not center anything with this place,
and even you
Yes.
I was
Do you believe that people like us
can come to Harvard?
The world turns,
and you are not a dot,
everything goes on without you
situations do not favor
what you want
The needs of others and their
emergencies will always be
your strongest
I believe that people become frustrated
by the harshness of life
So spend time immersed
in those frustrations they
call anger
So continue to keep
eyes closed
situations as a whole
and all those little things
who contributed
to make it as
Since my parents small
I have never given much right,
and this has allowed me
to realize that
the little things that one day
would be my person
For this I have never asked
why things went
in one way or another
I understand ..
You can not say that I was happy,
in fact this made me very sad,
but I was aware
but accept the
because basically I have always known
that day
ce l'avrei fatta
Is there anything else you want to tell us?
I loved my mother,
most of my life
She was a drugged,
was un'alcolista
had become almost blind
and was also schizophrenic
But ..
I never forget
that .. I loved you
even if you did,
continuously,
continuously ...
This scholarship
for me is very important
because I would not
go to college without it
Had an average of
95 out of 150 across the winning class
He obtained and completed
5 years in excess of 2
and there is successful while
a homeless
Having lost his mother early
and with the father toxic employee
but it is more just that I talk you
then you present the winner
the sixth edition of
the scholarship of the New York Times
Liz Murray
Now everything has changed,
my life will never be the same e..
and I do not know what else to say except thanks
thank you very much
Liz!
Liz, how did you succeed?
How could I not do it ..
my parents showed me
the alternative
Do not try displeasure
for your child?
Displeasure?
Sleeping in the subway,
gather food from bins
garbage
Well no,
that was always
my life
I think .. I think I have been lucky
because they are deprived
any sense of security
and was this a spur
and force them to look ahead
I had to do it,
there was no alternative
so I arrived at the point where
I thought: OK,
working hard, I give you to do
the straits of forces
e.. we see
Now I am about to go
to college, e. ..
and the New York Times
if they bear the costs
So you were lucky ... but
there is something that changes
if I could do it?
Yes
back
ever
while to get my family
Dento are still at college,
I found a job at the New York Times,
I found an apartment
no longer have to pull back their lives
but I do ...
All those I know,
what I did
fragments splashing away,
I forget the little things
but it's so hard to pull ahead
alone
that's why I told you so,
Why do I mention
my story
and now put down the burden,
put ashore
and I will go ahead
Ciao, Mom