Bring in the prisoner.
Creegan must die.
In uniting the underlords and
reestablishing law and order,
I vowed that all remnants
of the lawlessness
that preceded would
be utterly wiped out.
Its memory alone would be
enough of a reminder
and a deterrent.
So after reviewing
the charges before me,
charges of crimes
against humanity and mutantity
for blatant complicity
with the Bailies,
I have no choice
but to condemn the defendant
to death.
That's right.
Bring it on.
May your evil die
with you as well.
I'm glad to see Marla
stand true to her word.
A little law and order
might be...
just what
we need down here.
Cleo, cheer up.
This is a good thing.
Since when is an execution
a good thing?
Don't waste your compassion
on Creegan, Cleo.
Believe me, he wouldn't
return the sentiment.
See, back in my time, when
people didn't believe in things...
they went out with signs
and protested them.
Now you just blast 'em.
Listen, despite the dozens of people
that wanted to, nobody blasted Creegan.
That's right.
He was tried and found guilty.
So, what, you didn't believe in
punishing criminals in your day?
No, I don't believe
in capital punishment,
executing criminals.
So, if a criminal is found
guilty as charged...
Right. Exactly.
If they get the right criminal
and not some innocent guy...
which has been known
to happen, you know.
And that's not even talking
about the barbaric side
of strapping somebody
to an electric chair
and then frying them.
It's gross.
Sarge, there's a situation in
the maximum detention block.
Voice, do you think maybe
you can give me a signal
when you're gonna
shout in my ear?
Get used to it.
No, I don't wanna
get used to it.
Voice, when are you and Hel
gonna kiss and make up
so you can get back in
her head where you belong?
When I feel Hel is ready.
In the meantime, Sarge,
you're acting team leader
and there is a situation
in the detention block.
It's Creegan.
Creegan?
Come on, this way.
Surround the perimeter.
Come on, move it.
We put him back
in his cell.
He said
he wasn't feeling well.
The oldest trick
in the book.
We had to drop the force
field to run a bio-scan.
He got a hold
of the med tech
before we could throw
a force field at him.
Creegan insisted
on talking to Hel.
Voice says Creegan's
only gonna talk to you, Hel.
Hello, Hel.
Okay, Creegan.
Let's get this over with.
You have an appointment
to keep.
Oh, yes, my execution.
I must admit, I thought
the sentence a little extreme.
Can you imagine me dead?
Yes, many times.
What do you want?
It's what you want, Helen.
Would you really have me
let loose of this mortal coil
without me revealing
all my secrets?
Don't listen to him, Hel.
It's just another one
of his sick mind screws.
That's right, Helen.
It's just a mind game.
What can I
possibly know about Voice?
Nothing.
I don't wanna play anymore.
I'm tired
of the way you weave
your sick little lies
with bits of truth.
I'm not interested.
Take what you know
to the grave.
As you wish.
Personally, I'd want to know
why Voice has chosen me,
to fight her private
little war with the Bailies.
Let him go first.
Thanks for playing.
Wait.
Hel.
I'm listening.
From the day you woke up
with that Voice in your head,
you've wondered
haven't you, Helen?
Who is she, really?
And why does she show such
a particular interest in you?
Sarge, stop this now.
Hel, get back.
What do you know?
Everything.
Oh!
That's my body.
You're a dead man,
Creegan.
No! Wait.
Sarge.
Hel, are you okay?
I'm fine, Cleopatra.
No harm done.
What did he say to you?
I'm not who you think I am.
Forget it.
He's mad.
Five hundred years
into the future,
she will enter a world
where machines rule the Earth.
Mankind has been driven
underground.
And Cleopatra
is about to discover
there's no place like home.
"In the year 2525"
"There are women with the will to survive"
"Fighting for a brand new day"
"Nothing is gonna get in their way"
"And in the year 2525"
"Three women keep hope alive"
"Joining forces to reclaim the Earth"
"Looking ahead to humankind's rebirth"
CLEOPATRA 2525 2x10 "IN YOOR BOOTS"
Subtitles by subXpacio
Oh, yeah.
Oh, I need a drink.
Hey, cup of mash.
Cup of mash.
A glass of 103-Level mash
to settle my nerves.
I think I'd need something
to settle my stomach
if Creegan kissed me
like that.
It'd almost be worth a shot
of the hard stuff
just to wash the taste
out of your mouth.
You're
uncharacteristically quiet
on the subject, Voice.
How do you feel
about your old friend Creegan
taking his
last foul breath? Hmm?
You hear the question, Voice?
Tell Hel I'm pleased justice
is being served.
Voice says justice
is served, the usual.
You know,
that must be tough,
having had the Voice
in your head for so long
and then all of a sudden
she's gone.
Gone?
Oh, yes, it is.
You don't understand.
Creegan has escaped
in my body.
I mean, Hel's body.
I need to talk to my team.
I wouldn't believe me, either.
Nice ploy, Creegan.
The old "body switch. "
I've got to try that one.
Hey, hey,
somebody stole my body!
You've got the wrong guy.
I swear!
It's me, Creegan, Tox.
Tox?
We go way back.
The B-factories,
the tunnel wars,
the first-ever
multilevel peace talks.
The ones that
crashed and burned.
You were behind
that blood bath?
You and Creegan? You and me?
Those were the days.
It's gonna be hard
to imagine the underground
after they
demolecularize your ass.
Thanks.
Yeah.
Without you around
to shake things up,
Hel and her like are gonna
have the run of the place.
Tox, I'm getting out.
Do you understand,
you sorry excuse
for a human life form?
And you're gonna help me.
You really going down there
to protest
Creegan's execution?
Yup.
I'm sorry, Hel. I know that
Creegan killed your dad,
but I have to stand
by my convictions.
Knock yourself out,
Cleopatra.
Cleo, wait up.
Are you going to help me
with the protest?
I can make up
another sign in a jiff.
Nope, I just wanna
get a good seat
for when they scatter
that sick bastard's molecules.
That's great.
That's the spirit, yeah.
Hey, Hel? You comin'?
No.
No, uh, in a weird way,
Creegan's been such
a big part of my life,
I don't think I could stand
to see him vaporized.
You two have fun.
Okay.
Guards! You gotta stop him.
Creegan's gonna off himself!
What's going on
here?
Keep it down,
you losers.
Step away from
the force field.
I said, step back.
He's gonna do it, man.
Wow.
He's gonna kill himself.
That's the plan, baby.
Not on my watch.
Shut down the force field.
Fry, Creegan, fry.
Do it now!
Get up, Creegan.
I said, get up!
Yeah, mate!
Freeze, Creegan.
Sorry.
Nice, Creegan.
I think I pulled something.
The, uh, deactivator
is on his belt there
for my door.
Sure. Right, I'll stay here.
Creegan, Creegan...
Creegan, yeah!
Go, Creegan.
Shut up!
Hold your fire.
Get him! This way, come on!
I knew you
wouldn't leave me, buddy.
Come on, now. Do it.
Encrypted, encrypted,
encrypted.
Is there anything
in this blasted lab
that I can use?
Hel, is there a problem?
I don't know, Mauser.
I seem to be having trouble
with the command
override system.
Everything seems to be
functioning properly.
What systems were you
trying to override?
You'll do for starters.
Ooh.
Clemency for Creegan.
Okay, so he's evil, you know,
but he's still human.
Clemency for Creegan.
You can't demolecularize
your conscience.
Clemency for Creegan.
What is this? Texas?
Cleo, it's me, Hel.
Hmm?
You have to
listen to me.
Creegan pulled
some kind of switch
when I was in his cell.
He's me now.
I know it sounds crazy.
You have to help me
to get to Marla's chambers.
I have to convince her
to delay the execution.
Mmm.
Now, I'm going to
take my hand away.
Just take it easy.
Help!
It's Creegan. He's escaped.
Somebody just shoot him!
Creegan?
So much for not believing
in capital punishment.
Anybody-
Cleo, you have to help me.
Security breach.
Get away from me, you freak.
They're coming
for you, Creegan.
Lockdown sequence activated.
Don't call me Creegan.
Freeze, Creegan.
Hold it.
You've got
nowhere to run.
No.
Let Cleo go.
Sarge!
Sarge, listen to me.
Nothing you could say
interests me.
Sarge, do you have
a clear shot?
Cleo is not clear, Voice.
Sarge,
do what you have to do.
Sarge.
Let Cleo go,
or I will kill you.
Get them!
Cleo!
Damn it.
I believe there is
a piece of equipment
in this lab
to lead me to Voice.
That would be you, Mauser.
Where did we put that
Voice beacon of yours? Hmm?
Ah, yes,
behind your left ear.
Hel, are you in the lab?
Voice,
it's been a long time.
Hel, the lab sensors are offline
and I can't contact Mauser.
Technical glitch, Voice.
In fact, I'm performing
a diagnostic on him now.
I feared the worst.
Hel, Creegan has escaped
from his cell.
I won't make a very
good hostage you know.
We all have orders
to die rather than negotiate
with creeps like you.
Hel and Sarge won't hesitate
to sacrifice my life...
to take you down, mister.
Sarge hesitated back there.
I would have, too.
Cleo, what I told you before
was true.
You're Hel.
Yes.
Are you trying
to establish some kind
of insanity defense
or something?
Hel, Creegan's escaped.
He's taken Cleo hostage.
I heard.
We must recapture Creegan
before he does
any more damage.
Sarge, is everything
all right there?
I still can't
contact Mauser.
Hel, where's Mauser?
We were having some problems
with our lab systems.
So, uh,
Mauser's all over it.
Sarge, I registered
a massive power overload
in Mauser's systems
before I lost contact,
as if he'd been
badly damaged.
Voice is worried.
She got some weird
power readings off-
I told you, Mauser's fine.
Are you going to waste time
interrogating me
or are we going
to find Creegan?
I'm sorry, Sarge.
It's just that the thought
of what that fiend
might be doing to Cleopatra,
just drives me crazy.
Yeah. Me, too.
But, we still may be able to track
her down through her gauntlets.
If she's
still wearing them.
Get your hands
off of me.
Give me
those gauntlets.
I can prove to Sarge and Voice
that I'm the real Hel.
Hands off my gauntlets.
Damn it, Cleo, let go!
I win.
You just keep
your distance, freak,
or I'll zap that clown makeup
right off of your face.
Fine.
Fine, we'll just wait here.
Huh?
You know,
I bet Sarge and Voice
have already activated
that tracer in your gauntlet.
I just hope Sarge gets here
before Marla's guards do.
Why do you want
Sarge so bad, huh, Creegan?
I'm not Creegan.
Right.
I don't know what game
you're playing at
but I'm not
buying into it.
What are you doing?
I'm not letting you
lure my friends into a trap.
No, no!
You are so lucky
I'm not the real Creegan.
Got her. Cleo's in Shaft 87,
Level 209.
Wait a minute.
212, 216, 220.
She's not stopping.
You don't think
Creegan whacked her
and threw her
down the shaft, do you?
No, no,
I really don't think he did.
Our motion sensors
indicate activity this way.
Look alive.
Yes, sir.
I wish Sarge could
see how difficult
you're making things for me,
she'd be really impressed.
Creegan.
You're a great man.
Why don't I leave
you two alone? Ha, ha.
I want some distance between
myself and Marla's goons,
so if you don't mind.
No problem, boss man.
We'll hide you.
I think it would be better
if we, uh, split up.
Remember the old hidey-hole
from the Tunnel Gang days?
Sure.
It's still there.
Marla will never find us.
Come on.
Bring your friend.
Creegan.
All right. Let's go.
Sarge, Marla's people
have recaptured 11 prisoners.
Let me guess, none of them
are Creegan or Cleo?
I'm afraid not.
Still no sign.
Run the surveillance hologram
of the escape again.
I knew Creegan was
obsessed with you, Hel,
but now he's trying
to copy your moves.
He is not flexible.
He's got no ass.
Jump forward.
Freeze it.
See somethin'?
Are your
gauntlets charged?
Always.
Follow me.
It's just Tox.
Hey, Creegan.
Oh! There's a new smell.
You should feel
right at home.
This is a great day!
Marla and her kind have tried
to impose their law
on the underground, on us!
Who does
she think she is?
Yeah!
We make our own
laws down here.
Yeah.
We answer to ourselves!
Yeah!
And to Creegan!
Yeah, Creegan.
Nice going.
You tell them, Creegan.
You're the man.
Thanks.
Yeah, thanks a lot, um,
well, it's so nice to see
some old-old familiar faces,
uh, once again.
Drek,
Scuzz.
I didn't think I'd ever be
this close to any of you,
uh, ever, and I mean that.
I really appreciate you
inviting me down here
to this wonderful hideout.
So, thanks.
So what are you all
staring at,
you bunch of
brain-dead shaft oozes?
I just escaped
from Marla's cell!
Let's do some crimes!
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yeah, whoo.
Good to see you again,
Creegan.
Yeah, welcome back.
Leaving so soon?
I was just going
to the powder room.
Grabbing a hostage
was a smart move, Creegan,
Yeah.
but we're in the clear now
and she's just a liability.
I want some of that.
Back off, Tox.
I grabbed this one.
She belongs to me.
Sorry, Creegan.
You're right.
You kill her.
Kill her.
Come on.
Well, go on then.
Kill her.
Are you
giving me orders?
No.
You listen to me,
you pus-ridden,
crusty-faced, sewer leech,
I make the rules.
Next time you tell me
what to do,
I'll be wearing
your skin as a suit.
You got that?
Oh.
This little cupcake
is mine.
Oh, I'll kill her
in my own good time.
In the meantime,
we're going to have some fun.
Yeah.
I'd rather you just kill me.
Creegan.
Go, Creegan!
You're the man.
Whatever you're going to do,
just get it over with.
But no kissing.
Don't worry, Cleo.
You're not my type.
What?
I told you, I'm not...
Ah, forget it.
Let's get out of here.
Sarge.
Why can't you just
die with dignity?
Hel! No!
We let the law
deal with him.
Of course.
Sarge! Hel isn't Hel!
Watch her-
Come on, scumbag.
Let's go.
You don't have
to watch this, Hel.
Creegan is the most fiendishly
brilliant mind alive.
I won't rest until I can
see him dead with my own eyes.
That's far enough.
Just look at him.
Sarge,
something's hinky here.
Yeah, you don't like
executions, I get it.
No, Hel's been acting weird
ever since she went
into Creegan's cell.
Defending him.
Talking up his genius.
She just called him
"fiendishly brilliant. "
What, did she buy a word-of-the-day
calendar or something?
What, Hel uses a few big words
and all of a sudden she's-
What about at the bar?
She forgets that you have
the Voice in your head
instead of hers?
And why is she being all
formal, calling you "Cleopatra,"
when Creegan just
called you "Cleo"?
Yeah,
you see what I'm sayin'?
Just remember what I said.
If you're going to do this,
make sure you
got the right guy.
Final words, Creegan?
"Spend some time
in slave chains,
see the world
through new eyes. "
What?
That's what you told me
when I saved you
from the slavers
that double-crossed you.
You said there was more
to life down here
than squeezing
profits from misery.
What kind
of a trick is this?
I- I don't think
it's a trick.
Cleopatra, that's enough.
Creegan has been found guilty.
Carry out his sentence.
Yeah! Do it, now!
I think we need
to reopen this case.
I order you to be silent.
Sarge! Trust your instincts.
Does that sound
like the Hel you know?
He told me to keep my eye
on you, Hel, and I have.
Quite frankly, I don't think
you've been yourself today.
This is absurd.
Carry out his execution! Now!
Yeah.
That's enough!
What?
By my authority as magistrate,
I order a 24-hour stay.
Return the prisoner
to his chambers.
Kill the clown.
No!
Demolecularization initiated.
Evacuate chambers immediately.
No!
Hel!
In the end, I'm glad
it turned out this way.
I much prefer
a firing squad
to that humane contraption
they had you in.
Cleo, get back!
It's no use, Sarge.
The escape countermeasures
have been activated.
Then override them!
Do it!
Hel!
Hel, can you hear me?
Hel, talk to us!
It's not workin'!
Come on!
Nice moves, Helen.
You work that body in ways
I never thought I could.
Must be the female touch.
Maybe,
I still know my weaknesses
which are now your weaknesses.
It's over,
Creegan, they know.
Knowledge isn't everything.
Got it. Let's go.
Don't move.
No, no, hey, get Creegan!
Creegan!
Oh, I mean, Hel,
or whoever that was.
Uh.
Hel?
Yeah, it's me.
How did he do it?
Creegan smuggled this
into his cell
inside a hollow tooth.
Pretty ingenious.
Hel, you were trying
to tell me, and...
I'm sorry I was so slow
on the uptake.
Forget it.
I wouldn't believe anything that
came out of his mouth, either.
So this little doohickey
can change you back?
I hope so.
I really don't want to spend
every day looking at that face.
Hey, It's no picnic being
on this side, either.
I'm sure it's not.
Don't worry.
We'll bring Creegan in.
Hey, just tell your men
to go easy
with those
shock batons, huh?
They really sting.
Come on, let's move.
Sarge?
Yeah, Voice.
Sarge,
I still haven't been able
to establish communication
with Mauser.
And someone has
just re-encrypted
the lab's defensive system.
He's in the lab.
Okay, Sarge, you go right.
Cleo, stay low, go left.
Remember,
that's my body in there,
so low-power weapons only.
Once you pin him down,
I'll move in
and make the swap.
Let's go, team.
What?
Nothing.
Hel!
I wanted to keep this party
a little more intimate.
So I reprogrammed the door
to only admit you.
You're just
dragging this out, Creegan.
Marla and her men
will be here any minute.
If I were you,
I'd do everything in my power
to keep that from happening.
Anyone else comes
dragging through that door,
and I trigger the lab
self-destruct systems.
The blast would surely kill
all your little friends
outside that door
and there will be plenty left
for Marla and her boys.
But the most
delicious death of all
will be yours, Helen.
The last thing you'll see
is your body
being blown into
a million pieces.
Voice, can you
override lab door security?
I'm trying every
access code, Sarge.
But it'll take some time.
Sarge, do you read me?
Creegan, I mean, Hel.
What's going on in there?
Creegan's armed
the lab auto-destruct.
Tell Marla and her men
to keep some distance.
You'd better back off, too.
I'm not going
to abandon you, Hel.
Just do it, Sarge!
What's this gonna
get you, huh?
You blow up the lab
and you'll die, too.
What have I got to lose?
Hmm?
You and Marla
were only too happy
to make my death
a public spectacle.
No regret, no remorse.
Is that justice, Helen?
Or your own lust
for vengeance?
You were going
to do the same to me.
My point exactly.
You've crossed the line.
We're just the same now,
you and I.
That's right, Marla.
I want you and your men
at least 20 levels back
till you hear from me.
Or until you hear
a really loud noise.
We're not leaving?
What do you think?
Voice,
any luck with that door?
Only 300 quadrillion possible
key combinations to go.
Great.
Cleo, stay here.
Where are you going?
A shielded access vent
runs into the lab
from the next level up.
There's an auxiliary
control station inside.
And if I get to it
I should be able to shut down
the auto-destruct.
Sarge, you know
that vent is protected
by a security force field.
I know about
the security, Voice.
So I'm gonna need you
to help me get through it.
Sarge, be careful.
We could make a deal.
You want your body back.
I want mine.
You make the switch and I'll
tell Marla that you cooperated
and I'll personally see to it,
that you have your
death sentence commuted.
I thought you wanted
to see me fry, Helen?
Come on, now.
Don't wimp out on me.
Stick to your convictions!
Whatever happens, you're not
walking out of here.
Maybe not,
but in the meantime,
Mr. Mauser and I
have some unfinished business.
Oh, I hope I don't make
a mess out of his brain
looking for this Voice beacon.
Oh, well.
Come out, come out,
wherever you are.
One more step
and we go out together.
Oh.
What happened
to the good old days
when we could just leave
a key under the mat?
I can see the force field,
Voice.
Can you shut it down?
Yes, but I can only leave
the field down
for a few seconds
without setting off
the lab alarms.
Is that enough time?
It'll have to be.
Force field deactivation
in three, two, one.
There's that Voice beacon.
Sarge, take the next right
to the control panel.
Come to Daddy.
Laboratory
auto-destruct activated.
Now you've done it.
Detonation in one minute,
25 seconds.
1:25, 1:24.
Damn it!
1:13, 1:12, 1:11, 1:10
1:09.
Cleo, get out of there.
I'm not gonna make it!
I'm not leaving you guys.
31, 30, 29
25, 24
21, 20.
Cleo, get out of there,
the lab's going to blow!
19, 18.
Not exactly the execution
you had in mind, huh, Helen?
13, 12, 11, 10
9, 8, 7...
Goodbye, Helen.
6, 5, 4
3, 2, 1.
No.
Auto-destruct
sequence aborted.
Goodbye.
Creegan.
No.
Command:
override lab security door.
Don't move, Creegan,
or I'll zap you.
Cleo, I'm Hel!
I'm not falling
for your mind games again.
Cleo, no!
You, okay?
Thanks, Cleopatra.
Don't worry, I got him.
You are still Creegan, right?
All systems check out.
Thank you, Hel.
It feels good
to be back on-line.
Oh, me, too.
Although,
I do have to say
that I'm a little
disappointed in you guys.
Excuse me?
Mmm-hmm.
We just saved you
from being fried.
Well, yes, eventually.
But I can't believe you
couldn't tell the difference
between myself
and a megalomaniacal killer.
Now that hurt.
Well, Creegan put on
a pretty good show.
And you have to admit,
there is a bit of a tyrant
in both of you.
Well, don't get me wrong,
I love that about you.
Cleo, how are you doing?
Feeling any better?
No.
Oh, come on, Cleo.
At least you stayed true
to your beliefs.
No one got executed.
Yeah, but I don't back
the catch-and-release program.
I just let the baddest guy
down here walk.
See you. Bye-bye.
Be good now, okay?
Cleo, your gut feeling
saved Hel's life.
Yes, and it's true
you did manage
to let Creegan
slip through
your fingers today.
But, thanks to you,
I get to see tomorrow.
Yeah.
Okay.
Subtitles subXpacio and TusSeries