Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org
What I hate most
it's the guys sticky.
Those who cling
and know
that means "no".
Normally, if the other not remember
is dropped.
Finally, I give up.
Good night.
Go away.
Leave me alone.
Go!
Go, get out Get out.
Go home.
Christopher
it's Michael, on Friday night.
If you want us to review,
my number is 555
3745. Call me.
I wanted to see
the path of work...
I think you forgot
your watch at home.
And your underpants.
It was great Saturday night.
As I have no news
I call you.
Hello, it's me.
Why you not remember?
Where have you got that?
Chuck sent them.
The guy with the golden retriever.
The bodybuilder.
You have not met
2 days ago?
Si It makes me uncomfortable,
Secretaries talk.
Provided he has not signed the card.
They read everything, especially Lori.
"To Larry. Provided that night
be the first
a long series. "
"I embrace you. Chuck."
You're dealing with a madman.
Someone who sends 12 roses
too fast is not stable.
What should I respond?
Do not answer.
Surely this is insane.
Let him know that I've had.
Surely not!
Above all, do not remember.
I do not know
I am not the cause.
Our company has 60 people.
You think he will land
in your office
with a gun? Stop raving!
Is a loser.
While it is fairly weak
to send flowers
is that it will not
premeditate your death.
A normal guy would not
send me roses?
I forgot to tell you about the guy
I met last night.
What's his name?
I know him?
His name is Clark. As Kent.
95 kg, fed
U.S. beef to 100%.
You can tell he grew
wearing heavy stuff.
What do you do?
Is what I'm gay?
In your opinion, you did what?
Bedford?
Mr. Lake has arrived.
Tell him I'm coming.
Very well, sir.
Well, I gotta go.
See you at the muscle.
It works. Hello.
Larry!
Your roses.
I know what you think.
"What a jerk!" Right?
But it's not true.
I am honest, that's all.
Sorry for the delay.
My boss is a neurotic.
Do not worry,
we had a quarrel.
You always do this!
What, again?
We can not have a discussion
that remains between us?
Stewart does not care.
Not true, Stewart?
I think it's cute, actually.
Me, I'm not crazy. OK?
Sorry.
In short, we argue not.
I leave you.
No. You've been invited to dinner
then you stay.
The grumpy will calm down.
Moreover,
why you are disputing?
Give your version first.
I want to influence Stewart.
- Tom wants to go elsewhere.
- It is necessary?
- What?
- Wrong.
You want an open relationship.
- I never said that.
- But if.
I want a more free.
And what does that mean?
Yes, what does that mean?
I do not know.
Change the subject.
- Christopher!
- Susan!
- Lunch.
- You forgot.
I'm sorry.
I have not for long.
Leave me a minute.
It's a mess in my life
now.
- I fucked Jim out.
- Again?
- It has been another girl.
And a guy.
It gives in threesomes?
In fact, they were four.
But the second girl was in the toilet
when I landed.
I never liked.
You know the best?
He asked me to join them.
What a pig!
In fact, it was not too bad.
I had never done a girl.
It was my last chance
sleep with him.
You know, I'll have already spoken.
I know, the Italian Stallion.
But frankly, are not you ashamed?
I screwed up at the door
once
our little affair ended.
It freed me, somehow,
me use him
for one last orgasm.
You can make me a great service?
What, again?
Table No. 12.
Look.
And?
That's him.
Give me 12
and I give you three of my tables.
It is imperative that I serve.
As you wish.
I think I'm in love.
You must not be the only
on the list.
You want a drink
Started?
Chris, wait.
What's up, Dave?
As usual, I have too much work.
To whom you say. I had 3 customers
on the back in two weeks.
I told
not to accept this job.
- How's Tom?
- Good.
Always so excited.
We fucked last night.
Give me the details,
it makes me jealous.
You fuck not?
You're new in town?
It is not very talkative.
Not too much.
I'll inflate?
Do you.
I need a boyfriend.
I wanted to call you.
Tom and I basically
Sunday dinner with the guys.
You can come if you're free.
I do not know.
It was at 20h,
you'll have time to go to the muscle.
- It's here.
- Who?
Cock-of-Horse.
- Is he here?
- Yes. Come on.
Go ahead
I'll join the other side.
Well, you're there. How are you?
- Good. You just arrived?
- I'm leaving.
- And you?
- Me too.
It's nice
I want that box,
but I rather feel
go to a cattle fair.
You're amazing.
You want to stay single?
No, not at all.
But I'm tired
not to fall on the right.
I prefer to masturbate
that kiss
with a guy who I can not stand.
Can I help you?
According to Tom, you not let
their luck guys.
- You're lucky to be with him.
- Change not matter.
I give them their chance.
I left her luck to Alan.
But it was a bastard.
- And Troy?
- It was a real cunt.
What has he done?
First
someone was greedy.
He met
thinking I was rich.
But you are rich.
Does that mean
I'm looking for a guy venal?
This is not to say that I
I settle down with a poor.
I want a rich,
like everyone else.
For what?
To be even richer.
In your place
I do not throw stone.
How?
You're not really found a spot
free-and-the-penny.
Having written both
our wills,
You should know that I am not
with him for the money.
That is where I am coming.
You're not with Tom for the money
and I broke up with Troy
that he was with me for that.
And my cock, of course.
We know that as a big worry.
You can return to our sheep?
So this dinner?
Promise me
it's not a stunt.
Juror, spit.
He does not understand.
What Tom is mixed, anyway?
They have their own problems.
And they plan
on the other.
They fail
to solve their problems.
Then they organize meals
for people
because they are bored together.
What? Your blacklist?
Somehow.
You've slept with all these guys?
And you've kept their numbers?
I am impressed.
Once I have a new,
I an old balance.
Interesting.
Who is Carlo Gastonbil?
This exotic-sounding name.
An architect. Egocentric.
And Louis? 1m70, blond.
A nice guy.
But nipples bizarre.
There's no Blacks?
I got more Ebony
you, darling.
Look at me like that.
How do I look?
Me not blame your failure with Jim.
He dropped me
or me?
A bit of both, I think.
You do not dump.
This is ridiculous.
But it's true.
It might do you good.
It's crap
Typical of a therapist, that.
Nobody deserves to suffer.
It never happens to you nothing wrong.
I told you, you.
Fuck you!
You remember Pete,
we met last year?
- The guy with the Jacuzzi?
- Absolutely.
He invited me to a party Jacuzzi
tomorrow night.
- You want to come?
- I can not.
Skip the muscle for once.
I go to Tom and Dave.
- Well, cancel.
- It's impossible.
Why?
With me, always t'annules.
Forget it.
I will not cancel this meal
just to go to a party fuck.
I have my priorities.
It is more important
maintain friendly relations
that fuck with strangers.
Really?
Wait.
Joe, hello.
I was going to call you.
"Joe, hello.
I was going to call you. "
I assure you.
Avoid you? Not at all.
But I have a monster job.
I do not understand.
Why I go out with you
if I was not interested?
You do not think I would tell you
I'm not playing
this kind of small games.
I have a double appeal.
I can remember after that?
Promised in 5 minutes.
What?
I said nothing.
It forces me to lie.
Not judge me too quickly.
He is too eager, and you know it.
Guys like him
seek dishonesty.
And if I do not answer his calls,
he had better drop it.
I do not understand.
What do you want?
I want a guy who takes me
see a ballet from time to time.
When it takes you not
baseball, right?
You want an athlete
sensitive and interested
to culture?
Exactly.
It is quite your style.
An athlete law graduate.
- I believe it.
- What?
You had to play more
matchmaker.
Is not
to play matchmaker.
- I play matchmaker?
- I do with it.
I'm talking to guests.
Just because that's your style
that...
It may be with someone.
- This is the case?
- I know.
Dave?
I told you, I stay out of this.
Surely the ice man.
Will you go to open?
Hello. The evening is already rife.
I'll take that?
Thank you.
I live underneath.
Super.
So I replied:
"Why you thought I wanted
buy City Hall? "
You're very calm.
Do not tell me that you work
for mayor.
What are you doing?
I work in publishing.
Stewart is an editor
very popular.
- You know Clifford Anderson?
- Sure.
- It is nice.
- It's an old friend.
The edition I have also tried
a time
but I decided
I would rather earn my living.
You're horrible.
Dave, your pie with figs
is a delight.
It's true.
You've really exceeded.
It's Tom who does the cooking.
Really?
A recipe from my mother.
- You should give it to Jay.
- With pleasure.
It's very easy to do.
You're not cooking, you?
I'm just coffee. Black.
Who reveut?
Christopher, cream,
please.
I said to Tom
we had gone to Savannah
and that my mother had prepared
a sweet potato pie
to fall down.
Nice to meet you. Good night.
I'm sure they're groping
Stewart on the couch.
- No.
- Of course it does.
Stewart only
for months.
And Christopher
style is not to wait.
Forget the sofa.
They must be at stake.
- Kiss me.
- What?
Kiss me.
There was garlic in the chicken.
I'm Rick.
Christopher.
I spent a good evening.
So do I.
If you want people to reconsider,
we can exchange our numbers.
Willingly.
Thank you very much.
Thank you to you. Soon.
You find it strange
a guy you hold your hand
and after he disappears?
No. I know guys
sucking other guys
and ignore them in the street.
Personally, I find it odd.
It's not so strange as that.
- You'd do that, you?
- What?
Take the hand of a guy
and not talk to him?
He spoke to you, anyway.
"Nice to meet you"
is not making conversation.
It had yet
commonalities.
- Who?
- For example...
I know.
We're both gay,
enough to make conversation.
The Stewart please.
How?
I have not seen in this state
from Key West.
It interests me absolutely not.
I promise.
Hi, Christopher.
We met with Tom and Dave.
Good memory.
Stewart, right?
Pile hair.
You like to drag you come here?
Not bad.
You just subscriber?
No. My roommate would love
I subscribe,
but the muscular,
is not my thing.
In fact, I came
him shut up.
I'm going.
It was nice to meet you.
Yes, me too. Bye.
You know
I said...
I can call you one of these days?
Sure.
Your number?
Super. Well, I'll call you soon.
Above all, force yourself, you dirty bastard.
You want my picture?
Hence my anger. It has nothing to do
tart with figs.
You do not find
my anger is justified?
Me, I think.
What do you think, Tom?
Pardon?
What was the question?
You like to be a lawyer?
T & P is different
the normal job as a lawyer.
T & P?
Trusts & Properties.
I'm paid to flatter the rich.
It's better than it did air.
Your job should be rewarding.
Not financially.
You know
I thought that call you.
I asked you your number.
You were funny
when we met.
In Tom and Dave?
I was bold.
It's nothing to say.
I do not know what came over me.
Usually I am not.
You had beautiful hands.
I wanted to touch them.
I was a little drunk
Then I moved to act.
It was good.
- A little wine?
- Yes, thank you.
And you, my dear?
A little, thank you.
How do you occupied your spare time?
You like sports?
Just baseball.
Must we go there.
I'm downright crazy
baseball and ballet.
So says.
You have a wedding list?
It was a dinner.
And?
I do not know.
It is nice, he is an editor...
All this I know.
You did?
No, we have not.
- It draws you not?
- I never said that.
You, Christopher Bedford
you're out with a guy that attracts
and did you even try?
Exactly.
Why?
Because sometimes
sex, it can ruin everything.
There is potential.
It can give something.
If he recalls.
Call him, you.
- It was called this morning.
- It is noon.
He wants to be hanging around.
It would do you good, it changes.
What does it mean?
It would do you no harm,
a guy who is not in your boot.
This guy, I feel good.
Before the end of the summer
you scrub.
You have one of those fantasies!
Holding our breath.
For the moment,
is beyond question.
It's getting late.
I gotta go.
Wait.
I spent a good evening.
So do I.
But...
I want to rush into anything.
Good.
Thank you very much.
Good night, Chris.
Good night, Stew.
To let
Your personal message
press the star key.
Hi, guys.
I am a Black single,
30 years
professionalism hard.
I want a man
for a discreet meeting,
vaguely intellectual
and without headaches.
- Who would have thought?
- Do not tell anyone.
Anyway,
I speak only to Tom.
Especially not with Tom.
Stewart and him are good friends.
I do not want him to know
I really feel.
You're in the melodrama?
You can talk!
You were such
when you met Tom.
Guess
you are moved to act.
You think of nothing else
than sex?
I am discreet
my privacy.
Sure.
And I'm the queen of England.
You die of envy
give me the details.
I tell you what I feel
and you, you want to know
if I am done.
I am extremely disappointed, David.
And if you're not gone
in bed with him,
that I will be disappointed.
Everyone knows
you're going fast.
Why do you take me
for Marie lie down there?
This is what you are, remember.
What? Two appointments
and did you score any points?
I'm not kidding.
I am not kidding you,
and it fucks the chips.
Better that I go.
You want to get a drink?
My God, I know.
Everything goes so fast.
- You're right.
- Really?
Do not move too fast to act.
No, of course not.
Glad to hear it.
Make yourself at home.
It's cool here.
You're rich or what?
Splurge.
I love your white hair.
I have a weakness for old.
I like you well, Danny.
This is Donny.
Sorry. Donny.
Donny and Marie Like.
You'll excuse me?
I have to check my pacemaker.
Super! I believe it.
Do not start, David.
And touch me.
Hello. Riding high?
Are you Christopher, I guess.
Delighted.
I'm Kenny, the roommate Stewart.
Cock-of-Horse is his roommate?
When Larry finds out that...
It's great. You will leave
all four lovers.
Go ahead, tell me.
Does he snore?
But as a child.
I think he loves me very much.
When I saw Dick de Cheval
He immediately told me:
"You have to be Christopher."
It was really cool.
It is revealing, I think,
his roommate know my name.
That means that about me.
You think?
Absolutely.
It makes the muscle where?
Nowhere.
It will not!
You mean you saw 2 times
a guy who is not muscular?
Stop your car, Larry.
It is well.
I do not seek perfection.
- You fucked how many times?
- 4 times this week.
- And in the morning?
- It is awesome.
When I woke up this morning
he smiled.
What is a good sign.
He has no regrets.
I hope so.
He kissed me,
and you know what he said?
I was not there.
- Guess.
- No idea.
You never guess
what he said when he woke up.
- You give your tongue to the cat?
- Yes.
He said: "Hello, my prince."
It's a romantic!
I could have died on the spot.
It is so nice,
it makes me happy.
Do you find
I've changed?
I am obliged to say yes.
Really?
I feel a new man.
I had you ever seen like that.
You think I'm in love?
Or
you got a drug problem.
I can fall in love with a guy
which is not a perfect body.
Someone who is...
kind, gentle and caring.
As Stewart.
It was not a perfect body.
It has love handles.
He has a flabby belly.
But he has these eyes...
I love his eyes.
They are beautiful.
My God!
What color are they?
No, really
beautiful eyes.
This is the kind of eyes that reassured.
Super.
What do you know Stewart's ex?
Everything.
Why? And you?
He wants to talk about it.
Without revealing too much,
I would say it has suffered a lot.
His ex has well conned.
- He has cheated?
- For years.
They had alliances,
lived together
had a joint account,
the whole shebang...
Fortunately
they wore hoods.
They still see themselves?
- It has been found.
- Super!
It took me to put its foot down.
I said: "Mr Donnelly..."
- The name of the client:
Mr. Donelly -
I said: "Mr Donnelly,
"You have hired
to work.
"So you think
our company can provide
"Knowledge
in international regulations
"For transport
of your hardware equipment. "
If you had seen his face...
You could have heard a pin drop.
It was incredible.
One of my best experiences
Geizocorp home.
You're hot.
You, you're hot.
I feel an erection now, right?
- Naughty boy.
- You love it.
You should be careful.
Otherwise?
Otherwise, I could
fall in love with you.
It takes courage to say that.
You're really talented
to break the mood, you know?
- Boudin not.
- I do not sulk.
Are you asleep?
You hear me snoring?
I miss it.
My snoring?
Novelty.
They look...
packed one by one.
I'm excited about you.
- But no.
- Really?
Moreover,
You do not have to be.
We have been together for a lease
and you want to look elsewhere.
I want to go elsewhere.
We decided to talk about it anymore
since our friend Danny.
Donny.
It's true, sorry. But...
They looked so...
Lovers? Yes.
Stable? Not particularly.
When have you seen Christopher
be like that with someone?
One thing is certain:
I envy you.
How?
Because if they break,
you'll have to pick up Christopher
spoon.
They will not break.
Hope.
Sorry to be grumpy.
Do not worry.
I used to.
Good. Here I am relieved.
So do I.
I zap the muscle.
I have a party.
You want to come?
With pleasure,
but Stewart and me
it has something planned. Sorry.
Roses?
They are beautiful.
Stewart has sent me
with a poem that I have here.
I'm all ears.
"How to express
"My joy at having
a suitor named Chris?
"The beating of my heart
not feigned
"I drink your kisses
as we drink from the chalice
"You're the one
I want to know
"You're beautiful, you're smart,
Chris you're
"When we're together,
my heart capsizes
"The prospect of being at your side
is a true delight. "
It publishes what?
It works well with...
What is the name
the guy you saw?
Which?
I know more.
The collector of works of art.
You talk about Freddie, the dealer?
Ah yes. So?
It's over. He launched
a Grecian urn on the head.
It was time to leave.
Damn!
I'm supposed to call Stewart
he took his day.
- A +.
- Wait.
One second.
Stewart is there, please?
Yes. Is Ken?
It's going very well, thank you. And you?
There is no better. I
on the terrace of Tom and Dave
watering the flowers and sunbathing.
Want to leave a message?
Tell him I called.
It would not work.
He left racing
it will be here in 1 hour
I will be unreachable.
I'm going to the muscle early this evening.
You're at the Met, right?
I told myself
that I had already seen.
I recognized your cock horse.
Shut up.
You got a hot bod, dude.
If only.
I swear.
How do you interview your abs?
I'll be muscular too, tonight.
We tell our secrets?
You show me your program
for abs, and I...
Today
I am the pectoral muscle.
Great, we have seen earlier.
Hello.
"You show me yours
and I, mine. "
I prefer not to hear.
Go, three...
Super. You're in great shape.
Go to the shower.
A man well done
which we would all muscles.
Blonde with short hair
military style.
I get tired of beautiful ass.
A beautiful smile.
He must have perfect teeth.
From the beautiful pecs.
Pretty and big tits.
He must have blue eyes.
Yes, because it makes me crazy.
I have tremendous respect
for the struggle of African-Americans.
As a white,
I have to fight relentlessly
to free myself from the ivory tower
my privileged existence
lower middle class.
Every day, going to work,
I listen to Black Lady Mombasa.
Really?
If he still says: "I am
a simple man, I vomited.
My mother always told me:
"Love yourself if you want people to love you."
You are cynical.
I find it touching.
Because you come from Iowa.
It is in Iowa?
You knew that, Chris?
Stop the chambering.
It is likely on its origins.
Dessert?
You have cheesecake?
It is a little late for that.
Do not be a killjoy.
Life is too short.
Tom, you take a dessert?
From chocolate mousse.
Nothing for you?
A cappuccino, please.
I would give
for the kids this guy.
Stop!
You mean you think so
incredibly attractive?
Not particularly, no.
Why?
Too perfect.
You think they love each other?
Who? Tom and Dave?
Yes, I guess.
In their way, cynically.
I too liked the movie.
I was sure.
It made me cry.
Really?
So do I.
But I tried to hide it.
I noticed.
Really?
Happy anniversary.
In two months our
unexpected happiness.
And commitment.
In this regard,
I have something for you.
Stewart, stop!
Are not you excited?
Sorry, I'm really tired.
You're not even
a little bit excited?
You can stop
talk like a kid?
What is wrong with you?
I'm lame.
We must kiss every night?
No. Once a week
it would be nice.
If a guy is buddy-buddy
with you to the muscle,
that means he is interested?
What?
You think Dick de Cheval
has a crush on you?
I do not know.
- Love you?
- Not you?
- I am not married.
- Me, yes?
You alone know.
I do not know. Kenny my mate
and I noticed once or twice
he touched.
You should maybe you do.
You speak of him
that your man.
- You so...
- It's true.
Stewart and me, it's serious.
It has no meaning for you?
Does not reverse the roles.
All this has nothing to do with me.
Absolutely none.
You're my friend, right?
You do not care?
I need you.
None of us want
embark there,
then change the subject,
you want to?
Okay.
Sometimes
I want to go out with a guy
with whom I want to kiss
all the time.
Gender,
I would have to keep me
not to snatch his clothes.
And it's not the case?
It's wrong to want to be with a guy
which makes me bend to the muscle?
I am the water retention?
Where?
Here. That is all swollen. Tasters.
What do you think?
You have reached an agreement?
No.
But her last boyfriend was wrong.
And to hear Tom,
it was completely destroyed.
I do not know what to say.
You should perhaps slow down.
Love is really complicated.
I hope you would tell me
if you found me superficial.
Of course I would tell you, idiot.
I love waking up naked
next to a blonde.
An arsehole rebounded.
From superb calves.
Hairs on the arm
going in this direction...
Beautiful cheekbones
a square jaw.
Blonde hair, short.
Cut very short,
like a kid.
A beautiful smile
with perfect teeth.
We should see his veins.
Large feet.
Large pink nipples.
But smooth.
With a nice muscular back
and a nice little ass.
The big biceps.
I may be angry,
I know.
Whenever I'm excited
it looks like...
Talk to David, not me.
Talk to your lover.
I want you to be more sexual,
I guess.
What you trying to say, Tom,
is that your sex life
to both frustrates you.
I go to the bathroom, I'll be back.
How many drinks you have buses, Lar?
Enough to get drunk mouth,
Stew.
Hello, dude. You're super cute.
Thank you.
He's your guy over there?
That's cool. I also have a guy.
But it is often on the move.
I am very discreet.
Call me
If you've wanted to have fun.
I tried to engage
conversation with your friend...
Do you mind?
You do it block the view.
Sorry, Lar.
Be more forgiving, Lar.
He grew up on a farm,
It captures not always all.
Obviously.
Good luck.
It is I who should tell you that.
"It's cool.
"Me too, I have a guy.
"But it is often on the move.
"I am very discreet.
"Very discreet."
Good morning.
Sorry about last night.
How?
It was a bad idea.
But as I neglected Larry
recently,
I said...
I know not what I said.
You do not have to apologize.
Larry was stretched.
But I enjoyed myself.
- I would have liked to be alone.
- I understand.
I had forgotten that these bars
it can be depressing.
You go to the shower first
or me?
One has only to take together.
Me apply the cream?
Sure.
Which do you want?
The factor 8, it will be.
Thank you.
Why you never put me,
me?
You've already asked me?
No. She's very nice, Mom.
She sits in front of me.
Yes, I left on the table.
Near the phone.
With instructions.
I swear
it is very nice.
I do not know.
Do not leave.
She wants to talk to you.
I am your appointments 15h.
Mr. Pennyfruger.
Call me Norbert.
Hello, Norbert.
I'm not there.
Damn, Stewart!
Excavation not my business.
Okay, I won.
Stewart is always...
Him, he is innocent.
It is the victim.
That's not the victim.
We all have issues
in a box, right?
No?
We all have issues
in a small box.
Hidden in a drawer
or in a cupboard.
We all somewhere
a box of phone numbers.
Or maybe an old directory
with numbers in it.
But they throw.
You got the time
go drink a beer tonight?
No. Stewart us
a romantic dinner.
Match Postponed?
No problem.
Sorry for the delay.
At the muscle, I...
Stewart told us about your dinner
then it was invited.
Does it bother you?
There's only like this
we can see you.
We have not beep you, Christopher.
It's great.
If you buy together
I do the transaction.
What's for dinner?
Norbert This is very nice.
But I do not feel ready.
And my mother put
incredible pressure
for I am with whites.
However, I tried
Blacks encounter.
But hey, it is in Boston.
Or, I have not
Jim is mourning.
Maybe my fear
to get involved with Norbert
is one way
to cling to a man
which I know
will not make me happy.
Finally
it seems logical?
Does it seem logical
Susan?
Looking...
I was thirsty.
You're thirsty?
Me, I'm hungry.
Did you hear?
Relax.
Wait.
Come, I know where you can go.
Relax, baby.
You fear nothing with me.
Tom.
Cheri.
- You hear?
- I'm sorry.
It's not you.
There's someone on the roof.
And?
A nice little round ass.
The hair cut short,
like a kid.
Biceps hard as steel.
While blindfolded.
Perfect teeth.
Blue eyes.
Large feet.
The big biceps.
Enough!
A beautiful back.
Large feet.
Blue eyes.
The big biceps.
While blindfolded.
But sweet.
Enough! Enough!
Where were you?
I was thirsty.
Tomorrow night
could dine with you.
That way, Kravitz
disembark not unexpectedly.
No problem.
Super. I love you.
Sleep, OK?
You love me?
Good morning.
Wait, Dave.
Slept well?
I'm sorry.
It happened, that's all.
What? Are you going?
You're a great support.
You know, Christopher,
I hope for you one day
you understand
there is a difference
between spending your time to apologize
and live your life.
Stewart is Christopher.
I hope it still works
tonight.
We dine with me.
Call me at the office.
Larry, you got a minute?
Just one. What is it?
I messed up.
Yesterday evening
Tom surprised me with Kenny.
You say nothing?
It is so poorly.
Do not think I have nothing to do
but I have to make this work at 10am.
Sorry.
Stewart is still Christopher.
You have not called, I hope
it's always good for tonight.
I'm not going to muscle,
then you can call me at home.
I'm not there, sorry.
Leave a message, thank you.
Stewart's me.
I called
several times to work.
It still works, dinner?
I'm going home,
then call me.
I'm not there, sorry.
Leave a message, thank you.
Stewart's me.
I prepared the dinner, but...
We need to talk.
Then call me back.
I'm not there, sorry.
Leave a message, thank you.
Stewart?
If you're there, pick up.
Damn
thou wouldst speak to me.
Go Stewart!
Pick up. I know I screwed up.
But I thought we loved each other.
I had a good time.
So do I.
We exchange our numbers?
Sure, with pleasure.
Do you remember me, eh?
How? I know you?
This is not the first time, Chris.
Pardon?
You really do not remember.
It's crazy.
- We have already slept together.
- Oh yes.
- Stop playing.
- I'm not playing.
Stop your car.
I'll refresh your memory?
Another day.
What's going on?
Nothing.
I want to be unpleasant,
but I get up early.
You kissed me 2 years ago.
We met at the Gay Pride.
Remember?
We'll talk another day.
But here, I...
"That you reach here." Right?
- I never said that.
- I understand.
You remember.
Ask yourself this problem?
You should go.
Does it bother you not
not even a little?
We slept together
and you've completely forgotten.
I find it disturbing.
I have not said to have forgotten.
Me, I remember very well.
- Will you go?
- Not right away.
Now, who plays?
Farm.
You want me to call the police?
I frighten you, Chris?
I give up to three
to leave my apartment.
You're kidding.
Un ..
Do not do it, Chris.
Two...
Three.
Four.
Damn!
T'appelleras person.
It can be civilized
and talk like adults?
- What do you want?
- A confession.
That's it. Acknowledge
that you gave me your number,
I've called several times
and thou hast never recalled
after telling me
you wanted to see me
and that it was extraordinary at the stake.
Admit that you lied,
fuck me at the door.
You remember, Chris?
I'm sure.
I know you remember
for me tight in your arms
and telling me
that had you ever been
with someone as well.
I know you remember me.
How could I forget?
Me, I remember you.
Admit it.
You've rolled in flour.
I admit that I gulped.
Yes, I gulped.
You've pretended not to see me,
but I know you saw me.
When I came to say hello
in bars
're leaving no
because you not remember me,
but because you had recognized.
Sorry
if I hurt you.
You're not sorry.
Scared.
There's a big difference.
"I'm sorry
if I hurt you?
It is I who am sorry.
But tonight
'll have you to do better.
You gotta do better!
You think so?
You'll force me?
We play this little game?
I asked you a question.
I asked you a question, shit!
You're completely barjo!
Shut up!
- Fuck you!
- Shut up!
Try yourself to kill me or what?
I bleed!
Shut up.
Shut up!
I should kill you, kind of crazy.
I do not give a damn about you,
or to have slept with you,
or i hurt you.
I do not give a fuck
what you think!
How dare you believe
I could worry
a poor pitiful shit
like you?
You're nothing at all. Nothing.
I'm great.
I'm super nice.
I have money, a good job.
Everyone wants to be with me.
Why I care about you?
And you know best?
When a guy you remember
after two weeks
that he cares.
It will neither talk to you, or kiss you,
or talk to you, or even see you.
Put yourself in the skull's it.
I've kissed
I used you.
Got it? I've kissed
and I used you.
You're a shit, a loser.
I'm a fucking winner.
And I should kill you.
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org