How does it kill someone feel?
Like my father always said:
"It is better to become a 12-judge
than six range. "
What your father did?
-You know it well.
He was a hero.
The vast majority of New Orleans
is under water.
Tens thousandth of homes and businesses
have been destroyed.
This is our country's history
the worst natural disasters.
The Mayor Nagin has ordered
almost all the 1 500 police officers --
Iopettamaan rescue
and to go to prevent theft.
Oh, hell, is it Kenny?
-On.
What do your partner here did?
-We made a distinction.
I was 9 district.
People were stuck in here.
I did not receive half off
until the water rose.
Help me.
Dead työparisi,
Kenny Cowlings ...
What about her?
What do you want to know?
You tell me.
-Did he bribe?
If Kenny had taken bribes,
I would have killed him.
There have been flooded,
I need help.
All the bandits shot at.
Go out of business confidence.
You moron.
You can not even bear telkkaria.
Let's go to hell.
What the hell are you doing?
-Come down from there!
I do my job.
-Come on down.
Siivoamme your sotkut.
-We 're in this together.
Come on down!
-Go out of himself. I do my work.
Come down now!
-I. Take care of your own work.
You shot a man for no reason.
-He deserved it.
Stan Johnson, 5 circuit.
-Are you a cop?
I will handle this.
Ammutko are you cops?
Drop your weapon.
Calculate it!
Andy Devereaux.
-Hi. Stan Johnson.
Where is your partner?
-He left when the water rose.
I stayed here. Where are you from?
-Chicago. I came here only.
Lucky boy.
-Did I not?
He shot the man accused.
-New Orleans atmosphere is gone.
... Katrina hit the city
and suburban areas.
New Orleans residents
prayed for mercy.
... the victim is increasing.
Whole neighborhoods are gone.
Residents now get to know
that they might not be able to return.
... the number of dead
can rise to thousands.
The conditions get worse still
two dam fell.
Approximately 80% of the city
is now under water.
We are the storm,
which many of us are afraid.
I do not want to be alarmist --
but people need to realize
that the situation is serious.
Hence the dramatic instruction.
Everyone must now leave
New Orleans.
Rekkalasteittain water, ice,
food, medicines and tents ...
More than 1 700 cars will be ready
to bring supplies across.
Coast Guard has worked with
great two days --
and it has saved
more than 1, 000 vulnerable people.
The aim now is to find a space
tens of thousands homeless --
and to save the people katoilta
desert Super Domen area.
Reconstruction takes a long time.
It will take many years.
Violent looting
have increased.
Many movements have been stolen
all the weapons.
Armed gangs
dominate the streets.
Half a year later in.
How you doing?
- What do you do?
Go inside only.
How you doing?
-What do you do? The new gold teeth?
Hello. Do you have something for me?
Hello, darling.
Latin Kings!
Hell, Chamarro!
Was it here?
-No.
You now have a new pair.
You trust him?
True on earth.
Look at these.
Swarm wannabe-koviksia.
Have been here all day.
Surely this asshole?
Welcome to my bileisiini.
This is a good stuff.
Welcome back.
-Thank you.
Stop!
Drug Police.
What am I doing?
-Hands behind the head.
I just want to chat to you.
Take a look at this, Stan.
What sort of guy doing
Sig Sauer holds?
You got henkkarit?
What about the name?
-I said to George Carter.
I know this. Downey Little.
What are you in my park you do?
There is tallota lawns,
piss or sell stuff.
Turn around.
Show it to set.
To calculate it, or I shoot you
shit head.
Come on!
-Shoot, Stan.
Let go.
-Put him in irons.
Get up.
This is my park.
I make you a 9-mm-sterilization.
Do not do it.
Shoot at him, Stan.
-Not good enough. He is not a threat to us.
He wanted to shoot kytän.
Will save lives by shooting him.
I will shoot him.
-Do not shoot! I know important stuff.
You do not know shit.
-Tiedänpäs! Ray Delacroix'sta.
Buddy hengaa Alvarado Street.
What?
What does he look like?
-Black dude with a pisamat.
It has a handsome green Caprice,
which have large rims.
Why I am interested
dealer for the youths, which has a fine track?
That guy is a drug agency of men.
Why I am interested
drug cop Delacroix?
Get on it.
Hell! Latin Kings!
Are you okay?
-I.
We had luck.
-But Downey Littlellä not.
When his partner
were found dead --
He requested the transfer for you,
so that you can start to his paired.
Yes. Palkkakin was better.
I have a wife and three children.
Please tell me the family.
-You have to evaluate my family.
This will be your data.
-I do not tell my family.
Then we talk about a couple of your privacy.
-What about him?
He always goes to the door first.
He has received a dealer for the youths in jail
and killed the pair.
Does it
opinion of him?
Our group, except
Police here are a joke.
The situation is getting worse
before healing.
Gangs have become here in the whole country.
My and Andy's like, guys
keep your world up.
Hell, that is boring.
Looking for something vibrant.
Huvittaako go?
-No.
You have to learn to love this.
Come on, Barney.
Do not just sit on the egg in hand.
What the hell is that?
-That is a Santa Claus.
That is a ghost.
I have not given permission to drive here.
Without the lights yet.
Want to play?
-He slows down.
Would you like to give me a reason?
He wants to play.
-Let's go with.
Are you ready?
-Let 's go. Where did he go?
Keep eye on her, Barney.
In this way we go.
Do not lose him.
Right or left?
-Left.
Right here.
-Where the hell is he?
Maybe we should go.
Leave it to another night.
That bastard can not shave
the center of anything and everything.
There he is.
What do you have? At least not in
chickens and watermelons.
Ajatko to me, asshole?
-Don 't you know who you talking about?
I do not give a shit.
Lift the window and tell me to hell.
Shut up, pisamanaama.
-Steal Christmas cartwheel?
Will kill you in Satan now.
Hands-ratille!
Drug Police.
If you breathe, you're dead.
Watch her, Barney. -Hell.
I thought that we just pelleiltiin.
Go to hell!
I am the drug agency!
-Ah, so you?
Bribes that welcomes cop.
Yeah, but I am still alive.
You do not take bribes,
but now you're dead.
The die is cast.
What about confirmations?
-You are my actions.
What are you now did you, Barney?
You shot him on the head.
-Is he a drug agency?
Quite a story. Well shot.
Lohduttaudutaan half & half play.
Half of his money,
his half their substances.
In this world, man is nothing
if he does not have the money.
I shot him on the head.
Well-shot.
We are fucked.
Do you know do it?
Make this statement.
I studied the car.
Teenkö message?
-Yes, do it, Barney.
What if we were seen.
-You are a ghost!
I, the number in this town!
Can you hear me, assholes?
Oh, hell, Barney!
This is a great evening.
Make a declaration, it already is.
-Tapatat me yet. The Devil's crazy.
Don 't you feel it?
This is the best part.
I know the whole ruumiissani.
How repairs are progressing?
-The roof is still a hole.
I can lend you the money.
-Me pärjätään, but thank you.
Andy? That contribution this ...
-Shut up. You did well.
Do not chasing siskoasi.
For further back.
The food is almost ready.
Do something.
Korjataanko roof this morning?
Hello? So.
After all, it is good.
-Who is it?
Wait a minute.
So. Okay.
Insurance agent said,
that the rain damage will be replaced.
Let go, bitch.
-Around here there is talk about!
Ask for forgiveness from him!
I do not want to hear that word anymore.
The FBI. Where are the marksmen?
-There.
Vasquez? Ballentine?
-Yeah. Who are you?
Agent Brown, FBI.
Do you know what you did?
I have only done my job.
Your work?
I shot-dealer for the youths Ray Delacroix'n.
You shot the FBI agent.
-Was he in your men?
Had taught
that the police may shoot.
You looked badge?
-Yes. But he shot first.
HIGH Friendly.
What happened, Vasquez?
He attended kimppuumme. We showed
badges, but he fired anyway.
Why did he do so?
-Look him up.
The man was a complete lunatic.
Go to the station and make a report.
-He deserves a medal.
Cardiac pump blood pasi few minutes
before he was shot in the head.
The first body hit,
he raise the gun shoot.
They shot him on the head
self-defense. Well shot.
I believe that the husband executed a
her third shot.
Where is this job, was he?
-It was the FBI investigation.
Clean your pesänne.
My husband is decent.
Your department is legendary.
Suspected of being beaten, the drug is lost
before storage ...
Do you have proof?
-For more than imagine.
So this was the first
ampumavälikohtauksesi? -Yeah.
How does it feel?
Time-good.
It was clear to me soon,
that I have to shoot --
if I was going to perform my work,
and so was able to do so.
How does it kill someone feel?
-I made only a job.
It was a legitimate kill.
There are animals.
I will take care of the animals.
One calf Delacroix'sta spoke.
I would like to chat to him.
It is too late.
If you do not wish to be contacted psychic.
Did he say anything interesting?
-Said kusipääksi me.
Is that why you shot him?
-Here in the city departed eaten.
Departed eaten.
It was late and I was hungry.
I like dark meat.
Precisely.
He seemed a good meal,
so I shot him.
Oh hell kuustoista,
give a little food.
I kyttänä city,
Who the hell are you?
Rumors have, therefore, correct?
So you really eat the dead.
Really? I like
socks pins at the top --
and a dry ass spike fooled.
You do the job you are to me the information,
who lost your takianne.
Lincoln freed the slaves.
I will not help you.
You will help, since you submitted
Delacroix'n hell.
Hypätkää only.
The water is warm.
But bring floats.
-Floats with. Was there more?
Stan, can I give to you
lap dance at a later date.
He should deal with.
-Provides turpaan?
This is bullshit.
I have not done anything. Let me.
Do not väännä hard.
Ferraro!
Office. Now.
Yes?
The FBI has perseessäni in such a way that seems
I would regard as the Hoover stringejä.
Are those guys imbalance?
The warning signals are there.
The normal feeling of guilt
after the shooting --
leaves me with the other
thinking less.
It can lead to
vainoharhoihin and isolation.
All of this region blocks
are controlled by gangs.
The game is a lot of drug money.
Therefore, the police may be freer rein.
Receive or adopt?
-So it just is. Reply now.
Your report has not yet been completed.
I believe that one of my crew
has made a deal FBI.
Has he sung kytistä other?
They said so.
They want to know
what I would do the cause.
But if this is a traitor ...
-Do I have to explain this?
That is an internal investigation of thing.
-You must tell the facts.
I assessment of their mental condition.
Confidentiality
protect them.
You can break it
if they violate the rules.
If you happen to hear something ...
If sattuisin find a traitor ...
Talk to me Ferraro.
You are in my job.
It is a good old 3NG through.
Chamarro and the Latin Kings
handled the job well
These were 3NG-gang.
Angered, they Do Ragsit?
Latin Kingsit?
Before the angle of five friends,
set up the gang.
But this setting does not trade.
It is illegal in this country.
New Orleans drug trade
shares are now trading.
Perhaps this is, however,
only a local gang war.
Why the FBI is interested?
-It always is.
It will explore
the same stuff.
Look at this.
Relax a little.
They do not know why we are here.
Someone has taken ahneeksi.
-Do you want to start a gang war?
3NG are gone.
New Orleans is ready.
Willing to take.
-We have to decide who is the number.
Do you vote?
It was the number of votes in favor.
Fuck you.
Check out this one.
-Come on.
I am the center of the city.
We departed eaten.
Delacroix was a pile of shit,
kind turpaan beaten.
You are as Edgar Allen Poe.
Look at this.
-We 've got company.
Follow her, Barney.
Mahallesi country Satan.
Look at this.
Abrakadabra.
You live here in the corner.
You do not move,
and you do not say a word.
They extorted.
-It is now my turn.
What is your name?
-Tanya.
Jimmy Dean.
What do you do?
Where should we go?
-Directly ahead, hell.
Do not the big tele, slut.
There is only mulkunimijöitä.
-Bye. Wait a little.
What's Amman name is?
Open the door, Selina. Here is a police officer.
Need a search warrant.
-Tanya gave permission to.
Open the door.
-You have trouble.
But if I have to break the door,
viewfinder, you kamasi.
And then you put in irons.
Open this goddamn door.
Hands up!
Hands-up, Satan.
Do you want us to hit you?
Calculate the bag.
Where were you going?
-I do anywhere.
You drag it.
I want to see your face.
What we have
-Look at this, Barney?
What do we have?
-This show will start from one.
Now I get it, why you are in a hurry.
Are you a conditional?
Spread your legs.
-Do not be afraid.
You need to sit the rest of you.
For increased
cocaine possession as a result.
What things do you have?
-Do you know Ray Delacroix'n?
He is dead?
Who do you think you killed him?
He was the FBI agent.
-I did not know it.
And hell!
Now, starting with the station.
Come on.
-Now you want to talk?
Sit down, bitch!
What do you know? Tell me.
What news do you have?
Ray always hang out FEMA's camp.
FEMA?
After all, it is federal.
Fucks with me?
Did you this?
-I. Kai you believe me?
We do not want problems.
Relax.
Do not kiss the mouth, narkkarihuora.
I do a full search.
How long is it going?
Small-time. Make yourself a drink.
Partner may be a little hard.
-I like kovistelusta.
Oh, shit.
Not the mouth!
We do not want problems.
Kiillota badge?
Just like that.
Remove the handcuffs.
Fine Moment
huumepoliisimme history.
I studied his documents.
-Kenny is gone. Stop already.
No, but your father.
Or, because I am here I am.
I just wanted to know
Why live to the edge.
I am a good cop.
All you need to know.
I am concerned about safety.
-Are you worried about me?
It is nice.
100-meter radius of this
made crimes. We are looking for them.
And then what?
-We do not hesitate. We apply the law.
Shooting incidents do not think.
It is a reflex.
If pahis going to shoot STAN,
ampuisin him. And vice versa.
So trust the Parisians?
-Yes.
Trust your partner to contact you?
-He is safe in my parinani.
You have over there, the weapons displayed at night.
Against the closed door.
If you want to secure your partner,
wait for reinforcements.
Do not chasing legends.
-You know me all, right?
If you knew
I had already ordered.
What now?
It is late as hell.
My father hated a couple of the Night Services.
My father gave her to go home.
Him it is not obstructed.
Why not?
He thought that the city raises
when people go to bed.
City was his auspices.
It was to save from evil.
What night are you done?
Were man ever caught?
Scout 1-11, are you free?
Someone took the garbage out.
Russian, Asian and black
the same tomb.
Clearly gang war.
The war is over.
Chamarro is hoidellut all.
How many of you think we can find?
What is wrong?
-Nothing.
N7B ... 9F7.
A car owned by Jason Trotter.
-Jake Jambalaya.
Pimp gangs.
Rolled Kennylle and me.
He drives kuutospiiriin.
Who are they?
That is Chamarron house.
Run the back side.
How you doing?
In this way you're treated.
Jake Suck dick, bitch!
What are you doing?
Very good run Sunday.
Now walk a little.
Without the exploration permit or anything?
You know yourself,
what happens over there.
Invitation confirmations.
-We can not tell about this in advance.
I do not want to be shot.
-Come on, Stan.
If assholes aimed at us,
we will shoot them.
They have so much firepower,
We do not need to aim for.
This is fear itself.
When the shotgun yskäisee,
they do not shoot no longer.
If someone shoots one of them to us,
I send him to hell.
Then the other will strike fear.
I do not let them shoot you.
You know why?
You have the charisma.
What does your wife say?
That I should keep feature.
He is dependent on me.
What you distinguish them?
My death.
-What else?
What is the purpose of this is?
-Once jutustellaan.
You do not jutustele.
You want to hear something.
I do not know what you're looking for,
but you can not find it.
What scared me to ask?
Go to bed, slut.
How is it going, Jake? All right?
-Yeah. I have something for you.
Go to deal with the ropes.
But do not kiss.
How are you, Jake?
-Hey, Andy?
What the hell is it?
Who is this is a nigger?
I'll take part in the death of Kenny reason.
-Shut up.
Tell me, what is happening.
After all, we are pals.
You must believe me.
I do not relate to this way.
Do not treat me this way.
-Freeze!
Do not move.
Drug Police.
Get your hands on your head slowly.
Counting to ten. One ...
-Stop it, Andy!
Two. Three.
Four.
-Raise your hands! He is serious!
Six. Seven.
Hands-down.
Eight.
-Hands up!
Nine.
-He is crazy.
Nine and a half.
Not expect to ten.
Oh, hell!
Easy-just now.
Take me to the hospital.
Andy!
Thank you. We came here and shots
why. We were examining the area.
We opened the door, they shot.
We defended ourselves.
I understand.
Drove over, and we heard
five to six shots.
We went in to call for help
to save lives.
Vaaransimme security
to protect others.
I hate it
when you treat me like a baby.
Come on!
-Have you seen any?
Do you know anything?
-I.
Go for it.
Ase!
We got him.
Barney, what have you done?
Oh, shit.
She does not have a gun.
-Oh, hell.
What did you do, Barney?
-Hell. Hell.
He aimed at us, and that's it.
Well shot.
I'll take the taxes off.
Asshole aimed at you
and you shot him. Barney!
I understand.
-Come on now.
Here cavalry comes.
They shot at you, Jake Jambalaya.
Want to know who did it?
Fuck you.
You are in fact the killer.
It is said that the death of
freak out in stages.
You are not yet dead.
Do you have to tell.
It applies only to
that die of old age.
Not when shot at,
stupid asshole.
You are right.
I have the knowledge Delacroix'sta.
He was a FEMA camp
much of their time.
Lakeview?
-Right.
See you in hell, assholes!
I've been found innocent.
But, four people have died
shooting in three years.
Yes, I am a good shooter.
Answering violence with violence.
-Yes.
If the door should now be second man --
aimed at my head,
what do you do?
Ampuisin him.
And I want to thank you for me.
Re wasting your time.
I'm not getting you search permission.
We try to play the judge.
-Not good enough.
You mikkejä
and you do the job you tapes and photos --
and then you get the permit.
None of the judge does not apply here.
Do not jauha shit.
Shooting Anne studied.
Be happy badge.
They do not accept it.
-Who?
I can not do anything.
You will not get permission to search FEMA camp
without the pictures and tapes.
Where do these jätkiä found?
Goddamn cops.
Is it good?
This information. You understand?
-I understand.
What now?
-The matter is now official.
The FBI is examining my miehiäni.
The FBI received a tip
rejected a search authorization.
They suspect that the men do
search without a warrant.
FBI to call me and says,
that my husband take bribes.
"If you warn them,
you are corrupt. "
Are they to blame?
-Too little pay.
The fact that they are
the police here.
What do you mean? -People
are tired of the violence.
They are tired of the city.
Does loyalty to the law
less than miehiäsi item?
Do you know them. They hakkaavat
confessions of people
They steal, and maybe worse.
What would you
in my situation?
Warn them.
-I can not.
Why are you telling me this?
We are trying to prevent the gang war.
City must build again.
Dealer for the youths are not waiting for.
They give go ahead.
And it gives you permission
do whatever you want them?
No, but my street is not determined by
no judge or jury.
The streets, I will conclude.
I am the law.
What if the law is corrupt?
-You think that I am corrupt?
My belief does not matter.
-Bullshit.
You sectors have taken part in this.
-I get money for its avoidance.
But did not you see it yourself?
-What?
The problems are many.
We try to improve the situation.
We come to work and try to
direct people to the middle of the ruins.
We are working on and we remain on course,
so that you can do your job.
You keep us in the same manner.
-So you want to change me.
You want me to be softer.
Then it would be hope.
Hope the police district,
hope for the city.
Hope for you.
What are the most afraid of?
Some other time.
Maybe.
Andy ...
Treated with this rules.
Thanks for the advice.
-It is not advised.
Hello.
-Hey.
Hello, Andy. Kuis passes?
-What did you say?
Excuse me.
-Hey, Andy.
Turn bag.
-Shutdown the box.
A great TV.
-Yeah.
We received the last
insurance money.
They left a little extra.
Bye. Love you.
Bye.
Love you.
Cadillac us.
-No, we will take it.
I do not want this Buickia.
It stinks.
I get to choose first.
-Mexican and Cadillac ...
You coming, Stan?
-Joudutaanko me this shit ämpäriin.
Why are we taking this shit?
Oh hell.
This is just shit heap.
Ready?
-On. We look to them.
Go on, boys.
Hell, it's Tanya.
Selina!
Who?
-She gave this tip.
Treated with this rules.
-Thank you vinkistä.
Wait. This is a trap.
-What?
What do you mean?
-This will not work without a permit.
It has not been before to have been a barrier.
No, no, no!
What is happening there?
-Someone showed us.
Are you sure it was a trap?
-I knew that something had gone wrong.
Who of us laverteli?
Friendly?
Pepe? Barney?
Barney has been weak.
And it's not friendly. Perhaps Pepe.
You told them.
What are you horiset?
-They were warned against the camp.
I am not doing anything.
-Lying.
Fuck you, Brown.
I am not afraid of you anymore.
I am no longer cooperate.
We should perhaps look teikäläisiä.
Wait. We agreed
that the city Cleaning up.
We have the same side.
-It is my goal.
I do not know at all
what your goals are.
I am sorry if you feel like it.
Look around.
No one is safe here.
No one.
Fuck you, Brown.
The FBI. You leave four under.
Call you later.
We came to resolve
Drugs police payola problem.
We have evidence
The murder charge for.
But before we continue,
we offer you a contract --
if you want to prove other corrupt
against police officers.
I have not seen the police
using the wrong position.
There is not a corrupt police officers.
-Not in hell.
We act according to the rules.
-You are all the same.
Grab the offer,
because you are corrupt.
We have corruption
one of your police officers.
Did you receive someone on your side?
Idiot selling drugs
FBI-agent.
He has admitted theft,
sales and crime lavastamisen.
She 's set piece guilty guilty?
Tell me something new.
False evidence against the police?
-You can use him to testify.
In addition, we have a witness who
saw all murdered in the house.
He saw you and your partner
opening became a battle.
That is bullshit.
He saw you and the Former Ball
shoot weapons in a non-member.
Laitoitte his gun in his hand
and took his money.
Was there more?
In that case, I am leaving.
You have a mess.
You mean crack hooker?
You acknowledge, therefore, that he saw it?
If it was the crack whore,
I gave to go --
he was certainly there,
but did not see anything.
Ammuttaessa people are hiding.
He did not see anything at all.
You will not find a single judge --
who believes in crack-whore-word
hero of the police against the word.
You did not call up reinforcements.
You do not want anyone to see,
how are you.
You had no suspicions. Went
only to steal and kill.
Shooting gave a reason to go inside.
We had time to call help.
Our man speaks the truth.
We believe in him.
And so a jury believes.
We collect the evidence. It is
easy as the rain kastuminen.
Several arrests
was invented.
Lavastitte evidence and even
you shot the innocent victims.
They were convicted of crimes
they did not do so.
Lie. I am not a lawyer,
but I know these things something.
I can tell,
that this strategy will not last.
If you let the criminals free
to testify against us --
you suggest,
that they have been convicted innocent.
They employ more and more criminals,
or lawyers, and the city loses.
All of this supposed
liars because of the police.
You can get us into action
if you get a second on your side.
Only a corrupt do so
and they are not living up to testify.
The rule of thumb is that the drug world
is always a corrupt law enforcement.
Corrupt police officers, prosecutors,
corrupt CIA and the FBI.
But police want to
scapegoats.
One more thing.
You did just a crime --
disclosing
The FBI, the identity of the witness.
I told you anything.
-Said that it is a corrupt cop.
How long do you think that it will take,
until we find him?
Write the reports --
that Jake Jambalaya reported important
information prior to his death.
I tell them to you.
But he said it,
what I wanted to know.
How do you get the suspects to talk?
It is hard to describe,
but I can tell.
I can imagine.
-Tell me everything.
I do not in any case tell
you anything.
You do not know to whom you talk.
You are the witnesses.
I blame these pellejä
FBI-disclosure of the witness.
If you and your husband have exceeded this limit,
I can not protect you.
I'm sorry.
-Listen to me.
They are the earnest.
-You think I fear prison?
I fear that you do not reach the prison until.
-No, you have to be involved.
Me and Stan did not let on.
-I do not look laver.
We find out who lavertelee
and building a trap for him.
Shoot at him.
-No, it is not.
What about the witness, Andy?
-I gave her to go.
He did not know anything.
Small fearful junkie.
You varastitte,
and you gave me a contribution.
Yes you get a share.
-Moron!
He defrauded you
uncover it.
What else you laverrellut?
-I did not know that varastitte.
I did not know that he is a witness,
because I did not know the offense.
And I do not want to share that
because I did not steal.
Do I understand ten o'clock käskyäsi
right? Stealing is a bad thing.
But lying, pieksäminen,
killing --
Liberalization of witnesses,
because you want to marry, it is good?
You have the Bible as an idiot.
-I 'm not married drug addicts.
I have not hit anybody,
who has not shot me first.
I have not killed anyone,
which is not shot at me. Roughly.
It is a sick hint,
that the use of the junkie.
Your girl gave us tips.
-I will show him the place.
If you talk to me about yet,
you will have a disastrous accident.
Goddamn fool.
-Andy!
He led me to the trap.
What could I do?
Rode a child too much
Bob Eno's arms or what?
Asshole.
-Barney, now stop.
Why you can not keep the mouth closed?
-Come on now.
Tanya, Barney here.
I do not like it.
Take up arms.
Now.
Shit!
Play Now
larger stakes.
Come, go down.
They cut the languages.
-Incredible ...
He is no longer nuole
badge.
All right, darling.
Come on, Barney!
-I miss you.
The case is not ready.
Why tell us? -Säikyttelyä.
This park was filled with dealer for the youths,
but we Siivosen it.
Forget about this park.
-I can not.
My dad found here.
Was not found.
I do not know what he looks like --
but I have seen
his face a thousand times.
I jahdannut him for years.
Now I will stop.
We can not fight the FBI's receipt.
Maybe we should just give up.
They want to export weapons,
so that we can not manage the park --
and then we lose the town.
This is my city.
You are too deep.
Loosen a little.
What do you do?
I have a wonderful stuff.
Drug Police.
Hands on your head.
Turn around.
Great, that obeys.
If you do not answer my questions,
scatter your kneecap.
I understand.
-This is my park.
The park is for trade purposes.
Well I did not want to hear.
There may be shot.
I am a subcontractor.
-Who?
For the Spanish Florida.
Latin Kings?
-They have to accept everything.
Tell me the name.
Tell me the name!
Chamarro.
-Where?
FEMA's camp.
From there, I acquired stuff.
What you are now found in the top?
What is available?
-20 On crack.
Earn 200 bucks
or seated in 5 - 10 years in prison.
It is not worth it.
The ski park hell.
Run!
Where did he hide the stuff?
Ass
Thompson submachine gun.
Tommy-gun.
600 shots per minute.
Quite well in 1921.
Davey Johnson. City
all-time great lawyer.
Thanks, Andy.
-I have questions.
Every time you raise a prosecution
pahista point --
do equally well, because it
operates. To you it goes. So far so good.
When was the last time you have seen
police certificate unreliable?
The judges and the prosecutor's office
will cooperate with us.
I mean, we are your support,
we facilitate your work.
Now the FBI nuuskii places.
We can not prevent.
But if you give the FBI
use us scapegoats --
I am of all with me.
Be taken to the press like hell.
The judges are always in front of me
presented practical prosecutors.
Do you know how many I have received
locked up? Get the license!
I put hard against.
I would like to search the permit.
Sorry, but as long
than the FBI is examining you --
none of the judge
does not give you permission to search.
As soon as I tried.
We are so close.
Goddamn lawyers.
-Fucking cops.
That's quite a poky hole.
-The cops ratsasivat home.
You know, many men were lost?
-Do you want to nose cloth?
You could have warned me!
Do you think that this is the game!
You wanted to clean the city
mess with their own hands.
Watching another
seized when the other gangs.
All win.
-Why did the bodies were put into the swamp?
It was sloppy.
Please beads,
but do not show tissejäsi.
If ryssit yet again,
I will kill you. Do you understand?
Are you doing to me
one more favor.
Everyone has murtumispiste,
is it true?
It is not only self-aware in advance --
and afterwards it is too late,
nor deeds can be undone.
Are you close to murtumispistettäsi?
Työparin with is like a marriage.
It is a two-man
integrity agreement.
What is your and Andy's happened between?
I feel like I did a suicide
and change my mind at the last minute.
Suddenly, I get it the joy of life,
which I did not realize that I have.
I understand that.
I understand very well.
What caused this?
-The FBI.
They will follow us.
Want to destroy us.
You have nothing to fear
if the supply rules.
What does that even mean nowadays?
Like Andy says:
It is difficult to work paskassa
and to become a clean home.
But he does so.
All other
consume a little shit at home.
He comes home to clean.
-What about you?
Recently, I have done things,
I do not particularly proud of.
Have you violated the law?
-I am probably stretched it a little.
But the FBI is wrong.
They are chasing the condition of men.
I do not know
how can I fight against it.
Just tell me the truth.
When things do not go wrong.
I do not even know what the truth is anymore.
Police issued HIGH
John Friendly murder.
He was shot in
in front of their homes in New Orleans.
Witnesses, two masked men
shot by friendly --
this comes home
22 Kelo's time today.
John Friendly pacify
gangs controlled the streets.
He was the policeman of 30 years.
He was sure was not the
wife and three children.
The FBI is examining the case.
HIGH John Friendly
was murdered tonight.
Do you think that it is he?
I do not know. Pepe has been bribed,
but this is too big.
Who it is,
we have bigger enemies.
Who?
He sold his soul FBI.
That house has been bribed.
They killed Friendly
and we turn next.
I represent the city.
I do not eat fish club.
If I am not respected,
I lutkat slaughtered. Shut-kii.
Barney is ready.
Going without a confirmation?
-There is a hell cops soon.
When they come to arrest us.
Are we even the cops anymore?
The time-far from it.
Drug Police!
Drop your weapon!
Who is a contact?
-I 'm not a snitch.
Damn!
Why would you even heräsit morning?
Who is a contact?
-I am not a snitch.
Tell it before he kills you.
-Who is a contact?
I made the contract the FBI.
I had to destroy the other gangs.
Brown told us
when the future was the raids.
He warned us
search authorizations.
He would pay guarantees
where we will end up.
They dominate
airports and borders.
Corrupt cops.
You are all the same.
Pepe!
I did not know that it is you.
I have seen.
Excuse me.
Stop!
Are you okay?
-I.
Are you all right, Barney?
-He is dead.
Who?
-Pepe.
I killed him.
I do not deliberately, Andy.
Pepe is dead.
Drug Agency gave
Latin King Sille power.
Where should we go?
-Where we met.
There, it all began.
You now have a new pair.
You trust him?
Shoot him, Stan!
I can borrow money.
-Me pärjätään.
Fine gogglebox
We have corruption
one of your men.
You are too deep.
Relax a little.
Have they changed over here?
-Kamat are here.
It looks clean.
Examined in places?
No, Stan.
Here we met.
Do you have to tell me?
-No.
I made a mistake. I needed the money
when the baby was coming.
Then came Hurricane.
I do not save the world like you.
I have to earn their livelihood.
I earned enough.
You are a father, hell.
-Are you gonna shoot me?
You are a traitor.
Were Brown breads and the like
Prosecutor turned kimpustani.
You lied to flooding up to.
Every day, every hour.
Ruined my investigation.
Brown made me stick
when I took the money. I'm not perfect.
I'm not me, either.
But I am työparisi.
It did not involve you at all.
It happened
before I met you.
You partner,
and I want to help you.
But you have to sit down.
-What do you mean?
I will be happy to assist you,
but you have to jail.
I do not have nowhere to go.
-You 're not shoot me.
I am your partner.
-What I should have done?
What I had to do?
-I do not know, Stan.
Calculate the gun, the dealer for the youths.
-I am the FBI to, I am no dealer for the youths.
Chamarro talked about.
You stay up.
I had to use Chamarroa.
We have the same side.
This is over, Brown.
-I'm still here.
That is the pig,
you are jahdannut throughout your life.
Let me shoot him.
-Not good enough. He was considered reserves.
I can make you a good offer.
-Do not go to that yarn.
This must be resolved now.
-Please help a little.
The case is now closed.
-Agree on what happened.
Agree with what happened?
-Kai me this is silent?
We're a pair.
I know that you do not look laver.
We do not have much time.
-Agree on what happened.
We were forced to
to defend ourselves and shoot.
Say it.
I was forced to shoot.
Ammuitko are you him?
Ampuiko he himself?
Was it an accident?
Wished he ..?
-He was my partner.
Are you all right, Andy?
3 years after Katrina
Subtitles by lavan_joy