- Martha Marcy May Marlene -
"MARCY"
"MARCY MAY"
Where are you going?
Marcy?
What are you doin' here?
We were worried about you.
- Well, I'm fine.
- Yeah?
Patrick's worried about you.
- I just wanted to come into town.
- Oh, I could've given you a ride.
- I wanted to walk.
- Through the woods?
Can I get you something?
- No, thank you.
Are you done?
- Yeah.
You're not gonna finish that?
Okay, thanks.
You ready to go?
- Not right now.
- No?
Hey, don't do that.
Come here.
You are shaking.
Calm down.
Alright, you take care of yourself.
Hello.
Hello?
Hi!
- Martha?
Yeah.
- Oh my god!
Where are you?
I'm not sure.
Upstate I think.
- You're in New York?
Yeah.
I think.
- When did you get back?
Martha?
What's wrong?
What's happened?
Uhh... I don't know.
I should go back.
- Go back where?
Uhh... I have to go,
I can't stay gone.
- No, no,
no. Don't go.
Don't go.
I am sorry for calling.
- Martha! Please, Don't hang
up. Don't hang up the phone.
Do you want me to come get you?
I can't wait that long.
- What do you mean?
Tell me where you are
and I'll come right now.
No, It's okay,
you don't have to.
- Martha, I want to see you.
Please.
- Martha?
What's going on?
- Not much.
- Are you alright?
- Yeah.
- Are you sure?
- You were really upset on the phone.
- Sorry.
I over reacted.
- To what?
- We got in a fight.
- Who's we?
- Me and this guy.
- Your boyfriend?
Did you guys break up?
Yeah.
How long were you together?
- I don't know.
Maybe a year,
more or less.
You were here the whole time?
You've been back in New York for over
a year and you haven't called me?
- I'm sorry.
I made you some tea.
Thanks.
You're dripping, everywhere.
Ted should be up from the city soon.
He'll make us some dinner.
- I'm pretty tired,
Is it okay if I just go to bed?
Get a goodnight sleep tonight,
you'll be as good as new tomorrow.
Well?
She seems okay.
What did she say?
- Not much.
she's really tired.
Where's she been?
She had some boyfriend,
they were living in the Catskills.
- What?
It's okay.
- Not really Lucy.
It's fine.
She's here now.
- How long's she gonna be staying again?
I have no idea.
You did a lot of worrying.
I told you,
It will be okay.
Martha!
Welcome!
- Hi.
It's great to finally meet you.
- Yeah.
Did you sleep alright?
- Mmhmm.
Good.
So, How do you like the house?
It's nice.
It's just a rental.
- Yeah... well,
I love it.
I didn't know there was a lake.
Yeah.
Do you still like to swim?
You don't live in the city?
We do. We just like to come up
here on weekends and holidays.
You know, Ted's working on
this new building down town...
and as soon as its finished,
we're taking one of the new apartments.
You want to see the pictures?
Do you think she's
excited to have you back?
This is just the view,
Obviously, the interiors aren't
finished. But, it's nice right?
Anyway, We were supposed to move in
the spring but construction halted, so,
it'll just be a little while longer.
Just gonna be a little while longer.
Okay, sorry,
no more work talk.
Aren't you hungry?
Not really, sorry.
You have to eat something.
It's okay,
I can make you something later.
Where are we?
Connecticut.
How far are we?
From what?
Yesterday.
You mean where I picked you up?
About 3 hours.
Why?
I was just wondering.
Is that him?
Yeah.
Hey!
Is this Martha?
Hi.
How're you doing?
Great.
You've got a really nice place here.
It's as much yours as it is mine.
I thought you quit?
I did.
I worry for you.
I know.
I'm sorry.
Don't apologize to me,
it's your body.
Zoe...
Look after this girl.
For once in her life,
she deserves some real care.
- I will.
She's been great.
Everyone's been really great.
Martha.
You look like a Marcy May.
Marcy was my grandmothers name.
Well, there you go.
I'm going in.
You want to join?
Sure.
You coming?
In a minute.
Martha!
Seems an interesting swim wear.
Martha, get out of the water!
What?
Get out of the water.
Why aren't you wearing any clothes,
What is wrong with you?
You can't do that around here,
you know.
- Why?
Because there are kids
around and people come by.
- So?
You just can't.
Get out of the water.
We don't do that kind of thing.
Get out.
You could've just asked me.
I have a bathing suit you can borrow.
What's wrong with you, Jesus?
You need to eat.
I will.
I'm just going to sleep
a little more first.
Okay.
I'm sorry I got frustrated
with you before.
- It's okay.
Eat.
- Hey Marcy.
- Hey Max.
- Where do they go at night?
- I don't know,
I never get invited.
You want to have a drink with me?
They won't be back for a few hours.
- I shouldn't.
I'm not going to drink
for awhile actually...
I think it's a good idea for me.
- Alright.
Wake up everybody!
Good Morning.
I'm sorry, Patrick.
- What are you sorry for?
How's everything going so far Marcy May?
- Good.
You like it here?
- Yeah, it's great.
I want you to feel at home.
- I do.
Thank You.
I know, People have abandoned you
your whole life. Your father...
I don't blame you for
not trusting people.
If you ever want to have
a meaningful relationship,
you need to let your guard down.
It's not your fault,
but it's there.
If you feel safe here,
and I hope you do,
let us in.
We just want to help you.
Zoe: Yeah,
we think you're fucking awesome.
If you're going to live here...
You need to be apart of things.
Play another song.
How are you feeling today?
Good.
Yeah?
So... uh...
I stop by the juice place,
and i got you Kale with ginseng.
Do you mind,
just put your feet off the counter.
I got you a Kale in ginseng.
Cos it's just...
I thought,
it might make you feel better.
If that doesn't looke appealing to you,
I also got a pineapple orange.
- Yeah, that might be better.
Thank you.
Oh, I also got you a protein bar
just in case you want a snack.
Why is the house so big?
The house isn't so big.
It's big,
for two people.
Yeah, but we like to entertain.
Sometimes,
friends come up for weekends
and sometimes we have parties.
It's just good to have space.
So no one else lives here?
Of course,
no one else lives here.
You're married?
Yeah.
When?
April.
I tried to get in touch with
you, but uh... apparently you
got rid of your cell phone?
- I lost it.
You didn't think of getting a new one?
I got used to not having it.
Cocktail anyone?
- No, thank you.
Martha?
Was it a big wedding?
About forty people.
Mostly Ted's family.
Did Aunt Dora come?
- Yes.
Did she smoke like chimney
and complain about everything.
- She's not that bad.
You didn't need to live with her.
You lived with Dora?
She lived with me after mom died.
Where were you?
College.
I'm sure she'd love to
know that you're okay.
- She hates me.
- She doesn't hate you.
Look at me.
Oh, come on.
I don't have any pictures of you.
You look gorgeous.
It's really rather irritating.
There you go!
You don't need to shake it,
that's a myth.
Is it true married people don't fuck?
What?
No!
Put this on.
- You're kidding.
- Martha, your clothes are disgusting,
just try it.
- Why does it matter?
Because It's feels good to put on
something nice and comfortable.
It looks really good you,
you little shit.
- Whatever makes you happy mama bear.
You're making fun of me and
I think it looks really good.
She seems better today.
Yeah.
I wish I didn't have to go tomorrow.
Let me take you.
No,
I don't want to leave her alone.
You'll be nice to her right?
I'm always nice.
I know you feel like something
bad just happened with you.
but you have to trust me,
it was not bad,
That was truly good.
We've all been in this situation,
and we wouldn't all still be here if
what happened in that room was bad.
We all love each other very much,
we are all together on this,
you have to trust us.
Do you believe me?
You're so lucky,
I'd give anything to
have my first time again.
- Really?
Yeah, it's so special.
I can't remember anything,
I just...
woke up and felt this pain.
That's the cleansing.
It's good. It means it's working
if you can't remember things.
You're cleansing yourself
of the past and the toxins.
You need to share yourself,
don't be selfish.
- I'm not.
So smile then,
enjoy this amazing night.
It only happens once.
KATIE: We switch off jobs each day...
so we all know how to
do different things.
Do you knit?
No, I can learn though.
Oh no, that's okay,
you'll find your role.
It takes time for people
to find their role...
in a new family.
Mostly, We sell blankets in town.
'Cos, We still need some money,
but when the farm's up and running
we'll be self sufficient...
and we'll never have to
worry about it again.
but...
It's hard to get machinery
and live stock without cash.
- When do you think that'll happen?
Well, Hopefully by the end of the summer
but we'll see.
- That'll be nice.
No, it's not nice,
It's essential.
We need to be able to
survive out here on our own.
The Government can't
keep bailing people out.
Businesses will close
and people will starve.
- Do you actually think,
that's gonna happen?
Yeah.
It's inevitable.
People can't keep on living like this.
It's unnatural.
Is that a new song?
Yeah, I wrote it yesterday.
That's really great,
that's nice.
- Thanks man.
Alright, This is called Marcy's song.
?
Well she,
she's just a picture.
?
Who lives on my wall.
? Well she, she's just a picture
? And the reason, reason,
reason it is so small.
?
With a smile so inviting
and a body so tall,
?
Well, she's just a picture
Just a picture
?
That's all.
Well you stand there,
?
stand there with the nightshade,
Her dripping
?
ripping down your hands
And you ask me,
?
ask me about the lightning
And the lady, lady, lady
?
she understands,
It's a dream for the future
?
and the water for the sands
And the strangeness
?
is wandering
Through many callin' lands?
TED on phone: I'm going into this
meeting in fourteen fucking days!
Great, that's all I wanted to hear,
Thank you.
What are you doing?
Cleaning.
I thought I'd help out more.
Alright.
I'm going to take the boat out,
do you want to come?
Is Lucy coming?
No, She had to run to the city.
Come on,
I'll teach you how to drive the boat.
It's okay.
Come on.
You want one?
How have things been with you and Lucy?
Fine.
Is it strange to spend time together?
No.
Why?
It's been a long time.
I don't know,
it's normal I guess.
Where is she?
She's at the doctor.
Why?
We're trying to have a baby.
What?
I just can't imagine it,
Lucy holding a baby.
Why?
She wouldn't know what to do with it.
Do you want a baby?
If she's happy,
I'm happy.
So you're unhappy!
What now?
No, no,
no... she's doing well.
She's doing well.
Do you want another?
She's relieved to have you back.
You worried her.
Why?
Cos you disappeared.
You haven't called in two years!
I just lost track I guess.
It's good to let people
know where you are Martha.
People worry.
I didn't think Lucy
would worry about me.
Well, she did.
Can I go swimming?
You don't need to ask.
What are you watching?
- Football.
- (Mimicking Ted) Football.
Who do you want to win?
Chelsea.
It's amazing, right?
Do you want it?
Not if it makes you feel weird.
It's yours if you want it.
What about this three...
as a set?
Do you think they go well together?
You took them?
- Yeah.
They're really nice, Lucy.
Jesus Christ!
Martha, what are you doing?
Nothing!
Jesus, you can't just come in like that.
Sorry.
God damn it,
what's wrong?
I'm just having a hard time,
sleeping alone.
But all you do is sleep.
Christ!
Just stay, Stay.
Why would you think it was
okay to come in like that?
I don't know. It's a big bed,
you guys were on the other side.
You can't come into our
room when we're having sex,
that's not normal!
It's private.
- Sorry.
You don't need to apologize,
I just...
I need you to understand
why it's not okay.
Do you?
- Yeah.
Well?
Because it's private and not normal.
Just lie down Martha.
Oh God!
This is just brilliant!
Just go to sleep.
I'm sorry you slept out here.
Thank you for being patient.
I didn't have much choice,
Did I?
I have two weeks a year to
come out here and try to relax,
I know.
I am under so much pressure right now.
- I know you are.
..to get this building up and
running or the bank takes it.
That has nothing to do with Martha.
My point is,
I don't need the extra stress.
I'm her only family.
She needs to know that she
can depend on me right now.
It's complicated.
As complicated as it might be,
we can't ignore the fact that...
her behavior is fucking insane.
I'm sorry.
Do you ever hear things
hitting the roof at night?
No.
Where did you pick up gardening?
There was a garden where I lived?
You're good.
I'm good at some things.
I know you are.
Was he ever physical with you?
Who?
- Your boyfriend.
What do you mean?
Did he ever,
hit you?
- No.
You had a bruised ear,
when you called me you were hysterical.
- I never noticed.
Are you sure he didn't hit you?
Yeah.
You can tell me.
He never hit me.
I wish you felt more
comfortable talking to me.
- I do.
- So, talk!
I had a boyfriend,
he lied to me,
I left.
That's it.
Not everything doesn't
have to be a big deal.
I'm still your big sister, you
know. I get to ask you questions.
That's fine.
And I'll beat someone's ass
if they are mean to you.
I don't think you can beat anyone's ass.
Maybe not,
but i'd like to try.
Hey... Don't stare!
You okay?
- Yeah.
He's right.
I don't know why I'm so weak.
You're not.
You'll quit.
Who's that?
Her name's Sarah I think.
You should handle her.
- You think?
- Yeah. You're ready.
Zoe could help but you'll be great.
We share all of this,
if it fits,
you can wear it.
Cool.
And this is where we sleep.
You can take any bed that's open
or you can sleep downstairs.
I'm hungry,
can we eat?
We don't eat until the evening.
- Really?
You'll get used to it.
Your body doesn't need that much food.
He's beautiful.
Whose the mother?
Katie.
but we all help out.
Is Patrick the father?
Uh huh.
Looks just like him.
All the kids here are boys?
He only has boys.
You're good with him.
Do you want to hold him?
I don't have to take care of them do I?
Not if you don't want to.
There are plenty of jobs you can do.
You'll find your role.
It takes time for to find their
role in a new family... huh?
I called my dad today to ask for money.
Does Patrick know?
Yeah, He asked me to.
Sometimes, if there's something
we really need I'll call.
How was it?
Fine, they're not bad people.
Did he give you the money?
Yeah.
He thinks I'm on drugs.
Did you tell him that you're not?
No, that's why he gives it to me.
I guess he'd rather pay for it
than think I'm sucking dick for it.
I've done drugs.
Not a lot...
but I've tried pretty
much, everything...
except heroin.
It's good to try everything at least
once. You find out who you are that way.
What about drinking,
do you drink?
No.
I have,
but I don't.
Good, we don't drink.
It just makes you
angry and less focused.
Don't get the wrong idea Sarah. We
don't really talk to our old families.
- I wouldn't call my Dad anyway.
Hey.
Have you met Sarah?
Sally, yeah.
That's enough.
Half is fine.
Excuse me.
I can finish this,
if you want to go to bed.
- I don't mind.
Why don't you get some sleep.
Oh, hi.
Hi.
What do I have to do?
Nothing you don't want to.
Drink this,
it will help you relax.
Thanks.
It's herbal.
It starts the cleansing.
We've all done it so there's
nothing to worry about.
Do I have to wear this robe?
I know it seems a bit silly,
but it's a part of it.
You look amazing.
Thanks.
It's your special night with him,
enjoy it,
you'll be great.
Shouldn't we start cooking?
I just made some potato salad.
And Ted's cooking the fish.
I thought we were going to cook.
We cooked last night.
Oh, yeah.
Do you ever have that feeling
where you can't tell if...
something's a memory or if
it's something you've dreamed?
Not really.
Do you blame me for anything?
No.
Like what?
I don't know.
I'm just trying to figure
out why we stopped talking.
I didn't think about it.
Really?
We were far apart.
Sometimes I wonder
if, maybe I could have
taken better care of you.
- The past doesn't matter.
- It does matter.
I took care of myself.
I know you did.
Sometimes, I think I could
have done more though.
Stop.
You really never think about it?
No.
You're not angry at me?
I know you don't think much of me.
but I knew what I was
doing then and I still do.
No, Martha,
I think the world of you.
Sometimes, i just think
I should have come home.
And make sure you went to college,
you had so much potential.
- I don't need your guidance now.
And I didn't then...
I'm a teacher and a leader,
you just...
never let me be that but now
I know I am, I know who I am.
Teacher and a leader?
What are you talking about?
I always...
I was the one who encouraged you,
To push yourself, always.
but you're the one who shut me out.
Martha.
Just because we're sisters doesn't
mean we need to alk about everything
that comes into your head.
Come on,
don't be rude.
Are you coming?
So what are your plans Martha?
For what?
Life.
I don't know.
Are you thinking about
what you can do for job?
No.
You're at an age where you need to
start thinking about a proper career.
Why?
It's a part of adult life.
There are other ways to live.
Really?
Sure.
Like what?
I don't know.
People don't need careers,
people should just exist.
He's just saying we should
start talking about...
what you're interested in.
Maybe we can help you get some ideas...
That we can put together.
There are moments in my life,
When I would love to just,
go to France and just exist.
- You can do that if you want to.
It's not that simple.
Yeah, It's not your fault but...
you learned to measure success...
by money and possessions.
It's just not the right way to live.
- not the right way to live?
And what is the right
way to live exactly?
Martha, What is the right way to live?
Is it, vanishing off from
the face of the earth,
and not calling your family
for two years, untill they're
worried sick about you...
Is that the right way to live?
or is it, I don't know,
living without posessions...
until you actually need someone
and turning up on our doorstep,
Where you know you can get some.
Is it the right way to live?
You sit there lecturing us
about our lives, and so far...
I have not witness one side that
you have any values of your own.
You should remember that Martha,
you're under my roof...
and you're eating my food,
you should watch your mouth...
because you are rude!
- You don't know anything about it!
Hello... Hello.
Who's this?
Zoe?
Is she not there?
She's not.
Where is she?
Who is this?
Okay, my turn.
Alright Max,
was this just an excuse to grope Marcy.
I'm teaching her how to shoot.
and then you just squeeeeeeeeeze.
Hey, Patrick.
- Hey.
Focus.
Take a deep breath.
Feel the tension leaving your
stomach and over to your hand.
Think of someone who hurt you.
Lied to you,
feel it.
Feel it,
feel how they made you feel.
Let it build.
Let it transfer to the gun.
building in the gun.
Breathe out,
Now release.
Feels good right?
- Yeah.
Now try that.
What do you mean?
Shoot it.
They're living animals.
So, shoot Max then.
Fuck this.
Don't walk away from me Max.
The cat has terminal cancer,
it's in excruciating pain.
- I can't.
Max has no substance,
he's just here to free load and be
around the girls but you're different.
you're a teacher and leader,
You don't see it because no one
let you believe it before me.
You're a teacher...
and a leader Marcy,
now prove it.
The cat reminds you of some fluffy
thing you think you used to love...
misguided emotions.
I could spend my life being selfish,
living alone, using this gift for
me but I've sacrificed in order
to be what you need me to be.
Why don't you trust me?
- I do trust you.
Then you shouldn't need
me to explain everything.
Why did you do that?
You said it was sick.
One of them was sick,
Zoe knew which one it was!
Just do it already!
Jesus Christ!
God...
God!
you scared me.
Sorry.
Did I wake you?
No.
I can't sleep.
Me neither.
I was going to watch a movie.
You want to watch?
- I should try to sleep.
It always helps me.
It's better than lying in bed awake.
Should I get some breakfast?
Hey!
Press them together.
I think that's better.
You look really pretty.
- Thanks.
What's you name?
- I'm sorry?
- I'm Mike.
Can I get you something to drink?
I used to drink this.
- Straight?
I thought you weren't
supposed to drink Mike.
- I'm not drinking.
You think you're so fucking smart.
Hey, what is going on?
He's a fucking liar.
We have to leave.
No, we all have to leave.
I know him.
No, no, no... We all have to leave.
You don't wanna live with this.
Martha, What is wrong with you?
He's fucking here!
Stop touching me,
You're not listening to me!
Take a deep breathe,
Martha, Take a deep breathe.
What is going on?
I have no idea.
Martha please try to breath.
please try to breathe.
Can you tell me what
you're talking about?
I don't know what you're talking about.
Please try to breathe.
okay.
Take a breathe.
Swallow.
What the fuck.
Hey, we can go.
What do you want?
Nothing.
No need for that!
Uhmm... we are leaving now.
So, come on guys.
Sorry.
Jesus Christ!
Calm down.
If you calm down no one will get hurt.
What do you want?
We don't want anything.
Just get out.
We're just looking at the house.
It's nice.
We wouldn't have come in,
if we think you were here.
Just Leave.
I would but I can't be sure
you won't call the police.
I won't.
You didn't take anything...
so just go,
I just wanna make sure
my family to be safe.
- Safe?
Why wouldn't anyone be safe.
Unless you call the police,
everything will be fine.
I won't.
I give you my word,
So, please go.
Get the fuck out of my house.
Marcy, go now.
I made you something to eat.
It's too hot,
let it cool for a minute okay.
I'm sorry I ruined the party.
You didn't ruin the party,
it's fine.
Is it over?
Yes, you slept through the night.
That's good.
Do you wanna try and
sit up to drink the tea?
I don't need it.
You okay?
- Uh huh.
We are working hard to create
something special here.
Do you feel that?
You'd be willing to throw it away?
- No.
Then, you understand why this happened?
You know that death is the most
beautiful part of life, right?
Death is beautiful
because we all fear death.
And fear...
is the most amazing emotion of all
because it creates complete awareness.
When you're scared it forces you
to be completely aware of your...
surroundings and the moment you're in.
It brings you to NOW...
and that makes you truly present.
And when you are truly present,
that's nirvana,
that's pure love.
So, death is pure love.
Hello?
- Hi, is Watts there?
Who's this?
- Jane.
Is Watts there?
Can I help you?
- Who's this?
Marlene Lewis.
What's your last name Jane.
- Heller, sorry,
do I have the right number?
I don't know,
do you?
It's a Jane.
- What?
Jane.
Hello.
Hey.
How are you?
Sure, let's do it,
I'll be around there on Friday.
No, that was my cousin Marcy,
Okay, sure.
Alright, I'll see you then.
I'm glad you called.
Alright, Bye.
Marcy.
You don't eat until they're finished.
You know better.
I know, Sorry... Katie.
LUCY: Who's Katie?
What?
Who's Katie?
Oh, nothing.
Lucy?
Yeah.
Is this...
from the past or is this now?
What?
I don't remember waking up this morning.
Why don't you go sit down,
I'll finish this.
What's going on?
Who the fuck knows.
She needs to see someone.
I know.
I'll start looking into places tomorrow.
Places?
I don't think she should
stay with us anymore.
We can't do anything for
her when she's like this.
I don't want to talk about it anymore.
Okay?
Zoe?
Yeah.
I can't stop thinking about that man.
I know.
It happens though,
we're never really dead or alive,
we just exist,
so he's still existing,
but it's in a parallel time.
Just don't think about it.
It's Zoe,
can we talk?
Can you let me in?
- Haven't you learned anything?
- I have.
I felt like we had a connection.
We do!
Maybe I asked too much
from you too soon.
I'll expect less of you from now on.
Okay?
I'm sorry.
Shhh.
You're my favorite.
I won't lose you.
Are you alright?
- What the hell happened?
- She kicked me down the fucking stairs.
what's it gonna fucking take, Lucy.
You could have killed him.
- I was confused.
About what,
what are you so confused about?
- I thought he was someone else.
You thought he was someone else?
What the fuck is wrong with you?
What is wrong with you?
I'm not doing this anymore,
Okay, I'm not gonna do this
anymore. I beat myself up over
you for years and I'm sick of it,
I'm sick of chasing you
down and worrying about you.
I'm sorry.
You need help Martha.
I know.
What happened to you?
- What happened?
- I don't know!
We're going to get you proper help.
Are you going to send me away?
I don't know how to help you.
Please don't. Please don't.
- I can't help you, Martha.
No.
We're trying to start a family and
I don't feel safe with you here.
Lucy?
Yeah.
You're going to be a terrible mother.
Do you have any money left?
No.
- No, i didn't think you did.
We'll make sure everything
is taken care of.
Hey.
You're going swimming?
- Yeah.
It's a bit chilly.
- I don't mind.
I think we both said some things
last night that we didn't mean.
Yeah.
We scheduled an appointment
for you tomorrow morning.
What's it like there?
It looks nice.
It's not that far from us.
We're heading back to the
city in about an hour.
You're gonna be ready right?
- Yeah.
Are you okay?
Yeah, I'm fine.
It came out of nowhere.
- THE END-
Subtitle by d3xt3r