Dr Sammael ?
Yes. May I help you ?
Excuse me but I'm finishing for today.
Melissa?
Dr Sammael, I'm gonna tell you
some really weird shit.
And you're gonna get real scared.
What do you want ?
Point it toward me all the time.
I just need you to listen.
I... I don't understand.
I'm Asmodeus,
Torturer of the 13th level of Hell.
I'm a demon.
All right...
It seems like we need to talk
Why don't you have a seat ?
Just like that ?
A fucking demon walks in your office
and does have a seat ?
I'm a little annoyed,
a bit frightened, but
I am a trained professional,
Mr Asmodeus.
Don't bother.
It's dead.
Now cut the shit,
I don't have much time.
All right.
You're a demon.
- Is that your problem, Mr Asmodeus ?
Shut up and listen,
before I rip your fucking throat out !
Let me give you some case history.
Satan tricked me into selling my soul.
But I got a second chance a few months
ago when my mother died.
Satan offered me a chance
to escape the pit,
to become human again.
As they say,
there's always a price.
No, thanks.
And you shouldn't either, Albert.
You really shouldn't.
- That's all right, I'll have one.
- Thank you.
Thank you, Albert.
You know,
in the short time that I've been here,
I heard nothing but good things
about your wife Theresa.
That woman was a saint, Father Anthony.
I just thank our Saviour in Heaven
that He took her
before she had to suffer any longer.
I know this is a very difficult time,
but we do have to be out of here
by five o'clock,
and it's nearly that time now.
Are you kicking us out of
my mother's funeral ?
It's okay.
Your mother is not here anymore.
She's with your... brother Mark.
You know that, don't you, girls ?
- Mary-Elizabeth !
- Catherine.
Catherine, let her go.
She needs the time.
Is it... Is somebody there ?
Is your baby all right ?
Excuse-me !
Wait !
A baby... who lived only one day.
Help !
Mommy, help me !
No !
It's okay.
I'm not gonna hurt you.
I'm the caretaker here.
Part-time, anyway.
Ivan's my name.
I'm Mary-Elizabeth.
I'm sorry that I screamed.
It's okay.
Imagine how I felt
the first time I looked in a mirror.
I was the vilest man I ever saw.
"Mary-Elizabeth !"
Do you know how worried we were ?
Now, Mary-Elizabeth,
are you alright, sweetheart ?
I must have fallen asleep.
Ivan Helped me. He's the caretaker.
Part-time caretaker.
I'm Albert...
I'm... Mary-Elizabeth's father,
that's why I...
want to thank you for your help.
Oh, you're Theresa's family.
I'm sorry for your loss.
- She was a real lady.
- Oh, thank you.
Look, do you need some extra work,
because I could use two... strong hands
for helping around the house.
I mean... especially now.
I could use the extra money.
G... Great !
You obviously believe that you're
a demon with supernatural abilities,
and you... you seem genuinely
sorry for raping her sister.
She was the only lady that
once ever gave a shit about me.
Rest of them can burn
in fucking hell for all I care.
Earlier you said that you were given
a chance by Satan to escape from Hell,
and to be born human again,
except there was a price.
Was raping Mary-Elizabeth that price ?
That was just the start.
A lot of death and a birth had to happen
so I could become human again.
Ah, jeez.
- Mary-Elizabeth ?
- Here !
- Mary-Elizabeth !
- Come here, girl.
Dad, I'll heat just some soup.
- Oh, no. Thanks. I just need to p... p... p...
- P... puh... puh... puh...!
Putter...around...your workshop.
Yeah, I know, I know.
Come down after five minutes,
and have some soup, and your pills.
I'm not a... child !
You know !
I'm not a child !
And spray some air-freshener
in there next time
you sneak for a smoke,
little boy.
I heard that.
And Mary-Elizabeth,
you should have something.
You know, you're not a model.
You can eat.
I'll be right back.
900-MY-BITCH,
who am I talking to, please ?
"I'm John. Who's this ?"
Jen. Now John, I need
to read you a little disclaimer.
And when I'm finished,
I need you to answer "Yes I agree",
if you agree to all the
conditions of our agreement.
Okay ?
"Yes I agree."
Not yet !
Welcome to 900-MY-BITCH. At no time will you
make any threats about me or any other individual.
- "Yes, I agree."
- Not yet.
You may never discuss topics such as humiliation,
personal degradation, cunnilingus,
anal penetration,
vaginal penetration, oral sex
or any kind of sex,
during the pre-screen portion of this call.
Do you understand and agree to the terms
of the 900-MY-BITCH agreement ?
"Now ?"
Yeah...
"Yes, yes, I agree.
What are you wearing ?"
What do you care, John, you little bitch ?
What the fuck is wrong with you, you little bitch ?
Can't get it up without calling me ?
Bitch !
You probably have giants scabs
on your joined hands,
stroking your deal, you worthless bitch !
Isn't that right, my bitch ?!
"It's true. I am a worthless bitch..."
It's me.
Listen, John, can you call back tomorrow ?
Same time, okay ?
Thank you for calling 900-MY-BITCH.
Jen, you know, if Catherine finds out
about those phone calls,
she's gonna kick you out so fast.
Probably... How are you, sweetie ?
You guys stayed a long time
after the funeral.
You okay ?
I don't know.
Did you ever have one of those dreams,
where you're falling and you can't stop ?
I feel that sensation all the time,
and I can't stop myself.
Jen, I don't want to live
without my mother.
You're scaring me.
You're going to be fine.
But it's gonna take some time.
You're not going to charge me $3.99
a minute for the physical contact, right ?
I don't charge urgence,
you can have it for free !
Stop it now, lesbo !
In your room !
This is a Christian household and
I will not tolerate deviant behaviour.
Catherine, we're just goofing around.
You're living under our roof for
next to nothing because of my mother.
Well, my mother's gone now.
And all she left me is a sick old stuttering father,
and a fragile sister to take care of.
So if you want to continue being my tenant,
watch your behaviour,
and no more late night guests.
Bitch.
Waky-waky !
Breakfast is on the table
for the next five minutes.
No thanks, Catherine.
I don't want any poached eggs,
wheat toast, cereals,...
How do you know I made that ?
We never have that.
Can't you smell it, Catherine ?
It's everywhere.
Get up.
I want to go through Mom's things,
and clean up the attic.
Dad and that... Ivan the albino are...
working in the workshop.
You've four minutes left.
Fifteen pounds !
"Mary-Elizabeth, come to breakfast...
now !
Oh Lord, you can't be sick today !
What's wrong with you ?
I gained fifteen pounds overnight.
That's not possible.
You're not pregnant, are you ?
I can't be, you know,
I've never even done it.
- I don't even have a boyfriend.
- You're sick to your stomach,
you can smell a cold breakfast
all the way downstairs,
and look at your stomach !
My God, look at it !
I just...
I just must be sick, that's all.
You'd better have a good explanation
why you have all the symptoms
of a pregant woman.
I don't know.
Honestly, Catherine, I don't !
No !
No, Catherine,
I am not a little girl anymore.
Get on the bed ! I wanna know !
I wanna know, you slut,
whom you spread your legs for !
You little slut !
Tell me !
So, you's a doctor, uh, Albert ?
You... Doctor Albert.
Oh yeah, I was an obstetri... trician,
before I contracted this...
lung problem.
Oh really ?
"whom you spread your legs for !"
"You little slut !"
- Hey, hey !
- "Tell me !"
- Keep it quiet down there !
Get in there !
Get in the tub !
- I'm gonna show you...
- Catherine, no !
- Oh yes ! You liked it, uh !
- No !
- Sit there !
- You wanted it ! You enjoyed it !
- No, no !
You wanted to feel it, the filthy,
filthy little pig inside your body !
- Nooooo !
- You enjoyed it !
How could you ?
A bastard into this family ?
Tell me who did this to our family ?
Tell me !
- Tell me who did this to you !
- I'm a virgin, I swear !
Tell me !
Catherine ! Stop it !
- Right now !
- Pregnant, she's pregnant ! Tell...
Leaver her alone !
Leave her alone !
It's all right.
It's all right, Mary-Elizabeth.
Tell me about Mary-Elizabeth.
You think she's the host ?
She might be the one.
Look, Father,
I know for a fact
she's never had any type of sexual
intercourse with anyone.
She's told me everything,
her entire life, in the confessional.
I doubt she's even been kissed.
Demons plant their seed mystically.
And always with a virgin.
You saw how Mary-Elizabeth
was at the cemetery.
And the Cardinal says a demon child
will be born on November 1st.
November 1st, the Day of the Dead.
The only that Death is
actually celebrated,
that demons can actually be reborn,
here on Earth.
The Day of the Dead.
What's going to happen
to the pregnant girl ?
Follow the Cardinal's orders.
That's something you don't see everyday.
Priest packing E ?
Some problems require more
than prayers and holy water.
Mary-Elizabeth isn't a problem.
She's an innocent human being
who just buried her mother.
Nick, I know you're emotionally
attached, but...
Look, I'm gonna do my part,
but I'm not going to bury
my head in the sand either.
Is this girl's family going to be hurt ?
The demon's unborn child
is going to force
Mary-Elizabeth to kill six people.
I've been ordered to observe.
Only I can't do anything
until the child is born.
That's insane.
Six innocent people will die.
And then you'll probably pay a visit
to Mary-Elizabeth and her baby with...
your pistol, your Bible...
And you don't seem to
have a problem with that.
I'm a professional doing a job.
No. I don't know who you were
before you joined the Holy Order,
but you are not a man of God.
You're an assassin.
Tell the Cardinal,
I won't be an accomplice.
This... is a medical miracle.
Let's go down to business, father.
Now, is she or isn't she ?
According to the test... yes.
Yes.
But that's not possible.
I believe you.
I mean, your hymen is unbroken
and I don't understand.
You are the... first pregnant
virgin I've ever heard of !
Not the first, father.
Not the first.
Maybe it's a divine intervention.
Why not ?
Maybe it's mother's soul
coming back to us, or... or...
it's the second coming.
How do you explain her gaining
fifteen pounds overnight ?
It could be, uh... toxemia.
What's that ? Do I have that ?
What about her nose ?
She smells better than a dog.
I don't know. I just don't know.
I mean, it could be a nasal receptor,
or an olfactory nerve,
overcompensating for
some of the conditions.
What about the hymen ? How do you explain
a woman getting pregnant
with an unbroken hymen ?
Mary, are you alright ?
- Mary ?
- No, I don't. Can you please leave ?
Leave ? But we live here.
Get the fuck outta my room !
That language is unacceptable.
What're you gonna do ? Ah, Catherine ?
Try and drown me again
like a bag of kittens ?
Go ahead ! I don't care.
I really don't, because none of this
makes sense to me anymore,
and I can't take any of it,
especially you !
Come on, Cath... Catherine, let your
sister rest. Let's go, let's go.
We'll figure this out, Mary.
We will.
"Hi, this is Jennifer.
Leave a message."
Hi Jen. It's me.
I was just calling to say I'm sorry.
Ah... Please tell my dad that I love him.
And I'm so sorry.
I just want...
I just wanna stop falling.
Thanks for being a friend.
Crap !
Sing, do something
to keep yourself awake.
Uh, an original then.
Let's see...
Driving back home to my baby...
'cause that's where my baby will be.
Hail Mary,
full of grace.
Our Lord is with thee.
Blessed art thou among women,
and blessed is the fruit of thy womb,
Jesus.
Holy Mary, Mother of God,
pray for us sinners,
now and at the hour of our death. Amen.
Mama !
Mama.
Call 9-1-1 !
Did you hear me ?
What the fuck is that ?
Hello, stranger.
Forever, little sister, forever.
Nothing. Nothing !
Fuck !
Shit !
What's this ?
Well, you're eating for two,
now, aren't you ?
You're wondering if I'm
gonna have the baby.
I am.
Alleluia.
She's having the baby.
Everything seems different this morning.
I don't know. Last night I...
I didn't want to live, and now...
I feel... rejuvenated !
Alive !
It's God's will.
But it has to remain a secret
until the baby's born.
Now, Dad can take care
of all your prenatal care,
and I can help you have
a safe home delivery.
I mean, I've helped Dad
so many times in the past,
and believe me,
homeopathic care is best.
Gin !
Hey you, crazy bastard, get in here.
Mary-Elizabeth, this is Lars.
My personal entertainment consultant.
I'm not, I'm your personal sex slave.
Do you think she wants to join us ?
Father Anthony,
any luck with the lightbulb ?
I fixed it.
Just a short.
Electronics is my hobby.
Oh, would you like me
to check the rest of the house ?
- I've got my gear in the car.
- Would you ?             - Sure.
That'd be a great time after
we return from the cemetery.
- This place is like a death trap.
- Okay.
Second month.
June 1.
Still missing your Mom.
The baby seems to be doing fine and Dad says
he can't believe my rapid development.
My belly has gotten huge in no time,
but that's okay.
I'm starting to feel
like a mother already.
I still don't know how
I became pregnant,
and I'm scared by some
of the other symptoms,
but excited by my bizarre cravings.
I'm ashamed to admit it, but it's true.
Catherine won't let anyone else see me,
to protect the family reputation.
But I guess Catherine knows what's best.
Okay... ready.
- Let's take a... picture.
- Sure.
All around, Mary.
Look.
Oh my God, Dad...
It's just like you said.
Just nothing to worry about.
Listen... I...'m sorry, sweetheart.
I... just don't want... to fail you,
like I did your mother and your brother.
Dad... you've never failed anyone.
I wonder.
Okay.
How... How's your energy level ?
I thought I'd feel drained, but I don't.
Actually, I feel really pumped.
You... wouldn't stay
in a shell this last month,
standing up for yourself, Mary,
and that's a good thing.
You know, this... pregnancy, seems to have
a positive effect on you.
- Flatterer !
- Yourself.
You just rest, ah ? Too much talk here.
I'm... gonna have a little...uh...
Shhh.
What's this ?
The foetus channel ?
Any cravings yet ?
My God... yes.
All my body has been doing
some very strange things.
My sex drive is insane.
Getting really horny.
You can borrow my pocket rocket,
be careful, it's worse than a real one.
No, no.
Get it off.
Come here girl !
Come get a treat !
Is that for me ?
- Hey !
- Hey, what's up ?
Uh, I need something,
do you have a minute ?
- Okay, what's up ?
- I need sex.
"I need sex." Who are you and what
the hell have you done with my friend ?
- What is going on here ?
- I can't explain it.
Although I feel like, if I don't have sex,
I'm going to kill someone.
Why don't you phone the mystery man
and tell him to come back
for a body call ?
I can't.
Who is he, anyway ?
Why do you keep it secret ?
I just...
I just can't say it, all right ?
It doesn't matter.
Oh my God,
Mary-Elizabeth wants
to fuck my fuck-buddy !
Thank you.
Pretty nice place.
But you should think
about getting a plasma.
I'm going to leave my business
card with my home number.
Can get you a great deal on HDTV.
Would you like a beer ?
No. Just you.
We have wine--
"--if you'd prefer.
- Jesus, Mary-Elizabeth, I don't wanna get drunk."
"Do you know how cute--"
you are ?
Come on, keep it in your pants,
get out of there.
I've never done this before.
It's okay, baby, I'll be gentle.
Can we go to bed now ?
Take me from behind.
Quickly !
- Do you want me to stop ?
- No !
Give it to me !
"Give it to me !"
Give it to me ! Give it to me !
Give it to me !
Alright, oh !
Hello, lover.
Stop this ! Something is poking me !
Come on, you little naughty !
- Faster, faster !
- No ! No ! Aagh !
Please !
No ! No ! Help ! Help !
Please, help !
No, please, help !
Stop, please !
Oh fuck !
What the fuck did you do to me,
you freak ?!
You're missing something, Lars ?
Are you hungry, baby ?
Yes mama, baby very hungry.
Eat, and baby be born,
baby be born !
Auf wiedersehen, baby.
So these killings were supposed
to make you human ?
Yeah. Make the blood flow again.
It wasn't working even though
my little sister was doing her best.
Please.
The vessel
is the... is the window
to the soul.
And Daddy needs me to be born, mother !
Think of it as prenatal care.
Now eat the sacred heart !
- No.
- Drink its blood.
- I can't !
- Why not ?!
Everyone eats flesh.
Animal or human, there's no difference !
- Flesh is flesh.
- It's wrong !
But I want it.
Didn't your saviour
tell his apostles to eat his flesh ?!
Drink his blood ?!
Don't you do that every Sunday at Mass ?
Now eat !
Drink !
Finish the rest.
"Please make your report, Father."
Cardinal Buenaventura,
it's an honour, sir.
The host still has no idea
she's carrying a demon's child.
Her physical development is rapid.
The feedings have been limited to one
sacrifice per month, as expected.
Your Eminence, I... I just dont understand
why we don't go in and
terminate the pregnancy now.
We can save the host and
stop the birth of this demon's child.
"You can't stop it till the moment
the creature is born."
"It's only vulnerable during birth."
But there's nothing mentioned in the Scriptures
about Satan's demon trying to sire a child
on Earth on the Day of the Dead.
"Would you have us yell fire
in a crowded theatre ?"
"There is a reason these goings
must be allowed, Father, trust me."
"All will be revealed."
"I know that this task
must be difficult for you,
"considering your conversion
from the military to the Church.
"But you truly are
the best man for the job.
"Give Father Nicholas my regards."
Thank you, your Eminence.
I will.
Third month.
July 1st.
My dreams have become
stranger and stranger.
Sometimes I'm not sure
what's a dream and what's real.
It's as if someone else has taken
control of my body.
Dad assures me that
I shouldn't be frightened by
my extreme mood swings
and cravings, but I am.
I disgust myself.
But I pray that everything will return
to normal after the baby's born.
Mary-Elizabeth,
it does your mother well.
It's perfect.
Thank you, Ivan
Loom me up, Mommy.
You ain't seen Lars lately ?
I called him a couple of times
but he never called me back.
Sometimes, he just disappears.
This rich divorcée whom
he met at a coffee-house one time,
next day, they flew
to Cancun for a month.
Forget him !
You wanna go out tomorrow night ?
I am getting half nuts in my cave.
But Catherine doesn't want
anyone to see me like this.
Jesus ! You're pregnant,
you don't have a lepracy.
Look, we'll sneak out to a club,
and I promise no-one
will know or see you.
Your sister will never even know you've gone.
Come on !
My treat !
Great, a club !
What am I supposed to do ?
Make you look thinner ?
Inside the house before someone sees you.
And Jennifer, cover yourself up.
This isn't a nude beach.
She's just sunbathing !
Don't make excuses for her.
I know what she's doing.
Now get inside.
Now !
What ?
You wanna get something off your chest
before I evict you ?
Do you see my hand trembling, Catherine ?
It's trembling 'cause I wanna
jump down your throat,
rip out your tongue
and strangle you with it.
So you'd better stay away
until I'm packed and out of here.
You hear me, my bitch ?!
I can't believe that you're
not living with us anymore.
Well, it's only an hour drive.
Tonight, I wanna get shitfaced, free of charge.
So all the drinks, alcoholic or otherwise,
are on the dude of the day. Got it ?
Are you sure the loud music's
not gonna hurt the baby ?
Nah. He's just gonna
dance the techno, that's all.
It's just so weird !
What do you say, baby ?
Yes, yes, yes.
Sweetheart, is this a bun in the oven,
or some kind of growth ?
No, it's a growth, like a
talking thing on your shoulders.
Okay. You two, leave. Get out of the line.
I mean because, she's either gotta
pop that thing or do like a billion abs.
Go on.
Come on, let's go.
Hey, even pregnant she still looks hotter
than most of the skinks you let in here, nazi !
Please Jen, let's just go.
- Mary ! Where're you going ?
- Just leave me alone.
Come on ! You can't listen to jerks
like that. You're beautiful.
No, I'm not. I'm a monster.
I'm a horrible monster.
Look at me.
Open your coat.
Open it.
Remember when Demi Moore was
pregnant and doing that magazine cover ?
Superb. And so do you.
I'do you !
Jen...
I can't bear to see you hurt.
Your kid's getting hasty.
Hello, friend.
Kiss my baby, Jen.
I said
kiss
my
baby !
You see, Jen, I'm the monster.
You're the beautiful one.
Why can't I feel anything ?!
Why couldn't you feel anything ?
Wasn't that part of your deal
with the devil ?
To become human ?
The deal was this :
Satan lets me become human again
if I knock off my sister,
force her to kill six people
during the pregnancy,
and to give birth to my demon kid.
Wait, wait, wait...
What happens to your kid ?
He raises chaos on Earth,
and replaces me as
Hell's torturer when he dies.
Every time she whacks someone,
I'm supposed to change,
I'm supposed to feel something.
But I'm not feeling shit !
And I still look like shit !
That's why I'm here.
Try to figure out what's going on
in my fucking head
before it's too late.
Father ?
I... I didn't hurt this girl.
...romise.
It... It was the pregnant girl.
I... I saw the whole thing.
Here.
Would you like to say
an act of contrition ?
Whassa ?
Never mind.
Forgive me, Father,
I'm truly sorry for
having offended Thee.
Hello, miracle baby.
That's what you are.
A miracle.
I wish we knew your father.
I think everything's gonna be alright.
Your Grandpa says he's not
sure about the delivery day,
because you grew so fast !
I wish I knew when the big day is.
If I knew, I'd have everything
ready for you when you arrive.
Well, why don't you want to tell Mommy ?
Come on, talk to Mommy.
Forgive me, Father, for I have sinned.
It's been over three months
since my last confession.
What's on your mind, Mary-Elizabeth ?
Father Anthony,
I was hoping it was you.
I... I don't know how to start.
I... I've been having visions and...
horrible, horrible dreams.
I have one about you and
the day that we buried my mother.
Dreams allow us to acknowledge
the inner urges we repress
without actually acting on them.
It's more than that.
Terrible things are going to happen,
or have happened, I don't know.
I don't know how to say this...
a man, a truck driver,
he died in an accident, two months ago.
But I dreamed about it
before I heard it on the news.
In my dream, I killed that man
just as they described it.
- Are you confessing the murder of this man ?
- No !
I mean, I don't know.
That's why I'm here, Father.
I... I'm pregnant, but I was a virgin,
and then, then I woke up one morning,
and I was pregnant and all
these dreams and visions began,
and I keep dreaming that I'm killing people.
And the cravings, yes, yes, the cravings,
and today...
today I saw my baby on the ultrasonic,
- I mean... it...
- Yes ?
What did you see on the ultrasonic ?
It branded me with some sort of symbol.
A star... but then it disappeared.
Pentagram.
Father, did you hear me ?
I'm listening.
I know it sounds crazy.
I sound crazy when I hear myself say it,
but that's why I can't tell my family,
or even Father Nick.
What do you think it is ?
Catherine said it came from Heaven,
but now I know the truth.
It came from Hell.
I believe you.
- You do ?
- I do.
Could I... really be pregnant
with... something... evil ?
Please, tell me what you really think.
I think you may be suffering
from some type of mental illness.
You may have even caught that
out of a traumatic sexual encounter
that caused your pregnancy.
But my dad examined me.
I'm sorry, Mary, but Albert hasn't
practised medicine in years.
He... may have made a mistake
about you being a virgin.
You said you believed me.
Dreams and delusions,
they can seem like reality.
But I burned my fingers
in the holy water !
Our cleaning lady pours
scalding hot water
in the holy water basins
at the end of each day.
She thinks she's cleansing everyone's germs.
She must have done it
just before you arrived.
I'm sorry, Mary. I'm sorry.
Your Eminence, I would like
to request a replacement.
I've heard your report
about the homeless man,
but that's an extreme situation.
There's always collateral
damage during a war.
You should know that better than anyone,
being a former soldier.
Your Eminence, I killed an innocent man,
not as a government's field agent,
or as a soldier, but as a priest.
I thought I'd left it all behind,
the killings, the assassinations.
I rationalize my past sins
as patriotic duty.
And now you have another going.
I enjoyed it.
Why was that ?
I had options...
...but I...
missed the thrill of the kill.
I can't lie to myself.
I killed him because he saw too much,
but I... enjoyed...
killing that man.
Once this mission is complete,
you have my permission
to turn yourself over
to the proper authorities.
Thank you, your Eminence.
You're experiencing the same guilt
and need for punishment
as Father Anthony.
The both of you care for your sister
and feel guilt over not
being able to protect her.
I knew it.
I fucking knew it was all in my head.
The clinical term is "psychosomatic".
A person's disease fighting ability
weakens under stress.
Like in a particularly
stressful situation.
As in raping your sister, for example.
Bullshit ! I'm supposed to be
human again, that's the deal.
You are experiencing
a human emotion : guilt !
I don't know about a demon
that would do that.
It's happening. Just slowly.
Or...
may I suggest that...
maybe you never really were
a demon to begin with.
Oh, I'm a demon, Dr Sammael.
And I care to look only for number one,
because I got one shot at
coming back a 100%.
Please, Mr Asmodeus, sit down.
We're making real progress here.
I told you, Dr Sammael, I'm a demon.
And you can't kill demons with bullets.
Stupid bitch !
Fourth month.
August 1st.
Every ultrasonic so far has been
back to normal since my delusion.
Thank God, the dreams have stopped too.
Everything is normal, except the baby's
still growing at an incredible rate.
Dad says that does happen
to a small percentage of women.
But I think that's kinda weird.
Still haven't heard from Jen
since that night at the club.
Guess she's busy.
Waky waky Mommy !
Baby hungry !
Oh my God !
"Oh my God !
No !"
Hungry, Mama...
Hungry...
Feed me, fucking sow, I'm hungry !
Shit.
The mike...
I'm gonna let you stay awake
for this one, Mommy !
I wanna savour your fear.
Feed on it.
And your daddy's heart at the same time.
No !
I won't let you.
Bitch !
You can't stop me now.
I'm already in my third trimester !
You've made me strong
with all that fresh meat, Mommy.
Who's slamming doors at this time ?
And do you remember
the feedings now, Mommy ?
I can smell that old goat
smoke downstairs.
How're you feeling, sweetheart ?
This is gonna be
one nasty feeding, Mommy.
I hope you brought a puke bag.
No !
No.
I won't let you.
You sound like you need...
some honey or a cup... cup of...
Hello grandpa !
Or should I say stuttering supper ?
God !
No !
Well, come on !
What is that...
thing ?
Oh Daddy ! Kill it !
Kill this monster inside me !
I don't... I don't understand !
Daddy please ! Get what you need.
Use that thing.
Hit it ! Hit it !
Hit it !
Hit it, fucking hit it, Albert !
Hit that motherfucker !
- I can't.
- Dad, just do it !
I can't hold it much longer.
I can't hurt you, sweetheart.
I can't.
No !
Bad Mommy !
You need to be punished !
Aah !
God !
Dad, I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry.
Is okay... It's okay, honey.
My adrenaline is
so high I can hardly... feel.
Oh my God.
Dad... it stopped.
We've gotta do something fast.
A sedative.
Bring me a sedative,
I'm gonna operate it.
Is there an issue, Father ?
Shit hit the fan, your Eminence.
Our host is fighting back, and winning.
That cannot be allowed to happen.
Sir, I know it's not my place to say this,
but there's another innocent
about to be killed.
- Can't we just--
- You're my main field operative, Father Anthony.
Follow your protocol.
I've lost my audio feed.
So I'm gonna have to expose
myself and go in.
Just keep drink... drinking.
But I... I'm trying.
I'm trying.
Oh my God !
Oh my God, I killed Jen !
And Lars !
And that trucker !
I'm a murderer !
- I'm a murderer !
- No, you're not.
If anyone was killed,
they were killed by that...
... thing.
Not you !
Now get undressed
and get under the sheets.
It's amazing.
I mean, it seems perfectly
normal now... now.
Mary, sweetheart,
I'll have to do something barbaric here.
So I want you to be... perfectly still,
so I... won't hurt you too much.
Dad !
Make it go away !
Shut up, you drunken cow !
Mary... just be still, please !
Be... still !
Pulp the sow, Grandpa,
and make her bleed like a pig !
Go on, stick her, stick it in her--
Don't... Don't listen
to it, just do it ! Just do it !
Yes ! Do it !
And watch your daughter die,
just like you wife did, you fucking hag !
Just do it.
Just do it !
Open her pussy, Grandpa !
- I can't do it.
- Just do it.
God ! Help us !
Oh God ! What are you doing ?
- Get a...    - No !
- Get a towel and clean the blood...
- while I'm doing this.
- You can't do this !
You can't do it !
I'm trying to save
your sister from a... monster,
- and you should be helping me to do it.
- Oh no !
Now shut up and hold that !
Hold it !
It's almost over. It's almost...
It's almost... over.
It's almost over, sweetheart,
almost over.
- No !
- Daddy !
Sorry, Albert.
No ! Leave him alone !
I told you I wouldn't let you
kill this baby, father.
It must be born
so Asmodeus can live again !
Yeah !
... gone to remain till baby's born...
While a year has come and gone,
since evil last tried to spawn.
Come down, come down, come down below.
The son of tradition waits to grow...
Mary-Elizabeth...
Shht ! Quiet !
Please don't talk, Father.
You wake the baby.
Father,
you're awake. Welcome back.
You've been in a coma for a month.
What... are you ?
Asmodeus the demon.
I used to be their brother.
Don't get all pissed, now.
I've calmed smarter guys than you.
Or how the Cardinal'd say :
Don't be stressed, Father,
I have withered brighter
men than yourself.
But why ?
Why did you have to use me ?
You didn't need a priest.
I'm the Torturer of the
13th level of Hell.
I fuck with people !
It's what I do.
You seem damn
comfortable in your custom.
I enjoy the irony.
Yeah, yeah, yeah...
We all know how good in killing
you are, Father.
There's another reason you're
chosen as the sixth sacrifice.
We need a murderer to complete
the birthing cabinet.
Nah, don't worry,
we still need you alive.
For a while.
Make sure you feed Mary tonight.
You heard Asmodeus.
Now go'n be ready to
give your sister a meal.
Why can't you do it ?
Because I fucking say so !
You got a problem with that ?
My brother runs this place.
I don't take orders from a...
tiny, pasty individual like you.
Bitch.
I read your book.
You say some really
nice things about me.
You should feel lucky.
It's a great honor to be the host.
That's why your sister's jealous,
you know that, right ?
That day she tried to drown
you the in the tub,
she knew you were the chosen one.
Because she's been
a virgin all her life.
But he didn't pick her.
He picked you.
So she took it out on you.
Sisters...hmm.
You want me to write
in your book for you ?
Fifth month.
September 1st.
Mary-Elizabeth is getting
as big as this freaking house.
Tonight I take her hunting
for a fifth sacrifice,
and I have a special plan for her.
Everything has been going real good
since we took over the house.
But you can still feel a little tension
between Mary and her sister.
And if there is one thing you don't
want around a pregnant woman,
it's tension...
Especially from a jealous sister.
So like the big man upstairs says :
"If thy right eye offend thee,
pluck it out and cast if from thee."
Amen, brother.
Hello, sister.
You're shivering.
No that's okay, I'm getting out.
Elizabeth...
Please, Mary-Elizabeth...
"Oh, Mary-Elizabeth, please, no."
I took care of you, don't you remember ?
I... I looked after you.
That's true, Catherine.
- But do you love me ?
- Yes, of course I do.
I love you. I'd do anything
for you but it's... it's...
- Would you do anything for me ?
- Yes, anything. Just command it.
All right, I command you to be my doll.
I'm gonna be a baby soon,
and babies love dollies.
Be my dolly !
Clean the dolly, Mommy !
Rub the dolly, Mommy !
Rub !
Leave me ! Leave me, please ! Leave me !
Scrub it up !
Clean the dolly in the tub !
Need to clean the dolly thoroughly.
Number five.
The sister.
"...first pitch and back into sandpit..."
"November 1st, the Day of the Dead,
is right around the corner.
"The Vatican knows the date
and wants you to know it..."
Crap ! On all the fucking channels,
nothing but crap !
I'm bored.
Talk to me.
Why not let me talk to Mary-Elizabeth ?
What do I get out of it ?
We both know I can't beat you, right ?
But I can try.
Worth a try, it should be entertaining.
Crushing your spirit.
It's better than wild trash on talk TV.
All right. You get sixty seconds.
Go !
What about your white monkey ?
What's to prevent him from zapping me
before my time is up ?
Sonofabitch !
Fine !
Sixty seconds... uninterrupted.
And as a bonus,
Ivan and I will not listen.
What could I've done to you ?
It's important that
you listen to me, Mary.
Really listen.
I'm not leaving this house, I know that.
But you... still have a chance.
- Don't say that.
- Just listen.
Everything you've done,
and will do to me,
is not
your fault.
You have not killed anyone.
If you survive this ordeal,
you'll have to accept that fact,
and forgive yourself.
Or the guilt will destroy you.
Your brother and that creature
inside of you will have won.
- But I killed my family. I was weak.
- No !
You're the only chance your
family has to survive this,
and continue in through you.
Do you understand ?
Do you understand me ?
You carry your family with you,
Mary-Elizabeth,
but you have to survive.
And then forgive yourself for surviving.
Good. Good.
I just pray to God
that you remember this.
I will.
How disappointing !
I knew you had a fucking Jesus
complex, but this, boy...
Very disappointing.
You gave my mother a glimmer of hope.
And now let me tell you what
you're going to give me, Anthony.
Tomorrow is my birthday.
And you're going to give me your heart,
and your blood,
and your head.
And give me the gift of life.
Now here's something to take your
mind off that horrible thought.
Don't let him bleed to death.
Our Father...
Who is in Heaven...
Hallowed be Thy name...
If you'd like to...
make a confession...
I'm willing to listen.
What ?
You do know that homosexuality is a sin.
You calling me a fag ?
That's a well-known fact that
99% of albinos are born with the same gene
known to cause homosexuality.
That's not funny, Father.
How many times have you touched
my penis with your stunt-gun ?
I ain't no fag.
But you keep playing with my cock.
I ain't no fag !
You hear, I ain't no fag !
I ain't no fag ! Damn priest !
Hear me ?
The priest is ready.
I can smell his fear,
and... anger ?
Ivan ?
Ivan !
Stop him !
You hear me ? I'm no fucking faggot !
What are you doing ?!
Fucking albino !
You just lost... the war.
The murderer has to die by your hand
or the contract is not finished.
You have to take the life
that captured the soul.
Nooooooo !
Fucking... damned... traitor... vile...
despicable... motherfucker !
You would have been perfect,
but you had to redeem
yourself by dying !
Don't smile like this at me !
Stupid priest, you think you won ?
Got rid of the murderer ?
But I still have one more move.
You just helped create
your own replacement.
Ivan... is now a member
of your exclusive club...
- of murderers !
- No !
- No, no, no !
- Yes, motherfucker !
No !
Daddy ! I'm coming !
Let's begin.
You selfish bitch, fight him !
Fight, Mary.
Fight the demon's child.
Don't do it, Mary. Get out of the house.
Get out of the house !
Please don't do that... sweetheart !
Get out !
That baby is mine !
I love you, Mary-Elizabeth.
Mom ?
I love you.
Be gone, be gone, the son of Asmodeus
is about to be born, bitch.
We grow weak... I'm ready.
I'm ready to be born !
Helpers !
Hold her up.
Filthy ! Unclean ! Foul !
My son will be born, you can't do anything.
Push !
Push now !
Push, bitch !
Come on !
Do it now, push !
That's it, little sister.
Come on, push !
He's perfect.
Let me hold him.
Dr Sammael ?
I am the Venom of God.
Lucifer is the one true Satan.
Demons are so stupid.
I have many names.
I play many roles.
Before Lucifer, I was Sammael.
Playing the role of the accusor,
the seducer, the destroyer.
Eventually I became known as Satan.
Your lord and master.
Are you ready to go back
to the 13th level of Hell ?
Rise.
I did everything you said.
You wavered. You had doubts.
You went to a fucking psychiatrist.
But I still did everything you wanted.
You have the child.
My son will serve you here on Earth
and replace me in the pit later.
Oh, I don't think so.
You're going back, now.
You promised.
You can't break our agreement now.
We have an agreement.
You can't...
We have a fucking agreement !
Please.
Please !
No !
No ! No ! No !
Oh, you did a really good job.
You get to live.
Flee.
Ladies,
I think he's finally find closure.
Heavenly Father,
Satan poisoned this young woman's child.
But you, Lord, gave the baby a free will.
Please, Lord, hear our prayer.
Mary-Elizabeth Martino,
will you dedicate your life
to finding your child,
and properly raise him following
the teachings of Christ ?
I will.
When you find the demon's child,
do you swear before God
and His son Jesus-Christ,
to protect the baby from all evil,
keeping him safe within the support
and the protection of the Holy Church ?
I will.
And I also dedicate my aid
in finding your child,
and I bless you,
in the name of the Father,
and the Son,
and the Holy Spirit.
Amen.
Subtitles : Intermodal (2009)