Subtitle by: Tarun
Are you sure you're eighteen?
- Why? Do I look older?
Alberta Scrubb?
- It's a typographical error
- It is suppose to be Albert A. Scrubb.
- Edmund, you are suppose to be helping
me with the groceries.
Better luck next time, ay, squirt?
Squirt? He barely had 2 years on me!
I am a king. I've fought wars
and I've led armies.
Not in this world.
- Yeah, instead i'm stuck here.
Doing battles with useless Clarence Scrubb.
If anyone so deserve the name.
What are you doing?
Nothing.
Come on then.
Dear Diary.
It is now day 253.
since my ratchet cousins
Edmund and Lucy invaded our house.
Not sure how much long i can cope
living with them.
Hard to share my things.
If only one could treat relatives like
one who treat insects,
all my problems would be solved.
I could simply put them in a jar.
Pin them to my wall?
- I'm home!
- Hello?
- Note to self.
Investigate legal ramifications
of impaling relatives.
And that concludes the war news from the western front.
- Hi, Uncle Harold.
I've tried to find some carrots
but all they had were turnips again.
Should I start making soup?
And Alberta is on her way home.
Uncle Harold?
- Father.
Edward making faces at you.
Why, you little...
- Father, he's going to hit me.
Edmund look, it's from Susan.
I do wish you were here with us.
It is such an adventure.
But nothing like our times in Narnia.
America is very exciting.
Only we never see father.
He works so very hard.
I was invited to the British consul's
tea party this week by a naval officer.
Who happens to be very handsome.
I think he fancies me.
It seems that the Germans have made the
crossing difficult right now.
Time are hard. Mother hopes you both won't mind
another few months in Cambridge.
Another few months?
How will we survive?
You're lucky. At least you've got your own room.
I'm stuck with mullet mouth.
Susan and Peter are the lucky ones.
Off on adventures.
- Yeah. They are the olders we are the youngest.
We don't matter as much.
Do you think i look anything like Susan?
Lucy, have you seen this ship before?
- Yes, it's very Narnian looking isn't it?
Yeah. Just another reminder that we're here
not there.
There once was two orphans who wasted their time.
believing in Narnian nursery rhyme.
Please let me hit him!
- No.
Don't you ever knock?
- It's my house.
I do as I please. You're just guests.
What's so fascinating about that picture anyway?
It's hideous.
You won't see it from the outside of the door.
Edmund look, looks like the water is actually moving.
What rubbish, see? That's what happens when you
read all those fancy little novels and fairy tales of yours.
There once was a boy called Eustace, who read books
for facts which were worthless.
People who read fairy tales are always a sort of becoming
a hideous burden compared to people like me.
I read books with real information.
- A hideous burden?
I haven't seen you lift a finger
since we've been here.
I hope you won't mind I tell your father it was you
who stole Aunt Alberta sweets?
- Liar?
- Really?
- Edmund, the painting!
- I found them under your bed.
And you know what? I've licked every one of them!
Ew! I'm infected with you!
What is going on here?
- Lucy, do you think...
This is some kind of a trick. Stop or I'll tell mother.
Mother!
I'll just smash the whole thing.
Do something!
- No.
Help me.
- Let me go.
Let go.
Eustace, swim!
- What's going on?
Swimming!
Swim.
It's alright! I got you.
Caspian?
- Lucy.
Edmund, it is Caspian.
- You're safe now.
Are we in Narnia?
- Yes, you are in Narnia.
I don't wanna go. I want to go back to England!
I'm going back to England!
Hold on.
That was thrilling!
How in the world do you end up here?
- I have no idea.
- Caspian!
- Edmund.
It's great to see you.
- Didn't you call for us?
No, not this time.
Well, whatever the case, i'm just glad to be here.
Ahh! Get that thing off me!
Reepicheep!
Your Majesty.
- Hello, Reep.
What a pleasure.
- The pleasure is all mine sir.
But first, what to do about this,
this hysterical interloper?
That giant rat thing just tried to claw my
face off!
I was merely trying to expel the water from
your lungs sir.
He talks! Does anyone understand? He just talk!
- He always talks.
Actually its getting him to shut up that's the trick.
The moment there is nothing to be said your highness,
I promise you I will not say it.
I don't know what kind of prank this is.
I wanna wake up right now!
Perhaps we can throw him back?
And being abducted by a kind
of zeepiratencarnival.
I demand to know just where in the blazes am I?
You're on the Dawn Treader.
The finest ship in Narnia's navy.
Was it something I said?
See to him for me.
- Your majesty.
Men.
Behold our castaways.
Edmund the Just
and Lucy the Valiant.
High King and Queen of Narnia.
Aslan.
Look! Susan's bow and arrows.
- Lucy
- My Healing Cordial and dagger.
oh, May I?
- Of course. They are yours.
Peter's sword.
- Yes.
I looked after as promised.
Here.
Hold it if you wish.
No, it's yours.
Peter has given it to you.
I did saved this for you though.
Thanks.
Since you've left, the Giants in the North
had surrendered unconditionally.
And we defeated the Calormen army of the
great desert.
There is peace across all of Narnia.
- Peace?
For three years.
And have you found yourself a queen in those
three years?
No. Not one to compare to your sister.
Hang on, so there are no wars to fight
and no one is in trouble...
Then, why are we here?
- That's a good question.
I have been asking myself the same thing.
So, where are we sailing?
- To get back the throne from my uncle.
He tried to kill my father's closest friends and
most loyal supporters.
The seven Lords of Telmar.
They fled to the Lone Islands.
No one has heard from them since.
So you think something has happened to them?
- Well, if it has...
It is my duty to find out.
What lies east of the Lone Islands?
Uncharted waters. Things that
you can barely imagine.
Tales of sea serpents and worse.
Sea serpents?
- Alright captain, enough of your tall tales.
Where skies i want to be, where the waves are sweet.
Descends upon you, Reepicheep.
That's pretty!
- oh! Thank you.
A "driad" sung to me when i was just a "materling".
I can't divine the meaning but i never forgotten
the words.
What do you think past Lone islands is?
I've been told the furthest east one can sail
is to the end of the world.
Aslan's country.
- Do you really believe there is such a place?
We have nothing if we do not believe.
Do you think you can actually sail there?
Well, there is only one way of finding that out.
Only hope one day I'd earn the right to see it.
Your majesty.
You have grown stronger, my friend.
Seems I have.
Alright! Back to work.
Edmund, Do you think if we keep sailing
to the end of the world, we just...
tip off the edge?
Don't worry, Lu.
We're long way from there.
I see you're still talking nonsense.
Are you feeling better?
- Yes, but not thanks to you.
It's like I have an iron constitution.
- You're ever "vesitence" ever I see. (?)
Found your sea legs?
- Never lost them.
It's just given a shock of things. (?)
Obviously have the cutest position, (?)
due to my intelligence.
I don't think he has "apute" anything (?)
I'll have you know as soon as
I find civilization.
I'm contacting the British Consulate.
Having you arrested for kidnapping.
Kidnapping is it? That's funny.
I thought we had saved your life.
You held me here against my own will!
- Did I?
(???) in that quarters
It's like a zoo down there!
He's quite the complainer, isn't he?
- He is just warming up.
Landfall.
The Lone Islands.
Narrow Haven's portal.
Strange. No Narnia flag in sight.
The Lone Islands
always been of Narnia's.
Seems suspicious.
I say we prepare a party
Drinian?
- Forgive me, Your Majesty...
But the chain of command starts with Prince Caspian
on this ship
Right
- We use rowboats. Drinian, pick some men and come
on shore.
Men the row boats! Throw the sailer and prepare to
go out.
and get ready to lower the anchor.
En route! (??) lies ahead.
Can't we just wait till the morning?
There is no honor in turning away from adventure land.
Listen!
Where is everyone?
Come on, jelly legs.
- I'm capable of getting out myself!
And you're certain you're related by blood?
Reepicheep, stay here with Drinian's men
and secure the place.
We will head up.
If we don't come back by dawn,
send the party.
- Yes, Your Majesty.
Yeah, looks like nobody is in.
So do you think we should go back?
Do you want to come here and guard...something?
Ah, yes.
Good idea, cousin.
Very..um, logical.
I've got it.
Don't worry.
I'm ready to go when you are!
Who are all these people?
- Why are they've been crossed out?
Looks like some kind of fee..?
- Slave Traders.
Look out.
Unless you want to hear this scum squeal like
a girl again,
I would say, you should drop your weapons.
I'm not a girl.
- Now!
Put it down!
- Useless..
Put them in irons.
- Come here you!
Get your hands off me. Let go!
Take these two to the market.
Send those other two to the dungeons.
Listen to me, you insolent fool.
I am your king!
You're gonna pay for that!
- Actually...
someone else is going to pay.
For all of you.
You all right?
- Yeah.
It is hopeless.
You'll never get out.
Who's there?
- Nobody.
Just a voice in my head.
Lord Bern?
That was me once.
I do not deserve that title anymore.
Is he one of the seven?
Your face. You remind me of
a king that I once know.
That man was my father.
My Lord, please forgive me.
No, please.
No!
- Mommy!
Get back.
Stay with daddy.
- Don't worry. I will find you!
Mommy!
Where are they taking them?
- Keep watching.
What happened?
- It's a sacrifice.
Where did they go?
- No one knows.
The mist was first seen in the east.
Reports of fishermen and sailors
disappearing out at sea.
We lords have made a pact...
to find the source of the mist
and to destroy them.
They each set sail,
But none of them came back.
You see, If they don't sell you to the slave
traders
You're likely to be fed to the mist
- We have to find Lucy.
Before it's too late.
- I offer 60.
I bid 80!
- 100 for the little lady.
120!
- 150.
Anymore bids?
SOLD!
Come on, move!
And now, for this fine speciment!
Who'd kick off the bidding?
Come on now, he may not seem like much,
but uh..he is strong.
Yes, he's strong alright. Smells like
the rear end of a Minotaur.
That is an outrageous lie.
I won the school hygeine award,
two years running!
Come on, someone make your bid!
- I'll take them off your hands.
I'll take them all out of your hands.
For Narnia!
Thanks, Reep. I knew you would come.
- Your Highness.
Grab the keys.
Keys!
oh, you're a boat in a magical land.
Can't you row yourself?
I hope that wasn't British consul.
Your majesty!
- Wait.
My wife was taken just this morning.
- Daddy!
I beg you, take me with you.
I want to come.
- No, Gael. Stay with your aunt.
I am a fight sailor, been on the seas
my whole life.
Of course, you must.
- Thank you.
But Daddy!
- If I ever not come back...
Now be good.
My king!
This was given to me by your father.
I hid it safely in the cave.
All these years.
- I thought that is Narnian sword?
It's from your Golden Age.
There are seven of those swords.
Gifts from Aslan to protect Narnia.
Your father entrusted them to us.
Here. Take it.
And it may protect you.
Thank you, my Lord.
And we shall find your lost sisters(?).
Edmund.
Dear diary.
There has been extraordinary turn of event.
I have been abducted by my cousins and set
to drift in uncharted waters.
In some ridiculously looking boat.
What's worse, as I share quarters with obnoxious
mouse thing,
My thought banking with my cousins was bad enough.
So far, every person I met in this strange place
suffers
from the most florit delusions
Chasing for green mists and looking for lost lords.
I can only assume this is the result of poor diet.
Everyone are barking mad.
Cousin Edmund is no exception.
He spends every spare second rubbing that thin sword.
Like it's some magic lantern.
Poor fool clearly needs a hobby.
It is going to be magnificient.
Do they come in a smaller size?
Peeving Marmud (?)
He's more delusional than my cousin.
In England we have mousetraps
and that sort of things.
Speaking of food, do you think I can get any
do you?
Uh, why you talking to that bird?
I just naturally assumed that...
- (Laughs) He's talking to birds.
He is as mad as a looner that one.
Shoo! Go go.
Are you aware sir...
Stealing rations is a capital offense?
Up here.
You.
- Men have been killed for less.
For What?
- Treason and sneakiness...and general nuisances.
Just hand over the orange and we'll let the matter pass.
I don't know what you're talking about.
- Allow me to...
I've had quite enough of you.
- Unhand the tail.
The Great Aslan himself gave me this tail.
No one. Repeat. No one touches the tail.
Period. Exclamation mark!
- Sorry.
Now. I will have the orange, then I will have satisfaction.
Puh, puh, please, please, please, um. I'm a pacifist.
Watch it.
- Sorry.
Are you trying to run away?
We're on a boat you know.
Can't we just discuss this?
That is for stealing, that is for lying,
and that was for good measure.
(Laughs) That's the spirit! We have ourselves
a duel! Catch.
Now, come on.
Take your best shot.
Is that it?
Come on, boy.
Stop flapping your wings like
a drunken pelican.
Hoist!
Keep your leg up.
Yoo-hoo! Over here.
On your foot.
On your left, your right.
Got it? Come on.
The Nimble. It is a dance, boy.
Come on now. And again.
Oh, no.
And that!
Look.
Gael, what are you doing here?
It seems that we
have an extra crew member.
Welcome aboard.
- Your majesty.
Call me Lucy.
Come on.
Come on, look lovely, back to work!
Good match!
I will make a swordsman of you yet.
Yes, well...it's the plane we look more even
it would be an entirely different result.
(Laughs) Indeed.
It looks like uninhabited.
If the Lords follow the mist to the east,
they would have stopped here.
It could be a trap.
Or it can held some answers.
- Caspian?
We spend the night on shore.
Scout the island everyone.
Ay, Your Majesty.
Seems they have brought a pig.
This one. It's female.
So is this one.
This one reads.
Let's take her.
There is no escape!
- We are scary.
What are you?
- We are terrifying invisible beasts.
If you could see us, you would be really
intimidated.
You forgot to mention that we all are
very large.
What do you want?
- You'll do what we ask.
She will!
- Very clear. Well put!
Or what?
- Or death.
Death.
Well, I won't be much use to you when
I'm dead now, would I?
I haven't thought of that.
- No, you hadn't. Fair point.
Alright. Then we'll just kill your friends!
Good idea.
- What do you want with me?
You'll enter the house of the Opressor.
What house?
- This one.
Upstairs, you'll find the book of incantation
recite the spell that makes the unseen, seen.
Well put chief, well put.
- Very. Yeah.
Well, go on.
We haven't got all day.
Remember what will happen to your friends
You've been warned.
- Yeah.
Right.
Why don't you do it yourself?
- We can't read.
Can't write for the matter of fact.
All that.
- Yeah.
Why didn't you just say so?
Beware of the opressor.
- He is very aggressive!
What makes the unseen, seen.
Got it? Don't forget that!
Ed, wake up.
Wake up!
Look.
Where's Lucy?
Lucy!
Everybody up!
- Get up.
This way.
- Move!
The Book of Incantation
MAXIM TO HEAL Pain
A MAXIM TO FORGET
With these words, Your tongue must sew.
For all around there to be snow.
An infallible spell to make you she,
the beauty you've always wanted to be.
Susan, what's going on?
I'm beautiful.
No! wait.
Make me she, whom i'd agree.
Aslan?
A spell to make the unseen, seen.
If the 'p' in psychology,
the 'h' in psychiatry...
invisible ink and the truth
in theology.
Caspian, Lucy's dagger.
Stop right there or there is!
The spell is complete.
Now all is visible.
What sort of creatures are you?
- Great ones.
With the head of a tiger and
the body of um-different tiger.
You don't want to mess with us!
- Or what?
Or I'll claw you to death!
I'll run my touch right through you!
I will crush you with my teeth.
- And i'll bite you with my fangs.
You mean squash us
with your fat bellies?
Fatty bellies?
- Or tickle us with your toes?
What have you done with my sister, you little pip squid?
Now, calm down.
- Where is she?
Can I tell him?
- Tell him, chief.
In the mansion.
- What mansion?
Oh. That mansion.
Now, I'm getting tired of you leaving me behind.
The thing came back.
This place is weirder and weirder.
He's calling us weird.
- Lucy! Your majesty.
- Caspian and Edmund.
This is Coriakin.
It's his island.
That's what he thinks.
You have wronged us, magician.
I have not wronged you, I've made you
invisible for your own protection.
Protection?
- That's aggressive! Opressor!
I have not opressed you.
- But you could have!
If you wanted to!
- Be gone.
What was that?
- Loot(?). But don't tell them.
What were those things?
- Dufflepuds.
Of course.
Silly me.
What did you mean when you said you made them
invisible for their own good?
It seems to be the easiest way
to protect them.
From the evil.
- You mean the mist?
I mean what lies behind the mist.
It's quite beautiful.
I mean for a made belived that and
a made believed world.
There is the source of your problems.
The Dark Island.
A place where evil lurks.
It can take any form. It can make your
darkest dream come true.
It seeks to corrupt all goodness
Steal the lights from this world.
How do we stop it?
- You must break its spell.
That sword you carry, there
are six others.
Have you seen them?
- Yes.
The six lords, they passed through here?
- Indeed.
Where are they heading?
- Where I've sent them.
Break the spell.
You must follow the Blue Star...
to Ramandu's Island.
There the seven swords must be laid
at Aslan's table.
Only then can the truly magical power
be released.
But beware. You will
all about to be tested.
Tested?
It will do everything in it's power
to tempt you.
Be strong...
Don't fall to temptations.
To defeat the darkness out there
you must defeat the darkness inside yourself.
For reasons beyond my comprehension
We have taken the advice from the senile old coup(?).
who doesn't possess a razor, and
walks around on a dressing gown.
So we're back in the bathtub and
and lost in the tempest. Brilliant!
14 days of being tossed like a pancake,
not the slightest sight of land.
The only consolation is that everyone is finally
as miserable as I am.
Except for that show-off talking rat.
He is one of the annoying glass is always
half full part.
So, we're stuck here...
with half rations, we have
food and water for two more weeks maximum.
This is your last chance to
turn back, your majesty.
Not in this storm.
Needle in a haystack trying to find this
remoteless place.
We can sail way past and knocked to the end
of world.
We can be eaten by a sea serpent.
You'll see when the men are getting nervous.
These are strange seas we are sailing
the lights that which i've never seen before.
Then perhaps captain, you'd love to be the one
to explain to Mr. Rince that we're abandoning
the search for his families?
I'll get back to it.
Just a word of warning,
the seas can play nasty tricks on a crew mind.
Very nasty.
Transform my reflection, cast into affection
lashes, lips and complexion.
Let me like whom I agree,
cause more beauty over me.
Ladies and Gentlemen,
Ms. Pevensie.
Edmund?
- You look beautiful, Sister.
As always.
- Peter!
Excuse me Miss,
Can I get a photo?
Mother's gonne love this,
all her children in one picture.
Smile!
- Hang on. Where am I?
I mean where's Lucy?
- Lucy, who's Lucy?
Susan, what's wrong?
Come on now Miss.
A nice big smile!
Edmund, I'm not sure about this. I think
I want to go back.
Go back where?
- To Narnia!
What is Narnia?
- What's going on?
Stop this!
Lucy.
- Aslan?
What have you done, child?
I don't know,
but that was awful.
But you chose it, Lucy.
I didn't mean to choose all that. I just wanted
to be as beautiful like Susan.
That's all.
You wished yourself away,
and with it, much more.
Your brothers and sisters wouldn't know Narnia
without you, Lucy.
You discovered it first, remember?
I'm so sorry.
You doubt your value,
don't run from who you are.
Aslan!
Father.
Edmund.
Come with me.
Join me.
Edmund?
Lucy.
I can't sleep.
- Let me guess. Bad dream?
So either we're all going mad,
or something is playing with our minds.
I doubt the Lord stopped here,
there is no sign of anything living.
Right. Well, once you have got on shore, take your men
for food and water.
The three of us will look for clues.
- You mean the four of us?
Come on, please don't send me back to the rat.
- I heard that!
Big ears.
- I heard that too.
Look. We
not the first on the island.
The Lords?
- Could be.
What do you think could be down there?
Let's find out.
What is that?
- I don't know. Looks like some kind of a gold statue.
He must have fallen in.
Poor man.
- You mean, poor Lord.
The crust of Lord rest in him.
- And his sword.
We need it.
Be careful.
Your sword hasn't turn to gold.
- Both swords are magical.
He mustn't have known what hit him.
Maybe, or maybe
He was onto something.
What are you talking about?
What are you staring at?
Whoever has access to this pool,
could be the most powerful person in the world.
Lucy, we'll be so rich
no one can tell us what to do, or who to
live with.
You can't take anything out of Narnia, Edmund.
Says who?
- I do.
I am not your subject.
You have been waiting for this, haven't you?
To challenge me. You doubt my leadership!
You doubt yourself.
You're a child.
- And you're a spineless sap.
Edmund?
- I'm tired of playing second fiddle...
First it was Peter, and now it's you.
You know I am braver than both of you.
Why did you Peter's sword?
I deserve a kingdom of my own!
I deserve to rule!
- If you think you're so brave...
prove it!
No!
Stop it!
Both of you.
Look at yourself.
Can't you see what's happenning?
This place has tempted you.
It is bewitching you,
This is exactly what Coriakin is talking about.
Let's just get outta here.
Oh yes, follow the imaginary blue star,
to the island of Rabandoedoe...
Like the seven steak knives
on the table of a talking lion.
Nonsense.
What is that?
I must be dead.
You are definitely dead.
You wouldn't be needing that one wont you.
Finally, a favorable turn
of events.
What foods did you found?
It is volcanic, My majesty.
Nothing grows.
Where is Eustace?
I believe he's out not helping us loading
the boats.
Eustace!
I have got a bad feeling.
I'm going to find him.
I'll come with you.
Eustace?
Treasure.
Trouble.
Eustace's.
No.
I'm sorry.
- He was just a boy.
I shouldn't have left him.
What could have happened to him?
In this place? Anything.
And he wasn't the first.
It's Lord Octesian.
We should find this... sword.
What was that?
Is it the volcano?
Oh no, that's not a volcano.
All hands on deck.
Archers, arm yourselves!
Take your positions
and wait for my command.
What is it doing?
- Fire!
He will break the mast.
Hold your positions.
Fire!
Edmund!
- Lucy.
I AM Eustace
You've got to be joking!
He must have been tempted by the treasure.
Everyone knows that the dragon's treasure
is enchanted.
Apart anyone from here.
Is there any way to change him back?
- Not that I know of.
Aunt Alberta will not be pleased.
Sorry about the hand, oh boy.
I can be a little over zealous sometimes.
The boats are ready, sire.
- We can not leave him.
Well, we can't bring him on board, Your Majesty.
You and others take one boat back.
The rest of us stay here until morning.
and work out what to do.
- But you have no provisions.
And no means of staying warm, My Majesty
And you were saying?
I've never seen these constellation before.
Me neither.
We are long way from home.
When I was a boy I used to imagine sailing
to the end of the world.
To find my father there.
Maybe you are.
I miss my mommy.
I miss mine too.
Don't worry, you'll see her again.
How do you know?
- You just have to have faith about these things.
Aslan will help us.
But Aslan could have stop her from being taken.
We'll find her, I promise.
Somehow.
Trouble sleeping?
Now now, all is not lost as it seems.
I'll stay up with you if you wish.
To keep you company.
You didn't even believe in dragons this morning.
You know, extraordinary things
only happen to extraordinary people.
Maybe it's a sign!
That you've got an extraordinary destiny
Something greater than you could have imagine.
I can tell you one or two of my adventures
if you like, just past the time.
Believe it or not, you are not the
first dragon I've encountered.
Many years ago,
too many that I care to imagine.
I was with a band of pirates
and I met another dragon.
Much fierce than you.
Lucy, wake up.
Look.
The Blue Star.
Everybody up.
- What?
It is the blue star.
- Wake up.
Pull.
Put your strokes in there, lads!
Pull!
The wind has left.
So how do we get to Ramandu Island now then?
My guess is something doesn't want us to get there.
Pull.
If I'm getting hungrier,
I'm gonna eat that dragon!
Don't worry, Eustace, they will
to deal with me first.
If we don't get to landfall by tonight,
they might as well eat them...
What are we hitting?
Eustace, that's brilliant!
En route!
We can't be sure that the other Lords even
made it to Ramandu's Island.
You got us there! What did I tell you?
Eustace, you're extraordinary!
Wait.
Lord Revilian.
Lord Mavramorn.
Lord Argoz.
He's breathing!
So are they.
They're under the spell.
It's the food!
Hey, it's the stone knife.
This is Aslan's table!
The swords.
Let me take it.
That's six.
We're missing one.
Look!
Travellers of Narnia
Welcome.
Arise!
Do you look hungry?
- Who are you?
I am Lilliandil.
Daughter of Ramandu.
I am your guide.
You're a star.
You're most beautiful.
If it is a distraction for you, I can
change forms.
- No.
Please.
The food is for you.
There is enough for everyone
that welcome to Aslan's table.
Always. Help yourselves.
Wait.
What happened to them?
These poor men were half mad
by the time they reached our shores.
They threatened each other with violence.
Violence is forbidden at the table of Aslan.
So they were sent to sleep.
- Will they ever awake?
When all is put right.
Come. There is little time.
The Magician Coriakin told you
of Dark Island?
Yes.
For long the evil will be unstoppable.
Coriakin said, to break the spell,
we need the seventh sword on the Aslan's table.
He speaks the truth.
- But we found only six.
Do you know where the seventh is?
In there.
You will need great courage.
Now, don't waste your time.
How we meet again?
Goodbye.
So what do you think it's in there?
Our worst nightmares.
Our darkest wishes.
Pure evil.
Tavros, unlock the armory
Archers, prepare yourselves.
Dock the lanterns.
Let's get ready.
When I grow up,
I want to be just like you.
When you grow up,
you should be just like you.
If case we don't get through,
whatever this is...
I want you to know I think of you as my brother.
Me too.
You gave up your sword.
It was not mine to keep.
Use this.
But it is...
- Peter would like you to have it.
Here it is, my friend.
The battle awaits.
Eustace, no. Wait.
Stop.
I will not accept surrender.
A true warrior does not flight out of fear.
Look at me when I'm talking to you.
I'm a mouse.
You a dragon.
You have a skin of leather.
You breathe fire.
Come on, let's meet our destiny.
No matter what happens here.
every soul standing before me, has earned a
place on the Dawn Treader.
Together we traveled far.
Together, we have faced diversity.
Together...
we can do it again.
So now is not the time to fall in fears and
temptations. Be strong!
Never give in.
Our world, our Narnian lives
depend on it.
Think of the lost souls
we are here to save.
Think of Aslan.
Think of Narnia.
- For Narnia!
For Narnia!
Helene?
We can't see a thing.
The fog is too thick.
You're a great disappointment
to me.
You call yourself my son?
And act like a king.
Edmund.
Come with me.
Be my king.
I let you rule.
- Go away.
You're dead.
- You can never kill me.
I will always be alive
in your mind, silly boy.
No!
- Edmund?
Are you alright?
Keep away!
- Who's there?
Will we not fear you!
- Not, are you?
Keep away!
- We do not leave.
You will not defeat me.
Caspian, the sword!
Lord Rhoop.
You cannot own me!
- Stand down.
Let's get him onboard, quickly!
Be calm my Lord.
- Off me, demons!
We're not here to hurt you.
I am your king.
Caspian.
My Lord.
You should not have come.
There is no way out of here.
Quickly turn this ship about
before it is too late.
We have the sword.
Let's go!
Let's turn this ship around.
Do not think.
Do not let it know your fears,
or it will become them!
Oh no.
- Edmund.
What did you just think of?
- I'm sorry.
What is that?
It's too late!
Get on the boat
Come, walk.
Don't let me down.
No fear. No retreats.
For Narnia! Take that.
And that.
Eustace, hang on!
I'll kill it.
- No, the sword!
Eustace!
Come back.
- We are doomed. Doomed!
Turn this ship about.
- Stop him.
Rowers.
To your rowing position.
Forward at double speed.
- Aslan, please help us.
Pull.
Pull!
Where are you?
You must stay here until someone comes and
get you!
Ed! We run the serpent, smash him on the rocks.
Stay on the port, I will keep it on the ground.
Look out!
Pull!
Try to kill me, come on!
Come on here.
No!
- Edmund.
I'm still here.
Brace yourselves!
Move!
We can beat this.
We must get closer.
- Everybody to the main deck.
Get ready.
I want everyone here.
Ready...
now!
Put his head down!
Heave!
What are you trying to prove, Edmund?
That you are a man?
Do it!
I can make you that.
I can make you my king.
Just take my hand.
Just give it here.
Do it!
Come on!
No!
The spell, it has lifted.
Edmund, Caspian, Look!
Narnians!
Mommy!
- Helene.
Mommy.
Let's have them onboard, clear the decks.
We did it, i knew we would.
It wasn't just us.
- You mean?
I'm here, Lucy.
Here, Lucy.
I'm in the water.
I am a boy again.
A boy!
Eustace! I see your wings have been clipped.
Where sky and water meet.
Where the waves grow ever sweet.
It's sweet!
Look.
Aslan's country.
We must have be close.
Well, we've come so far.
So what was it like?
When Aslan changed you back?
No matter how hard i tried,
I just couldn't do it myself.
Then he came towards me.
It was sort of hurt, but...
It was good pay.
Like when you pull a sword from your foot.
Being a dragon wasn't all bad.
I mean I was a better dragon
than a boy, really.
I'm so sorry for being such a sob(?).
It's okay Eustace.
You were a pretty good dragon.
My friends, we've arrived
Aslan.
Welcome, children.
You have done well.
Very well indeed.
You have come far.
Now your journey is at it's end.
Is this your country?
- No, my country lies beyond.
Is my father in your country?
- You can only find that out on yourself, my son.
But you should know that if you continue,
there is no return.
You not going?
Can't imagine my father would be very proud that I
gave up what he died for.
I spent too long wanting what have been taken from me
but not what was given.
I was given a kingdom.
People.
I promise to be a better king.
- You already are.
Children.
I think perhaps it's time we went home actually then?
I thought you loved it here?
- I do!
But I love home
and our family as well!
They need us.
Your eminence, ever since i can remember, I've
dreamt of seeing your country
I have had many great adventures in this world,
but nothing has dampen that yearning.
I know I'm hardly worthy,
but with your permission...
I'd lay down my sword for the joy of seeing
your country.
With my own eyes.
My country was made for noble hearts such as yours.
No matter how small that can be.
Your majesty.
- Nobody deserves it more.
It's true.
May I?
- Well, I suppose...just this..
Goodbye, Lucy.
Don't cry.
I don't understand.
When will I see you again?
What a magnificent puzzle you are.
And a true hero.
It has been my honor to fight beside such
a brave warrior.
And a great friend.
I won't be needing this.
This is our last time here, isn't it?
- Yes.
You have grown up, my dear one.
Just like Peter and Susan.
- Will you visit us in our world?
I shall be watching you always.
How?
- In your world...
I have another name.
You must learn to know me by it.
That was the very reason you were brought
to Narnia.
That by knowing me here for a little,
You'll know me better there.
Will we meet again?
Yes, dear one. One day.
You are closest to me I have as family.
And that includes you, Eustace.
Thank you.
Will I come back?
Narnia may yet of need of you.
Eustace! What are you doing up there?
Jill drops in for a visit.
We spoke often of Narnia in the days that follow.
And when all my cousins have left.
After the war ended...
I missed them with all my heart.
As I know all Narnians will miss them
Till the end of time.