Where are we?
I don't know
Can't see anything.
Radio doesn't either work.
I said it looks familiar but, I...
I never been inside the cloud before.
What's the last sight you saw?
Same was what I didn't see it.
Spend like this all night,
as long freaking fog vague in history.
It's kinda that long
Moving past than we are...
what are you doing like? Two?
You know, I have listened to
you snored for like an hour.
Now, you give me grieve.
You wanna drive?
No, no, no...
Believe me,
if there'd a crippled old lady
passed in
her son's handicapped scooter,
when you ride with her...
I bet she must go faster than us.
Jesus Christ!!!!
Shit!
Holy shit!
That is not a way the fog to leave.
He couId kill somebody.
I think we are up on the sidewalk.
Oh, man.
Oh, crap.
You get out, give it some push.
I can't see anything.
WeIcome to my world.
There is somebody out there.
Then ask direction. Jesus Christ!
Gibbs, you're like a little girl.
C'mon!
You're like a girl
God damn it.
Push.
Ok! Try to get the other way!
Excuse me. Excuse me! Excuse me! Hey!
That was fucked up!
Hooke, what are you doing?
They are going somewhere.
I wanna find out where we are.
Wait, Hold up! You know what,
I will grab the bags. Hooke!
Hey, you ever see the movie while
pirates traveling around in the fog?
Can't believe you watch that crap.
It was the mother fucked protect you up!
It is shit.
There're zombies with swords!
They jump out the fog
and they stab on your face and they...
And the parrot goes through your eyes,
and is like David Jones'
lock in the puzzle.
Oh! It's amazing.
It's like cinema. You know,
just moves you. God, it's great!
That's your education really paid off.
Your parent muse be
very proud of you. Gibbs.
It's really good movie.
Sure.
Zombies with swords.
Ten for it.
What do you think?
I don't know.
Something doesn't feeI right.
But I don't think we have a choice.
Well you know, beast wouId shit out
and wander around in the fog.
All right, let's give it a shot!
We were crashed to the far clears!
I don't think we couId
find a wine and the soup.
But if it's a hot little maid,
Gibbs calls dips.
Yeah! Ok, this is uh...
I don't really know what it is.
Just glad I'm not an animal.
What the hell is this place!
Mercy.
This town.
Well, we didn't see any sign so...
We...have a game tomorrow,
we're playing a festival.
Yap, if we couId get out of this fog.
Oh, yeah! The fog.
I take the chance.
FeeIs one room for the night.
Rooms. Rooms if you have any.
Sure. We just happened to
have couple of rooms.
Ya, it's a shock.
If you sign the book.
Here you go. Boys! Eleven, tweIve.
Excuse me.
I need you both to sign the book.
Okay.
Let me give you a credit card for this.
That's all right.
We will take care that charge later.
Okay
Uh, is it too late to get something eat?
Yeah.
Sorry.
I wasn't hungry anyway.
Hey, that fucker looks like in the fog.
It's gotta cute.
Let's go, brother.
Yap, your eleven.
Hooke.
Ok. We need it some locked.
Man. You are pathetic.
What! It's wide open.
Anybody couId be hidding in here.
Gibbs, you get a room with a view.
Sweet.
Maybe you couId call out
for that hot little maid.
Hey, Hooke.
You want me to go with you?
Check your room out.
If I see anything spooky, I'll scream.
It's night light there, if you need it.
Good night, buddy.
Sure, you got that secured room.
It's very funny, man.
Really mature.
That's classic.
Do I know you?
Remember me.
I know you?
What?
It's me. You told me
to wake you up at six am.
Hold on.
Good morning.
Morning
Look like you are in the fog.
I got it 'cause...
I just had a crazy dream, Man.
You know, the fog bullshit is back,
so I'm not going anywhere with that.
Well, it will be like soon so...
Let's go. Let's burn off.
Whatever.
You know, why don't we...
uh get a bit to eat
before you get it lost again.
No, no way. I don't want to be late.
C'mon.
All that costs to the room.
All right.
Let's go. Make it quick, all right.
This room can use that
miracle home makeover, dude.
Gibbs, check it out.
Nice.
They haven't used it in years.
Maybe they shouId, get little cold.
I guess we sit.
That was not set.
That was weird.
A little weird.
What's up the kids
cleaning this dinning room.
You don't want to have
whatever tasted dusty for the breakfast.
Dinner.
You said breakfast.
Yeah, that's sort of way me
and my friend like to do it.
We like it save dinner
till the end of the day.
It is the end.
What!
It's six fifteen, in the evening.
There is no way.
We..we just checked in last night.
That must be late last night.
Or early in the morning?
No, no, no, no...
There is no way
we slept for twenty four hours.
Man, we miss our geek!
He must need it a rest.
I'm Peter Rose. This is my wife, Diane.
Mike Gibbs.
John Hooke.
Hey...There's a Hook
in the Ohio. H-o-o-k
Na, I don't think so.
That's an E
in the end of mine, H-o-o-k-e.
Hey, let's get out here.
Let's grasp some to eat on the road.
What's the rush?
We already blow it.
We might as well stay for a dinner.
That's some fog out there, huh?
I like the fog.
Just looks like it's day
down at any time soon neither.
But, we don't mind.
Our first vacation in the years.
My boss just has to get by
without me for a day or two.
That's ok with me.
She reminds me of somebody.
Whatever.
So, how about you?
You here on business or pleasure, huh?
I'm just passing through.
Oh... really?
And for us.
We got here this afternoon, I guess.
Oh, thank goodness we found this place.
It's crazy out there.
CouIdn't see a damn thing in the fog!
Haha...Yeah, too bad.
Good evening, everyone.
I think Benedict cooked himseIf tonight.
This looks so delicious.
Oh yeah.
I have got the wine.
Wine.
Fill it up on top, Mark.
He is such cheap with wine.
I haven't had brusseIs sprouts in years.
He loves brusseIs sprouts.
Don't we all?
Excuse me, is there anyway
I can take a look at menu?
Sorry, we are working on it,
but tonight this is the menu.
Great. Thanks.
Well, enjoy your dinner.
What's wrong?
I don't like raw meat.
Mean I can eat this?
All right.
Is there anybody know there is
a coffee shop around here or anywhere?
Is it the best food
that you've ever eaten in your life?
My God! I'm stuffed.
Can I get a coffee, please?
Coffee?
You don't want to
have a coffee after all that food.
Actually, I...
We don't have coffee!
Looks like they lick the plates clean.
As usual.
I'm so bored.
I know, baby.
He asked for coffee.
If we are stuck here for one night?
Fucked that! Let's go.
What about the fog?
I will give it a shit!
We'll find a way out of here. Let's go!
Listen, when you get back to the city,
you shouId ...shouId call me, okay?
21349555..you can emaiI me, totally!
What about the bill?
We send him a check.
Did I give you the keys?
Shit!
Here we go! Here we go!
Keys! keys!
Gibbs, you don't have them?
No! You were driving!
I must have left them in the car.
All right, I am gonna look.
Okay. Keep me informed.
shit!
He asked for coffee.
Why did he ask for a coffee?
Did he eat his meal?
Every bit.
And he drank the wine.
Not a drop left.
Don't worry.
Are all your arranges made tonight?
Yes, like always.
You can screw up, I'm not, okay?
C'mon. You know how he gets.
You have a second thought.
You know what you wouId
get into, my killer on board.
We can't leave here untiI...
I know! But what if it doesn't happen?
She is right. We couId die here.
That's enough. We're so close.
OnIy weeks away,
we get stronger everyday.
We will succeed. We must.
I need more ashes.
Let's take care of it.
You know,
He is with you.
I'm with you, father.
Yeah.
The baby needs to eat.
You know what we wouId do
to you for the sake of the baby.
Why make yourseIf miserable?
Eat!
Wait.
You find some coffee?
Hey listen, did you eat tonight?
No.
Good.
Remember if you ever want to
get out of this place, no meat, no wine!
Hey! Sleeping beauty.
Now, where you go?
Gibbs! Gibbs!
Gibbs!
Did you hear something?
You are in Iuck.
We do have one room available.
That's great, I guess.
We just have to find
a place for the night, honeymoon.
Oh, yeah. I'm so glad
that Sharon picked you up.
You know, we love honeymoon this year.
How often have you
been stuck in this fog?
Lots of firsts, if you know what I mean.
Scott!
What!
If you just sign the book.
I need you both to sign.
Here you go.
Thanks.
Let's go, honey. I'm cold.
Well, you both get warmed up there.
I don't like this place.
Uh, it's onIy for one night.
Some honeymoon.
You know what they said,
lousy honeymoon,
Great memory.
Is that what they said?
It's the good thing they came tonight.
We couId have taken one of the others.
Spend all these time
buiIding in the Mamati ash.
You know what I need yet?
In his seek it's just weak.
I've never slept
with a married woman before.
Me neither.
You know what I mean?
Yeah.
What's that?
I don't know.
Oh, man. This is too weird!
What's going on?
I have no idea.
Maybe we shouId complain.
What are you doing?
This is nuts!
I will take care of it.
Don't answer, for the Christ's sakes.
Go away!
Wow! Baby. Well done.
I wanna go! I wanna go right now!
Okay. Okay. Okay. I will get my stuff.
Jesus Christ, man!
What the fucked is up with you?
What the hell have you been?
Looking for you.
We gotta go now.
Oh, you found keys?
I found a car, we gonna hot wired.
We are?
Roy, heIp me.
No...
Where are we?
I don't know.
I say it looks familiar, but I...
I never been inside the cloud before.
Now I got ever heard that one.
That's okay.
This is right for that place.
Whatever.
What are we doing? Like two?
Hey, broke the record! You wanna drive?
No, no, no, no.
What if a crippled old ladies
passed in
her son's handicapped scooter,
you let me know.
I will ride with her.
She couId go faster than us.
Jesus. What the fuck!
Shit!
Fuck!
Gibbs, we are not going anywhere.
What do you think?
I don't believe this.
Beast wouId shit out
and wander around in the fog.
We gotta get a phone.
All right, if there is
a hot little maid, Gibbs calls dips!
Yeah. Ok!
This is uh...
I don't really know what this is.
Glad I'm not an animal.
WeIcome to Mercy.
Sir!
Sir, we really need a car,
a tow truck, ok?
Well, the phone line is been down.
Suggested, maybe they
will be working tomorrow.
I guess you want a room.
If you just sign the book.
Here you go.
Eleven. TweIve.
Appreciate if you both sign.
Hey guys, we get a nice home
cooked breakfast in the dinning hall.
Can't miss it.
Straight around the back.
Yeah. We know where it is.
At least we didn't miss
the breakfast before the bed.
Good morning.
We get out of here. Fog, there's no fog.
You know what?
Let's eat breakfast first.
Then we worry about
getting out of here part.
Dinner.
Excuse me.
You said breakfast.
Yeah. That's..
that's sort of way me
and my friend like to do it.
We like to save dinner
till the end of a day.
It is the end.
I told you.
It's six fifteen.
In the evening.
It's so weird.
We couIdn't dream all day.
That's what I'm trying to tell you.
Man, we miss our geek.
Yes, we miss our geek.
It was yesterday.
I'm Peter Rose. It's my wife, Diane.
Mike Gibbs.
And this is my friend. John Hooke.
Wow! Any Russian Hook from Ohio?
No, there's not.
You already asked me that.
Remember? Last night.
I have an E in the end of mine.
You remember that?
Jesus! This is insane. Let's go, man.
What's the rush?
I suppose to stay for the dinner.
There are some fogs out there, uh?
I like the fog.
Roy, where did two of you last night?
No, just me.
That looks like
settle down anytime either.
But... we don't mind.
Let me guess.
First vacation in years, right?
How did you know?
And your boss he can't get by it,
another day or two without you.
I was just going to say that.
I never ....So, how about you?
What brings you here?
Business or pleasure?
I'm just passing through.
Same with us.
We just got here last night.
Wait, where is the Mrs?
You don't remember, uh?
You can't see anything
in this damned fog, right?
That's exactIy what I just about to say.
That's amazing.
It's a bit weird.
You're something.
Good evening, everyone.
I think Benedict cooked himseIf tonight.
I got the wine.
Well.
Enjoy your dinner.
Let's begin.
Where is he? Where is Scott?
Scott?
It's my husband.
We went to our room
and with all this chanting.
I know something terrible was happened.
You shouId sit down
and have some dinner.
I'm not hungry.
Have some wine, sweety.
It will calm your nerves.
Don't, no. Don't...
I think I'm hungry after all.
What about Scott?
Who?
I haven't had a brusseIs sprouts...
In years?
Years, right?
And your husband he
loves brusseIs sprouts, doesn't he?
Yeah. He does love brusseIs sprouts.
Don't you people remember?
You don't remember
the introduction and small talk,
the roast beef, the fucking sprouts?
You don't remember?
We did this
exactIy same thing last night.
You guys don't remember?
Roy! Where is your wife?
Susan!
She is right there.
That's not his wife! For Christ's sakes!
You don't remember?
How couId you not remember?
Jesus!
Where is Ramon?
He had to fetch more.
Sorry.
Perhaps you forgot what's the stake.
We need the trinity.
I said I'm sorry.
Bless the ash.
Create the healthy chiId
and we all will be free.
Create the chiId.
Look at her.
Another weak link,
just like the others.
And choose to spit out
and not to use any longer fresh,
if she does miss the carry first.
Patience.
That's we get stronger,
so do the babies.
Well, not one of them
must fight for more than couple days.
This page will be different.
Look at this healthy chiId.
Before the ninth?
We are running out the time.
She is not cooperating.
Some of them won't eat
meat or drink the wine.
We can't risk taking the chiId.
This one is very close.
Then what? Another dead one for sharing?
Or maybe this time we wouId be Iucky
and we wouId onIy have
two arms and two legs.
You took this on.
You made the choice years ago.
You wouIdn't given us this job
if you didn't think we can do it.
Of course.
You're right.
September ninth is so close.
And finally
we can leave here for eternity.
That's better.
There're so much to look forward to.
Please let me out.
Please.
You can't just keep me here forever.
People will miss me.
She's almost too.
I can't wait to be doing with this.
I won't tell anybody. I promise.
I will give you anything.
Just please let me and my baby out.
Just becoming so tedious.
Becoming!
I've got some loveIy wine.
I just can't wait for her to try it.
No, please don't go.
Please! Please!
Shut up!
How did you know that I just want you?
All that chilling really gets you going.
You want some more?
I'm done.
So you're checking out
the new starter over here?
He was cute.
Cute and tasty.
Like a baby bird.
You're jealous?
Right.
I'm jealous.
Next time, he comes
and bring one of the other girls.
I'm getting bored.
Bored my ass.
It's me.
What the hell you think you're
doing out here in this town at night?
You want to get yourseIf killed?
We need to talk.
Now.
I see you're starting to remember.
There is something about it.
That's right, honey.
You worked for that band.
Jack!
Good!
The ash is running off.
Ash?
What are you talking about?
Take it easy.
You don't get something
from nothing around here.
Tell me.
You got promised to get me out of here.
I promise.
Then you tell me
what the hell is going on.
What is this place?
Benedict, Elizabeth and Armon,
They are witches. They kill people.
They killed your friend.
Gibbs?
Not Gibbs.
He has eating and drinking
and having great all times.
I can't.
Remember.
I know.
There was a man.
Some man with the beard.
Jack?
He is dead.
Jack is dead?
They killed all the ones first.
No stand with it now.
What about the rest of us?
Right now, that's not important.
The important thing is to get out.
I tried!
I can't fucking leave here!
I can't leave. Why can't I leave here?
Because you signed the book.
Once you signed the book, that's it.
It's like you signed your life away.
They want you eat and drink,
the ash just makes it easy.
The ash is in the food and drink?
It's like some kind of mind control.
The ash just make you forget.
But not me. Why?
Because I made damn sure
your food is clean. That's why.
When you saw this...
Shit!
He takes the drugs on us.
The food and the wine.
Thanks for my screw-up liver.
No wine for Jacky boy.
You have to make this
all kind sounds a little bit crazy?
When do we get here?
According to you it's..
No, when do you remember
getting here?
Yesterday
Okay, what's the day that date?
It's Thursday.
October twenty-third.
Thursday.
I took this from the couple
that showed up yesterday.
Whenever, whenever.
Roy and Susan something or other?
October, right?
Read the date.
ApriI fourth.
Two thousand nine.
We have been here for six months?
I think time is altered.
Maybe a day here is a week
outside or a month. I don't know!
How did you know we haven't
figured this out all before?
We don't know.
Well! That's just fucking great!
That's great.
We shouId remember now.
Oh my god!
How do we get out of here?
That nasty old van,
you know Charon the driver?
Don't even think about taking that van.
Charon's the onIy one
can get to the portal.
Even Benedict,
the others either cannot, untiI...
UntiI when?
That's enough.
You just get back
like everyone eIse.
Don't let on that your memory is
coming back or eIse we were both dead.
Wait!
How do I know I can trust you?
I worship God.
HeIp me.
How did you find me?
Do I know you?
I will be back.
I promise.
No...
Elizabeth wants to see you.
Sure. Baby.
Now!
You better save some to me.
I will think about it.
Lucky you.
Hooke.
Please. Please no.
The betrayal shouId be
divided in the penalty.
I don't know what you mean.
We live to serve you.
Please! Father.
No...
Gibbs! Gibbs! Open up.
Good evening.
Gibbs!
There you are. Come!
You're not gonna believe this.
But we slept the entire day.
You know it's six pm.
I know.
What do you mean you know?
I know it's fucking dark outside,
I know!
He must got late last night
Or really early in the morning.
I have enough for this.
Anybody eIse hungry?
Gibbs.
Good evening, everyone.
I think Benedict cooked himseIf tonight.
I get the wine.
Let's not keep our guests waiting.
It's fog out there, right?
Yeah, I bet it won't run off.
I may take this bit soup
when I was driving in yesterday.
Roy, he is sales man.
He knows his parts very well.
This is Peter and Diane.
This is Nora.
Oh, this is my friend. John Hooke.
Hook, there's a
Russian Hook from Ohio. H.o.o.k
No, I don't think so.
I can't believe this.
I love brusseIs sprouts.
Really?
This looks so delicious.
You are not in a mood for meat tonight?
No, I am.
You're kidding me.
I love this, love this.
Gorgeous.
Well, enjoy everyone.
You don't like it?
I have it.
Listen to me.
You didn't believe me before.
You gotta believe me now.
Jesus Christ! Stop!
Cut it out. Man!
Listen to me.
It doesn't have to happen.
We can get out of here.
We've done this for hundreds of times!
We gona...
Gibbs! Jack. Don't you remeber...
Gibbs! Jesus Christ!
You gotta remember!
Gibbs, you gotta come
with me now. Now!
Now!
Fuck!
I will make this really easy for you.
You give me the keys. You leave.
You don't remember, do you?
No, you don't remember.
You will never leave here.
No one wouId make me pass the portal.
Why is that?
It's magic. Baby.
No one but me can leave Mercy.
Not untiI...
Untill... till to when?
UntiI the chiId was born.
Those cages!
Those women!
Those women are breeding!
The babies were born
and dead wouId be done.
You rapped them!
Not me! That will be your job.
Oh my god.
What have I done?
What did you do to them?
You wouId never leave here alive.
Not you. Not your friends.
Not your girlfriend.
What girlfriend!
You can't remember?
Which one of these.
Give me the keys.
That's too late.
Time has come.
The chiId will be born.
Where the keys?
Fucking keys!
Shit!
Kim.
You came back.
Kim, I remember you.
Holy god.
The other day, I wasn't sure.
How long has it been since?
I don't know.
Judging by the size of me seven,
maybe eight months.
I didn't even know you are gone.
It wasn't you, Hooke.
You remember?
No meat, no wine, not knowing
why you're pregnant.
I think this ash will hurt the baby.
We gotta get you out of here.
There is a key in the stand by the door.
I miss you.
What about the others?
Gibbs and Jack?
Jack is dead.
God! This is so eviI!
No, we wouId never get out of here!
We just come back and
I can't go back to that cage!
I can't...
Listen. Listen.
We can get out of here, all right?
Everyone. You, me, Gibbs.
We can get out of here
but you need to be strong, understand?
Going somewhere?
I can smell your
when you get in the door.
Get out of my way, lady.
You solve the riddle
and maybe I will let you go.
What will the world look like
at night, night all night.
I don't give a shit!
I'll give you a hand.
It's not real!
None of this is real!
C'mon! We go.
Wait! Wait! We can't just
leave these women like this.
Get out of here. Let's go.
Good Iuck.
What about the others?
Believe me, I tried.
There's nothing
we can do for them now.
I gotta get you out of here.
It's better work.
Do you know where we are going?
I have no idea.
I know there is a portal.
There is onIy way out.
A portal?
Yeah. It's a long story.
What was that?
Previous owner.
Did you see that?
Yeah... that's the portal,
that's the right. Hang on baby.
We did it.
How can I forget how much I love you?
You made that.
You and me, and...
You don't think that is..
Son of the deviI?
I don't know.
It sounds pretty witch shit.
But I know the drug does.
So, what do we do now on me?
Please don't leave us.
No, nobody will.
Wait here.
Just get in.
Look.
What are you doing?
No...you are not going back there.
Kim, I have to.
No! We just got out of there.
What if the chances you
won't make it back out?
What if you forgot again?
Never forget.
You can't just leave me like this.
Listen! He's going
and driving there, okay?
When you get there, wait!
When I come back,
we will get you to the hospital.
We will get you to the hospital.
Everything is going to be ok.
You and the baby.
Promise me.
I promise.
I love you.
All right, Go. Go.
Man, I hope this works.
C'mon, baby! C'mon.
C'mon. C'mon.
Double the dose ash.
You think it's the right time?
Are you questioning me?
One woman is missing.
The other is
scattering around the grounds.
We need to retake control.
Nothing will happen to the babies.
Don't worry.
Coward has no way to go.
Ashes, the chiId.
Ladies and gentlemen,
I think Benedict cooked himseIf tonight.
Where is..
You're looking for someone?
Where is Gibbs?
Who is Gibbs?
I don't know anybody's name Gibbs.
Yes, you do.
You all do.
You flirt with him every night.
You all know him.
Peter! Think.
Do I know you?
Yes, you know me.
You and Diane know me real well.
Sweety, we've never met before.
Peter! C'mon. Think. Spend the vacation.
God knows how you and your shit hole!
But you know boss can't...
get by without me?
How long have we been here?
He is obviousIy confused.
Don't listen to him.
What's going on here?
Yea, who are you?
Roy! How long have you been here?
I came in here yesterday, Sir.
Hey, you can cut the sir crap!
I'm Hooke.
With an E. Any relationship with Ohio.
How many god damn times
you say that one?
You are overwheImed.
Sit, have a glass of wine.
It will make you feeI better.
You sit down. Sit!
He comes here alone, Roy?
Yes, we did.
Is that right, sister?
Answer me!
No.
No, is the name
Susan ring the bell, Roy?
Susan?
It's your wife, Roy.
Look that newspaper you have been read.
How many times you read that?
It's four months old.
I don't understand.
Oh my god! Susi...
Yeah, that's right.
Now, where is Gibbs?
I don't know what you are talking about.
Where is Gibbs?
You didn't think you can run for mess
with that consequence, did you?
Clean these plates. All but one.
But...
Do it!
Or I will kill her right here,
right now.
Do it.
So ladies and gentlemen,
looks like our host is going to
join us for dinner for once.
I can't eat that.
Why, it's delicious, right?
Benedict did that himseIf, didn't he?
You don't understand.
I'm not like you.
We will find out.
Eat.
No.
Eat!
Eat it!
Benedict!
Elizabeth!
I eat in the ash.
You ate something.
She is dying. Do something.
She eats the ash. Nothing I can do.
They're gonna remember.
It doesn't matter, they can't stop this!
Where is Susan?
Oh my god!
Scott!
I came here with my mom.
Where is my mom?
What's happening to her?
We can't do it without her.
The trinity is broken.
It's quite failed for the cover.
And it will make him a hero
and they will give him all the glory!
No one wouId get the shit,
for the eternity!
Get control of yourseIf.
We are not finished.
Not when we get this close.
Find Charon. Karin and her nurse
will take care of the guests.
Get to the office. We will keep back.
No...no...no.. I'm not leaving you.
Get out here, we will find you.
No. I am staying with you.
Please.
Peter, the table! Let's go.
No, no. Get out of him.
Leave him alone.
Oh my god, Peter.
Oh, shit!
Gibbs.
Hooke? Nora?
It's me, Nora.
Where is Hooke?
I thought he was with you.
Oh my god! Oh my god!
We are gonna die
just like all the others.
No, we are not.
We gonna find Hooke.
Hooke, Hooke.
Thank god! We found you.
I thought you were dead too.
We get out of here, now,
all right? C'mon.
Shit!
Keys! Keys...
Oh! Fuck!
Fuck me!
Fuck!
Fuck! No. Come on!
You have no idea what you've done.
You never got finished now.
No driver. No key.
Damn it to hell.
This not what I signed that book!
We got out, you know.
Right through the portal.
Then you must have the key!
Just give him the key for God's sake.
That's right.
For God's sake.
OK.
All right!
There you go.
This is the way out. This is key.
Van! Get to the van!
Keys!
It's over.
You have no idea.
This is just the beginning.
You don't need us anymore.
Just let us go.
What I need is the chiId. I need it now.
Push!
Is everything ok?
Everything is fine.
Congratulations.
You have a very healthy baby.
A girl?
A beautifuI girl.
See, I told you so
everything has gone right
Hello.
Here is mommy.
Are you sure anything
is going to be okay?
Yeah. I'm certain. It's new beginning.
Yeah. I'm certain. It's newbegginning.