Wlth the passage of the
Freedom of Observatlon act,
a new and mlghty weapon In the war
on terror was placed In our hands.
The flrst major step
mandated under the new law
was to unlte the vast array of separate
publlc and prlvate survelllance cameras
throughout our natlon
Into a slngle network-
the Optlcal Defense
Intelllgence Network,
- named O D I N.
O D I N monltors every form of
domestlc electronlc communlcatlon
for crlmlnal actlvlty.
The most vlslble and hlghly
successful addltlon to our eye llne
has been the Introductlon
of a powerful new set
of state-of-the-art moblle
robotlc survelllance cameras
known as Eyeborgs.
Lord, glve me eyes
that I mlght see.
That's better.
What Is he up to?
Terrorlst bastard.
Yeah, I'm
looklng at you.
Excellent.
Cool.
Look,
I got something.
Something big.
Only-I don't
know what it is.
Show me.
What Is
thls, now?
Show me what
they've got.
Clear left
and zoom.
It's somethlng new
they're developlng.
It's something
we've never seen before.
We dld It.
Come on.
We lost the slgnal.
Should we move In?
Negative. Hold positions.
We got company.
Shells?
Yeah.
Now, I wonder
how it got in here.
What?
Wait a minute.
Hey, you don't think that I brought
I think
- you just got careless.
Damn it.
Move in, move in.
Go, go, go.
Go around back.
Here we go.
Key on us.
Find him.
All rlght, llttle frlend.
Show me what happened here.
You were so hot
on stage tonlght.
I just
love your band.
What's it
called again?
Painful Daze.
Right, Painful Daze.
Brandon, you're
an awesome slnger,
and out of all those
glrls, you plcked me.
Well, you seem...
Special.
So, you got
the stuff?
Oh, God, oh, God.
Relax, it's
a friend.
G- Man.
Who's she?
She's cool. So you got the stuff?
You know what
you got to do.
I- I know. I'll
break it good.
Enjoy your stuff.
What was that?
J ust forget
about it, okay?
Is that what
I thlnk It Is?
As promised.
Genulne homegrown...
North Carolina tobacco.
Oh, my God.
I haven't
had a clgarette
slnce the government
made smoklng lllegal.
God, you taste
llke an ash tray.
You too.
That is so hot.
What was that?
Shh.
Okay, Marsha.
All right. If Brandon
calls you or anything,
just let me know, and I'll
do the same, all right?
Okay, thanks.
Nothing. He disappeared with that
chick after the show last night.
Nobody knows where he is.
Palnful Daze,
you're up.
Okay. Well, Jarett, I
hope you know the lyrics,
because you just became
lead singer of the band.
What lyrics? Nobody knows the lyrics.
It's just a bunch
of incoherent screaming.
Thank you, guys, so very much.
You guys have been awesome.
Get ready to go balls to
the walls with Painful Daze.
Sldeshow 321 Alpha
through 411 Charlle.
No subs,
all sectlons.
Don't worry, man.
Hey, we'll find him.
We'll find him.
I just wish
we knew his target.
H i.
U m, hey.
We're Palnful Daze,
llke It says
on the drum.
Okay, let's,
um-rock.
Subject vehlcle,
I D posltlve.
LB 5059 reportlng.
Sectlon C-47.
Full up.
He must be Inslde.
Pin down C-47.
Get me some eyes
inside that club.
Negatlve. Not
wlthout a warrant I
Bureaucracy.
Search warrant approved.
Send them in.
# And he knows
what to do #
# But people hear
thls Is true #
# No matter what they do
They just stlll get through #
# Tlme and tlme agaln #
That's Sankur.
That's our man.
Let's let the Eyeborgs flush him out.
Attentlon, everyone.
A Department
of Homeland Securlty
emergency defense
operatlon Is In progress.
Everyone please remaln calm and
follow all Instructlons as glven.
Once agaln, a Department
of Homeland Securlty
emergency defense operatlon
Is In progress.
Everyone please remaln calm and
follow all Instructlons as glven.
Whoa!
Everyone please remaln where you are.
D H S, put the gun
on the ground!
Back off.
Step away from
the girl, Sankur.
Don't make this harder than it is.
On the ground, now.
Now.
You can't stop me.
Away. Move,
move, move.
Stay away! Stay
where you are!
I mean it.
Take hlm down.
I'm dolng
thls for you.
Put your guns down.
Thls Is for everyone.
J im, suppression
fire only.
We need hlm allve, Jlm.
We need hlm allve.
Suppression fire only.
Suppresslon flre only.
Suppression fire
only. Go, go!
Ah.
Go, go, go.
Move out!
Suppresslon flre only.
Suppresslon flre only I
Stay down.
We've got
to stop them.
What was that?
What?
What are you doing?
We needed him alive.
Well, you got your target.
It's this punk kid over here.
Wake up, Amerlcal
The president is lying.
Are you hurt?
No, I don't think so.
Where is the truth?
They're watchlng us.
They're watching
us all.
They're watchlng
us all I
You're a lucky
son of a bitch.
That little Eyeborg
just saved your life.
Oh, God.
I've got a gig.
You're lucky
to be alive.
Any idea why this guy would
be taking a shot at you?
No, I don't know.
What's your name?
U h, Jarett.
I'm with
Painful Daze.
Jarett. Last
name, Jarett?
Hewes.
H- U-G-
No. H-E-W-E-S.
You mean like-
Yeah.
Next you're gonna
tell me you're related.
He's my uncle.
You serlously want
me to belleve
that the president of the U
nited States is your uncle?
Hey, he's serlous.
You do have a gig,
playlng for the presldent of
the U nlted States next week.
Yeah.
Well, he's
a good man.
He'll get
my vote again.
Yeah. Yeah,
yeah, me too.
Hey, llsten, you thlnk we could
just not tell anybody about thls?
I got enough nut jobs
coming after me as it is.
Yeah. Our job
is keeping you safe.
Keep the family
relations quiet.
Okay, thank you.
Yeah, well, we know where to find you.
Ronnl?
You don't suppose hlm belng the presldent's
nephew has anythlng to do wlth thls?
Gunner.
Donut run.
Gunner, Gunner.
Agent Reynolds.
Yeah. Ms. Hoppy,
isn't it?
Barbara Hawkins. What
happened here this evening?
Nothing. It's
all over.
We heard reports of gunshots
from this establishment.
Yeah, there
were gunshots.
And why was that?
Because guns
were being fired.
Was there a reason,
or are you and your men
just the sort to enjoy shootlng
off thelr loads whlle people watch?
Not if you're filming
it. Good night, Ms. Harpy.
Hawkins.
J ust in the
nick of too late.
You know, they have machines that'll
do your job now, minus the lip.
We're off.
To make the news.
You just
got careless.
I didn't do it.
Are you saying I can't trust
what I see with my own eyes?
You're not seeing it
with your own eyes.
You're seeing it
with thelr eyes.
All right. Let's talk
about last night.
The kid. You were
trying to kill him.
Why?
The kld Is
a stepplng stone.
To the president?
He's not
the president.
He was never elected
into office.
Funny, I thought
we had an election.
Not an election,
a coup!
Computerized voting.
No paper trail.
The exit
polls showed him
tralllng the whole day,
and then some computer
announces he's
our new presldent?
Oh, this guy
looks like
the love child of Charles
Manson and Karl Marx. Ew.
He doesn't look like a Marx brother.
Oh, cute.
Their guy wins,
it's democracy.
Our guy wins,
it's a coup.
Actually, I voted
for the other guy.
Really?
U h-huh.
Me, too.
Oh.
You want
some coffee?
And the only way
we can take America back
is to kill
Benjamin Hewes.
President won't be in
town for another two weeks.
And you knew you dldn't have two weeks,
so you went
after the kid.
You're just putting nails
in freedom's coffin.
My job is to protect freedom
and the people of this nation
from those that would do them harm.
I n that case, we're on the same side.
What say we go after that
son of a bitch Hewes together?
You realize you're
facing federal charges.
U nder the Freedom
of Observatlon Act,
it is a government offense
to tamper with, disable,
or otherwise
interfere with
the operatlon of an
offlclal observatlon devlce,
which basically
means you're screwed,
'cause you're going to pay
for that Eyeborg you shot.
Now, take some time and
come up with some names
by the time
I get back.
How about Kyle?
And Sharon?
Damn shame what happened
to your family.
I am sorry about that.
I'm sure you are.
But if it wasn't for
what happened to them,
we wouldn't have Eyeborgs
to scrape out scum like you.
Don't let that freak get to you.
He's not.
Go figure.
Well, ain't you
a cute little thing.
Oh, there he Is.
Agent Reynolds.
Ms. Hawkins, what are you doing here?
I'm trying to get a straight answer
about what happened last night.
I have no comment.
Oh, thank you,
thank you, thank you.
Wait.
Decaf.
There was a shooting last
night at a public facility.
Turn that camera off. No,
don't turn the camera off.
You have no right to film in this
building. I do, I am in the lobby.
Turn that camera off
or I'll shoot you.
- He can't shoot you.
- I will shoot you.
He is allowed
to be in the lobby.
Everybody wants to be a
comedian. What's that all about?
Hey, drink up. First they ban
cigarettes. This will be next.
H uh?
Obviously, you're
hiding something.
- I'm not hiding anything.
- No! Turn that back on!
Hey, hey.
Oh, God. No, no, no, no. U h-uh.
Security breach. All sections initiate
lock-down procedures immediately.
I nltlate lockdown
procedures Immedlately.
J ust stay here!
Thls Is not a drlll.
Oh!
Ashley, talk
to me.
The subject is headed
toward the south hall.
Damn.
Toward the west lobby.
East stairwell, now.
East stairwell.
Yeah, he's in
the west lobby.
There he is.
U p there.
Now in the
north stairwell.
Come on,
go, go, go.
Got you.
Ah!
I need you to override the
emergency lock-down on level six.
Overriding the lock-down
on level six.
Come on.
Agent Warner,
are you in yet?
Hang on.
Let's go.
Override lock-down,
level seven.
Abort lock-down.
Come on.
No! No!
D H S agents are uncertaln
how a suspect who was In the
process of belng Interrogated
managed to escape from the
room and commlt sulclde,
but an Investlgatlon
Is under way.
Jack.
Horrlble turn of
events, Barbara.
Absolutely horrlble.
Thank you, Barbara.
I n other news,
Presldent Benjamln Hewes...
My uncle's politics take a turn
to fucking derangement land,
and people want
to take it out on me.
I mean, I haven't even seen
him since I was a little kid.
I don't even know him anymore, you know?
I wouldn't vote for the son
of a bitch, and we're related.
Jarett, at least
you're still alive.
I mean, God knows I never
thought I'd say this.
As much as those Eyeborg
things creep me out,
you would be dead
if it weren't for them.
Tsk.
M m.
Look, I am sure the
guitar man can fix her up.
Yeah, well, if G
- Man can't, no one can.
I could use
a little fixing, too.
H m!
Yeah?
Oh, look.
It's your uncle.
As presldent, there Is
nothlng more Important
than protectlng the people.
Great. Now he's cutting
into my sex life, too.
That Is why I supported the
Freedom of Observatlon Act.
Now, wlth my new law,
every camera
In the natlon,
as well as mllllons
of moblle unlts,
have been llnked
dlrectly Into O D I N.
Man, millions
of mobile units.
...a network that never
sleeps, never rests,
and never stops
looklng out for you.
Yesterday, the
State Department
Issued yet another
terror alert,
thls tlme cltlng the
natlon of Zlmbeklstan.
What? Zimbekistan?
Are they your next
target, M r. Presldent?
How many more natlons wlll we Invade
before you're
satlsfled we're safe?
The flnal debate
wlll be held next week,
wlth our own Wlnston Salem playlng host
to the presldent's
contlngent. Jamle Kell reports.
Jlll, I'm standlng outslde
the Mlllennlum Center,
from whlch the presldent's slde
of the debate wlll be broadcast.
I'm gonna
be there.
I cannot belleve
you convlnced me
to play
thls fundralser.
Oh, stop whining.
He is desperate
for the younger vote,
and you
need the gig.
J ust take advantage of it
and invite some fans along.
Yeah, right.
He won't even let me bring the band.
He only speaks In front of
Invlted, supportlng crowds,
for security reasons.
As wlth
prevlous debates,
the candldates are In
dlfferent locatlons
to create a less centrallzed
target for terrorlsts.
What are you doing?
Do you remember that wedding
gig you did last month?
The two ladies
who got married.
No, the other one.
Oh, the forelgn guy?
There has deflnltely
been a bank error.
Come and
check it out.
Only Indlvlduals especlally
Invlted by the presldent
are permltted Inslde
the debate hall.
Obvlously he
llked us.
Obviously a computer hair-balled up
a decimal point in the wrong place.
I mean, I'll have
the bank fix it,
but do you remember that terror
alert on the news, about Zimbekistan?
Yeah?
Well, that's where all
this money came from.
What?
Yeah.
Oh, shit!
Ronni, the last thing I need
is for the government to think
that I'm in some kind of
business with terrorists.
I mean, If U ncle B's opponents get ahold
of that, thls could be really serlous.
I know, I know, I will
have it fixed by tomorrow.
Look, who
never fails you?
My Ronni.
That's right.
Don't ever forget it.
I'm glad you
failed once.
Yeah, me too.
Or I'd have
never met you.
You know the most romantlc
thlng you ever sald to me?
U m, put on this collar
and bark like a dog?
No, but that was dope.
The flrst
tlme we talked-
M m-hm?
Jarett, just shut up
and fuck me already.
U h, yeah, that was it.
No, no, play it again.
That's not what happened.
I locked that door.
I keyed in
the codes.
I got the
red light.
Not according
to O D I N.
Database confirms
what the cameras show.
You keyed the
unlock code twice.
Then the
database is wrong.
Are you postal?
There's nothing wrong
with the database.
You keyed the
wrong codes.
Video shows it, and
computer records confirm it.
It's wrong.
I locked that door.
What are you saying? I can't trust
what I can see with my own eyes?
J im, you were there. What happened?
I'm sorry,
I didn't see it.
What do you mean,
you didn't see?
You were standing
next to me.
You were upset.
You've keyed those
codes a thousand times.
This time, you
made a mistake.
And that's how I'm
writing it up, all right?
E. O. F.
Play it again.
George! George, you can't do
an end of file on this one.
Because?
Because Sankur was trying
to kill the president.
What if he wasn't
working alone?
No one was
working with Sankur.
How do we know that?
Because the head
office said so.
They've had this fruit
basket flagged and monitored
ever since he checked out The Anarchist's
Cookbook from the local library.
He was a lone nut.
Now he's a dead nut.
Well, at least let Bradley
and I check out his apartment.
Jesus, Gunner!
We might find-
Don't you get it?
You've got good friends in high places,
probably because your testimony
helped get the Eyeborg system on-line.
Aw, come on! Don't
pull that on me, George!
But push
this too far-
and someone may press
charges for negligence.
Don't let one mistake
ruin a great career.
I'm not ordering you
as a supervisor.
I'm telling
you as a friend.
Let it go!
What kind of a tenant was Sankur?
He was very,
very quiet,
and he was
very strange.
They always are.
Oh, am I gonna
be on television?
Maybe.
Oh.
These doors
kind of stick.
Oh, there we go.
Thank you. We won't be long.
Oh, take your time.
You know, I'm a fan of yours.
Oh, thank you.
Bye.
Thank you.
Bye bye.
Whoa.
Suddenly the clutter In my
apartment doesn't seem that bad.
Gunner said they were done here, but it
doesn't look like anybody's been in here!
There's got to be
something really good here.
Ho, ho, ho.
Here's something good.
M r. Deller's, it's
been such a long time.
How are you doing?
Eric, don't even
look at this.
I've got it
under control.
It's like running
into your ex-wife.
Glad to be rid of her, but
there were some good times.
Come on, Eric, give it
- You take this and I'll take this.
Pry it loose. Pry it
loose. Pry it loose.
Okay.
Oh!
Look at this, look
at this, look at this.
What?
This is the kid,
the punk rocker that Sankur
attacked the other nlght.
He's related
to the presldent.
He's related to the president.
That's what Gunner was hiding!
Yeah, probably worried
you'd report it.
And risk losing
my reporter's license?
I don't thlnk so.
Do you think he's hiding something else?
Yeah, he did seem
a little tense.
A llttle tense? He
threatened to shoot me.
Wait a minute, wait a minute. Sankur
claimed this D H S footage wasn't real.
Is it possible that this is fake?
Sure. I mean,
computers these days-
Anybody can make
a computer composite.
But to make It reallstlc-looklng
and rendered In real tlme?
Now you're talklng some
serlous processlng power.
Would you check it out for me, please?
Worth a bottle
of Deller's?
No, it's not.
I'm kidding, I'm kidding, I'm kidding.
Of course I'll do it
for you, Barbara.
Come on I
We're offl
Off to make
the news, baby.
# I can't belleve It #
# The way you
Look sometlmes #
# Llke a trampled flag
On a clty street #
# Oh, yeah #
# 'Cause I'm a 21 st
Century dlgltal boy #
# I don't know how to llve,
But I got a lot of toys #
# My daddy's a lazy
Mlddle-class Intellectual #
# My mommy's on Vallum
So Ineffectual #
# 21 st century boy #
# Scream for more #
# Aln't llfe
A mystery, yeah ##
Hello, G-Man? G-Man?
You're supposed to stay open
tlll 5.:00. Where are you?
G- Man?
El hombre de guitar.
Wlnd blows
open my door,
and who floats in
on the breeze?
None other than the nephew
of the almlghty hlmself.
Come on,
G, not again.
Stlll a llttle touchy about belng
related to the bastard-In-chlef, huh?
You really wanna talk politics to
a guy with purple hair? Seriously?
How's It hanglng, J?
It's good. You?
Eh, long and llmp, but
at least I can walk on It.
Now what graces you
to my doorstep?
Check it out.
Let me guess
- Brandon bounclng around on stage agaln?
U h, no. Brandon's,
llke, mlsslng.
What?
He disappeared with some chick
after the H igh Point show.
Well, if not
him, then who?
A freaking
Lie-borg did this?
Hey, It saved
my llfe, man.
Really, I'm serious. I
know you don't like them.
Don't like them? That's
an understatement.
Look, I can count seven or elght of
them damn thlngs, rlght from here,
and every one of them
photon-sucklng spy-bots-
Wired directly to
your uncle's office.
Yeah, I'm actually pretty
sure the O D I N mainframe
is not sitting
in the Oval Office.
M ight as well be.
We, the people, sure don't
run this country anymore.
Looks llke my uncle wants me to
play thls fundralser next week.
Never figured the
C- in-C for a headbanger.
Thlnk you can
get her done?
Patience, kid, patience.
I love the extremeness
of your life, man.
As long as those Eyeborgs are around.
Dude, they're
just cameras.
An E B saved your
life, didn't it?
Yes. By taklng a pretty plcture of you?
No. By gettlng between me and a bullet.
Wow. Pretty smart move for
a camera, don't you think?
Ah.
Here. Read thls.
"The Freedom
of Observatlon Act?"
Are you kidding me? Did
you actually read all this?
More than the stupid senators
and congressmen that passed it.
Check out page 742.
" I n the absence of any formal
law enforcement authority,
"a unit may act as needed
to obstruct a perpetrator
In the commlsslon
of a crlme. "
So yeah, If a terrorlst Is
about to blow up a bulldlng,
and there's no cops around to stop It,
then an Eyeborg
can stop it.
Exactly.
What is wrong
with that?
What's wrong with it?
Yeah.
It's not limited to just
terrorists blowing up buildings.
What If an Eyeborg catches
you dolng somethlng wrong,
and no one's around
to stop it?
It can do
whatever it wants.
They're just
security cameras.
What if it's
not just a camera?
What if somebody
puts a weapon in it?
Think about it.
Robot soldlers
Inflltratlng soclety,
seeklng out enemles
of the government.
This is America.
Thlngs llke that
can't just happen.
Man, you really had me golng there
wlth all that consplracy crap.
It's not crap.
I was there
when they first used robot
soldiers to kill people in GW2.
I'm telling you-
Eyeborgs keep
us safe.
"Those who choose safety over
freedom deserve neither. "
Benny Franklin, 1776.
Those who would play for the
president need a working guitar.
Jarett, 5: 27.
I'll get her all pretty
for you. Don't worry.
All right.
Hey, thanks, bro.
See you.
Oh, God, look out.
My God, he's got a gun.
Ha. What
do you know?
M m.
Eric, hey,
what's up?
I did what
you asked.
I went over Sankur's
homicide video,
and guess what I found?
What?
Plxel blendlng.
What does that mean?
If you create a 3-D
object In a computer,
you can render It wlth 2-D,
but If the angle's too steep,
you get artifacts.
The only way to get
somethlng llke that perfect
Is to have a 3-D scan
of the person.
Wlthout that, there's always
some flaw to glve It away.
I n Sankur's clothing,
there's an area
where It looks llke- You
guessed It- Plxel blendlng.
So does that mean the
video could be fake?
That's what I just sald.
Oh, I knew somethlng was up.
Beam It over to me rlght now.
U m, this system's
not networked.
What, are you In the Stone Age?
It keeps from gettlng vlruses,
all rlght? Hold on. Okay.
Look, I got the chip in hand. I'll come
over and show you what I'm talking about.
That's even better. I'm gonna be
home in ten minutes. Go right now. Go.
What is this?
Barbara, I was
just kidding.
Jeez, you want
to get me fired?
Get off of me!
Let me go!
Let go of me.
What are
you dolng?
you doing?
Ahh!
Ahhh!
Yeah, whoo!
Now that's how you
make the news, baby.
Thank you.
You have
been "dis-armed", baby.
Damn.
Hell's a'popping.
See what you can find out.
I'm sorry.
No, I'm okay.
I'm okay.
We D Led Eric
leaving the station.
And these are from
the trafflc camera.
Eyewltness sald he nearly kllled
her when he ran a red llght.
He was all over the road,
completely out of control.
Were you aware that Eric had
a history of alcohol abuse?
Yes, but he was always so definite
that his drinking was in the past.
Why did you call us?
This was a traffic accident.
What made you thlnk
It was a D H S matter?
This is going to sound
a little crazy now,
but I had Erlc analyze
the Sankur homlclde vldeo.
Why?
Sankur sald the vldeo wasn't real,
and Eric's a video expert,
so I had him analy ze it.
He said it looked fake.
He was coming to show me.
Report from
the forenslc guy.
Sounds a lot less plausible
coming from a drunk.
But he didn't sound drunk.
Computer analysis.
Shows he had almost
a full bottle today.
I'm sorry.
But he
didn't sound drunk.
Coffee?
So how'd you
find me here?
My little
friend showed me.
Oh, yeah. I keep forgetting you
are the father of the Eyeborgs.
That's not
my favorite title.
It's just that everybody knows
that if it weren't for you,
the O D I N system would never
have gone beyond the testlng stage.
That's because I testified in
front of the senate committee,
and you reported
how I felt.
Look, Gunner, I had a story to do,
and it was about
how you felt.
You weren't just another law
enforcement officer bucking for a tool.
Your story- What
happened to your family-
That is what
moved people.
I just wanted to catch the bastard
that killed my wife and took my son.
I know. And you got
the Eyeborgs instead.
Yeah, and a very nice note
from the vice president,
thanklng me for my
support on hls pet project.
Look, how close were you with Eric?
He was like a little brother.
He was a pest sometimes,
but I don't know what I'm
going to do without him.
If he was drinking again, do you
think he would have hidden it from you?
Like you hiding that the kid who was attacked
the other night was the president's nephew?
You are on a need to know basis.
I couldn't have
his identity compromised
by puttlng hls
name on the alr.
Do you know
what this is?
A journalist's license.
When the government
started requiring
that journalists be licensed,
most of my colleagues quit,
but I stayed.
Do you know why?
Because my husband was
killed in the last attacks,
and I swore I'd do
whatever I could
to prevent anyone from havlng
to feel that klnd of paln.
Other reporters
called me a traltor,
but I believe
in what I did,
so don't treat me like
I can't be trusted.
Are you certain that Eric
was right about the video?
Absolutely. I
am posltlve.
Because if you report
what I'm about to tell you,
we could both be brought
up on Patriot Act charges.
Well then, I guess it's all
about trust, then, isn't it?
I must be
loslng my mlnd.
Flne. There
are thlngs-
Small thlngs,
but a lot of them.
...Vetoed pendlng leglslatlon,
prohlbltlng
domestlc deployment,
saylng wlth the ever-changlng
nature of the terrorlst threat,
It Is vltal to keep
all optlons open.
Earller thls afternoon,
Vlce Presldent Rutledge
Introduced the latest
In a developlng llne
of mllltary
klller robot soldlers.
Bastard.
These robot soldlers,
whlch are belng
deployed today,
are deslgned to protect
our men and women overseas
and our chlldren at home.
Why dld the presldent
veto a blll
deslgned to prohlblt
domestlc deployment?
Terrorlsm knows no borders.
Now, the presldent and I
are gonna be explorlng
every optlon avallable
to make sure that we protect
all the cltlzens of thls country.
Go.
You got to
stop the project.
Is your line encrypted?
It doesn't matter.
They know.
Where are you?
Look, I don't think
I have much time.
You-you got to
cancel the project.
Davld, calm down.
It's rlgged
and ready.
Well, unrig it.
U nrig it now!
David?
The president.
The Eyeborgs.
I know the truth.
What truth?
God help us all.
They're here.
Nol
Robot rats.
Come on, try to get a plece
of me, you slllcon psychosl
You little
binary bastards.
Llttle dlgltal dlngoes.
Ahh I
Ahh!
Hey, G-Man.
Hey, G,
You in there, man?
Hey, G, it's Jarett.
Hey, hey, hey.
Help, help, help.
Help. Hey, hey, hey.
Help, help. Help. Help.
Help. Hey. Whoa.
G- Man! G-Man!
Oh, God.
G- Man. I
need an ambulance.
I'm in Liberty and Trade
Street behind M idtown Guitar.
Don't tell me
to calm down I
Want to go
over the part agaln
about what you
saw In the alley?
I saw an Eyeborg rushlng
out, and It attacked me.
Eyeborgs aren't allowed on
private property without a warrant.
I know that.
There's no warrant
Issued for thls property,
so there's no way there
was an Eyeborg Inslde.
Video surveillance
in the alley.
No, no,
that's not rlght.
No, It wasn't a man.
It was an Eyeborg.
It was one of those, it was
one of the big spidery ones.
Yeah, but
I see a man.
But you're not seeing
through your eyes.
You're seelng
wlth thelr eyes.
I saw what I saw.
What are you dolng?
Are you golng nuts?
I'd like to know if my partner's going
nuts before you get us both killed.
I don't know, J im.
J ust cut me
some slack.
I'm working
on something.
Is that the guitar
G- Man repaired?
Yeah. G-Man
was the best.
Can I take her?
Sure. It's
not evldence.
Try to stay
out of trouble.
I just want to go home
and be wlth my glrl.
Guilty conscience
there, partner?
Is thls a joke?
Come on.
Come on, son. I'll
buy you some ice cream.
My momma warned me
about guys like you.
Thank you,
I ris. Ahhh.
Isn't thls fabulous?
Sure you don't want some?
It's freedom vanilla.
What's the
deal, man?
Am I under arrest here?
I mean, every time
something bad happens-
I thought this would be
a safe place to talk.
And now
G- man is dead.
I thought thls would
relax you a llttle blt,
because you seem to be
very tense most of the time.
Now, of course, I'm eating
freedom vanilla ice cream
in an exotic car wash
with a D H S officer.
I believe you saw an
Eyeborg the other night.
Thank you.
I can't be certain, but I think
someone hacked into the O D I N system
and Is controlllng them.
Focus!
What?
Yeah, no, I know.
I thought there were-
I think someone's trying
to kill the president.
H uh? Are you
kidding me?
No, I'm not.
Someone-
Someone has compromised
our surveillance system.
Like who?
Like terrorists.
Ooh, terrorists.
I'm so scared.
The government made the Eyeborgs,
they control the Eyeborgs,
but if something goes wrong,
it's never the government's fault.
There's a traitor somewhere, somewhere
probably high up in government office.
Maybe even Inslde
the D H S.
What do you want me
to do about it?
I need you to contact the presldent.
You have found the wrong guy for that.
We're talking about
his life here.
I can't do that.
Why not? You're the only one
that can go dlrectly to hlm.
- They won't believe me.
- Why not?
They won't believe me. Look,
there is an entire branch
of government that's set up to
protect him. You don't need me.
Listen, son.
Whether you want to be involved
in this or not, you are.
Now, you, the president, and anyone
connected to you could be in serious danger.
We don't know anyone
In Zlmbeklstan.
So what you're telling me
Is that thls money came from
the government of Zlmbeklstan,
and not a
prlvate Indlvldual?
Well, you or somebody
higher up than you
is gonna get this money
back to Zimbekistan
if we have to be here till
Gulf War 7 breaks out. Capisce?
All right, I expect to hear from
you within the hour. Thank you.
Get-
Get-get out.
Get out.
Shoo. Get out!
You're not supposed
to be in here.
Fine. If you won't
get out, I will.
Call Jarett. Call-
Call Jarett.
I'm sorry, command
not understood.
Call-Jarett!
Hey, baby, you will never guess what-
Jarett, help.
What?
Ronni? Hello, hello?
Can you see me?
Jarett, help.
Yeah, you're breaking up.
I can't really see you.
What's going on?
Are you all right?
Ronni?
Ronni, I'm on my way.
I'm on my way
home rlght now, okay?
Hang tlght.
Ronnl?
Shit.
Jarett!
Ronni? Ronni?
Ronni? Hey, Ronni?
Ronni?
Ronni, are you in there?
No, no, no, Ronni.
Ronni! Ronni!
No!
Please, Ronni. Ronni.
Ronni.
They're calllng
It a sulclde
because she had a
history, but I told them
what I thought I saw on the phone-
An Eyeborg- When she called me.
And what did the police
say when you said that?
There was no record
that she called.
Dld you speak
to your uncle?
No, I trled. I can't get ahold of hlm.
He's coming here tomorrow. I
need you to make that meeting.
No, no. I
can't. I can't.
I can't do that.
Jarett, I know this is
really hard on you,
but think about
what happened to Ronni,
what almost
happened to you.
Your uncle could be
in extreme danger.
Well, that's not my problem. That's not.
No. That's not my
fucking problem.
You have no idea what you're
asking me to do here, okay?
I never, I never
talk to my family.
I mean, I am so far over on
the other fucking side of this-
And there's
no way-
I'm not.
No. I'm-
Jarett Hewes?
Yeah?
Please hold for
the presldent.
It's him.
Jerry?
U ncle Benjamin.
I heard about
what happened,
and I am so sorry.
Is there anythlng
I can do to help?
No, thank you.
U m, it's just...
I
- I need to tell you something. I need to talk to you about the Eyeborgs.
Walt just a mlnute.
Wlll you excuse
us, please?
Now, Jarett, llsten
very carefully to me.
Thls Is not a secure llne, and I'm
not In a posltlon to talk rlght now.
But It Is very Important that you
not mentlon thls to anyone else.
J ust promlse me you'll
be there tomorrow nlght,
and we can sort thls out face to face.
I really don't know
if I can be there.
Jarett, please.
At least let me see you
after what's happened.
Okay.
Okay, I'll
be there.
I'll see you
tomorrow, then.
Okay, bye.
He sounded concerned.
It doesn't seem like you're
on the other side, does it?
Okay. Okay. I will play that fundraiser.
It's what Ronnl
wanted me to do.
But if I'm going to walk in there
and try to convince the president
that security cameras
are killing people,
I need some
real proof.
I'll get you
the proof.
You just be there.
Okay.
Let's go.
Llve from 44 H D
electlon central,
thls Is campalgn coverage
of Declslon Amerlca,
wlth Jack Romero,
Jlll Coppola,
Barbara Hawklns, Jamle Kell,
and the Eyewltness News Team.
Good afternoon to you.
I'm Jack Romero.
And I'm Jlll Coppola.
Comlng to you llve from our
state-of-the-art electlon central newsroom.
Today, Eyewltness News' contlnulng
coverage of Declslon Amerlca,
and the final presidential
debate of this election.
We begin our coverage with
Barbara Hawkins at the debate site.
Barbara?
Thank you, Jlll.
The day of the debate
has flnally arrlved
In Wlnston-Salem at the
beautlful Mlllennlum Center.
The presldent's llmo
arrlved moments ago,
and we've been Informed
that he was escorted Inslde,
where a crowd
of Invlted supporters
awalts hlm
behlnd closed doors.
Oh.
This is a great
idea you had,
checking out what's
his face's shop.
G- Man.
I know what happened
here. I saw the movie.
Well, now you can
read the book.
Ha ha ha.
That's funny.
Take a look at that.
What do you suppose
made this?
Look, I know what I saw in the video.
Well, let's take
a look inside.
Although only supporters
are allowed near the presldent
for securlty reasons,
there are, In fact,
many protesters
demonstratlng agalnst
hls pollcles here today.
For safety, such dlssenters are
kept far away from the presldent
In tlghtly regulated
flrst amendment zones.
Thank you, Barbara.
You ever thlnk about
how easy the Eyeborgs make It
to get convictions?
If you mean having video of a crime
as compelling evidence, then yeah.
It's hard to
argue with video.
Exactly. No
cross examination.
Was there anything
on the computers?
Nothing. Our guys went over
it from the last bit and pixel.
Someone that doesn't
trust machines
wouldn't put anything
in there.
He'd be doing things
the old-fashioned way.
You heard It here-
The presldent says
he understands and agrees
that we are way In
over our heads flnanclally,
yet he contlnues to perpetuate
the problem by contlnulng
to put more money Into a
system whlch Is controlllng us,
and my goal
Is to cut that out.
What are
you dolng?
It's hollow.
What?
There Is one word
that the senator llkes
to use a lot
wlth reference to O D I N,
and that's control.
There's a very blg dlfference
between observatlon and control.
Here. That's
it. Come here.
...the O D I N system.
And from conceptlon
Into development,
Into manufacturlng,
Into Implementatlon,
many, many jobs
have been created.
Good afternoon, M r. Hewes.
Take that, please?
I thlnk to the tune of over slx
mllllon jobs have been created,
and ladles and gentlemen, every one of
those jobs Is wlthln the U nlted States.
We have greatly Increased
the gross natlonal product,
and Increased the tax base and the
revenues of the federal government.
It pays for Itself,
ladles and gentlemen.
D H S to Secret Service,
Headliner has entered the building.
What's this?
Look at these deslgns.
Weapons on the Eyeborgs?
They must be fake.
She's not lax at all,
and we both know that.
We just dlsagree.
We slmply dlsagree.
Hello?
We all know how I feel about It,
and I'm hoplng one day, she'll
reveal how she feels about It,
and what she wants
to do Instead.
I want to make one
thlng perfectly clear,
and that Is I agree wlth the presldent.
I belleve that we should be protected.
I belleve that we do need securlty.
However, there Is
a very thln llne
between belng protected
and an Invaslon of prlvacy.
God.
What's this?
Looks like C-4.
It's more like
a C-4 variant.
It's odorless
and malleable.
This could get past the
scanners without a problem.
There's no scent. The
snlffers would mlss It.
G- Man had to get it
near the president. How?
We are not watchlng
the Amerlcan people.
These are cameras and moblle
unlts. They are not human.
They are observlng
and recordlng behavlor.
There are many levels, and the
flrst level Is behavlor number one.
N umber one Is slmply
normal human behavlor.
There's no threat.
There's no red flag.
When a moblle unlt
or a camera
sees behavlor that Indlcates posslble
crlmlnal actlvlty Is In the works,
It goes to level two. Stlll, no
human eye Is on the human belng.
I can't get a signal down here.
Come on, we've got to warn them.
Let's go.
Jlm, be careful.
What? Maybe they can
help us get a signal.
Guys, we need for you to get us-
J im.
No.
J im?
Damn.
Come on, Ed.
Gunner, what the hell
happened to you?
J im Bradley's dead.
How?
The Eyeborgs have
been compromised.
How can the Eyeborgs
be compromised?
And that's not
our only problem.
Jarett Hewes,
the president's nephew,
has a bomb hidden
in his guitar.
The kid's already
in the building.
We'll secure
the perlmeter.
You take a team in and get
the president out of there.
Yes, sir.
Sanchez, get your
team together.
Let's not hurt the kid. He
doesn't know he's been set up.
What's going on?
What happened?
Terrorists have control
of the Eyeborgs,
and Jarett's guitar is rigged
to assassinate the president.
That's not funny.
No, you're right.
It's not.
Round them up.
Move them out.
What's the situation?
The debates are
still going on
but we can't contact
anyone on the radio.
Our first priority is
to get the president out.
U nderstood.
Let's go, commander.
Yup. Sanchez?
D H S, Secret
Servlce. Stand down.
Where are
the president's guards?
I don't know. They should be here.
We're taking the president off-stage,
then we get him out of the building.
Gunner, wait. Let's get a
twenty on that kid first.
Coyle, take a team.
I want you to sweep the bulldlng.
Sanchez, I want you to do
a perlmeter wlth a team,
and I want
the bomb squad-
Gunner, Gunner.
It's not real.
Oh, Lord.
He's not real.
What's going on?
Where's the president?
There is no president.
What?
I don't understand.
Did terrorists-
There are no terrorists. No terrorists,
no election, no president,
no more democracy.
O D I N has
been using us.
That's why we Invade one
country after another-
So it can breed.
You're recording
this, right?
J ust keep recordlng
and sending it
to the station.
Where's Barbara's feed?
It must be some
klnd of a problem
wlth the robot camera we gave her.
Have you called her?
There was no answer,
but there's nothlng for her
to do untll the debate's over.
I suppose.
Well, no more.
Not on my watch.
I want that boy
out of here.
Ed, can you hear me?
Right here, right here.
What do
we do now?
Hlgh, low. On two.
One, two.
Ladies and gentlemen,
this is unbelievable.
There Is no presldent,
no room of
Invlted supporters.
We've got to get Jarett and
that bomb out of this building.
O D I N wlll go
to any extreme,
even kill our own
American heroes,
to keep It secret.
Cover.
No one knows
how long thls-
Barbara.
What are you doing here? You all right?
I can't move my legs.
We'll get you
out of here.
No, no, have you found Jarett yet?
He's somewhere in the
building. I don't know where.
The basement. They've
got him in the old jail.
How do you know?
I've done a mllllon
storles on thls place.
It used to be the old federal building.
We've got to
get past them.
No, there's another way.
See that slot up there?
It's part of the old
survelllance tunnels.
They connect every room
In the bulldlng.
Oh. There's a door
behlnd that curtaln.
You just get in there.
You can get to the
basement and get Jarett out.
Sanchez, send a bravo
team. Go with Gunner.
Go.
Leave me the nine mil,
another clip, and I'll be fine.
Don't do
anything stupid.
We'll get you
on the way out.
Go, go,
go, go, go.
Where is Barbara?
We have gunshot flre from
wlthln the Mlllennlum Center.
Communications have been
compromised. Let's go quietly.
Oh!
Team, gol
I'm here.
Help, help.
Help.
You all rlght?
Oh, my God, what's happening?
Where's U ncle Benjamin?
He's dead.
Probably has
been for years.
But he's
the president.
Not anymore.
What Is thls?
I don't know. Some kind of
3- D scanner or something.
Oh, God.
Ahh. Ahh.
Let's be very careful with this.
Thank you.
Don't thank me. There's a bomb In It.
Go.
Fall back.
What's happening
out there?
As far as we know,
the presldent Is safe.
But we can nelther conflrm
nor deny at thls tlme.
What the hell
are those?
An Eyeborg no human ever designed.
Coyle, what'd they do to you, man?
Jesus.
Come on.
Gunner.
Gunner, take
the guitar.
Get him out.
I got you covered.
No, Sanchez.
Come back, San-
Barbara.
Jarett!
Jarett, son,
come here, son.
Come here.
Look at me,
look at me.
I need you
on your feet.
All right?
You understand?
Okay!
All right,
give me your arm.
Come on.
Come on!
Gunner, what happened
to the others?
Doesn't matter.
We got to go.
Oh, no. Oh, God.
No, you
can't move me.
Yes, I can.
Take Jarett.
I can barely walk.
Come on, we haven't got much time!
No, you take Jarett and take these.
These are the computer
chips from my camera.
They'll have everything
that happened today.
They'll be the last
recorded video.
It's the only proof you'll
have of what happened.
Barbara.
I'm taking you out.
Promise me you'll take these out.
Promise me, Gunner!
Promise me!
Yes.
I promise.
All right, look, you
promise me something-
Whatever comes through
that door, do not move.
They are programmed
to attack. Do not move.
And I will be
back for you.
I know. I know.
I know.
Come on, son. I'm
getting you out of here.
Come on,
look at me.
Look at me. You can do
this. Put your arm around me.
Agaln, I'm not sure If
gunshots have been flred,
or If It's somethlng that sounds
llke gunshots. Standlng by.
Do you know what I've got here?
The delete key.
No.
I, Thomas Rutledge,
do solemnly swear-
That I wlll falth fully execute the
offlce of presldent of the U nlted States-
You are looklng at
hlstory In the maklng-
Footage just released, showlng
the former vlce presldent
In an undlsclosed locatlon
taklng the oath of offlce
and assumlng hls posltlon
as the next U. S. presldent.
Welcome to Eyewltness
News. I'm Jack Romero.
And I'm
Jlll Coppola.
The new commander-In-chlef
wasted no tlme
deploylng a
coordlnated assault
Involvlng army, navy
and alr force troops
agalnst the tlny, oll-produclng
natlon of Zlmbeklstan.
We have Irrefutable proof
that Zlmbeklstan Is Involved
beyond the funds glven
to the traltor Jarett Hewes
for hls Involvement In thls
terrorlst assasslnatlon plot.
Sad to say that we
dare not trust anyone,
not even our
own relatlves.
My admlnlstratlon has
just begun Implementlng
sophlstlcated
securlty provlslons
deslgned to protect you.
Wlth that, God bless you,
and God bless Amerlca.
Sam.
Thanks, man.
See you soon.
What about
that vldeo?
Everybody knows that
vldeos can be faked.
Regardless of the
motlves of people,
they're deslgned
to confused you,
so you must ask yourself, each
and every cltlzen of thls country,
ask yourself one questlon
and one questlon only-
Who do you belleve?
A government that Is
sworn to protect you,
or a ratlngs-hungry
medla beholden to no one?
Dude, thls outflt
so does not work for me.
Eyeborgs use visual
pattern recognition.
Besides, you
look good in it.
Really, man? Here?
I mean, just-
It was either here
or the exotic car wash.
I thought this would be
better for your soul.
H mm. Wanna know
my preference?
Oh, no, I don't.
The world thinks
I'm dead already.
Look, we go
public with this,
and I get out there
In front of cameras-
Trust me, it's been
done with cameras before.
Gunner, I can't just
slt here and do nothlng
whlle people
are out there dylng.
Barbara's-Barbara's video has
gone viral all over the net.
It's spreading like
crazy, going peer-to-peer.
Even O D I N
can't stop it.
So what do we do?
Be patient.
People aren't just accepting
what they hear anymore.
Things are changing.
We have to
stop the machine.
We will.
Have faith, my son.
Thank you, Father.
The Lord gave me my
eyes to see for myself.
I don't need
yours anymore.
# I'm not a bellever
I'm not a detractor #
# I'm don't
Follow the herd guy #
# Lamb to the slaughter #
# I'm a reslstance
The new revolutlon #
# The why generatlon
Electrlc thrlller #
# Here are your eyes #
# Are they burned
Through my mlnd? #
# I can feel
I can breathe It Inslde #
# Freedom's calllng #
# Heroes are falllng #
# We'll flght untll
The clty's burnlng #
# The apocalypse Is dawnlng #
# Freedom's calllng #
# Heroes are falllng #
# I know how much
You llke to watch #
# Watch thls #
Coming up next on Eyewitness News
44 H D, a nation mourns the loss
of its longest-sitting leader
since F D R and recalls his legacy.
All the while, even
under more tight security,
the Vice President is sworn in as
the nation's new commander-in-chief.
Also, U S condemnation of
Zimbekistan for the attack,
and threats of military
retaliation against the tiny nation
in response
to the unprecedented-
No one knows how long
O D I N has perpetrated thls-
And builds
a new coalition
A presldent that's merely
an artlflclal flgurehead.
...nation.
U h, clearly some kind
of technical problem there.
Some kind of
a ghost-like-
We're not quite sure
what that was we just saw.
Perhaps some kind
of practical joke
by somebody with a very
sick sense of humor.
But I'm sure the F C C and this network
will investigate and
prosecute those responsible.
Meantime, we apologize
for the interruption.
We hope you'll stay with us through
the break and into our next program.
Stay tuned, and thank you.
Was that-?
Damndest thing
I've ever seen.
# Here are your eyes #
# Are they burned
Through my mlnd? #
# I can feel
I can breathe It Inslde #
# Freedom's calllng #
# Heroes are falllng #
# We'll flght untll
The clty's burnlng #
# The apocalypse Is dawnlng #
# Freedom's calllng #
# Heroes are falllng #
# I know how much you llke #
# Freedom's calllng #
# Heroes are falllng #
# We'll flght untll
The clty's burnlng #
# The apocalypse Is dawnlng #
# Freedom's calllng #
# Heroes are falllng #
# I know how much
You llke to watch #
# Watch thls ##
What do you belleve?