(wolf howling)
(low growling)
CRASH
BANG! BANG!
(woman screaming)
(woman struggling)
(snarling/growling)
(woman struggles)
AHHHHHHH!
OH!
(snarling/growling)
Leave her alone!
(werewolf growling)
(snarling growling)
(woman screaming)
(girl crying)
(fire crackling)
(gasp)
¶
(Nathan)
Hey, look who's up.
Hey. What are we doing here, Nathan?
I think I took a wrong turn somewhere.
I'm just trying to get a signal
on for the GPS but nothing.
I know the way from here.
We should get going.
Okay, sure.
Whatever.
You had
a good sleep?
(Virginia) Yeah, thank you for driving.
(phone vibrating)
Hey, look at that-
Keswick-
(Nathan on phone) Sorry, I'm
having a hard time hearing,
(Nathan on phone) just
call Agent Walker, okay?
He's handling my cases
while I'm away. Thank you.
I thought you were
gonna turn that thing off.
It's off, it's off.
(Nathan)
Look, I promise-
This weekend is all about
me meeting your family.
No work, no phone.
(Virginia)
No gun.
I don't think my family are
going to be that intimidating.
(Nathan)
Promises, promises...
¶
(Nathan) Wow, this place
is in the middle of nowhere.
(Virginia) The perfect
place to forget our jobs.
(Nathan) Don't worry, my phone
doesn't want to work up here anyway.
Wow!
Now that is a house.
(Nathan) I didn't know I
was marrying into money.
Don't get any ideas.
The house has been in the
family for generations.
It's amazing.
(Gran) Welcome home, Virginia.
(Gran laughing)
You're too skinny.
You say that every time
I've been away for a while.
Because it's true.
(Virginia) Jake! Look at you!
(Jake) Welcome home, Red.
Where's Marcus?
(Gran) Uh, at work.
He'll be home tonight.
You guys I want you
to meet Nathan.
It's a pleasure
to meet you.
(Nathan)
You must be Jake.
Jake will help you
get your bag
show you to your room,
get you settled.
I don't mean to be an
ungracious hostess but
I'd like to spend some private
time with my granddaughter.
Understood.
(Jake) So you're the guy
who's banging my sister huh?
Well, if you knew anything
about your sister
you'd know it's
the other way around.
I heard you
call her 'Red'-
Everybody in the
family call her that?
Yeah, it's, uh, a name
of honor given to
the first born daughter in
each generation of our family.
So it's not because
of the red hair?
(Jake laughing)
No.
Well, what does
it mean?
You'll have to
ask Virginia.
It feels good
to be home.
So nice
to have you here.
Everyone sleeping under
the same roof again.
If only for
a little while.
How's that job?
Keeping my skills
sharp.
Any activity within
the den?
No they're
behaving quietly.
Adhering
to the truce.
That's good.
I need to talk
to you about something.
I wanted to wait until
we were face to face.
I want to tell Nathan
about our family history.
What we do is difficult for
people who were not born into it.
Just as difficult on
those who are.
It's a lot to trust
to someone.
I've never brought anyone
home for you to meet before.
It's important to me
that he knows me.
All of me.
I don't want to lie to him
for the rest of my life.
It'll have to be a
family decision.
Of course.
Virginia-
Are you sure
he's the one?
Well I'm so glad that we
finally get to meet you.
I was starting to think
you guys didn't exist.
I'd like to see my
granddaughter more often.
She just doesn't
want you to know
what we really do
out here.
Hey, remember, you're
talking to two Federal Agents.
So how did
you two meet?
Actually we met
at the academy.
I was sort of, I guess,
top dog for a little while-
And your granddaughter
showed up and kicked my butt.
No, I did not.
(Nathan) Yes, you did, Virginia.
That reminds me, um-
Why do you guys
call her Red?
Yeah, why is that?
(Gran) Why do you want
to marry my granddaughter?
(Virginia) Let's not embarrass him.
That's okay,
that's okay-
Um-
Well, I, uh-
I guess
she challenges me.
(Gran)
You like challenge.
I do.
Dude-
You have no idea.
(Virginia) Okay, I think we
should unpack before dinner.
(Nathan) I just have to run out
to the car quickly for something.
Thank you.
Play nice.
(Virginia) Nathan, you
better not be on the phone!
You have to keep
your mouth shut.
Oh, here we go-
Hey hey hey-
Ga- Ga- Ga-
Gabriel-
Hey! Hey!
Hey!
I'll go get help! Stay with
me and I'll be right back!
Help! Somebody call the police!
Hurry up!
(Nathan)
I don't understand.
(Nathan) What the hell happened?
(Gran)
It's Xavier.
(Nathan) You know who this is?
Yes, did he say anything
to you before you left him?
He said a name-
Gabriel.
(Nathan) Am I the only
one bothered by the fact
that I was just talking to
this guy five minutes ago?
And now he's
basically incinerated?
It's physically impossible for
a human body to burn this fast.
(Nathan)
Finally.
Sheriff-
Agent Keswick, FBI.
That's him?
Yes, Marcus.
This is Nathan.
Am I missing
something here?
(Jake) This is our brother, Marcus.
Jake, get a shovel and
a bag out of the truck.
Let's move this stuff
before anyone else sees.
(Nathan) Whoa, whoa, hey
- There's protocol here.
We gotta get
the medical examiner
to check this out first
before we touch anything.
Virginia, you brought him
here, you deal with him.
I am gonna have
to tell him.
We've been left
with no choice.
Tell me what?
Virginia, what the hell
is going on here?
I need to show you
something.
We have a problem.
Yes, we do.
(Virginia) I need you
to keep an open mind.
My family is not only
involved in law enforcement.
We are also hunters.
Of a sort.
Okay, so you hunt.
What the hell
does that have to do
with the dead guy outside?
It's what we hunt.
Okay, what am I
looking at?
It's what we hunt.
(Nathan) But, but these are...
Werewolves.
Oh, come on.
Gimmie a break.
Nathan!
I just need
some time.
Nathan!
Whoa whoa whoa-
Virginia, let him go.
No. Whoever killed
Xavier is still out there.
He's a big boy he can
take care of himself.
It's not a full moon,
he's gonna be fine.
Let's go. Come on
inside, come on inside.
Come on.
Let's go.
Come on...
(thunder crashes)
(Nathan on phone)
Hello!
Hey, can you hear me?
(Nathan) This is Agent Nathan Keswick.
(Nathan on phone) Can you
hear anything I'm saying?
Son of a bitch-
(trees creaking)
(branches snapping)
Anybody there?
(Nathan)
Hello?
Somebody here?
Are you lost?
(Nathan) Who the hell are you?
And what are you doing out here?
(man) I was just out
here taking a stroll.
(Nathan) A stroll? In the rain?
I prefer to be
out here in nature.
Well, it's not safe. There's
a killer on the loose.
What kind of killer
would that be?
(Nathan) I'm not sure.
Some kind of animal.
Could it have been
a wolf?
What kind of wolf
would rip a man apart?
Something like this.
(snarling/growling)
(man screaming)
(werewolf growling)
(Nathan breathing
heavily)
(werewolf snarling)
(Nathan groaning)
My name is
Gabriel.
(Marcus) You going somewhere?
Nathan's been gone
too long.
We need to go
after him.
With Xavier dead I've got more important
things to worry about than your boyfriend.
Fine,
I'll go alone.
I'll send Jake.
(distant howl)
That's impossible.
It's not a Werewolf.
It's not a full moon.
(Virginia)
I'll go ahead.
(Virginia) Jake, come on! Let's go!
(Jake) Nathan! Nathan!
(Virginia) Nathan!
Nathan, where are you?
(Virginia)
Nathan, answer me!
(Jake)
Red, wait!
Nathan! Nathan, are you alright?
Nathan, get up!
Get up! Get up!
Are you hurt?
Nathan!
Answer me!
Are you hurt?
Everything you said
was true.
It was a werewolf.
Yeah. We followed his
trail directly to you.
You're lucky
to be alive.
He said his name
was Gabriel.
I watched him turn.
How did you get away
from him?
I don't think I did.
(Virginia)
Did he bite you?
No, I don't
think so.
I
- I'm sorry. I have to be sure you weren't bitten.
(Nathan)
And if I was?
You'll transform
and I'll have to kill you.
(Nathan groaning)
(Virginia)
You're bleeding.
What?
Did he bite me?
No,
no you're okay.
He's okay,
he just hit his head.
I'll radio Marcus. Tell
him we found Nathan,
and meet you back
at the house.
(Jake) I'm gonna see if
I can track this thing.
Be careful. We're dealing with
something we've never seen before.
(Virginia)
Here, let's go.
Okay.
Slow, slow-
Come on.
One, two, three-
Okay, I'm okay.
Okay.
(Virginia) You're
okay. Just take it slow.
What's wrong?
Hold on.
You okay?
Stay right here.
(Marcus) I was looking
for you what happened?
Nathan ran into a Werewolf
that can phase at will.
(Gran)
Is he bitten?
No, no,
thank God.
The Wolf's name
was Gabriel.
That must be the wolf
that killed Xavier.
Okay did he have any
special markings?
Did he have any
markings?
I just watched a man
turn into a Werewolf.
That may be a common day occurrence
for you people but not for me.
What the hell's going
on here Virginia?
The dead man, at the
end of the driveway?
He was the leader of one
of the last wolf packs.
Our family had a truce
with him.
As long as they stayed
in the deep woods,
kept themselves locked
away during the full moon-
We agreed not
to hunt them.
Okay, Nathan, what did he
look like in human form?
I don't know.
He's-
Middle aged,
six foot four-
Wait, wait, we're not
dragging him into this.
He's in this.
You brought him into it.
We have a dead pack leader and
a wolf who can phase at will.
(Virginia)
I won't allow it.
You wanna marry this guy, you
want him to understand what you do,
then he needs to see it first
hand, see if he can stomach it.
Let the man make up
his own mind!
The only thing that I
wanna make my mind up about
is going upstairs
and getting some sleep.
(Marcus) This is all insane.
I'm impressed that he survived a
werewolf in the first encounter.
Few people do that.
Maybe he is cut out to
be part of this family.
Or maybe somebody
wanted him to survive.
(slow breaths)
(Marcus)
Where's Nathan?
Still in bed.
Exhausted.
These perimeters are
clear. I think we should-
(Jake) Marcus! Virginia! I'm okay!
It took all night but
I tracked that wolf
just outside Tanner's
River before I lost it.
That town is outside
the designated territory.
Is the entire clan
is about to go rogue?
It's possible. But, if even one of them
set foot into the town, that's
a violation of the truce.
So?
We going hunting?
We are.
(Jake laughs)
Alright.
Hey.
That thing I saw
last night-
How do we kill it?
(Virginia) There's only
one way to kill a werewolf.
(Virginia) A silver
weapon through the heart,
bullet or blade,
doesn't matter.
It's an involuntary
transformation
triggered by the full
moon it ends at dawn.
This Gabriel seems like a
different kind of animal.
You get bitten by a
werewolf, you will
turn into one of them
by the next full moon.
(Jake) There's a chance that
the effects can be reversed
but only if you kill
the wolf that bit you
before you make
your first human kill.
You kill a human, you're
cursed for as long as you live.
So basically,
don't get bitten.
Once you're bitten,
you're never the same.
It's like a disease or drug
addiction you can't kick.
The wolf is always
a part of you.
You ever turn
one back?
A werewolf,
I mean.
Grandmother did.
Once.
Who was it?
Our grandfather.
Our family's dirty
little secret.
If we're hunting during the day
how do we know they're not wolves?
(Marcus) They may not look
like wolves but they are.
How do we make sure
we don't kill a human?
A werewolf test.
UGH!
It's a pellet filled
with silver halide paint,
burns the flesh, marks them and
causes a mild transformation.
Mild transformation?
What does that mean?
You'll see.
God!
Okay, okay,
alright!
(Virginia) Tanner's River is
the edge of their territory.
(Marcus) Anyone from the pack
caught within the town is fair game.
(Jake) And fair game means dead.
What the hell
happened here?
It was before
the truce.
It was a course of 3 nights
practically everyone here was turned.
My family had no choice
but to put them down.
An entire town?
That's why it's so
important that we
never let them out
of their territory.
Never let them get close
to the rest of civilization.
Truce or no truce.
We should have wiped
them out a long time ago.
(tires screeching)
(footsteps)
Go go go go go!
(Marcus) Looks like we
got a couple of rogues.
(Marcus)
Shooter in position?
(Nathan)
Affirmative.
Nathan, you see your wolf from
last night you let us know.
(shot firing)
(wolf growling)
(blade slicing)
(groaning)
(wolf growling)
(shot firing)
(shots firing)
I love this.
(gun shots firing)
(shot firing)
(Gabriel)
Nathan...
What are you
doing?
(shots firing)
¶
You alright?
Yeah, thanks
to Nathan.
I'm good.
Is this your wolf?
No.
(shots firing)
(werewolf screeches)
(sounds from trunk)
(girl screams)
Please,
don't hurt me!
Grab her.
Come on.
(Virginia) It's okay,
it's okay. You're safe now.
(Virginia)
Did they hurt you?
It's okay,
it's okay.
Just tell us
what happened.
I was running out of gas
and I pulled off the highway.
And there was
a gas station.
And there was just
dead ends-
That's where
they put me.
(girl sobbing)
You and Virginia take
her to the hospital.
Tell them we'll be by
later to file a report.
Virginia will know
what to say.
Okay where are you
gonna go?
We'll sweep the rest of the town,
make sure there's nothing else.
Jake!
Let's go.
Is she okay?
Are you sure
they didn't hurt you?
They said they were gonna
use me In the next game.
What game?
I don't know.
From what they
were saying.
Once you go to the game,
you never come back.
(girl crying)
(people groaning)
(people crying)
Come on!
(girls crying)
(footsteps)
Your ancestors
were strong.
Their blood is
in your veins.
They were
unstoppable.
Your ancestors roamed
free on this earth.
But now the hunters
define us.
They've driven us to
this rotten little patch.
They say we're
ruled by the moon!
I say it's
all a lie!
We can change at will.
(people crying)
(bones cracking)
(people gasping)
No one here,
but us humans.
So it would seem.
Do you see the way
they look at you?
You should have killed
Xavier much sooner.
To survive
we must evolve.
(Nathan)
Hey.
You okay?
Thank you.
For what?
For keeping our secret.
Not saying anything
to that girl's parents
at the hospital.
Well, it's all about
family right?
I'm not sure my family's
been the best thing for you.
Is there a reason that you
never talk about your parents?
I didn't really
know them.
I was so young
when they died.
How did they die?
Killed by a Werewolf.
I'm sorry.
What's bothering you?
Nothing, I'm fine.
I liked killing that
Werewolf today.
I enjoyed it.
I felt no sense of
remorse whatsoever.
Made me feel
powerful.
Is that wrong?
No.
(girl crying)
Tonight you'll learn
what it's like.
To be like us.
To live in
a primal state.
If you will it,
you will survive.
Set 'em free.
I want you
to turn me.
I don't wanna die.
I wanna live.
I wanna be like you.
(growls)
(screams)
(truck engine)
(growl)
(screams)
Just relax. I'll end
this quickly for you.
(deep growling)
AHHHHHHHH!
(werewolf snarling)
AHHHHHHH!
Don't move, don't move! Stay calm!
Don't kill me,
don't kill me!
It's okay!
It's okay, believe me.
You're safe with us.
No, we have to go! The
wolves, they're coming!
They're coming!
(Virginia)
It's okay-
Is this the game we've
been hearing about?
The game?
They hunt humans?
Yes!
(gun shot fires)
(wolf dies)
How did you know that
wolf was there?
Instinct, I guess.
Okay there's no record here of any
wolf being able to transform at will.
Nothing.
So is this Gabriel some
kind of new breed?
Being able to transform at
will, it changes everything.
Especially if he's teaching the
rest of his pack to do the same.
The guy at the farmhouse
he's been with them for weeks.
He said this wolf
is also telepathic.
He said that Gabriel can somehow
communicate with those he's turned.
Is that even possible?
I dunno, Red.
I'm seeing things that I never
thought I'd see in my lifetime.
We have to wipe
them out now.
Every last one
of them.
No more excuse,
no more truce.
No more mercy.
You guys go upstairs
get some rest.
First thing in the morning
we start at Tanner's River,
work our way to the farmhouse,
see if we can pick up the trail.
Gran-
There's something about
Nathan that bothers me.
What?
I dunno, it's just
a feeling I get.
Keep an eye on him.
(Virginia) Nothing up here to report!
I can't see anything
out here either!
We've been looking all day
we must have missed something.
(Virginia) I think we should
lock up here for the night.
Maybe wait 'til
the full moon.
Check that.
(heavy breathing/
struggling)
Nathan?
(growls)
(Nathan growls)
(Marcus)
Virginia, move!
Don't kill him!
(Nathan growls)
(Nathan growling)
Hit him before
he moves!
(taser tasing)
You put us all
in danger.
(Marcus) We need to lock him up.
What happened?
You've been infected,
Nathan.
Last night you turned
into a Werewolf.
Did I hurt anyone?
No, no,
thank God.
How did this
happen?
Gabriel must have
bitten you.
I should have looked
more closely.
You said-
You said that if I
turned into a Werewolf,
you were gonna have to kill me.
Wait here.
I'll get you some
clothes.
You shoulda let me kill
him.
Not everything is black
and white, Marcus!
It is to me!
That's always been
your problem.
If you could see anything
outside of being a hunter.
I don't wanna see anything
outside of being a hunter!
This is what I am! I'm good
at it! I like being good at it!
Your narrow view of the
world is a liability.
No, I'm not the bad guy here,
you're the one who's wrong.
First responsibility is
always to protect this family.
Always. You shouldn't
have brought him here.
Nathan is family!
As far as I'm concerned!
Forgive me for wanting to have some
kind of life outside of being a hunter!
Marcus if it had been
Jake, Virginia, or me,
would you have been
able to kill so easily?
We all make mistakes,
Marcus.
No one got hurt that's
the impotant thing.
It is time to forgive
and move on.
We have to stick together
now more than ever before.
We know who
infected him, right?
He hasn't killed
anyone.
What's the problem?
We can turn him back.
We gotta hunt Gabriel to
the ends of the earth anyway.
It's not that simple,
there are repercussions.
They're manageable.
It's not gonna turn out
well for you and him.
Then, it'll be my problem
to deal with.
After we turn him back.
Not yours.
I got him into this
I'm gonna get him out.
With or without your
help, Marcus.
(Marcus)
I'll help!
I'll help.
(Marcus) But it's only
because I wanna hunt that son
of a bitch down
and kill him myself.
For the record, if that
happen to me, I want
one of you to kill me rather
than let me live like that.
I'll make a note of it
for future reference.
(Gabriel) That's it. You can do it.
Yes, you can.
There is a beast
in all of us.
(Gabriel) Just waiting to be summoned.
Feel it coursing
through your veins.
You've got to
give into it.
(Gabriel) Get rid of
that painful human side.
It's just too hard.
Really?
Perhaps you should
lie down. Take a nap.
I'd like that.
Sleep tight.
(screams)
So-
Shall we try again?
You know it's an amazing feeling when
you are in the throws of transformation.
It is such joy.
Such ecstasy.
And to think that you can have
that sensation whenever you want it.
That's what you desire.
That's what you thirst
for.
Now let that desire
drive you.
(breaths and growls)
Well done.
Well if he can do it,
who's next?
Hey.
How's he doing?
Nathan?
He's strong.
He's a good man.
Yeah.
He is.
Any activity?
It's all quiet.
I plotted out their movements
over the last 3 days.
Given what the guy
at the farmhouse said,
they must still be hiding
out in Tanner's River.
I wish he could have
given us more information.
He was hysterical. It must
have been like a bad dream.
Ah this is
a bad dream.
Do you agree with Marcus? About Nathan?
I don't know, Red.
I just want
all this to be over.
Hey.
So, is it time?
It is.
The wolf stays here.
The license plates, we
should have noticed before.
Notice what?
(Marcus) They're all out of state.
By the look of it they've been louring
people off the highway for quite a while.
(distant sound)
Go go, go!
1, 2... go!
This should make you
sleep right through it.
It's for the best believe me.
Okay.
Thank you.
Thank you for being so
concerned for my safety.
It's not for your safety,
it's for my own.
Is it true?
That you were able to turn your
husband back after he got infected?
It's true.
Was it the right choice?
That's a difficult
question, Nathan.
Please.
I would really like
to know the answer.
He liked being a wolf.
He resented that I took
the choice away from him.
On more than one occasion I found
him trying to turn himself back.
Eventually he did.
And so I had to kill him.
I'm sorry for what
happened to you.
I know that you are a
victim in all of this.
But I will not let my granddaughter
go through what I had to.
Not if I can help it.
You and jake head down
that way, I'll go down here.
Splitting up's not
such a good idea.
Make sure none
of them get past us.
I'll be fine.
What is this?
Welcome.
I've been looking
forward to this.
(Gabriel)
Get some rest.
Nathan!
(Nathan growls)
(Virginia screams)
(Virginia struggling)
(Virginia crying)
Gabriel, I presume?
After I've had a bad
dream,
I find it's helpful to
get a good stretch.
Where are my brothers?
Worrying about their
future, I hope.
Our newbies are eager to
make their first kill.
And me?
I intend to
kill you myself.
The last female warrior
of the hunter blood line.
You're a monster.
You and all your kind.
Now
- We're the perfect match.
I am going to kill you,
Gabriel.
Once upon a time
I would have run.
(distant growl)
Jake, Jake!
(Gabriel screaming)
Hunters, we honor you.
For our newcomers, you will
be their first kills.
You will give them the opportunity
to show what they're made of.
The chance to become
permanent members of the clan.
Set them free!
Jake!
Jake we've got to
stick together!
Always!
We gotta find someplace
to make a stand.
We're never going to
out run them.
Find a weapon
or something!
Marcus!
They never checked
my boots.
Our odds of survival just
improved dramatically, let's go.
(Marcus) Come on, Jake! Come on!
(Marcus)
Come on!
Where'd they go?
I don't know.
Jake, go back-
Go back to town,
get Virginia!
Get Virginia,
Jake.
What about you?
I'm good, I'm good.
I just-
I'm gonna find him.
Go!
Go go go!
(struggles)
Did you expect them
to kill this many?
No, I did not.
(yells)
(screams)
(fights)
Where's my sister?
Done.
(screams)
They're not back yet.
Something must be wrong.
I'm going after them.
I'll come with you.
No.
You'll only
slow me down.
He'll pay for this,
I promise you.
(Gabriel) Don't fool yourself, Nathan.
(Gabriel)
You're with us now.
(Gabriel) Look deep
inside yourself Nathan.
(Gabriel) You know it's
true. You wanna be a wolf.
(Gabriel)
Nathan-
(Gabriel) Their death was inevitable.
(Gabriel) Yours doesn't have to be.
Welcome.
Don't be afraid.
It's just me.
In your head.
Oh yeah?
Well then come out
and face me.
(Gabriel) If they kill
me you'll change back.
(Gabriel) Think of what I've given you.
(Virginia) Nathan! Nathan!
(gun shots firing)
Nathan!
Virginia!
Oh Virginia,
you okay?
Just get me down.
Where are my brothers?
I gotta get you down-
Nathan, where are
my brothers?
We don't have time for
this!
No!
(Gabriel) Should you choose to
remain with her, she will kill you.
(Gabriel) That is of
course unless you turn.
(Gabriel) You could have it
all, turn her and it's all yours.
(Gabriel) Tonight I
will be coming for her.
When I was a little
girl all I wanted was
to grow up
so I could hunt.
Carry on the family
tradition.
Seemed so grand,
so exciting.
It made us special.
The secret
we couldn't share.
Knowing something
no one else did.
It was magical.
I felt the same way.
We all did.
Now it's all
come down to you.
You mustn't let a single
one of them live.
I don't plan to.
Here, wear these.
We don't want you
touching any silver.
Okay, I'm gonna head
back down alright?
Hey!
You forgot these.
Got it.
Okay. I think that's
the last of the guns,
and they're all fully
loaded with silver.
Good.
Then, we're ready.
I think I'm running out
of time.
I'm gonna end this
tonight.
I think we better get me in my
cage. I can feel it starting.
I'm gonna make this
right.
Virginia,
it's time.
You go, I'll put him
in his cage.
(struggles)
You gotta try a bit
harder, Virginia.
Aren't you the slippery
one?
Too bad about your
brothers, Virginia.
I wish I could tell you
they died well.
But in the end, I find all
pure humans are cowards.
I'm so sorry,
Nathan.
(gun shot fires)
I told you,
I'd kill you, Gabriel.
You'll never kill
all of us.
Nathan!
(Virginia crying)
(Virginia)
Nathan!
Nathan?
GRRRRRRRR!
(Nathan snarling)
(Nathan howling)
You're bleeding.
It's okay,
it's not my blood.
Gabriel's dead. I think
the rest of the pack, too.
Good that means
it's just me then.
It wasn't supposed
to end this way.
It doesn't have
to end.
I wanna have a life
with you, Virginia.
That would be nice.
Just lock me away for
the full moon, that's all.
That doesn't work.
Virginia, you've
been bitten.
Hey, this gives us
a choice now.
We can do this.
It doesn't have
to end this way.
I was so stupid.
I wanted
a normal life.
I wanted everything my
family fought to protect.
I'm sorry I ever
brought you here.
Hey-
I'm not sorry.
I'm not sorry,
okay?
We can do this.
Trust me.
Everything's
gonna be okay.
I promise.
I'll find a way to
control the change. Okay?
(Nathan struggles)
I love you, Nathan.
I always will.
(Virginia crying)
"Her parents warned her not to
venture beyond the edge of her village.
"For within the forest
lived an unspeakable evil.
"An evil so powerful the elders
only dared speak of it in whispers."
(wolf howling)