Yare, yare!
Take in the topsail
Tend to the master's whistle!
Bestir, bestir!
Good Boatswain, have care
Where's the master?
Play the men
I pray now, keep below
Where is the master, bos'n?
Do you not hear him!?
You mar our labour,
keep your cabins
you do assist the storm
Nay, good, be patient
When the sea is
Good, yet remember
whom thou hast aboard
None that I more love than myself
Silence, trouble us not!
Out of our way, I say!
Yet again? What do you here?
Shall we give o'er, and drown?
Have you a mind to sink?
A pox o' your throat, you bawling,
blasphemous, incharitable dog!
Work you, then
Hang, cur, hang! You whoreson,
insolent noisemaker
we are less afraid
to be drowned than thou art
Off to sea again!
Lay her off!
Hell is empty and all the devils here!
If by your art, my dearest mother, you
have put the wild waters in this roar
allay them...
O, I have suffered with those that
I saw suffer
A brave vessel, who had, no doubt,
some noble creature in her
dash'd all to pieces
Poor souls, they perish'd!
Be collected
No more amazement
tell thy piteous heart there's no
harm done
- O, woe the day!
- No harm
I have done nothing but in care of thee,
of thee, my dear one, thee
my daughter, who art ignorant
of what thou art
nought knowing of whence I am
nor that I am more better than Prospera
master of a full poor cell
and thy no greater mother
More to know did never meddle
with my thoughts
'Tis time I should inform thee farther
So. Lie there, my art
Wipe thou thine eyes, have comfort
The direful spectacle of the wreck
which touch'd the very virtue
of compassion in thee
I have with such provision in mine art so
safely ordered that there is no soul
No, not so much perdition as an hair
betid to any creature in the vessel
which thou heard'st cry,
which thou saw'st sink
Sit down, and be attentive
Canst thou remember a time
before we came unto this cell?
I do not think thou canst, for then thou
wast not out three years old
Certainly, ma'am, I can
By what? By any other
house or person?
Of any thing the image tell me that hath
kept with thy remembrance
'Tis far off, and rather like a dream
Had I not Four or five women
once that tended me?
Thou hadst, and more, Miranda
Twelve year since, Miranda,
twelve year since
thy mother held the Dukedom
of Milan and its princely power
But are not you my mother?
The very same, who long ago was wife
to him who ruled Milan most liberally
who, with as tolerant a hand toward me
gave license to my long hours
in pursuit of hidden truths
of coiled powers contained within
some elements to harm, or heal
I brooked no interruption
but your squalling
for thou, child, art a princess born
O, Heavens!
What foul play had we, that we
came from thence?
Upon thy father's death, authority was
conferred as was his will to me alone
thereby awaking the ambitions of my
brother and thy uncle, call'd Antonio
- Thou attendst not...
- Good Madam, I do!
I pray thee, mark me
that a brother should be so perfidious!
He whom I did charge to execute
express commands
as to the prudent
governing of fair Milan
instead undid, subverted
Dost thou attend me?
Ma'am, most heedfully!
Perverting my upstanding studies
now his slandering and bile-dipped
brush did paint a faithless portrait
His sister, a practicer of the black arts!
A demon, not a woman, nay a witch!
And he full-knowing others of
my sex have burned for no less!
The flames now fanned, my counselors
turned against me. Dost thou hear?
Your tale, ma'am, would cure deafness
To credit his own lie he did
believe he was indeed the Duke
confederates wi' the King of
Naples to give him annual tribute
and bend my Dukedom yet unbow'd
to most ignoble stooping
O the heavens!
Now the condition
The King of Naples, being an enemy
to me inveterate
hearkens my brother's suit
which was, that he, should presently
eradicate me and mine
out of the dukedom
and confer fair Milan with
all its honours upon my brother
whereon, one midnight
did Antonio open the gates of Milan
and, i' the dead of darkness his
ministers for the purpose hurried thence
me and thy crying self
Wherefore did they not
that hour destroy us?
Dear, they durst not
so dear the love my people bore me
In few, they hurried us aboard a bark
bore us some leagues to sea
where they prepared a rotten
carcass of a boat
not rigg'd, nor tackle, sail, nor mast
the very rats instinctively had quit it
there they hoist us to cry
to the sea that roar'd to us
to sigh to the winds whose pity sighing
back again, did us but loving wrong
Alack, what trouble was I then to you!
O, a cherubim thou wast
that did preserve me!
Thou didst smile
Infused with a fortitude from heaven
that raised in me
an undergoing stomach
to bear up against what should ensue
- How came we ashore?
- By providence divine
Some food we had
and some fresh water
that a noble Neapolitan, Gonzalo
out of his charity, did give us, with rich
garments, stuffs and necessaries
which since have steaded much
Of his gentleness,
knowing I loved my books
he furnish'd me from mine own
library with volumes
that I prize above my dukedom
Would I might but ever see that man!
I pray you, ma'am
for still 'tis beating in my mind, your
reason for raising this sea-storm?
By accident most strange
bountiful fortune now my dear lady, hath
mine enemies brought to this shore
Here cease more questions
Thou art inclined to sleep
'Tis a good dulness, and give it way
I know thou canst not choose
Come away, servant, come
I am ready now
Approach, my Ariel, come
All hail, great master!
Grave dame, hail!
I come to answer thy best pleasure
be't to fly, to swim, to dive into the fire
to ride on the curl'd clouds
to thy strong bidding task Ariel
and all his quality
Hast thou, spirit, perform'd, to point,
the tempest that I bade thee?
To every article
I boarded the King's ship
Now on the beak, now in the
waist, the deck, in every cabin
I flamed amazement; sometime I'd
divide and burn in many places
the fire and cracks of sulphurous roaring
the most mighty Neptune
seem to besiege
and make his bold waves tremble
yea, his dread trident shake
Hi ho!
My brave spirit!
Who was so firm, so constant, that
this coil would not infect his reason?
Not a soul but felt a fever of the mad
and play'd some tricks of desperation
The king's son Ferdinand, with hair
up-staring was the first man that leap'd
cried; Hell is empty
and all the devils here!
Why that's my spirit!
But was not this nigh shore?
- Close by, my master
- But are they, Ariel, safe?
Not a hair perish'd
On their sustaining garments
not a blemish
but fresher than before
and, as thou badest me, in troops I have
dispersed them 'bout the isle
The King's son have I landed by himself
whom I left cooling of the air
with sighs
in an odd angle of the isle and sitting,
his arms in this sad knot
Of the King's ship, the mariners,
say how thou hast disposed
Safely in harbour is the King's ship
in the deep nook, there she's hid
the mariners all under hatches stow'd,
who, with a charm, I have left asleep
Ariel, thy charge exactly is perform'd
but there's more work
What is the time o' the day?
- Past the mid season
- At least two glasses
The time 'twixt six and now must by
us both be spent most preciously
Is there more toil?
Since thou dost give me pains let me
remember thee what thou hast promised
which is not yet perform'd me
How now? Moody?
What is't thou canst demand?
My liberty
Before the time be out? No more!
I prithee, remember
I have done thee worthy service
thou didst promise to bate me a full year
Dost thou forget from what
a torment I did free thee?
- No
- Thou dost
- I do not, ma'am
- Thou liest, malignant thing!
Hast thou forgot the foul witch Sycorax
hast thou forgot her?
- No, ma'am
- Thou hast
Where was she born? Speak! Tell me
Ma'am, in Algiers
O, was she so?
I must once in a month recount what
thou hast been, which thou forget'st
This damn'd witch Sycorax
for mischiefs manifold and sorceries
terrible to enter human hearing
from Algiers, thou know'st,
was banish'd Is not this true?
Ay, ma'am
This blue-eyed hag was
hither brought with child
and here was left by the sailors
Thou, my slave, as thou report'st
thyself, wast then her servant
And, for thou wast a spirit too delicate to
act her earthy and abhorr'd commands
she did confine thee into a cloven pine
within which rift imprison'd thou didst
painfully remain a dozen years
within which space she died
and left thee there
thou best knows what a torment
I did found thee
thy groans did make wolves howl
and penetrate the breasts
of ever angry bears
It was mine art,
when I arrived and heard thee
that made gape the pine,
and let thee out
I thank thee, master
If thou more murmur'st I will rend an oak
and peg thee in his knotty entrails till
thou hast howl'd away twelve winters
Pardon, master
I will be correspondent to the command
- and do my spiriting gently
- Do so
and after two days I will discharge thee
That's my noble master!
What shall I do? Say what?
What shall I do?
Go make thyself like a nymph o' the sea
Be subject to no sight but thine or mine,
invisible to every eyeball else
Go! Hence with diligence!
Awake, dear heart, awake!
Thou hast slept well. Awake!
The strangeness of your story put
heaviness in me
Shake it off. Come on
We'll visit with Caliban, my slave
who never yields us kind answer
'Tis a villain, ma'am,
I do not love to look on
But, as 'tis, we cannot miss him
He does make our fire,
fetches in our wood
and serves in offices that profit us
What, ho! Slave!
Caliban! Thou earth, thou! Speak
- There's wood enough within!
- Come forth, I say!
I must eat my dinner
There's other business for thee.
Come, thou tortoise! When?
Thou poisonous slave, got by the
devil himself upon thy wicked dam
Come forth!
As wicked dew as e'er my mother
brush'd with raven's feather from
unwholesome fen drop on you both!
A south-west blow on ye
and blister you all o'er!
For this, be sure, to-night thou
shalt have cramps
side-stitches that shall pen
thy breath up
Urchins shall work all exercise on thee
thou shalt be pinch'd as thick as
honeycomb
each pinch more stinging
than bees that made 'em
This island is mine by Sycorax my
mother, which thou tak'st from me
When thou camest first, thou strok'st
me and madest much of me
wouldst give me water with berries in't
and teach me how to
name the bigger light
and how the less,
that burn by day and night
And then I loved thee and show'd
thee all the qualities o' th' isle
the fresh springs, brine-pits
barren place and fertile
Cursed be I that did so!
All the charms of Sycorax toads,
beetles, bats, light on you!
For I am all the subjects that you have,
which first was mine own king
and here you sty me in this hard rock
whiles you do keep from me
the rest o' th' island
Thou most lying slave, whom
stripes may move, not kindness!
I have used thee, with humane care,
lodged thee in mine own cell
till thou didst seek to violate
the honour of my child
Would't had been done!
Thou didst prevent me: I had peopled
else this isle with Calibans
Abhorred slave
which any print of goodness
wilt not take
I pitied thee
took pains to make thee speak
You taught me language, and my
profit on't is, I know how to curse
The red plague rid you for
learning me your language!
Hagseed, hence!
Fetch us in fuel. Shrug'st thou, malice?
If thou neglect'st or dost unwillingly what
I command, I'll rack thee with old cramps
fill all thy bones with aches, make thee
roar that beasts shall tremble at thy din
No, pray thee
I must obey. Her art is of such power
So, slave: hence!
Come unto these darkened sands
and then take hands
Curtsied when you have and kiss'd
the wild waves whist
foot it featly here and there
and, sweet sprites, the burden bear
Hark, hark! The watchdogs bark!
Where should this music be?
I' th' air or th' earth?
It sounds no more: and sure,
it waits upon some god o' th' island
Thence I have follow'd it,
or it hath drawn me rather
but 'tis gone
No, it begins again
Full fathom five thy father lies
of his bones are coral made
Those are pearls that were his eyes
nothing of him that doth fade
but doth suffer a sea change
into something rich
and strange
The ballard does remember
my drown'd father
This is no mortal business, nor no
sound that the earth owes
I hear it now above me
The fringed curtains of thine eye
advance and say...
say what thou seest yond
What is't? A spirit?
No, child: it eats and sleeps and hath
such senses as we have, such
This gallant which thou seest
was in the wreck
I might call him a thing divine, for
nothing natural I ever saw so noble
It goes on, I see, as my soul prompts it
Oh spirit, fine spirit! I'll free
thee within two days for this
Most sure, the goddess on whom
these airs attend!
Vouchsafe my prayer may know if
you remain upon this island
and that you will some good instruction
give how I may bear me here
My prime request, which I
do last pronounce, is
O you wonder!
If you be maid or no?
No wonder, sir, but certainly a maid
My language! Heavens!
I am the best of them
that speak this speech
were I but where 'tis spoken
How? The best?
What wert thou, if the King
of Naples heard thee?
A single thing, as I am now, that
wonders to hear thee speak of Naples
He does hear me
and that he does I weep
myself am Naples
who with mine eyes, never since at ebb
beheld the King my father wreck'd
Alack, for mercy!
Yes, faith, and all his lords
At the first sight they have
changed eyes
Delicate Ariel,
I'll set thee free for this
A word, good sir
I fear you have done yourself
some wrong. A word!
Why speaks my mother so ungently?
This is the second man that e'er I saw,
the first that e'er I sigh'd for
They are both in either's powers
but this swift business
I must uneasy make
lest too light winning make the prize light
One word more
I charge thee that thou attend me
Thou dost here usurp
the name thou ow'st not
and hast put thyself
upon this island as a spy
to win it from me, the sovereign on't
No, as I am a man
There's nothing ill can dwell in
such a temple
Follow me. Speak not you for him:
he's a traitor
Come! I'll manacle thy neck
and feet together
sea-water shalt
thou drink. Follow!
No. I will resist such entertainment
till mine enemy has more pow'r
O dear mother, make not too rash a trial
of him, for he's gentle and not fearful
What, I say, my foot my tutor?
Put thy sword up, traitor
For I can here disarm thee with this
stick and make thy weapon drop
- Beseech you, mother
- Hence! Hang not on my garments
Ma'am, have pity. I'll be his surety
Silence! One word more shall make
me chide thee, if not hate thee
Thou think'st there is no more
such shapes as he
having seen but him and Caliban
Foolish child!
To th' most of men this is a Caliban
and they to him are angels
My affections are then most humble
I have no ambition to see a goodlier man
Come on, obey!
Thy nerves are in their infancy
again and have no vigour in them
So they are
My spirits, as in a dream,
are all bound up
My father's loss, the weakness
which I feel
the wreck of all my friends, nor this
dame's threats, to whom I am subdued
are but light to me
might I but through my prison
once a day behold this maid
All corners else o' the earth
let liberty make use of
Space enough have I in such a prison
It works
Come on
Thou hast done well, fine Ariel!
Hark what thou else shalt do me
Be of comfort. My mother's of a better
nature, sir, than she appears by speech
Thou shalt be free as mountain winds
then exactly do all points
of my command
To th' syllable
Come, follow. Speak not for him
Beseech you, sir, be merry
you have cause, so have we all, of joy
for our escape is much beyond our loss
But for the miracle,
I mean our preservation
few in millions can speak like us
Then wisely, good sir, weigh our
sorrow with our comfort
- Prithee, peace
- He receives comfort like cold porridge
Look he's winding up the watch of
his wit: by and by it will strike
- Sir
- One... Tell
When every grief is entertain'd
that's offer'd
- comes to the entertainer
- A dollar
Dolour comes to him, indeed. You have
spoken truer than you purposed
You have taken it wiselier
than I meant you should
Therefore, my lord...
Fie, what a spendthrift is he
of his tongue!
- I prithee, spare
- Well...
I have done
- But yet...
- He will be talking!
Though this island seem to be desert
- Uninhabitable and almost inaccessible
- Yet...
- Yet
- He could not miss't
The air breathes upon us here
most sweetly
As if it had lungs, and rotten ones
Or as 'twere perfumed by a fen
Here is everything advantageous to life
True: save means to live
Of that there's none, or little
How lush and lusty the grass
looks! How green!
The ground indeed is tawny
With an eye of green in't
But the rarity of it is, which is
indeed almost beyond credit
that our garments, being,
as they were, drenched in the sea
are now as fresh as when
we put them on first in Afric
In Tunis
At the marriage of your fair daughter
Claribel to the King of Tunis
You cram these words into mine ears
against the stomach of my sense
Would I had never married my daughter
there! For, coming thence, my son is lost
and, in my rate, she too
who is so far from Italy removed
I ne'er again shall see her
O thou mine heir of Naples and of Milan
what strange fish hath made
his meal on thee
Sir, he may live
I saw him beat the surges under him,
and ride upon their backs
- I not doubt he came alive to land
- No, no, he's gone
Sir, you may thank yourself
for this great loss
that would not bless our Europe
with your daughter
but rather lose her to an African
Prithee, peace
We have lost your son, I fear, for ever
The fault's your own
So is the dear'st o' the loss
My lord Sebastian, the truth you
speak doth lack some gentlenes
You rub the sore, when you should
bring the plaster
- Very well
- And most like a surgeon
It is foul weather in us all, good
sir, when you are cloudy
Foul weather?
Very foul
Prospera! Prospera!
All the infections that the sun
sucks up from bogs, fens, flats
on Prospera fall and make her by
inchmeal a disease!
Her spirits hear me
And yet I needs must curse
But for every trifle are they set upon me
sometime like apes
that mow
and chatter at me and after bite me
then like hedgehogs which lie
tumbling in my barefoot way
and mount their pricks at my footfall
Sometime... am I all wound...
with adders who with cloven tongues
do hiss me into madness!
Lo! Here comes a spirit of hers
and to torment me for bringing
wood in slowly
I'll fall flat. Perchance he will
not mind me
Here's neither bush nor shrub,
to bear off any weather at all
and another storm brewing
I hear it sing i' the wind
Yond same black cloud, yond huge one
looks like a foul bombard that
would shed his liquor
If it should thunder as it did before
I know not where to hide my head
Yond same cloud cannot choose
but fall by pailfuls
What have we here?
A man or a fish?
Dead or alive?
A fish! He smells like a fish
a very ancient fishlike smell
A strange fish!
Were I in England now, as once I was
and had but this fish painted
not a holiday fool there
but would give a piece of silver
There would this monster make a man
any strange beast there makes a man
When they will not give a penny
to relieve a lame beggar
they will lay out ten to see
a dead Indian
Legged...
like a man...
and his fins like arms!
Warm o' my troth!
I do now let loose my opinion,
hold it no longer
This is no fish
but an islander, that hath lately
suffered by a thunderbolt
Alas, the storm is come again!
My best way is to creep
under his gaberdine
there is no other shelter hereabouts
Misery acquaints a man with
strange bedfellows
Do not torment me! O!
The master, the swabber,
the boatswain and I
the gunner and his mate
loved Mall, Meg and Marian
and Margery
but none of us cared for Kate
for she had a tongue with a tang
would cry to a sailor, Go hang!
She loved not the savour
of tar nor of pitch
yet...
yet a tailor might scratch her
where'er she did itch
then to sea, boys, and let her go hang!
Then to sea, boys, and let her
This is a very scurvy tune to sing
at a mans funeral
Well, here's my comfort
What's the matter?
Have we devils here?
Do you put tricks upon's with
savages and men of Inde, ha?
I have not scaped drowning to be
afeard now of your four legs
The spirit torments me. O!
This is some monster of the isle
with four legs
who hath got, as I take it, an ague
Where the devil should he learn
our language?
I will give him some relief
if it be but for that
If I can recover him, and keep him
tame and get to Naples with him
he's a present for any emperor
Do not torment me, prithee
I'll bring my wood home faster
He's in his fit now and does not
talk after the wisest
He shall taste of my bottle
Come on your ways
Open your mouth. This will shake your
shaking I can tell you, and that soundly
You cannot tell who's your friend
Open your chaps again
I should know that voice! It should be...
but he is drowned: and these are devils
O, defend me
Four legs and two voices a most
delicate monster!
Come
Amen! I will pour some
in thy other mouth
Stephano!
Doth thy other mouth call me?
Mercy, mercy! This is a devil,
and no monster I will leave him
Stephano! If thou beest Stephano,
touch me and speak to me
be not afeard, for I am Trinculo,
thy good friend Trinculo
If thou beest Trinculo, come forth
I'll pull thee by the lesser legs
If any be Trinculo's legs, these are they
Thou art very Trinculo indeed!
How camest thou to be the siege of this
mooncalf? Can he vent Trinculos?
I took him to be killed with
a thunder-stroke
But art thou not drowned, Stephano?
I hid me under the dead moon-calfs
gaberdine for fear of the storm
And art thou living, Stephano?
O Stephano, two Neapolitans 'scaped!
Prithee, do not turn me about
my stomach is not constant
These be fine things,
an if they be not sprites
That's a brave god and bears
celestial liquor
I will kneel to him
How didst thou 'scape?
How camest thou hither?
Swear by this bottle
how thou cam'st hither
I escaped upon a butt of sack
which the sailors heaved o'erboard
I'll swear upon that bottle
to be thy true subject
for the liquor is not earthly
Here! Swear by this bottle
how thou escapedst
Swum ashore, man, like a duck
I can swim like a duck, I'll be sworn
Here, kiss the book
Though thou canst swim like a
duck, thou art made like a goose
O Stephano. Hast thou any
more of this?
The whole butt, man
How now, mooncalf!
How does thine ague?
Hast thou not dropp'd from heaven?
Out o' th' moon, I do assure thee
I was the Man i' the Moon
when time was
I have seen thee in her
and I do adore thee
Come, swear to that
Kiss the book. Swear
By this good light, this is a very
shallow monster!
I afeard of him? A very weak monster!
The Man i' the Moon! A most poor
credulous monster!
I'll show thee every fertile inch
o' th' island
And I will kiss thy foot
I prithee, be my god
Come on then
Down, and swear!
I shall laugh myself to death
at this puppy-headed monster
A most scurvy monster!
I could find in my heart to beat him
- But that the poor monster's in drink
- Come, kiss
I'll show thee the best springs
I'll pluck thee berries
I'll fish for thee
and get thee wood enough
A plague upon the tyrant that I serve!
I'll bear her no more sticks
but follow thee thou wondrous man
A most ridiculous monster
to make a wonder of a poor drunkard!
I prithee, let me bring thee
where crabs grow
and I with my long nails will dig
thee pignuts
show thee a jay's nest
and instruct thee how to snare
the nimble marmoset
I'll bring thee to clust'ring filberts
and sometimes I'll get thee young
scamels from the rock
Wilt thou go with me?
I prithee now, lead the way without
any more talking, Trinculo
The King and all our company else
being drowned, we will inherit here
Farewell master: farewell, farewell!
A howling monster!
A drunken monster!
No more dams I'll make for fish
nor fetch in firing at requiring
nor scrape trencher, nor wash dish
'Ban, 'Ban
Ca- Ca- Ca- Ca- Caliban
has a new master
Get a new man!
Freedom, high day!
High day, freedom!
Freedom, high day,
high day freedom!
O brave monster! Lead the way
This my mean task
would be as heavy to me as odious
but the mistress which I serve
quickens what's dead
and makes my labours... pleasures
She is ten times more gentle than
her mother's crabbed
and she's composed of harshness!
I must remove some thousands
of these logs
and pile them up,
upon a sore injunction
My sweet mistress weeps
when she sees me work
and says, such baseness
had never like executor
I forget: but these sweet thoughts
do even refresh my labours
most busiest, when I do work
Alas, now, pray you, work not so hard!
I would the lightning had burnt up those
logs that you are enjoin'd to pile!
Pray, set it down and rest you
When this burns, 'twill weep
for having wearied you
My mother is hard at study
pray now, rest yourself
she's safe for these three hours
O most dear mistress, the sun will set
before I shall discharge
what I must strive to do
If you'll sit down, I'll bear your
logs the while
Pray, give me that: I'll carry it to the pile
No, precious creature, I had rather
crack my sinews, break my back
than you should such dishonour
undergo, while I sit lazy by
It would become me as well
as it does you
and I should do it with much more ease
for my good will is to it,
and yours it is against
You look wearily
No, noble mistress 'tis fresh morning
with me when you are by at night
I do beseech you, what is your name?
Miranda. O my mother,
I have broke your hest to say so!
Admired Miranda!
Indeed the top of admiration!
Worth what's dearest to the world!
Poor worm, thou art infected!
This visitation shows it
Full many a lady I have eyed
with best regard
and many a time the harmony of their
tongues hath into bondage brought
my too diligent ear
For several virtues have I liked
several women
never any with so full soul
but some defect in her did quarrel
with the noblest grace she owed
and put it to the foil
But you...
O you, so perfect and so peerless
are created of every creature's best!
I know only one more of my sex
no young woman's face remember
save from my glass, mine own
nor have I seen
more that I may call men than you,
good friend
how features are abroad, I am
skilless of: but, by my modesty
I would not wish any companion
in the world but you
nor can imagination form a shape,
besides yourself, to like of
But I prattle something too wildly
and my mother's precepts
I therein do forget
I am in my condition a prince,
Miranda
I do think, a king I would, not so
Hear my soul speak!
The very instant that I saw you,
did my heart fly to your service
there resides, to make me slave to it
and for your sake am I this
patient log-man
Do you love me?
O heaven, O earth,
bear witness to this sound
I beyond all limit of what else i' th' world
Do love, prize, honour you
I am a fool
To weep at what I am glad of
Wherefore weep you?
At mine unworthiness
which dare not offer
what I desire to give and much less
take what I shall die to want
But this is trifling
and all the more it seeks to hide itself,
the bigger bulk it shows
Hence, bashful cunning, and prompt me,
plain and holy innocence!
I am your wife, if you will marry me
If not, I'll die your maid
To be your fellow you may deny me
but I'll be your servant whether
you will or no
My mistress, dearest
And I thus humble ever
My husband, then?
Ay, with a heart as willing as
bondage e'er of freedom
- Here's my hand
- And mine
with my heart in't
and now farewell
Till half an hour hence
A thousand thousand!
Had I plantation of this isle,
my lord and were the king on't
what would I do?
'Scape being drunk for want of wine
No occupation: all men idle,
all and women too
but innocent and pure: no sovereignty
Yet he would be king on't
The latter end of his common
wealth forgets the beginning
Nature...
Nature, without sweat or endeavour
would bring forth, of its own kind
all foison, all abundance
to feed my innocent people
- No marrying 'mong his subjects?
- None, man, all idle
whores and knaves
I would with such perfection govern,
sir, t'excel the Golden Age
- God save his majesty!
- Long live Gonzalo!
And, do you mark me, sir?
Prithee, no more
Thou dost talk nothing to me
I do well believe your Majesty
and did it to minister occasion
to these gentlemen
who are of such sensible
and nimble lungs
that they always use
to laugh at nothing
'Twas you we laughed at
Who in this kind of merry fooling am
nothing to you so you may continue
and laugh at nothing still
What a blow was there given!
Nay, good my lord, be not angry
No, I warrant you: I will not
adventure my discretion so weakly
Will you laugh me asleep?
I am very heavy
Go sleep, and hear us
What, so soon asleep?
I wish mine eyes would, with
themselves, shut up my thoughts
I find they are inclined to do so
Do not omit the heavy offer of it
It seldom visits sorrow
when it doth, it is a comforter
We two, my lord, will guard your person
while you take your rest
and watch your safety
Thank you! Wondrous heavy
What a strange drowsiness
possesses them!
It is the quality o' th' climate
Why doth it not then our eyelids sink?
- I find not myself disposed to sleep
- Nor I my spirits are nimble
They fell together, as by consent
They dropp'd, as by a thunder-stroke
What might, worthy Sebastian
O, what might?
No more!
And yet methinks I see it in thy
face, what thou shouldst be
Th' occasion speaks thee
and my strong imagination sees
a crown dropping upon thy head
What? Art thou waking?
Do you not hear me speak?
I do, and surely it is a sleepy language
and thou speak'st out of thy sleep
What is it thou didst say?
This is a strange repose,
to be asleep with eyes wide open
standing, speaking, moving
and yet so fast asleep
Noble Sebastian, thou let'st
thy fortune sleep, die, rather
wink'st whiles thou art waking
Thou dost snore distinctly
there's meaning in thy snores
I am more serious than my custom
You must be so too, if heed me
which to do trebles thee o'er
Well, I am standing water
I'll teach you how to flow
Do so. To ebb hereditary
sloth instructs me
Thus, sir
Although this lord hath here almost
persuaded the king his son's alive
'tis as impossible that he's undrown'd
as he that sleeps here swims
I have no hope that he's undrown'd
O, out of that no hope what great
hope have you!
No hope that way is another way
so high a hope
that even ambition cannot pierce a wink
beyond but doubt discovery there
Will you grant with me
that Ferdinand is drown'd?
- He's gone
- Then, tell me
Who's the next heir of Naples?
- Claribel
- She that is Queen of Tunis
she that dwells ten leagues
beyond man's life
she that from whom we all were
sea-swallow'd though some cast again
and, by that destiny, to perform an act
whereof what's past is prologue
what to come in yours
and my discharge
What stuff is this? How say you?
Say, this were death that now
hath seized them
why, they were no worse
than now they are
There be that can rule Naples as
well as he that sleeps
O, that you bore the mind that I do!
What a sleep were this for your
advancement! Do you understand me?
Methinks I do
And how does your content tender
your own good fortune?
I remember you did supplant
your sister Prospera
True. And look how well my
garments sit upon me
My sister's servants
were then my fellows
now they are my men
- But, for your conscience
- Ay, sir: where lies that?
Twenty consciences, that stand
'twixt me and Milan
candied be they and melt,
ere they molest!
Here lies your brother, no better
than the earth he lies upon
If he were that which now
he's like, that's dead
Whom I, with this obedient steel three
inches of it can lay to bed forever
whiles you, doing thus,
to this ancient morsel
this Sir prudence
who should not upbraid our course
Thy case, dear friend,
shall be my precedent
As thou got'st Milan,
I'll come by Naples
Draw thy sword. One stroke shall free
thee from the tribute which thou payest
and I the King shall love thee
Draw together, and when I rear my
hand, do you the like
to fall it on Gonzalo
While you here do snoring lie
open-eyed conspiracy
his time doth take
If of life you keep a care
shake off slumber and beware
Awake! awake!
Good angels preserve the King
Why?
Why are you drawn?
Wherefore this ghastly looking?
What's the matter?
Whiles we stood here securing
your repose even now
we heard a hollow burst
of bellowing like bulls
or rather lions
Did't not wake you?
It struck mine ear most terribly
- I heard nothing
- O, 'twas a din to fright a monster's ear
to make an earthquake!
Heard you this, Gonzalo?
Upon mine honour, sir, I heard a
humming, which did awake me
As mine eyes open'd,
I saw their weapons drawn
'Tis best we stand upon our guard,
or that we quit this place
Let's draw our weapons
Lead off this ground
and let's make further search
for my poor son
Lead away
Now Prospera shall
know what I have done
So, King, go safely on to seek thy son
You're blind drunk!
Tell not me! When the butt is out, we will
drink water: not a drop before
Therefore bear up, and board 'em
Servant-monster, drink to me
Servant monster?
The folly of this island!
They say there's but five upon
this isle; we are three of them
If th' other two be brained like
us, the state totters
Mooncalf, speak once in thy life,
if thou beest a good mooncalf
How does thy honour?
Let me lick thy shoe
I'll not serve him
he's not valiant
Thou liest, most ignorant monster
Why, thou deboshed fish thou
Wilt thou tell a monstrous lie, being but
half a fish and half a monster?
Lo, how he mocks me!
Wilt thou let him, my lord?
Lord quoth he! That a monster
should be such a natural!
Lo, lo, again! bite him
to death, I prithee
Trinculo, keep a good
tongue in your head
If you prove a mutineer... the next tree!
The poor monster's my subject
and he shall not suffer indignity
I thank my noble lord
Wilt thou be pleased to hearken once
again to the suit I made to thee?
Marry, will I. Kneel and repeat it
I will stand, and so shall Trinculo
As I told thee before
I am subject to a tyrant, a sorceress
that by her cunning hath cheated
me of the island
Thou liest
Thou liest, thou jesting monkey, thou
I do not lie
Trinculo, if you trouble him any
more in's tale by this hand
I will supplant some of your teeth
Why, I said nothing
Mum, then, and no more
Proceed
I say, by sorcery she got this isle
from me she got it
If thy greatness will revenge it on her
thou shalt be lord of it
and I'll serve thee
How now shall this be compassed?
Canst thou bring me to the party?
Yea, yea, my lord!
I'll yield her thee asleep, where thou
mayst knock a nail into her head
Thou liest: thou canst not
What a pied ninny's this!
Thou scurvy patch!
I do beseech thy greatness, give him
blows and take his bottle from him
Why, what did I? I did nothing
I'll go farther off
Didst thou not just say he lied?
Thou liest
Do I so? Take thou that. As you like
this, give me the lie another time
Why? I did not give the lie
Out o' your wits and bearing too?
A pox o' your bottle!
And the devil take your fingers!
Now...
forward with your tale
- Prithee
- Stand farther off
Come, proceed
Why, as I told thee, 'tis a custom with
her, I' th'late afternoon to sleep
there thou mayst brain her
having first seized her books
or with a log batter her skull
or paunch her with a stake
or cut her wezand with thy knife
But remember first
to possess her books
for without them she's but a sot,
as I am
nor hath not one spirit to command
they all do hate her as rootedly as I
Burn but her books
And that most deeply to consider
is the beauty of her daughter
Of women I've seen but these
and Sycorax my dam
But she as far surpasseth Sycorax
as great'st does least
Is it so brave a lass?
Ay, lord
she will become thy bed, I warrant
And bring thee forth brave brood
Monster, I will kill this witch
her daughter and I will be King
and Queen
and Trinculo and thyself shall be
viceroys
Dost thou like the plot, Trinculo?
Excellent
Give me thy hand
I am sorry I beat thee
Within this half hour will she be asleep
Wilt thou destroy her then?
Ay, on mine honour
This will I tell my master
Thou makest me merry
I am full of pleasure
Come on, Trinculo, let us sing
Flout 'em and scout 'em
and scout 'em and flout 'em
Thought is free! Grog 'em then flog 'em
and flog 'em and grog 'em
Thought is free
Nab 'em and stab 'em,
stab 'em and nab 'em
Thought is free
Bag 'em and hang 'em,
hang 'em and bag 'em
Thought is free
Play 'em and flay 'em, flay 'em
and play 'em. Thought is free
What is this same?
If thou beest a man, show thyself
O, forgive me my sins!
Mercy upon us!
Art thou afeard?
No, monster, not I
Be not afeard: the isle is full of noises
sounds and sweet airs, that give
delight and hurt not
Sometimes a thousand twangling
instruments will hum about mine ears
and sometime voices that, if I
then had waked after long sleep
will make me sleep again
and then, in dreaming,
the clouds methought would open
and show riches ready to drop
upon me that, when I waked
I cried to dream again
This will prove a brave kingdom to me,
where I shall have my music for nothing
When Prospera is destroyed
By'r Lakin
I can go no further, sir
I needs must rest me
Old lord, I cannot blame thee, who
am myself attach'd with weariness
Sit down, and rest
He is drown'd whom thus
we stray to find
and the sea mocks our frustrate
search on land
Well, let him go
I am right glad
that he's so out of hope
The next advantage will we take
thoroughly
Let it be tonight
What harmony is this?
My good friends, hark!
Marvellous sweet music!
Give us kind keepers, heavens!
A living drollery
Now I will believe
that there are unicorns
If in Naples, I should report this
now, would they believe me?
We have stomachs
Will't please you taste of what is here?
Faith, sir, you need not fear
I will stand to and feed
although my last, no matter
since I feel the best is past
You are three men of sin!
Whom destiny hath caused
to belch up you
and on this island where man doth
not inhabit
you 'mongst men being
most unfit to live
I have made you mad
You fools! I and my fellows
are ministers of fate
the elements
of whom your swords are temper'd may
as well wound the loud winds
as diminish one dowle
that's in my plume
But remember
for that's my business to you
that you three from Milan did
supplant good Prospera
her and her innocent child
for which foul deed the powers,
delaying, not forgetting
have incensed the seas and shores
yea, all the creatures,
against your peace
Thee of thy son, Alonso,
they have bereft
and do pronounce
by me lingering perdition
shall step by step attend you
and your ways
Bravely the figure of this harpy
hast thou perform'd, my Ariel
My high charms work
and these mine enemies are all
knit up in their distractions
they now are in my pow'r
I' the name of something holy, sir
why stand you in this strange stare?
O, it is monstrous, monstrous!
Methought the billows spoke
and told me of it
the winds did sing it to me
and the thunder
that deep and dreadful organ pipe
pronounced the name of Prospera
it did bass my trespass
Therefore my son i' th' ooze is bedded
and I'll seek him deeper than e'er
plummet sounded
and with him there lie mudded
But one fiend at a time,
I'll fight their legions o'er
I'll be thy second
All three of them are desperate
their great guilt, like poison
given to work a great time after
now 'gins to bite the spirits
I shall follow them swiftly
and hinder them
from what this ecstasy may
now provoke them to
If I have too austerely punish'd you,
your compensation makes amends
for I have given you here a third
of mine own life
or that for which I live
all thy vexations were but
my trials of thy love
and thou hast strangely stood the test
O Ferdinand, do not smile at me
that I boast of her
for thou shalt find she will outstrip all
praise and make it halt behind her
I do believe it against an oracle
Then, as my gift and thine own
acquisition worthily purchased
take my daughter
But If thou dost break her virgin-knot
before all sanctimonious ceremonies
no sweet aspersion shall the heavens
let fall to make this contract grow
As I hope for quiet days,
fair issue and long life
the strongest temptation shall
never melt mine honour into lust
Fairly spoke
Sit then and talk with her
she is thine own
Monster, your fairy
which you say is a harmless fairy
has done little better than played
the Jack with us
Monster, I do smell all horse-piss, at
which my nose is in great indignation
So is mine. Do you hear, monster?
Good my lord, give me thy favour still
Ay, but to lose our bottles
in the pool
There is not only disgrace
and dishonour in that, monster
but an infinite loss
That's more to me than my wetting. Yet
all this is your harmless fairy, monster
What, Ariel!
My industrious servant
- Ariel!
-What would my potent master?
Here I am
Go bring the rabble, o'er whom I give
thee pow'r, here to this place
Incite them to quick motion
for I must bestow upon the eyes
of this young couple
some vanity of mine art; it is my promise
and they expect it from me
- Presently?
- Ay, with a twink
Before you can say "Come' and Go"!
Do you love me, master?
No?
Dearly my delicate Ariel
O mistress mine, where are you
roaming?
Oh stay and hear!
Your true love's coming
that can sing both high and low
trip no further, pretty sweeting,
journey's end in lover's meeting
every wise man's son doth know
What is love? Tis not hereafter
present mirth hath present laughter
what's to come is still unsure
in delay there lies no plenty
then come kiss me,
sweet-and-twenty
youth's a stuff...
...will not endure, will not endure
Look thou be true
Do not give dalliance too much the rein
the strongest oaths are straw
to the fire i' th' blood
I warrant you madam
The white cold virgin snow upon my
heart abates the ardour of my liver
Well...
No tongue! All eyes! Be silent
I had forgot that foul conspiracy
of the beast Caliban
and his confederates
against my life
Avoid! No more! No more!
This is strange. Your mother's in some
passion that works her strongly
Never till this day saw I her
touch'd with anger so distemper'd
You do look, my son, in a moved sort,
as if you were dismay'd be cheerful, sir
Our revels now are ended
These our actors, as I foretold you,
were all spirits
and are melted into air
into thin air
and, like the baseless fabric
of this vision
the cloud-capp'd towers, the gorgeous
palaces, the solemn temples
the great globe itself, yea, all which
it inherit shall dissolve
and, like this insubstantial
pageant faded
leave not a rack behind
We are such stuff
as dreams are made on
and our little life is rounded with a sleep
Sir, I am vex'd
If you be pleased, retire into my cell
and there repose
a turn or two I'll walk, to still
my beating mind
We wish your peace
Come with a thought!
I thank thee, Ariel. Come
What's thy pleasure?
Spirit. We must prepare
to meet with Caliban
Ay, my commander
Say again, where didst thou leave
these varlets?
I told you, ma'am, they were
red-hot with drinking
I left them I' the filthy-mantled
pool beyond your cell
There dancing up to the chins,
that the foul lake outstunk their feet
This was well done, my bird
The trumpery in my house, go put it
out, for stale to catch these thieves
I go, I go
A devil, a born devil
on whose nature nurture
can never stick
on whom my pains, humanely taken
all, all lost, quite lost!
I will plague them all, even to roaring
Pray you, tread softly
We now are near her cell
O no
Prithee, be quiet. Seest thou here?
This is the mouth o' the cell
Give me thy hand. I do begin to
have bloody thoughts
O King Stephano! O worthy Stephano!
Look what a wardrobe here is for thee!
Let it alone, thou fool!
It is but trash
O, ho, monster! We know what
belongs to a frippery
O king Stephano!
Put off that gown, Trinculo!
By this hand, I'll have that gown
Thy Grace shall have it
I look a dream, don't I
How can it be real
Look at the business, Gov'ner
What do you mean to dote
thus on such luggage?
Let's alone and do the murder first
Be you quiet, monster
Mistress line, is not this my jerkin?
Do, do! We steal by line and level
and't like your Grace
I thank thee for that jest
Here's a garment for't
Wit shall not go unrewarded
while I am king of this country
Monster, come, put some lime upon
your fingers, and away with the rest
I will have none on't. We shall lose our
time, and all be turned to barnacles
Monster, lay-on your fingers,
or I'll turn thee from my kingdom
- Go to, carry this
- And this
Ay, and this
Hey, Mountain, hey!
Silver!
Fury, Fury!
There, tyrant, there!
Hark!
They roar!
Let them be hunted soundly
At this hour lie at my mercy
all mine enemies
Now does my project gather to a head
Shortly shall all my labours end
and thou shalt have the air at freedom
Say, my spirit, how fares the King
and's followers?
Just as you left them
All prisoners, ma'am
The King, his brother and yours,
abide all three distracted
but chiefly him that you term'd, ma'am
'The good old lord Gonzalo'...
His tears run down his beard, like
winter's drops from eaves of reeds
Your charm so strongly works 'em
that if you now beheld them
your affections would become tender
Dost thou think so, spirit?
Mine would, master
were I human
And mine shall
Hast thou, which art but air
a touch, a feeling of their afflictions
and shall not myself
one of their kind be kindlier
moved than thou art?
Though with their high wrongs
I am struck to th' quick
yet with my nobler reason
'gainst my fury do I take part
The rarer action is in virtue
than in vengeance
They being penitent
the sole drift of my purpose doth
extend not a frown further
Go, release them, Ariel
My charms I'll break
their senses I'll restore, and
they shall be themselves
I'll fetch them, ma'am
Ye elves of hills, brooks,
standing lakes and groves
and ye that on the sands
with printless foot
do chase the ebbing Neptune and do
fly him when he comes back
you demi-puppets that by moonshine
do the green sour ringlets make
whereof the ewe not bites
and you whose pastime is to make
midnight mushrooms
that rejoice to hear the solemn curfew
by whose aid
weak masters though ye be
I have bedimm'd the noontide sun
call'd forth the mutinous winds
and 'twixt the green sea
and the azured vault, set roaring war
to the dread rattling thunder
have I given fire
and rifted Jove's stout oak
with his own bolt
the strong-based promontory
have I made shake
and by the spurs pluck'd up
the pine and cedar
graves at my command have
waked their sleepers oped
and let 'em forth
by my so potent art
But this rough magic I here abjure
and, when I have required some
heavenly music which even now I do
to work mine end upon their senses
that this airy charm is for
I'll break my staff
bury it certain fathoms in the earth
and deeper than did
ever plummet sound
I'll drown my book
There stand, for you are spell-stopp'd
O good Gonzalo, my true preserver
and a loyal sir to him you follow'st
I will pay thy graces home
both in word and deed
Most cruelly didst thou, Alonso,
use me and my daughter
Thy brother was a furtherer in the act
Thou art pinched for't now, Sebastian
Flesh and blood, you, brother mine
that entertain'd ambition, expell'd
remorse and nature
who, with Sebastian, would
here have killed your king
I do forgive thee, unnatural
though thou art
Their understanding begins to swell
Ariel
fetch me the skirt and bodice from my
cell I will discase me, and myself present
as I was sometime Milan
Quickly, spirit! Thou shalt ere
long be free
O I shall miss thee Ariel
but yet thou shalt have freedom
so...
Behold the wronged Duchess
of Milan, Prospera
I bid a hearty welcome
Whe'r thou be'st she or no, or some
enchanted trifle to abuse me I not know
thy pulse beats as of flesh and blood
and, since I saw thee,
th' affliction of my mind amends
with which, I fear, a madness held me
This must crave and if this be at all
a most strange story
Thy dukedom I resign and do entreat
thou pardon me my wrongs
But how should Prospera
be living and be here?
First, noble friend
let me embrace thine age
whose honour cannot
be measured or confined
Whether this be or be not, I'll not swear
Welcome, my friends all
But you, my brace of lords
were I so minded I could here
pluck his Highness' frown upon you
and justify you traitors
at this time I will tell no tales
- The devil speaks in her
- No
For you, most wicked sir
whom to call brother would even
infect my mouth
I do forgive thy rankest fault, all of them
and require my dukedom of thee, which
perforce, I know thou must restore
If thou beest Prospera, give us
particulars of thy preservation
How thou hast met us here
who three hours since were
wracked upon this shore
where I have lost my dear son
Ferdinand
I am woe for't, sir
for I have lost my daughter
A daughter?
When did you lose your daughter?
In this last tempest
But, howsoe'er you have been
justled from your senses
know for certain that I am Prospera
Welcome, sir
This cell's my court
I pray you, look in
Sweet lord, you play me false
No, my dear'st love,
I would not for the world
Yes, for a score of kingdoms
you should wrangle
and I would call it, fair play
If this prove a vision of the island,
one dear son shall I twice lose
Though the seas threaten,
they are merciful
I have cursed them without cause
Now all the blessings of a glad
father compass thee about!
Arise, and say how thou camest here
O, wonder!
How many goodly creatures are there
here! How beauteous mankind is!
O brave new world, that has
such people in't!
'Tis new to thee
What is this maid with whom
thou wast at play?
Is she the goddess that hath sever'd us
and brought us thus together?
Sir, she is mortal: but by
immortal providence she's mine
I chose her when I could not ask
my father for his advice
nor thought I had one
Give me your hands
Be it so! Amen!
Was't well done?
Bravely, my diligence
Set Caliban and his confederates free
Untie the spell
Every man shift for all the rest
Coragio, bully-monster, coragio!
If these be true spies which I wear
in my head, then here's a goodly sight
O Setebos, these be brave
spirits indeed!
How fine my master is!
I am afraid she will chastise me
What things are these, my lord
Antonio? Will money buy 'em?
Very like. One of them is a plain
fish, and no doubt marketable
These three have robb'd me, and
had plotted together to take my life
Two of these fellows
you must know and own
This thing of darkness
I acknowledge mine
I shall be pinched to death
Is not this Stephano,
my drunken butler?
And Trinculo is reeling ripe.
How camest thou in this pickle?
I have been in such a pickle
since I saw you last
that I fear me, it will never
out my bones
Why, how now, Stephano!
Touch me not! I am not Stephano,
but a cramp
You'd be king o' the isle, sirrah?
I should have been a sore one then
This is a strange thing as e'er I look'd on
What a thrice-double ass was I
to take this drunkard for a god
and worship this dull fool!
Go to! Away!
Hence, and bestow your luggage
where you found it
Or stole it, rather
Sir, I invite your Highness and
your train to my poor cell
where you shall take your rest
for this one night, and in the morn
I'll bring you to your ship
and so to Naples
where I have hope to see the nuptial
of these our dear-beloved solemnized
and thence retire me to my Milan
where every third thought
shall be my grave
My Ariel
Chick
That is thy charge
Then to the elements be free
Where the bee sucks there suck I
in a cowslip's bell I lie
there I couch when owl's do cry
on a bat's back I do fly
after summer, after summer merrily,
merrily, merrily... shall I live now
under the blossom that hangs
on the bough
Now my charms are all o'erthrown
And what strength I have's mine own
Which is most faint
O, release me from by bands
With the help of your good hands
Gentle breath
gentle breath of yours my sails must fill
Or else my project fails
Which was to please
Now, I want...
Spirits to enforce
Art to enchant
And my ending is despair
unless Ibe relieved by prayer
Which pierces so that it assaults
pierces so that it assaults
Mercy itself and frees all faults
As you from crimes would pardonned be
Let your indulgence...
...set me free
Now I want
Spirits to enforce
art to enchant
And my ending is despair
Unless I be relieved by prayer
Now I want
Spirits to enforce
art to enchant
and my ending is despair
Unless I be relieved by prayer
Which pierces so that it assaults
pierces so that it assaults
Mercy itself and frees all faults
As you from crimes
would pardon'd be
Let your indulgence
...set me free