Don't mention anything to the guys.
Okay?
No.
Hello. How are you?
What's up Fausto?
Why so late?
We got a job early in the morning.
So you already did a "quickie"?
Something like that.
That's good.
- An early bird!
- We got 1 0 bucks each.
For breakfast...
At least it's something.
- Better than nothing.
- It was good as a starter.
- What did you do?
- Something simple.
- But what? What was it?
- Something easy.
Don't want to tell us?
- How you doing?
- They won't even pay 1 0 an hour.
It's time the price went up.
I got here at 7.:00
and you weren't here.
- We left at 6..30.
- Wow!
Here we are,
trying to get some work.
- Since the morning.
- Like all of us.
But nothing comes.
What time did you get here?
At 7.:00?
You have to be early.
- Here comes one.
- Come on.
Move fast!
How many?
Five!
Take one more?
There goes work!
He filled it up!
You've got to move fast.
But that guy always pays little.
They left with a leech!
That's why we didn't get up.
He pays little.
- Have you worked with him?
- He's a "cheesecake."
You mean cheapskate.
Poor guys, they'll regret it.
Let them work!
Tomorrow they'll tell us
about their adventure.
He only took old guys!
No, man! He took
the best and freshest!
Fucking heat!
Let me tell you a story.
A clean-cut guy
stopped the other day.
He asked for only one
and pointed at me.
So I went with him.
He took you in his car?
He said he was from the Minutemen.
So I panicked.
But he told me not to worry
because I had survived the desert.
So I deserved to be here.
We drove to Hoover Park.
He told me the job
was going to be in his truck.
I started to get suspicious.
He told me it was a special job.
I told him I was not a mechanic!
He told me it was okay.
What did he mean by "special"?
First, he offered me
some Bacardi Cognac.
Why?
Tell me another one!
Like when you got raped!
When that black guy got you
in Long Beach.
I'll be back.
He wanted to get me happy.
Then he touched my leg...
Good morning...
Can you go get my Aunt Lidia?
Yes, thank you.
Auntie, how are you?
Sorry. Things are getting better.
I'll be able to send money soon.
Yes, I got a job.
Don't be like that
when I'm so far away.
You don't know
how things work here.
How is Elvira?
I'll send some soon.
Okay. Bye.
Aren't you going to give me
God's blessing?
Thank you. Bye-bye, Auntie.
I haven't called them
in like three months.
How many guys do you need?
That lady always passes
but never picks anyone.
She only likes to look.
"Window Shopping."
To see who she likes.
Today, someone
is supposed to pick us up.
Who told you that?
Someone that stopped by yesterday.
Here comes one.
Ten dollars an hour is okay.
Eight is too little.
Ten dollars per hour.
Take your tools.
Let's clean up the area
and open a ditch
about half a meter deep
and half a meter wide.
Why don't you take off
that fucking back pack, man?
What did your aunt tell you?
That Elvira is almost
completely blind now.
I told her that things
will be better soon.
- With the money?
- Yes.
This is for you.
For you...
You promised to take us back.
Don't you remember?
What's this guy saying?
He doesn't want to take us back.
He has things to do.
He said he would take us back!
Look...
He has the same shoes as me.
Damn Gringo!
Fucking guy
didn't want to bring us back!
But we made it.
What's your plan?
See you tomorrow.
That's it?
We catch the bus over
on Montana St.
Bye, Jesus.
Wash it good, boys!
We'll have some beers at the park.
Let's forget the damn gringo,
keep the money,
throw away the shotgun.
- But we already agreed, man!
- You agreed!
I didn't say anything!
Don't be a pussy, bro.
Don't you worry about it.
Calm down, man!
Let it go!
Let's bust their faces, man!
Let's go!
Relax, bro.
Give me the shotgun.
Fucking gringos!
In the crop fields
we'll get us some women.
It's so pretty here.
Tomorrow is Independence Day
in Mexico.
If we were back home,
we'd be drunk by now.
Get the knives.
Put them in a bag.
Sit over there.
Sit down.
For the money.
Yes. John.
This lady is crazy.
Fausto, let's go for a swim.
Get in the water, please.
Take a hit.
Give it a try...
So you feel the effect.
Come on, don't be a coward!
Calm down!
You're acting like a brat!
No more?
La Venada, Guanajuato.
Be careful.
Yes.
Jesus.
Think of Elvira.
She's almost blind.
Jesus!
Let's leave, please!
Let's go.
It's time to go!
Don't touch!
Why did you kill her?
You're the one
that brought me here.
Let's go.
Hold on.
I can't hear well.
My ear is bleeding!
It's the woman's blood.
Good morning!
Who is new here?
Today we will work
about eight acres!
You will be paid by the hour!
- Okay?
- Yes.