Good morning.
Good morning,
Sylvester.
Morning, Mama.
Good morning, Gertie.
Good morning, Aunt Sarah.
Don't run...
with them eggs, Arnett!
Big Baby?
Ma'am, Miss White?
Big Baby, come...
over here, please.
Morning, Miss White.
Morning. Would you run this
over to Mr. Wright at the store?
Yes, ma'am, Miss White.
Big Baby...
Ma'am?
The name is Wright.
Yes, ma'am.
Mr. Wright,
got your breakfast!
Mr. Wright!
Oh, Mr. Wright!
Mr. Wright,
I got your breakfast!
Stay where you are,
Big Baby!
Stay where you are!
I'm coming!
Mr. Wright! Mr. Wright,
I got your... breakfast.
A nice day, ain't it?
Y'all get on now.
That'll be two pennies, please.
Thank you.
Girl, you better...
go away from here.
How's the family?
Morning, Miss Sarah.
Morning, Mr. Bryce.
Lovely day, ain't it?
Ooh, that it is.
You got that egg
for me, boy?
Yes, sir.
There you are.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
- Here you go, Mama.
- All right.
All aboard!
Shoot.
Shoot, for Christ sake!
You little mullet!
What, are you an Audubon fella?
You a bird-watcher?
Come on.
This is going to be the first
boar you smoked yourself.
You know what them
Seminole injuns say?
You don't?
They say you only supposed
to kill what you gonna eat.
They say it's a sin
if you don't.
Damn Seminole.
Listen here.
Don't want you around
that colored boy no more.
Arnett?
Don't look right, my boy
trailing around after a nigger.
But he Arnett.
He's my friend.
That hurt?
No.
Why you cryin'?
I ain't crying.
You'll be a man soon.
I'll get you there.
Hey, Duke!
Seen any niggers out here?
No, sir.
Well, one escaped off
the chain gang near State Road.
Name's Jesse Hunter.
He might have headed
for Rosewood.
You keep an eye out.
You see him,
don't shoot him.
Bring him to me.
All right. Yes, sir.
I say shoot him.
Drive.
Aunt Sarah!
Sheriff.
Morning.
I got a surprise for you.
- I wonder what it is.
- Don't move.
Come on, baby. Stop it.
James, come on now.
Don't act like a child.
Fanny. Fanny.
Stop it now.
Stop it.
Oh, Fanny.
I said stop it.
Go to work.
Damn!
Morning, Sarah.
Morning, Mr. Taylor.
Floors need scrubbin',
Aunt Sarah.
Relax, child. We already done
scrubbed all the cypress...
out of these old boards.
Watch out!
Excuse me, Mr. Taylor.
Goddamn.
So he won't come
around here, huh?
Earl, put the gun away.
Hell, that boy ain't
no more off a chain gang...
than I'm
governor of Florida.
Sit on down.
Bye, Emmett.
All right, settle down.
I'm gonna tell you a story, OK?
Pay attention.
"Once upon a time,
"there was
a pony named Dark...
"who every night took
little people to Sleepy Town.
"One night, as Dark Pony
started off,
"he met a little boy named
Naughty who called out...
"Please let me go.
"So Dark Pony whoaed...
"and Naughty
hopped on his back...
"and away they went.
"They went galloping..."
- Who's that?
- I don't know.
Hey, Cousin Scrappie.
Mr. Carter!
You got yourself
a customer!
Hey, mister,
why ain't you got a car?
I like a horse.
Car's faster.
I ain't in no hurry.
You got a name, boy?
Yes, sir. Name's Arnett.
Booker T., meet Arnett.
Arnett, this here Booker T.
Why ain't you in school, boy?
I'm workin' for
Miss Fanny Taylor.
She payin' you
to follow me around?
Can I help you, mister?
Horse threw a shoe.
Need all four done.
Hell, can't get to it
till tomorrow.
Closing early tonight.
Why so?
It's New Year's Eve, sir.
Dance tonight,
8:00, Mason Hall.
Put that horse in the stable.
I'll take care of him for you.
That's a pretty horse, sir.
Thank you.
Now, Lemuel,
you know me, I'm fair.
I charge a dollar a jug.
But since you're
into me for $12 already,
I'm going to have
to put you down for three.
Three dollars?
Oh, now, Mr. Wright,
that ain't fair.
I... I know
I owes you a lots,
but I'm
a regular customer.
One dollar.
Thank you, Mr. Wright.
You better stop
drinking, Lemuel,
before I own...
your house.
Free of charge.
Go see after
your father.
Thank you, Mr. Wright.
Future customer.
Sorry, I don't extend
credit to strangers.
You own that plot
of land across the way?
I will...
this time tomorrow.
Look at this,
all these melons, no good.
Spoiled. Hog food now.
Jewel, darlin',
you got to throw these out.
You got some.45 shells?
Clean out.
Be going to Gainesville
first thing in the morning.
I'll pick some up.
You still be around then?
Might be.
What's wrong
with you two today?
Every time I try to tell you
to do something,
you won't listen.
You know, I will smack you.
I'll smack you.
No more playtime for you, none.
Not today.
Mornin', teacher, ma'am.
I wonder
if you can tell me...
where a man can find
hisself a good meal?
Y'all go inside.
Well, my name ain't
"teacher, ma'am." It's Beulah.
Folks I know
call me Scrappie.
Well, folks I know
call me Mann...
Miss Scrappie.
Nice to meet you,
Mr. Mann.
Likewise.
Now, this here Rattler,
Mr. Mann.
He a deer dog.
He help me hunt,
'cause he can get real quiet,
know what I mean?
All right, come on, boy.
This way now. This way.
So, what, uh,
what you selling now,
Mr. Mann?
What makes you think I'm selling
something, Mr. Carrier?
Well, I figure a colored fellow
with nowhere particular to be,
that man be
sellin' something...
or he runnin'.
Well...
you figure wrong...
friend.
Come on inside.
Hey, Gertie,
got some good news.
Mr. Mann here
ain't sellin' nothin'.
Turn that music down.
My husband
got a suspicious mind.
Oh, yes, I do.
He's sweet on you.
Scrappie, come over here
and help me with this bird.
Must be New Year's.
Yes, sir.
Come on in, Mr. Mann.
Evenin', Mr. Mann.
Ma'am.
Thank you.
This is my brother James,
his wife Emma,
and their daughter Jewel.
Be quiet.
Scrappie,
show the man a seat.
You can sit here.
Thank you.
Scrappie!
Now, I had a talk
with Mr. Andrews...
on your behalf today.
What about Mr. Andrews?
Mama, that old cracker...
caught hisself whistling
at Scrappie and all that.
What?
Yeah, that's right.
I went over there
and gave him some words.
Sylvester, what you say
to them people now?
Mr. Andrews, I come to have
a word with you about my cousin.
Now, I expect you
to show her some respect.
You expect, boy?
I don't like Scrappie
feelin' scared around nobody.
That a threat?
Ain't no threat needed.
I'm just sayin'
I don't mess with your peoples,
I don't want you
messin' with mines.
Now, I thank you
very kindly, sir.
Sylvester, you can't talk
to white folks like that...
and not expect a rope
around your neck.
Look, times
is changin', Mama.
Now, I ain't
no sharecropper.
I'm a music teacher.
Times ain't never changed
for no crackers, boy.
Don't you forget
they burned a colored man...
over in Wylie last summer
for winking at a white woman.
Sure did.
I know that, Mama,
but it's all right for them
to whistle at Scrappie?
No, that ain't right.
What do you think about all this
business, Mr. Mann?
Oh, that man
ready to eat.
Would you like to say
the blessing, Mr. Mann?
No, ma'am.
I'll do it, Mama.
I'll do it.
Thank you for the bounty
of our lives...
and the blessings
you've bestowed on us...
at home and family.
Can I have my yams now?
Who wants ham?
I want some yams.
Scrappie,
come eat a part of the bird...
that went over
the fence last.
Well, at least ask him...
all right, all right.
Ma'am, I ain't had a supper
like that in a long time.
Thank you kindly.
You're welcome.
You been drifting long,
Mr. Mann?
Seem like forever.
That ain't no kind
of life for a man.
You get yourself
a good piece of land,
the right woman...
a man can make
a new start 'round here,
make something
of hisself.
Ain't that right,
Scrappie?
Well, Aunt Sarah think Rosewood
colored folks' heaven on earth.
Best place these
old eyes ever seen.
Colored folks own
all the land around here.
All the businesses, too,
except for
Mr. Johnny Wright's store,
and he a halfway
decent white man,
if there ever
was such a thing.
Most of us doin' better than
them folks over in Sumner.
You ever seen a place
like Rosewood, Mr. Mann?
No, ma'am.
"Well, we know how to get money
when we need some," said Pecos.
"All right,"
nodded Essex.
"That's fine.
"But don't tell anybody
I told you...
"or I'll cut off
your ears."
He's a tough
character, Essex.
"Well, cross my heart
and hope you die,"
replied Lightning fervently.
"Well, that's fine,"
replied Essex.
"Now, go home
and shut up."
"Or lose your ears,"
added Thunder.
And that's it.
Next chapter next week.
I'm going up Sumner, buying
a drink for some of the boys.
John, I was thinking
we might read aloud...
from the Good Book tonight.
It'll still
be good tomorrow.
All right, boys, up to bed.
Dad, come on.
Dad, could we please stay
up just a few more minutes?
Best do what
your ma says.
She ain't my ma.
Timothy.
What'd you say?
What'd you say,
Timothy?
What was that for?
That's so you don't get
to thinking like your brother.
Get on to bed now.
Get on to bed!
Sorry about that,
Mary, love.
I guess the boys
still miss her.
You do, too, I reckon.
You're damn right
I miss her. Pardon me.
Only natural. Only been gone
7 months... 7 months, 3 days.
I'm going to
that auction tomorrow.
Get that plot of land.
Does that mean
we're staying, then?
Ain't no sense
of moving away.
I get Bradley's 5 acres, build
some bins out back, sell feed.
Make enough money,
in a few years,
we'll move to Gainesville,
open a bigger store, biggest
they ever seen in Florida.
Did you ever consider
how I feel living here?
Why don't you go on
and have that drink?
You be all right
alone here New Year's?
I got Jesus with me.
Go ahead.
There he is.
Gertie looks good.
Watch yourself,
there, Carter.
Watch yourself there.
I'm gonna cut a rug.
Cut a rug.
Go on, cut that rug,
but don't cut it too deep.
Come on.
Dance like he's riding
Booker T.
Twirl that man, Scrappie.
Listen here, now.
Y'all take notes, all right?
I don't want to have to
do this more than once.
Come on, man,
show him how to do it.
Sylvester can't
do no dancing.
Africa.
Nigerian.
My arm!
My arm! My arm! My arm!
I got you. I got you.
I... I brung you
some coffee.
I'm sorry.
It's all right.
I shouldn't have
snuck up on you.
You ridin' out today?
I might be here
a couple more days anyway.
Thinkin' about lookin' in on
that piece of land over there.
Bye.
Mornin', Mr. Mann.
Mornin', boy.
Tomorrow's my birthday.
You gonna come to my party?
You gonna have cake?
Yes, sir, chocolate.
Why is she skippin'?
Good coffee.
Morning, Mr. Mann.
Small town, people talk.
Old hangover remedy.
My granddaddy
taught me.
Here's to the new year.
I'm sober now.
You got some peaches?
Story going around is you
was over there in the big one.
How long you fight?
Few months? A year?
I'm a veteran
myself, Navy.
Spanish-American War.
Of course, the ass we kicked
only took one day.
Steamed into Manila Bay
May 1, 1898,
aboard the gunboat Concord
under old George Dewey.
Set them 8-inch guns a-blazing
till smoke blotted out the sun.
Sunk the Spanish fleet,
steamed out May 2.
Only eight Americans
got wounded.
I had the audacity
to be one of them.
Where were you? France?
Put my foots
in Germany, too.
Germany?
I'd like to see
the Kaiser's face...
when you come runnin'
out of the Black Forest.
We didn't have
no coloreds on the Concord.
Whole ship
full of good ol' boys.
Wouldn't have
took to it.
Maybe.
The mortars start flyin',
the gas start blowin',
there ain't much color
in them trenches.
Is that right?
You got them.45s?
.45s. Funny thing
about the draft.
I can't understand it. Pull
a colored boy out of his home,
send him over there, tell him
dig trenches, kill white folks.
That seem right to you?
I wouldn't know
much about that, sir.
I volunteered.
You been double-timing me.
Seeing that married Miz Connelly
over in Wylie.
I know.
Where you going?
Back to work.
Don't you turn
your back on me...
when I talk!
Damn swamp tramp!
What you crying about?
What you think
you're doing, hitting me?
You little swamp tramp!
Huh? You little chigger!
You don't hit me!
Girl...
Get out! Get out!
Get out!
Philomena!
M-Miz Taylor?
Is you all right, ma'am?
Go away, Philomena.
B-But...
Get out.
Get out!
So you fight
in the war?
Kill anybody
over there?
I mostly dug trenches.
Still, it must've been
grand seeing Chicago...
and New York.
Shoot, I ain't been
nowhere but Rosewood,
Sumner, Cedar Key,
three times to Gainesville.
Why you come back south?
Maybe...
I was looking
for Rosewood.
Thank you.
Well, how come you ain't never
settled down before now?
I was married...
once.
My Aunt Sarah, she say
I ask too many questions.
I'm sorry if...
How old you be,
Scrappie?
I'm 17.
No man?
- No young ones?
- No.
I just take care of
my little cousins, though.
Come on.
Where you going?
What you think
about this land here?
Well, I...
I likes it fine.
Mr. Wright...
He going to buy it, though.
He buying up everything.
Maybe.
Hey, anybody!
Hey, boy!
Yes, sir.
You a traveling man?
Who asking, sir?
We gots to help him.
He ain't our problem.
He a Mason,
took the oath, same as us.
He's a white Mason.
Do you think
he'd help you?
Aaron, boy, I swear,
sometimes you ain't got more
sense than some of these horses.
Now, I'm telling you...
that man...
he ain't nothing
but trouble.
Yeah, well, let me
tell you something.
See, I ain't no boy.
See, I's a man.
I's a Mason.
What you be, Sam?
Everybody sit down.
Let's get this done.
Bradley, you got the deed?
Uh, yes, sir, I do,
Mr. Andrews.
No, no, boy,
I haven't paid for it yet.
We got to sell it first.
Here. Give it here.
Give it here, boy.
We gots here 5 acres
in Rosewood...
adjacent to
Mr. Johnny Wright's store...
sold as is,
cash only.
Let's open up
at $52 an acre.
52, 52. Who'll give me
52 down front?
53, 53, 53
from Monroe.
54, 54, 54.
Who'll give me 54?
54, 54.
John Wright again.
Thank you, John.
55, 55.
55, anybody?
Monroe, 55?
$54.
Going once,
going twice...
$55.
Boy, you know that's
$55 for each acre?
That's damn near $300.
Yes, sir, I do.
Thank you kindly.
Cash?
Where's that nigger going to get
that kind of money?
I have $55.
Get back to work.
Afternoon, Miss Fanny.
Help!
Help me!
Somebody please
help me!
Somebody!
Help me!
Help!
Please!
Help me!
What's the matter, now?
Please help me!
Help me!
What's going on?
Fanny, what happened?
Nigger.
It was a nigger.
What?
He broke in my house,
and he beat me up.
It was a nigger!
It was!
Sheriff! Sheriff!
Here comes
that boy again.
That would be Emmett.
Sheriff!
Take a breath, boy.
What's the matter?
Your daddy's still
caught on fire again?
Fanny Taylor got herself
beat by a nigra.
Oh, shit.
Damn.
Earl, that
scatter gun loaded?
No.
Where the hell's my...
my shells?
Can't find my damn shells.
Here.
Go to the mill.
Get James.
Hold on!
Keep this quiet before
I get the whole story. Go.
- What's going on?
- Mind your own damn business.
Come on, boy.
When I want you
to do something...
and I tell
you to do it...
Fanny Taylor's been
raped by a nigger.
Go on out there
and do that!
Hey, James, I need
to talk to you.
Your wife's been beat and raped
by a colored man.
What the hell
you talking about?
57.50.
$58.
58.50.
$60.
Boy, how you planning
on paying $300?
You got a bagful of gold?
Could be, sir.
Henry...
can't you see
what this boy's doing?
He ain't going
to buy nothing.
He's just driving up the price
for old Bradley.
Mr. Andrews, sir,
I don't know that man.
With all due
respect, Mr. Wright...
if that what you believe,
maybe you should
stop bidding.
You gonna let that nigger
beat you, Johnny?
60 goddamn 50.
A nigger raped
Fanny Taylor.
Listen up.
We got to call
this off for now.
What? I ain't going nowhere.
I got a bid in.
We'll pick it up
tomorrow at $60.50.
Let's get this done now.
John, Fanny Taylor's
been raped by a nigger.
My deed.
I'll lock up the deed.
Boy, your name
Jesse Hunter?
No, sir.
I suppose you
can prove that?
Got my discharge, sir.
Just who do you think
you are, boy?
With all due respect,
Mr. Wright,
long around
this time tomorrow,
I expects to be
your neighbor, sir.
Welcome to
Levy County, Mr. Mann.
Get out of the way.
Come on, back off, now.
Come on, come on, come on.
Jesus, Fanny.
Who raped you?
No, jeez, Ellis,
I sure wasn't raped.
I just got beat.
I was beat badly.
Badly.
He was so big.
He's so black,
that boy.
She says she was raped.
Raped and beat.
Shut up, y'all!
Everybody go on out of here!
Show's over!
You heard me!
Go on home!
Go on!
Come on.
Let's go in the house.
It's OK.
It's all right.
It's OK. Come on!
Give her some breathing space!
Damn.
Listen to me.
We've known each other
a long time, huh?
I want you to think
about this, now.
You tell me.
This is Ellis.
You tell me the truth.
Was it truly a colored
that done this to you?
Be sure, darling,
that is all I'm saying.
Yes, he was colored.
He was a nigger,
nigger, nigger!
Jesus, angel,
what happened?
You seen
this boy, Sarah?
Ain't got to mess around. We
got to do something about this.
No, Mr. Ellis.
I ain't seen nothing.
All right.
Hey, what y'all doing?
Miss Fanny... Miss Fanny Taylor,
she got raped.
- And beat.
- And she got beat,
and she said it was
a colored man.
But it was a cracker.
I seen him.
Well, I guess now we're looking
for a nigger convict,
escaped yesterday
off the chain gang near Wylie.
Name is Jesse Hunter.
Oh, good.
Here are the hounds.
Take them all around back,
pick up a scent.
Go on.
You acting like you the leader
of this here mob.
I am the leader,
and this ain't no mob!
We got him, boys.
See where they're headed?
Y'all see where
they're headed?
Come on, boy.
Shut up, y'all!
They got a scent!
Hush.
Go have a look.
Y'all go that way.
He ain't done nothing!
What did the boy do?
Y'all be quiet!
Be quiet!
Poly! Poly!
Put that gun away!
- This is serious business.
- Yes, sir.
You got to tell me
the truth, boy.
Did you rape
Fanny Taylor?
- Rape?
- No, sir! No!
Do you know who did?
I don't know nothing,
Mr. Walker!
You know who did!
Go!
My boy ain't done nothing!
Hey! Here comes
old Johnny Wright.
Hello, Johnny.
Hey, Bobby.
John.
How's that new wife
of yours working out?
She's coming
right along.
Sorry about that auction, John.
The boy bid.
Yeah, a hell of a thing.
What you got here?
Now we got
a good one.
That boy raped
Fanny Taylor.
Is that right?
We got us
Aaron Carrier, John.
Aaron Carrier?
Watch that gun, boy.
How you doing, Johnny?
You got the wrong boy.
Hate to tell you, Aaron Carrier
wouldn't rape a fly.
Dogs led us
straight to his house.
You know the boy that did?
Nigger won't talk,
either, John.
I know his family.
Let me talk to him.
Yeah, hell, maybe you can
get something out of him.
I sure as hell can't.
Aaron, this is Mr. Wright.
You know something
about all this?
Duke, how's he
supposed to talk
when you're choking him
like that?
Well, he don't need
to talk, Johnny.
He need to hang from
one of them trees over there.
Y'all think
this is real funny?
Hey, you would, too, if you was
the one that sold me this rope.
Good point, John.
He's a good boy.
He ain't done nothing.
Duke, don't hurt him.
Emmett, come on over here, boy.
Hold onto this rope.
There's a boy.
You know this boy's
family as well as I.
That's right.
I do. I know.
And you know
he's a good boy.
They're good people.
They're good people,
but we got a dilemma
here, John.
We got a dilemma. I'm going
to tell you what it is.
Hounds don't lie.
Be a man, now.
You got to take that rope
and snap, crack.
Can't lynch that boy, Ellis.
Can't lynch him.
I ain't going to let
nobody get hanged.
I ain't going to let it happen.
It won't happen.
Now grab that rope.
Come on, grab it.
About 4 summers ago,
I went over to Chiefland.
A colored boy over there
was looking in the window...
at a white girl
watching her take a bath.
Did he say something?
No, he didn't.
Maybe he don't know nothing
if he didn't say nothing.
You should have seen them
go crazy on that boy.
Beat him
about half to death.
Boy wouldn't stop
screaming.
We helped him to the railroad
track. Number 7 come along...
cut his head clean off.
Niggers don't run around
like a chicken.
Once that head's off,
he's dead.
S-Sam Carter.
Sam Carter?
What about Sam Carter?
What about Sam?
Sam the blacksmith?
Sam Carter
raped Fanny Taylor?
No.
A man. A Mason.
What man?
Who you talking about?
Sam took him in the wagon.
We was holding the oath.
What are you
talking about?
String him up!
This boy's under arrest!
I'm taking him to jail!
We're going to string
this boy up.
Oh, no, you ain't!
All right, take the boy,
but don't you let him go.
Hey, don't you worry about
what I am or ain't going to do!
You hear me, Poly?
- We're going to get Sam.
- You get on out of here!
Do you understand?
You go do it!
Hey, listen to me.
You go with them.
Don't let them do nothing until
I get there, you hear me?
You go, too.
Ellis, you go.
I'll take old Aaron in.
Them boys is all riled.
Aaron, this is
all your damn fault!
You should've said
something earlier!
Damn!
Carter! Carter!
Hey, Booker T.
Up, boy. Up.
Thank you, Mr. Wright.
Sam, what you know about
this Jesse Hunter, boy?
I don't know nothing,
Mr. Andrews!
All niggers don't know nothing!
Where's Jesse Hunter?
Mr. Purdy. Mr. Purdy.
You a Mason.
You got to believe me.
I don't know
no Jesse Hunter!
Yeah, you do,
you damn nigger!
Come on, let him go!
Come on! Hold it! Come on!
He's not against you!
Stop it! Stop it!
You shut up and get away!
Sam! Get up!
Talk now!
Talk to me, Sam!
Talk to me.
Better say something.
As...
as God is my witness,
I don't know...
Jesse Hunter.
It was that drifter. That rich
nigger from the auction!
That big buck
with the black horse,
is that him?
Come on, let him talk.
Damn you!
Look at me!
Aaron told us
you gave him a ride!
Now you show me
where you put him out!
Show me, Sam.
I can get you out of here.
Show me, boy.
You going to show me?
We going to string you up.
Let's go. Get up.
If we don't pick up
his trail where you say,
you one dead
black son of a bitch.
What you got, Earl?
Nothing, Ellis.
Nothing?
Y-you can kill me...
but you all...
you can't eat me.
You ain't
no Seminole, boy.
Duke.
Get back! Get back!
Damn it, Duke!
What'd you do that for?
Goddamn, Duke.
Dumb son of a bitch.
You could've killed me!
He's sure dead.
He ain't dead.
Well, let's
clean this mess up.
Hang him up in this tree
over here.
OK, men, I've had
enough of this!
I'm the law here,
you hear me?
Let me in here!
Back off now!
Let me in there!
Stop it, y'all!
Stop it!
A white woman
was beat and raped...
by a colored boy!
Now, you want to tell
her husband, her children,
that this boy don't
have to pay for that?
I'm supposed
to uphold the law!
Aw, law!
Whose law, nigger law?
You wasn't nothing but
a damn chicken farmer...
till they gave you
that stupid badge!
You want to get re-elected?
You want
to get re-elected?
- Leave me alone!
- Then leave it be!
I got your watch,
Sam Carter!
I got your watch!
You're always so gentle.
Soft touch.
You treat me like
I'm some kind of angel.
You are
an angel to me.
I'm just a woman, James.
I'm just a woman.
Things are getting crazy
out there, Fanny.
They're likely
to get worse.
Sam Carter's
lynched already.
The blacksmith?
What'd he do?
He give that nigger a ride.
A ride?
Sam Carter?
I didn't know.
There's things that
I ought to tell you.
Evening, Mr. Taylor.
With all that's going on
and everything,
we thought y'all could use
some hot cooking.
Thank you kindly, ladies, but
my wife ain't feeling too well.
It's all right, James.
Evening, Miss Walker.
Oh, Fanny...
you poor child.
Oh, I brought you
a quilt, too.
I brought you
sweetbread.
Don't you worry.
That nigger going to be dead...
before you
finish your pie, OK?
Get a wagon.
Now, me and Mr. Mann just cut
Sam Carter out a damn tree.
Y'all hear me?
Dirty, low-down
bastards...
took my boy.
They got my cousin
Aaron over in jail.
There's Sumner
behind this business.
They say it's for
his own protection.
Now how that sound?
What we need to do, we need
to pray. Now, dear Lord...
I ain't in no praying mood,
preacher.
Now, what I want to
know is right now,
what y'all mens prepared to do
if they run back here?
Not if, Sylvester. When.
I'm goin' to shoot.
Come on, sit down now,
Big Baby.
You by yourself
there, Mr. Wright?
I am, Sylvester.
Sylvester, them crackers
so riled up,
we don't know
what they going to do.
They don't know what
they goin' to do.
That's how
a lynch mob be.
Now, I say we send
the women and children...
to Gainesville right now.
John, we can't go nowhere
and leave that boy in jail.
No! Them dirty bastards...
can take my boy
out of that jail...
and hang him whenever
they take a notion.
Don't worry about it,
Uncle.
We ain't going nowhere.
We ain't going nowhere,
Bradley.
Now, we own this here land.
We pay taxes on it.
Now, we don't bother
nobody around here.
We keep to ourselves.
Now, colored folk just
can't be running all the time.
There comes a time
when you got to stand up...
and defend your rights.
Sylvester! Sylvester!
Listen to me. And you listen.
Hold on there
for a minute.
We got to think about
these here children.
Oh, I am thinking about
the children, preacher.
Now, you suppose they thinking
about our children?
Mr. Mann.
If there be some trouble
around here, sir,
we could sure use
your help.
I just came
from one war, friend.
I ain't looking
for another one.
Let him go, Sylvester.
For all we know,
he could have been...
the one that done this thing.
They said it was... they said
it was a stranger anyhow.
You're talking crazy
now, preacher.
I wish y'all luck.
He ain't done nothing.
What was that,
Aunt Sarah?
Mr. Wright, would you
kindly excuse us, sir?
I seen his face.
He was white as butter.
What?
This what they teach you
in the Army?
Pack up and run
when things get hot?
Thank God the Navy
don't let in...
What? Go on and
say it, Mr. Wright.
Thank God the Navy
don't let in niggers.
I was going
to say cowards.
That's right.
I got you figured, Mann.
You one of them
loud boys, big talk.
Figure you can say anything
to a white man...
as long as you start out saying,
"With all due respect."
First sign of trouble,
you duckin' your head running.
What you going to do...
when that mob come
down the road?
You going to grab up
your rifle,
defend colored folk?
What you care?
Man does what he has to.
Ain't that right?
Just like a colored boy
back from the war...
with a pocketful of money.
Ain't that right?
You the massa
of Rosewood, huh?
Say, boy...
these people know me.
They trust me.
How long you live here,
Mr. Wright?
Nine years.
I been in Rosewood
one night...
they asking me to stay.
Now, you pack up
your truck...
see who tries to stop you
from leaving.
You wasn't going
to say nothing.
You was just going
to leave me?
Three, four weeks,
this all blow over.
Then I come back.
But I thought we...
Why, I didn't think you was
just going to run off, is all.
Ain't you a soldier?
Scrappie.
Them boys looking
for a colored man...
ain't nobody seen
around here before.
Now, ain't no way
in the world...
one man got enough bullets
for all them crackers.
Your own preacher
ready to serve me up.
But if I stay,
I'm asking to be hung.
Look here.
They give me this
for saving lives.
Most important thing
anybody ever give to me.
You keep it for me.
Hold on to it
till I get back.
Now, can you do that
for me, darling?
Morning, Judge.
Multiple gunshot wounds.
Missing ear...
fingers...
various other parts.
By Jesus, your boys really
got to this one, huh, Ellis?
Yes, they did, sir.
Levy County is growing.
We need us
a sheriff up here...
who can handle
these nigger problems.
Is that you, Ellis?
Now hold on, Judge.
Oh, I think I got everything
under control now, Judge.
I hope so.
We ain't talking about...
breaking up fights
on Saturday night.
You can't control
your colored,
we're going to replace you
with someone who can.
Cause of death:
"Mischief at hands unknown..."
Write that down, Earl.
All right now!
Get on in here!
Fall in here, everybody!
Now, hush up!
Everybody, come on, now!
Don't lollygag!
I want to give you
a day off.
What's that, Boots?
He says you
got the day off.
All right!
That colored boy
what assaulted Fanny Taylor,
he's still out there
somewhere.
So I'm gonna give you
the day off...
so you can go help
with the search.
All I expect is...
if you find him...
well, you know what to do.
Oh, Lord, Auntie,
they're likely to come
in here and kill us all.
You got to tell them
that man was white.
Child, you don't think...
they going to listen
to old Aunt Sarah?
They'd just as soon as
string me up...
like they done Sam Carter.
You ain't never seen crackers
act the way I know.
When I was a little girl,
about 7,
still on the Willowbrook
plantation...
old massa's son stole $20
out of the family chest...
for a cockfight.
Massa knew he took it.
As blue as Jesus' eyes,
he knew.
But just the same...
he whipped my daddy
half to death.
It don't matter what man
was beating on Fanny Taylor.
Nigger.
It's just another word
for guilty.
Here you go.
Thank you, Mr. Bryce.
You're welcome.
You're a nice gentleman.
Look, why don't you get your
peoples on board, Aunt Sarah?
Take them up
to Gainesville for a while.
Don't much like the looks
of things around here.
Things been
looking the same...
as long as I can remember,
Mr. Bryce.
You take care of yourself.
Take that.
Put it on the side there.
Board!
Sylvester?
- Go inside the depot, Mama.
- Sylvester!
Mama, it's all right.
Mama, go on.
Johnny.
Sylvester!
Do you know the whereabouts
of this Jesse Hunter?
I do not.
You arrest that man
who kill Sam Carter yet?
Don't you get
uppity with me.
I've come to warn you.
There are some boys
over there in Sumner...
let on if they was you,
they wouldn't let sundown
catch them around here.
Well,
they ain't me... sir.
Why don't you be
a good boy...
and go visit some
of your other relatives...
for a little while, huh?
I am trying
to help you here.
They're all over there right now
getting all full of liquor...
and making nooses.
You hear me!
Huh?
Sheriff...
If you really
want to help...
I appreciate it
if you wouldn't allow...
them boys to come
'round here.
Now, I was born and raised
in Rosewood.
This here is my home.
And I'll be damned if I let
anybody run me off it.
Now, you can tell
them boys that.
Tell them
your damn self.
Damn colored fool.
Go home, Mama.
You're gonna have to
settle your account...
before I can
sell you the shells.
Want me
to settle the account?
That's right.
All right.
Go home, Jewel.
Girl, you best
get out of this store.
She belongs here.
She belongs right here.
Do you see
how you do my cousin?
Get out this store
right now, Jewel! Get!
Can't you listen
to nobody?
Sheriff give you good advice.
Why ain't you leaving?
I thought you a smart boy,
Sylvester.
I thought you
a smart boy.
Here is your money,
Mr. Wright.
That should settle
my account.
Sylvester...
Dumb...
Hurry up!
Here come them boys.
They ain't got nothing.
What'd you find?
Snakes and ticks.
Them colored folks
got to be hiding that nigger.
What time is it,
anyway?
Well, let's see...
by old Sam Carter.
Bourbon time.
I'll tell you, boys.
If anybody's hiding
Jesse Hunter,
my money's
on Sylvester Carrier.
That nigger,
he hates us white folk.
He does.
You know,
he's got a piano.
A nigger
with a goddamn piano.
I've been working
all my life,
I ain't got a piano.
You don't know
how to play one.
That ain't the point.
Old man Cummer,
up in that house of his,
he's got a piano.
That nigger's got one,
and I don't.
Now, how does that look?
Yeah, and he's married
to that white woman.
Gertrude ain't white.
Hell, she look white.
Well, she ain't.
She's half Negress,
half-Seminole Indian.
He says.
It wouldn't surprise me
if he was hiding that bastard.
Hey, Judge.
I tell you, Duke.
Can I get that bottle?
Go ahead now,
make a wish.
Blow the candles out.
Open this one first, Arnett.
Open that one.
Oh, yeah,
that's nice, Mama.
Yeah, that's real nice.
You're a man now.
You need a suit of clothes.
Arnett, open this one here
and that one, too.
Sylvester got that one.
Simmer down.
Be quiet!
Sylvester, come on
out here now, boy.
We want to talk
to you.
Bring that Jesse Hunter
on out here with you.
Yeah, that's right.
Bring that boy with you.
Jesse and Sylvester are probably
sitting up in there.
Shut up
that damn dog.
Sittin' up there now
eating pork chops.
Laughing at us all.
Goddamn, Duke!
Son of a...
You had no call
to do that.
It's just a damn dog,
Ellis.
I'll have
no more shooting.
How you expect the boy
to come out here...
if you're going
to shoot his hound?
Hell of a shot!
Sylvester!
You'd better get out here now.
Wait, Mama!
Mama, hold on!
Get out the window, Mama.
All right. I'm gonna
go get the guns, Mama.
You stay
out the window.
No, Sylvester!
Mama, just stay out
the window.
Y'all children
get down right now.
Get down under the table
right now.
Scrappie, Gertie,
you keep these kids down.
Big Baby, get down!
Get down!
We don't want to talk to you.
We want to talk to your boy.
Boys, why don't y'all
go on home?
Miz Sarah, we want
to talk to Sylvester.
You get him out here!
Right now!
Mr. Walker, my boy don't know
nothing about this business.
You let him
tell us that.
Let Jesse Hunter
tell us something.
Boys, I know y'all.
I was midwife to more
than half of you...
and some
of your young ones.
Bring that boy
out here now!
I done seen you come up
from babies to now.
Ain't nothing
going to come of this.
It don't make sense.
My Sylvester ain't had nothing
to do with this mess.
We ain't never known
no Jesse Hunter.
I was there
with Miss Fanny.
I seen the man's face
as plain as day.
And most of you mens know that
that man was white!
Who fired that shot?
You tell me right now.
I told you
no more shooting.
Didn't I tell you that?
Aunt Sarah.
Poly, get back here!
Shut up, Walker.
Quit squealing
like a stuck pig.
I'll take this boy out myself.
Damn you,
get back here!
Pledge your souls
to hell!
Get back under there.
Stay there! Stay down!
Get inside, son.
Go on inside.
Hold your fire!
Think we got him?
I don't know.
We gonna need
more bullets.
You go and tell,
tell the judge
what happened here.
Go!
Rest of y'all men, get back!
Go on. Stay low.
I'm right here.
I'm right here, Mama.
Hold on!
Hold on, OK, Mama?
I'm right here.
Don't try to talk,
Mama, don't try to talk.
Don't...
Don't let them
s-s-surround you, baby.
It's all right.
I won't, Mama.
You just hold on, OK?
Mama, no, hold on.
Mama, hold on.
Y'all take what you need
and no more!
You hear me?
Y'all hear me?
How am I going
to be paid for all this?
You just keep track,
that's all.
Y'all shoot Sylvester,
Ellis?
Don't know.
They shot Aunt Sarah,
though, John.
Aunt Sarah!
What the hell's
the matter with you, Ellis?
You let them come here
and shoot an old woman?
I didn't let them do that.
You call that
upholding the law?
What kind of sheriff
are you?
Henry and Poly are dead.
Shot by them damn nigras.
Where'd Sylvester
get his ammunition, John?
All right, come on.
Come on. Hurry up!
Hurry up!
Come on! Come on!
Take those babies,
go hide in the woods.
Y'all babies going
to get in the woods now.
Go on!
Go hide in the woods.
Go on. Hurry up.
Sylvester,
I ain't leaving you.
Gertie, they gonna
come back here...
and try to kill all of us.
You and Scrappie got to go hide
these children in the swamp.
We can't take the babies
out there. It's freezing!
There ain't no place else.
Go on and get out of here.
What about Aunt Sarah?
Just go on and get, girl!
Come on. Let's go.
Gertie. I'll be there.
You got to go. You got to go.
Come on,
Big Baby, get!
I can shoot,
Sylvester.
Big Baby gonna shoot.
All right.
All right. Come on.
How many are there
in the house?
Sylvester, Jesse Hunter,
James Carrier.
Probably that drifter.
Yeah, Rodney. Listen.
You get together
all the men you can find...
and you hightail it
to Sumner.
Now, you make sure
they bring rifles.
What happened?
Three dead white men
is all.
We done got ourselves
a goddamn nigger revolt up here.
Hold your fire!
There he is!
I think I got him!
Hold your fire!
Goddamn you!
Burn!
Light 'em up!
Some of y'all
pick Henry and Poly up.
That Sylvester?
You son of a bitch!
You want me
to burn her, too?
Couple y'all men,
come over here.
I want y'all to carry her down
to the nigger graveyard.
Go on!
I'll do it
if you make me deputy.
You're deputy now.
Go on, pick her up.
Hey, boys,
I'm a deputy!
Hold on to that now.
Grab the other side.
Hold on, Bobby.
Hold on.
This wasn't
supposed to happen.
She worked
in my damn house, Ellis.
Then give her a decent
Christian burial, James.
You men, grab that end.
Damn, what did
this old crow eat?
Come on, lift it up!
Look out now!
Look out!
Aunt Sarah
come in the morning.
She clean up.
Aunt Sarah ain't coming.
No. You right.
It's Sunday.
Aunt Sarah
ain't comin' no more.
No more, no never.
She's dead.
Sylvester, too,
dead as hell.
Sam Carter.
Half of Rosewood's dead,
and they ain't caught
your nigger yet!
Sarah...
Why they hurt
that old woman?
She never done nothin'
to nobody.
Y'all need
to come on down here.
We're gonna need some help.
Some colored beat and raped
a white girl.
Yeah, them niggers need
to be put in their place.
Hell, they done forgot
who they are.
I'm gonna get me one.
We're gonna string up
all them darkies.
Yes, we'll gather
at the river
The beautiful,
the beautiful river
Gather with the saints
at the river
That flows...
Y'all hear what happened
in Rosewood?
A colored boy
killed four white men...
and raped three
white women.
Soon we'll reach
the shining river
Soon our pilgrimage
will cease
Soon our happy hearts
will quiver
With the melody of peace
Yes, we'll gather
at the river
The beautiful,
the beautiful river...
Right over there!
There he is!
Get him!
On that horse!
Give me my gun!
Jesse! You were better off
on that chain gang, boy!
There he is!
Let's go, boys!
Come on! Get him!
Move it!
Let's get out
of here.
Drop that gun!
Get them horses
out of here!
Hey, you hold
that horse down!
Now, get him on over there!
Go on!
Oh, Ellis,
let 'em run!
Let 'em run! Howdy-do!
Ooh, here come the parade.
Hey, listen up! Come on!
Come on over here!
Come on!
15 niggers jumped us
in the woods!
They was armed
to the teeth!
What? They bump
you in the head?
Sure enough did!
You go on
and get them, then!
Let's all get 'em!
- Was it back there?
- Back yonder.
Go now!
Hey, Ellis, you got
a phone call, Ellis.
Not now, Earl!
It's the governor, Ellis.
Pretty exciting stuff,
huh, Ellis?
Go right inside, Timothy.
See the nigger?
They got him.
No. You've got
to look and see.
You've got to
remember this.
It's somethin' you've got
to remember. Look.
What? What?
Mr. Wright,
you have to hide me.
You are crazy.
I can't run.
Mr. Wright, I don't know
where my boys are,
and my baby girl
is somewhere...
in the woods.
Mr. Wright...
they killed my Virginia.
They find you here,
they'll burn my store.
You best run
hide in the woods.
I can't run!
I got shot
through my side.
I can pay you.
We'll put you in
the back storeroom.
Thank you.
We'll talk about that
deed later, Bradley.
God bless you,
John Wright.
Get some clean
white rags, blanket.
Here they come.
What are you fellas
doing in the road?
Hold steady, boys.
You can back up
right now!
Move them trucks out!
Come on!
You know
what to do now.
We got business
to take care of!
OK, now...
Get them trucks
out the road!
- Turn around!
- What are you boys doing?
You need to get on
out the road!
We got business to take
care of over there!
Turn around!
You ain't bringing all this
into our town.
Oh, yeah, we are.
We're looking for a colored
fugitive name of Jesse Hunter.
Our coloreds
are law-abiding folk!
Bronson don't want you.
Now turn around!
What are you all going down
on us for?
Y'all gonna
protect niggers?
That ain't no way
to treat a white man!
Oh, hell,
he ain't here.
I'm gonna remember this!
Now, go on in there
with them.
Ready?
Hey, Bobby!
Hey, we're goin' back over.
You comin'?
Yeah.
I'll be along in a bit.
You save me some.
Them niggers, they runnin'
like chicken, boy!
They in the swamp now.
We're gonna get 'em!
Them's church bells.
My daddy's ringin' 'em.
Them crackers
be ringin' them bells.
Now, you stay put, you hear?
No. That's my daddy
in his church.
He tellin' us
it's safe to come home.
No, Denny, Lee Ruth...
Maybelle!
Denny, come back here.
Denny, no.
Come back here.
Bust it up, boys!
Bust it all up, now!
Bust it all up!
Niggers!
Come on. Git.
That's a fire, now,
ain't it?
Well, look,
this come out perfect here.
13.
Then you pull that
through there, see?
Now, you pull
on one of those.
That's perfect.
That's good.
There you go.
Pull tight.
There you go. That's good.
Now you've got it, boy.
There's your noose.
Now you make one.
Just like this one.
Oh, that's a good one.
That's a good one.
Good boy.
Here. Use these
and cover yourself up.
It's all right.
You're all right.
Scrappie, I'm freezing.
Scrappie, I'm hungry.
Quiet, y'all!
They're gonna hear us.
They done
killed everybody.
Aunt Sarah,
Big Baby, Sylvester.
Scrappie.
Look.
It's more than 50 children
hidin' around in the swamp,
and they been
out here all night...
with nothing to eat,
and they're cryin',
and they're freezin'.
What we gonna do?
Y'all be quiet now.
Now, hush!
Hush. Just hush.
Stop fighting.
Arnett...
Front and center.
Quit crying, Arnett.
You ain't a little boy
no more. You a man.
Now, you see any tears
in these eyes?
I need you to be strong.
You're my lieutenant,
understand?
Yes, sir.
Now, you gather up
these women and children.
You're gonna move deep
into the swamp.
All right.
We gots to move.
Get up.
Come on. Get up.
Come on. Move.
Let's go. Move!
I knew you'd be back.
It's gonna
be all right.
Let's move it.
Get him up.
Oh, he's bad.
He ain't gonna
last out here.
Emma, there ain't nothin'
the matter with me.
- I can walk.
- Daddy.
There ain't
no place to go.
You come too late!
All right, Timothy.
Upstairs with the Turners.
Put him upstairs, too,
in the front.
That's enough.
Let's go. Upstairs.
Everyone upstairs!
And clean this place up.
Look at this.
Clean this up.
Oh, my God!
This is not happening.
What's the matter
with you?
I know you don't...
I know you don't like having
colored folks in the house,
but this
is a serious time.
Is that what you think,
that I don't like livin' here
'cause of the colored folks?
Is that what you think?
Well, what is it, Mary?
I am caring for the colored
folks in my home!
It's my home, too.
I know.
Yes, it's your home.
You all treat me like
a guest in my own house.
I got news for you,
John Wright.
Carol is dead.
She's dead.
She ain't comin' back,
and I ain't leavin'.
Oh, God!
Put me down.
Put me down!
Emma!
Put me down.
I hear you're hiding folk,
Mr. Wright.
I need you to put away
old James here.
You're misinformed.
You best take him.
Go hide in the woods.
No. I don't want
to go in there.
Take him, and go
hide in the swamp.
I ain't gonna
go in that house!
- John Wright?
- What?
I know what you been
doin' with my daughter.
What?
- Hush now.
- I can run like you.
No, you can't.
Now, you gonna get us killed.
Just hush!
Come on, Mr. Wright.
You the massa
around here.
I ain't a massa
of nothin'.
You best git
while you can.
- What's the matter, Mr. Wright?
- Git!
Don't he owe you enough
to save his life?
You son of a bitch.
How much it take for you
to hide this man?
$10? 15?
How about 60, goddamn 50?
I'm gonna blow
your head off!
This man's life
worth one acre of land?
Hide the man, John,
for God's sake.
Let him in.
Come on.
No, Mama.
Come on, baby.
No, Mama. It's all right.
You go on.
Go, Mama!
I'm all right.
I can't go in there, Mama!
Take care of Papa.
Come on!
Come on, now. Git!
Go.
I'll be all right, Mama.
What's the problem, boys?
What's the matter?
We want James Carrier.
Right now.
Well, I ain't seen him.
Hell, I ain't seen nobody.
Damn it, John.
We caught his daughter.
We know he's here!
What did y'all
peckerwoods do to her?
Where's she at, damn it?
Where's she at, Ellis?
Come on now!
It's her daddy we after!
Explain to me why you
want to lynch a cripple.
We ain't lynchin' nobody
don't need to be lynched, John.
I just don't see
no sense in it.
John, James Carrier
was in that house...
with Sylvester
and Jesse Hunter!
Yeah. We just want to ask him
a few questions, John.
That's all.
Well, that's all fine,
but I ain't got him.
All right, boys!
Stay back!
You get off my porch!
Get off my...
Don't you come near!
Simmer down!
Johnny,
you want these boys...
to go through
your wife and children?
Is that what you want?
Come on!
Bring him out!
We will!
That's what we're gonna do!
You give me your word,
all you want to do
is question him? Yes?
That's more like it!
Y'all wait here.
Get that nigger out here!
He was in the house
the whole time.
Get that damn nigger!
John!
John, where
are you going?
You're not going to let
those people have him?
Mary, please.
If I don't, they'll come
in here and shoot us all.
They just want to
ask him some questions.
I'll be with him to make sure
they don't do more than that.
I'll be with him.
Now, James...
We got old Sarah over here,
resting her soul.
If you don't tell us
where this Jesse boy is,
we're gonna have to put
you in there with her.
It's a big box!
Why ain't
my sister buried?
'Cause you ain't
buried her yet.
Dig a hole,
nigger.
I ain't got
but one good arm.
We ain't got
but one good shovel.
Come on. Get up here,
you old crow,
and dig your own hole.
Come on!
Show us what
you're made of.
Come on! Let's go!
Grab that shovel.
Let me see what you can do.
Get him goin'!
Whoa! He's eager, ain't he?
James, stop it.
Just trying to help him put
that shovel in the ground.
James, listen here.
I want you to tell these boys
where Jesse Hunter is.
He was in that house
with you, wasn't he?
Now, tell me, hear me?
Listen up.
James, you tell them
something, hmm?
James, look at me!
You tell them something,
for God's sake.
I'm pleading to you.
Sheriff,
I can't lie to you.
I ain't never met the man.
Fair enough.
Stop! Duke!
God! What's the matter
with you, Duke?
What the hell
is the matter with you?
Oh, hush up, John.
You done went and turned
nigger lover on us.
Ever since your wife
passed away,
you ain't been the same.
I'm goin' home, y'all.
Nigger lover, my ass!
You stupid
piece of white trash!
What did you call me?
Don't you nigger lover me,
you white trash!
Come on!
Think of who you are.
Think of what
you're saying.
Don't do this.
Nigger lover.
Nigger lover!
Whose side you on,
Johnny Wright?
Don't even care a white man
got shot!
You forgetting
who you are, Johnny?
Go home, Johnny.
You go home right now.
You got the money
that man owes me?
Y'all gonna pay me for
all the money I'm losing?
Hell, no!
Killin' all
of my customers,
runnin' 'em off.
You watch who you
call white trash, boy!
That's right.
Just 'cause you rich
off nigger money,
you think you better
than all the rest of us?
That's right!
You get all the money
in Florida, Johnny Wright,
you still ain't nothin'...
but a dirt-floor cracker!
Shopkeeper!
Hey, now, wake up.
Come on.
Come on. We got to go.
Time to wake up.
We're going to go this way.
Gertie, where are we going?
Keep quiet.
We're going to go this way.
I ain't got no bullets.
Share!
Hey, y'all be quiet!
Y'all be quiet.
Want them crackers
to hear you?
Bring the train to the old road
near Kelly's pond.
Get there, listen
for the engine whistle.
That's on the other side
of Sumner, Mr. Wright.
How we gonna do that?
You're askin' us
to take these children...
through all
them crackers?
Can't stop near Rosewood.
It's Kelly's pond or nowhere.
No men on the train.
That's the plan.
How we know we can
trust you, Mr. Wright?
Got no choice.
In the trenches now.
8:00.
That's three hours.
Get these folks there.
I'll bring the train.
If you're lying,
I'm comin' for ya.
Soldier, if I'm lying,
you're dead.
Yes, sir.
We agreed
about the men?
Yes, sir.
That includes you.
Johnny, we just went through
there this morning.
It ain't nothin'
but ashes and smoke.
Town's in purgatory.
Billy, it's a real simple thing,
we do it right.
They got boys
on all the bridges,
all the main roads
lookin' for colored men.
We go in at night,
round back to Sumner,
pick up the women
and children,
sweep them off
to Gainesville.
He's talkin' about Sumner!
That's where the whole
damn thing started!
You're askin' us to risk
our engine, Johnny!
Who are you
Bryce brothers,
a couple of rich boys
playin' on your train?
To hell with you.
You boys puffin'
around the countryside...
wavin' and tootin'
your whistle?
To hell with you!
These are real folks dyin',
women and children ain't
done nothin' wrong to no soul.
That ain't fair,
Johnny!
Don't talk to me
about fair, Billy!
They shot Sarah Carrier down
like a dog on her own porch!
I ain't asking you
to risk your train!
I'm asking you to risk
your asses!
Think they gonna let the women
and children through?
I don't know.
Wait, wait.
Stay here.
Damn.
Let's go.
We gotta move.
How far out are we?
About 40 minutes.
Can't we move
this thing any faster?
Push that throttle, J.B.
Don't you be telling us
how to run our train, Johnny.
We gotta take it easy on her.
She ain't been acting right.
Oh, she ain't?
You boys been treating this
train like a little sister...
since I known you.
Get her moving.
She can't handle it!
Get this
son of a bitch moving.
J.B., give her a little.
Feel better?
Yeah.
I feel better.
I'm tired.
I don't feel like going.
Hush up.
Hush up, be quiet.
That truck coming, boys.
Watch out, now.
Watch yourself.
Get on up.
Come on.
Wait, wait.
Might as well
come look.
Make room
for my boy here.
Why you cryin', boy?
There's babies in there.
A nigger is a nigger, boy.
None of us like it.
God made the world
the way it is,
and we just got
to live in it.
You get as old as I am,
you become a man...
you're gonna learn
a lot of things.
A nigger is a nigger, boy.
That's the way.
You understand me,
Emmett?
You understand me?
She's overheating!
Damn it!
Damn it, I told you!
We're stopping,
we're stopping!
We can't stop.
No, no.
Don't you get it?
We are stopped!
We can't go anywhere!
It's your fault!
Your fault!
Goddamn
counterbalance pin!
Damn it!
J.B., leave him alone.
You gotta check the engine.
Don't you heathens
touch my porch.
Step aside.
We hear you're hiding niggers
in here.
Turn around, Earl, before I
send us both to damnation.
Jesus Christ, Mary.
That damn thing
ain't loaded anyway.
Oh, yes, it is.
You got any niggers
in there, Mary?
Willing to kill a white woman
to find out, Bobby?
Now turn around
and get home.
Get on, get!
Come on, Earl.
Ain't no niggers around here.
Come on, y'all.
Come on, now.
You men best hope the Lord feels
merciful come Judgment Day.
Hush.
Everybody
front and center.
Lieutenant.
Where's Arnett?
He gone.
Where's Minnie?
Stay put.
What y'all boys need to get
this engine running again?
Somethin' we ain't got.
Counterbalance pin.
What is
a counterbalance pin?
Oh, it ain't nothin'.
Piece of metal
about this long.
Be quiet.
Minnie, be quiet.
All right, y'all men, listen up.
Let's call it a night.
Bobby, Earl, give me a hand.
Get these men out of here.
Y'all go home.
Go on.
No more camping out in my town!
You hear me?
Hush, y'all, hush!
All right,
I see you in there.
What you up to, Duke?
What do you see?
Hold still, now. Right up
against that tree, y'all.
Go get him.
Minnie.
Minnie's back.
Where you been?
What...
He gonna get killed
looking for you.
Show you
to rape my wife.
Put him up!
Simmer down, y'all!
I had a nice quiet town here,
but you put an end to that,
didn't you, boy?
Wasn't no colored boy...
had nothin do to with
what happened there.
Shut up.
Shut up, Jesse.
That ain't my name.
Clear a path.
Get back, get back.
Run the nigger up.
Ha, damn you!
Come on,
you stupid horse!
Just shoot
the damn horse.
Booker T., go!
Goddamn.
That is one strong buck.
Why won't he die?
He gonna die, he gonna die.
His neck ain't that thick.
Oh, he'll die,
only he probably didn't have
nothing to do with it.
Well, truth be told,
none of 'em did.
What the hell
does that mean, Ellis?
It means, James,
that you know
as well as I do...
what Fanny'd been
doing lunch times.
Some of y'all know
better than others!
That's right.
Should have never
listened to her.
That woman's
a wildcat.
Booker T.!
Shoot him!
Sorry I had to say it
that way, James,
but this thing's gone
far enough.
Fanny lied...
to you, to me,
the whole damn town.
Deep down, I don't think
I believed her from the start.
If that's how you feel,
why'd you take her word
for this, Ellis?
What choice I got, huh?
I am the sheriff.
Damn.
My badge.
What's gonna
keep it in place?
Prayer.
Move it!
Come on, move!
Get on board, get on board,
get on board.
Get 'em on,
get 'em on!
Come on, move.
Get on, get on!
Come on. We ain't gonna sit
on the track all night.
Move!
Get them on!
Quickly!
Let's go!
Let's go. Let's get the hell
out of here.
You can't come on!
Let me on this train!
I said get down!
If they find men on this train,
they'll kill everyone!
Get off!
Please!
Stop the train!
Get back.
If they find men on this train,
they'll kill all
the women and children!
You can't come on here!
No!
Get down,
get down!
What the hell you doing?
This is a war!
We're in the trenches!
Jesus Christ!
Come on, girl.
Child, stay down.
Stay down.
Y'all can get up now.
You can't go, Mann.
You just can't.
Don't leave us, Mann.
Please don't leave us.
Hush now.
Y'all gonna be safe.
Scrappie in charge
from here on in.
Arnett, you're a lieutenant.
You help her out.
Take these
children inside.
Y'all gonna be all right.
That's Booker T.!
Mr. Mann, who is that
riding your horse?
It's Sylvester.
Uncle Sylvester made it.
All right! He made it.
Sylvester,
how you doing?
Uncle Sylvester's alive.
I ain't got all night, Mann.
Gertie, y'all get
to Cousin Wilma in Gainesville.
Come on.
I'll be waiting for you
in Gainesville.
Won't be waiting long.
How'd you get out?
They carried me...
in my mama's coffin.
They were here.
A mob.
They tried to get in.
What happened?
Mom scared 'em off.
Boys.
Come here!
Get up! Get up!
Liar!
Damn you, woman!
Where you going, boy?
You little crab.
You eat my food,
then you walk away sideways.
Emmett!
Emmett, come on back
in the house, boy.
L... I'm sick.
My hands is hurting me bad.
I need your help,
and my back...
Emmett, I don't mean
to be hard on you, boy.
I just want
what's best for you.
I want to learn you
how to live in the world.
I hate you!
You ain't no man!
I don't know
what you are, Daddy.
Emmett, you come
back... Emmett.
Don't you walk away.
Come on here, boy.
Emmett, come on
back in here.
Which way are you headed?
Same as you, friend.
Going to catch that train.