♪ Burn Notice ♪
The Fall of Sam Axe
Original Air Date on April 17, 2011
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
So, February 1, 2005.
0800 hours.
This begins the inquiry
into the mission herein
referred to
as "Operation
Provide Support."
Commander Axe, do you have
anything to say before we begin?
Uh, well, sir,
it's actually
more of a question
than a statement.
Can I have a beer?
You may not have a beer.
But you may stand up
and raise your right hand.
Do you swear to tell the truth,
the whole truth,
and nothing but the truth,
so help you God?
Yeah.
Uh, sir,
am I on trial here?
'Cause I got the word about
wearing the dress whites,
and now we're doing
the whole oath thing.
For now, this is not
an official legal proceeding.
Think of it
as an informal conversation
to sort out exactly
what happened here.
We've got
over a dozen casualties,
some structures destroyed,
a few vehicles destroyed.
This little disaster is gonna
take some serious sorting out.
I mean, that's why
I suggested the beer.
I'll ask you not to waste
my time, Commander Axe.
Now, can we begin?
You're the boss, sir.
Let's start with how
you first became involved
in this operation.
Ah.
Uh, that kind of depends.
There's kind of
the "official" beginning,
and then the "unofficial"
beginning.
You know what I mean?
Right, well, uh, okay.
This whole thing began...
in bed.
A couple weeks back,
I had just started seeing
a lady by the name of Donna.
Great gal.
Thing is, we were still
getting to know each other,
and it turned out, uh...
I didn't know her
as well as I thought.
Pretty good.
You should come by and teach
the teams a few moves.
You should teach my husband
a few moves.
Wait a second. Your husband?
You're married?
Oh, don't be that way.
It's fine.
Uh, well, no,
actually, uh...
It's not fine.
I kind of have a thing
about that.
He barely looks at me now.
It's like he's not even
my husband anymore. He's just --
oh, my God. He's here.
What?!
I don't understand!
He should still be in D.C.!
That's your husband?
You're married
to Admiral Maitland?
Just -- just go, okay?
No, no, not that way!
He'll see you!
No! The bathroom!
Well, it's been great.
Now, as a S.E.A.L.,
I've been involved in evasive
maneuvers, but this...
...Was an unusual
tactical situation.
Hey, Donna?!
What's the matter with Buster?
He's going crazy out here.
I don't know.
Still, same principles apply
in any hostile encounter
when you need to get out clean
without engaging the enemy --
identify an escape route...
Ooh!
...And blend seamlessly
into the surroundings.
Wait, wait --
how exactly does this relate
to the mission
in question?
Uh,
I'm getting there, sir.
This -- this is important,
I promise.
I just don't want to hear any
more of your romantic escapades.
Is there a point?
Okay, so, that night...
...I headed out.
Now, with this type of problem,
some men will duck and cover,
others will turn to booze.
Me? Let's just say I have
my own secret weapon.
I swear, every time I see you,
you look different.
Comes with the job, Sam.
Hey, nice tan, Mikey.
Where you been?
Someplace sunny.
Well, it agrees with you --
I remember how pasty you got
when we were stuck
back in Poland in '92.
Hey, how long you in town?
A few days of debriefing
at least.
We'll see.
So, not to impose, but you feel
like advising an old buddy
with a sticky situation?
How sticky?
Sticky like, let's get a table
and a few more rounds.
Sam.
An admiral?
It had to be
an admiral's wife?
Yeah. Yeah, yeah.
So, look, what do you think
I should do here?
Go to Maitland
and explain.
Tell him you didn't know
who she was
until things had already
gotten out of hand.
In fact,
call him right now.
Mike,
that's not what I --
look, I was more looking
for that super-spy advice
on how to keep this quiet.
You remember that thing in Kiev
with Misha?
When he sold out the wetwork
team on their way to Paris?
Hell, yeah.
What about that?
That's the kind of secret
that stays secret.
Because if it comes out,
people get sent to Siberia.
This will come out
as soon as Maitland
looks sideways
at his wife.
Seriously, Mike, you know,
I know you're a smart guy,
but you've dated,
like, one lady,
and she was
a frickin' psycho.
I'm just saying...
You may not be the expert
on this whole boy-girl thing.
My job is to know what people
are gonna do before they do it.
Which is how I know you're
not gonna take my advice
and this is gonna blow up
in your face, Sam.
I don't know.
I mean, how smart
can spies be, right?
You're always fighting
on the side with no guns.
There are certain rewards
to fighting on the side
with no guns.
Tell you what, one day,
you're gonna give me
some spy lessons, deal?
Deal.
Mm. I got to go.
You gonna be all right?
Yeah, I'll be fine.
Thanks for the beer.
Oh, and, Sam...
...Be careful.
So, I have a few more drinks
and head home,
figuring that maybe it's best
not to get relationship advice
from a spy.
Thing is,
turned out the spy was right.
Commander Axe?
You need to come with us.
Says who?!
You were in my house...
In bed with my wife!
And don't even try to deny it,
'cause I found your belt.
Does that look familiar?
I talked to Donna,
and she told me everything.
Admiral,
I was unaware, sir,
that she was your
significant other.
You were unaware?
You're a Navy S.E.A.L.!
You're trained
in battlefield awareness,
and you didn't see my name
on the mailbox?!
Well, sir, I wasn't exactly
in that frame of mind, sir.
A-as you can imagine,
I was otherwise occupied, sir.
I'll stop talking now,
sir.
So, I checked my docket
for an assignment
that would get you
out of my sight
for the foreseeable future.
And I think I found
just the thing.
Oh, not Siberia.
Please not Siberia.
You're going to Colombia.
Tonight.
Oh, sir,
with all due respect,
I'd need to pack, sir,
and, well, uh --
Are you refusing orders?
No, sir. No, sir.
Of course not.
It's just that I --
well,
it's been a while, sir.
And, of course,
for a mission in South America,
I should really brush up
on my Spanish.
Well, you got a 12-hour
plane ride, so...
...Brush up, amigo.
"Amigo."
That's "friend," right, sir?
Get the hell
out of my office!
So, like a good soldier,
the next morning
I was up bright and early
enjoying a first-class
plane ride down to Colombia.
Hey!
What the hell
are you wearing, brother?
I got issued these.
You do know most of Colombia
is green, right?
Yeah, I don't think
the guy who issued them
wanted me to blend in.
Can you turn that crap off?
You know, I was
supposed to be takin'
some Green Beret named Donohue
down on this mission.
Heard he got drunk
and set a tank on fire.
Guess you screwed up
even worse, huh?
Yeah, it would seem so.
What did you do?
Must have been
something crazy, man!
Look, I don't
want to get into it, okay?
Suit yourself.
Good luck, big guy!
Yeah, thanks.
I read over the mission.
Essentially I was going down
to check on reports
of unrest in the region.
Basically,
a local Colombian official
with connections in the states
called in a few favors.
He needed someone to observe
and report on a situation
so he could scare up
some U.S. military aid.
And I was the lucky guy
who got to do the observing
and reporting.
So, I read the file, but I was
hoping you could fill me in
on the basics
of the situation.
I was dropped into this
a little...suddenly.
This group, the so-called
"Espada Ardiente,"
has been staging serious attacks
all over this countryside.
And the situation is getting
only worse and worse.
We need help.
Espada Ardiente.
Is that some kind of homegrown
insurgent group?
Yes. Actually,
we don't know much about them.
There's someone
I would like you to meet.
Will you follow me,
please?
Commandante Veracruz!
Let me introduce
Commander Axe.
It is a pleasure,
Commandante Veracruz
has worked before with American soldiers.
He is at your disposal.
I believe we have
mutual acquaintances.
I trained at the school
of the Americas in '92.
Well, hell,
if you trained there in '92,
I knew every last
son of a bitch
that made you do push-ups
in the mud.
Vick Rayburn.
No, no, no. You mean...
"The terror."
That's the guy.
..."The terror." Of course.
So, what's the plan?
We have intelligence
that Espada Ardiente
is planning to attack
an international clinic
run by a group
called "Doctors For All."
A hospital. Seriously?
Unfortunately, yes.
Until now, they have stayed
clear of civilian targets.
The clinic sits in a strategic
pass in the mountains.
We believe the terrorists
want to use it
to take control
of that region.
Our plan is for you
and Commandante Veracruz
to get there
before that can happen.
I trust we are
in good hands?
Of course.
Thank you, sir.
Goodbye.
Let's meet the guys.
Fantastic. Please.
Hello, señor.
Whoa, oh!
So it was the standard drill.
I met Veracruz's team.
And we headed out up the
mountains toward the territory
that this Espada Ardiente group
was occupying.
Spent a couple days
driving up and down mountains
and getting carsick.
Not much to report, at least
until we got further north
and started seeing
some of the places
these guys had attacked.
It was mostly little stuff --
blown-up vehicles,
burned campsites --
but it was enough
to make me think
we needed to get
to this clinic asap,
make sure nothing happened.
The clinic
was conveniently located
in the middle of nowhere.
After our long trek there,
I figured they'd offer us
a beer for our trouble.
But they weren't exactly happy
to see us.
Okay, this is --
this is just crazy.
Why would anyone attack the clinic?
I'm sorry, doctor.
But our intelligence indicates
there may be an attack.
And so what are we
supposed to do, hmm?
Uh, evacuate?
That would be best.
We can give you
until tomorrow to --
to -- to --
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Tomorr--
listen, I've got people in there
too sick to move.
Now, how am I supposed to
evacuate by t--
Okay. Hey, guys. Hey.
You know, let me handle this.
American to American.
I'm Canadian.
Uh, North American
to North American?
Look, you know, we're not trying
to bust your chops here,
but you're not gonna help your
patients if you guys get shot.
Listen, sir,
we don't have any problems
with the Espada Ardiente,
okay?
Un segundo, un segundo.
Okay, please.
So -- so just tell me,
how am I supposed to
evacuate my clinic by tomorrow?
Hey, Ben.
Hi.
Why don't you go
and take care of the patient?
And I've got this.
Yeah?
This way, soldier.
It's, uh, "Commander,"
actually.
Sorry about that.
Yeah,
what's his problem?
He's a doctor.
It's his job to cure people.
You're a soldier.
It's your job to kill them.
Take a wild guess what his
problem might be, bright eyes.
And you are?
Amanda Maples.
I'm with the local
food relief program.
We work out of the clinic.
Nice threads, by the way.
Really subtle.
Yeah. It's a long story.
Ah.
So, you want to talk
to your buddy in there?
'Cause you guys
could be in danger.
Yeah, I'll do my best.
For now, though,
we'd all really appreciate it
if you'd get lost.
'Cause if we weren't
a target before,
we definitely will be
if you guys don't leave.
As a soldier,
I can't just leave.
Sure you can. You just --
you get in the truck.
And you turn the key,
you put your foot on the
pedal -- it's on the floor --
and you go.
What's going on?
Who's the kid?
She may be with one
of the terrorists.
We caught her sneaking
into one of the trucks.
Aah!
Hey, hey.
Everybody
just calm down here.
Geez. Okay.
So, kid...
Okay, guys, come on.
She's just looking for something
to eat. Let's not go crazy.
It's not our mission to rough up
hungry teenagers, right?
No. Of course.
Of course. Of course.
Here you go, kid.
So, look,
I talked to the doctor
and the lady
from the food-aid program,
but they don't know anything
about an attack.
All I got out of them was a
polite invitation to screw off.
We will make camp nearby.
If there is an attack,
we will be ready.
Veracruz's camp
was pretty remote.
But let me tell you, his guys
were seriously well-armed.
I didn't know exactly
who we were up against yet,
but they had enough firepower
to wipe them off the map.
So I decided I'd just keep
my head down, do my job,
and make my reports to H.Q.
Like a good boy.
Commander Axe
for Admiral Maitland, please.
Yes, sir, uh, no contact
with any terrorists yet, sir.
We're a couple of miles
from the clinic.
Good. Carry on
as long as it takes.
Sir, what exactly does
"as long as it takes" mean?
It means "next time,
stay away from the wives
of ranking officers."
Uh...
See you in a few months.
Roger that.
Hey. Just calling to command
to let them know what's up.
Fantastic. Perhaps you would
like to relax, eat some supper?
My men and I are
going to scout the area.
Oh, good. Well, I'll go with
you. My gear's right in there.
Actually, señor, it is better
if you stay here.
Whoa. Stay here?
I mean, I can't exactly
observe and report
from the inside of my tent,
can I?
Come on, I can handle
a little night scouting, huh?
I'm sure you can,
Commander Axe.
But I am responsible
for your safety.
If we make contact
with the terrorists,
we will come for you
immediately.
This is where things
kind of started to go sideways.
You might want to mark that down
in your notes.
"Things went sideways."
So, what did you do?
I guess you could say
I modified my orders.
Well, señor...
Buenos noches.
So I decided to conduct
a scout of my own.
I did a basic perimeter check.
Searched for tire tracks,
signs of activity.
The only hostile forces I found
was a nest of spiders
as big as quarters.
And in the middle of fighting
those little bastards off,
I hear voices.
I go in, check it out,
thinking maybe it was
the Espada Ardiente guys.
But what do I find instead?
Veracruz,
unloading a bunch of weapons
from a hidey-hole
in the mountain.
I listen in
on their conversation,
and guess what I hear --
they're planning on attacking
the clinic themselves
and making it look
like the rebels did it.
And after I make my report...
We destroy the clinic then shoot
the American in the head.
Son of a bitch.
I bet lots of stuff
go bad in an operations.
But finding out
I was supposed to get killed
as part of a plot
to get U.S. military aid?
That was a new one.
So I just stayed calm
and made my way back to camp
as efficiently as possible.
Wait a minute.
Wait a minute. Wait a minute.
L-l-let's go back, here.
I'm confused.
Y-you're saying
you did not make contact
with Espada Ardiente
at this point?
- Because our reports indicate --
- Well, where did you get the reports?
From Veracruz's
paramilitaries?
And, what, you think
they were gonna announce
that they were
officially planning
on putting two in the back
of my head?
What I really
want to hear about
is how you were kidnapped
by terrorist forces.
Oh. Yeah, well,
that's not entirely accurate.
See, I couldn't let Veracruz
know that I was onto him.
So I put together
a little kidnapping scene
for them to find
and double-timed it
back to the clinic.
Man, what -- what the hell
are you doing down here, man?
It's 5:00 a.m.
You and me need to talk.
Now.
Okay, so,
I-I-I'm confused here.
Why would anybody
want to attack us?
Because it's a ploy.
If they can make
this terrorist group
look like they massacred
a clinic and killed yours truly,
Veracruz can do
anything he wants down here
and get a blank check to do it.
Right, but here's the thing --
we're not political. Okay?
I've never even heard
of the es-- w-what is it?
Espada Ardiente.
Yeah.
It happens all the time.
I saw it when I worked
in Africa.
Some military group
needs aid,
so they do something
really terrible
and blame it
on their enemies.
The point is, you guys
got to move fast, okay?
So, in the meantime,
I need your sat phone.
Yeah, okay.
Good luck there.
When we need to make a call, we have
to go all the way to Santa Marta.
Seriously?
You got nothing?
Hey, we're not
the Mayo Clinic.
And quick question --
how do you propose that
we get out of here?
On our --
on our Medevac helicopter?
Or our fleet of ambulances?
We are a tiny clinic
in the mountains.
I'm not the one
you're fighting here.
I'm just trying to
lay it out for you.
And we appreciate it.
But this Veracruz of yours
is looking for you,
and we can't have him
finding you here.
So...just go.
We can take care of ourselves.
He must have
been kidnapped.
Did you hear anything else?
No, nothing.
Sorry, Commander.
It's okay.
You still have an important role to this
mission, señor Garcia.
When I tell the Americans
what happened,
I will say
you bravely tried
to fight off
the Espada Ardiente.
But sadly...
You were killed.
Throw his body
in the ravine
and take pictures
for the report.
And the clinic?
With the American gone,
there's no use waiting.
We will destroy the clinic
ourselves and make the report.
So the bad news was Veracruz
was making his move early --
a fact I learned
when I ran into a familiar face
on the road.
Oh. Jesus, what --
You're the kid from earlier,
right? The food thief?
What the hell
are you doing back here?
I'm trying to get people
out of the clinic.
Okay. Whoa, whoa,
whoa, whoa, whoa.
Slow down a second.
Since when do you speak English?
I used to watch
"Full House."
You know, Veracruz is coming!
We have to go!
Veracruz?
How do you know he's coming?
I was watching his camp.
You were spying
on his camp.
I wasn't spying.
I was trying to steal food.
And they caught me,
and then I tried again.
What do you care?!
Veracruz shot one of his men
for letting you escape!
He's on his way here now!
Hey. Whoa. Oh.
No, no.
Not you again.
I thought
I told you to go --
Yeah, yeah, I remember.
I got a new plan.
We're gonna get everybody
out of here. Now.
Uh, c-commander,
could you maybe --
can you slow down
and then explain?
Yeah.
This is not the time to slow down.
Veracruz and his men are
on their way here right now.
And with these roads,
we got about 30 minutes.
Hey, can you be a sweetheart?
Grab these oxygen tanks.
Wait,
I thought you said
that Veracruz wasn't coming
until later.
Yeah, he changed his mind.
Funny how that happens.
Okay, what are y'all doing
with my stuff?
Let me ask you -- do you have
a secret cache of weapons
around here
that I don't know about?
No, I don't have
a secret cache of weapons.
Right.
I didn't think so.
Here you go, kiddo.
So, between, uh, these tanks
and the fuel out back,
we should have just enough
to blow the place.
What?! No! Whoa!
No, no, no!
You're not going to
destroy the clinic!
Isn't Veracruz coming
to do the same exact thing?
No, Veracruz wants to
destroy the clinic
with the people inside.
I want to destroy the clinic
to create a distraction
to save the people.
Little bit
of a difference.
Okay, this is insane.
No, you can't do this.
Look, guys,
you can't really believe
that Veracruz's guys
are not gonna see
everybody leaving?
We got to cover our tracks.
He's right, guys.
It's the best way.
See? The teenage thief girl
agrees with me.
Now, boys and girls,
this is happening.
You stay here, you die.
You come with me...
We live?
Well, the odds
are a little better.
So, look,
let's do this.
Get the patients outside,
load them in the trucks,
and let me know
if you see any bad guys.
I can't believe
we're doing this.
What about me?
You and me are gonna build a bomb.
Oh.
We're gonna
build a bomb.
Okay, we got diesel, oxygen,
propane out back...
The whatchamacallit
that's my defibrillator.
Right.
You wouldn't happen to have
any nitrous oxide, would you?
No. We are a bush hospital.
Not a suburban dentist's office.
Look, what am I supposed to
be doing here?
Hold on. Okay, great.
Take that.
This is your detonator.
Yeah. That's gonna go --
okay.
Tape that right on top of that valve.
Okay.
Real quick -- the warning label
says "keep away --"
Yeah. That's right.
We're building a bomb, okay?
So you do the opposite of what
the warning label says.
Hey, how we doing
out here?
My God. She ran off,
and she won't stop crying.
Hey, hey, sister.
Easy, now.
Now, I'm not an expert here,
but I don't think
that's how you get a kid
to stop crying.
Sí. Blech!
Rápido, por favor.
Easy-peasy.
Let's get the hell out of here.
You set up everything
like I told you?
Yes, yes, yes, I did --
I set my tank
by the support beam at the front
just like you said.
Are you sure you got it right?
We can only push this button once.
No, I'm not sure
if I got it right.
How am I supposed to
know if I got it right?
Okay, people,
the second I hit this,
that thing goes,
we got to be on the move.
It's the smoke and the fire
that's gonna cover our escape.
Okay.
Here goes nothing.
I didn't mean it that way.
New plan.
A new plan? I got to trigger it manually.
What do you mean?
Manually?
No, no, no, no, no!
Wait. Wait, wait, wait.
Stay in the truck!
No. Maybe I can fix it.
Maybe I can --
I guess you fixed it.
What the hell did you do?
I maximized the pressure.
Because you told me -- you told
me to maximize the pressure!
Yeah, I know. I just didn't know
you were gonna do it so well.
You got talent.
Wait a minute. Wait a minute.
Wait a minute.
We're safe, then.
Oh, no.
We're a long way from safe.
Uh, sorry to keep
you guys waiting.
Uh, sir, do you know that they
locked me in my room last night?
So I got to say, this is
starting to feel less and less
like an "informal conversation."
Still just an inquiry,
Commander.
Although after
yesterday's testimony,
I wouldn't make
any travel plans.
Thanks for the heads-up.
Now, amidst all the tales
of your heroics,
we seem to have lost sight
of your initial mission,
which is gathering intel
on a terrorist organization
known as "Espada Ardiente."
Right. I was just getting
to that, actually.
So, after the unfortunate
sacrifice of the clinic,
we all regrouped
a few miles up the road.
Well, they're not after us
just yet.
I'm guessing that by the time
they sort things out,
we're gonna have
about an hour head start.
An hour? All of that back there
bought us an hour?
Is that supposed to
be good news?
Look, I don't know
what to tell you.
It's better than a minute,
worse than a day.
So in the meantime, we got to get
those folks someplace we can hide.
The closest town
is Santa Rosa.
Yes, yes. .
There's a clinic there.
Yeah, unfortunately, we can't go
to the nearest town that has a clinic.
It's the first place they're gonna be
looking for a bunch of sick people.
They need medical
attention, okay?
- Why don't we just drop them off?
- Well, you might as well
hand them over to Veracruz
and save on gas.
Now,
where else can we go?
No place else.
All the other
so-called villages
are just a bunch of houses
and a church.
I know a place.
A camp, nearby.
A camp? Whose camp?
Espada Ardiente.
Oh. Okay.
Do you remember back when you
were just a hungry teenager
who couldn't speak English?
You said you'd never even heard
of the Espada Ardiente.
I lied.
They can help us.
They can hide the sick ones.
You know what?
I don't think
we have any other choice.
Looks like we're going with
little miss terrorist here.
Just to clarify,
Commander --
you decided to join the group
that you were sent to Colombia
to investigate?
Well, "join" is kind of
a strong word, sir.
I mean, uh,
we were in trouble,
and there were not a lot
of options in the area.
All right.
And this Beatriz you mention.
I have no record of her.
Well, that's not surprising.
She's a kid.
She's a kid who led you
to a suspected terrorist camp.
What do you want me to say?
I mean, she was
a mystery to me, too.
This kid --
well, sir, you would understand
if you met her.
Okay, so, um...
Why am I the only one
wearing a blindfold?
'Cause
I don't trust you.
- You're a soldier.
- Oh, that's why.
Do your parents know
that you hang out
with the Espada Ardiente?
- Don't talk about my parents!
- Okay. Hey. Easy.
You know, what I'm
trying to say is this --
most girls your age
are into, you know,
makeup and stuff, malls.
Do you see any shopping malls
around here?
Uh, no.
You blindfolded me, remember?
There are none.
So no more questions.
Okay, look,
I'm not trying to pry.
I'm just curious how you
hooked up with these guys.
They're my friends.
Okay.
So, how much longer
till we get to your friends?
I got to get my hands
on their communications
equipment and call in.
Uncover your eyes.
We're here.
You got to be kidding.
This?
This is
the Espada Ardiente?
Yes.
Is there a problem?
What -- well, this is,
like, 12 guys.
I was hoping
for some kind of army
or something to keep us
from getting massacred.
Look, Espada Ardiente is --
and what does that mean, anyway?
"Flaming"
something or other.
"Sword"!
You don't understand!
"Ardiente" means
fearless, passionate.
We burn to defeat
our enemies.
Right, okay. I got it.
The "flaming sword."
So what if they're small?
We can fight
just as hard as anyone!
Look, I hate to cut
your speech short, sweetheart.
But you know what?
The size of your army matters.
Okay?
It matters a lot.
I mean, you're not gonna win
a war with a flock of sheep.
Look, it's all
about firepower.
Do these guys
have any equipment?
Most of our men
have hunting rifles.
Ammunition is low,
but --
You're not making me feel
any better, here, kid.
Or how about experience?
Some of them
were in the army.
And our best fighter
is Luis.
Oh,
the big guy there?
No.
The one next to him.
Wonderful.
These guys took out a truck
full of paramilitary troops?
How do you figure that?
Luis shot the tires out of their truck,
and it went down the hill.
They killed his goats!
His -- his goats?
You're serious?
Your best fighter
is a goat herder?!
Goat herders? Really?
Ihola! Ihola!
Ben.
Oh, no. Is her cough back?
Let me see.
Okay, so,
I did a little recon,
gathered a little intel.
First thing --
you really shouldn't call them
filthy goat herders.
I didn't call them filthy.
And the only reason I called
the one guy a goat herder
is 'cause he has goats
and he herds them.
Yeah. They're farmers.
Anyway, seems their land
is valuable
as some sort of drug transport
to the coast.
So someone paid off Veracruz
to force them out.
They fought back,
got lucky a few times --
and Veracruz thought they were
bigger than they actually were.
Pretty much.
Okay, listen.
Guys, she's got malaria.
Okay, and without the right
medicine, she could die soon.
Look, I'm tap-dancing
as fast as I can here.
I'm just trying to keep
everybody breathing.
Me too, man.
Me too.
The man wants to know
why your pants are blue.
The jungle is green.
Please tell the man that
I don't want to talk about it.
So,
what's with Beatriz?
She seems to have,
uh, anger issues.
It's, uh, kind of par
for the course
when you see your father shot
in front of you.
And she wandered
into the Espada Ardiente camp
the next day,
and they took her in.
So she's, what,
the mascot?
Yeah.
Something like that.
Oh, uh, one more thing.
You have a new name in camp.
"La barbilla."
"Barbilla."
What's that again?
Um, "barbarian"
or something?
No. "The chin."
The chin.
Doesn't make any sense.
They train every morning.
It's the same thing
they do in the army.
I'm pretty sure in the army
they fire their guns.
You think that's funny?
Are you laughing at them?
No, I don't think
it's funny, kid.
I think
it's anything but.
But is is not an army.
They got no training.
Luis there
is about 100 years old.
Don't even get me started
on the big guy there.
They need weapons!
And I know you can help them!
I saw you back at the clinic,
and you made those explosives.
They need more than weapons.
Trust me -- in a real fight,
these chumps
would get slaughtered.
Aah!
Hey. Just having
a conversation here.
Nothing to look at.
Everything's cool.
Now, look, I'm sorry
about your dad, okay?
And I'm sure that your flaming
sword buddies are very brave.
But believe me -- brave guys
bleed just like everybody else.
What do you think?
Uh, the truth?
They need help more than we do.
A-and so what does that mean?
Are we -- are we stuck here?
No, it means I got to figure out
a way to call back to my C.O.,
get him
to shut Veracruz down.
All right.
We've been over this.
There isn't a phone
for 200 miles from here.
Veracruz
has a sat phone.
Yeah, but, wait.
You can't go back to Veracruz.
Well, why not?
I mean, right now he thinks
I've been kidnapped
by our new friends there.
I'll just go back and tell him I escaped.
Oh, yeah.
And he's gonna be like, "oh, my
God, it's so good to see you,"
and hug you
and shoot you in the head.
No, I doubt it. He needs me
to help him sell the story
about the flaming sword.
Should be enough
to call out.
Hey.
What if you're wrong?
Well, then, I get shot,
and you try your luck
with the goat herders.
Try it!
Okay, uh, better get going.
I want to get to Veracruz
before he makes camp.
Before you go,
I want to ask you something.
Are you really
gonna do this?
Are you really gonna
go for help?
Yeah,
it's like I told you.
- I'm gonna go back, make a call --
- People say a lot of things.
Now, I just got everybody out
of the clinic safe, didn't I?
I mean, what does a guy
have to do
to get some credibility
around here?
I've been in hot spots
all over the globe.
And when things first get rough,
everyone's a hero.
And then reality sets in,
and promises are broken.
And if you let these people
down, I want you to know
that I will personally find you
and kick your teeth in.
Amanda, I'm not gonna
let anybody down.
I may get my ass shot off,
but...
My teeth are safe.
Before we move on,
Espada Ardiente's leadership
consisted of this man,
Louis Mendez,
of the Colombian
armed forces.
His name was Luis.
And, yeah,
that looks like him...
About 100 years ago.
He looks good
in uniform.
Did you gather any more intel
on their command structure?
They were farmers.
They didn't have command
structures. They had sheep.
Why do you think I was going
to get some help?
Okay. Fine.
We'll come back to that.
What happened
after you left?
Well, I drove back
toward Veracruz.
I mean, I knew
his team's drill well enough
to find a scout or two.
Once I got to the neighborhood,
I ditched the truck,
put on a little
kidnapping makeup...
...And hoofed it
until I ran into a couple
of Veracruz's scouts.
Oh, man. It was horrible.
They were working me over,
asking all kinds of things.
How did you escape?
I was lucky.
They only sent a couple guys
with me to el baño,
and I managed to run off.
We searched for you
everywhere.
When the terrorists blew up
the clinic, we feared the worst.
It wasn't "the worst," but
it was still pretty damn bad.
You know
they were setting up
to give me the
car-battery treatment?
These guys
are frickin' monsters!
Yes, they are.
Now you see why we need your
help fighting this menace.
100%. I say we track them down
and light these bastards up.
Excellent. Good to have you
back, Commander Axe.
We need help. Okay?
Asap!
Okay, Commander.
I understand.
But let me ask you this --
how the hell
did this happen?!
You're supposed to be down there
observing and reporting,
not starting
some guerilla war!
Well, I observed
the sons of bitches
trying to kill me
and massacre hospital,
and I'm reporting it.
All right, look,
I'll make some calls.
But, Axe, if this
is some cheap ploy
to get yourself
pulled out of there...
It's not about me.
Now, you help these people,
I will gladly let you
kick my butt at a time
and place of your choosing.
But, please, for the love
of God -- I got to go.
Axe.
The men are ready.
We should start looking
for the terrorists before
they have time to move.
Yes, we should. Time for a
little payback, am I right?
So, at this point, I was just
trying to run out the clock.
I had to give the guys
from the flaming sword
enough time to get their truck
off the road
and back to their camp.
And I needed
to keep Veracruz's men busy
long enough for help to arrive.
Yep. Pretty sure
we're going this way.
But, no.
That's not --
that's not it.
Iperfecto! Iexactamente!
Ah.
What is the delay?
Uh, well, I was just
talking to your boys here.
I was telling them
that the --
the camp
is pretty much up there.
See the tire tracks here?
This is the same tread as
their vehicles that they use.
Yes, I can see.
You are
an excellent tracker.
You are also
an excellent liar.
What the hell
are you doing?
I just spoke with
Department Governor Perez.
His men intercepted your call
an hour ago.
Ay.
I am hurt you think
so little of me.
You honestly thought I would
take no precautions?
Hey, come on.
This is just a misunderstanding.
No.
No, I don't think
it is a misunderstanding.
I think I understand
very well.
Now...
Show me where they are
on the map.
You know, why should I?
You're gonna kill me anyway.
I might.
And...I might not.
The question is whether
you want to die here,
or keep breathing
a bit longer
and hope you prove useful enough
to save.
Show me
where their camp is.
If you are wrong...
I'll put a bullet
in your brain,
and maybe that
will help you remember.
Uh, well,
come to think of it,
that -- that mountain range
does look familiar.
So, how does it feel to be saved
by filthy goat herders?
Well, I owe you one, kid.
Let's go.
No, no, no, no. Not until you
promise not to insult them again.
Say what?
- Promise.
- Oh, for God's sake. Okay, I promise.
They're the greatest
part-time farmer army ever!
Can we go?!
Geez!
Aah!
So, Veracruz saw
through your plan?
Oh, and it gets better.
Veracruz is looking around,
and he's close.
He's gonna find us
within 24 hours, tops.
Ok-- okay.
So what am I supposed to do?
Because I got an old house
full of sick people --
there's a CIA outpost
about 50 miles away.
50?
The pilot who brought me down
here told me about it.
I think
it's our best bet.
50 miles.
Are you on drugs?
Do they do testing
for soldiers?
Because we can't get all
of these people 50 yards.
I understand that.
Kid, can I talk to you
for a second?
What?
I want to
ask you something.
How did you end up
with these guys,
speaking English
like you do?
What do you care?
Well, because
we're in a tough spot,
and I'd like to know
who I'm dealing with.
My father
was a journalist.
From El Espectador
in Bogotá.
He was in this area,
reporting on the situation
with the farmers.
That's what
got him shot?
Yes.
I knew Luis from the interviews
my father did.
I didn't know where else to go
a-after my father died.
So Luis brought me to the camp,
and he let me stay.
I'm glad he did.
I need your help.
I got to put this little army
together.
But there's a problem --
those guys hate me,
and I speak Spanish
like a third grader.
But they like you, and you speak
English like a champ.
So...
Por favor?
Talk to them.
And if I like what you have
to say, I will translate it.
Esteemed gentlemen
of the flaming sword...
It's not "flaming" sword!
Oh, God, forget it.
Just talk. Just talk.
I know we didn't get off
to a great start.
I made some mistakes.
You made some mistakes.
Then there was
the whole goat-herd business.
It's not like
it didn't happen.
But that's behind us.
Now, I'm a soldier.
And I've got
all the training
and a fistful
of combat ribbons.
But today -- what?
Stick with me.
Okay.
But today I damn near
got my brains blown out.
And the only reason why
I'm still breathing is because of you.
And that made me
realize something.
If we're gonna
save ourselves...
...And give Veracruz
the ass-whipping
he so richly deserves...
Was that what I said?
The point is that
we need to do it together.
So I'm standing here
before you today
to ask for your help.
Now, I've got a plan,
but it is not gonna fly
without you.
So I need to know
right now...
...Are you with me?!
Espada Ardiente.
Espada Ardiente!
Okay,
now let's get training,
'cause, man,
we got to get organized.
Wait right there. Stop.
You're saying that you were
training the terrorist group?
Did you train them?
Yes or no?
Did you work with this man,
Louis Mendez?
Yeah, look, Luis was one
of the guys. He was on --
He was the senior operative
in the Colombian military
in the 1980s
until he disappeared,
presumably, to start this group!
And now you're giving this man
military secrets and training?
All I can say, sir, is the only
secrets I gave away
were the secrets
of the Analee High School
J.V. football squad.
Okay, guys.
Listen up and listen good.
These are the plans
for battle.
This first one here
is called the nickel defense.
If things get rough...
...The scouts fall back.
This last one is called
the prevent defense.
Why is that?
They've all fallen back.
What the hell's
their problem?
All of these plans
are for retreating!
The men want to know what's
the plan for an attack!
No, they don't
need to know that one.
See, we're just trying to
keep them in the game. Mondo.
You're killing me.
Okay, I have a plan
for attack.
It's called
the "zone blitz."
And it's all about disguise.
Let's hear you say it.
All together.
"Zone blitz!"
Z-zone blitz!
Z-zone blitz! Z-zone blitz!
Now let's just hope to God
you never have to
say those words again.
Next day, we moved out
with the patients in one truck,
and the flaming sword guys
packed in the others.
It was only 50 miles, but when
the whole country is a mountain,
miles are kind of
like dog years --
every one more like seven.
And, of course,
there's the worst part
of driving to a CIA outpost --
it's not gonna be on the map.
Quick update --
I didn't run away.
I went to get help,
just like I said.
Yes, and you almost
got yourself killed.
That should
count double, then.
Uh, why would it
count double?
It only counts double
if you actually come back
with some help.
If you nearly die
a senseless death,
that counts as,
like, half.
Okay. Half.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
Okay, so,
tell me something.
Do-gooder...
Food-aid worker...
I mean, why so cynical?
If you're asking that,
you probably haven't spent
a whole lot of time
around aid workers.
Okay.
Well, I mean,
you get into this
because you want to make
the world a better place,
and it turns out
that there's a lot of people
who want to make it
a worse place.
And we're outnumbered.
By a lot.
By soldiers, you mean?
Not just soldiers.
But usually, when there are
people are going hungry,
there's some guy with a gun
making it happen.
Speaking of hunger,
you haven't been eating.
Why is that?
These guys need it more than me.
Believe me.
I figure it this way --
if we make it,
I got a head start on
the 10 pounds I want to lose,
and if we don't, well,
dead guys don't get hungry.
You're not like
the other soldiers I've met,
Commander Axe.
I'll give you that.
Call me Sam.
Sam it is.
I know that you want me
to kiss you right now.
- And, believe me, I would love to.
- What?
But I'm just saying,
it's a bad time, is all.
- No, no.
- Any other time, I'd be all over it.
Oh. No comprende.
Seriously.
I was just making
conversation here.
That's what that was.
Yeah, just drive.
For the record,
she wanted me to kiss her.
So, anyway, we keep going.
So, as we're getting
to the main roads
out of the mountains,
I'm getting that itchy feeling,
an itchy feeling
that just keeps getting worse.
Oh, you've got to
be kidding me.
Hey.
Uh, okay.
This is not good.
No, no.
This is just rain.
Okay? It doesn't take much
to start a rock slide.
You always see fallen rocks
and trees in the road.
Yeah, well, I don't see
a lot of trees or rocks.
I just see this tree here
right in the middle of
a hard-to-defend position.
- A hard-to-def--
- Yeah.
What do you propose we do?
Back those trucks up
and proceed with caution.
Oscar can clear it.
Hold on a second, okay?
I don't think that thing
fell by itself.
The sooner we cut the tree,
the sooner we can go.
It's fine. It's fine.
So, while they're clearing
this tree from the road,
I'm getting a real bad feeling,
one of those "too quiet,
I don't like this place,
something weird is going on"
feelings.
You, uh...
You might want to stay here.
Now, I know, of course,
that there's a fine line
between caution and paranoia.
People tell you about
gut feelings all the time.
But if you follow
every gut feeling,
you never get anything done.
Still, sometimes something
feels funny for a reason.
They know we're here.
What?
They know we're here!
Prevent defense!
Aah!
No!
Luis!
- Hey, help me with something.
- Whoa, whoa, whoa. Where you going?
Look, those guys
are just scouts, okay?
They're trying to keep us here
until reinforcements show up.
So we got to block that
switchback down there before --
well, before that.
Yeah, here they are,
right on time. Come on.
Push! Push!
Push now! Ivamonos!
Aah!
Yeah! Yeah!
Very groovy! Come on, guys!
Okay, go, go, go.
We got to go. Got to go.
Now listen everybody.
We got lucky back there.
Those guys got excited, and
they made a lot of mistakes,
but it's not gonna
happen again.
So we got to move,
and we got to move fast.
Now, if this map
is not garbage,
we are close
to a CIA outpost.
We can get there by nightfall
if we hurry.
Understand, señor?
All right, let's go.
Can we talk?
Ah, listen, you know,
about before, it's --
Oh,
you're talking about --
No, I'm not talking
about that, actually.
If you want to
embarrass yourself
with your fantasies,
knock yourself out.
What I want to know is...
Once we get there,
what happens?
Well, maybe you haven't
been paying attention.
We get there, we get help.
Oh, so it's as simple
as that.
Who said it was
gonna be simple?
So, we used
what head start we had,
but it was pretty slowgoing.
In those mountains,
the good roads are bad,
and the bad roads, well,
they aren't really even roads.
This is ridiculous.
I can't even tell which way
north is anymore.
You're sure that it's here?
- Yeah, it's around here somewhere, yeah.
- Really?
Because there's nothing
on this map that says --
we are looking for a secret
intelligence facility.
They don't put them
on maps.
That's how you know
they're secret.
Right, right,
right, right, right.
But isn't it possible
that this guy
that told you about it
is wrong?
- Because honestly --
- Okay, there it is. Right there.
Now, you want to check it out,
or should we just
chalk this up to my imagination
and go home?
But do -- do we just knock,
or is...?
Now you want to kiss me.
This isn't some kind of joke,
is it?
I don't joke
about mass murder.
It's kind of
a touchy subject with me.
So, guys, what can we do, here?
You got any weapons?
We got a couple .45s
and a --
you know,
and, like, a box of ammo.
Other than that, we've got,
like, a lot of computers.
We got maps.
DVDs. Some good movies.
We're an observation outpost.
Observing.
Yeah, doing
communications support and...
Not wearing night goggles
going on raids.
We're not a fortress.
Okay, what about all the antennas
on the roof? Can you call out?
Yeah, yeah.
We can do that.
Well, get on it, then.
We need help right now.
What you got, medicine-wise?
Yeah, we'd call that
"not much."
Okay, hold on, now.
It's better than nothing.
I told you, man.
It's just us out here.
I mean, its me, Gabe,
and the donkey.
Donkey?
The burro.
We take her into town
for supplies and water,
but, you know, the roads around here...
Yeah, tell me about it.
This expired,
like, two years ago.
What's up?
I called in to the military base
in Santa Marta.
And?
Are they sending anybody?
They said they need to see you,
in person, and talk to them.
They said the base chief
needs to meet with you.
I guess there's some confusion
about your, uh, situation.
Okay, well, how the hell
am I supposed to
get to Santa Marta --
on the burro?
On the chopper.
It's out back.
The chopper.
Why didn't you say so?
Okay, now we're
getting somewhere.
So, you really have to go?
You can't just call them?
No, they got reports
that I was kidnapped,
that I was killed,
that I've gone rogue.
So I-I got to go out there
and drag them back myself.
Who will you bring?
Well, the Colombian military's
been working
with the U.S.
on some anti-drug runs,
so they got attack copters,
troops.
Veracruz will find
this place soon.
Yeah. Probably sooner
rather than later.
That's why
we got to hustle.
Okay. Let come.
That is out of the question.
We're overweight as it is.
We should go.
Listen, kid.
I'm coming back, okay?
I'm not gonna
let you guys down.
Okay, so, how well do you know
these Colombian military folks?
I've done some joint operations
with them.
Well, 'cause I was thinking if
they can run this up the ladder,
it'd be good to get
some embassy involvement,
maybe arrange visas
for some of these folks.
We can call Washington.
There's a refugee program
we might be able to get them into.
Sounds good.
Here we go.
- Hey, guys, how long is this gonna take?
- Hard to say.
As soon as we land, we'll find
the foreign affairs officer,
get the ball rolling
on paperwork.
Paperwork?
Yeah, for going back.
You know the drill --
authorization reports...
...Duty orders.
...Debriefing reports.
Hang on a second.
You guys didn't mention
anything about paperwork
when we were down on the ground.
What are you talking about?
It's protocol, man.
The CIA's not gonna send out
a military tactical team
without checking it out.
Why they hell didn't you
mention that back there?
And, uh, what,
cause a riot?
Hey, we got rules to follow,
like anybody else, pal.
Those rules
are also pretty clear --
when a facility's
been compromised,
you take the classified
material and bug out
without causing an
international incident.
Keyword there
would be "without."
I thought you were on board
with all this,
especially with
all that embassy talk.
Visas.
Guys, you promised
those people down there.
- I promised those people.
- Grow up, man.
No way we could have
ever given them
anything near
what you promised them.
Not unless U.S. personnel
were under direct attack.
There's a point
in a soldier's life
where he's got to decide
whether he's gonna follow
the letter or the spirit
of his orders.
So you can't do anything
unless Americans
are under direct attack,
right?
That's right.
What about you guys?
Do you count?
Land the chopper. Now.
You held two
CIA officers hostage
on behalf of a suspected
terrorist group?
That's treason.
Do you think I wanted to?
Do you think
I had a choice?
Sir, we were
not gonna get help
unless those guys told the brass
that they were under attack.
I did what I had to do.
I see.
You had to kidnap them.
"Kidnap." Get out of here.
I was just helping them
do the right thing.
Helping them.
With a .45-caliber pistol?
Well, you know
what they say, sir.
Guns don't help people.
People help people.
You are in a world of hurt,
soldier.
Commander Axe,
as we reconvene
this inquiry,
I am obliged to ask you
if you would like us to
assign you a military lawyer.
- A lawyer?
- I'd advise it.
I thought I was just
making a report here.
Oh, we've gone beyond that,
Commander.
Now, we've detained and
questioned a few of the people
that were involved
in your little adventure,
and there's quite a case
building against you.
Wait, wait.
You're rounding people up?
Yes, the farmers, the doctor,
Amanda Maples.
Those are my friends, sir.
They didn't do anything wrong.
It's standard operating
procedure, Commander.
"Standard operating procedure."
Why don't you bite me?
You're speaking
to a superior officer!
Stand down, Commander!
Now, you've underestimated
the sheer size of this fiasco.
And by all accounts,
you are standing
in the middle of it,
dead center.
So, last chance --
do you want to
exercise your right
to legal counsel?
I'm good.
You know what these proceedings
could result in.
Yeah, me getting thrown into a
hole for the rest of my life?
Yeah, I got it.
I also know that a lawyer
is not gonna make
a damn bit of difference.
Now, sir, you want to hang
this mess around my neck,
you go for it,
but leave my friends alone.
You're in no position
to negotiate, Commander Axe.
Now I want to hear
about what happened
after you drew your weapon
on two CIA field agents.
All right. Fine.
After my "conversation"
with the CIA boys,
we went back
to the outpost.
And let me tell you
something, sir --
everybody was real glad
to see me.
- Change of plans.
- That was quick.
You do know that the town
is the other way?
I thought you were going
to get help.
- Yeah, there was a little hitch.
- What kind of a hitch?
Turns out
our CIA buddies
were not such good buddies
after all.
They were planning on leaving
everybody to the wolves.
I disagreed
with that plan.
What --
and they are...?
Tied up
in the helicopter.
Oh, that is not good.
Okay, so, um, now what
are we supposed to do?
Aren't you the one who said
that we were going to
get slaughtered?
That's not gonna happen.
So you have a plan?
Uh, no, but I know
where to start.
Make the call.
I'm not calling in.
Do it.
You'll thank me later.
Yeah, I'm pretty sure
we won't thank you.
Yeah, you will. Because Veracruz
is following our trail here.
And when he does,
he's gonna wipe this place
off the face of the earth,
and you two yahoos with it.
What do you want?
I want you to call
your CIA buddies,
tell them to get the
Colombian military out here,
the national police -- the
works, everything they got.
You're gonna burn for this.
Yeah, but that's
not the question.
The question is whether
you're gonna make that call...
Or if I'm gonna have to
make you make the call.
Yeah, it's Gabriel Manaro
out at station 412.
We got a situation here.
Some kind of rogue military
force is attacking our position.
Just helping you sell it.
Yeah, yeah, that's --
we're firing back at them.
We need supp--
be more convincing.
Jesus! No.
No, I'm not talking to you.
We need help!
We need support now!
Send it! Send the help!
Military support! Now!
Help us!
I am at station 4-1-2!
Yes! Yes! Just hurry!
They'll have a team here
in three hours.
Three hours?
Veracruz is just up the road.
He's gonna be all over us
in three hours.
Yeah, well, they're coming
from over the mountains.
That's what it takes,
dude!
That's the fastest they can
get here. It's not magic.
What's going on?
Who's shooting?
- That was me just making a point.
- Okay, what?
Well, I got good news
and bad news.
Good news is,
help is on the way.
Bad news is, we're gonna have to
hold out until it gets here.
Okay, señors.
Hey, look what I made.
That's a hell of a bomb.
Wow. You got a gift.
Well, you know, I've been
doing field medicine
for a long time.
You learn to improvise.
Yeah, well, I've known
a lot of field medics,
but they don't have your chops
with explosives.
- Good work.
- Thank you.
Where's the kid?
Can I talk to you
for a sec?
What?
You know, this, um --
this fight with Veracruz,
it's gonna be rough.
We got to hold them off
for a long time.
So I was thinking
it would be a good idea
if you just stay back here
and watch the CIA guys.
Stay here?
I'm fighting with the others.
Okay, okay.
Just hear me out here.
Now, you're still young, and
you've done more in this fight
than any kid
should ever have to.
Those men
killed my father.
I think it's safe to say
if your dad was here,
he wouldn't want you
catching a bullet.
I mean, think about it.
What would he say?
I don't know.
He's not here.
He would say a kid as tough
and as smart as you
is gonna have
a big future.
He'd want you to grow up
and see it, wouldn't he?
He would want me to stay.
So you'll stay?
No.
But thanks anyways.
You remind me
of my father.
And I didn't listen
to him, either.
Kids these days.
All right, mount up!
We did a little recon
when we got out to the road
and we got some more bad news.
Veracruz's buddy Perez
showed up,
and he brought more guys
with him --
a lot more guys,
with a lot more guns.
Still, there wasn't much to do
but stick with the plan.
We had our little explosive
device cobbled together
from some C-4 charges
the CIA guys had
in case they needed to blow up
their computers in a hurry.
The way I figured it,
if we could plant it
at the right spot,
we could block the road
with a couple thousand pounds
of burning truck wreckage
then pin Veracruz down
for a while.
You should probably go.
No. No. Do it.
That is, assuming we didn't
blow ourselves up first.
Okay. Let's go.
I know we were not expecting
the reinforcements.
And the odds are, um,
kind of against us.
But what the hell?
You're the flaming sword, right?
Now, look, they got to
come from down there.
When that bomb blows,
it's gonna be our job
to slow them down.
'Cause if they get through here -- pbht! --
We are sitting ducks.
Pbht!
Sitting ducks?
It's an expression.
It's like ducks in a pond,
ducks in a row. It's easy to --
How bad is this?
Oh, well, maybe we had
a solid chance
before that troop transport
showed up.
But now...
And how long do we
have to hold them?
Help comes
in about two hours.
Veracruz and his men,
give or take 90 minutes,
so I think we got to hold out
for about a half-hour.
Can we do that?
Well, with the terrain
on our side, maybe.
But it's gonna be
a long half-hour.
But, hey, it could be worse,
right?
It could be raining.
Let's do this.
Now, at this point, we didn't
have a whole lot going for us.
On our side,
we had the high ground
and the element of surprise.
On their side,
they had manpower,
equipment, body armor,
superior weaponry,
radio communications, and
pretty much everything else.
Is he on it, or is he not on?
He's not on it.
If he was on it, it would --
Luis, now!
Ha! Flaming sword!
Damn right.
Flaming sword! Attack!
Zone blitz!
Good shot, Mondo.
The men are running
out of ammunition.
Tell them to act like
they're shooting.
Just keep looking mean, pretend
like they have ammunition.
What?!
Just do it!
I pulled out every trick
in the book.
But the thing is,
at the end of the day,
there's just no good substitute
for bullets.
No!
Okay, uh, I don't think
they're buying it.
All right, look,
game over.
Tell them to fall back
to the trucks.
Old man! Let's go!
No.
Wait.
W-what is he doing?
He's covering us.
Let's go. Let's go.
Espada Ardiente!
I got to go back.
Ben.
I got one more charge,
just in case.
We got to get him.
Aren't you
full of surprises.
Oh, Jesus.
He's dead.
Are you okay?
No! I'm shot!
That's right.
Stupid question. Okay.
Let's do it.
Get him inside.
Damn it.
Where the hell are they?
Beatriz, they're coming.
Let's get inside.
Get off me!
Don't! Please, kid. I'm begging you.
They killed Luis,
and I'm going to fight them!
Look, I know that he meant
a lot to you, okay?
But he was a soldier.
He was protecting you.
Don't make his death
meaningless
by standing out here
and getting yourself killed.
Please, if you won't
go inside for me,
at least do it
for the old goat herder.
Where the hell are they?
Call 'em again.
How much longer?
'Ca-- 'cause we're
running out of time up here.
It's -- the situation
is getting urgent --
Yeah, is this
the station chief?
I got to know how much longer
this is gonna take,
and your numbnuts officer here
can't tell me.
Who is this?
Who is this?!
Deputy assistant intelligence
director Chuck Finley.
That's who.
I'm down
from NSA headquarters here
doing a random sigint check,
and I ran into this little
disaster area of yours.
Now, where are these troops?
They're 10 minutes away,
sir.
10 minutes?
This thing will be over in 5.
Get on it.
Chuck Finley?
Yeah. Made a lot of money
betting on him back in the day.
I'm thinking
it's a lucky name.
I guess we'll find out.
Between the flipped truck
and the firefight,
we bought ourselves some time.
But it wasn't too long before
Veracruz was in position,
and we were
about to get creamed.
Keep everybody inside.
When the shooting starts,
make sure they're away from
the windows and down low, okay?
I'm going out there.
You're what?
I got to buy us
some more time.
Sam, if you go out there,
Veracruz will kill you.
Yeah. Maybe.
But if I manage to die slowly,
that'll put you guys
just a little closer
to getting out of here.
No, no, no. You're at least
taking your gun.
If he sees that I have a gun,
he's gonna shoot me on sight.
Don't worry about it.
I got an idea.
No, no. Wait.
I mean, they --
you can't --
ju-- if you just --
stay alive.
I'll do my best.
Still, you know,
if we were gonna kiss,
we should probably do it now
just in case.
I don't want to...
That is a lot better
than a kick in the teeth.
Whoa. Whoa.
Hey, guys,
we need to talk.
What is there to talk about,
Commander Axe?
Oh, we got a lot
to talk about.
I'm here to negotiate
the terms of your surrender.
Our surrender?
Is that supposed to be funny?
How long
before they get here?
I don't know. Soon.
They better get here
soon.
Man, you just love doing that,
don't you?
How many are there
inside?
Believe me, y-you don't know
what you're up against.
Yes, "Espada Ardiente."
We know.
No. No.
It's the flaming sword.
Believe me, you don't want to
mess with them.
And why is that?
'Cause I've fought
all over --
Afghanistan, the Balkans,
Southeast Asia.
I've never seen guys
like this.
I count a dozen men
with old rifle--
farmers,
by the look of them.
Yeah? You think
that's all we got?
Then what am I
doing here?
I'm a commander
in the Navy S.E.A.L.S.
You think
I'm gonna be wasting time
with a bunch
of smelly farmers --
smelly, stinking,
unwashed farmers?
No, no.
You boys have made
a grave miscalculation.
That's why I'm here
with my one-time-only,
not-to-be-repeated
offer --
unconditional surrender
right now,
and I'll let you
walk away.
You're bluffing.
What is he doing?
No!
Ohh.
All right, all right.
Because I am feeling...
Generous and, uh,
merciful...
I'm gonna give you
one more chance.
Surrender right now.
Okay? I'm serious.
What is he doing?!
I'm telling you guys,
you're just making it worse
on yourself.
Ugh, we should finish him.
Wait!
Let's see this flaming sword,
shall we?
I'm telling you guys,
you're gonna regret it.
Aah!
I've heard the old saying
about soldiers
praying in foxholes.
It's a natural response
when your friends are dying
and everything you care about
is about to get destroyed.
But I got to say,
in my experience,
prayer is pretty iffy
as a battle plan.
Aah!
But I'll also say this --
when you need a miracle,
there's nothing like it.
Hey, guys.
Say hello to my friends.
I call them the newest members
of the flaming sword,
you crooked son of a bitch.
Sam -- Sam Axe.
The good guys --
it's the good guy--
uh, Los buenos.
Los buenos.
So, you guys ready
to surrender now?
Aah!
Man, that felt good.
Sam Axe!
So, you gonna make it?
Yeah.
Yeah, I think so.
Well, I got to say,
if you ever reconsider
the whole medical thing,
you'd make a hell
of a soldier.
Okay.
All right, I will -- I will,
uh -- I'll keep that in mind.
Listen, Sam...
Thank you.
Thank you for everything.
Back at you, doc.
All right.
Help this man up.
So, what happens now?
Well, it's gonna take a while
to sort this all out.
My guess
is that Veracruz and Perez
are gonna be going off the grid
for their foreseeable lifetimes.
No, I mean,
what about you?
Oh, I'm probably gonna get spend
some quality time
at the nearest
covert military facility.
Well, uh, good luck.
Thanks.
And, uh...
Thanks for the kiss, huh?
I mean, I know
you probably only did it
'cause you thought
I was gonna die, but --
Oh, my God.
Commander Axe...
You need to come with us.
Señor Axe...
And here I am.
That's quite a story,
Commander Axe.
Thanks.
How does it end, sir?
There's only one way
it could end --
a court martial.
Well, sir, there is actually
one more part of the story
that you should
probably hear.
I mean, I was saving it
in case you decided to be
a stand-up guy about all this,
but I guess
that's not gonna happen.
What are you talking
about?
Do you remember the little chat
I had with Beatriz
after Luis died?
Well,
there's something I left out.
He was protecting you.
Don't make his death
meaningless
by staying outside
and getting yourself killed.
It's my fault!
It's my fault --
all of this.
Now, the first half
of the discussion
went just like I told you.
It was in the second half,
though,
where things got
really interesting.
Kid, don't say that.
This has nothing to do
with you.
The flaming sword -- they knew
what they were getting into.
There's no flaming sword!
What the hell
are you talking about?
My father interviewed Luis
for the newspaper,
and I went with him,
so I knew all his story --
that he was in the army
and he went away to be a farmer.
After my father was killed,
I went back to Luis.
I gave him the name
of "Espada Ardiente,"
and I convinced him
to fight!
Wait a minute.
So all of this
was your idea?
Everything.
I should die here.
Now, look, kid...
This is not over,
not by a long shot.
Now, we're gonna
get through this.
And I've been around long enough
to know when this is all over,
there's gonna be hell
to pay.
You want something to live for?
You want to help your friends?
'Cause I got a job
for you.
You any good
with a camera?
So, I figured if anybody
could get away clean
after that little skirmish,
it was a kid.
And a kid
with connections
at the largest newspaper
in Colombia?
Well, that could be
mighty handy.
I had her grab one of the
cameras from the CIA outpost
and take pictures --
a lot of them --
of everyone and everything...
...Then get herself
down to Bogotá,
and go back to her dad's
old newspaper...
Beatriz!
...And once she got there,
to talk to someone she trusted
about putting together
a couple of stories.
Now, one of these stories
should be in today's paper.
In fact, sir,
isn't there a piece
on the front page today
about Luis,
talking about how he died
under mysterious circumstances?
There was. Yes.
Oh, how interesting.
Why don't we all
take a break?
Yes, sir.
You don't really think
that anyone's gonna take
this girl's word
over that
of the United States military?
Well, the girl
did have extensive access
to a covert
CIA outpost, sir.
I mean,
imagine what she saw
and took pictures of.
Tell me, what happens when spies
who are under official cover
get their pictures
in the paper?
I mean,
that can't be good, right?
You wouldn't dare.
This is the sort of thing
that you don't want revealed
to the world, Admiral,
and it's gonna be --
things that could end
a guy's military career,
and I'm not
talking about mine.
What do you want?
Thanks for asking.
First,
you let my friends go.
Then you rebuild
the clinic.
The flaming sword guys
go back to their goats,
I get
an honorable discharge,
and we keep our mouths shut
about this forever.
In the words of my buddy
Mike Westen,
"this is the kind of secret
that stays a secret."
That's blackmail.
No. Actually, sir, I believe
this form of extortion
is known as "graymail."
It's much nicer
than blackmail.
I believe
we're done here, sir.
Agreement between
commander Sam Axe
and the United States
military court.
Under the terms
of this agreement,
Commander Axe hereby agrees
not to discuss, reveal,
or otherwise disclose
his activities
between January 22nd and
January 31st of the year 2005.
He is to receive
the following --
an honorable discharge
with full pension,
a change of clothes,
first class air transport
to the city of his choosing,
and one ice-cold beer.
Executed February 20, 2005,
by Rear Admiral James Lawrence,
United States Navy.
Welcome to Miami,
Mr. Axe.
Thank you.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==