Gently.
Can you get a better view?
Omar, a meter to your left.
Be careful where you step.|You might kill us all.
Land mines.
In the Middle East, they're everywhere.|Just walk into a field and help yourself.
We will use these to strike terror|into the hearts of our enemies.
For a man who is willing to die|for his cause...
cannot be stopped.
- Don't you agree, my friend?|- Of course.
But first, we must kill all the frauds,|all the imposters...
and... all the double agents.
You understand.
Excellent. So far everything's going|as planned.
Halir's group is called Bright Star.
Their goal is to destroy|all symbols of modern decadence.
Their weapon of choice: suicide bombings.
The bombs are constructed|from land mines...
so the materials can't be traced.
Last night we sacrificed a mole...
in order to protect|a more important contact:
Gregory Formitz.
A dealer in forged documents,|passports, visas, press credentials.
He supplies Bright Star with fake IDs.
If we control Formitz,|we have a chance to stop Bright Star.
We've been brought into this one|a little late. So we have to play catch-up.
We need any intel we can get.
Michael, it's all yours.
You'll be our liaison with Formitz.
Madeline has prepared a profile.|You may find it useful.
Formitz is from a wealthy family.|Intelligent, well-educated.
He ranked first in his class|at medical school.
Medical school?
He dropped out|three days before graduation.
Because?
He was a younger son, a rebel.
He wanted to cause his family|the maximum amount of disappointment.
Did it work?
Yes. They never spoke to him again.
His alliance with terrorists arose partly|as a way of continuing to rebel...
partly because danger appeals to him.
So, betraying Bright Star to us makes|it even more dangerous.
Exactly.
So betraying us to Bright Star in turn...
might up the ante even further.
Very good.
Our analysis indicates there's little chance|of that happening soon.
But as time goes on,|the chance will increase. So be alert.
- Birkoff, you got a minute?|- No, not really.
- We want to tell you something.|- It'll have to wait.
We're getting married.
I asked her last night.|She accepted right away.
Okay, don't congratulate us or anything.|It's all right.
Congratulations.
I'm sorry. I'm just surprised.
Yeah, me, too. But you've got|to get lucky sometimes, right?
- When's the big day?|- Tomorrow.
I have to hurry because she might|come back to her senses.
That'll never happen.
- We just wanted you to know.|- Thanks. Congratulations.
See you later.
Hey, buy you a drink? Come on.
- Back off!|- Okay.
You go out when I tell you!
- I was sick.|- I decide when you're sick!
No! Don't!
I've been soft on you, huh?|Gonna change now-
Excuse me.
You get out, and don't come back.
You two all right?
It's just gonna be worse|when he comes back.
He won't come back.
Thanks.
Formitz?
- You're my contact?|- That's right.
You just took out that pimp?
Idiot, the idea is to maintain a low profile.
This is not gonna work. I'm out of here.
Sit down.
Let go of me.
If you don't sit down,|I'm gonna make a scene...
that'll give you|the highest profile in this neighborhood.
Sit down.
Fine. But from now on,|we attend to our business...
and we let other people|attend to theirs. All right?
- You do business with Bright Star.|- Yeah.
We want copies of all IDs and credentials|you provide them with.
Not the way it works.
Halir, their main man, calls me,|tells me where to meet.
I bring the blanks, he brings the pictures.
He watches me make the IDs,|takes them when I'm done.
There are no copies. Except up here.
- I need names and descriptions.|- What would I need?
Give me your bank account information.|You'll have the money within an hour.
Just like that, huh?
Of course, if I'm lying,|I never get the chance to spend it, do I?
Names.
I only have one, so far.|Ahmed Mujani. Posing as a journalist.
- Going where?|- First stop, Beirut. After that, I don't know.
When?
Halir didn't say.|But I got the impression very soon.
See you again.
Ahmed Mujani.|Formitz says he's the bomber.
Where is he?
From Beirut he went to Berlin,|then to Hamburg.
He checked into the Milo Hotel last night.
Cross-ref the hotel with potential targets.
It's three blocks from|the International Trade Center.
I'll assemble a team.|You prepare the tactical.
Nikita. Status?
The delegates are all inside.|There's over 100 in one room.
They've been screened.|He'll come from out here.
- Michael, report.|- The security team hasn't seen him.
- He could be disguised.|- We're aware of that.
Craig, check out the elderly lady|with the shopping bag.
I'm on it.
Excuse me, ma'am.
Got the target.
Let's go.
What's up?
- Walter and Belinda are getting married.|- That's great!
No, it's not great. Belinda's in abeyance.
She's scheduled for the Rio mission.|There's no way she's coming back.
Is there anything that you can do?
I took her off abeyance once before.|Operations found out.
Do you think I should tell Walter?
There's no point. Just let them|be as happy as long as they can.
Look, I gotta go and meet Formitz.
You're gonna be on comm.|Take down the names. Okay?
Yeah. Okay.
The bomb came from|cannibalized land mines, as we expected.
- What about the detonator?|- It's another dead end.
Garden variety. Could have come|from a thousand sources.
Did the bomber go in the bus depot|as an evasive maneuver...
or was that his intended destination?
It was his intended destination.
You're sure?
It was my impression during the mission,|and the tapes confirmed it.
Then we're facing an extreme situation.
They're targeting innocent people|in public places.
Anywhere, anytime.
Formitz is the key more than ever.
- He and Nikita are getting along?|- Well enough.
- She's meeting him again this afternoon.|- Good. Keep me informed.
Birkoff, he's not here.
He'll show. He was late|last time, too, remember?
Okay, it's over an hour.|This guy needs to learn manners.
What's his address?
We agreed to stay clear ofhis home.
Birkoff, give me his address.
3301 Van der Weil.
Hey.
- What's up?|- Nothing.
Erica, the girl I was with before...|I can't find her.
She never stays with a trick.|That's one of her rules.
And she wouldn't break it.
Especially with what's been happening.
What's been happening?
Girls have been disappearing.
And they find them...
- What, murdered?|- Mutilated.
I mean, she should have been home|hours ago.
She's my friend.
- What's your name?|- Danielle. Yeah.
Listen, Danielle, I'm sure|that Erica's gonna turn up.
Hey, it's gonna be all right.
What the hell is this?
- Where have you been?|- Occupied!
You're not supposed to come to my house.
Yesterday, I saw 40 people die.
Some of them were children.
I don't want|to see that again, understand?
Maybe I lost track of time.
Don't be late next time.
Who pays for my lock?
You do.
- You had a meeting with Halir last night?|- Yeah.
Names.
Three. I wrote them down yesterday.
When's your next meeting?
He'll call.
You'll let me know.
Where did you find this?
It's my sister's.
You're lying.
It belongs to a girl called Erica.
She was at the bar last night.
So what?
So, she's missing.
Missing. What does that mean?
Why don't you tell me?
Where is she?
I'm the only contact|you have with Bright Star.
Without me, you can't stop them.
Where's Erica?
You want to see her?
Yes.
Sure. Why not?
Come on. You can say hi.
It's not cheap or casual.|I spend a long time selecting them.
It's like I know them.
It means something, you know?
Why didn't you tell me?
He's a very frightened man.
Murder gives him a feeling|of being in control.
I know Section makes compromises.
But he's Jack the Ripper.
We need him.
Shall I tell you what he does?
That won't be necessary.
It's simple arithmetic.
We sacrifice a few lives to save hundreds.
Stay focused on the mission.
Try remembering the faces of the people|at the bus depot...
just before the explosion.
Did you know about Formitz?
He just contacted us.|You beat the hell out of him.
I can't go back there.
If I do, I'll kill him.
You will go back.
You will not kill him.
I want to apologize for what I did.
I'm sorry. The body was just|a little bit of a shock.
I believe you collect stamps.
A Belgian Jubilee. Very nice.
Come in.
I was right, wasn't I?
It doesn't matter what I do.
You need me.
It feels great having someone to tell.|It makes it even better.
I don't want to hear it.
I've already picked the next girl.|It's that friend of Erica's. The young one.
You leave her alone.
No. I've already decided.
See, I dreamt about it|from the first time I saw them together.
Now, I'm doing it.
- Don't you touch her.|- Or what?
The Rio team leaves|in a couple of minutes.
I'd like you to give Walter|a message for me.
Give it to him yourself when you get back.
You know I'm not coming back.
Tell him he's the best man|I've ever known.
I love him.
And it's not such a bad thing|to die on the happiest day of your life.
Will you tell him that for me?
Sure.
Thanks.
$200 for one hour.|You ever made that much before?
Sure.
Liar. Let's go.
Hey!
Get lost, right now.
Look. Are you sure about this?|Have you thought it through?
Put your hands on her again|and I'll kill you.
- Get lost!|- Okay.
What do you think you're doing?|He was going to pay me $200-
Erica's dead.
No.
Was she...
She was murdered by the man|that you were just talking to.
No.
- You're a cop.|- No, I'm not.
- But you'll go to the cops.|- No, I can't.
- Why not?|- Because I just can't.
Let's just get your things and go.|Come on.
Where?
Someplace safe.|Just get your things and we'll go.
- No, I need to work.|- Not tonight, you don't.
No, I'll stay away from him.|I mean, I'll work-
He'll find you. He'll track you down.
He'll torture you and then|he's gonna kill you. Do you understand?
- You're scaring me.|- Good. Get your things.
- I don't even know your name.|- It's Nikita. Let's go.
You'll be okay here.
How long am I supposed to stay here?
I don't know.|Until I say you can go out again.
If you need money, I'll get you some.
Who are you?
- Do you have someplace to go?|- No, I don't.
Parents?
I'd rather die than go back to them, okay?|I mean that.
All right. No lectures.
But, Danielle, if you leave this room...
you will die.
Do you understand that?
I'll get back as soon as I can.|Promise me you won't leave until then.
Yeah, I promise.
Lock the door after I'm gone.
- No mission?|- No.
What did you call me in for?
Where were you?
No place in particular.
Formitz's last intel was accurate.
One of our teams in Prague|was able to prevent the bombing.
Good.
They took the bomber alive. It's a woman.
She might lead us directly to Halir.|We wouldn't need Formitz anymore.
- I thought you'd like to know.|- Thanks.
She broke?
No. And she won't.
It hasn't been that long.|How can you be sure?
I'm sure.
Perhaps if we just held off|for a little while...
and let her remember|what it's like not to feel pain.
Then suddenly hit her with it.
It won't work.
Can I at least try?
We're finished. Let's go.
Where?
To a cell.
I'll stay here.
I said, we're finished.
I had a son.
He was three when they came to my|house and murdered him and my husband.
I no longer feel pain...
and I do not fear death.
You will give me comfort...
then begin again, worse than before.
What will you do,|break every bone in my body?
What else do you wish to break?|I'll save you the trouble.
An embassy in Vienna, an airport|in Istanbul, another in Bucharest.
All within the last four days.
- Bright Star?|- They're picking up the pace.
We can't just intercept the bombers.|We have to get to Halir himself.
- What about the prisoner?|- She's very unlikely to crack.
If we have to use Formitz,|we'll have to do it quickly.
They're starting to use other forgers.|They may not need him much longer.
We'll have him set up a meeting|with Halir. Someplace we can access.
Formitz will be extremely reluctant|to take that kind of risk.
Nikita will have to persuade him.
Is that a problem?
The relationship between Formitz|and Nikita is not without difficulties.
Why is that?
She's become aware of his habit.
She has a job to do.
I would hate to feel that she's regressing.|Becoming sentimental again.
She's not.
Then can she or can she not|persuade Formitz to meet with Halir?
I'll go along.
- We need a contingency.|- I agree.
- Any ideas?|- One or two.
- Your boyfriend?|- A colleague.
- Three's a crowd.|- Deal with it.
When's your next contact with Halir?
Like I told her, he calls me.|Tells me what to bring, where to meet.
Next time will be different.|You'll set the terms.
It'll never happen.
You tell him you know the name|of a traitor inside his organization.
Do I?
One will be provided.
It's still risky. He'll be heavily guarded.
We can deal with that.
You set the meeting. We'll triple your fee.
And provide sanctuary afterwards.
Of course.
Now, I will need|certain other things as well.
- Such as?|- She knows.
Forget it.
I'll give you an hour to think it over.
He wants the girl.|He won't cooperate unless he gets her.
Where is she?
I don't know.
Michael, find another way.|Pay him more money. Threaten him.
He's unstable as it is.|Threats might spin him out of control.
Even if I knew where Danielle is...
I wouldn't give her to that monster.
- I haven't said you should.|- That's what you're thinking.
You're gonna tell me to remember|those people at the bus depot.
Do you?
Good news.|The prisoner cooperated after all.
Gave us a way to Halir.
When I last saw her,|she was breaking her own bones.
You should have had more faith|in your own suggestion.
We let her rest, then brought her back in.|It worked.
- So there's no need for Formitz?|- Apparently not.
Halir will be meeting a courier|at 4:00 p. m...
in an Arab market in Berlin.
We'll tag the courier, follow him to Halir.
You'll remain in Section|to assist Birkoff with tactical overview.
Any other questions?
- Nikita, come with me.|- Birkoff, the mission-
- Walter just found out Belinda's dead.|- What?
Walter, you're scaring me.
What are you doing?
He asked for it, he's gonna get it!
You're gonna shoot Operations?
Right between the eyes.|Get out of my way!
Walter, I'm sorry Belinda's dead.|I'm sorrier than I can say.
How many times have you told me|not to take the Section personally.
I don't care what I told you!
It's pointless. They'll kill you, too!
I don't care!
I do!
So does Birkoff|and so do a lot of other people here!
We need you, Walter. I need you.
What would Belinda tell you to do?
Would she tell you|to throw your life away?
Or stay here for the people that need you?
It's not fair.
You've gotta go on, Walter.|You gotta go on.
That's what she would want.
What's happening here?
Nothing. We're just talking.
You and Birkoff|should be at your terminals.
I know. We're going now.
I'm sorry about Belinda.
The courier should arrive in a gray sedan.
Here he is.
He's on foot. Entering the square.
Team 1, tag him.
The courier's been tagged.
He's heading toward the northeast corner.
Hello, my friend.
What do you have for me today?
We've got Halir.
Perimeter status.
Perimeter's clear.
You can go.
Why was Formitz at the meet?
The original courier was detained.|We substituted Formitz...
a face Halir would trust.
- Why did he agree to help?|- More money.
No.
Section found Danielle|and gave her to him.
He knows his way around.|Perhaps he found her himself.
You called me in. Told me|about the prisoner. Let me interrogate her.
Meanwhile, Section was out|looking for Danielle. Isn't that right?
No.
Madeline lied when she told me|the prisoner broke.
Madeline wouldn't bother to lie.
She might.
To keep that mission running smoothly.
I want the truth, Michael.
Did the Section give Danielle to Formitz?
No.
What are you doing here?
Halir was taken.
- My God. Who took him?|- You know.
I don't. How would I know?
Because you betrayed him.
Are you crazy?
We have names. Dates.
They made me do it.
Formitz is dead.
Can't say I'm too sorry about that.
You don't seem to be surprised.
Dangerous line of work he's in.
His death compromises our ability...
to deal with the remnants|of Halir's organization.
We'll just have to find some other way.
This is important, Nikita.
I want the truth.
Did you give him up?
No.