IN MEMORY OF EARL J. LEE
DEAR HUSBAND AND FATHER
Hello, Etta.
I am your uncle Donnie.
The last time I saw
you were a baby.
And I'm your aunt Charlene.
Donnie is the brother of your dad,
rest in peace.
How would you feel if you and Pam
come and live with us
in the birthplace of your father?
How much do you weigh?
"You weight, what is?
I do not know. "Sixty-three kilos?
Let me see your stomach.
Do not do that.
Prove this for me.
Here comes Mama!
What will happen
when you turn this car?
- Nothing?
- Are you sure about that?
Because the circus is in town
and mother is as bad.
Okay.
That's my baby.
The circus is in town
and mother is as bad.
Watergate!
"I like that game.
"Yes, I know you like.
Well ...
Come, Bessie!
Oh, sorry!
Good Intentions
NUDE GIRLS
FULL BAR
What does "Shangri-La"?
It's a cute name for a brothel.
I want a brothel!
No honey, you want a "steed".
Help your brother
with the letter C.
Welcome to Myra, Georgia
Founded in 1886
Population 2214
Home of the cousin of Robert E. Lee
That's the dumbest
I've ever heard.
"You are the dumbest
I've heard.
- Shut up!
- You shut up!
Come on, boys.
Come here!
I'll give you change.
- I go first!
- No!
Do you have change for a dollar?
Shane!
God!
Children are out!
-Ches, I bought something.
"I thought we were saving.
Yes, but give me your shirt.
Do not you pay a discount.
I shall return.
The next time you need something,
just tell me to me.
I need something.
- What is that?
"They're fireworks.
Someone buy
all that can make
before Labor Day.
Should win
enough money at it.
How your last three plans?
I ...
Ches, how can we save money
for college ...
if whenever we have a little,
you blow it?
One of my inventions will succeed.
What if not?
What do we do?
Mommy! Help!
"I thought you had settled.
"I managed ...
Vomiting in the car, I know.
- Come here!
- Hold on, son!
Come!
Yes!
- You hear that?
- The engine is running!
Man, can you hear those horses?
It is a "rush"!
These stallions
are crazy!
Chester! Come on!
- Turn that already!
- Out!
Hey. Kyle no longer talk much.
Honey, that's because he is man.
At first
talked all the time.
Now comes the work
and turn on the TV.
It remains a sweet,
but it is very quiet.
But does he still want ...?
you know.
Yes, all the time.
I think that you need to close the factory
fun for a while.
Let him know that the entrance
not free.
Pam ...
Pam!
He has to learn
to think outside of your box. "
Shane, stop struggling with
your brother broke his leg.
Shane! Chris!
Help your uncle Kyle
to fix their racecar.
Here is
my future race team.
Come here little weird.
Want to show you
to change tires
in less than 14 seconds?
Give me that.
Well.
Hey. "Shane?
Shane, bring your brother here
and return to fight.
But he breaks his leg.
Come on!
That's my race team!
"Ches?
Why sometimes is not enough
a woman loves a man?
What?
I mean, look at Pam.
Kyle goes to Shangri-La ...
- Again with this?
"But she loves him.
He also loves her. You know?
It's just that the words and stuff
is difficult for some men.
Simply do not know say so.
And why he goes to a bar
of naked women?
- Do you really want to know?
"Yes.
Well. I'll tell you.
I like sunset, right?
I know you like
because whenever I see you watching
and sometimes make you mourn.
Do you remember the mountains
Yellowstone
on our honeymoon?
Yes, they were amazing.
A French man discovered them,
and named "Grand Tetons".
- Do you know why?
- Why?
Because he thought were
most wonderful
I had ever seen.
You know what "Teton"
in French?
It means chest.
- Ah!
- What?
Can not name a mountain
Big Boobs.
-Look it up if you want.
"I will.
Good.
That's the issue. You see, when we
to those bars of naked women
we see nothing
that beautiful sunsets.
If I ever catch you
looking at a couple of sunsets
eclipse will be damned
longer than you've ever seen.
-Ches, are you asleep?
-No.
Ches.
I do not want to hear you talk more
team about your future career
with Kyle and children, right?
Well, I was just kidding.
Kids will love
race cars.
Besides, I am
new sponsor.
What?
Only until you can get
a carburetor.
Can you imagine?
"Inventions and Liquor Chester
on the hood of his car
across the line
the end of the race.
Chessy, he has never finished
a single damn race.
- Are you crazy?
-No. I'm not.
He is your future husband.
I believe in him.
And you're not alone.
What's wrong with being a mechanic?
Kyle is mechanical.
My dad was a mechanic.
The mechanics
do not go to college.
Your dad did not go to college.
And why is it so important?
My dad was a good man.
Yes, Ches, Dad
was a good man.
But he was poor.
And we
we barely survive.
We are robbing Peter
to pay Paul
I do not want children to have
to fight for every measly penny.
One of my inventions will be successful.
Oh, Ches! No.
Children ... the only way
children will have a better life
is if they receive a good education.
And not chasing a dream
impossible half-finished.
"A half-finished?
When did you see that I leave something
half-finished?
- What was that?
- Nothing!
"I can not find them.
"Keep looking.
Ah ...
I found them!
Can I prove it?
You are very young.
I would like if I touched or
until I was eight years.
Hello?
I got the bill of your materials
fireworks ...
"Ches?
What? I told him to send him here.
"$ 336? Are you crazy?
Etta in a week
will triple the money.
God!
Oh, boy!
Are the children well?
No thanks to your stupid
fireworks.
Ches, may have died.
At least we
insured by fire.
Not by this fire.
Make fireworks
is illegal in the State of Georgia.
Should arrest you, Chester.
Consider it a personal favor
I will not do.
I put green this time.
How nice, Chester.
Well, come on!
Fight the fire.
One of my inventions will succeed.
Whenever we have a little,
you ... squandered it.
Good evening.
- Do not move!
- Ay!
Do not shoot me please, sir.
I have kids.
Put the money in the bag.
Please call 911.
The sheriff has just gone
Liquor to Chester.
Can you tell me your name, sir?
Sir?
Sorry about your door, Chester.
Hey, SWAT team.
He is gone. Oh ...
"They just rob me.
- Ches!
No!
Yes, the son of a bitch
was $ 200.
But ...
It will not happen again.
Who would want to shoot today?
I will not shoot anyone, Bo.
Looking for more ...
a deterrent.
Shooting is a deterrent.
It is the best deterrent there is.
It really has
many nice things.
Thank you, ma'am.
And how its value rises over time
how they do in the program?
If you know what to buy.
These two me
I look very similar.
Why this comes so much more?
Mainly it is for your state.
Honestly, every time
I'm leaning more
to sell these pieces
Internet.
Twelve-gauge shotgun.
Pumping action.
Once you put
the cartridge into the chamber,
soar alone.
Pow!
Here you go.
Still,
thousand dollars is a lot of money.
Would you accept 700 for it?
"For you?
They could be 800.
You sure are generous.
I saw this in
The traveling exhibition.
Did you ever handle a gun?
I can not say yes.
Meet me in the lagoon.
Come on.
Have you ever been restored?
No, ma'am.
Because restoring damaged ...
... the value of the piece.
Although you knew that, obvious.
High, high, high ...!
When did you steal a deer
liquor store?
Not often. Well.
Underpins the fat, right?
Aim to half of the body,
well have much margin for error.
Forward.
This is a big investment.
Very big.
If an investment
should take into account
higher status
This piece from here.
Oh no! No. ..
take this $ 800.
800 then.
Yes, but did not tell
Chester about this.
"It's a surprise.
"Yes, I would.
Hell, Ches.
I shot ... me.
Nobody shoots the target of Bo.
Give me the gun.
I'm afraid, honestly,
I can not sell
a firearm.
What?
How?
Hi, sweetie, what's this?
It is an antique table of rosewood.
Is not it beautiful?
Yes, where did he come from?
"From Uncle Jeffrey.
- A gift?
No. He died.
What was Jeff?
You met him last summer.
Do not think I've ever known.
Yes, I knew.
You liking it very much.
There seem to be very sad
respect.
Because he was sick
for long.
It was rather a relief.
Cancer?
- What?
-Jeffrey.
Yes .. yes.
Yes
Today I stopped by the store Bo.
Ches, no!
He wanted to buy a shotgun.
But I wanted it to sell.
Good. We have two children
they need their father
much more than $ 800
that guy took.
Who said it was $ 800?
I told you 200 because
I did not want you to worry.
Ches! You said 800.
Now, eat.
I'll attend.
"Etta Milford?
You are under arrest.
I love doing that.
- Ches's at home?
"Here, Ernie.
"By chance
not have one of those ...
... you took brownies
the baseball tournament for children?
There was not one, Ernie.
Here are some fresh
in the pantry.
Do you hide evidence?
I can not hide anything, Ernie.
- What is that?
"My first million.
It looks like a Swiss Army knife.
Yes, but have you ever seen
a Swiss Army knife with light?
"Yes.
- Really?
All the time.
"Hi, honey.
"Hello, beautiful. Come here.
Can I get you some dessert?
Depends on what you have.
Well ...
Apple pie warm.
Chocolate cake.
Fruit salad.
But I think the fruit cake
is better.
Yes, I think I'll try the cake.
You should get very good tips.
Shut up, Ches.
"The usual?
No, I will eat fruit salad.
Then you bring.
Thanks, honey.
Who's minding the store?
I'm trying something new ...
Why spend
much money on this?
No one runs to over 30 km
per hour in this desolate town.
Why does it always
both yearn to fines?
In villages like this,
most likely
is that it is someone you know.
And only means that another person
will think you're an idiot.
Do people think I'm an idiot?
Do not know. Everybody thinks
the others are idiots.
But when you're
new in town,
no sense
start with the left foot.
Let them be.
But we're cops.
I think you concentrate
much of it.
We have one.
Yes!
35. A new record.
Turn it on.
I brought you your favorite, enjoy it.
Wrecked car.
No.
It makes no sense to spend
five dollars in the restaurant
when your beloved wife can
prepare the same for a dollar.
Let me ask you something.
Cents ...
Do you cry when you play?
Every little bit helps.
Now, eat.
Hey ... Ernie said what?
He suspects the man who opened
The new thrift shop.
"The Old Curiosity Shop?
Since moving here. Boom!
I steal, "as well?
But I know how to recover the money.
Machine nutcracker with
best players in Atlanta Braves.
Braves most popular players,
honor of the region, do you follow?
Which players?
Not sure yet.
Not even wears the uniform
Braves team.
It is a work in progress. Eh ...
Voila!
The pecan.
"State number one
producer of pecans?
-Georgia.
"You're joking.
No, no. This is good. See?
This is good.
Of course, it is assumed that now
should break the shell ...
... but this is only a prototype.
- Did you do this?
"Yes.
And a gentleman in Atlanta
told me to do a lot more
extent that they can do well.
- How much will it cost?
"Only $ 11 each.
If I could get a hundred ...
"$ 1100?
- Are you paid for?
"I paid him.
I still have no money.
It is not Labor Day.
Chester!
No desperdiciarás
our money on this!
A waste?
This is me.
You know.
I am not this.
Is the liquor store?
It's not what I like.
You know.
I always knew.
No. That's me.
I can feel it.
Come here.
What does that say?
-Pan.
"Go and bring a bit of your mother.
Hello.
The table that I sold.
Have you served us well?
You do not hear that.
It's in my hall, aging
and becoming more valuable every day.
I have some new parts
new arrivals
if you want to go to see them.
I was bottoming
after this table.
Well, I have almost no space.
Perhaps it will sell all
a colleague in Savannah
at a discount price.
It was great to see.
Why is looking like that?
Son, your mother is
a very beautiful woman.
That's their way
make me a compliment.
You can do that sort of thing
when you charge less
than other markets.
Of course, if it were not so ...
would be considered inappropriate.
Is not it true, Mr. Simmons?
Very beautiful.
I want to be like him when I grow up.
- A chef or an elf?
"I'll be a fireman.
Yes?
How about fire chief?
You know, if you study
and receive a good education,
can be anything you want.
You can have things and do things ...
Dad and I never had.
Hey ... go to the living room
watching television.
Did you find this chair
at a flea market?
Years ago, yes.
Remember how much you paid for it?
Five dollars, maybe.
- How much do they worth today?
"No idea.
I think I would
about a thousand dollars.
Damn!
How beautiful surroundings.
Why you can not do that?
Wow, this is a beautiful piece.
"Surely yes.
- What?
- Huh?
You sure can not be interested
in that chair Windsor?
It is the 19th century.
Again try to sell me
expensive parts.
All I can do
is buy this.
I'll take it.
Well, you can take it.
Can reservármela?
Why should I go for cash.
"I can read the future.
- Predict the Future?
Yes, I have ways.
In fact, I know
where will you go in an hour.
Where will I go?
I think you'll
in the back seat
my Cruiser, handcuffed.
You're bad!
No idea how you see.
Always be
where to find you, Ernie.
I want a pint
pieces of chocolate, please.
"Today you are your own?
No, I have to watch Rob Buck
Chester store now.
I think we would have more crime
if we had more laws.
You understand what I mean?
Ernie, how are you
your wife ... Angela?
She is fine,
thanks for asking.
Well.
I guess I'll see later.
"Have a nice day, ma'am.
Good-bye.
Hi, guys.
Who is hungry?
Here you go.
Backwards. Come on.
Come and eat.
Mama needs a new chair.
There is plenty for everyone.
"Buck? Are you there?
We have a 3-8-7
in progress
Twelve on the road!
"3-8-7?
Goats in the middle of the road.
Could you leave that
and come help?
My God, we
a bloody stampede! Come on!
Are you serious?
You know that another liquor store
in the next town?
20, 40, 60, 70 ...
Is that new?
Yes
110, 15 ...
If you do a habit of this
Will you buy a rope?
This thing hurts.
Ah!
- Ah! Here comes the train.
- Ah, Earl!
Here comes the train.
I can hear the whistle!
Calling all cars, there
liquor store robbery in Chester.
Please respond immediately.
Damn!
"Like I'll bring the beers, huh?
I do not want the other junk.
This time I want Bud.
Shaping in the area
excess in the hips ...
- What are you looking at?
- See that?
This woman invented
a pair of nylon stockings
That make the rear
That woman looks like a peach!
God! For me
it looks great.
Agreed.
Well, what aspect
had a criminal?
What was he like?
Plump, with mask and gun.
Did you see anyone out there
with that description?
Hey, son.
I did not steal.
Do not be angry with me.
Ernie, is the second time!
What the hell happened ...
I just got out of a situation
dangerous to come to assist you.
What happened?
"Was actually a squirrel?
I think we forget
who you're talking.
No, I know exactly
with whom I speak.
I know by the chocolate sauce
on your lips, constable.
Whatever. We ...
... catch this bastard.
"I must get some Bud.
"You do not drink Bud beer brand.
I guess this is
a good time to start.
You put on your account?
Or do you pay now?
For any other strange thing ...
you know, call me.
I had a strange conversation
with Kyle last night.
Closing the plant
fun, right?
Yes, Chester said that you had
furniture inherited recently.
Did he say that?
Apparently Yes your relatives
are dropping like flies.
I mean who are my relatives.
And I'd never heard of them.
I had that chair
in the basement for centuries.
Sure.
And that table?
Someone I know
is very curious this morning.
Etta! I saw that chair in the shop
Zachary last week.
I'm sure it's
common design.
No, no. It was this! One day I took
food and bumped into her.
The tag said $ 1,500.
I almost had a heart attack. I figured
he would make me pay for it.
Was it not so?
I knew it. I knew it.
I knew it!
Where did you get so much money?
"I took a loan.
- Who?
The store.
Chester would not allow that.
Oh, my God.
My God. God ...
No! There is not, above.
- Come on! Arriba!
- God, Etta!
You were stealing
to your own husband?
Will cross the floor
and you'll go straight to hell.
"No, I'm investing in your future!
- With a table and a chair?
"Until now.
- How now?
You can not think
to do it again!
I do not know! Still did not think well.
Okay?
Yes of course.
This last time
Chester really shocked.
God, now what?
What are you doing
a wolf in the car?
That is not a wolf.
It's a watchdog.
Honey, come and see.
We saw something similar
Yellowstone
and said he was a wolf.
The wolves are related
with dogs.
Some dogs
somewhat resemble the wolves.
So this too.
That thing
looks exactly like a wolf.
God!
Chris, Shane, Get away from there!
The next to the thief
Chester appears
will have a big surprise.
Should he take that thing to the store?
Yes
Why? Why eat
the thief before you eat?
The man who sold it to me
gave me a brochure with their orders.
Sure I'd like to see.
You are in the car.
My fault.
You may want to drop a note.
Hi, Uncle Kyle!
I did not know that your sister got married.
He never married.
I told them to call you uncle
to understand the hint.
Hey!
Uncle Kyle!
Shane, get down!
Shane, down!
It makes no sense
annoy Uncle Kyle
when he is doing something
who knows he should not.
There is nothing wrong
a bit of harmless fun.
Mr Simmons,
I'm raising a girl.
Please do not contradict
front of him.
Get in the car.
Stay here.
Right back.
I said, "I do not care, man.
I have a black cousin. "You know what?
They do not understand anything.
What the hell?
Yes, dear, yes, honey!
Load and shoot!
- Stop!
- What the hell are you doing?
I can not speak, Buck.
I'm busy.
Hello, Etta. I did not know it was you.
See you later.
Will let you do that?
Is Etta Milford.
When you were here
longer understand it.
Just stay behind
that line there.
Are you sure?
I do it every day.
Sitzen Sie!
That is supposed to calm,
but I think what makes her angry.
Do you have a name?
I've been calling
"Shut the snout.
Shut the mouth!
"It's therapeutic, right?
"Something like that.
Pasa and find what you want.
There are pig ...
"Okay. Bye.
"Goodbye.
Hey, I'll have no customers
if you keep barking like this.
I do not earn much money.
Pam is the only thing I
that really matters in this world.
All the money you would spend
I have to spend it on this.
And strippers.
Who do you think you are?
Did you ever think
maybe not your duty
decide what is right
for everyone else?
She is my sister.
How funny.
You say it as if you were his mistress.
"I do not like.
"For this is good for you.
Very beautiful.
Here you go.
Trouble in paradise?
Some types just want to be
freer than others.
Kyle needs a little help
to be driven to the corral.
So talking about me
before getting married?
Chester, you were born in the barnyard.
Hey, Bo. What happened?
Zachary happened.
I rented the place.
"Temporarily".
Yes
Let's take it back.
What is all this?
The Santa's workshop.
Just ... this ...
... becomes this.
Zachary comes here every night
to work with the furniture.
Yes, he has become
a science.
So he fakes
selling antiques.
Yes, well ...
Can not say
I agree.
But ...
sells most on eBay.
You can sell anything
on eBay.
A guy tried to sell
his kidney on eBay.
- No!
"Yes.
He was not allowed.
- Ready?
- Countdown!
Three, two ...
- Arms!
- Yes!
Right there!
A little of this, a bit of that!
Right there! Come back here!
Right there!
Yeah, baby!
Hey!
What the hell did you say?
What I said to whom?
Kyle.
Well, children. Come on.
Get in the house a minute, let's go.
So ready.
Go.
Finish in a minute.
What you earn
to threaten me and my boyfriend?
I would not say it was a threat.
Etta, he saved the money
to buy me a ring!
Yes, a ring Etta.
And you had to ruin everything.
I know he's going to that club.
Go to your boss.
Pam.
For once in your life,
Stay out of my life.
God knows we already have enough
issues assailing Chester.
"You should watch what they say ...
- You know what?
The best thing that could happen is
someone was listening to this.
- How did I do?
"Six miles per hour.
Improving this, braggart.
Let me show you how.
"Come on.
- Ready?
Yes!
- Yes! How did you like that?
- Is this what they do?
Sometimes.
Am I eligible?
Place your bets.
Hey!
Etta!
Just who he wanted to see.
Hear, hear!
- What is the rush?
"Things to do.
Are you too busy
to see the business of your life?
"Yes.
"As you wish, but what the hell?
You're here, I'm here,
We have good things there.
Come on.
"Do not take long, come on!
"Okay.
Is this your first time.
When was the last time
you did calibrate it?
And where are the business
of which I spoke?
Ah! I sold them.
- So fast?
"Yes, ma'am.
Okay. Gotta go.
No, wait.
Just ... Wait!
I was just about to close.
Can I offer you a tour?
Could you show the details
antiques business?
I have an idea of the details
of which you speak and no thanks.
Wait, wait. Come on.
Never give him a chance
for no man.
God!
Go!
That's not right.
"Stay here.
"I will go to see what happens. Please?
We're closed!
Blow me down!
Lipstick.
Now yes, friend!
Let me show you what happens
the next time your armed robber
try to steal.
This is robbery!
Put all your money
in my stocking.
Did not you hear?
I said you put all the money ...
In half my fucking filthy!
Unless you put your money on my half
I'll shoot you in the face!
Sorry, sir. This transaction
can not be processed
this protective armor
I installed.
Thank you very much.
How are you, Sheriff?
Kyle, hello.
A hole?
If you are busy,
back later.
No, Kyle is preparing single
to remove the glass.
Must speak for a second.
What, Ernie?
Well ...
We know
long ...
Yes
Well ...
Last night I saw something ...
What?
"Bubis?
Did you see boobies, man?
"Good?
Zachary!
He is not here.
What are you doing here?
The last time I was drunk
I promised Zach
would look after his shop.
Drunken Promises stink.
Where is he?
Do not know.
"But I'll tell you spent.
"No, no, no.
Ouch!
It is an antique table of rosewood.
Is not it beautiful?
God!
Security guard Zachary
a good record of everything, right?
Yes, my friend.
It is extremely
flammable, Ches.
Okay.
I do not do it again.
I told you not like!
I will go for adhesive bandages.
We need to talk.
- Can you wait?
- Are you going to bed with Zachary?
- What?
- Answer me!
-Ches, children are upstairs.
- That's not the right answer!
No, I'm going to bed
with Zachary.
Ernie says he saw last night.
"Ernie says?
I went to ask
on some antiques.
Turns out he was interested
in a couple of different boxes
and gave him a slap.
That's what I saw Ernie.
I stopped by his shop this afternoon,
And guess what I discovered?
Expand Cart.
One of a table, a chair.
No uncle Jeffrey,
and no cousin Jake!
You complain all the damn day:
"We have to save money,"
and sales to buy furniture
do not need.
No, not furniture, Ches.
They are investments.
Yes, I saw on TV
people have antiques
who think they are worthless
and end up being worth
thousands of dollars!
This crap does not.
Yes, Ches, look!
This is the 18th century.
I have a book with a photo
exactly like a table
in a museum.
Then, when we need
money for college
We sell!
It is like money in the bank
you can end up spending.
It's safe.
These things are becoming more valuable.
- These are copies, Etta!
"Of course not.
Watch this.
Queen Anne Chair
crafted in 1920 with ...
I went to his workshop.
Our television
is older than that chair!
Why I do this?
I do not understand how to raise the money
to buy to get started.
It costs us survive
in the situation we are.
On top of this maniac
It's stealing, and you ...
No!
Oh no!
I'm sorry, Ches.
Do you stole from me?
No, I stole for us,
by children.
Where are we going?
To request a refund.
Good afternoon, Etta.
You do not seem the type murderer.
How could you deceive me?
What?
I tried to buy
truly ancient pieces.
But, no.
You wanted good prices.
From this damn program
TV, everyone is looking for money.
I had to sell
I make furniture
to maintain
the shop open.
That money was for my children.
Well, call the police.
You know what ...
... is the strangest thing.
You say you have little money.
But every time
they steal your husband,
you enter here full of cash.
We are the same, Etta.
I'm not saying that's wrong.
Perhaps the humble
inherit the earth,
but spend very badly waiting
all others die.
Thought so.
Do not make me angry, Etta.
These children ... suffer much
with a mother in prison.
You should do assess that weapon.
Wait here, kids.
May God bless the USA, my friend.
Hands up!
Now!
Dude, she's my favorite.
It's spectacular.
Look at her.
Damn!
What do you think, mate?
- Ay!
- Damn!
Here you go.
"Need help?
Where are we going?
- Did you see Thelma and Louise?
- Who are they?
Two robbers who jumped
on a cliff with the car.
That's the most stupid
I have ever heard.
Come quick!
I'm trying.
I'm very nervous ...
"Mom was very angry with you.
- Shut up!
- You shut up!
- Hey! I said shut up!
I said shut up. Ouch!
Hello?
Shane!
Is that your car?
Shane! Turn! Turn!
- Beware of the truck!
- Shane!
Mom!
Dad!
Help!
Get in the truck.
Get in the van
now.
What the hell was that?
-Ches ...
- What did my kids in the car?
You know what could have happened?
They could have died!
- Etta!
- Etta?
Oh, no ...
My God.
- What is past?
"Chester, I ...
- I do not use that!
"That's all I found.
I use red.
I want my mommy.
Mother always knows
I use red!
I looked for you all night.
Damn, Etta!
You scared me so much.
God, Pam!
Sign in God.
And how are the kids?
As well as could be expected.
And Ches?
I think you should give
some space.
Etta ...
Etta, you were always so strong.
Maybe it's time to start
to have a little faith in people.
You know, I was there
the day that Dad died.
You were only a baby.
I promised
would never need anyone.
Never trust anyone.
That would take care of me and you alone,
and would receive a good education.
And then mom was ...
And I failed.
I did not study anything,
I did not care about me,
I did not care about you.
Hell, I did not care for anyone.
You have not failed!
Look ...
Dad died,
but, honey,
We are still here!
You can solve this.
Your family still loves you.
Even Kyle still loves you.
I punctured its tires.
Yes, I know.
Let's go to breakfast.
Row, Row Your Boat
Gently down the river
- Gently!
- What?
- It gently, you said something else!
- Mom!
Shut up.
Hey!
What the hell you looking at?
Bitch.
Here you go.
Eat something.
Come.
So if I'm good
Chester let me go home.
Yes, that's the plan.
Except that the same
will happen again.
"You start stealing again?
No! He spent all our money
in their crazy inventions
and children do not go to college
or have what they need.
O. ..
Or you, Miss,
give him a chance.
And you'll be proud of him.
I liked enough ...
that baseball nutcracker.
Eat your food.
Nothing you can do
about it now.
"Pam?
We will do business together.
No. You're crazy.
How is your ice cream?
Tell you what,
it feels great in my mouth.
Are they still open?
"Five more minutes.
- Can I use the bathroom?
Thanks!
- Want one?
"No, maybe not.
"Testing, one, two.
"I'll leave in an hour.
Yes?
How strange to see you here, Ernie.
I like ice cream.
Yes
Clear.
Good night!
I thought I could find you here.
I've never been here before.
Ernie, I need your help.
After what you did
Chester?
Why did you say
I was cheating?
This is not
my first rodeo, miss.
I saw what I saw.
And I heard what I heard.
Now for the first time in your life
you can help someone
you really need,
or we can do to force.
Looks like the force.
Because the circus is in town
and mother is as bad.
Ay.
I touched your hair, sorry.
Oh, yes!
You make me feel like a king.
I feel like a king!
Good job, Ernie!
Protects and provides your services!
Do not think you know
and the librarian, O'Neill!
Do not tell Angela, right?
No. No.
But this girl,
could do
for a few beers, Bud.
She really likes beer.
And not the only thing she likes.
Ernie.
I need your help.
I thought we could
paint here, in this way.
This does not seem right.
What?
We are police!
How do you feel now?
What can I do?
You paint.
Take care you, Picasso.
I will cover Time
from 7:00 in the morning.
... football.
Well, was it tight
and central player?
Yes!
I grew up ten minutes from here.
- Yes? That's great.
- Yes!
This way behind.
- That is the helmet he used?
- Yes! Want to try it?
Maybe later.
Good morning, Buck!
Ernie said he could use
the computer.
What business do you have with Ernie?
After today, no more.
Thank you very much. Thank you.
Handled with care, beautiful.
Thank you.
Hi, how are you?
Stop at the side, please.
These prices are
absolutely incredible!
I do not know how you do it!
Me neither.
Hi, honey.
How young so considerate.
"You should take good care.
"That I do.
What is the problem, sheriff?
Violation of Section 23.32.31
Vehicle Code.
Bring a light off.
Registration and driver's license.
I take the mechanic
immediately.
Registration and driver's license,
please.
Hey! That's my table
fucking idiot!
Oh no, fortunately there are more
where it came from that.
Okay, no problem.
- What? Wait, that's not mine.
"I see.
I suppose the fairy
of marijuana left it there?
It's oregano. Sniff it.
- It's oregano, sheriff! Sniff it!
"Get out of the car.
I do not smoke, and do not cook.
- You must be kidding!
"Hands behind ...
Entitled
to remain silent.
Anything you say ...
What the hell is this?
Lord.
I say this very often.
Please.
Do not ruin the moment.
Yes, sir.
Entitled
to remain silent.
Anything you say
can be used against you ...
Sheriff, things
that truck is mine.
These furnishings are from my shop!
Are taking my stuff!
Things that truck is mine!
How can be yours,
if they are in the truck of them?
"Those things are mine.
-Lie.
This is unacceptable, sheriff!
Am I entitled to a call!
"Yes, I will call.
"Wait.
There are two empty cells.
Why am I here
a guy naked?
Come to papa.
How is everything?
I'm almost done scanning them.
Well.
Let me know if you need help.
Thanks, Ernie.
Your welcome.
Your friend, Zachary.
It seems he is wanted
in four states.
Mail fraud, fraud, theft,
assault, violence.
Wow!
Yes
Of the worst sort has happened
for this town.
And I caught it.
It feels good
finally be the sheriff.
Ernie, you're the sheriff.
"I know.
So ...
What's where Chester
led you on your anniversary?
- Saranby?
-Saranby.
Last night I saw in the closet ...
... Angela's dress.
And while I do not give
an excuse to use it.
Yes I too have
some elegant clothes.
I was somewhat adjusted
but I suppose
that if I let the ice cream ...
I think this
is a very good idea.
"Yes, I know you think that.
"Yes ...
Can we open them?
Do not know.
Do you think you can open them?
I think so.
I think it's Christmas.
Here are Shane, Chris and Mom.
Merry Christmas.
Okay, guys, break your ...
Merry Christmas,
received a hair dryer!
Hey, that's my foot!
Mom is here?
"Go back to sleep.
"I thought I heard my mom.
She's not here.
Sheriff!
Do not make me go in there for you.
Hello!
You know? I have a cot there.
You could use it if you want.
I'm fine.
I go to Atlanta.
No, not going as well as you are
I will take Miss Sunshine.
Why do not you join us?
Okay, Ernie,
thanks anyway.
I said calm down!
I need to use
my pepper spray.
There's a wasp! Ouch!
Some people never learn.
Ya, stop!
Hey, hey, Ernie! Him ..
Yes
I'll wait ...
Are you okay?
I'll be fine.
Hey, Etta, once you serve.
Yeah, this is Chester.
I are stealing again.
Yes It's her.
How you're eating dinner?
Ernie, dammit!
Mr. Simmons brought this.
Thought you would need.
This completes the entire game.
We had a quiet day.
But I will give some
hundred dollars.
Do not.
Okay.
Let's see what's in your wallet.
Chester.
You know
how stubborn I can be.
And then start
to get ideas in my head.
As steal all our money.
I know that makes no sense.
I always wanted to have children
more opportunities than us.
Is not trusted
that I could?
No.
And that I was wrong.
What? Take the money
was not enough,
Did you have to steal
my nutcracker?
I took him to Atlanta and I got together
the manufacturer of the speaker.
The first batch of a hundred should
be ready next week.
"The first batch?
I ordered two.
"200?
Are you crazy? I ...
I can not sell two hundred.
He did not even know if I can sell one.
Well ... and sold.
-A $ 21.50 on eBay.
- What?
It says here
18 people auctioned.
And not bad
to be a one-day auction.
Costing $ 11 to make it,
earn just $ 10.
$ 10.
$ 10
200 nutcracker ...
Two thousand dollars!
And perhaps the beginning of our
saving for college.
One of them succeeded.
I did.
Yes .. did.
Now go home.
I know there are a couple of kids
who miss their mother.
Subtitles: Arigone
As for this weapon, comes
of the Civil War era.
Interestingly, very similar
the rifle that is believed
that General Robert E. Lee
he gave Ulysses S. Grant
at the end of the Civil War.
Grant returned
many years later.
Esperance but not much.
Because this is not the rifle
Robert E. Lee,
distinguished
by initials
recorded near the latch.
Unfortunately, this rifle
was lost in history.
Her whereabouts are unknown.
Due to the excellent condition
his gun
in an auction could be worth
between six and eight thousand dollars.
However, if the weapon appeared
Lee in the auction,
that figure is closer
a one million dollar.
Wow! Great.