(birds chirping)
You said this was a shortcut.
If we'd kept to the road,
- we'd be in Sentinum already.
- (growls)
We're lost!
No, we're not.
Just follow me.
(bleats)
Look at that.
There must be
some hunters out here.
Man:
I don't see anyone around.
How about roast hare for supper?
I say we take the lot.
That sheepskin will fetch
a good price in Sentinum.
(heavy footsteps,
creature snarling)
- (creature snorts)
- (bleating)
- (creature grunts, roars)
- Man: What's that?
Aw, it's just an animal.
(creature thuds)
(growling)
Oh...
- (roars)
- It's a cyclops!
(grunting)
(screams)
Let it go, Titus!
Let him have it.
(roars)
(people chatting)
(neighs)
By your look, Senators,
I see bad news travels fast.
An alarming loss, Caesar.
I think we should forbid transit through
the territory pending an investigation.
That's not good enough, Casca.
The cyclops declared war on Rome
- by murdering our citizens.
- My nephew's right.
The only decision left to make,
Senators, is...
whom do we send
after this monster?
If Livius, our recently deceased
and much missed leader of the Senate,
were here today,
I know what he would advise.
He'd say, "Send the best
and bravest young officer.
Send my son Marcus."
Good idea, Casca. Tell Marcus
to assemble his troops right away.
- I'll bring him the message myself.
- Good.
(laughing)
(gasps)
Marcus, I thought I'd find you here.
Marcus!
(smacks)
By the order of the Emperor Tiberius,
you are to set out at once
to subdue a cyclops that ambushed
and killed two of our merchants.
But of course, Falco.
And would you like me to take care
of that petrifying witch Medusa
on my way back?
(chuckles)
This is not a joke, Marcus.
There's a cyclops out there.
It killed two of our merchants
and ate them. We know this
from the one man that survived...
- Menander.
- (chokes)
Menander?
You could take anything he says
with a pinch of salt.
The cyclops is a story told
by drunkards and beggars.
Those beasts were
exterminated long ago
when Augustus himself
wiped out the last of them.
And even if
one cyclops did still exist,
he's hardly a threat to Rome.
That's not your decision
to make, is it?
I suggest you muster
your men at once.
(chair clatters)
Apparently they'll have
to carry you up the road.
The only way they'll ever
have to carry me
is triumphant into Rome.
Tell the Emperor Tiberius
I salute him and obey.
I don't think I've had the pleasure
of making your acquaintance.
I am Falco Maximilius.
- Flavia Corona.
- I'm delighted to meet you, Flavia.
I've heard that you were the star
of the evening at Cato's Saturnalia.
You know, I'm planning
an evening of my own.
A symposium...
just like Plato's...
with the most distinguished
philosophers. And just one woman
is invited to join us
in discourse on the art of love.
Would you be interested
in joining us, Flavia?
Of course.
(Marcus chuckles)
Severus, fetch Tarquin
while I round up the others.
Sorry, Marcus, Tarquin paid me
to take a couple months' leave.
He paid you? If he wants leave,
he's supposed to pay me!
I was going to pass it on to you,
but after a few drinks...
I just...
- Here's your money.
- But I don't want the money.
I want the man,
so find him!
And tell him to report
to duty at once.
Yes, sir.
(sighs)
Halt!
(bleating)
Menander wasn't lying after all.
The cyclops ate them.
The one thing Menander
wasn't lying about.
He claimed the cyclops ambushed them
while they were looking for a shortcut.
I think he saw them trying
to steal his food.
There's some sheep too.
They probably tried to grab them.
Severus: He could be lurking
around here anywhere.
- Send scouts?
- No!
We flush him out.
Ho!
- Put the cloaks over your armor.
- Yes, sir.
(bleating)
(cyclops roaring)
Charge!
(shouting)
Adjust your aim!
(blows whistle)
Fire!
Pull it tightly!
(cyclops grunting)
No!
I didn't order you to kill him.
But your orders were
to subdue him, sir.
That's right, so I'm going to bring
this beast back to Rome in chains.
Let everyone see that Marcus Romulus
has subdued the cyclops.
Tarquin, get the chains.
Marcus:
Severus!
No!
Aim your spears
at his eye now!
Shackle and blindfold him.
(low growling)
To Rome!
Falco: I have
a little problem to tell you about.
Saragosa is complaining
that he ordered
two lions
and two tigers for the games.
- Mm-hmm.
- But the cyclops attacked the caravan
bringing them from Carthage.
Supposedly he tore the animals apart
- and ate them.
- What a beast!
- What's this?
- The price of the animals.
Saragosa expects me
to pay for them?
They were killed
on a Roman road.
Let's eat.
Who are you?
Who sent you?
He's Julia's son, Uncle.
Julia... your herbalist.
I know who Julia is.
Don't ever
creep up on me like that.
Didn't your mother ever tell you?
No?
(chuckles)
If I don't trust a yes-man,
what do you think I feel about a man
who answers both yes and no
to the same question?
Very shrewd, Uncle.
I'll have him flogged and sent away.
So someone else can turn him
against me? No, Falco.
He's so stupid,
he could be dangerous.
He may be stupid, Uncle,
but he's also Julia's son,
and she's been a good
and faithful servant.
Hmm.
What about his father?
We can't be certain
who he was, can we?
Exactly.
So...
(clears throat)
You're adding on to your new villa?
Just a small addition.
Nothing extravagant,
given the times we're living in.
Of course.
Have that slave boy arrested
for assaulting me
and then sell him to your overseer.
Girl, more wine.
Begone.
(man and woman moaning)
(knocks on door)
Oh, wait.
Wait wait.
Come.
Ah. It's about time
he showed up.
Get rid of the girl.
Make sure
she doesn't steal anything.
(hammering)
Cletus!
You are six months
behind schedule
and 20,000 denarii over budget.
Give me one reason why
I shouldn't have you beaten
and crucified in the middle
of the Forum for everyone to see.
A thousand pardons, Vizier.
With our armies fighting the Huns
good slaves are hard to come by.
I will double my efforts.
Everyone,
including Tiberius himself,
knows about my renovations
because of your sloth.
Be quick
before I lose my patience.
(hammering)
(screams)
You clumsy old fool.
And that's for wasting
the time of two men.
Cletus.
Don't be a fool.
You'll only get a public execution.
Back to work.
(sobbing)
Barbara, bring me a hot one.
Hey, you, farmer boy!
Come on, burn it.
(whimpers)
Julian.
Boy, get on with it!
(grunts)
(shrieking)
Now work him.
(wails, crying)
We all have to answer
to the name "boy" here,
but you are Julian,
and I am Gordian.
Put this on.
(horse neighs)
I don't see Marcus.
Do you, my dear?
If he'd succeeded
in subduing the cyclops,
he'd be leading his troops
in triumph.
Guard!
Go warn the emperor
it's bad news.
Marcus Romulus has failed.
Go!
(crowd cheering)
(cyclops growling, roaring)
Boy, stop the guard from telling
the emperor that Marcus has failed
or I'll look like a fool. Run!
Flavia!
What are you doing?
I'm going to see what Marcus
has under his blanket.
The cyclops perhaps?
- (cyclops roars)
- (screams)
Citizens of Rome!
I have returned
and I bring with me
the beast that has been
terrorizing our countryside.
I give to you
- the cyclops!
- (loud cheering)
(roaring)
(crowd laughing)
Shoo! Go away.
I congratulate you, Marcus.
You and your troops acquitted
yourselves well.
Thanks to you
another enemy
of Rome is in chains.
(whispers)
Ah yes.
I just have one question.
Why did your second-in-command lead
the triumphal return to Rome?
I sent him ahead to escort
my fallen comrades,
so that the proper honor
and respect was paid to them.
You see, I knew that once
the crowd saw me
lead the cyclops captive into Rome,
- it would be a circus.
- Hmm.
And quite a circus
it was, huh, Falco?
In that case, I commend you...
and promote you
to the rank of tribune.
I thank you, Caesar.
I believe it is customary
for a land grant...
a modest land grant
to be awarded.
You've just been elevated to tribune
and you have the effrontery
to ask for more?
I'm simply asking for what I deserve
and for what is customary.
But if it is a question
between the two,
I would rather have the land
than the title, Caesar.
The Emperor Tiberius
rewards as he sees fit.
And what the emperor gives,
he can also take away.
There will be no land grant
and I revoke the promotion.
Falco:
Dismissed...
Centurion.
Fine, now let's go over the menu
for the banquet.
Rome's victory over the cyclops
calls for boar as the main dish.
- Half a boar.
- What?
A whole boar split lengthwise...
serve one half, store the other.
- Don't you think that'll look silly?
- Excuse me?
Anyway, half a boar isn't going to serve
all the guests we've invited.
Then split the guests...
put the first tier in the dining room,
second tier in the annex.
Serve the second tier eggs and greens.
(chuckles)
Put Marcus in the second tier.
Ah.
- (cyclops growling)
- (crowd laughing)
(screaming)
(wood creaking)
Cyclops, no!
Stop right there.
(shrieking)
(chomping)
- Stop him, Caesar.
- Caesar: Stop!
Do not kill the creature.
(chomping continues)
I think he was hungry.
You're right. Find the butcher,
tell him to bring meat...
the biggest cuts he's got.
Now why did you want me
to save that awful creature?
I have an idea for you
to save some money
- on the games.
- Really?
- What?
- Throw the cyclops into the arena.
Hmm. I shall have to pay to put
the gladiators up against him though.
Not if the man-eating cyclops is pitted
against the vilest criminals in Rome.
It would be far more entertaining
than executing them
and the public will love it.
It's a good idea, Falco.
We'll start with the lowest of the low...
Cletus's convict slaves.
- No, but they're building my villa.
- Easily replaced.
- You think Rome is short of slaves?
- Well, actually...
- Are you disagreeing with me?
- No...
Emperor.
- Cletus's slaves it shall be.
- Good.
We have new orders.
They want him hungry.
(cyclops roars)
(growling)
- Any sign of Barbara?
- I don't see her.
- Hey, shut up!
- (spear clanks)
Guard!
- Guard!
- (banging)
- What do you want now?
- Where's our bread?
You tell Cletus if we don't eat,
we can't work.
He don't care.
Barbara?
Barbara!
Yes?
Get on with it.
Of course.
Higher.
Higher and more pressure.
(crunching)
(gasping)
Barbarian...
you wanna play rough, do you?
(grunting)
You want me to beat you?
The slaves haven't eaten.
Shouldn't I bring them
their bread?
No.
But they'll be
too weak to work.
They won't have to.
Barbara?
(rooster crows)
You there! Halt.
- Gordian...
- No talking!
No, please, I saved
the biggest one for Gordian.
- Why?
- It... it's his birthday.
(chuckles)
Yeah, his last one.
Well then, make the most of it.
What is this?
A love letter from Barbara?
She can't write.
- She can't draw either.
- The message is clear enough:
We're to be thrown into the arena.
Our only hope now is escape.
(cyclops grunting softly)
Shut up, you one-eyed bastard.
(snorts)
That's what I thought.
Bark's worse than your bite.
The big ones always are.
Oh ho ho ho!
(men laughing)
(man whistles)
- All of it.
- (grunts)
(chatting)
(pot smashes)
(roars)
(men gasping)
(chomps)
(roars)
- (flies buzzing)
- Oh my God!
Get the troops.
Tell them the cyclops is loose
and it's killing people.
Now run!
Barbara!
- Where do you think you're off to?
- The cyclops is loose.
He's killing people
and eating them.
Good job. Now you run home
and stay inside, okay?
He's gonna try and leave the city.
I want you to alert
the guards at the gate.
We'll split our forces...
you flush out the neighborhood
east of the Temple of Jupiter,
I'll scour the western sector.
Tarquin, keep the people
off the streets.
I don't want another person
killed by that cyclops.
The rest of you with me!
Cletus:
Barbara.
(basket thuds)
Come here. There's nothing
to be afraid of,
- unless you lie to me.
- (cyclops grunts)
Back!
Open it up... quickly!
(keys jangle)
- Open the door!
- (roars)
No! Let me in!
(cyclops departing)
Move!
Now's our chance...
while the troops are going
after the cyclops.
In case anyone sees us,
the story is...
I am your owner now,
leading you to safety
and away from the cyclops.
- (arrows flying)
- (roars)
Column, march!
Archers!
(screams)
Halt!
Archers, bring up the ballista.
Cyclops, surrender or die!
(roars)
Fire!
He's still alive.
Shall I kill him?
No.
The Emperor Tiberius forbids it.
Just make sure you secure him
properly this time.
Yes, sir.
(door clangs, rattles)
- (cyclops roars)
- No!
Cyclops, no.
You are never getting
out of here again.
- (roars)
- Sir?
Tiberius summons you.
There has been a slave uprising.
(sighs)
I warned all of you.
As long as Marcus remains in the guard,
there is incompetence.
From now on, listen to me.
Remember that.
The scum of the earth...
slaves convicted of crimes
against their masters
and sentenced to hard labor
murdered my overseer Cletus
when he was bringing them
extra bread
out of the kindness of his heart.
They found the loaves
on the prison floor,
stained with his blood.
They slit his throat
with his own key.
(panting)
You sent for me.
I hope you've managed to secure
your prisoner this time, Marcus.
The slaves would never have
escaped the city
if the entire garrison
hadn't been deployed
to recapture the cyclops.
True, Falco. True true.
There's no time to lose. I'm dispatching
you and Marcus immediately
to capture these murdering slaves.
Show them no mercy.
Give them no quarter but bring back
as many as you can alive.
I want all of Rome
to watch them die in the arena.
One more thing:
Since Marcus has been demoted,
you, Falco, will be
commanding officer.
Marcus will follow your orders.
Now go
make yourselves heroes.
They must be heading for the harbor,
thinking they can trust
the Greeks to ship them out.
Maybe this lot's
smarter than you think.
They could take the pass into Gaul.
Wait for my order!
I'm waiting.
Follow me.
There they are.
They're nowhere near
the harbor road.
If you were a runaway slave,
would you take a Roman road?
This is easy. We can
catch them in a pincer movement.
Come on, Julian, you can...
(shrieking)
Charge! With me!
Easy, tiger.
Cletus's ring.
So you're the one that killed him.
Guards,
crucify him.
- Chain her.
- (spits)
Go and hurry them up.
Gordian? Stop!
Gordian, I freed you.
I failed.
I tried to farm... wrong place,
drought and debt,
creditors sold me.
- You don't deserve this.
- What do you think you're doing?
This man was my slave.
I freed him once,
I'm freeing him again.
He's not a criminal.
He killed my overseer
and led the slave revolt.
I found another one.
He was playing dead.
Julian.
I defended you to the emperor
and you show me your gratitude
by joining the uprising.
- Gordian didn't kill Cletus.
- Liar!
Tiberius was right. You'd stick a knife
in any of us if you had the chance.
It's a waste not to use
a perfectly good cross,
isn't it?
When they throw him into the arena
to face the cyclops,
you're gonna wish
you'd let him die on the cross.
He looks like a good fighter.
Take him away and deliver him
to the gladiators' quarters.
Deliver the rest of them
to the dungeon.
And as for you...
you're under arrest...
for disobeying the orders
of your commanding officer...
and Tiberius.
Follow.
Marcus Romulus,
Centurion.
You defied the direct order of Falco,
your commanding officer,
by deliberately freeing
Cletus's murderer
and a leader of the slave revolt.
I find you guilty of treason.
Now treason
is punishable by death.
However, in honor of your late father's
services to Rome,
I grant you
a choice of punishment:
Decimation of your troops...
Every other man, step forward.
Every remaining man,
execute them on my order.
...or you can volunteer
- to be a gladiator.
- I volunteer.
My men have committed no crime.
And since you won't allow me
to fight as a soldier,
- I'll fight in the arena.
- Yes, you will.
Starting tomorrow
at my Victory Games.
The entire lot of them, sir?
Wait!
Unchain her from the rest.
(cyclops grunting)
(roaring)
Look at me.
Cletus used you
for construction?
No, I cooked for him.
You'd certainly whet
any man's appetite.
Attention!
Strip him.
Sword.
Take him away.
Turn around.
We've enough
to throw at the cyclops,
but I could use another whore
to service the gladiators.
Very good. Take her.
Ah. Is everything ready
for tomorrow?
- Yes.
- Good.
And you brought the accounting
of the expenses to date?
Mm-hmm mm-hmm mm-hmm.
What's this?
An entire lamb for the cyclops?
Why are we feeding him?
He eats his guards if we don't.
- Let's find him some cheaper meat.
- No problem, Uncle.
(crowd cheering)
Citizens and free men of Rome,
welcome to the best, the biggest,
the most spectacular
gladiatorial games
ever presented
by your great Emperor Tiberius!
(cheering)
Three days of fights to the death
between the bravest of gladiators,
- three days of...
- Come on, go on!
- Get on with it!
- But there is more.
He's an arrogant bastard,
isn't he?
You've seen
men torn apart by tigers,
you've seen
men devoured by lions,
but now, for the first time ever,
right here
you will see men face off
against a far more terrifying
beast of prey,
bigger than any man on earth:
In all his fighting fury,
the legendary,
the one-eyed cyclops!
But first,
the murderous slaves.
What shall be their fate?
Hanging?
Crucifixion?
- Or the cyclops?!
- (cheering)
- Louder.
- (chanting) Cyclops! Cyclops!
Cyclops! Cyclops!
Cyclops. Cyclops.
Seeing as how our emperor
is a fair and generous man,
he has decided to give
the slaves a fighting chance.
They shall be given one sword
and one shield.
(slaves muttering)
(laughing)
Man:
Bring on the cyclops!
(cyclops roaring)
Don't worry, citizens, the cyclops never
bites off more than he can chew.
(roaring)
Please please, stay in your seats.
Our generous emperor has agreed
to provide a few lucky citizens
vouchers for free food
- during the intermission.
- (cheering)
- Can he spare it?
- (giggling)
What are you laughing at?
What did he say?
He said it's a wonderful idea.
It cost you so little, Tiberius,
and it means so much to them.
Gordian, wine?
Sit, please.
We're equals now.
Equals? No.
I was born a slave,
sentenced to die as a criminal.
You were condemned to be a gladiator
only because you tried to save me.
I should have
enlisted you in the army
instead of freeing you
to fail as a farmer.
At least I had the chance
to fight for my life,
unlike my fellow slaves.
We tried to escape because we were
condemned to die in the arena.
Perhaps we can't escape
our fate, Marcus.
We're not here
because of fate, Gordian.
- We're here because of Tiberius.
- Ringmaster: Gladiators!
The finest priestesses
from the Temple of Venus
at your command.
Barbara!
She tried to help us... got me word
we were to be thrown into the arena.
Nuh-uh-uh!
No no no.
I'll take this one.
I like a fighter.
So fighting slaves and barbarians
isn't enough for you
that you also spend
your off-duty time in the arena?
It's hardly a choice.
I was condemned
to fight as a gladiator
- as punishment for my treason.
- What did you do?
Falco tried to crucify Gordian
for a crime he didn't commit.
I chose to free him.
Barbara, huh?
Beautiful name.
It means
savage and uncivilized.
To me it means
pride and courage.
I have never seen
a woman fight like you do.
I had nothing to lose.
I'd rather die fighting to be free
than die in the arena
torn apart by the cyclops
- to amuse the Romans.
- Me, I'd rather fight to win.
- And claim me as your prize?
- Not as my prize,
as my ally...
against Tiberius and Falco.
(crowd murmuring)
Ringmaster:
Citizens, hold onto your seats
for the big event
of this second day of Victory Games.
(cheering)
Citizens, a special announcement.
Marcus!
Ringmaster:
For the final day of the Victory Games,
two gladiators
new to this arena...
I'll see you tonight.
...Marcus and Gordian will face off
in a fight to the death.
(crowd roars)
(crowd chanting)
Marcus, Marcus, Marcus...
I'm betting on the handsome one.
- Falco: Which one do you mean?
- Flavia: The one with the net.
He's done for.
(chanting)
Live live live live live!
Citizens, a special announcement:
For the final day
of the Victory Games,
three pairs of gladiators
chosen by lot
shall fight to the death.
Our gracious Emperor Tiberius
decrees that
the victorious gladiators
shall be granted freedom!
(cheering)
- Free Marcus!
- (crowd chanting) Free Marcus!
Free Marcus!
Free Marcus! Free Marcus!
Flavia, it's time for you to go home.
My guards will escort you.
- Free Marcus!
- Free Marcus! Free Marcus!
Free Marcus! Free Marcus!
Free Marcus!
Ah. May I have
a private word with you?
Flavia, you startled me.
You are a sophisticated man
and your help is needed
at the highest level on an extremely
confidential matter.
This is strictly between us.
Understand?
You've come to the right man.
Whatever it is you tell me,
I won't even think about it,
let alone pass it on.
By the way,
you've outdone yourself
with the arrangements
for the games this year.
Thanks to you, the public
is singing Tiberius's praises,
and I'll make sure
Falco tells him that.
You are a woman
of many generosities, Flavia.
You have a new very striking-Iooking
slave girl with long hair,
- attending the gladiators.
- I know just the one you mean.
- I selected her personally.
- I've come to borrow her.
You are interested
in her services?
Not personally, no.
Falco sent me.
Ah. Falco.
Tired of his new plaything
so soon, is he?
- I am truly sorry.
- Don't be.
- It's not what you think.
- You mean
the dark-haired slave girl has
attracted the attention of...
Shh! Don't even think about it.
Oh ho.
(cyclops roaring)
Girl, where's Barbara?
Man:
Huh? Come on!
Marcus: Hey!
Are you gladiators
or cowardly savages?
Torturing him when
he's powerless to defend himself?
Feeding him worse
than your dog?
- He's a cannibal.
- Because they're starving him...
to sharpen his appetite
for your flesh in the arena.
Girl, bring me the meat.
The rest of you,
back to your quarters.
(cyclops rumbling)
(cyclops roars)
You can go.
Cyclops.
"Meat."
Cyclops:
Meeeat.
- More?
- (grunts)
More meat?
Where were you?
I waited all night... like a fool.
A person of rank sent for me.
I had no choice.
Who? Falco?
- He dies.
- No, not Falco.
Flavia.
She wants to help.
She's on your side.
Trust me,
Flavia is only out for Flavia.
You underestimate her.
She's using her position
to find out
what Falco and Tiberius
are really up to.
She's communicating
with you through me,
because she dare not
talk to you directly.
Go on.
Falco is pushing Tiberius
to name him his successor.
Tiberius feels threatened because
you are becoming too popular.
The tide is turning against him.
He fears a rebellion
to restore the Republic.
He was always paranoid.
He was threatened by my father
for the same reasons.
Maybe. But Flavia says
the people admire you.
You are the son
of the great politician.
You're the one
who captured the cyclops.
You're their hero in the arena.
In an uprising they'd follow you.
You heard them.
They want you free.
And I'll fight for that freedom
every chance I get.
Tomorrow, if you're lucky,
you'll have a chance
to win that freedom.
Yes!
But the price is to kill
another gladiator
or the cyclops.
Flavia says Tiberius will never give
the cyclops a chance to be free.
When the people tire of him,
he'll be executed.
How fickle is the applause
of the crowd, Falco.
First Gordian was a hero,
then suddenly Marcus is their favorite.
And shouting for his freedom?
Who can explain it?
It's circulating through
the marketplace
that Marcus the gladiator
is the same centurion
- that captured the cyclops.
- No no no.
No no, you might
want that drink, Uncle.
News from the front isn't good.
Which front?
- All of them.
- (groans)
The legions fighting in Pannonia
are demanding the same pay
as the praetorian guards here,
and there's been
a camp mutiny in Germany.
I suppose they want
more money too?
Worse.
They've lost their faith in you.
They think you're stretching
the troops too thin.
Decimate them. That'll show them
how thin I can stretch them.
And you should know this:
The Forum is buzzing
with hero-worship for Marcus.
Who better than Marcus
to lead a coup against you?
He'd have the people's support
and half the army.
Captain of the guard!
Triple my protection
at the games tomorrow.
Wait!
What about Marcus?
I'll take care of him.
(grunts)
Cyclops.
- Meat.
That's right.
Meat.
Cyclops?
Tomorrow...
I fight.
If I win,
me free.
Meat.
Fight!
Kill!
Win! Me free.
- Meat.
- No.
No meat.
Free. Free!
Meat!
Cyclops.
(coos)
(growls)
- Free.
- Free!
- No.
Cyclops no free.
Me free.
Never free, no matter
how many men you kill.
- (stomps) Free.
- No.
Never.
(cyclops grumbling)
Citizens of Rome,
the Emperor Tiberius...
commander
of our invincible army,
dedicates the final day
of the Victory Games
- to you, the people.
- (crowd cheering)
You are noble Romans all,
you who wish to reward courage
and victory in the arena
with the great gift of liberty.
You have spoken
and your emperor has heard.
In tribute to your wish,
three sets of gladiators
chosen by lot
will fight to the death.
The victors shall be
granted their freedom.
Attilicus versus Pompeii.
Place your bets on who will die...
and who will win his freedom.
Attilicus versus Pompeii.
(cheering)
Picking combatants by lot
makes no sense.
Pompeii and Attilicus
are not well matched.
This is going to be over
in just a minute.
They should just pit the victors of the
last two days' games against each other.
I'm sorry, Gordian.
I would just rather know
that at least I'm going to have
a chance to win my freedom.
Marcus, they have to let you fight.
Flavia told me if they don't,
the public won't stand for it.
(cheering)
(chanting)
Kill kill kill kill!
Kill kill
kill kill!
Kill kill kill kill!
Attilicus, from this day forth,
you are no longer a gladiator,
but a free man of Rome.
The emperor presents you
with this wooden sword.
(crowd cheering)
And the next two gladiators are...
Gordian
- and...
- Marcus, Marcus, Marcus!
Gordian versus...
(silent)
Gordian versus Goldoni
the Sicilian.
Keep Goldoni on the run
and tire him out.
He's fast, but you're faster.
Three times lucky they say.
They're gonna call you
for the last match, I know it.
Then we'll meet again
as free men.
(cheering)
Gordian shall be granted freedom!
Citizens and free men...
the last fight for noble death
or glorious liberty
- shall be between...
- (crowd chanting) Marcus, Marcus!
Marcus, Marcus,
Marcus!
Marcus, Marcus, Marcus!
Marcus it is, my friends.
Call Marcus to the arena.
Bring Marcus to the arena.
Marcus versus...
the cyclops.
Ringmaster:
Marcus versus the cyclops!
Open the gate.
What? Stop. No!
- Stop the fight.
- Stop the fight, stop the fight!
- (booing)
My fellow Romans,
I share your outrage.
Quintus Maximilius,
I hold you responsible as manager
of these Victory Games.
Are we barbarians
that we take delight
in sheer slaughter?
No, we want worthy opponents,
well matched.
Without this,
neither victory
nor death has meaning.
The cyclops is
twice the size of any man.
Therefore I will not make
Marcus fight him alone.
Bring me the casket.
Another gladiator chosen by lot
will fight alongside Marcus.
That's better.
The final fight shall be
the cyclops versus Marcus
and the most ferocious,
the most savage,
the most terrifying barbarian
ever captured alive!
(all laughing)
- Get it!
- Chosen by lot?
What do they take us for? This whole
thing is rigged... it's obvious.
Are we gonna
let them get away with this?
- Open the gate!
- Stop the fight!
Stop the fight! Stop the fight!
Stop the fight!
Bring on the cyclops!
(grunting and roaring)
- Free Marcus!
- Free Marcus! Free Marcus!
- Free Marcus! Free Marcus...
- Cyclops?
Here here! Here!
- Marcus!
- We've got to help them now.
Are you with me?
Now is the time.
Open the gate!
(sword clangs)
Free!
Free free!
(roars)
Kill him and you're free.
No! Cyclops, no free.
(roars)
Free!
- Kill him.
- Free!
Cyclops, what are you waiting for?
Never free!
Kill him!
(growls, grunting)
Gordian, the axe!
Tiberius!
Your tyranny is over.
Handle this.
Yes, Uncle.
Flavia, go home.
Guards, kill the cyclops.
Kill him!
You!
Call out the city cohort.
Come with me! Come with me!
Go!
(whimpering)
(bone cracks)
Free! Free.
(roars) Free.
Cyclops, look out!
The beast is dead!
No, the beast lives...
but not for long.
(gasping)
Barbara:
He's dead.
Romans!
We're free!
(cheering)
Long live the Republic!
(chanting) Long live the Republic!
Long live the Republic...
(cheering)
(dramatic music playing)