[buzzing]
[animals squeaking]
[bell ringing]
[squirrel chatter over radio]
[spirited orchestral music]
(music)
[irritated squeaking]
I like this one.
Hey, dad.
Did you know
that breakfast
Is the most important meal
of the day?
Of course it is,
sweetie.
Honey, I don't think
any more bears are gonna fit.
You're gonna rip the bag.
They'll fit.
I don't think so.
(Lilly)
well, breakfast only works
If you actually sit down
and eat it.
Oh.
(mom)
okay.
That's it.
Okay.
(dad)
good.
I got it.
Good.
Oh.
Hey, good one.
Owen, don't eat
those wild berries.
You don't even know
if they're safe.
They're safe, mom.
The madman left them
for me.
Here we go again.
Bigfoot lives.
Owen, let's just pretend
for a moment
Your madman
of the mountain is real.
Is he mad, like angry,
Or is he mad,
like cuckoo?
(Owen)
I don't know.
I'll ask him next time
I see him.
Well, if you ask me,
The only madman
of the mountain is you, Owen.
Believe whatever you want.
Okay, honey.
Can you get those
down there?
Yeah.
[bright instrumental music]
(music)
[shrieking]
[chattering angrily]
[snapping]
[cat meowing]
[sighs]
Relax, dad.
It's only a Teddy bear
convention.
I know.
It's for your mother,
though, you know?
I mean, come on.
Wow.
Look at all
this ingenuity.
What does it all do?
Well, this...
This is my semi-automatic
high velocity delivering system.
Wow.
It needs a little work.
What have you got here?
This is my solar powered
anti-theft device.
[sizzles]
Whoa, oh, wow.
That is cool.
Aw, showtime.
Right, here.
Okay.
Good luck
at the convention, mom.
Thanks, honey.
Okay, while we're gone,
Lilly's in charge.
Yeah, I'm your baby-sitter.
You're still man
of the house, though.
I love you.
Okay, we'll call later.
Okay.
Bye, mom.
Bye, dad.
Hey, don't forget
to put the milk away.
[melancholy music]
(music)
That leash isn't
gonna bring her back.
Yeah, I know.
But it makes me feel better
to see it there.
She was old and sick.
Dogs die, Owen.
Just like people.
[airplane engine roaring]
[chewing and mumbling]
It's good.
[woman over loudspeaker]
your attention, please.
Flight--which is it?
226 from Los Angeles will be
disembarking from gate six.
Who's gonna move the steps now?
No, okay, I've
got to go on break.
Refueling is Sam's job.
I've got
to go on break, guys.
Hey sister,
move it along.
You're blockin' my view.
Excuse me?
Hey!
It's me, you knuckleheads.
Ah, Blackie.
(Arty)
is that really you?
Hey, when'd you become a nun?
Zip it!
I'm incognito.
You're not in cognito,
boss.
You're here in Cheney.
It means I'm in disguise,
morons.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah.
That's brilliant.
We would've
never recognized ya.
Boys, meet
the million-dollar mutt.
Aw, hey.
All right.
Let's split before the cops get
suspicious or the dog has to--
Aww!
[laughing]
Come on.
Hey, are these the wheels?
Over here, boss.
You call that wheels?
Sorry, boss,
it's a rental.
Someone stole our car.
Well, maybe
you should've rented two.
One for each foot!
Hey!
Get out of here.
Come on.
[grunting]
yeah, ha-ha.
Get in there.
[car engine revving]
[snapping]
[rousing music]
(music)
[dog barks]
See you guys tomorrow.
Hey, Meagan.
Hey, Owen.
(woman)
who is it, Meagan?
Nobody, grandma,
just the paper boy.
[dog whimpers]
[giggles]
Hey, pixie.
[dog barks]
So, Meagan...
I was wondering...
Are you going to the
fourth of July picnic tomorrow?
Maybe.
Well, maybe
I'll see you there.
Maybe.
[dog barking]
I've got to go.
I'm okay.
Hello, Owen;
thank you.
Morning, son.
[growling and barking]
[snapping]
[grunts and mutters]
[suspenseful music]
(music)
[screams]
[loud crash]
[water rushing]
Look what we caught,
a dork.
How you doin', dork?
I don't want to fight you,
Dexter, but I will.
[mockingly]
I don't want to fight you,
Dexter, but I will.
What have you been doing
hanging around my girl?
Around who?
Meagan Todd.
I deliver a paper
to her house, that's all.
Stay away from her,
understand?
Whoa.
Did I say you could go?
Sweet.
[sarcastically]
your folks too poor
to buy you a real iPod?
I bought that myself,
with money I earned.
Hmm, delivering papers?
Yeah.
Like these?
No, Dexter!
I have to deliver those;
don't.
[boys snickering]
No, not my bike.
What the heck is that?
Another one
of your dumb inventions?
Be careful,
it's loaded.
[jeering]
what's it do?
How's it work?
[snapping]
[grunts]
[laughing]
[shouting]
No, Dexter, no!
Not my bike!
No!
[bike splashes]
[snickering]
Pants!
No!
[laughing]
Later, dork.
[bike creaking]
[engine revving]
Ooh, tell us
about the heist, boss.
Yeah, the
dangerous parts.
Well, what's to tell?
I mean, I didn't
pull the job.
All I did was
pick up the package.
We're just
the delivery boys.
Well, what's
with the pooch?
How do you think
Mr. Inside
Got me and the jewels
past security?
The dog
is the package.
Ahh.
Cool.
Hey, so when
do we get paid?
Just as soon
as we make the delivery.
Ah--where's the drop?
Thelma's truck stop,
route 16.
About 80 Miles
up the road.
We don't have to be
there till midnight.
What happens at midnight?
You turn into a pumpkin.
[laughing]
Screwy, what are
you talking about?
Someone will pick up
the package.
Who?
I don't know,
and I don't care.
Well, how they gonna
know that it's us?
Because we're the ones
with the dog, you dummy.
Oh.
[grunts]
Find some place
to stop, all right.
This makeup
is killing me!
Hey, what's your problem?
[retching sounds]
[all yelling]
[electricity crackling]
[car honking]
[all groaning]
Come on.
Knock it off.
All right, here.
Give me the bag.
You take the dog,
all right?
And don't
let nobody touch her.
Hey, boss!
We made the headlines.
Don't show me that.
All right?
I'm supposed
to be blind.
[sighs]
Get rid of it.
[dog barks]
Whoa, horsy!
Sorry, ma'am,
this is the men's room.
Here's the women's room.
[grumbling]
What a sweet
young tyke you are.
[grunting]
Bless you.
He likes the stick.
Look at that.
Hey, stop, stop!
Don't do that.
You're hurting her.
Better stay back, kid.
This dog bites.
(Arty)
yeah, real bad.
[growls]
She's starving!
When's the last time
you gave her any water?
[blubbering]
[guffawing]
I did not think of water.
Come on.
Hey, doggie,
you like the stick?
You like the stick?
Look out, look out!
[laughing]
(bud)
did you see that?
That's a boy, that's a boy.
Hey!
Whoa, tough guy, huh?
[dog lapping loudly]
This harness
is way too tight.
[mimicking sarcastically]
[laughing]
[gasps]
What's the matter,
grandma?
Never seen
a nun before?
[exclaiming]
ohh!
Tails.
Heads.
[clears throat]
Are either of you
with that pervert in there?
Hey, kid.
Away from the dog.
[growls]
[growling]
(bud)
hey, easy, boss.
Kid was just givin'
the pooch a drink.
Well, how nice of you.
Get him in the car.
(Owen)
what?
No, hey!
Oww.
Not the kid,
the dog!
Oh, right.
Right, the dog.
[dog growls]
Oh, oh!
Don't--grab her!
Don't let her escape.
Bring me that dog!
Dead or alive!
[dramatic music]
(music)
[clattering]
Ohh!
[crashing]
[rousing music]
(music)
Okay, girl.
Now's your Chance.
You've got to run.
Go on.
Where's
the dog, kid?
Up there.
Come on, follow me.
As a rule, um--
I don't like
the woods, boss.
There's things
in there
With teeth.
[growls]
Uh, yeah--
come on!
Don't worry, mister,
I'll find her.
I know these woods
like the back of my hand.
Yeah, you'll get
the back of my hand
If you don't.
What are you--
Sorry, boss, sorry.
Hey, kid.
Slow down.
You've got to hide.
Quick.
[whimpers]
[grunts]
[growls]
There she goes!
That way!
[snorting]
Ooh!
Okay, go, girl.
Go.
Hey, I'll lead.
[branches crashing]
Oww!
[birds chirping]
[exhaling deeply]
I am dyin' here.
Me too.
Let's head back.
Shh!
[glass tinkling]
What's that?
[branches snapping]
[exclaiming]
[screaming]
[whining]
Ahh!
All right,
what's going on, kid?
Just stuff in the trees
and these stick people.
They're a warning.
Look.
"trespassers beware."
Of what?
Chipmunks?
[laughs nervously]
No.
The yellow line.
The what?
Look.
(Owen)
yellow Clay...
Marking his territory.
(Blackie)
his?
Okay, whose his?
The madman of the mountain.
The crazy hermit
Who lives on top of the Ridge.
Anyone who crosses
the yellow line
Risks life and limb.
Oh.
[laughing]
that's baloney.
You don't believe me?
Kid, I wouldn't believe you
if you were my mother.
Arty.
Come here.
Why me, boss?
Come here!
[suspenseful music]
(music)
Hey, madman!
[laughing]
[mockingly]
I just crossed
your stupid line.
Come out, come out,
wherever you are.
[guffawing]
Yeah, madman,
who's yellow now?
[singing]
[animals chattering]
Just a dumb squirrel!
Aren't you
a little darlin'?
You're so dumb.
Your ugly's so cute.
Come here.
Arty!
We ain't
got time for cute.
Ow!
[chattering]
Ahh!
Ahh.
Ow!
They don't like us
near their tree.
[growling]
[shrieking]
Ow!
[yelling]
Run!
[metal creaking]
What is this place?
What is that thing?
It's a scarecrow.
I built it for the madman
To protect his garden
from the birds.
Ah, you're
a clever kid.
But you don't scare me
with that madman nonsense.
He's leadin' us
everywhere that dog ain't.
That's exactly
what I was thinking.
[grunts]
[suspenseful music]
(music)
I'm gonna find you,
kid,
And that dog too.
And when I do--
No, you won't.
(bud)
boss, take it easy.
[rousing music]
(music)
[panting]
Hey.
Hey, girl.
I'm here to help you.
You can trust me,
I promise.
I know where we can hide.
Don't be afraid.
The madman likes dogs...
I hope.
Stay right here.
Come on.
That's chatterbox,
and that's blabbermouth,
And that's their tree.
That's why I marked this area
with yellow lines
So I would never forget.
Stay away from them...
And never touch their nuts.
[dog barks]
Weird, huh?
It belongs to the madman.
Come on.
[bright instrumental music]
(music)
Welcome to my fort.
You can see
tomorrow from here.
Oh, and check this.
Way down there
is my house.
Come on.
I'll show you around.
Shh!
What is it, boss?
I thought
I heard water.
A creek
Would lead us
out of this jungle.
How do
you know that?
Because I was
a cub scout,
And just before
they kicked me out,
I learned that
if you follow water,
It'll lead to people.
[laughing]
That's dumb.
How can water
know where people are?
Turn around!
Oh--oh, boss.
No.
I said turn around.
[yelling]
[snapping]
Hey.
[squeaking]
[laughs]
See?
I've got everything I need.
Now I've got you.
[melancholy music]
(music)
You would've liked shadow.
You could have
been best friends.
But now that she's gone,
Mom won't let me
get another dog,
'cause my sister
has dumb allergies.
But that's okay.
You can live here.
[dog barks]
Him?
He's the best inventor
that ever lived,
Leonardo da Vinci.
And these are my drawings of
some of his amazing inventions.
And this
is my tennis ball cannon.
I don't get many visitors,
And when I do,
It's usually just Dexter Clopp
and his gang of losers.
That's why I built this thing,
To keep Dexter away.
No, girl.
This is home to someone
you don't want to meet.
Just stay away
from this box, okay?
You sure have a fancy collar.
These can't be real.
No tag.
No owner.
No name.
I'm gonna call you Diamond.
[dog growls]
What is it, girl?
Don't worry, Diamond.
We're safe here.
Those men
will never find us.
They don't even know
where to look.
[gasping]
Water.
I need water.
[wheezing]
Well, well, well.
The kid's bike.
Owen "p," huh?
Now we got a name
for the little devil.
Aw, dang.
Address is all worn off.
Eh, small town.
How many boys
named Owen can there be?
Boys and dogs
go together
Like peanut butter
and jelly.
Find the boy,
We'll find the dog.
Let's go hunt.
Ooh, I want that bell.
[electricity crackling]
[both screaming]
That kid's a menace.
[dog barks]
The madman built that.
It's kind of like
his mailbox.
I bring him old newspapers
So he'll know
what's going on in the world.
I heard he was a monster
Who used to work at a circus.
People paid to see him.
Then one day,
he ran away to these woods...
To be free.
Come on, girl.
Time to head back
to the fort.
[dog lapping water]
Okay.
If anyone comes,
head for the woods.
You got to stay here, okay?
[whimpers]
No, if I don't
make it home for lunch,
My sister will freak
and call my parents.
I've got to go.
[whimpers]
Stay here, okay?
I'll be back.
I promise.
There.
No!
Oh.
There he isn't.
[laughing]
Sorry.
Hey, kids.
Come here;
come here.
He's about this tall.
Nah,
I don't know him.
[mutters]
(Arty)
these chili dogs are good.
(bud)
aren't you on a diet?
What is it
with this kid?
I mean, doesn't
he have any friends?
Get in the car.
They left this morning.
Yep, just me
and my little brother,
Who's sitting here
feeding his face.
[dog barks]
Hold on.
Did I just hear
a dog outside?
No.
Oh, nothing,
I just--
I thought I heard a dog,
And you know what
that means for me,
Sneeze city.
(Lilly)
yeah.
Yeah, I am.
No.
Yeah, I know.
Okay, bye.
Wow.
You're a great cook.
Really?
I thought you said
my food was barf.
Well, it usually is,
But this time
it was really good.
Well...
Then have
some more, sport.
[distant voices]
Ooh, my show's on.
Aww, sick.
You're creeping me out.
[burps]
Oh, mom left some apple turnover
for us in the pantry.
Let's wait.
It's not healthy
to eat dessert
Right after
a heavy meal.
Okay, let me
get this straight.
Um, you ate my cooking,
And now you want
to wait before dessert
Because it's healthy?
Are you my little brother
Or some alien
who's taken over his body?
I'm an alien.
I ate Owen hours ago.
How did you
get so dirty?
And why do you
smell like a--
[sneezing]
A dog?
Thanks a lot.
A cockle burr?
Just go take a bath.
I hate baths.
Well, I'm in charge,
And I say,
go take a bath
And change
your dirty clothes
Before you get
the couch all dirty
And I get blamed.
Oh, oh!
Use soap.
Yes, master.
Come on.
Over here.
Come on,
we've got to go upstairs.
Hurry.
(Owen)
hold still.
Hey.
Why you got
so many cockle burrs?
Where'd my brush go?
Who are you
talking to in there?
No one.
I'm singing.
(music) la-la la-la la (music)
[water splashing loudly]
Hey, stay out!
Don't use my shampoo.
I won't.
[shampoo squirts loudly]
[sneezing]
I think it's you
I'm allergic to, Owen.
[laughing]
[guffawing]
Can we get these?
(Blackie)
no, but you can
get back in the car.
[grumbling]
Get in the car!
Hey, kid.
You seen a boy
named Owen?
[villainous laugh]
Okay, let's go.
Oh, no;
we got the carpet wet.
[whispering]
come on, in here.
"Diamond heist."
[dog whimpers]
Shh, quiet, quiet.
"$5-million
worth of diamonds were stolen
"in what authorities suspect
was in inside burglary job
Of the Los Angeles
jewelry exchange."
Huh.
"thieves chose flawless
diamonds, weighing only grams,
Able to fit
in the palm of a hand."
Wow.
"detectives are tracking leads
"and seeking suspects
for questioning,
"including a husky nun
caught on surveillance tape
"entering the exchange
shortly after the theft.
"seven minutes later,
"the same suspect
exited the exchange,
Led by a seeing eye dog."
You?
Oh, my gosh.
5 million bucks.
Now I know why those guys
Were so interested
in the newspaper.
They aren't after you.
They're after these diamonds.
We have to go to the police.
Come on.
[engine roaring]
[car backfires]
No, set all the clocks back,
Then they'll
think you're home on time.
[chuckling]
yeah.
I know, but yes.
No, no,
you look totally cute.
Mm-hmm.
[giggling]
no.
Yeah.
There it is.
(Blackie)
406.
[all laugh]
[car door slamming loudly]
Shh!
You two go check
around back.
Okay, uh-huh.
No, I can't go.
Well, I'm stuck baby-sitting
my little brother.
Really?
And your brother keeps
his mouth shut for ten bucks?
Oh, oh, check it out.
Aww!
Is that poop?
[whispering]
you stepped in poop.
[laughing]
That's awesome.
Hey, come on, bud.
Blackie'll never know.
No, get down.
He's gonna see.
[jeering]
can't make me.
Did you check his bod?
He's ripped.
[knock at door]
Oh, hold on.
Someone's at the door.
Come on.
Come on, bud.
[whining]
Call you back.
Yeah?
Hi.
Sorry to bother you,
little miss,
But I'm lookin' for my dog,
A kind of a golden mutt
with hair.
And some folks
say that they saw him
With a boy named Owen,
who lives here.
Yeah, um,
that's my little brother.
I'm not surprised.
He's a dog nut.
Yeah, well,
kind of a dog nut myself
And really would like
To get mine back.
Don't worry,
these are just my...
Associates,
And they are helping me to...
Find my dog.
Yeah, and when
we find him, we're gonna--
Give him a big,
fat reward.
Isn't that right,
guys?
[together]
yeah, uh-huh.
Oh, well, I Haven't
seen any dog.
But wait here,
and I'll get Owen.
Okay.
Owen, some guys
want to talk to you.
Owen!
Um, he's not here.
Oh, actually,
he's probably at his fort
Until dinner time.
Ah, fort.
Thank you.
Oh, and where exactly
Would the fort be?
Just top of that Ridge.
Where the madman
of the mountain lives?
No, that is just a fairy tale
That Owen made up to keep
intruders away from his fort.
No, there's nothing up there
But poison Ivy,
ticks,
I don't know, snakes.
Snakes?
[cell phone rings]
Hello?
[gasps loudly]
Okay, Chad Austin
is going to be there?
Don't worry...
If my brother found your dog,
It's in
really good hands.
[girl over phone]
who are you talking to?
No, it's just someone
for Owen.
Oh, my God,
I'm freaking!
(Arty)
snakes.
See, boss, nothing
to worry about.
Diamonds
are in good hands.
Yeah, but they're
not in my hands.
Luckily we got
plenty of time.
Wait a minute.
Kid's got to eat,
right?
Yeah, right, boss.
She said he'll
be up there until dinner.
And when he comes back--
[together]
we grab him.
Ah.
Ooh, yeah.
Oh, hello, Owen.
What can
we help you with?
This.
Oh, the Diamond heist
down in L.A.
What about it?
I know who did it.
I've got proof,
Right here.
The dog did it?
No, she's innocent.
See, the thieves needed
someplace to hide the diamonds,
So they--
[insistently]
so they--
So they hid them on Diamond!
Hid what?
The diamonds on Diamond.
On who?
On Diamond, my dog.
I mean, their dog.
I mean...
She was their dog,
but now she's my dog,
Because I--
Owen, we don't have time
for stories today.
But it's not a story.
But it sounds like a story
like your madman story.
But there really
is a madman in the woods.
He escaped from a circus.
And now he's best friends
with Bigfoot, right?
Why are you smiling
When the thieves
are right here in Cheney?
We hear you,
And we are gonna
keep an eye on 'em,
Won't we?
Well, don't you
want to even see
The diamonds
on her collar?
Owen, do me a favor.
Just deliver the paper;
stop reading it.
Come on.
(Owen)
hey, Meagan.
Hey.
Who's this?
Oh, my new dog,
Diamond.
Cool name, Diamond.
Can I pet her?
Sure, I'll carry that.
Diamond...
Shake.
Wow, did you
teach her that?
No, she's just
real smart.
Pretty collar.
Yeah, I know,
she had it on when I found her.
Found her?
Yeah, abandoned
in the woods.
Who would
do something like that?
Diamond thieves.
Who?
It was in the paper
about these three crooks
Who stole these diamonds.
And one was a nun
who really wasn't a nun.
She--I mean, he used Diamond
to smuggle the diamonds
Out of L.A. To here,
And that's why
I helped Diamond get away.
That's when
she became mine.
So you mean the diamonds
on her collar are real?
Yes, and they're
worth like $5 million.
The police chief
didn't believe me either.
I want to, Owen, but--
Have you ever thought
about being a writer?
Because you have
a wonderful imagination.
Yeah, Owen.
Just imagine what
I'm gonna do to you now.
Hey, Meagan.
What do you want,
Dexter?
Didn't I warn you
to stay away from my girl?
Didn't I?
I will never be your girl,
Dexter Clopp.
You're such a monkey butt.
What'd you call me?
A monkey butt.
What are you gonna do,
Dexter, hit a girl?
Yeah.
[yelling and shouting]
[dog barks loudly]
[groaning]
That's not fair.
Ow!
[boys laughing]
Stay away from my girl.
(boys)
weakling! Wimp!
He can't even get up.
Loser.
[grunting]
This ain't over,
dork!
(boy)
wait till next time.
Yeah.
You'll be sorry.
Boss, look, the kid!
Ooh, and the pooch.
Quick, make a u-eye.
[tires screeching]
[car horn blaring]
Owen!
My groceries.
Sorry, I got to go.
Diamond, come on.
[dog barks]
[crunching]
Come on, come here.
[muttering]
[dramatic music]
(music)
Come on, girl,
it's not safe here anymore.
Ooh!
Nah, that was me.
[whimpering]
What is it, girl?
Looks like no one's
gonna help us.
It's just you and me.
The first thing we've got to do
is hide these diamonds.
Then we've got
to get the fort ready...
Just in case.
Come on, we've got work to do.
[rousing music]
(music)
[sniffing]
[squeaking]
[buzzing]
Diamond?
(Owen)
where are you, girl?
[Diamond barking]
[barks]
Hey!
Don't run off like that.
You scared me.
What's the matter, girl?
What'd you see?
[barking]
[buoyant music]
(music)
Don't worry;
the madman knows I'm here.
He hasn't bothered me yet.
[chittering]
No, Diamond,
that's just stinky.
[growls]
[hissing]
I warned you.
Come here.
Let me see.
[dog whimpering]
There, good as new.
[laughing]
What's that?
How'd this happen?
As soon as we're
sure those guys are gone,
I'm taking you to the vet.
Get some rest.
It'll help you heal.
[chattering]
[screeching]
[footsteps approaching]
[creaking]
Shh.
[whispering]
Diamond.
Wow, the madman.
He gave me these porcupine
quills for my apple turnover.
He must be lonely
living up here all by himself.
He sure likes you, though.
And I guess you like him too.
Come on, Diamond.
Oh, no!
I'm gonna be late for dinner.
If my mom calls
and I'm not home,
She'll ground me.
Okay, stay here.
If anyone comes, hide, okay?
[phone ringing]
Hello?
Oh, hey, mom.
[shrieks]
[chuckles]
Ha-ha, very funny.
Oh, yeah, mom;
he's here.
Oh, in the backyard
looking for bugs, something.
Yeah, just a sec.
Here, Tarzan,
it's your mommy.
Hi, mom.
Hey, hands off.
No, not you, mom.
Mom, if a dog,
a really nice dog,
A super cool dog,
A dog that never barked or shed
Or scratched the furniture,
or chased cars--
If a dog like that
followed me home...
Could I--
But, mom!
It's not my fault
she's allergic.
What if I kept it in my room?
Okay, mom.
I understand.
Lilly's more important.
Bye.
I can't help it, Owen.
I was born with allergies.
Let me guess, you've fallen
out of love with my cooking,
And now you need
to get back to your fort.
So tell me about the dog.
What dog?
What are you talking about?
I know, Owen,
all about it.
The owners came
looking for it today.
Who?
What?
When?
Yeah, these three dirty guys.
Oh, and I think
that the mean one
Was a little upset
that you borrowed his dog.
What'd you tell them?
The truth:
That you were at the fort.
You didn't tell them
where it was, did you?
Of course not.
[sighs]
Are you in some kind
of trouble?
[knock on door]
Well, what if it's them?
What do I tell them?
Tell them I moved.
Yeah,
I moved away to school.
Now, that's brilliant.
Yeah, you lived here
this morning,
But now you moved?
Don't open it, Lilly.
Maybe you should just give them
their dog back.
You guys
are early.
You're still
on baby-sitting duty?
[both scoff]
Oh, look,
There's
the baby now.
[laughter]
Get it in gear,
girl.
Boys are waiting.
So you're going out?
Look, don't give me
a hard time about it.
You keep your mouth shut
About this
to mom and dad,
And I'll keep quiet about you
hiding that dog at your fort.
Okay, deal.
Oh, what'd you
name him?
It's a her,
and I named her Diamond.
It's a pretty name.
Hey, don't forget
to lock the door.
[laughs]
come on.
(bud)
you see that boss?
Big sister's leaving,
And someone just
pulled the blinds.
Kid must be home.
All right,
as soon as she's out of sight,
We move in.
[affirmative grunts]
[inhales loudly]
[farts]
[groans]
[grunting]
[farts]
[laughs]
Oh, oh, jeez.
Did you to fart factories
have to have chili dogs?
[grunts]
[farts]
And bean burritos today?
[laughs]
[smacks lips]
oh!
[farts]
Oh, oh, all right.
Just--
I'm dying here.
[Arty laughs]
[farts]
Roll down the window.
[laughs]
Oh,
unlock the door.
I can't.
Don't worry, boss,
I'll fix that stink.
No!
Don't light that...
[explosion]
[coughing]
Match.
[wheezes]
[sniffs]
Hi, kid.
How's the dognapping biz?
[laughter]
(Owen)
ah! I didn't steal your dog.
I'm just protecting him
from you.
Yeah, well, you don't
have to hide her,
Because
I'll give her to ya,
As long as you give me
what I want.
You want those
stolen diamonds.
I read all about 'em
in the paper.
Well, the kid
can read, huh?
Look, I risked my life
for those rocks.
Now, we can do this
the easy way,
Or...
We can do this
the messy way.
Messy way,
messy way.
(bud)
yeah.
[grunting]
[laughter]
Diamond!
No, no, no, no, no.
[growling]
[shouting]
[all shouting at once]
[growling]
[shouting]
[Diamond barking and growling]
Oof!
[sniff]
[disgustedly]
oh!
Ow!
Come on, Diamond.
Follow me, girl.
[barks]
[men yelling distantly]
Come on.
[gasping and panting]
I need water.
I need air.
And I need
those diamonds now,
Or we're never gonna make it
To that truck stop
rendezvous on time.
Hey, lookee there.
Ho--hold it.
Ahh.
I bet they're empty.
It's a booby trap,
No doubt triggered to go off
the second you touch 'em.
Nah.
That tricky little--
Boys, let me teach you
about the kind of menace
We're dealing with.
Watch and learn.
Ooh.
You're history, kid.
[buzzing]
[yelling]
[men shrieking in distance]
Diamond.
[Diamond barks]
Diamond?
Hey, come here.
You saved me.
Soldier, it's time
we prepared for battle.
[rousing music]
(music)
Okay, we need two more.
Last one.
Come on, move in.
[wheezing]
This kid ain't normal.
No way.
(Blackie)
come on.
[men arguing]
I am gonna lose my mind.
Battle stations, Diamond.
Lock and load.
(Owen)
go back while you can
Before the madman finds out
you crossed his woods.
There is no madman.
Your own sister told us that.
And you believed her?
Boy, you're even dumber
than I thought.
[snickers]
This is your last Chance
to retreat.
Not without
the diamonds, kid.
Okay, but don't say
I didn't warn you.
Oh, hey, look at that.
Kid's playing soldier now.
[laughing]
[loud thunk]
Oh!
[groaning]
[laughs]
Lucky shot, boss.
Yeah, let's get him.
Yeah.
[yelling]
Stop playing, Arty.
This kid--
He's smart.
We need a plan.
We got a plan.
Yeah, we want
to go home.
[barks]
You hear that?
That's 5 million bucks barkin',
And you guys want to go home.
What's the plan,
boss?
All right.
We rush the fort
from three sides.
Bud from the left.
Arty from the right.
And me straight up the center.
Yeah.
[laughing]
[screaming]
[whooping]
Get over that way.
What are you doing?
Go that way, go.
[whooping]
Aw, we're too late.
He got away.
Come on!
[whooping]
[growling]
Ah, ohh!
I know you're
out there, kid.
You and my mutt.
Spread out.
[barks]
There they are!
Go, go, go.
Run, Diamond.
[yelling]
[box clatters]
I got you now, you dumb dog.
Ooh!
[skunk spraying]
Ahh! Ahh!
[coughing]
[Diamond barks]
You think that's funny?
[electronic girl's voice]
mama, mama.
Mama, mama.
Mama, mama, mama, mama.
Ow!
Come on, kid.
We can work this out.
(Owen)
I'm over here.
[snapping]
Oww!
[whispering]
hey, bud, you all right?
[high-pitched voice]
watch out for them pygmies.
What pygmies?
[shrieking]
Them pygmies.
How about that?
(Blackie)
ow!
Ow!
(Arty)
it's okay.
You're doin' good.
Ow!
You okay, boss?
No, I am not okay,
mouse brains.
Go find me something soft
to sit on.
Oh, this ought to be real gentle
on them sore cheeks, boss.
(bud)
yeah, yeah, yeah.
Like sittin' on a cloud.
Easy, boys.
How's your tushie?
Is it on there?
What are you doing?
Go find the dog.
Stay cool, boss,
we'll find the mutt.
Lookin' for me?
Kid, hey, hey.
You're outnumbered.
What's all that yellin'
about out there?
You find him?
[hissing]
Ow, ow.
[shrieking]
[steam hissing]
Ahh.
Had enough?
[yelling and jabbering]
Say cheese!
[bulb flashing]
Oww!
I got ya!
Gotcha,
you little demon.
Diamond!
Oww.
[whimpers]
ouch.
[Blackie yelling]
Oh, hey.
This must be what the kid uses
to climb up there with.
Careful,
it could be a trick.
[grunting]
Not this time.
Grab hold.
[together]
oops.
Avalanche!
[both shouting]
Think we outsmarted
him this time.
[laughing]
Clang!
[whimpers]
What's the matter, girl?
[Blackie whistling]
Run, Diamond.
[whimpering]
Something's wrong with her.
Leave her alone.
Well, about time...
Me and miss mutt
had a reunion.
[Diamond growls]
Oh, listen to her.
So happy to see me.
She hates you, and so do I.
Not for long,
'cause you two got a date
with Mr. Switchblade.
Oww!
Go, Diamond.
All right,
put down the stick, kid.
The war's over.
Is it?
Yeah, and you lost.
Now, I don't have time
for any more games.
I got to meet someone
at midnight,
And I can't be late!
Yeah, that's it.
Right where you belong.
(both)
we got the dog.
That is the last time
this dog gets away from me.
Hold her steady, boys.
Give me the knife, boss.
What are you gonna
do to her?
Don't worry, kid.
She won't feel a thing
Ever again.
[laughing]
[whimpering]
[whines]
What did you do
to my package, kid?
She was hurt,
so I helped her.
Let her go, and I'll tell you
where I hid the diamonds.
[whines]
Okay.
You show me
where you hid the diamonds,
And you and Cujo here
go free.
[grunts]
[laughs]
Whoo.
Come on.
Mush.
Giddyap. Mush.
Giddyap.
[both grunting]
[laughing]
What the heck
is this?
You expecting
a flood, kid?
[laughs]
a flood.
Go tie her up.
That's where I hid them:
In the boat.
This better not be
another trick.
Bud, Arty.
Check it out.
Come on!
[chuckling]
Ahh.
Ah, what's this?
Come on; are the rocks
in there or not?
Ah, ain't nothin' in here
but a mess of glue, boss.
Well, kid,
You had your Chance.
I risked my life
for those rocks, okay?
And I need
those diamonds now.
[chittering]
Oh.
[squishing]
Ha-ha-ha.
Found 'em, boss.
Ooh, are you sure?
Bring 'em here.
Uh, we're--
we're stuck, boss.
Catch.
[chuckles]
What are you
trying to pull?
What do you mean?
That's them.
This collar is nothing more
than a cheap trinket
That I picked up
at the airport
To celebrate the heist.
Fake?
But I thought that--
That means...
That the real rocks...
Right.
Still in the mutt.
What do you mean
in her?
Let me show you.
[men laughing]
[chittering]
Ooh.
[barks]
No.
Stop hurting her!
Oh, I'm gonna teach you
what hurt is, kid.
[growling]
Get 'em, boss.
Yeah.
Ooh.
No, you don't.
Now it's your turn.
Get him!
[yells]
[laughing]
Whoo!
[screams]
[choking]
[screaming]
[both screaming]
[all screaming]
Diamond.
Oh.
[screaming]
Throw out the anchor!
It's glued.
Do something,
you idiot!
[screaming]
[tires screeching]
Please, don't die,
Diamond.
Hang on, girl.
[screaming]
Out of the way!
Move, move!
[yelling indistinctly]
[horns honking]
Get out of the way!
[woman screams]
Run for your lives!
[hubcap clattering]
Move, kid!
Oh!
What?
Ah!
Oh, no.
[screams]
[rats squeaking]
Crash!
[screams]
Look out!
(man)
run!
Get out of the way!
[woman grunts]
Throw out the anchor!
Tie it off!
Ooh!
[together]
heave-ho!
[loud scraping]
[indistinct radio chatter]
[laughter]
Can I take your order?
[woman on radio]
13, 80, 61.
Sure, babe,
get me a lawyer on the double.
I'll have
one of them too.
And a chili dog with fries.
To go.
(man)
get your hands up.
[somber guitar music]
(music)
[dog whining]
[sobs]
Thanks.
[dog whimpers]
It's late, Owen.
Where have you been?
We need your help.
[whining]
[engine stops]
[dogs barking]
(Owen)
mom.
Dad.
Sweetheart,
we came as soon
As we got
Lilly's message.
What on earth
is going on?
Son, will you follow me?
Can they come too?
That would be fine.
[sniffs]
I'm just--
it's my allergies.
I just better wait here.
[pensive piano music]
(music)
(man)
son, your dog is over here.
[uplifting instrumental music]
(music)
Diamond!
And she's going to be fine.
Whose dog?
You are very brave,
Owen.
Young man, we're proud
of what you did.
What'd you do, Owen?
Hey, he collared
three dangerous criminals.
He also saved
this animal's life.
If I hadn't
removed these
From inside the dog
when I did,
She surely would have died.
From inside the dog?
I'm lost.
The thieves
used this animal
To smuggle
the diamonds
Past the security guards.
So here they are,
chief,
$5-million worth
of Precious Stone.
[low whistle]
Your son,
A real hero.
Diamond's the real hero,
Her and the madman
of the mountain.
The who?
The madman of the mountain.
He saved my life.
Your madman isn't mad,
And he didn't escape
from any circus.
He didn't?
No, his name
is Carl Westminster,
And he's been living
up in them woods for years,
Ever since his wife died
in a car crash
And he was badly burned
trying to save her.
Yeah, he's scary as the devil,
but trust me,
He is a harmless soul.
He's also my friend
And Diamond's friend too.
[barks]
(Owen)
just think, girl,
For a while,
You were the richest dog
in the world.
She still is,
sweetheart,
Because she met you.
Does that mean
I can keep--
I know you miss shadow.
I miss her too.
I wish we could keep this
beautiful dog, but...
I know,
Lilly's allergies.
I miss shadow too.
And if Diamond
will make us all happy again,
Then the heck
with my allergies.
[sniffs]
You've just given me
a great idea.
Lilly made me realize
That there was someone
who needed Diamond more than me.
It wasn't the easy thing to do,
but it was the right thing.
Don't worry.
You'll always be my dog.
But this is for Lilly
and the madman.
[whines]
I'll come visit you every day.
You be good now.
[sobs]
I love you, Diamond.
Go on.
It's time to go home.
[barks]
[sighs]
[barking]
[fireworks exploding]
[dog barks]
(crowd)
oh!
Oh, oh, wow.
You see that?
Yeah.
[together]
oh!
Hey, boss,
you're missing it.
Oh, wow!
[laughter]
Oh, oh, oh.
[groans]
Oh, yeah.
You see that, bud?
Yeah, it looked
just like a lot--
Yeah, like a lot of
little diamonds floating down.
Ow, boss!
(Luke Benward)
(music) standing in line
with some friends of mine (music)
[cheerful squealing]
(music) asking for some change (music)
(music) look to my left
before I step (music)
(music) I could turn away,
but I can't forget (music)
(music) his face (music)
(music) staring back at me (music)
(music) everybody's got a story (music)
(music) everybody matters (music)
(music) get up, get up, get up (music)
(music) we could make it better (music)
(music) so come on don't wait (music)
(music) it takes you (music)
(music) it takes me (music)
(music) to make somebody's world (music)
(music) a brighter place to be (music)
(music) right now (music)
(music) get up, get up, get up (music)
(music) yeah (music)
(music) just get up (music)
(music) get up, get up, get up (music)
(music) see a lonely girl
in the hallway (music)
(music) sitting by herself every day (music)
(music) do you wonder (music)
(music) what's going
through her head? (music)
(music) should you be her friend
and jump right in? (music)
(music) do you pretend
and just blend in? (music)
(music) it's up to you, (music)
(music) so what you gonna do? (music)
(music) 'cause everybody's
got a story (music)
(music) everybody matters (music)
(music) get up, get up, get up (music)
(music) we can make a difference (music)
(music) hear me when I say (music)
(music) get up, get up, get up (music)
(music) we could make it better (music)
(music) so come on don't wait (music)
(music) it takes you (music)
(music) it takes me (music)
(music) to make somebody's world (music)
(music) a brighter place to be (music)
(music) right now (music)
(music) can you imagine a place, (music)
(music) a beautiful day, (music)
(music) where nobody
felt replaceable? (music)
(music) come on,
imagine a place, (music)
(music) a beautiful day (music)
(music) when nobody felt that way. (music)
(music) get up, get up, get up (music)
(music) whoa, whoa (music)
(music) yeah (music)
(music) yeah, yeah (music)
(music) ooh, ooh, yeah (music)
(music) it takes you (music)
(music) it takes me (music)
(music) to make somebody's world (music)
(music) a brighter place to be (music)
(music) just get up,
get up (music)
(music) whoa (music)
(music) hear me when I say (music)
(music) get up, get up, get up (music)
(music) we could make it better (music)
(music) so come on don't wait (music)
(music) it takes you (music)
(music) it takes me (music)
(music) to make somebody's world (music)
(music) a brighter place to be (music)
(music) right now (music)
(music) get up, get up, get up (music)
[distantly]
(music) get up, get up, get up,
get up (music)
(music) just get up (music)
(music) get up, get up, get up (music)
The End
+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+
+ |T|h|e| |D|e|a|f| |B|o|y|s| |F|o|r| |B|o|y|s| |G|r|o|u|p|  +
E N J O Y   this   SRT   SUBTITLE   R e l e a s e
http://www.imdb.com/title/tt0969250
Dog Gone - Diamond Dog Caper (2008) English for hearing-impaired.srt
FPS: 23.976
+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+-+
+ |T|h|e| |D|e|a|f| |B|o|y|s| |F|o|r| |B|o|y|s| |G|r|o|u|p|  +
We want more subtitles right NOW!
1) All DVDs to be subtitled
2) All VIDEO GAMES to be subtitled
3) All videos/DVDs used in lessons at school to be subtitled
4) More pre-recorded & live subtitles on TV
__       _             _            _        _            _
//_ _   / | _  _ _/|  /_)_      _  /_`_  _  /_)_      _  / `__     _
// //_' /_.'/_'/_|/   /_)/_//_/_  /  /_//  /_)/_//_/_  /_;//_//_//_/
_/                    _/              /