Yeah, Kirk with the scene
down here at the county line.
We have nine officers along the route,
and we are here standing by.
Come on!
Hold on,
Sal!
Advise Highway Patrol
to set up roadblocks. Over.
Move it.
I'm coming. I'm coming.
Two escaped felons
last seen heading eastbound.
Could be armed and dangerous.
Advise the Highway Patrol
to set up roadblocks. Over.
Advise Highway Patrol
Dispatch, this is Bravo.
Requesting an additional
K9 unit confirmed to Sector 4.
- Hold position.
- Anybody see tracks?
Okay, Bravo. On their way. Over.
Nothing this way.
Crap. Sergeant?
Do something! Shoot!
Hit him back.
Get out of there.
They're shooting.
Why? No, no!
Please, help!
Let's get out of here, huh?
Come on, Sal.
Listen.
Can anybody hear me? Over.
This is bad, Sal.
Let's get the hell out of here.
Captain Bradford, this is Dispatch.
- Unable to receive last message.
- Shut up.
Please repeat. John?
- This is bad.
- John? You there?
Can anybody hear me?
Over.
All units report
to Sector 4 immediately.
Over.
All units report to Sector 4 immediately.
Can anybody hear me?
Repeat, this is...
Eddie, the shotgun.
- Can anybody hear me?
- Eddie, the shotgun.
What did this?
I don't know.
Could have been a gator.
But I'd rather not find out.
Come on, let's move.
Good morning, Delmar.
Five more feet to the truck
and it would've been.
What's that?
I said, "My sweet Lord, I'm in luck.
It's Mrs. Brannigan."
I used that cream that you recommended
on Fluffy's sores,
and they cleared right up.
But now she's got this terrible gas.
Fluffy!
Do you have any suggestions?
Yeah. Stop feeding her fruit.
But oranges are her favorite.
Have a nice day.
Today's special.
Rats à la carte.
Delmar, would you
get rid of them things?
You know, with
the breeding rate in rats,
in just about 18 months,
two of these little hairballs can produce
one-and-a-half million offspring.
It's too bad you're not a rat, Delmar.
With odds like that,
you might actually get laid.
Yeah, said the man
in the grease-stained apron
with the rotten teeth
and breath to match.
Esther, next time you hear
scurrying around in the cupboards,
might I suggest an exterminator?
Thanks, Delmar.
Good afternoon, ladies.
Hi, Doll-mar.
Doll-mar.
That's cute. That's real cute.
You ladies weren't swimming
down at Bailey Pond, were you?
Yeah. So?
That's too bad.
I was just headed down that way
to post the signs.
There's no swimming
down at Bailey Pond.
Why not?
A couple of fishermen
pulled some trout out of there,
and they had these big,
bloody sores on them.
I can't confirm it yet,
but I think it's
them flesh-eating bacteria.
Young man!
Can I get my check, please?
Yeah.
You have a good day.
Animal Control to Officer Coates.
Officer Coates, this is
Animal Control Headquarters.
Come in, Delmar. It's me, Cleavis.
It's Cleavis.
Cleavis, what's my day look like?
Oh, yeah, boss.
Some lady out at the trailer park
says her dog's gone missing.
And Mel Gordon says
he's got a snake living under his porch
with a mouth so big,
it could eat a basketball.
I told him to lay off the sauce,
but he insists that you
go out and take a look.
So what are you doing?
Holding down the fort.
Why don't you get off your lazy butt
and help me out?
What's that?
I said, Mel Gordon sounds crazy.
I'll check it out.
Copy.
Jay, in case you hadn't noticed,
the road has now ceased being a road.
Yeah, dude.
Where the hell you taking us?
I'm just following the directions
Dr. Abramson gave us.
Dr. Abramson.
Dr. Abramson is a well-known
and well-respected scientist.
He's head of the ETF.
ETF.
What's that stand for?
Equal Treatment for Fat Girls?
Try again, Einstein.
It's the Environmental Task Force.
Bunch of lab coats
sent down here on the federal payroll
to find a solution to our eel problem.
Didn't know we had an eel problem.
Monopterus albus, boys.
Asian swamp eels.
No one knows exactly when the first one
came off the ballast of some cargo ship,
but indeed they came,
they stayed,
and now they're taking over.
I don't know why you always call that guy.
He's such a joke.
Delmar's cute.
You want to get rid of them rats?
Feed them some of your chili.
Get back to work.
Watch out.
Excuse me.
Damn dogs been in the trash again!
Damn dogs.
Don't do that!
You call me?
Never mind.
Where the hell is that little panty-sniffer?
Yeah.
Where is your dad, loser?
Like to launch the canoes
before Christmas.
He said he w-would be here.
Did he happen to say
wh-wh-wh-wh-when?
I'm here! I'm here!
Sorry I'm late.
Casey, don't forget your sunblock.
Ass-crack.
10 means 10. You got it?
Thank you, Lott, for your
constructive criticism.
All right, are we ready to go?
How about you, Everett?
You ready to go?
Sure, Dad.
Okay.
I got some extra just in case,
so keep it with you.
Hey, Cliff, let me talk to you a minute.
Listen.
If anything happens
to my boy out there, I mean anything,
I'm going to jam this stick up your ass
and roast you like a marshmallow.
We understand one another?
Yeah.
Good.
Let's go over some safety instructions
before we get going.
While you jocks are
doing this for extra credit,
we're doing research
that could save the environment.
The eels are threatening
the entire ecosystem.
This guy, Dr. Abram-injun-son,
he's going to get rid of them?
Yeah. He's looking
for some kind of weakness.
Dude, an Achilles eel.
Extra credit kicks ass.
C-minus, here I come.
- Okay, guys.
- Paddle faster.
Let's get our gear
and have a great weekend.
You might want to
actually try to paddle.
- Now, you kids have fun.
- All right.
- Bye.
See you, buddy.
Y'all be safe out there!
You hear me?
Bye. Love you.
What are you looking at, dork?
Just paddle.
We're not trying to cause
any unnecessary anxiety.
We just ask that you keep
your eyes and ears open
and your doors locked.
If you go out at night,
make sure you take
a flashlight, mace, and your cell phone.
I would also recommend
going in pairs or groups.
Dogcatcher's here.
Otherwise, just go back
to your normal routine.
Chicken and beer.
That's my normal routine.
Maybe you could add a breath mint
and a shower to the list.
You heard the sheriff.
Let's clear out of here.
You're just jealous.
Hey, Delmar.
Hey, Sheriff.
That's how it's gonna be, huh?
The divorce was your idea, remember?
Let's not start.
So what's all the hubbub?
Two prisoners escaped from
County Penitentiary last night.
The search party is missing
and hasn't reported in.
I saw the APB.
You think they're headed our way?
We're just playing it safe.
We're warning everybody
that lives along the river.
Yeah, well, escaped convicts,
it's outside of my area of expertise.
You know somebody
that's missing a dog?
I did. That was me.
Delmar Coates, Animal Control.
How you doin', ma'am?
Well, hello there.
Uh, what kind of dog is it?
An Irish Wolfhound.
Big dog, hard to miss. Name's Duke.
I'd just set out dinner.
How long has he been missing?
Since last night.
Has he been sick at all lately?
Oh, no.
Duke's as healthy as a horse.
Only three months old.
Well, I'll check it out.
Wait here, ma'am...
Like I was saying,
Duke's never not
come home for dinner.
I even made
his favorite food... watermelon.
He just loves watermelon.
What's with all the fruit?
Hasn't anyone heard of pet food?
Now, if I were Duke,
where would I be hiding?
Did you find something?
I don't know. Maybe.
Cliff's Canoe Club.
My office warned Cliff
about the convicts.
He'll take care of the kids.
59 bottles of beer
Take one down, pass it around
58 bottles of beer on the wall
Whoa.
What happened here?
Dr. Abramson?
Yo, Doc.
Hey, hey, hey, hey.
Careful. That might be loaded.
Hey, hey, hey.
Don't point that thing
at a lady. Come on.
You all right, Holly?
- Don't point it at a guy.
- Sorry.
Dr. Abramson?
That must be Dr. Abramson's hat.
- Dude, I've seen this movie.
- Yeah.
The guy's missing,
and all they find is his hat.
Yeah, and when he goes to pick it up,
only thing under there
is his decapitated head.
That's so funny.
That's real mature.
I'm telling you.
- You're such infants.
- No!
Don't do that! Stupid!
What was that?
Please tell me that was just
a harmless little guppy.
Shoot it, dude.
Shoot what, Mark?
I don't see anything.
Over there.
What are we looking at?
Dr. Abramson?
Well, that depends.
Are you my interns
or are you with the EPA?
Uh, we're from the university.
Dr. Soren Abramson,
and welcome to my laboratory.
Dr. Abramson, I'm Holly Shubert.
It's a pleasure.
I've admired you...
your work for...
The pleasure is mine.
And you can call me Soren.
Uh, Jay Wells, sir.
It's just... It's a pleasure to meet you.
- We talked on the phone.
- How do you do?
Mark.
Hello.
- Dean.
- Yes.
Well, it's absolutely
wonderful to have you all.
If I may.
Thank you very much. Right.
As you can see from the current state
of my organizational system,
I am in desperate need
of a few extra hands at the moment.
So if you'll all get your equipment,
we'll get started.
How much further?
Not much farther.
I recognize these trees.
Is this it?
Duke? Come on, boy!
Duke.
Come on, Duke.
I never meant to hurt you, you know.
Okay. Here, Duke.
Here, Duke.
Delmar.
It's gonna be dark soon.
We gotta get back.
I was hoping we could still be friends?
Of course we can, Sheriff.
Something just
brushed up against my leg.
- There! There it is again!
- Whoa!
Whoa, whoa, whoa, Annie Oakley.
What the hell is it?
It's just an eel. It's a baby eel.
Jeez, I thought
it was a water snake.
There it goes.
Aw, damn.
Is that Duke?
Well, what's left of him.
Oh, what could have done that?
Gator, probably.
A very, very hungry gator.
Come on, let's head back.
Oh, great. Oh, what the hell?
Oh, my God.
You wouldn't be overdoing
the chocolate again, would you?
Because I know how you tend
to be an emotional eater.
Screw you, Delmar.
The hole was here. I didn't do this.
Forget it.
I wouldn't do that.
Why not?
You don't know what
made that hole, Ruth.
Well, I can't walk back all that way
with one damn shoe.
Come here.
What?
This isn't exactly what I had in mind.
Just shut up.
Enjoy the ride.
Pepper.
Pepper, Daddy's home.
Pepper?
Pepper!
Wow.
She's taking it hard.
Yeah. Well, a lot of people can get
real attached to their pets.
Some folks actually prefer
animals over people.
Yeah. I was married
to somebody like that.
Well, from what I understand,
it has something to do
with the fact that pets
don't want us to be different.
They accept us the way we are.
Well, I really appreciate
what you did back there.
You didn't... You didn't have to do that.
No, but I wanted to.
Well...
I better get back to work.
Hey, Ruth.
Yeah?
It really wasn't all that bad, was it?
I remember some good parts.
Pepper!
This is gonna be a big one.
Oh, yeah.
What?
I see.
Take a look.
Notice anything unusual?
Looks like some kind of
chromosomal disorder.
Exactly.
I call it the Abramson gene.
It's a defect I discovered
in some of the eels.
It causes sterility
both in the male and female.
I found a way to reconstruct it.
Genetic engineering.
Is that legal?
I assure you, from a scientific
point of view, it's quite legal.
But is it ethical?
These eels have no known predator.
They're at the top of the food chain.
They devour everything.
It'll save the ecosystem.
Now, is that ethical?
Hey, Doc!
What are these?
Eel traps.
We'll use them
to collect eels downriver.
So these are, like,
to catch the babies?
No, adults.
We could run into some
as large as 3 feet.
How in the hell's a 3-foot eel
gonna fit through a hole this size?
Same way I do, dude.
Lubricated.
You're half-right.
The eel secretes a mucus to facilitate
its movement over dry land.
It can be quite slippery.
But more to the point,
the eel is almost completely muscle.
Like me.
It can redistribute its mass to fit in
almost anywhere it wants to go.
Wait a minute.
You just said that
they move over dry land?
Won't they die out of water?
They have gills for their
primary oxygen intake,
but they can also respire
through their snout.
Pretty bad-ass, then?
You don't know the half of it.
They have a mouth
full of razor-sharp teeth
and a jaw so powerful...
I knew a man.
Eel got hold of his leg.
He had to cut off its head
before it'd let go of him.
Did that really happen?
What do you think?
Fluffy?
Hold on.
Sure you want to do this?
No.
Then why are we...
'Cause life is complicated.
Let's get complicated.
What about...
Fluffy?
Fluffy.
Sweetie.
Sweetie, where are you?
Did you hear something?
No.
Help!
Dude, this sucks butt.
Yeah, it does suck.
But we need the extra credit.
What are those?
A little power-up.
Man, I thought you were off the juice.
Look, this isn't steroids, dawg.
It's Gluco-Zee supplement tablets.
I don't know, some kind of new
instant energy thing, dude.
They taste like sugar.
It's 'cause they are sugar, idiot.
Jeez.
Just shut up and pull up the trap.
You know what? This does suck.
Jay's probably back there
all cuddled up with Holly in the truck,
and we're out here with the freakin' eels.
What's so funny?
You like her.
No.
I know that look, dude. You're lying.
No, I don't.
Yeah, whatever, Gaylord.
Dude.
Look in the window.
She's hot and naked and ready.
Dude, dude, dude, dude,
dude, dude...
Dude.
That is the extra credit
we've been waiting for.
Get out of here!
Perverts!
Thank you.
- Thank you very much!
- Yeah!
Holy crap!
Dude, someone lost a canoe.
Animal Control.
Where's that joker Delmar?
Why didn't he come out here
to check on this damn snake?
Oh, hey, Mel.
He's probably been busy.
You sure what you saw was a snake
and not maybe a pink elephant?
You take yourself, and you go
straight to H-E double toothpicks.
I know what I seen!
Give me 15 minutes.
But, Mel, there better
be a snake out there,
or I'm gonna break that bottle
over your head.
Delmar?
How is it I don't remember
having this much sex
when we were married?
When did you have the time?
If I wanted your attention,
I had to dress up like a bear
or paint myself like
a deadly African swamp fish.
Not a swamp fish.
More like a blowfish.
You want to get something?
Starving.
And you want to go to the diner.
Mel?
Mel Gordon!
Oh, come on, Mel.
Don't go playing games with me now.
Son of a...
Aw, gee, Mel.
What'd you go and do to yourself?
- Something's wrong.
- This is weird.
Are they closed?
That would be a first.
Well, looks like someone tried the chili.
Think it was those two
escaped from County?
Let's take a look.
Aw, jeez.
I thought I got rid of all those.
I have to call this in.
There is food all over the...
That's not food.
Ruthie!
All hell's breaking loose.
I've just come
from Mel Gordon's place.
I found him up on the roof dead.
Something took a bite
out of him, a big bite.
Hell, Ruthie, he was gone
from the waist down.
Delmar, one of your
trucks was out there.
Excuse me. Coming through.
I found this.
Aw, Cleavis.
That ain't the half of it.
I just got a call from Dr. Abramson.
Some of his college interns
found a canoe
out by Kerchner Crossing.
Problem is last anybody
saw this canoe,
it was full of members of
the Mountain View Canoe Club.
All right. I'd better head up there.
Wait.
One of them boys missing
is Lott Dryer's son.
He's out there now. He's all riled up.
He's putting together
some sort of damn posse.
Gonna hunt down whoever's responsible.
I'll deal with it.
Get me the most recent
mug shots on those convicts.
You don't think they had
something to do with this?
Somebody did a number on this place.
Or some thing.
You okay?
Yeah.
See that?
Just like I told you.
This is your cousin's place?
Yeah. Come on.
Come on.
Contact Fire and Rescue.
See if we can one
of their choppers in the air.
We're gonna need
eyes on the ground, too.
Get as many volunteers as you can.
I want a deputy assigned to each group.
Make sure they all have maps
and communications.
Got it.
They were last seen right here,
moving in this direction.
Now, we form a line.
Push those sons of bitches northwest.
Sheriff, our kids are out there.
Ladies, we're going to find your kids.
Just give all your information
to Deputy Horner.
It'll be okay.
Look out!
If you see anything...
I mean anything... suspicious,
don't worry about the ammo.
Rounds are on me.
You want to talk to them students,
that's them over there
with Dr. Abramson.
What are we looking for, exactly?
Delmar, will you take that?
I've got bigger fish to fry.
Okay, now, right here...
Lott Dryer.
You can just climb back into that truck
and head yourself on home.
One of those boys out there's mine.
And I'm gonna help find him
whether you like it or not.
We're going to find your son.
It's the cowboy tactics
that's not the kind of help I need.
Ruth... he's the only boy I got.
Fine. But if you get in my way,
I'll have you arrested.
Any of those sons of bitches
lay a hand on my boy...
you'll arrest me...
for murder.
I knew I'd find you
slithering around out here.
Delmar.
Somehow, I knew our paths
would cross again.
Tell me about the eel.
Eel? What eel?
Esther out at the diner is dead.
Cleavis is dead.
Mel Gordon, all dead.
Now, you tell me
about the goddamn eel.
What is happening here?
Ask him.
What's the story?
Officer Coates seems to believe
that I might be partially responsible
for what's been going on around here.
Not partially. Entirely.
We're talking about a giant eel here, Ruth.
A mutant.
One of Dr. Frankenstein's monsters.
Really, Delmar. Monsters?
Delmar, I've got two escaped felons,
a dozen parents worried
half out of their minds.
Now, I'm sorry.
You can't expect me
to spend my resources on a witch hunt.
Besides, do you really think
the ETF would have
one of their top scientists
going around creating
a race of killer eel?
No. Not since they suspended him
six months ago.
Doc?
Tell them the truth.
We hatched a specimen in the lab.
It grew to 6 feet in the first two months.
I was about to publish our results
when it attacked a colleague.
Killed him.
I mean, she escaped
before we could trap her.
And you didn't tell anyone?
Nobody in the task force
wanted to admit that we'd
made the problem worse.
God help us.
We embedded a tracking chip
in the eel's jaw.
I've been out here
looking for her ever since.
Dude, this so isn't worth the extra credit.
Sheriff, I had no idea
this was going to happen.
But if I can catch her, I can destroy her.
Oh, Dr. Abramson.
Lou!
Lou?
Where are you hiding,
you fat, chicken-eating bastard?
Well, somebody's been here.
Hey, let's see what's for dinner.
Lou.
If that's dinner,
maybe we should have
stayed in the joint.
Tonight was meatloaf and gravy.
Eddie, don't be a jerk.
Eel's a delicacy.
The Greeks eat that crap
for their Christmas dinner.
Yeah, I'll stick with turkey and trimmings,
if you don't mind.
So where's this cousin of yours?
Well, my guess is
he's out picking dingleberries
to bake us a dingleberry pie.
How the hell am I supposed
to know where he is?
Take a seat,
'cause we are not going anywhere.
Sit down.
I'll find him.
Sal, I'm hungry.
This is where the scouts
left yesterday.
This is where
the canoes were found.
I've marked with an X
the places of potential eel attacks.
Diner, trailer park,
Mel Gordon's place.
This modulator controls
a small electrical current
that will draw the eel towards us.
When she gets close enough,
we'll track her using this device.
Now, the signal isn't very strong,
so she'll be right on top of someone
before you know it.
And when she's close?
I've packed enough cyanide
in this crossbow bolt
to drop an elephant.
One shot and it's
calamari for everyone.
Calamari is squid, you idiot.
Now, the eels will generally
stick close to their dens,
provided there's an ample food supply.
Any sign of this thing,
anything abnormal,
give me a holler and I'll get there.
What about a unicorn?
Should we give you a call
if we see one of those?
Can it, Lott.
Listen, Sheriff.
There's no way in hell
I'm walking in that water
if this wacko's firin' off
one of those battery charges.
We're searching for convicts.
If there's a big bad eel out there,
I'll take care of it.
How you plan to do that?
The old-fashioned way.
Watch out!
- Look out.
- Cool.
That's just great, Lott.
How much you know about eels?
I know enough to kill 'em.
It's not that simple.
They're quiet, and they're hard to find.
And if they're under
the water out there,
you won't see them
and you won't hear them.
Delmar, you're scaring me.
If I might interject, Delmar's correct.
You can be right on top of one
and not know it
until the creature pulls you under.
All right, Doc.
If I say I can handle it,
I can handle it.
All right.
My team will search the nest area.
Deputy, take yours up north
to Kerchner Crossing.
Everybody else,
follow the river along south
down to Elliot's Station.
Right, the only question remaining is
who's going to carry
the tracking devices?
No way.
I'll take it.
I think I should...
I should probably take that.
Agreed.
All right. Any more questions?
Yeah, I have one more...
Great. Let's move out.
All right, guys. Let's go.
- Yeah!
- It's on!
Keep your eyes peeled.
She could be anywhere.
How come I didn't get a gun?
Shut up, retard.
Follow me.
Don't piss me off, kid.
Not funny.
Any sign of it?
Not yet.
I suggest we change positions.
Here. Catch.
Doc?
You said this eel was 6 feet
at two months, right?
Well, it's four months old now.
Wouldn't that mean it's,
like, 12 feet or more?
Could be, yes.
That's an awful lot of fish.
You think there's enough
cyanide in that thing to stop it?
Well, there'd better be.
Otherwise, we're in
an awful lot of trouble.
This thing could live
for a few hours after we hit it.
Did you get a chance to study
the eel's metabolism in the lab?
No. Apart from the specific
mutation we made to the gene,
we didn't look at it.
What specific mutation?
It can't metabolize sugar.
Sugar?
Yes, well, the orange growers
in this particular area
are a powerful lobby,
and they were afraid
that the eels would devour
the nearby orange groves.
Anyway, shall we?
Lou, you taking a dump?
He ain't got anything to eat in this place.
You eat what you catch here.
- That's the rule.
- Sal, I'm hungry.
And I just sprung you from jail.
Now keep quiet, okay?
I'll be quiet.
Hungry and quiet.
What in the hell?
Oh, you've got to be kidding me.
I bet them kids got plenty of food.
Yeah.
Let's go visit the camp a little bit later.
Come on.
Maybe they went this way.
Come on, guys. We have to find them.
You heard what Lott said.
He's gonna roast me
like a marshmallow.
Real charmer, isn't he?
Yeah, sweet as vinegar.
Anybody got any chaw?
I got some jerky.
I got some turkey jerky.
Hey, Chubby.
You know, you really need
those complex amino acids
to keep your blood sugar up
because breakfast is the most
important meal of the day.
Come on, Pete.
Don't lag so far back.
Pete?
Aw, no, Blinky, run!
Go faster!
Don't look back!
Come on, Blinky!
Go. Go, go, go, go, go!
Come on!
Run, Blinky, run!
Come on, Blinky!
Keep running!
Don't look back!
Run, Blinky!
They're having cheerleader
tryouts next week.
I'm gonna be sick.
So, Holly, how does it feel
to ride on the varsity bus
for a while instead of Jay-Vee?
Excuse me?
Well, I was just saying it must be nice
to shake yourself
of Jay the Super Brain for a change.
I'm not interested in Jay.
We're just friends.
I think what the moron's
trying to say is it's nice
you're hanging with us for a change.
So is that supposed
to be a compliment?
- Yeah.
Well, thank you.
So, Holly, you don't really
hate football, do you?
I mean, that's just a joke, right?
No.
I really do hate football.
How about you guys?
You don't really hate reading books
and expanding your mind, do you?
- Yeah!
I think reading pretty much sucks.
But then again, I've never had somebody
to talk to about books or foreign films
or anything mind-expanding like that.
Well...
you could always...
talk to Jay.
Dude, she played you so good.
- That was sweet.
- Yeah.
Mark, take a walk.
Holly, wait up.
Oh. I see how it is.
You guys go have fun.
I'm just gonna...
Don't give me another thought.
Guys!
Guys! Sheriff!
Sheriff, come over here!
Guys, come over here!
Oh, my gosh.
It's the Canoe Club.
The camp's been torn to pieces.
That's got to be the eel.
Hey, Sheriff.
You think that eel wears
a prison-issued work boot?
Do you?
A boot doesn't prove anything, Lott.
Proves those sons of bitches
are out there with my boy.
We've got plenty of tracks to follow.
Yeah, it looks like they head west.
Doc, you better bring the boat.
Dude, don't you ever leave me.
See what happens?
All right, everyone.
Let's spread out.
20-yard intervals.
All right.
You heard her, men. Let's go!
Give me that. Thanks, bro.
Bye, Holly.
I'll be nearby if you need me,
so just holler, okay?
Alone at last.
What's that supposed to mean?
Nothing. So which one am I,
Dumb or Dumber?
Please tell me Mark is Dumber.
Yeah, you're just Dumb.
You think about it?
Yeah, I think about it.
With me or just in general?
I told you I think about it!
I think, according to some researchers,
opposites attract in about 75% of...
Shut up.
What was that?
What was it?
Oh, my God!
Oh, make it go away!
Please.
Hey! Hey, guys!
What the hell is going on here?
Jay, don't. It's here.
Where?
In the water!
It's here?
Holly?
Holly...
Where is she?
Look at it.
Damn. Did you see that thing?
15 feet, easy.
We hit it. It's like it didn't even faze it.
Unless you hit it in the head,
these little guns are
not going to help at all.
What happened?
Jay's gone.
Damn it.
- You guys, bring the boat around.
- Let's go!
Shots came from over there.
Let's move it!
I don't know how you stayed alive, kid!
We're the only ones left!
You and me!
Run!
Run, kid!
Come on, kid. Run!
Who is it?
Think you mean, who was it?
Eddie Mason.
One of the escaped convicts.
Or what's left of him.
She is really close.
This way, everybody.
Everett, honey.
Do you think you can
tell us what happened?
I mean, where are the other kids?
Sweetheart,
I know you're scared, and that's okay.
But we need to find the others.
Do you think you can tell us
what happened and where they are?
Listen, you little retard,
you tell me where my son is
before I knock your head off!
Lott, I am handling this.
You're doing a bang-up job, Sheriff.
Look at all the useful information
you got out of him.
Nothing! Dumb bitch.
Back off, Lott.
Go to hell, you little dogcatcher.
Come here, boy!
- I want to know!
- I said back off!
You're not in charge here.
If we're going to survive this thing
and find your son,
we need to work together, you got it?
You got it?
Okay. Okay.
Let go.
It's okay. You don't have to talk.
It's okay.
Maybe you could just show us.
Let's take a closer look.
Doc, you and the kids hang back.
Let's go.
Lott, don't go in there.
No, don't.
- What?
- Don't.
It's my boy?
Get out of my way.
Take a good look, Doc.
How you gonna make this one right?
How'd it get in?
Where are the bodies?
You're telling me it chewed its way in?
I guess we found the bodies.
Everett, are you okay?
The search is over. We have to go back.
I need to get the coroner's unit out here.
Lott, I'm sorry.
Me, too.
The search ain't over.
We might have found them kids,
but we haven't found that beast.
Everett, what's wrong?
What is it, kid?
Dude, you're freaking me out.
Gonna kill ourselves an eel.
Hey...
there's something wrong
with that stuttering dude.
Son of a bitch.
Everett, wait here.
What happened?
Mark!
You get the kids inside now.
Now!
Come on, let's go.
Start the generator, Doc.
Get ready.
This'll bring her in closer to us.
Perfect.
It's circling us.
Where?
She's studying us.
She's very close now,
and in for quite a shock, I might add.
There it is.
Coming your way, Doc!
Doc! Doc!
Shoot it, Doc!
Shoot it!
I can hack it.
Doc!
Doc.
Give me your hand.
Stay out of the water!
No!
No, Doc!
Is it dead?
Doc?
Wow.
Dr. Abramson killed it, right?
Yeah.
So he's a hero.
It's gone.
What do you mean, it's gone?
Let's go
before it decides to come back.
Get the kid. We're out of here.
Delmar, what are we going to do?
I told you, we're leaving.
Delmar.
We'll never make it.
The guns are ineffective
without the cyanide.
We'll never make it.
What do you want me to do, Ruth?
Well, that thing is an animal,
and that's your area of expertise.
There's got to be something.
Hey, guys!
There's something
wrong with the kid!
This is a medical ID.
Look. He's diabetic.
He's going into shock.
Check his pockets for insulin.
Here we go.
Hold on.
Come on, kid.
Oh, my God. That's it.
That's the reason the eel didn't kill him.
He's diabetic.
What are you talking about?
Soren said that the eel
can't digest sugar.
So it's essentially a Type II diabetic.
If Everett's blood sugar
level was too high,
the eel would have been
repulsed by the sweetness.
That's why he didn't finish the job.
We need sugar, a lot of it,
and very concentrated.
Sugar? I got sugar.
Mark's glucose pills.
Ruth, prep one
of those syringes, empty it out.
Get something to boil some water.
We need to liquefy the glucose.
Do you really think
this is going to work?
It just might.
Here you go.
You only got one shot
with this, you know.
Yeah, I know.
All right, you guys,
take Everett and head east.
Do not stop till you
get to base camp,
no matter what.
Okay, run. Go.
Good luck, you guys.
You're short on daylight.
You'd better hurry.
Keep going!
You ready to do this?
You?
It's animal control.
It's what I do.
Let's roll.
Come and get it!
Tasty human here.
If you can catch me, you can eat me.
Come on!
Where are you?
Come and get it, you dumb eel.
Come on!
Come on, you dumb eel!
Come and get me!
Come on!
Come and get it! Come on!
Come get me now!
Get ready!
Now!
Hey!
The Doc's poison,
it worked.
It worked, Ruth.
I think it's dead.
Come on down.
You okay?
I'm fine.
Yeah.
Nice shot, Sheriff.
Thank you.
That is one shot I will take credit for.
What the...
Unbelievable.
We're running out of options here.
Any more ideas?
Lott.
He's dead.
Yeah, but he's always prepared.
Lott, you son of a bitch.
I love you.
In case I don't make it.
You're gonna make it.
Be careful.
Daddy's home!
And he's got a present for you!
I'll cover you.
Chew on this, you big bitch!
Watch behind you.
Come on!
I'm hungry,
and I feel like unagi tonight.
Come on!
That's it.
Come to Papa.
Not yet.
Delmar!
Do it!
Kill it!
Delmar!
Come on, we've got
about nine seconds.
- Sit down.
- What...
Sit down.
I think we got it this time?
I don't know about you,
but I'm starving.
Me, too.
What are you in the mood for?
Anything but seafood.
I've been meaning to ask you something.
Well, you first.
A blowfish?
Subtitles by LeapinLar