Thank you, Tom. This is Kip Wellington
at Springfield Penitentiary,
where notorious inmate Shawn Gracey
is still on the loose.
Gracey was apprehended three years ago
by the police for the murders
of over 35 people
in a small suburban town.
Police and authorities
are still working around the clock
to capture this notorious criminal.
We will be following the story,
and I will be checking in as it...
No. Oh, my God.
Oh, my God!
Come on, Betsy! Betsy, please! Oh, no!
Betsy. Betsy, wake up.
Please...
You fucking asshole!
You just let her die?
Lmpressive wine cellar.
I was so surprised
you made your own.
I've always wondered if this worked.
No.
No!
Please no. No. Stop.
You know, they say the doctor says
a glass of wine...
it's good for the heart.
Hold still.
Could've aged it better.
Well, what do you think, Betsy?
Be honest.
Speak.
Yeah. Yeah, kind of.
I did the rest of
the 'shrooms last night.
Gave me messed. Up dreams.
Because I was bored, and I had them.
Yeah. Okay. Yeah.
See you there.
There you go.
Thank you, dear.
No problem.
My little granddaughter's
gonna love these.
I don't know why my son put them
up so high in the first place.
Doesn't matter now anyway, does it?
You're right.
Are you okay?
These days, not so much.
What's wrong?
It's nothing to worry about.
I think my doctor
has to adjust one of my pills.
Mrs. Spool, about your medicine...
What would I do without you?
I've been switching it out
for quite a while now.
All of it.
What?
- Yeah.
- Why?
I just wanted to see how long it would take.
Call 911.
Diabetes, high blood pressure,
congestive heart failure.
You know, you hung in there
a lot longer than I thought.
Please...
Tell me, does it hurt?
Yes.
Well, that's a bummer.
I always get the same thing.
- It doesn't hurt to look.
- That's what she said.
- That doesn't even apply.
- It always applies.
I would like to apply
your face to the bar.
You're so rough, Donna.
So how does the band sound
on the new equipment?
Fucking fantastic.
Although I need you to come on over
and help me with the wiring.
What's wrong with the wires?
It's gonna be my last hurrah.
Shut up, dude. You're not quitting.
Being in a band
in high school was cool,
but it's different now.
Old man Mike.
That's who you are now.
You have responsibilities
to the band.
I'm not being old, Sam.
I'm just telling... I'm being realistic.
What do you think, penis?
- Don!
- You serious?
My Christ,
will you just go talk to her?
Soon enough.
You've been staring at that girl
for three freaking years, Don,
and in that time, you've said what?
I don't know. 17 words to her.
And you're just pissed off
because I still got options.
You're the one that's getting hitched.
That's something
I don't want to talk about.
Shut up.
Besides, he's trying
to get back together with Liz.
- No, I am not.
- You totally are.
Okay. A little.
You're both nuts.
Only in my dreams.
Stop obsessing, Debbie Gibson.
Yeah. Snagged.
Jenn, give me the hot wings, please.
I'll take the usual.
I'm gonna empty the tank.
Can I get another orange juice?
- Sure.
- Thanks.
Aw, man.
Yeah, I'll have a burger.
Say, Jenn,
Dickhead Don
is having a party this weekend.
You son of a bitch.
Why don't you and Janet stop by?
We might be able to fit that
into our schedules.
Awesome.
You're a fucking genius.
- What?
- Nothing.
Everything come out okay?
Well, I'd love to stay
for the happy ending,
- but I gotta get back to frigging work.
- I hear that.
I told Elizabeth
I'd help her out at the store.
- See you.
- That's who you're tied to, pal.
I'll see you, Mike.
You're a pinky. Finger marionette.
You're a loser.
Don't forget to come over tonight
and help me out with the wiring, okay?
You got it.
Good day, Lizzie.
Nice of you to show up, bud.
Queen Elizabeth
couldn't start without me?
It just wouldn't have been any fun.
Besides, you were the one
that offered to help.
I didn't think you'd actually
take me up on it.
Creep.
So you're really gonna move?
I really am.
You're gonna miss me
and the guys.
Don, you knew I was planning
to move to Santa Monica
before Mom's heart attack.
She's feeling better.
Yeah. We can just buy the place
and let them retire in Florida.
Stop being such a goon.
I know.
I'm just saying.
We always fight.
You always start them.
Don't you realize
how perfect things could be
if, you know,
you just kind of did what I said?
Lived at my beck and call.
You are such a creep.
And besides, everybody knows
you love Janet.
Come on.
You know that's a goof.
No. You are.
Speaking of mature...
Oh, God.
Knock it off.
What are you doing?
I want that one.
Just one second.
Yeah. Speak.
Yes.
No. You're supposed
to click out of that.
My mom just got a new Mac.
No, Mom, you're not supposed to be
in System Preferences.
Just don't click on that.
I can't believe this.
Go help her.
Mom... Mom... Mom...
Mom, okay, look, I will come over
to the house to help.
Just don't touch anything.
Okay.
They never listen.
Go and help your mom, Don.
We can finish this stuff
in the morning.
You sure?
Unless there's any more literature
you'd like to swipe from me today.
No, actually, you can take this back.
Hey, you still having
that thing on Friday?
Yeah, of course.
You should come.
I'll see you in the morning.
I promise.
Do you gotta chew like that?
I mean, do you have to chew like that?
It doesn't ring, dick slap.
It just flashes a light.
By the way,
how'd you guys get in here?
Back door was open.
Okay, I gotta head to Doc's.
So where is the old coot anyway?
Didn't ask.
What is that smell?
Sorry. I farted.
No, not that one. The other one.
Doc Bates... he's semiretired.
He's got sort of
a dental office set up downstairs.
He has nitrous.
Don't even think about going
close to that entrance.
Party pooper.
Let's go, guys.
You think S. W.A. T.
Was a better show than The A. Team?
Cute doggy.
Thank you.
She really loves that dog?
Yeah, she does.
She'd love one of her own,
but I just don't have the time.
That's not yours?
No. It's Laurie's. We're neighbors.
We bring them here together
so they can tire
each other out, you know?
Isn't that cute?
You live around here?
No. I was just going for a walk,
and the bench looked comfortable.
You really should get her
a dog of her own.
Excuse me?
Yeah.
Kids need something to take care of.
It makes them better mommies.
Tina,
let's go.
Yeah, you agree. That's what I said.
Laurie, we'll see you later.
. Bye.
. Hi.
I know. He has the best house.
So they were like, "We'll
see you next Wednesday,"
and that was that.
I'm sorry.
Mrs. Muggles,
you really should leave people alone.
So obviously, party this weekend?
I know. Right?
I think he's bringing lots of beer.
You could've hired
somebody to do that.
Might be time to throw out the butter.
These wires look like a rat's nest.
I told you not to touch them
until I got back.
So, dude, I have a confession.
Don't do it, douche!
Do what?
Ah, fuck!
Honey, look what I did. I'm sorry.
Let me see if I've got
something to fix you up.
What do you got in here?
Really.
Oh, my God. I've always wanted
to see if this works.
Shocked myself good.
That's what you get.
Too bad it didn't kill you.
Oh, yeah? Hey, do me a favor.
Don't use these externals
until I get a chance to fix them.
Now, I knew that wasn't gonna work.
I'll tell you what.
I'm gonna be really, really nice.
I'm gonna put you out of your misery.
Seriously, I don't get how you dong bags
thought that inviting Janet
would be funny.
Oh, come on. Everybody knows
you're getting back together with Liz.
You're gonna work it all out
and end up like this asshole.
Liz was busting my chops
about her today.
I'm free. I could take Janet.
You're a douche.
Whatever.
I just wish you two
would get hit by a bus.
Hey, so, if I ever
get locked out or whatever...
And, actually,
you can do something for me.
I got a shitload to do on Friday
since it's gonna take me
a little while to get back,
so can you guys set up for me?
- Yeah.
- Yeah, I can.
Oh, and you should know
- that I gave the key to that girl.
- Who?
The girl from Craig's List.
The one that I found.
You know, the intern, the helper...
Whatever. I thought
I told you about her.
You didn't say it would be a girl.
Well, she's into music production,
and it's gonna look good
on her resume.
Such a Samaritan.
Do you even know what that means?
Yes, I do.
Can we go upstairs
and watch the movie now?
I told Nancy I wouldn't be too late.
What?
Fuck you guys.
...where notorious inmate
Shawn Gracey
is still on the loose.
- Any cute boys at school?
- Gracey was apprehended three years ago
by the police for the murders
of over 35 people
in a small suburban town.
Police and authorities
- Are still working around the clock...
- She's sleeping.
...to capture this notorious criminal.
We will be following the story,
and I will be checking in as it breaks.
Back to you, Tom.
I can't believe it.
That movie was bad.
That movie was just plain bad.
Young man,
there's no need to feel down.
Nice coat.
Okay, guys. Hey.
I gotta get up early
to help out Elizabeth.
Wow. Well, be careful you don't burn up
in the morning sun like a vampire.
- Vampire!
- I'll burn your face.
- Wow.
- My rapier wit.
Oh, shit. I forgot my trash.
Sellout.
- Both of you.
- Was that for you?
And now that you've littered yourself.
Dude, call me tomorrow.
How's it going, Karen?
How are you?
Who's the best?
You are.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
So guess who just
paid me a visit at my car.
Who?
- Tony D.
- Tony D?
- That guy's out of control.
- I know.
He got me last week.
He just wants your money.
You didn't give him any money, did you?
Of course I gave him money.
It's your fault.
You didn't give him any money?
No.
I gave him a banana.
I had a banana in my bag,
so I gave it to him.
Because you were concerned
about his potassium levels.
Right?
Well, you know,
I want him to be healthy.
- Thank you, Tom. This is Kip Wellington...
- Hey, look.
...standing outside Springfield
Penitentiary...
They still haven't caught that killer.
...where notorious inmate Shawn Gracey
is still on the loose.
- Gracey was apprehended...
- Scary.
...three years ago by the police
for the murders of over 35 people.
Who the hell's there?
What the...
What the fuck is going on?
Hope you don't mind.
I borrowed some clothes.
They smelled kind of clean.
What the fuck?
Who the hell are you?
What is this?
Okay, okay, okay.
All right. This is some kind of joke, right?
You're some kind of stripper
or something, right?
Yeah. That's very funny, guys.
It's hysterical.
Okay, here we go.
Thanks, guys.
This is great.
You can come out now.
God damn.
- What...
- I am not a stripper.
What the fuck?
Don't speak.
Fuck!
Do you like this now?
I swear to God,
when I get out of here, I'm gonna...
Come on.
Knock it the fuck off.
You will not move from this seat.
Oh, God! That's...
Oh, God!
Fuck! Fuck!
Fuck!
You will not sleep.
You want to see something
really scary?
Lts natural environment is a hole.
Time to go home now, buddy.
Son of a bitch!
Son of a bitch worm!
Why don't you just go home?
That is your home now! Go home!
That is your home now!
Disgusting!
I have to wash this shit off of me,
thank you very much.
Here, kitty, kitty, kitty, kitty, kitty.
All right.
Oh, shit.
Look at what I did.
Eat a bowl of dicks.
Well, you've got a dirty mouth.
We should clean that up.
Let me the fuck go.
Is it safe?
Un. Fucking. Tie me,
and I won't rip out your larynx.
Is it safe?
Is what safe?
No!
You look like a marlin.
Get it the fuck out!
Wait. Hold still.
Sorry. Tricked you.
What do you care anyway? It's out.
Here. Chew on this for a bit.
You're getting blood
all over the place.
I feel like I'm forgetting something.
The coffee.
Hey, I really like these mugs.
Where'd you get them?
Hot.
Why?
"Why"?
Why you can afford to live
in a place like this.
That's what I want to know.
It's just you. No housemates.
Go to hell.
You have no idea
where I've been, brother.
What happened here?
Go fuck yourself.
I don't want you to pass out.
What?
You'll see.
You got a lot of fun stuff here.
Hey, it's all yours.
Just get the hell out of here.
I don't want your junk, pal.
Oh, fuck!
Fuck!
Go...
Gnarly. A fake kneecap.
You must've had all kinds
of rehab for this.
"Are you coming by later?"
Sorry.
All tied up with work.
Stop by later.
Smiley face.
Oh, fuck!
Hey, asshole,
I brought some, uh, T. Shirts.
Hi.
Hello.
So you're her.
"Her"?
Craig's List.
Yeah.
Yeah, I'm Jenn.
That's funny. We know a Jenn.
Yeah. Who doesn't?
Seriously.
Yeah, so, I'm just doing
some work for him downstairs.
Really?
It's probably my band...
The Low Budgets.
I like it.
Well, we're having a show
this Saturday at the Rusty Nail.
You should come by
and bring some friends.
I totally will.
And I patched the external wiring.
You did? Really?
I've got a broad education.
I see that.
So the mix will be done
by the party for sure.
Sweet.
I'll probably see you Saturday?
I can let myself out.
You must be thirsty.
There you go.
It's good for you. Little more.
Little more.
Come on.
Sam's outside.
What?
Sam?
Sam, help me!
Don? Yo. Donny.
Don. Donny.
Did you pick up those...
What happened to your face?
What the...
You are not an intern.
Okay?
Don, I'm sorry about this.
Sam...
Get up, Sam!
You okay, man?
Kill that fucking bitch!
Sam...
Don, you're okay.
You're okay, hon. You're okay.
Jesus.
I wish the doctor could just give me
a pill to forget about this whole thing.
I know you do, sweetie.
Come up to bed.
Okay.
Okay. Be right there.
I'm never gonna
get used to that thing.
That's the point.
- Don't forget to...
- Pick up my suit.
I know.
Just reminding you.
Thank you, sweetheart.
You don't want to be late, Liz.
Yeah. Right. Okay.
I'll be back by lunchtime.
I'll be here.
Well, bef...
She's still not
gonna be there, Don.
DC's a pretty long commute.
And besides, aren't you living
with your girlfriend now, piggy?
It's a habit, I swear.
So how nervous are you?
Scared shitless, right?
No, not really.
That's bullshit.
That's what I want.
Don't forget your suits, dicks.
Don. Suits. All right?
Okay. And don't wear
that bandana, please.
I'm going to wear
nothing but the bandana.
Jesus!
I'm sorry.
I wasn't even thinking.
- Seriously?
- I'm sorry.
Okay.
I'm sorry, too.
You okay?
Yeah.
So what did the doctor say?
Really?
Wow.
It's pretty cool.
It's really cool.
Did you remember to...
No.
Wow.
Sam, help me!
That's enough.
It can wait.
Sam!
Aren't you nervous at all?
Just for the first dance.
Mike cannot dance a step.
I know. Don's not much
of a dancer, either.
I didn't meant it that way.
I know you didn't.
How's he been?
Is he still going to the shrink?
Yeah.
He still has some bad days.
But more good lately.
That's good.
He's a strong guy,
and he's got you.
Thanks.
Yeah.
You want to dance, Lizzie?
Go ahead.
You sure?
You know I hate dancing.
No! No!
What's wrong, honey?
Don, you okay?
I didn't have to dance with her, dude.
I feel like such a jackass.
It's no big deal.
I was so dumb.
Everyone understands.
I love you so much.
Oh, yeah?
Yeah.
Sorry.
That's okay.
I took a pill.
Jesus.
Jesus! What the fuck?
Get the fuck off me!
Get off me!
God. You were raping me.
What the...
Oh, my God.
You sick fuck! You sick fucking fuck!
You raped me.
I'll show you.
I'll show you what it
feels like to be violated.
My parents used to have these.
The Vietnamese invented this.
I learned about it in school.
No. No.
Oh, God!
Damn it!
God! Fuck!
Oh, God!
Fuck!
No.
- Fuck!
- Stay with me.
Stay with me now.
Sam!
Sam left you.
I had the craziest
fucking dream last night.
This morning, I guess.
Christ, will you just go talk to her?
You've been staring at that girl
for three freaking years now, Don,
and in that time, you've said what?
I don't know. 17 words to her.
- I...
- Sad, man.
Sad.
That's the girl in my dream.
You didn't just say that.
No. No. I. It's...
We know. The girl of your dreams.
Stop obsessing, Debbie Gibson.
Yeah. Snagged.
Okay, I gotta drain the tank.
Can I get another juice?
Sure.
Stupid mushrooms.
Awesome.
You're a freaking genius.
What?
You're staring.
I'm sorry.
Just thinking.
We always fight.
You always start them.
Don't you realize
how perfect things could be
if you'd just, you know...
What?
You were in the middle of saying
something earth. Shattering.
Yeah. I was.
You can be such a pillowcase, Don.
What are you doing?
Hello.
Yeah. Hi, Mom.
Wait, wait, wait. Just stop.
No, don't touch anything.
I'll come and help you.
Just don't touch anything else.
Okay.
I just got my mom a new Mac.
Go help your mom, Don.
We can finish this stuff
tomorrow morning.
Hey, you still having
that thing on Friday?
The mix isn't ready.
You know,
problem with the studio.
I'll let you know
as soon as I reschedule.
All right? I'll...
see you later.
Don!
On, God, no.
No, no, no, no. Leave her alone.
Please.
It's the funniest story.
Oh, hi.
Hello.
Don's expecting me.
Come on in.
I was just gonna make some tea,
and then we can go downstairs.
I'm just helping Don
with some recording stuff.
Oh, okay.
Sorry. My feet are killing me.
Don't be silly. Relax.
I'm Christine, by the way.
Elizabeth.
So has Don been working all day?
Oh, yeah. Since pretty early.
He gets really
into his work, you know.
Well, that's good.
Good for him.
How are you liking it?
I've been having
a lot of fun down there.
Really.
Come on, Elizabeth.
He talks about you all the time.
He does?
I probably shouldn't have said that.
But you did.
What does he say?
He says you're the one who got away.
Should've chased after you.
Sorry. I didn't mean to embarrass you.
You didn't.
It's been a long day.
I'll say.
- I got your text.
- Oh, shut up.
No.
If you hurt her, asshole,
I will fucking kill you.
Please...
Oh, yeah. What's this for?
What are you allergic to?
For God sakes!
Fuck! Fuck!
Peanuts!
Peanuts, for God sakes! God!
Fuck!
Seriously, dude, was that so hard?
Why are you doing this?
You need to stop screaming.
Help!
Go ahead and scream.
Scream your head off.
We're miles away from where
anyone can hear you.
Hey, you know where that's from?
It's from a movie.
Help!
Jesus, bitch. Figure it out.
This gray shit everywhere
keeps the sound down here.
Okay, I'm bored.
Let's play a game.
Hey, I know you.
No, you don't.
- I do.
- No.
You don't.
Oh, God! No!
No!
Don't kill Elizabeth!
Fuck! Fuck you, bitch!
I'll fucking...
fucking kill you.
Oh, no.
Now I want you to watch this.
Oh, God!
Oh, God! Fuck!
Oh, fuck!
Wait, wait, wait.
Cut me, Mick. Cut me.
You know that one?
I guess a Clockwork quote
might be more appropriate right now.
Can you think of one?
Please, whatever
you're thinking of doing...
No. That's Misery.
I'm so sorry, Elizabeth.
I'm so sorry.
No...
"Pull off gray safety cap.
Insert flat tip on thigh. "
Oh, God.
Now, that got a little crazy.
Now, who the fuck could that be?
I'm sorry. I work here.
Are you okay?
I don't understand.
You're fired.
I'm beat.
...notorious inmate Shawn Gracey
is still on the loose.
Gracey escaped
from this institution three days ago
and is still believed to be in the city.
If you have any info...
I gotta give it to you.
You're pretty resilient.
How much more you got in you?
Enough.
Good.
No!
So you're having a party.
What time are the boys getting here?
I don't know what you're talking about.
What girl doesn't love a party?
Hello.
- Hi.
- Hey, worker bee.
Just letting you know I'll be out back.
Yeah, okay.
You sure it's an assistant gig
and not some slave racket?
No.
I'm happy to do it.
He say when he's gonna be back?
No.
Mike's coming over after work.
That's all I know.
Well, I pretty much did the inside.
I mean, I wouldn't
open up any closets.
You don't want anything to come out
and bop you in the head.
Mike's bringing snacks.
Then the inside's done.
So I guess we have some time to kill.
You know,
I...
could give you a sneak peek.
He gave me the key
so I could finish some stuff up.
He's gonna be a while, right?
It's your band.
Yeah, but he's weird about...
letting...
Limited time offer.
Okay.
Let's make it quick.
I can't promise that.
Hey.
Slow down, buddy.
Whoa.
Crazy.
Welcome.
After you.
Why, thank you, ma'am.
I can't feel my legs.
What are you doing?
What are... Sam?
Don!
Don...
Seriously, dude,
couldn't think of anything better?
Heavens to Betsy.
I wasn't expecting such a bonfire.
You do know where
all this is going, don't you?
Why?
"Why"?
Because...
Well, doesn't matter anymore.
I'm not retarded, I just act a fool
Hey.
You must be the girl.
- I am.
- I'm Mike. How you doing?
Oh, hey. Nice to meet you.
I made some drinks.
Mind telling me if they're too strong?
I don't think that's possible.
Good. My kind of guy.
It smells in here. What is that smell?
I tried to make some "ors devores,"
but the blue Hawaiians look
like they turned out better.
You gonna join me?
Yeah. Yeah.
And in the yard, I saw Sam's car
out there, too. Where's he?
Next door feeding the cat.
But Don's on his way, so...
Nice. Looks like you've
had a few already.
Yes. Started early.
Here is to a night to remember.
And to drinking
with bow. Legged women.
- Bow. legged women.
- Right.
You know, I'm sorry we didn't have
more time to play.
Yeah.
Think I used too much?
Mike.
Oh, no.
No, no, no.
You never told me
if you liked my outfit.
I made it myself.
God grant me the strength...
To do what, Don?
Give you the strength
to get up and walk out of here?
Grant me the strength, God,
to kill this fucking bitch.
Yes, God,
give me strength.
I dare you.
Would you guys like some?
I'm good.
Having a good time?
Pretzels? Pretzels? No?
- Hey.
- How are you?
Have we met?
Oh, no. I don't think so.
Don hired me to help with the studio.
Right on. Nice to meet you.
- Good to meet you.
- Yeah.
You have a little red
on your neck there.
I was printing shirts for the boss.
- I'm a mess.
- Well, where are those guys?
- Smoking up inside.
- Of course.
I'm gonna go find them.
I cannot wait to hear the record.
Oh, God. No. Me, too.
I guess they don't really
call it a record, though, huh?
Anymore. What do they call it?
- You know what? I'm sorry...
- An album?
Album. They were sending me
out for an ice run.
- I got to run. I'll catch up with you later.
- Wait a minute.
Don't let them make you
do shit like that.
You know what? You're so sweet.
- It's my job.
- All right.
- It's all good.
Well, we'll talk about that
when you get back.
- Absolutely. Looking forward to it.
- Okay. All right.
- Okay.
- All right.
Hey, at least they caught
that asshole, right?
Now you don't have to worry
about getting killed in the streets.
The... Who... What...
The guy on TV.
The Shawn Gracey guy
who escaped from prison.
They caught him.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah.
Great.
That's a good thing, then.
- Yeah.
- Okay.
- Anyway...
- Yeah.
- Well, we'll talk.
- Bye. Nice to meet you.
- Have fun at the party.
- All right.
Hey! Hey!
No, no, no, no, no.
Don't pee. No, no.
Guys? Guys?
Hello?
Can't fucking see.
I can't fucking see anything!