I got you! You better run!
I got you now!
Come on!
Gillian!
What? What?
Do it again!
...a whole lots of money
I don't need
A big, fine car
I got everything
that a man could want
I got more
Than I could ask for
Daddy, could you
turn it down a little?
I don't have to run around
I don't have to stay out all night
Ooh, when my baby
kisses me
Chills run up and down...
- Daddy, can we just turn it down?
- When my baby...
Exactly!
I have been getting this all summer.
You have to stay on the island.
How many times are you gonna say that?
I've been back three days.
So I'm insecure.
You've spent the whole summer away.
School starts in two weeks.
I gotta know whether I should be
shopping around for a new best friend,
and Mr Wacko up there is your father.
- Hey!
- Here we go!
Son of a bitch!
Daddy!
You're in the wrong lane!
- Daddy, this really is not smart.
- I'm telling you, he's crazy!
- Would you pull over, please?
- What?
Hello! Hello, I'm over here!
I'd like to talk to you for a minute!
This is a two-way street.
What's the matter with you?
Pull over!
Daddy!
- You oughtta yield!
- What's your problem?
My problem is you didn't yield.
You saw the sign.
What does it say?
- In the car, now!
- I was ahead of you!
Ahead of me?
He said he was ahead of me!
You could get arrested!
What's wrong with you?
- That sign said yield!
- Just get in!
- You were not ahead of me!
- Get in the car!
I'm sorry. He's just...
Rachel!
- We're late for Esther and Paul.
- Sorry.
- You're right, he didn't yield.
- He didn't.
Come on.
Who's gonna be brave, huh?
Go ahead. Don't be shy.
Paul, come on, you gotta try this.
They say there's something spiritual
about feeding them in flight, but l...
I tried it.
One of them bit me in flight.
Don't believe them.
Stop. Come on.
- I already pulled a muscle.
- Come here.
Here. Here we go.
Here, birds.
- No dinner, no TV.
- See if they take it.
- Here you go.
- Oh, great. Thanks, Esther.
- You tell her yet?
- Hey, what scared the birds away?
It's the sound of your voice, Esther.
Are they skittish or intuitive?
- Tell me what?
- The complete truth.
He was supposed to fill you in
as soon as we left port,
but obviously he hasn't.
Those birds are rabid.
What? What?
What complete truth?
Well, you know, David's wife...
it happened, uh...
- With the boating accident.
- Right.
Gillian, where you goin'?
Esther, would you please
translate for me?
She never listens to me.
Come on, Gillian, not funny.
Get down.
Gillian, come on.
It's my birthday!
Let me have some fun!
It's your 35th birthday.
Grownups shouldn't be having fun!
Tell your mother
grownups don't scale things.
Grownups don't scale things!
Tell your father he's not my father!
He's supposed to be
my fun-loving husband!
This is incredible!
Mommy, please!
Paul, could you get her down?
Sure. As soon as
I unclench my fingers.
Mom!
I'm almost there!
Mom, you're scaring me!
This is so great!
You can come down now!
Rachel, try again.
She'll listen to you.
Mom!
Mommy!
Gillian!
Mom!
Daddy?
What?
What are you looking at?
Oh... nothing.
Nothing.
Hey! Hey, the ferry's here!
See it, David?
Oh, great.
David?
He asked me to call him that.
I'm 16, Rachel.
Give it up a little.
Tomorrow is her birthday?
So this is two years to the very day?
We didn't even think of it
until three days ago,
and then we were afraid
that you might back out.
You are fixing me up with a man
on the anniversary of his wife's death,
which also happens to be her birthday.
I absolutely would have backed out.
- She's upset now.
- Thank you.
What do you expect?
I mean...
how could he have agreed to this,
for God's sake?
- Well...
- Oh, my God.
'Oh, my God' what?
You mean there's more?
He doesn't exactly
know that you're coming.
Air.
He doesn't know I'm coming?
He does in a way, because
we're always trying to fix him up.
He doesn't know we are bringing
someone on this particular trip,
but I'm sure that we'll all
laugh about it over dinner.
It's okay.
Don't worry, it'll be fine.
We're already having fun.
This is great.
Easy, now. Here it comes,
straight down.
There you go. There we go.
- I see them. There they are.
- Hey, Paul!
Hey!
Aunt Esther! Hi!
Hi!
Hey! You look great!
Oh, sweetie!
Oh, look at you!
Three days away from me,
already you look different.
No, I don't.
Hey, Muscles.
Hey, Mr Cerebellum.
New toup?
Nah, it's the old toup.
- Hi, sweetie.
- Hi.
If we hustle, we can beat the traffic.
Is this all the luggage?
Hi.
Hi?
What do you mean, hi?
Who are you?
I'm leaving, that's who.
No, no, no, no.
David, meet Kevin Danford,
business associate.
She designs all our software,
and she decided
to join us for the weekend.
Under extremely false pretences.
Kevin took one of your literature classes
at B.U. For one day, years ago.
- Talk about a small world, right?
- Years ago. Well.
Next, Woods Hole,
Martha's Vineyard, and Nantucket...
Well, let's go.
Let's... let's go.
... departing in 45 minutes.
You knew.
I knew it was somebody
named Kevin.
I figured a fishing buddy.
- Paul doesn't fish.
- I thought maybe he started.
You think that's funny.
Just let me take the next boat back.
No, you're walking the wrong way.
This is going to be
a fabulous weekend.
You might think I enjoy carrying
the luggage, but you would be wrong.
I can't be both a bellboy
and a mediator.
We have a situation.
Did I tell you about this air,
or did I tell you?
I have been smelling.
You bottle it, you could take it home
and sell it, it's that good.
Come on, breathe deep.
In good stuff, out shit.
Come on.
In good, out shit.
Come on, Cindy!
In good...
Okay, all packed up, let's go.
Cool it.
And drive normal.
All right, Kevin, you sit in the front.
Could I just talk to you
for one second?
I can't get in the car
if you're leading me...
We have the potential
for a colossal disaster.
They're both alone,
so we arranged. End of story.
Look happy.
They're watching.
- Hello! Hi!
- Let's make the most of it.
- You're a negative person.
- That's another thing.
Don't trot out
your psychology platitudes.
Your training is in architecture.
These headshrinking seminars,
they're part of your midlife crisis,
and I hear you don't even
contribute to the class.
Who said?
- I've heard.
- Who said?
Come on!
You're holding up the fun.
Let's go.
Kevin, you get in the front seat.
Isn't this an amazing old car?
At least smile.
To reveal that you have teeth
might keep them distracted.
I am writing that one down.
This could get bumpy.
Everybody in?
Hey, slow down!
How about that ocean air?
He almost never crashes.
Bottle it, take it home,
and sell it, that's what I say.
What are you doing?
I was just noticing you've had
quite a developmental year.
You're gross.
Here we are. Everybody
gets to pick their own room.
First come, first served.
- I wrenched my back.
- That air!
- Smell that island air!
- Enough with the air!
Could I speak with you
a moment alone, please?
- Sure.
- Excellent.
Oh, yeah. Hey, I gotta pee.
- I'd like to hear this.
- Forget it, Cindy. Let's go.
Hey, you know, you may want to...
Paul and Esther,
they will grab the best room.
Look, I am very sorry.
I had no idea that this was
the anniversary of your wife's...
Oh, don't, please.
And I had no idea that you
knew nothing about my coming.
I'm quite prepared to leave.
I don't know how they could
possibly think that this...
You're here.
Tomorrow we've got a big sand castle
competition at Jetties Beach.
I'm excellent at castles.
I do the whole bit...
pillars, balconies, columns.
Moats?
What have they been telling you?
They're acting friendly.
Come on, he was angry.
This is your most gigantic goof ever.
It's for his own good.
It's unhealthy, all this seclusion.
- It was his wife.
- She was my sister.
- Life goes on.
- Again with the psychology.
If he refuses to recognise that,
maybe we should have
Rachel live with us.
She only gets to be 16 once.
- She'll never get this year back.
- We are here to enjoy a restful weekend.
She's got college, SATs,
not to mention socially.
Must you always be
your complete and total self?
What?
That's two.
I'm writing down two.
- Didn't I tell you?
- No, no, no, no.
No way.
You are not wearing that.
We both are.
I got one for you too.
Oh, my God,
look at your breasts!
Wonder Top. Cleavage.
I'm not going out like that.
I'm not gonna do it.
At some point in your life,
you are going to have to trust me.
And this is that point? While you're
wearing electric blue rectal floss?
Your diaphragm covers more than that.
When we learn to deal with men,
we gotta practice on the boys,
and this is how we
tease them with the goods.
- Now, let's practice our walk.
- Our walk?
Oh, yes.
The walk is very key.
And it's all hips, like this.
Oh, my Lord.
I am not doing that.
No way am I doing that!
We gotta own the beach, Rache.
The walk is ownership.
- I don't want to walk.
- At least slow down.
- We're barely moving.
- You're 39, I'm 42.
I only have sex by appointment.
Even then, it's with Esther.
Why do you do that,
all the putdowns?
- We don't really mean it.
- It gets boring.
Being caustic pre-empts kindness,
which is important since kindness
could lead to more sex,
and it is exactly how you picture it.
- Let's stop.
- What's the matter?
Don't you think it's insensitive,
fixing me up on her birthday?
Gillian has no more birthdays, David.
I'll bear that in mind.
- It's not natural for a man...
- Nature's the goal?
Most mammals mate for life.
For life! That's nature.
Some species, the surviving mate
remains faithful and monogamous
even after the mate has died.
Let me renew
your subscription to Nova.
I don't have to stand for this.
I can outrun you.
Oh, yeah?
He goes out there every night.
- Thursday, he was out all night.
- Doing what?
Staring at the ocean, I guess.
Is it, like, a sickness?
In your psychology classes,
do they have a name for this?
Oh, yes. It's...
he's nuts.
He will be all right. It's just...
He really loved her.
He's not the only one.
I know.
- Hey.
You're probably beginning to notice,
I never leave.
Why is that?
I live next door. My parents are away.
I'm orphaned here for the weekend.
You know about this weekend?
Oh, yes. It's, um...
an anniversary.
Not just that.
It's the anniversary.
Dress-up dinner,
castle-building, karaoke.
Gillian started it.
You know, they choose stupid songs
you'd never admit to liking.
- They what?
- A lot of Barry Manilow.
Weekend tradition.
This is the Gillian weekend.
You've got a cute way of talkin'
You got the better of me
Just snap your fingers
and I'm walkin'
- Like a dog hangin' on a leash
- What, are you kidding?
- This is your song?
- Yeah, so?
You're supposed to choose
songs you're ashamed of.
This is a classic!
I love this song!
You make me feel like dancin'
I want to dance the night away
- Come on, let's go again.
- No, I don't really wanna.
- Oh, you look fabulous.
- I know.
Might want to lose the gum.
Or not.
He's not gonna fall for you.
Live people
can't compete with dead ones.
Ask anybody.
Thank you.
I don't think so!
I feel like dancin'
Dancin'
Dance the night away
I feel like dancin'
Dancin'
I'm sorry, we were, uh,
we were just practicing for karaoke.
Sorry to intrude. I heard the sound,
couldn't quite believe it.
We're sorry.
Me too. You know what?
I miss Esther.
Sugarplum?
I think there's a plan
to give us private time.
The plan is to get me over Gillian.
It's been two years.
I'm not over her.
I see.
You can relax,
'cause if it makes you feel any better,
you're not my type.
Thank you.
Well... we'll see you at dinner.
Dinner, yes.
- Not too much.
- First off...
...I would like to toast us all
for looking so fantastic.
- Absolutely.
- Especially me.
It took me an hour to get into this dress.
And ten seconds for me to imagine
you out of it, Miss Teen Succulent.
- All right, glasses up.
- Sorry.
- To all of us.
- Cheers.
Ching ching.
Okay, I'm hungry. Let's eat.
Rachel said you have a baby.
You have a baby?
Yes, I have a little boy.
He's 3 years old.
And why I'm not back home with him
right now completely escapes me.
If you don't mind my being
a nosy little bug,
what happened to the father?
I mean, I know you're divorced.
He cheated on her, bad.
Rachel said.
Yes, my husband is out of the picture.
I have complete custody.
Completely out of the picture, David.
Did you hear that?
That's good news.
So, how come you don't have children?
Do you shoot blanks?
That's a personal question, Cindy.
I mean, if you really want to know...
Can I tell her?
You might as well.
We were afraid that
they'd turn out like you.
You are such a child.
Who's helping me
with the castle tomorrow?
We've got to be on the beach
by 7 a.m. Judging's at 2.00.
7 a.m.? I thought we were going
to the cemetery tomorrow.
No time.
We've got to start early.
I want to beat Megan Weeks.
I've lost to her three years running.
She's ungracious, arrogant,
and this year, she's gonna gag
on the taste of unmitigated defeat.
She's 9.
This is my entry tomorrow.
As you can see,
I'm gonna need some help.
Here's an aerial view.
Could you get the end of this?
What?
You have blueprints?
Sure. This takes organisation.
Look at these columns.
They're Corinthian.
How long did it take you to do that?
Esther.
I don't know. Does it matter?
- Does it matter?
- Pumpkin.
You're a professor of literature.
You spend your time
meeting with sand engineers?
We build castles every year.
Not with forklifts. You'll need permits
for that kind of construction.
What's the problem, Esther?
Honeybuns.
Sweetcakes.
I'd like to know the problem.
No problem.
- I want to know the problem.
- You want to know the problem?
Let me see if I can
locate the problem for you.
You're living on an island,
a practically deserted island in winter.
You're doing nothing.
I'm writing a book.
What have you written?
Let me see.
I'm the only one who gets to read it.
Everyone else has to wait.
You're protecting him.
I'm not protecting him.
Don't be reading my mind, Esther!
Can't we once eat without having
a free-for-all? I can't stand it!
Butt your nose right in.
Stick it in snug.
Can we just regroup?
We've got a terrific soup here.
Come on in! Wreck my life!
It's only mine!
It's been two years!
- Hey!
- Two years!
Listen to yourselves.
Can't we once not do this, one time?
Maybe you're not happy.
I don't know.
Or care.
But whether or not you're happy,
do you have to spoil our dinner?
My concern is for Rachel.
My unhappiness...
Honey. Sugar.
Stop calling me food.
This is not a stable home.
She's living with a single parent
who's an unemployed recluse
who does nothing but plan
Corinthian sand columns.
You can talk to me about a lot of things,
but parenting isn't one of them.
You don't know the first thing
about being a parent.
Maybe it's time that I found out.
Maybe Rachel should come
and live with us full-time.
Rachel.
Do you want to live
with Esther and Paul?
No.
Well, there you go.
End of issue.
You're not the first person
to lose someone you love.
This isn't original.
I'm going for a walk.
Well, they brought somebody.
A woman. Living.
Dead jokes. Funny.
They're all ganging up, Gilles,
sayin' it's time for me
to get over you and let you go.
You don't want me
to let you go, do you?
You can't ask me questions like that.
Why not?
'Cause you know my wants.
Or what I say I want
is really what you want me to want
'cause I'm here right now
only in your mind,
unless I'm real, which would mean
I'm kind of a ghost,
which I know
you don't want me to believe
'cause you hate the idea of being crazy.
- Why do you always do that?
- Do what?
Fire back in rambling sentences
with compound thoughts to confuse me.
- I don't do that.
- You do.
No, what you do is, you ask questions
you don't really want me to answer.
Whether I want to or not is moot
because you always dodge.
You did it alive, you do it dead.
Are you seriously gonna try
to outtalk me?
How's Rachel?
She's good, I think.
She seemed to have a good summer
with Paul and Esther.
The one rule we had
was she comes first.
We even stuck to that one.
- I know.
- She needs you to be there.
Especially this weekend.
I know that too.
You're okay, Mr Man.
I miss you.
You're okay.
I gotta run.
Get back here!
Go play with the live girl!
Gillian!
Come on!
Hey, kiddo.
I heard you yelling.
Were you yelling at someone?
Just myself.
- You talk to her, don't you?
- What?
Mommy.
You talk to her out here.
Oh, well, I talk to her all the time,
in my prayers.
You talk to her like she's
right in front of you out here.
No, that's...
Well, sometimes
I fantasise about stuff.
What's with this book
that you're writing?
Well, you know, it's, uh...
you know, it's...
You know.
- A lie?
- Well, yeah.
Is everything okay?
We haven't really talked much
since you've been back.
Yeah, it was kind of hectic
those three days,
what with just the two of us.
Do I tell you I love you enough?
You know, I read these studies.
With teenagers, you're not supposed
to say it too much.
They won't hear it after a while.
If you say it too little,
that can cause harm too.
Do I say it too much?
Too little? I...
I don't know.
You say it the right amount.
Come back and make me your wife'
And as he started to go
She said,
'Billy, keep your head low
'Billy, don't be a hero
Come back to me'
Paul, take it outside.
- As far away as possible, okay?
- Okay, okay, I'm finished.
- Hi, baby.
- Hi.
Next time you're gonna
have to pay for this.
- You out talking to him?
- Yeah.
How is he?
He's fine.
He cooled off a little bit.
He's fine now.
What'd you talk about?
Esther, he's fine, okay?
Maybe you do butt in a little too much.
Well, I'm sorry, but sometimes
I get scared for him,
and I get scared for you too.
You can always tell me
to butt out, you know.
Yeah.
Just don't worry, okay?
You don't have to worry.
What?
You tell me not to worry, but...
am I wrong to worry?
I'm tired. I'm gonna go to bed.
Good night.
Why can't you sleep?
How did you know I wasn't sleeping?
When two people are together
long enough, they sense things.
Plus which, you snore like an elk.
I have a court appointment
Monday morning.
What do you mean
you have a court appointment?
Rachel shouldn't be
living in this situation.
You're going to a court of law?
No, it's a tennis court.
I'm gonna play doubles.
What are you thinking?
She went from an A student
to C's and D's.
- Her mother died!
- No.
She still had A's the year after.
It was the second year
she started to bottom out.
It's not Gillian. It's him.
Her guidance counsellor,
whom David doesn't even talk to,
by the way, says that she's
retreating more and more.
She's been laughing and having fun
the last two months.
- With us, but look at her here.
- She doesn't want to leave him.
Of course not. Of course
she doesn't want to hurt her father.
But she's the one who's getting hurt.
He's done nothing to cause any judge
anywhere to take away his daughter.
- So we're supposed to wait?
- It's not your business.
- She's my sister's daughter.
- He's her father.
You're not her mother, you're an aunt,
an aunt who might want to be more,
but still just an aunt.
You want to write that down? Fine.
Maybe that way you'll remember it.
Don't do this, Esther.
Don't do this.
I don't want to do it.
Let's just...
Let's just see how the weekend goes.
I got some more shovels.
You know, now I see
why David had the blueprints.
- This is serious.
- Very.
They even come
from the Vineyard for this.
Now, this is Megan Weeks,
last year's winner.
Gee, Megan, what a lovely entry.
I was thinking of adding another victim.
Charming.
Oh, my God!
You madman!
Oh, tread softly, sweet maidens,
tread softly.
Wow!
Esther, kiss the king!
Oh, I take it all back.
This is amazing.
I take it all back. You're a genius.
Thank you.
Hey, what about me? I helped.
You want credit? Last night I'm nuts,
now you want credit?
I provided moral support.
Hey.
This is really cool.
You may breastfeed the king.
And should there be any leftovers...
What?
We got 'em, see? They're looking.
Who's looking?
Boys. Men. Ignore 'em.
More hip.
God, this thing is killing me.
My breasts hurt.
Just own the beach, Rachel.
Can you do that?
Walk cool. Own the beach.
Hi.
The judging is over. You're free.
- Oh, thank God.
- Arise, arise, my liege.
Gimme your hand.
They'll announce in 10 minutes.
- You okay?
- Let me get you a towel.
- Hang on.
- Too much sun, maybe.
Plus being buried.
- I'm a little light-headed.
- Sure.
You know, maybe it's just
thrill of the competition, huh?
Excuse me.
What are you lookin' at?
An act of God. Two acts.
- Turn around, you sweet things.
- Look at that.
Junior Mints.
Oops.
Rachel! Rachel!
- Hi, Daddy.
- Never mind 'Hi, Daddy'.
- You're practically naked!
- What are you doing?
- I'm making you decent.
- I'm wearing a bathing suit.
Go away.
Please leave the premises. You!
Hi.
Put that towel on!
Put that on!
We're on a beach!
Cindy, it's okay.
You're perfect, I want you to know that.
Don't you look at me.
- You're being ridiculous.
- What got into you?
Dad, what's the matter?
Dad, what?
Gillian?
Dad?
Gillian!
Daddy! Daddy!
Wake up. Come on.
Come on, hey, wake up.
Open your eyes. Come on.
Come on. There you go.
You thought you saw Gillian.
- Daddy, are you all right?
- Yeah.
- He's okay.
- I'm fine.
Too much sun. He'll be fine.
You won.
Hey! You won, you won!
Can we just have a little room?
Back up. Give him some air.
Megan Weeks is crushed.
Her life is ruined.
Come on, Rache, he's fine.
He's not fine.
He thought he saw her.
Maybe it was your bathing suit
that made him faint.
Speaking of which,
this is cutting off circulation.
It's lucky I don't pass out.
He screamed her name.
- Hey.
- Hi.
There's this party tonight.
Supposed to be good.
Wanna go?
With you?
Yeah.
Okay, sure.
I'll get somebody for you if you want.
I know how to snap my finger,
thank you very much.
I'll pick you up.
8.30.
Great.
- I have a date!
- Yeah, I see.
Tonight!
I caught that too.
So, what's with the meditation?
I have a date.
Dates scare me.
Yeah, me too.
You must have been nervous
getting off that ferry.
L-it was probably more terrifying
getting on the ferry.
By the time it docked, I'd...
Well, I-I wasn't nervous.
Why?
I don't know, really.
This might surprise you,
but I was hoping you and my father...
You don't even know me.
Well, you seem to be on this planet.
You're gonna scare the fish.
I'm sure what you're doing
puts them at ease.
- Feeling better?
- Much.
Great.
David, we got a problem.
Esther's worried
about Rachel living with you.
How many times
are we gonna play that record?
It's gone beyond talk now.
She's got an appointment
with ajudge on Monday,
and I think she might
move for custody or something.
What?
I didn't know this was coming,
I swear it.
She's going to court?
She doesn't want to,
and I'm sure it won't come to that.
I am telling you so you can
help yourself the rest of the weekend.
You've got to act normal...
you know, use a napkin at dinner,
try to breathe between sentences.
If you see Gillian again, wave subtle.
David, this is dangerous and illegal.
It's also very upsetting to me.
I have a problem with high speed.
The speed concerns me. Please.
Then shut your eyes.
I told you what I told you in confidence.
I hope you're not gonna barge in there...
Esther's planning to take my kid
and I'm supposed to keep my mouth shut.
Broach it to her naturally
so she doesn't know I ratted on her.
'How are you? Nice dress.
Make any court dates? '
Shut up!
That was very helpful.
Slow down, please.
Watch it! Jesus!
Just let me out of the car
right here. This is fine.
And you keep going into the trees.
Esther, a moment of your time, please.
What's wrong?
I need a moment.
Can I have a moment?
Certainly.
Excuse me.
You come here under the guise
of a vacation weekend,
and you have...
you plan to see ajudge!
- Calm down.
- It's like what?
You're punishing me for hurting too much.
I shouldn't hurt anymore.
The statute of limitations has run out!
- Let me tell you why I feel...
- Does Rachel know?
No. She would never choose to leave you.
I'm doing it in her best interests.
Rip her from her father!
That's her best fucking interest!
Do you want an adult conversation,
or see how many times you can swear?
Fuck you. How many's that?
I was on that boat too.
You have no priority on this.
- My priority is my daughter.
- Then make her one!
I want you to get out of the house!
I'm sick of you barging into my life.
If I hadn't barged in,
you wouldn't have a life, David!
I'm the one who found you, remember?
I'm the one who barged in
after you gobbled all the sleeping pills.
Let's not forget that little trivia.
Took me a long time to like you, David.
It's taken me even longer to care,
but I do care now.
If you want to throw your life
down the toilet,
I will cry for you
whether you believe it or not.
But if you think that I would let you
take Rachel down with you...
then you don't know who I am.
You have never made
the slightest effort to know who I am.
- Hi.
- Ready?
- All set.
- See you later, Daddy. Bye.
- Where you goin'?
Oh, I-I have a date.
Didn't I tell you?
I-I thought I did. Funny.
Daddy, you remember Joey.
Joey, my father. Daddy, Joey.
- All right. Bye.
- Wait. You're going out with him?
Yeah, we won't be too late.
See you.
Hold it.
- Do you take drugs?
- No.
How many holes do you have
in your ears?
- Six.
- Nose?
Three. Four.
'Night! 'Night!
'Night, 'night, 'night.
I'm gonna skip dinner.
Take a walk.
Remember the meteor shower?
A certain daughter was conceived
under those stars.
I thought I saw you on the beach today.
It wasn't you, was it?
No.
I must have been hallucinating.
It was different from the way
I see you here.
Who knows? Maybe they're right.
I am sitting on a rock, talking to a ghost.
I could go.
No.
I think I am in trouble.
A little.
Why?
I think maybe I'm sick.
I pretend I'm okay.
Am I sick?
I always hated good dreams.
I-I couldn't take
the disappointment of waking up.
And then I figured out a way to know
whether or not I was dreaming.
What are you talking about?
I realised that in most of my dreams
I'd ask myself, 'Am I dreaming? '
I'd never ask that when I was awake.
So I finally figured it out.
If I ever wondered,
is this a dream or not,
then I knew it was.
You ever wonder?
Don't leave.
I'm not leaving.
Joey!
- Hey, hey, Joey.
- Danny.
Rachel.
- Hi.
Have some punch.
It's a vintage batch I made myself.
- Yuck.
- It's a zombie.
What's in a zombie?
Rum and stuff. It's good.
I'll get some more.
Would you try talking to him?
You could be an objective voice.
It seems no matter what I say, he just...
Maybe if you weren't so shy about it.
This isn't something I want to do.
Then don't.
A man shouldn't lose his daughter
for taking long walks on the beach.
- It isn't just that.
- Then what is it?
Is there something else
you're not telling me?
No.
Then I don't see his crime.
His wife is dead, and he doesn't
want to let her go.
My husband let me go
while I was still living.
I'd prefer to think he was crazy.
If you could just talk to him.
And I hope you can hear
What the words
and the music have to say
It's so hard to explain
Everything that I'm feeling
Face-to-face,
I just seem to go dry
But I love you so much
That the sound...
You know, I-I didn't get a chance
to sing my encore, so...
Where is everybody?
Well, uh, Rachel went out on a date.
David ran away from home.
Kevin and Esther went looking for him.
So that leaves just you, me,
and the moonlight.
Come on, let me inspect you
for tonsillitis.
Have you been pathetic your entire life?
Uh, not yet.
Come on, don't look at me like that.
You enjoy this banter.
The bathing suits, the outfits,
the hormone 'I am woman' strut.
But don't worry, you're safe.
I'm married to Esther.
No, no, I'm safe, 'cause men like you
never do anything except sit on porches
and watch things and say things,
but never do things.
You think so, huh?
You wanna kiss me?
I beg your pardon?
We've been doing this flirting thing,
and you've been
staring at me since you got here.
You were practically drooling at the beach.
I'm sure you must have thought...
what it would be like.
Maybe we should just see.
Maybe you should just...
I don't know...
touch me a little.
Take a chance.
Nobody has to know.
See?
Men like you just sit on porches.
They don't do anything.
Hello.
Nice night.
Does my apologising for all this
have any effect?
None.
You think I'm a loon.
Yep.
Anything else?
No, that's it. 'Loon' sums it up.
You've got an opinion.
I'm a big boy.
She was beautiful, exotic,
and she died young.
And you've maybe romanticised her
into something mythical,
into something she wasn't.
I was with her for 18 years.
There's nothing illusory about my memory.
Just a theory.
He went out alone
on the beach again tonight.
If life were like a big truck...
what would be worse...
to get run over by it,
or for it to just pass you by?
Like from the side of the road,
just, it passes you by.
What?
A truck, Esther.
If life were like a goddamn truck,
better to get run over or passed over?
You're standing by the side of the road?
Yeah.
Do I get to drive the truck?
It's a big joke, right?
Just forget it, all right?
Forget it. Forget it.
It's fine, really.
If life were like a truck.
- Hey, easy.
- I'm fine.
I probably shouldn't have
had that second punch.
And they were big cups too.
They were, like...
I bet they were, like, 16-ounce cups.
- They were big.
- They were huge!
Which means I had, like,
a quart of zombie, and that's a lot,
because I've never really
drunk alcohol before.
I probably shouldn't admit that.
Drink a lot of water and eat some bread.
You'll feel less sick tomorrow.
Thanks.
- I had a good time.
- Me too.
Maybe we can
go to a movie or something.
- Now?
- Some other night.
Oh, that'd be great.
I mean, that'd be really, really great.
Oh, I-I'm sorry.
I am... so dizzy right now.
It's okay.
That was my first kiss ever
using my tongue!
I probably shouldn't admit that.
Oh! Oh, Daddy, hi.
Oh, I am so sorry.
L-l... That's so unlike me.
- Are you drunk?
- Oh...
- You're drunk.
- I just...
You're drunk. She's drunk!
The cups were bigger than they looked.
They were big cups.
Say goodbye to Joey forever.
Goodbye. Goodbye forever,
Joey. Call me!
Call me, okay?
I said I was sorry.
Get up to your room.
Stay out of this, Esther.
And then what? You're gonna
come up and talk to me?
- Or are you gonna go and talk to her?
- Who?
Do you know he talks to my mother?
Every night he goes out there,
he has conversations!
My mother appears,
and he swims with her,
and they probably even kiss.
You were out there again tonight,
weren't you, Daddy?
You were out
in the water with Mommy.
Weren't you?
I asked you to go upstairs.
- What did she say?
- Oh, she's drunk.
Does Gillian appear to you
out there on the beach?
Yes, she does.
You swim with her?
Yes.
Is she naked?
It's all pretend.
I know it's pretend.
You go out on the beach,
and you have imaginary
conversations with Gillian?
- People talk to the dead all the time.
- But the dead don't talk back.
David...
you're ill.
People dream. It's normal.
People dream. They fantasise.
You screamed at her today.
What kind of a daydream is that?
That was sunstroke.
David, don't you see what you're doing?
You're trying to deny she's gone.
That's why you won't go to the cemetery.
I don't like cemeteries.
You're carrying on an active
relationship with your dead wife!
There's no rule saying
that love has to die too!
Oh, that's such poetic bullshit.
Love is a feeling, Esther.
And if I feel it, it exists, it's real.
Grief is a feeling too.
I'm not grieving. I'm happy!
When I go out to the beach
at night, God, I feel better.
I look forward to seeing Gillian.
It makes me happy.
It... it... it makes me
happy, happy, happy.
Well, I'm happy for you,
Mr Happy Happy Happy,
but it's not normal to be spending
nights with your deceased wife.
You can't apply normal to me.
Should I give up the happiness
I've found for normalcy?
David, you can't
keep living in a fantasy.
Yes, it's a fantasy!
It's a fantasy!
How many normal married people
while making love to their spouse
pretend they're with somebody else?
That's a fantasy.
I have an emotional fantasy.
Why should I apologise for it?
Fine, just tell it proudly to the judge.
How dare you do this thing?
She's my daughter.
He's always running off.
Your goddamn sister
and my best friend Paul.
How can they do this?
Where's Rachel?
They don't know my life.
They don't know it.
They don't know!
I think they're upset now
because they do.
Maybe you shouldn't have
told them you talk to me.
Oh, I'm not insane!
I don't go to restaurants
and order for two.
When I go to the movies,
I buy one ticket.
- One ticket.
- I didn't create all this.
I'm just trying to survive it.
I'm just trying to survive!
I didn't climb the goddamn mast.
I didn't do that!
- I'm to blame.
- Maybe you are. You were selfish.
- You didn't think.
- I was stupid.
You're being selfish.
I screamed at you to get down.
I begged you to get down!
And who's up there now?
Who's the next to fall?
I'm not helping you this way.
I'm not.
Maybe I should go.
No! Don't, don't go.
I think...
I think it has to be soon.
But not tonight, not tonight.
I don't want to go.
Do you think I want to be gone?
I don't want to be gone.
Well, maybe if I go back to Boston,
you could be there.
They've offered me my teaching job back.
When I come home at night,
you could be there like you are here.
I don't know.
I can't let go.
Not yet, I can't.
I can't.
Okay.
I stop this,
then you're gone... forever.
- I'm not ready.
- I know.
- Come on.
- What?
One night like it used to be.
- One night.
Let's get you dressed.
This is crazy!
Put your hands out like we used to.
I hold onto handlebars now.
- No hands!
- Mom.
I'm passing you.
All right.
Okay, here I come.
Here I come!
No chance.
You're old, Mom. Give it up.
Funny.
Who's passing who now?
You're not gonna pass me.
Mom?
Rachel!
What, what, what is it?
- Who? Who?
- Mommy. She was... she was here.
It was... it was a dream, sweetie.
It was a dream.
Mommy, she was here.
No, she was here.
It's okay, Rache. It's okay. It's okay.
It was just a dream.
It was a dream.
Mommy was here.
You saw Mommy in your dream.
- She was here.
- It's okay.
Mommy was here.
- You had some dream.
- I didn't dream.
- Mom was here.
Mommy was here.
You want some tea?
Yeah.
- Okay.
- Tea.
Hey, Cin?
Why don't you sit over here.
Yeah.
I'll go make us some tea.
You'll be okay.
It's okay.
There, yes, ohh.
There, sweetheart, shh.
I really think that you should go up there.
I'm makin' the tea.
I really think she needs you.
She had a nightmare about her mother.
That's right, it was a nightmare.
It was a nightmare... ow!
Whoa, whoa, whoa. It's okay.
It's all right. I got it.
It's okay? David? David?
Yes, it's okay. It's okay.
She had a nightmare.
But she's all right.
She's all right.
No, I'm not.
I think I should go live with them, Daddy.
I can't. I'm sorry.
I see you go out there...
and talk to her at night,
and I know you want to make her alive,
but she's not alive.
And I'm sure that
you never meant for me
to know you tried to kill yourself.
She didn't tell me.
She didn't have to.
But every time you go
to that beach, she's...
I didn't see.
I'm sorry.
I didn't know.
You'll always be my father.
But I have to go.
I have to let my mother be dead.
Rache, what am I gonna do?
I'm stuck here.
You're gonna come visit all the time.
Oh, great.
And I'll get to play with Paul.
Always late.
Boat's not gonna wait.
Did you ever consider that?
Did I consider that you yapping
doesn't speed me up?
Was he talking about you last night?
What?
People pretending they're making love
to somebody not their spouse.
- Do you do that?
- No, do you?
Never.
We used to make love all the time.
Now it seems to be, I don't know...
seasonal.
We're not in our 20s anymore.
Yeah.
How would you describe our marriage?
Uh, you know, I'd describe it as, uh...
you know, it's very nice.
We have a nice marriage, Esther.
A lot of people don't have that.
You know, they say the reason
most couples want to have children is...
because they sort of want
to celebrate the marriage.
Do you think that's why
we never wanted to have kids?
Because we didn't feel
that we had anything to celebrate?
What was that thing last night...
that life passing you by,
that big truck of life... what was that?
I was just, you know...
I love trucks.
Can we just once be honest?
Can we be truthful with each other?
We don't want to face the truth, Esther.
I mean, the truth is that
David goes out there
and gets giddy every night
splashing around with a ghost.
And we're both jealous,
'cause he has something
that we've never known.
That's the truth.
We don't want to face that.
Hey.
Every day I get up...
I go to work...
and I come home to you.
I may not jump into bed
all the time wanting sex, but...
I sure as hell need you to be there
for me to hold on to.
And if that's not, uh...
then God didn't make little
green apples, however that goes.
Where are my brown shoes here?
Four-minute warning!
That horn means we got four minutes.
Okay, let's go!
Look after him for me?
- I promise.
- Don't try to date him.
It's okay. I got this.
Get a move on. I don't want to
put up with you people another day.
- David.
- Yeah?
We'll take good care of her.
You can count on that.
I will.
I got these. No, I got it.
No problem. I got it.
I got this.
- It was very nice meeting you.
- Well, I'm so glad I came.
You're a very romantic man, Mr Lewis.
If you ever do come over to the mainland,
I'm gonna fix you up
with one of my friends.
You're makin' fun again.
Say goodbye to your daughter.
Such a horrible thing.
Young love nipped in the bud.
Okay, postcards are beautiful
and cheap to send. Say goodbye.
Joey lives in Belmont. He's a renter.
I'll see him in a couple weeks.
Oh, joy.
- I'll call.
- Okay. Bye.
So...
there's something that
needs to be said here.
I wish I knew what it was.
Me too.
These are the times I miss her the most,
'cause she'd always know what to say.
She was the centre.
Dad, you were the centre.
It was always you.
She was the one climbing masts.
And letting go of handlebars.
Well... boat's gonna leave.
I'm sorry.
I wish I could stay. I'm just...
No, no. This is right.
You're doing what's right.
You're doing what's...
what's the best.
We don't... even need
to say goodbye, really.
- No, no. More like, 'See ya'.
- Yeah. 'See ya'.
We'll be seeing each other,
visiting each other a lot.
A lot, a lot.
Say hi to her for me.
See ya.
We'll call as soon as we get back.
Right. Yeah.
Have a good trip.
I'm staying.
No, you're not.
You're going. And I'm going.
I can get my job back at B.U.
- You mean it?
- I mean it. I mean it!
I mean it.
You know, I just have to close up
the house and settle a few affairs.
- I'll be on the morning ferry.
- Okay.
And no more crying.
This is a good thing.
- I know, I know.
- It's a good thing.
The boat's gonna leave.
He's going back to work at B.U.
He's gonna come back!
What're you looking at me for?
Just find me a real estate broker.
And a good therapist.
Somebody with
a little more training than Esther.
Uh, done.
And maybe till you find a place,
you come and live with us.
If you promise not to sing.
Hi.
You made a shadow.
You must've been thinkin' about me.
You remember that rule we had...
Rachel comes first.
That was our rule.
- Your rule.
- Mm-hmm.
I picked you some flowers.
I'm gonna miss you, Mr Man.
Oh, I can't let you be real anymore, Gill.
I can't.
I know, I know.
I gotta go on for Rachel's sake.
And mine.
Does it have to be today?
Yeah.
Okay.
I love you forever.
Me too.
Goodbye.
Downloaded From www.AllSubs.org