"Put on the full armor of God, to be able to stand
Against the wiles of the Devil,
For our struggle is not against flesh and blood,
BUT AGAINST ... SPIRITUAL FORCES OF EVIL
IN HEAVENLY REGlÕES. "(Ephesians 6:11-12)
My name is Luke O'Brian.
Working as a salesman during the day.
At night, I attended the faculty of law Billy Simon,
in Sydney, Australia.
My goal in life has always been to become a lawyer,
until ...
The Devil in the dock santacruz [A More Passionate Fans of Brazil]: P
The Devil in the dock some tragedies have made me question my own existence.
Some tragedies have made me question my own existence.
I wonder why the Lord allows Satan to do so much.
This was the worst year of my life.
Today, the country was struck by another mass murder.
This time a gunman killed 15 people in a hospital and then killed himself.
This is unacceptable.
No, it's ridiculous.
As an account can disappear?
Some human garbage and you stole my money ...
What kind of idiots working there?
Luke, stop it!
Honey.
Honey, are you okay? Sorry.
I was brought back to reality.
The world is lost.
Another news says that the price of gasoline continues to rise
and the oil companies do not give explanations.
"My God!" Sean, who hadn't seen the phenomenon earlier, cried out.
you see how things are?
My mother was killed by a drunk driver, Gwen,
and that same driver is loose in the streets,
together with other outcasts, including those who stole our money.
If I had Satan in my hands right now,
I cut into small pieces.
And do the same with the damn that killed my mother!
I go to the college library.
Everyone needs compassion,
a love that never fails.
What mercy upon me.
Do not tell me that I left the bullets in the house!
Then something happened.
Suddenly, a Bible came in the glove compartment.
I would have so departed from God what he thought about killing a man?
Why could not forgive him?
Why?
How I became what I am now?
A man who hated people ...
instead of loving my neighbor.
Who am I?
Take me as I am,
all my fears and failures.
Complete my life again.
Upon returning home, I realized that the spiritual battle we all face.
Satan approaches you as a lion, brothers and sisters,
do not forget it.
The biggest lie is to convince you that it does not exist.
And I believe in the devil.
Suddenly I realized that.
All the world's problems
somehow relate to this evil being.
So many lies and deception.
And because of this serpent,
the world becomes increasingly worse.
Then I thought about making a daring thing.
If the world is turning into a hell, I can try to kill some demons.
That was the day I decided to expose him.
Yes, you heard me right. Exposing Satan.
And I can show the wiles of the devil better than anyone.
If all we do, I can process only one
who brought the world their worst pain.
Luke O'Brian against Satan?
- That's right.
Satan?
Yes, exactly.
He's last name?
PROCESSED
I had the address of Satan to send a copy of the process,
but I have walked the path to a hearing before a judge.
Luke O'Brian against Satan?
Yes, Your Honor.
Satan is processing?
"Crazy?
Order!
Yes, Your Honor.
Are you aware that is the international court of human rights?
Your Honor, Satan has violated all human rights know that!
- It is with a psychiatrist?
- No.
- Do you take any medicine?
-Yes.
No, I was taking.
Mr. O'Brian is wasting the court with this ridiculous process.
Your Honor, I can prove that Satan is a viable defendant.
Through the process "Dogar versus Marlboro"
and Section 10-3 of the processes of international civil liberties ...
Very well. I understand.
And of course, Satan did not respond to this quote.
I would like to bring a prosecution in absentia.
And how do you expect to make that statement?
I've had to put in the newspaper.
Do you still read these things?
Yes, and I think that may be accepted if necessary.
Try to meet him in hell next time. Just a hint.
I knew she would nullify the cause.
I just wanted to vent my frustration against Satan.
But what she said next took me by surprise.
You'll have to send a notification to the defendant in this case, Satan.
Through a bailiff. I give you another 30 days.
But I can not do that, Your Honor.
I can not allow trials in absentia unless the defendant is cited.
Next case!
"What's this?
- It is a case against Satan.
- Is this a joke?
- No, it is not.
If it works here, I want to hand it to him.
70 lawyers work here. Choose who you want.
I see.
Hey, man,
why do you think Satan works here?
Give it to him to find it, okay?
Hey, this is a serious company, okay?
Yes, we have strippers, drunks and gamblers, but you know what?
Do not allow smoking inside, you know?
You are Satan worshipers?
Could they deliver it to him if they find him?
Thank you."
I see that the process gave a law firm,
a strip club, an investment agency and an oil company.
Why stop there?
Tried to deliver a shopping used car?
If Satan is somewhere you can be there.
Yeah, I did not think about it, Your Honor.
Would you like a trial in absentia against Satan.
Trial in absentia?
Yes, Your Honor. I want it plowed ...
that the case against him is 8 trillion dollars.
I will undo this process for technical details,
and because you are crazy.
Then the most amazing thing happened.
I will also penalize Io, because ...
Why?
I am here, Your Honor.
Have you had this strange feeling that a fake can be real, anyway?
And who are you?
- Satan, Your Honor.
- Oh, Your Honor.
Very beautiful.
So you two are in this together?
I am here to respond to the citation, Your Honor.
And I will address the process of Mr. Luke O'Brien.
"What's this?
Very good.
you almost got me.
Made my day.
It's a trick question? Where are the cameras?
Sorry, but it is very serious, Your Honor.
For I am not amused at all.
Neither did I.
Can prove that it is Satan?
Can you prove that I am?
____What is happening here?
Oh, my God! It's so hot here! Bailiff?
Bailiff? Why does the heater is on?
What do you think?
Oh, my God! Bailiff!
What happened to the heater? Check it out.
Assuming that whoever says it is,
realize the extent of what you're saying?
The land is mine. And I'll defend myself.
You have legal representation?
If I have legal representation?
I know what they are thinking. No need to say.
That man would be even the devil?
I must say you have a lot of courage, boy. Sue me!
Do you really know what you're getting into?
You are not Satan himself, is it?
And you're not Luke's silly, is not stupid?
For it is good to get good lawyers, because I'll beat you.
You're just a moron. Do you know how insignificant?
After all, in an instant ...
I can send you a small boat into the deep red.
Hey, I have God on my side, okay? And He created you.
Have a card there?
- I have no card.
"No?"
Well, here's mine.
Call whenever you want.
Hey, do not aspire to smoke.
See you in court, kid.
Oh, I know. Nice sleight of hand.
I needed someone to help me. Someone you trust.
There was only one person I knew.
Disappear.
Please, Mel. Do not talk like that to a friend.
Friends do not invite friends to render Satan.
I really need your help on this, please.
Luke, I just graduated.
My first case is not a suit against Satan.
Find another sucker.
Mel!
Do you judge set the date for the trial next week
What surprised everyone in the courtroom, including me.
After that, I was called to give a million interviews,
which, of course, refused.
Honey, I.
They may call it crazy, but Luke O'Brien is suing the devil.
Do you judge was about to dismiss the case
until a man appeared claiming to be the devil.
It was another day in court in Sydney weird.
Are you sure you want to continue with this?
Yes, of course.
The devil is responsible for what the world is going.
You said it yourself.
Yes, but I told you to go to court to sue Io.
Why are you doing this, Luke?
Because the devil is real and I have to expose Io.
I have to expose Io.
Ladies and gentlemen, please.
Thank you for coming so quickly to an important event.
Now, without further ado, I present my client,
who prefers to be called "Prince."
Here it is, your dream team.
The best lawyers around the world ...
are in Sydney for this trial.
"Great!
Here, you, your dream team.
The best, the brightest, the smartest lawyers in the world.
And also the most expensive.
Mr. Ice, Oxford, his IQ is 214.
He helped bring down a law that tried to find a cure for cancer.
I'm not sure about cancer, after all ...
when people are dying of cancer, they think more of God, is not it?
Now, do not be so paranoid, Prince, because ...
God is also cursed, right?
Curse God. This is an intelligent response.
Well, I liked you.
Miss. Black, graduated from Yale.
The youngest and best lawyer in New York.
67 wins and no losses.
Helped defeat an electric car in court.
Your customers, oil.
What would you say if I offered you $ 100 million
and asked in exchange for his soul?
100 million for my soul?
Why pay?
Thank you. Good answer.
- I like this team.
- Nice to meet you, Prince.
Mr. Thinktank, Harvard-educated lawyer.
- Thinktank.
____How are you lady?
Helped defeat the rights of passengers.
Your customers are the airlines.
Aviation? I hate aviation.
But I love, however,
see people in those long lines, is not it?
Waiting for security, removing his shoes.
I love to watch it!
And charge for excess baggage. It was my initiative.
Did you? I love greed.
- Welcome to the team.
- Thank you, sir.
Very well. Ms. Shy.
University of Sydney. His name is famous.
She is a shark in the courtroom.
I knew that was not satisfied with their pay.
All work by many dollars.
And it very well. And there are many dollars to you?
Ten million in cash.
See how she is bold?
Sith, please.
Not interested in defeating Satan?
That way, no, I'm not.
Nobody is helping me in this case.
Also, think of all the publicity.
Will be in every newspaper.
You will have many customers then
he will not even know where to start.
Seriously, I need your help. Please.
Luke, and even if the man is Satan? Have you thought about it?
"Yeah...and so what?"
You know that God is on my side. On our side.
God is on our side.
God....
You know that God does not like for breakfast?
Of cereals and nuts. And you're crazy.
Mr. Innocent. Io will adore. She graduated from Columbia.
Represents all the casinos in Las Vegas.
Las Vegas? He plays here, my friend.
It's my town. I love Las Vegas.
All those players, those idiots who lose everything.
I love when they play in 16 and gives 5.
All those guys idiots. I love it!
They are so disappointed!
I helped defeat a ridiculous case against passive smoking in casinos.
They said that a casino one hour equals three months of secondhand smoke.
Oh, I know. And what happened?
As in my úItima poker game, I won, of course.
I will defeat Luke O'Brian, he will give me great joy.
The Lord will do this.
Seriously. And you will take action and do so.
Okay, Luke. If I agree to help you,
will you promise to the end, no matter what happens?
- Why not?
- Then promise.
I promise.
Okay. I agree. Let's move on.
Thank you very much.
Mr. Inyourface, the faculty of Stanford.
Oh, Stanford, very good.
I know it sounds very selfish, sir, but ...
I am the greatest, so do not worry about anything.
Great. That's not what Muhammad Ali said?
- Prof. Fields, University of New York.
- Hi, teacher!
It's a ridiculous process and we will win.
Very well. Ridiculous. Winning. That sounds good. Thank you.
And finally, Miss. Scarlett.
It represents the tobacco industry.
No need to say more.
It is an honor to represent Io, sir.
Most of what they say about you is not true.
What do you mean? What they say about me?
I'm always slandered by these believers idiots.
About how much you are bad. It is not true.
Not at all! I am much worse.
A quick question. Raise your hands those who believe in God.
Very well. Raise your hands those who love God.
Like it? Like it? Like it? No one.
I think Luke O'Brien is our enemy as you.
He does not like God. But that still does not know that.
Very well. As everyone knows, this trial will be seen around the world.
Needless to say, my client never loses.
Never.
And what we know about this Luke O'Brian?
No need to worry about Luke O'Brian. He is finished.
Well, we should not underestimate Io.
We will not. That's why you'll end up with him.
And then came the first day of trial.
The jury was selected in a random electronic process following a new law.
That was crazy.
We are in front of the International Court of Human Rights,
where Luke O'Brian should arrive.
Look. He is there!
Luke! Luke! Luke!
I have a serious question for you. You're an idiot?
No.
- Luke, can not be taking this case seriously.
- Of course I'm serious.
Do you really believe he is the devil?
The devil is alive and well.
Luke, Luke, why are you suing the devil?
He ruined my life, ruined the world.
He has to pay for it.
- And do you really think have a chance?
-Yes.
I really believe, at heart.
Satan! Satan! It has something to say?
I always have something to say.
- Are you really Satan?
- Of course. Want to dance with Satan?
Hopes that the public believes is Satan?
Expects the public to believe that you should ...
$ 12,000 on credit cards?
____How do you know?
- You can start paying.
If it is Satan, then prove it.
Well, check this out.
I think he was surprised.
I can only say that ...
the world is full of losers.
How many people will sue me and blame me
because they could not do what is right?
Got it? They are losers.
Mr. Luke O'Brien, are you listening?
Satan, just want to say that I'm your fan
I love you, I'm crazy about you.
- I love the group Kiss.
What?"
Kiss! Kiss!
I hate Kiss. I prefer Tom Jones.
YOU DECIDE THE VERDICT WITH BARRY POLK
It will be the trial of the century, will be seen by audiences around the world.
Welcome to the "You Decide the Verdict."
I'm Barry Polk, and are now with me ...
Tony "Light" Anzaldo,
and Jasmine Williams. Welcome.
Tony, let's start with you.
Do you think that Luke O'Brian has a chance against Satan?
No.
Very well. Jasmine?
I think the world is rooting for Luke O'Brian,
and we all hope he wins.
"I don't...
We talk to Mark Engstrom, who is on the subject there ...
Tony, you'll love this. London, England.
Mark?
Barry, all in England are fascinated with this case.
And the question we all ask is: Is it really Satan?
Mark, excuse me a moment. We go back now
because the trial about to begin.
Stand-up
You may be seated.
The court is in session.
Are you sure you want to take this forward?
- No.
- The jury was chosen by a process ...
Well, yes.
She's OK.
Since none of the parties accept an agreement,
go to trial.
And want it very quickly, get it?
Have transformed our court to the media circus.
Promoter, its preliminary statement.
- Promoter!
- Yes, Your Honor.
Ladies and gentlemen of the jury,
I feel a little inadequate, after all ...
I'm doing the devil himself.
but...
is very important to remember that the world is at stake here.
And that this being has been the cause of all suffering in the world.
Your Honor, I protest!
My client is not a being, a fallen angel.
Right. Carry on, Mr. O'Brian.
That evil fallen angel is the cause of pain and suffering of the whole human race.
Objection, Your Honor.
He is assuming facts not yet proven.
It assumes that Satan is evil.
Denied. Carry on, Mr. O'Brian.
Thank you, Your Honor.
Prove, with a preponderance of evidence,
he has caused all the problems and pains of this world.
And the verdict should be against him,
at 8 trillion dollars.
"GOD IS DEAD"
Order!
Satan! Satan! Satan!
Defense attorney, his preliminary statements.
The audacity,
was a tremendous audacity,
make you my friends, leave their jobs
trial for this nonsense.
It's unbelievable!"
- Objection!
Maintained. Defender, please, no personal attacks.
Sorry, Your Honor.
Assuming, just for argument, that my client is really Satan,
prove that this man is not responsible
the problems that man with society.
And it is disturbing and reprehensible
it processes this man who did him no harm.
I finished. We can start the trial.
Promoter, its first witness.
Pastor Matthews,
- Satan is real?
- Yes, it is.
The Bible literally tells us so.
The name of Satan is mentioned 47 times in Bible verses,
- And the devil ...
- Objection, Your Honor.
The Bible can not be admitted as evidence in court.
Your Honor,
the Bible is the historical source more reliable than any that exists.
You can leave. There is even fiction.
Continue, pastor.
Be magnanimous. Let him use it. We will win it.
Satan, when he tried to Jesus, called for three things:
The temptation of the flesh,
the temptation of the eyes,
and pride that exists in man.
And what is his mission?
He opposes all that is good,
and tries to destroy the work of Jesus Christ.
That's right.
Destroy the work of Jesus Christ.
No further questions, Your Honor.
What is it, Pastor?
It is an apple.
And if I said this is the apple
bit that Eve in the Garden of Eden?
- Believe  me ...
- No.
Why?
- Why the apple that Eve bit ...
was full of worms now.
Brilliant deduction.
And there sat our client is guilty of destroying this man's life because ...
The Scripture says that Satan is a roaring lion seeking who will devour.
It seems to me very guilty.
And this apple is not the Garden of Eden?
I understand your question. Of course not.
Of course.
No further questions, Your Honor.
We have high drama on the first day of this ...
international trial live from Sydney, Australia.
We welcome all who are watching us.
Tony, comments?
Of course, the lawyers of Satan are having fun today.
This boy, Luke, I am sorry for him because they do not know what to do,
and if not careful, they will eat lunch in Io.
Jasmine?
Let us not forget that mankind is at stake.
That is a struggle of good against evil.
Jasmine has understanding, okay?
Satan is being processed, right?
Satan is the one being attacked by this idiot
which is threatening to put Iowa in prison.
Please have a little sympathy.
We will return soon after.
Your Honor, I would call John Door of Petroleum Windmile to testify.
Objection, Your Honor! What is the relevance of the witness, may I ask?
Think man, think.
Oil company, Satan, evil!
- You are John Door, Windmile of Oil?
- Yes, I am.
- Why are oil prices so high, sir?
- It's too high?
I did not realize.
Did not you notice? Is it so stupid?
Your Honor!
Sorry. Sorry.
Promoter, no personal attacks. I clear?
Yes, Your Honor. Sorry. Slipped.
Your Honor, I want the record in the file
that this observation was not only unpleasant anti-Christian
as well as vile and evil.
- Was observed.
Thank you!
Continue."
What you and all the other losers should do
is to earn more money and stop complaining.
Why do not you reduce the price of gasoline?
Because of the money. We have to make a profit like everyone else.
Your Honor, what is the relevance of this interrogation?
Denied. Continue.
Money is a vicious cycle.
His company raises the price of oil by a few cents
and then says that it is not a monopoly.
After announcing that care about the environment
and that are not making money.
Only this year you earned $ 50 billion!
Money and greed, is not it?
Protest! Argumentative!
- Forged!
- Ambiguous.
What is the purpose, Mr. O'Brian, this questioning?
The purpose? Show the love of money
it is the root of all evil.
- Protest again!
- Sustained.
Promoter, enough personal attacks. You understand me?
Yes, Your Honor. Sorry.
Mr. Door, believe in God?
No.
Thank you."
Let's take a short recess.
Wow...
Tony, it seems that Luke O'Brien came on a roll this afternoon.
This guy amazes me. At a time is an idiot, and the following is a genius.
That's right. I've just been informed that they are following us on ...
more than 20 countries that broadcast this event around the world.
Even in Pakistan, Hungary, Chile, Bolivia, Iraq,
and believe it or not, Jasmine, in North Korea.
It is. This tells me that there is much at stake in this trial,
and my prayers are with Luke O'Brian.
And he will need much prayer.
We came back after the break.
This was a dirty trick,
cheap, rotten, Mr. O'Brian, and you know it.
My client has nothing to do with the oil industry.
Well, you can deny, but your client is Satan.
- Have you thought about it?
- You're finished!
When I am finished with you,
may not exercise the right or the Antarctic.
- Mint?
No, thank you.
"What happened?"
It's okay. Only a little threatened.
- Oh, you threatened?
-Yes.
I have a feeling we're missing.
Look, do not worry!
I never tell me not to worry!
It's good to finish it the next chance, okay?
You have not seen my bad side.
Stand-up
Your Honor, the defense called to testify Luke O'Brian.
- Why are you calling now?
- I can not imagine.
Mr. O'Brian,
know what it means audacity?
Yes.
"Great!
And do not think audacity to use the precious time of the jurors
ridiculous with your process?
No.
How can you sit there with this guy jerk
and not have an ounce of shame?
Protest! He is suppressing the witness.
Repressing the witness? What is this? I have never heard this kind of protest.
Learned that in the course of law by correspondence?
What comes next?
Protest, he is not using deodorant and smells bad now.
Protest, he called me a bad name and made me cry!
____Enough already!
No further questions, Your Honor.
Pass the word to my co-counsel. Thank you.
- How about these dirty tricks?
- Were not low enough.
And how far should we go?
As low as hell.
- Your Honor, we can make a withdrawal?
-Why?
I need to discuss something with my colleagues.
Be quick, two minutes.
Wow, it seems the jury is siding with Satan.
I do not know how he can sit there and catch the defense lawyers.
And why would Satan bother to defend himself?
Listen, you moron, he will not have a free time?
I know when someone is real or not, and he really is. He is Satan himself.
Never call me silly.
- Finish him.
Yes, sir.
I apologize for my co-counsel, Mr. O'Brian.
Sometimes he exaggerates a little.
A simple question, Mr. O'Brian. Do you believe in God?
Yes, I believe.
And believe in Satan?
But of course.
Likes Satan?
What a silly question is that? Why do I sue someone I like?
Order!
You're right.
But do not think that is a lot of blaming?
Satan is behind everything.
Really?
I have in my hands a statement.
When her mother died, a nurse heard him say:
"God, how could you have let this happen to me?"
You said that?
What do you think?"
Not great, but a little better.
You are content with little, right?
I want this brat is destroyed.
He said that, Mr. O'Brien?
Yes, I said.
He said: "God, how could you have let this happen to me?"
Note that I emphasized the word you.
Yes, you're getting at?
You were not blaming God and Satan, right?
Order!
Order! I will not allow such disrespect in my court. Thank you.
No further questions, Your Honor.
Order!
If I hear that noise again, everyone must evacuate the cut, get it?
Mr. Wilson: Hi yes Id consider selling direct to you! The skirt is on its way & was posted so should reach you soon!! I will look up the delivery slip to see if I can see when it will be delivered & get back to you. Kindest Regards LOLITA J
Why did I get myself into this?
That lawyer was right today.
About what?
I blamed God ...
the death of my mother.
Need not be blaming themselves for it.
So many people question God in this life.
Yeah, but he caught me at all.
God could easily prevent her death,
but not avoided.
Your Honor, I call Satan to testify.
Do you swear to tell the truth, the whole truth and nothing but the truth?
But this does not apply to me!
Are you saying that for religious reasons refuses to take the oath?
I'm not religious.
Admits to being Satan?
Do not admit anything, I see nothing, hear nothing.
He admits that is the evil being who chased Eve?
Protest. It is based on unproven facts.
It was not established that Satan is evil.
- And it's leading the witness, Your Honor.
- It is also irrelevant, Your Honor.
Protest denied. Now all feel.
I do not chase Eve, right?
In fact, she came to me.
Just as you, Luke, again and again.
Sorry, but I never tried.
I think the scriptures are quite clear:
"He who loves this world is the enemy of God."
Think of all those who worked so hard at times
to buy video games instead of praying to God.
Now, come on. Admit the truth.
You came to me several times.
I want to talk about that October night in the hospital.
The night my mother was hit by a drunk driver.
____I do not remember...
- Shortly before she died,
- I knew you were there.
____I do not remember...
Do not you remember? Do not remember anything, right?
Now, I'm not dwelling on negative thoughts.
Or insignificant.
Negligible
- My mother was not insignificant!
- Now I know what it is.
All this is because his mother died
before you tell her I loved her.
It is not true.
How he must have felt guilty for being a bad son.
And that time you tore the Bible and threw it in the trash, huh?
As you were good. He showed it to her and God.
Stop, I'm saying.
- Oh, Luke!
- Stop talking about my mother!
She raised you so well and died so young, poor.
Safety
- I'll kill you!
- Do not talk about my mother!
I have not spoken of his mother!
Look at this boy, Your Honor. Look at him.
Sounds like a Christian?
It seems to be a Christian to you?
- Mr. O'Brian!
- I'll kill you!
Do not talk about my mother!
- Order!
- Wide!
- I did not tell his mother!
- Mr. O'Brian!
- This is not a Christian.
- This man is a barbarian.
- Mr. O'Brian!
If you lose control again in this court, I'll have you arrested for contempt-Io.
Let go of me! Let go of me!
- Do you understand?
- Yes, Your Honor.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
- It's okay.
- My mother was a saint.
Okay, apology accepted.
My mother was a saint.
I'm sure yes.
But is not my fault, is it? You can not blame me.
Think, Luke. Think.
No further questions.
- Let's take a short recess.
- Hey, boy! Luke!
A small recess!
Do not forget, we have to win the jury, okay?
This seems like a nightmare. I can not get out.
I..."
"Hey!
YOU DECIDE THE VERDICT WITH BARRY POLK
Well, well, well. What do you think that?
Well, if you want my opinion, Barry, this guy ...
have a screw loose in his head.
Yeah, but Satan convinced the jury that it was not responsible for the death of the mother of Mr. O'Brian.
Of course! The jerk blame everyone but himself.
It's pathetic. It's even worth looking at it.
Jasmine, any comments?
Why all this love for Satan? We are talking about Lucifer
the monster that caused the downfall of all mankind,
and you are finding great that Satan is winning. What is this?
Well, folks. Let's be civilized, we will maintain order.
First, that is not Satan.
You know how I know? I've seen Satan.
Wait, you saw Satan?
Okay, guys, sorry we can ...
I think the audience would like to stick to legal matters.
In short, Barry, Luke is weak, is no match for Satan.
Very well. What we do now?
- Now the fight will heat up.
- That's what I want to hear.
That's what I want to hear. I want to play low, low, low.
I destroyed this guy.
The court is again in session. Promoter continue.
Promoter?
The prosecution called to testify Satan.
In the Bible, the Book of Job,
Job you attack both physically and spiritually. Why is that?
Finally an intelligent question in this court.
The short answer is:
Because I wanted to try Io.
And he passed his test?
Yes, I know it's hard to believe, but he passed.
And that does not prove that you are responsible for the suffering of at least one person?
"Maybe.
So why can not be responsible for the suffering of the world?
Your Honor, I protest. Is leading the witness.
Denied. The witness may answer the question.
See, I'm not omnipresent.
I can not be in two places at once. Only God can.
God could stop me at any time, but did not.
You should do these questions to him.
By the way, what does that say about the mighty up there?
If he can prevent evil and does not,
what does that say about him?
I think this tells me that He gave free will to all.
Protest. She can not answer the questions of the witness.
I agree. Please keep your opinions to yourself.
Of course, Your Honor.
"Any more questions?"
No.
Bailiff! Bailiff, do something!
Stay calm, please. How did ...
Bailiff, take the court this thing!
She must have entered by ventilation, Your Honor.
Calm down everyone.
- What is your next move?
"Hey guys!"
need a little time, okay?
Just have to go to the bathroom.
Thank you."
Waiting for?
Wait a few minutes.
I ate oysters spoiled.
Why did you come to defend themselves?
Why did you want to sue me?
I did not think you'd show up.
Do not think I'd show up? What else is saying stupid!
So why did he appear?
I am here to defend my honor.
His honor? You're a snake.
Be careful, O'Brian. Can I sue you for libel.
The truth is a defense against libel.
Yes, of course. I forgot you know the law, is not it?
Okay. Call me a snake.
Actually, I like snakes. Have you eaten?
You know, I can not understand is why he turned against God.
You were the leader of worship, was a beautiful angel,
- And threw it all away.
- I did not throw anything away.
Actually, you know,
I am very attractive, is not it?
Listen, I like to just talk in the past,
but if you want a direct answer,
I thought I ...
be God.
What a mistake.
Still not finished, buddy.
And now wants revenge on humans?
I want to ask you something. Why are not you afraid?
Fear? Fear of what?
Now, I was in who made Jesus Christ was crucified.
Think about that!
- Oh, you think!
You see, Jesus gave himself on the cross
and that was the biggest mistake of his life, "buddy."
Remember the Garden of Gethsemane?
All the disciples fell asleep and he had no one to turn to.
Yet he was until the end is unbelievable!
Yes, what a great man! That's why I owe so much to him.
Listen, you moron. You will lose this case,
will be the laughing stock of the world.
Even children will point at you and say:
"That's not the idiot who tried to sue Satan?"
Listen, do not talk to this idiot without my presence.
Do not do this, please.
- Everything is under control, Mr. Banks?
- Of course it is.
Remember that we do not lose ever.
Great. Do not ever say that to me.
Have a nice day.
Would it be correct to say that ...
you left school because they do not stand the pressure?
Yes.
And that was the fault of Satan?
No, it was mine.
- Was his.
-Yes.
And is currently studying at ...
Doctor, please do not put your hand on the witness.
Sorry, Your Honor. He reminds me of my son.
So:
How can we compare the night course Billy's right to other universities?
How do I know?
Well, I graduated in law from Harvard. As can be compared to yours?
Protest!
Is protesting against his own lawyer?
Your Honor, I would turn to my lawyer if possible.
Please come here.
How dare you ridicule this man in front of everyone?
- Just wanted to show that ...
- So what if it is Harvard?
Big deal! Nobody cares! Listen, I'm the boss, not you.
We are here to represent the man there. It's not your show.
You know what? Go away!
What?"
- You're fired!
Your Honor, excuse my outburst, I'm sorry.
With the permission of the court, I'd like to replace the co-champion Iowa.
- The lovely Miss. Scarlett.
- Replacement accepted.
Thank you!
- Proceed with the questioning, please.
Good trick.
You have not seen anything.
We are losing the cause, Luke. Have you noticed that?
Yes, I noticed.
I can not believe the jury is on the side of Satan.
Wow, my name will be cited as the worst lawyer in history.
Luke, it is misleading to the jury.
It is the same.
I know that. He even fooled me.
____What can I do?
I asked: "Are you okay?"
- Yes, I'm fine.
- Are you sure?
-Yes.
- Are you ready to act in the way of the Lord?
- The way of the Lord?
I thought I was doing it. I am suing the devil, if you have not noticed.
For whose glory? His or his?
Honey, it's a little more complicated than that. You do not understand.
You know, the funny thing is that most people
lock a spiritual battle every day of their lives
and continue to live their lives without thinking about what God wants for them.
What do you mean?
I want to say that Satan does not care for those who are too busy for God.
Only care about those who are too busy to Satan.
Hello!
- Are you going to testify today?
Just want to say that this is my statement:
The trial became a battle of good against evil.
I have nothing personal against Mr. Luke O'Brien,
it is a wrong with the Bible, that's all.
Even so, it will be an interesting battle. Thank you.
You have 8 trillion in the bank in case you lose?
Why? Need a loan?
Mr. Satan, can you tell us what hell is like?
I can. It is very hot. Want to go there to see?
If it is Satan, then prove it.
What happened to him?
THE END OF THE WORLD
Hey, blind man,
really think the end is near?
I believe that Jesus will return soon, yes.
- And why is that?
- I am blind, but I can see.
The book of Luke says, "Be careful not to be deceived.
For many virãoo in my name, saying, 'I am! '
- Yes, I know. Thank you.
- 'This Time' pro'ximo '.
He said to them: "Nation will rise against nation, and kingdom against kingdom.
There will be great earthquakes, famines and pestilences in various places. "
I really believe that we are the generation úItima.
Congratulations. It sounds like it will be a cakewalk.
It is even a breeze?
- Something wrong?
- No, no.
Remember that blind out there?
- Blind?
- It is. Where will he go?
We tie the jury.
This case is won if we do not spoil everything.
- We bind all, huh?
- Tied.
You know?
I think we have to change the strategy.
Stand-up
Can you explain evil?
Did you hear my question?
Yes.
So:
Evil is good.
Are you saying that evil is good?
You still do not understand, is not it?
There would be no good without evil
and hence no evil without good.
So Ezekiel ...
- Ezekiel?
-Yes.
- One of my favorites.
"Oh, yes.
He said a beautiful thing about you. Say you were a leader of worship,
anointed as a guardian cherub,
you were on the holy mountain of God,
- And walked among the fiery stones.
- Sparkling stones.
-Yes.
So what?
So what? So you thought like God,
and that was a silly, right?
What kind of question is that, Your Honor?
Your Honor!
- Who is Jesus to you?
- What?
I said: Who is Jesus Christ?
Your Honor, what does this have to do with it?
Objection, Your Honor.
- Where do you want to go with it?
- Denied. Continue.
Your Honor, please.
Would you please sit down and be quiet?
Got it?
Thank you, doctor.
Who is Jesus Christ?
Witness, answer the question.
Yes, Your Honor.
Jesus Christ.
She's OK.
He was a good teacher, that's all. Nothing more.
It was a good teacher? I do not remember him saying anything.
Okay, he said he was God.
- Sorry, what did he say?
- Great stuff!
You heard me.
He said that was what? Sorry, but you can repeat to the jury and the court?
Have not you heard?
I will not repeat. If you have wax in your ears, go clean.
But the worst mistake of his life was crucify Io, was not it?
It's good to take care of that speech, boy.
He thought he had thought of everything, right?
Be careful what you say, boy.
Look around you. What do you see?
I've looked at. Why do not you look now? What do you see?
Who are you?
I am a believer in Jesus Christ
and love God. That's all I have to be.
Excuse me, Mr. O'Brian. Any more questions?
Wow! Here we are, another round of events. What do you think?
I think I never will see such a thing in our lives.
"What happened?"
This loser!
Okay, let's fight. From now on, it's war.
Where did this come from?
I don't know.
It was like ...
He waits a little...)
"Hey!
I asked: "Are you okay?"
-Yes.
I'm just a headache.
Don't worry.
Silence in court. All rise.
The court is in session.
You may be seated.
Let me make one thing clear.
Do not want to cry in court.
Understood?
Great. Can proceed.
Mr. O'Brian, has seen pornography on the internet?
-Yes.
- How many times?
I don't know.
How about 341 times?
- It would be a precise number?
- Objection!
Your Honor, this is irrelevant.
- Irrelevant? I think not.
- Denied. Continue.
Maybe that's the number.
But not after I got married.
And during that period, there were wars in Afghanistan,
Somalia, Iraq,
children were killed, a boy lost his mother.
Excuse me. Where are getting at?
I just want to know if Mr. O'Brien knew of these events.
Yes, I know.
So tell me. Why you chose Satan
instead of the other events?
Well, he probably did not choose.
____It was my fault!
My and my carnal desires.
So Satan is not to blame for his carnal desires?
No.
We have to work out our salvation every day. Day by day.
How they got that information, Luke?
I don't know.
Gwen knew the story of the internet?
No.
- Luke, I'm sorry.
- Look, give me a minute, okay?
I'm fine.
Luke,
you think this man is really Satan?
The session is reopened. Witness to testify again, please.
Sorry. Yes, Your Honor.
Mr. O'Brien, you said or not said a word
when someone off in traffic last week?
Protest! This is just a guess, Your Honor.
Where did you get this information?
We have a recording, we can show the jury.
And who was in the car to save it?
Your Honor, as we present this as proof.
We received a phone recording of Mr. O'Brian.
Say what?
Some phones transmit such recordings
and that is why we have the recording of the cell of Mr. O'Brian.
We have already presented as evidence.
Yes, right here.
That's odd. Continue.
- You said ...
- Yes! Yes, I said.
- That fellow I shut ...
- Yes or no, Mr. O'Brien?
Yes.
And you made a racist comment last week?
- What do you say?
____I do not remember...
And when did it become a Christian?
I accepted Jesus Christ in my heart for 7 years.
7 years old:
And swears and makes racist comments.
No further questions.
Mr. O'Brian, other racist comments that you said?
- Are you racist?
- He is a member of the Ku Klux Klan?
What kind of man you are? If you think even a Christian?
Please excuse me now.
How does it feel to see what's missing?
It is true that going to divorce?
Have you felt so down ...
he no longer has to turn to except to heaven?
Lord God,
I acknowledge that I have blamed everyone but me.
I even blame Satan, but did not see my own shortcomings,
my own flesh.
Forgive me, Lord. Forgive me.
Because of all the people of this land,
I am the biggest hypocrite
and the worst sinner.
Give me another chance to do the right thing the right way,
of Thy way, Thy will.
I want to win this cause.
Barry, most experts agree that this case is lost.
Luke O'Brien lost the jury and lost the case.
Amazing. Then his past came to torment Io.
Yes, that's right.
Now let's talk to Mark, live in London.
Mark, what is the consensus among people here in England?
Barry, most people I talked to agree that Luke O'Brien is a hypocrite.
He is suing the devil when he should sue himself.
God anointed Jesus of Nazareth
with the power of the Holy Spirit to do good
and healing all who were under the dominion of the devil,
that ...
- What does this mean to you?
- Wow, you're amazing.
He spoke this mantra all day, is not it?
What does this mean for me?
Absolutely nothing. At all.
The thief comes only to steal and kill and destroy.
I'll tell you one thing. I wanted to have the power to make you disappear.
You're too boring!
And Jesus was referring to you, then I ask:
How many people have you killed?
Objection, Your Honor.
He continues assuming the Bible as evidence.
We all know that is a lot of fairy tales, is it?
I ask that the entire line of argument is deleted from the file.
Denied. And by the way, Mr. Banks,
his commentary on the Bible is wrong.
Do you have any proof of his statement about "fairy tales"?
- Yes, Your Honor.
- Are they deaf?
Sit down, all of you!
According to the Bible, I killed ten people.
The family of Job, that's all.
But how many people God killed in the flood?
It is estimated that 100 million people were!
- Why not tell the truth?
- Want the truth?
You can not handle the truth!
Order!
I can handle the truth.
You know, Jesus said:
"I came that they may have life and have it abundantly."
He also said: "I am the good shepherd.
The good shepherd lays down his life for the sheep. "
So I ask:
Would you give your life for a human being, as Jesus did?
"Of course not.
Humans are garbage.
I'm just the garbage collector.
- Well put, Satan.
- Your Honor, I think we can not ...
____Sit!
Why get so nervous when I mention the name of Jesus Christ?
Why do not you ask me something fun, like death?
- Ask about the death, come on!
- Want to talk about death?
- Let's talk about death.
- How many people think are going to hell?
I do not know. You know best. Say.
Over two billion people, according to the book of Revelation.
- What about that?
- That man is evil,
God is just, and you have part in the guilt.
Oh, I know. Been in hell, boy?
It's not a fun place.
No. That's a shame, huh?
Because that's where you go.
Order!
We will have a recess of 15 minutes.
- That was amazing.
is
Now what?
- We need more witnesses.
ok
She's OK.
Pastor Pringle,
everything is God's fault?
No, not his fault.
He is the creator of all things.
However he gave us free will
that we should be free to choose.
It's just.
Thank you very much!
Thank you!
- Pastor Pringle, right?
ok
Let me get this straight. You said that God gives us free will
that every man can choose between Satan and God.
ok
- So if I go now to Mr. O'Brian
and throws a punch at his face, this is my free will?
ok
Very good!
So is not the fault of Satan if we follow this line of reasoning.
Well, Satan came to kill, steal and destroy.
It is clear from Scripture that he is behind all the world's problems.
However, we become responsible for our actions when we fall into temptation.
Thank you."
Pastor Philips,
can prove to me in 30 seconds or less that God exists?
- Objection!
- Denied.
The witness can answer.
30 seconds to prove that God exists? Can I do this in a sentence.
Something can not come from nothing is impossible.
Very well. Something can not come from nowhere. How so?
We can explain where life began, where thoughts began to explain,
but can not prove the moral conscience.
This is leaving scientists puzzled
and also proves the existence of God.
- And what is the mission of Satan?
- I think it is clear from Scripture.
He came to steal, kill and destroy.
- Is there a hell?
Absolutely!
And every day people have the opportunity to choose heaven or hell.
Thank you."
Do you think that Satan is guilty of 8 trillion dollars?
- Objection!
- Denied. Answer the question.
You can not put a price on the damage he did,
but humans are responsible for their own souls.
Thank you, pastor. That's all.
That's right, folks. The case is a back and forth like a game of ping-pong.
Tony, who is winning?
It's hard to tell, even if difficult,
but it was brilliant of him to bring different people to testify.
I would say that O'Brian is winning right now,
and he seems able to take the case to the end.
I think so. The jury is now supporting O'Brian.
- I'm a little worried, sir.
"A little."
Gentlemen, we are losing this cause. We need to change the methods ...
Who do you think you're talking?
You think as much, no? Just because you studied law at Stanford, is not it?
Work in a large firm? Only you know nothing, man.
And that goes for you too!
Listen, you better win this case, I'm warning you,
or my highest priority will pursue you day and night
this world and in hell, right? Now get out of here! Get out!
Never get tired of playing the bully?
You know, I still do not understand you and your wife, after all ...
or you are super super crazy or stupid to want to fight me.
I'm not afraid of you.
Yes, you can be more powerful than I on this earth,
but Jesus is infinitely more powerful than you.
Is quoting the Bible again, is not it?
I know, I know. So why not ask God to cure cancer in the brain of Gwen?
What?"
Oh,
She did not tell you? Wow.
What a pity. Well, she has brain cancer.
She only got 5 months of life.
- You're lying.
- Oh, yeah, I'm lying.
I know, after all Satan ... He always lies, is not it?
Well then why you did not ask her?
Everyone needs compassion,
a love that never fails.
- Gwen, I must ask you something.
What?"
And you have to be honest with me, okay?
Are you ill, dear?
____I need to know!
You're dying of cancer?
____Why do not you tell me?
Sorry.
You were so busy.
You know what? I want to continue the trial, all right?
I want you to win!
Are you listening? I want you to win!
____I love you!
Oh, dear,
I love you too much.
Stand-up
You may be seated.
The defense has something to say?
Your Honor, we ask the court to grant us a delay
and suspend this trial immediately.
Order!
Doctor, on what basis?
Your Honor, this man is not Satan.
Order!
Doctor, you understand what you're saying?
The fact that he admitted to be Satan is unmistakable.
Your Honor, according to international law, section 666,
the trial can not continue if there is doubt as to the identity.
Section 666? Never heard of her.
It's in your book. Page 341.
666. Here you are.
Prosecuting attorney, any comments?
Your Honor, it was established that he is Satan.
No, it was established, Your Honor.
Especially in the light of new revelations about our client.
Oh! Let's stop.
Doctors want to see everyone in my room now.
This is absurd!
Can I revoke your license for this!
Your Honor, we were alerted to the fact that our client is who it says it.
- He is not Satan!
____What are you saying?
He's crazy. We represent deftly
and he tricked us.
Oh, he cheated, he cheated?
You are not the best law firm in the world?
- He also tricked them to pay?
- Your Honor, he's not crazy.
I judge it, thanks.
We ask that the entire case is dismissed for lack of person.
- And under international law ... 393
- Will not quote the law!
This case will continue, but demand appears to be proof of identity.
You will have to prove that man is Satan.
- Your Honor, it does not ...
- Oh, stop it,
- And all come back to court.
- Thank you, Your Honor.
Good luck to you.
If you won or not,
you defended what he believed
and faced all that public humiliation.
You never gave up.
I respect that very much.
Thanks, I ...
I wish there was a way to prove this guy is the devil.
It is.
I asked: "Are you okay?"
- I'm fine.
Mr. Wilson: Hi yes Id consider selling direct to you! TShe skirt is on its way & was posted so should reach you soon!! I will look up tShe delivery slip to see if I can see wShen it will be delivered & get back to you. Kindest Regards LOLITA J
How are you?
- Okay, how about you?
I'm fine.
I thought I had caught that guy, you know?
He is too smart.
You are dealing with a power beyond his comprehension.
Luke, God is still in control.
Yeah, I feel that ...
What did you say?
God is in control, Luke. God is in control.
- Remember this.
____I love you!
Is that OK?"
Your Honor, the prosecution would like to bring Satan to testify.
"Hi,
Why did the court and this jury that you were Satan?
In fact, if I remember correctly,
I never said I was Satan, who said it was you.
You answered all the questions like Satan.
Well, someone had to defend Io, and that someone could be me, right?
Order!
As you make a living?
I sell used cars, and new ones as well, is.
Come see me, I make a special price.
Really?
For all of you a special precinho.
How about that, folks? But that cute.
It's all just a big joke to you, is not it?
Now, come on, we all had fun, right? I mean,
I had my 15 minutes, you had her,
all go home happy and satisfied, right?
After all, why did not you sued Satan?
No.
You're a rational person, is not it?
Yes you?
You would not do anything unusual in this court, would you?
There is nothing that is common in this court.
Order!
- Sorry, Your Honor.
- I meant ...
now that you turned out to be a car salesman ...
"Right, right.
You would not do anything crazy, would you?
- I think not.
- No, you do not do anything weird
- Before this jury, would you?
- Of course not.
No, after all, you now says he is not Satan.
That's right. Well, now we have fun, no? Now ...
- Wait just a minute more, friend.
- Hey! No. ..
- What ... No, no, no.
- Are you paying attention now, right?
Yes, sometimes ... You know what? Stop ...
Stop shaking it in front of my face, please. I'm asking.
- It'll be even better.
- Your Honor!
He's shaking a Bible here in front of me.
- I have something special here for you.
- I'm sure yes.
- James, chapter 4, verse 7.
- Oh, no.
Submit yourselves to God.
Resist the devil and he will flee from you.
Draw near to God, and He will draw near to you.
Cleanse your hands, sinners,
and purify your hearts, you who have a split mind.
Have you finished? Oh, no.
By the power and truth of these scriptures
and in the name of Jesus Christ,
get behind me, Satan!
How?
I said:
Stay behind me, Satan! In the name of Jesus Christ!
Excuse me, Satan, return to the witness stand.
Sorry.
- This was unusual.
I. .. I am sick, Your Honor.
It makes it all the time?
I bet that causes a lot of laughs, right?
You could not even be Satan,
after all, the Bible clearly says that if we resist the devil,
he will flee.
- But this does not apply to you, is not it?
- No.
I. .. I usually ...
Stay behind me, Satan!
I have a proposition for you, friend.
Come on, friend Luke, what do you think?
I give you everything you could want in this life.
Riches, beautiful houses, horses.
And what will this cost me? My soul?
Therefore, only your soul. It's nothing. His soul ...
You can take your offer and throw it in the trash.
Order!
Go back to the witness stand, sir.
This was very irrational.
In fact, you look up stupid now.
____How about that?
Would you please go back to the bank?
Will you shut up?
Not done yet! Shut up! Shut up!
And you, what are you looking at?
Something funny?
I know all about you.
I know all your secrets.
- Players are addicted to sex ...
- The witness ...
_____Shut up!
- Lord accused ...
- Go back to the bank ...
____Sit!
- Where is your place.
- Take your ...
- Shut up!
I know all about you, all of you.
I'm watching you.
- I want to know tShe truth.
The real truth, sincere and true?
I delight ...
I wreak havoc in the world.
In playing the rich against the poor,
race against race,
country against country, man against man,
but especially
man against God.
Yes, God.
God, God. Yes, God.
Do you know what God invented?
Now most of you are very idiot to realize it.
God created the oceans and the stars,
created compassion, forgiveness e. ..
stupid things like love.
He created good health, raindrops,
and the essence of jasmine.
You know what I created? Do you know?
I created the sound,
and how stupid you are, you loved it!
Humans love the sounds that I created.
Alarm automobiles, motorcycles, whistles,
nightclubs, gangster rap, techno music,
invented anything that creates noise.
And you know why?
The noise away any thought of God.
What is the problem?
Do not you love the song of hell?
Let me tell you a secret.
I invented the customer service.
Automatic answer, my idea too.
Notification unfair? It came from me.
A huge bill and unjust, by me.
Traffic tickets?
They are my utility companies, oil and car parks.
Who do you think applies fines? I do this to annoy you,
because I hate to the core!
You humans are pathetic.
I can try Ios with a chocolate bar
and you deny Jesus Christ in a millisecond.
After all ...
people are massacred in Rwanda, and you yawn.
Starving people in Haiti,
and you give a money supply in the church.
Failed!
What a bunch of losers!
War!
They knew that most wars begin over land?
Believe? For land dispute.
And yet, 75% of the land is unoccupied,
even in the U.S.!
Oh yes, I know, I started the wars,
but it is idiots like you need to finish what I started.
I need people who care about silly political disputes.
The left versus right,
is all a distraction, do you not see?
You know, you ...
you believe in God as much as I believe in fairy tales.
By the way,
I love the way depicted in the media.
That doll with a pitchfork,
horns and tail.
You humans are so stupid.
They are like a bunch of rats running on a wheel.
You see, every day people die,
and want to know?
They can be in two places, and are not really dead.
Are alive in heaven or in hell are alive.
You choose.
You know what my biggest goal?
It's me take you all to hell!
It is the world coming to an end, right? It better be fast.
I guess they wonder why I do what I do.
This is very easy.
It's because I hate to the core!
I hate every one of you!
Have a nice day.
THE TRIAL OF THE CENTURY
Your Honor,
ask the court to disregard any statement of our client.
He did so under duress of prosecution complete
and the civil procedure code 598.91,
it can not be judged by this court.
The problem, Your Honor, is ...
the mental state of our client, it's crazy.
As I do not want to appeal this case,
the testimony will be removed from the file.
Your Honor, I ...
I want you all to follow my instruction:
Do not take into account
nothing that the accused uttered.
Is based only on what they heard, saw,
and witnessed the events and statements from witnesses.
I clear?
Defence lawyer closure.
Distinguished members of the jury,
let's think for a moment ...
what kind of man sue someone in 8 trillion.
Individual and selfish,
wanting to attract attention, and that can not free himself from his past.
And even if my client seems to be charismatic,
even if he wants to make a scene in court, he is mentally ill.
He is insane,
he needs help,
of piety,
not a process.
And it should not be associated with all the evil,
or to be Satan himself,
and this is not the apple that Eve bit the fruit
in the Garden of Eden.
So I ask you
they conclude today
as well as any logical person would do and sober,
that my client ...
is innocent.
Now Mr. O'Brian, closure.
Mr. O'Brien?
Satan brought up my past.
He's right.
I did horrible things.
I said horrible things and cruel.
And I ask forgiveness from those who hurt.
Every day ...
there is a battle within me.
I know what I should do.
And sometimes do not.
I know I should not do.
Sometimes I do it anyway.
But this is the struggle to choose between good and evil.
Between God and Satan.
Each day is a struggle
to live a life that honors Jesus Christ.
But when we surrender our lives to Jesus
we are new people.
Satan's mission is to destroy God's work.
We humans are God's work.
We make mistakes and He forgives us.
Do not let Satan steal them from us.
Make him pay ...
for his attempts to destroy our lives.
Let him be punished for their hatred.
And thank God for his love
and forgiveness.
You see, the greatest trick the devil ever done
was convincing the world he did not exist.
But this illusion is over.
Thank you."
Stand-up
They reached a verdict?
Yes, Your Honor.
The jury is favorable to the prosecution
at 8 trillion dollars.
Order!
And Satan, you can go straight to hell!
Tasheila Jones, the news channel 2,
We are out here and the verdict was announced!
What do you think the verdict?
It was a fantastic result!
Luke fought for what he wanted and won. He did it!
What you want, your insignificant?
Can I have your autograph?
Are you kidding me? Get out!
Order!
TALK WITH DR. The GOD OF JAMES INJUSTlÇA
Oh, you woke up? It was a long night.
What?"
- How to get here, sir?
I do not know. I think I slept the whole night here.
Well, I do not want to wake Io, but ...
you were saying, "Get behind me, Satan!"
Stay ...
Oh, I must be dreaming!
Well, do not study too much.
Girls, girls. It's a new day.
It's a new day!
Gwen?
- Gwen?
- Luke?
- Where were you?
- Honey, are you sick?
No, I'm sick. Where were you? Not called me last night.
Sorry, dear, sorry. I went to the library
- And fell asleep.
- In the library?
I fell asleep and dreamed that you were ill e. ..
and you did not tell me the dream.
- You have cancer, e. ..
- Cancer?
- Are you sick? You are telling the truth?
- I'm fine, but ...
I thought you would kill the man who killed his mother.
Honey, no. No, no, you have to hear me. I had ...
a dream about the devil and I beat him,
I sued in court and won.
- E. .. What, him?
- I saw the gun in his car, Luke.
I saw the gun in your car!
I thought you were killing the man who killed his mother.
No, no, dear. This has already happened.
You can't.
- It's gone. I must be honest with you.
I would do it, but ...
Honey, I'm sorry.
- You scared me.
- I'm so sorry.
I found peace, dear.
I found my peace, I found God. I found my God!
And you know what? I'll forgive Io, Io I will forgive.
It's a new day.
And so began the first day of my new life.
A life that will obey the Lord and drive away the enemy.
I feel wonderful. Thank you, God.
You querser great, Luke?
You're not a loser.
Want to earn much money, Luke?
You're not a loser, huh?
Think of Gwen.
You have no authority over me, Satan.
Got it?
Who are you?
I am a believer in Jesus Christ.
The Savior, He can move mountains.
My God is mighty to save.
He is mighty to save.
Forever Author of salvation,
He rose and conquered death.
Jesus conquered death.
Take me as I am,
all my fears and failures.
Complete my life again.
I give my life to follow everything I believe.
Now I surrender.
I surrender.
The Savior, He can move mountains.
My God is mighty to save.
He is mighty to save.
Forever Author of salvation,
He rose and conquered death.
Jesus conquered death.
The Savior, He can move mountains.
My God is mighty to save.
He is mighty to save.
Forever Author of salvation,
He rose and conquered death.
Jesus conquered death.
Shine your light and let the whole world to see.
We sing to the glory of the risen King,
"Jesus.
Shine your light and let the whole world to see.
We sing to the glory of the risen King.
The Savior, He can move mountains.
My God is mighty to save.
He is mighty to save.
Forever Author of salvation,
He rose and conquered death.
Jesus conquered death.
The Savior, He can move mountains.
My God is mighty to save.
He is mighty to save.
Forever Author of salvation,
He rose and conquered death.
Jesus conquered death.
Shine your light and let the whole world to see.
We sing to the glory of the risen King,
"Jesus.
Shine your light and let the whole world to see.
We sing to the glory of the risen King,
"Jesus.
Shine your light and let the whole world to see.
We sing to the glory of the risen King,
"Jesus.
Shine your light and let the whole world to see.
We sing to the glory of the risen King,
"Jesus.
Shine your light and let the whole world to see.
We sing to the glory of the risen King,
"Jesus.
Shine your light and let the whole world to see.