Morning, gentlemen. Feet.
So happy you're here.
This is the third open house
and not one bite.
Well...
Don't worry.
I have everything
under control.
Anna, you are a realtor?
I'm a stager. I stage apartments
for realtors.
I transform ordinary spaces
into something special.
Most people don't know what it is they want
until I show it to them,
and so many places
need my help.
Not the Davenport,
of course.
It's just a very fine line
between elegant and dowdy.
I just think maybe
a quarter-inch higher.
Plus an eighth of an inch?
We'll get it right.
You did that on purpose.
Knock it off.
As I'm sure
you're aware,
apartments at the Davenport
don't come up very often,
and we have more than our share of applicants.
So, why you?
I have lived in Boston
my entire life,
and I have always
dreamed of living here.
And thankfully, I have found somebody
who shares that dream,
and I can assure you that you will not find
two people more in sync
with your exceptionally high standards and,
if I may be so bold,
your taste.
Thank you.
Wow!
With a bit of luck,
we might get some offers.
Come on, Charlie.
You know it's not about luck.
It's about preparation.
Put these in the oven half an hour before you open
and you'll have five offers before noon.
No luck needed.
Okay, say it with me.
Three bedrooms.
Concierge.
Full gym and swimming pool looking over the common.
I mean, come on!
Don't get cocky.
Why, you don't think
they liked us?
I like us.
Don't you like us?
We're okay. All right.
Okay.
Here we go.
Ready? And...
Ugly!
Excuse me?
Not you, sweetie.
It's Mr. Sheinbaum
e-mailing me updates
of his double bypass.
I'm glad
I skipped lunch.
No, no, no, this is good.
This is good,
because this way I don't have to go in.
We can go to dinner.
Studio apartment,
two offers already.
That's 'cause
you're a genius.
Have you packed yet?
Your flight's at 11:00.
I'm fine,
just you don't
be late.
We've got an 8:00 rez
and they're strict.
When am I ever late?
When your dad comes out of the woodwork
demanding to see his daughter, that's when.
I have to go, Jer. I haven't seen him in weeks.
Okay, just wouldn't want you all riled up for our very special dinner.
You know I don't like surprises.
You'll like this one.
See you.
Oh, Anna, this is gonna blow your mind!
What'd you buy?
A lot, I got a lot,
but that's not it.
I wanted to
tell you something.
Guess who I saw coming out of DePrisco's?
Who?
Jeremy!
You did? When?
On the way here.
The cab was stuck in traffic and I look over,
and he's walking
out of the store
carrying that little red bag.
The bag.
There's only one reason
people go into DePrisco's.
You're gonna have a better engagement ring
than me, you big jerk!
Oh, my God.
Did you know?
No. I mean, I did put his name on the mailing list
a couple months ago
hoping he'd get the hint,
but...
Oh! He got the hint!
I think he got the hint!
Okay, hold on, we gotta work on your surprise face,
'cause I don't want him to know I told you...
Okay, ask me.
Ready?
Will you marry me?
What? Are you scared? That was awful.
Try it again.
Okay.
Bigger eyes. And maybe a little,
"Who, me?"
The good news is, you have time to practice
between now and then.
Can I marry you?
No, thank you.
Already married, huh?
Getting engaged.
Engaged?
Dad.
My daughter
is engaged?
Gargon! Champagne!
Let's have a couple
of beers, banana.
I'll get them.
You're gonna
be married.
Jack Brady. Import-export, real estate.
Glad to meet you.
She's been four years with the guy.
What was he thinking?
I proposed to her mother
after a week!
I proposed to her
after half an hour.
Exactly!
Where's the lucky guy?
Packing. He has a cardiology
convention in Dublin.
It's a good thing that Jeremy
finally came around.
You might have had to follow him
to Ireland this weekend.
It is leap year,
you know.
Dad, do not tell
that story again.
Why not?
It's a family myth.
It is the
honest-to-God truth!
That's what Grandma Jane
did to Grandpa Tom.
They'd been dating for a while and
he was dragging his feet,
so she finally suggested they pay a visit
to the old country.
February 20th, Dublin, Ireland,
she hits him with it.
Boom!
Ring on finger, signed, sealed,
delivered.
Well, I'm not going to have to
pull a Grandma Jane.
That's my girl. I'm finally going to
get some grandkids.
Dad, I've got to go.
Mmm-mmm.
No, I just got here!
Yeah, well, you were late.
We said 7:00.
I'm just happy that we want
the same things.
You know, you always have it
figured out for us.
I mean, even with my crazy schedule and...
You know I appreciate it, right?
So...
So this is for you.
Jeremy.
They're earrings.
Yeah.
For my ears.
Oh! Sorry.
Oh, God.
Dr. Sloane.
Hey, Bill.
Oh! Sounds like you're gonna have to go in from the spine.
Send me a photo. I'll have a look. Okay?
All right. Sorry.
Why don't you
try them on?
Oh! Sorry. Sure.
Yikes. There's an aorta to write home about.
Look at that.
Honey, not here.
Yummy.
So, I...
It's not gonna work.
I'm so sorry, Anna. Bill says I really
"aorta" go in.
Look, he actually wrote that.
He wrote "aorta."
So I'll pick up my bag and just go straight
to the airport when I'm done.
Forgive me?
Of course.
Okay.
I am so sorry.
I love you.
Love you.
All right.
You "aorta" run.
It's a good thing that Jeremy finally came around.
You might have had to follow him to Ireland this weekend
and pull a Grandma Jane. It is leap year, you know.
"Leap-year proposals are an old folklore tradition
"that dates back to the 5th century."
Sure.
In Ireland, there's this tradition
that in a leap year, a woman can propose to a man on February 29th,
one day every four years.
Will you marry me?
Yes.
That's ridiculous.
Are you traveling on business or pleasure?
I'm going to propose to my boyfriend on leap day.
Are you now? Congratulations.
Thank you.
Jeremy, my boyfriend, is already there on business.
We've been together four years. Four years.
It's a long time.
It's not like I'm rushing anything
by doing this, you know.
He bought me earrings. Don't get me wrong,
they're beautiful,
but earrings don't exactly
say commitment.
Not that commitment
is an issue.
I mean, we're buying this apartment together
and it's perfect.
I know exactly how I'm going
to change it.
We're just gonna
knock down that wall.
You see? If we open up
the kitchen a little,
I think it flows better
into the dining area.
Just creates
a more free overall...
Ladies and gentlemen,
this is your captain speaking.
It looks like there's a spot of bad weather
up ahead,
so we may experience just a little bit
of turbulence.
I'm getting engaged.
I'm not gonna die
without getting engaged!
This is your captain here again,
ladies and gentlemen.
I may have underestimated
the storm just a little bit,
but I'm afraid we are being diverted
to Cardiff, Wales,
as Dublin Airport
has been shut down.
What?
Once landed, ground staff will be happy to book you
onto connecting flights
in order to get you
to your final destination.
Wales? No, we can't
land in Wales.
At least
we're landing.
Yes, but I'm on
a schedule.
Excuse me. Yeah, I need
to get through.
Cardiff, Wales Airport
regrets to announce
that due to
inclement weather,
all flights today
have been canceled.
I'm sorry, there's nothing very much
I can do about it.
I'm so sorry.
Yeah, could you move?
There are no more flights
until tomorrow.
No flights until tomorrow?
Tomorrow, madam.
Tomorrow.
I think that's what I said.
Didn't I, Beryl?
That is what
you said.
Well, no, that's not
going to work for me.
Look. I'm going to Dublin to propose to my boyfriend
on the 20th, leap day.
It's an old Irish tradition,
and I need to buy a dress
and find a ring
and book a restaurant.
So, between us girls,
I think you can see why I really need
to be there today.
Oh! Right.
Right!
Beryl, will you ring
Dublin International Airport
and get them to open a runway
especially for madam?
Right away.
We regret to announce that all commercial
passenger ferries to Ireland
have been canceled.
Will all passengers booked for the crossing
to Ringaskiddy
please report to
the information desk?
Hi. I'd like a ticket
to Cork, please.
Ferry's canceled.
What is wrong
with this country?
I usually blame
the government,
but this one's the weather.
Storm, see?
Well, we'll just see about that.
I'll find my own boat.
We're going to have to go
in to Dingle.
But I paid for Cork!
Okay. Dingle will do.
You can take the man
out of the fish,
but you can't take the fish
out of the water!
That a good one,
Dekko?
Hello.
Are you open?
Australian.
South African.
Actually, she's American.
Anna, from Boston.
I just need someone to tell me how to
get to Dublin from here.
Is there a bus, maybe?
1987.
I'm sorry?
The year the last Dublin bus
left Dingle.
No, no, no. The train
stopped running in '67.
The bus stopped
running in 1989.
It was 1987.
Okay.
Is there a taxi service
or something?
Perfect. Thank you.
My battery's going
to die any second.
Ma'am.
Oh, thank you.
Hello there.
Hello.
Hello?
Hello. Yes, I need
a taxi to Dublin.
Yeah, where you
calling from?
I'm in a funny little pub called the Carack or,
I don't know, Caragh?
Carahg?
Whatever.
We don't drive
American redheads.
What do you mean you don't drive
American redheads?
How do you know
the color of my hair?
Of course. You're the taxi driver.
Well, I need you...
I need you to drive me
to Dublin.
Dublin, is it?
Well, I'll tell you something about Dublin,
Anna from Boston.
Dublin is a city of chancers and cheats
and backstabbing snakes.
It's where the worst of humanity collects
to poison this fair country.
I wouldn't drive you to Dublin if you were
to offer me €500.
Jesus! I'd sell
me wife for €500!
Trust me,
you'd have few takers.
All right. Anyone else want to go
to Dublin for 500?
I'm your man, missus!
It's bad luck to start a journey
on a Friday.
Saturday. It's bad luck to start a journey
on a Saturday.
Tuesday!
No, it's Sunday,
to be sure.
Fine. It's late.
I'll just find somebody to drive me
in the morning.
So, if one of you can direct me
to the nearest hotel?
Or bed and breakfast?
Of course. Of course.
This is also the hotel.
Bathroom's down the hall. You have to flush it twice.
Seriously, twice.
Just like
the Four Seasons.
Okay.
I noticed a menu
on the bar?
It's closed.
Closed.
But given the famous
Irish tradition
of hospitality
and generosity...
I'll do you
a hang sandwich.
What's a hang?
Hang is a verb.
It's not a sandwich.
It did die. Of course.
Huh!
There we go.
Hey,
the lights are gone!
Oh, Jesus,
the lights failed again.
Women!
It's over now.
For the love of God.
What the hell you doing?
Plugging something in.
Give me that.
It's personal.
You fried my BlackBerry.
You fried the whole
village! Idiot!
Jackass.
You're here in Ireland?
Yeah.
I wanted to surprise you, but it's turned into
a complete disaster.
At this point I'm just glad
somebody knows where I am.
I mean, seriously,
you have no idea what passes
for a hotel out here,
or common courtesy.
I can't wait
to see you.
Well, I can't wait
to see you, either.
Well, when will
you get here?
I should be there this afternoon.
I just need to get a cab.
Great surprise, honey.
I love you.
I love you, too. Bye.
Sorry, Declan, you've had plenty of time
to pay your debt.
But I'm almost there. I'm down to the last
of the bloody interest.
Come on, Tommo, be reasonable,
would you?
You can't take
the blessed kitchen!
You'll put me
out of business!
The whole lot, or the kitchen goes
in the back of the van.
Give me a month.
A month? A week.
A week? God!
Ten days, €900,
guaranteed.
A thousand, Dekko.
That's the old interest right there.
The interest on the interest on the...
Oh, man.
Ten days, €1,000.
Okay. Okay.
You'll have it.
You have my word.
Done.
Later.
All right, lads.
Come on, then, let's do it. But only 'cause
you're desperate.
I'll drive you
to Dublin.
Will you get out?
€500, like you said.
Yes or no?
You're not a fan
of Dublin.
You've made that very clear,
so I won't inconvenience you.
It's not inconvenient
at all.
What part of "get out"
do you not understand?
A simple yes
or no will do.
Yes, you can
drive me, now...
Good. Be outside
in 10 minutes.
God!
Naked here!
By the way, it's 100 for the room,
and that includes the vandalism.
I'll leave you to it.
Naked here.
There you are, Bob.
Hop in.
Please tell me that
that is the car
that is taking us around the corner
to the actual taxi.
I'll have you know that is a Renault 4.
She's classic!
Worst fears confirmed.
She's rock solid right there!
Beautiful. Come on.
None of those fancy airbags
to get in the way.
Don't listen to her.
She knows not what she says.
Do you mind?
Ah! Sure.
Thank you.
How does that work?
Can you be careful with that? That was a gift
from my boyfriend.
He bought you
a suitcase?
It's a Vuitton.
What?
A Louis Vuitton?
Come on.
Is it yourself, Louis? Can I give you a hand
getting into the car, Louis?
She named her suitcase.
She's a crackpot.
You can't
go now, missus.
Why not?
A black cat just
crossed your path.
You can't start a journey
when you see a black cat.
Ten years bad luck.
No, it's not a cat,
it's a magpie.
Anyway, it's 15 years
bad luck.
Thirteen!
It's 12,
definitely 12.
Then I guess it's a good thing I don't
believe in luck, so...
Well, you ought to, if you're getting
into that, you.
Safe journey.
May the road
rise up to meet you.
See you, lads!
Good luck, Declan!
Bye, now.
I tell you
something,
they'll kill
each other!
Okay,
we're here,
on the road.
It's only February 27th. I still have two days
to get there, so...
Where are we?
I may even get there before the stores close.
I could get some shopping in.
That's the reason you're going to Dublin,
is to shop?
No, I'm...
If you must know, I'm going there to
propose to my boyfriend.
He's at a medical conference there.
He's a cardiologist.
We are applying to move into the most
amazing apartment,
and I actually thought he was going to propose
to me the other night,
but he didn't.
Yeah?
Yeah, and you guys have
this great tradition
that a woman can
propose to a man
on the 20th of February
in a leap year.
Yeah?
Yeah.
So I thought,
"Why not?"
Yeah!
Yeah.
I mean...
That's the stupidest thing
I've ever heard!
No, it isn't.
Yeah, it is.
No, it's a tradition.
It's a romantic tradition.
It's a day for desperate women trying to
trap themselves a man
who clearly doesn't
want to get married.
You've got to know that if your man
wanted to propose,
he'd have done it
already. Fact!
No one touches the music!
Are you crazy? You know nothing
about me or Jeremy!
You know what you are?
You're a cynic.
You're a lonely,
bitter cynic.
Better that than an idiot.
"Leap year, diddly-eye!
"Will you marry me,
diddly-eye?
"I've got a suitcase
called Louis, diddly-eye!"
What are you, the Lucky Charms
leprechaun?
You know what? We are done.
We're not talking anymore.
I'm not paying you to talk, I'm not paying
for your opinion.
I'm paying you to drive, so just
get in the car and drive.
Suits me, Bob.
And what is with
this Bob thing?
Aren't you going
to do something?
I am doing something. I'm waiting
for them to move.
For God's sake.
Hi, cows.
Look, I have spent the past 24 hours
in every level of hell,
and I am not going to let
your black and white asses
drag me any further, so if you know what's good
for you, you'll move.
It comes as a real shock to find out
that you speak fluent cow.
Now!
That's right.
Nice cows.
Let's move. Let's move along.
Come on, cows.
Why don't you propose something
to them?
Yeah, you guys are...
Wow, you're big.
We're gonna just...
Oh, yeah,
they're moving now.
Must be your personality.
Yours is a bit
more repellent,
so if you want to try...
That's right. That's how
you get things done.
That's it, girl!
That's right! That is how
you get things done.
You don't just sit around like some
backwoods Irish bumpkin.
You're welcome.
You might want to
just watch your
step.
$600 shoes.
Put them in the wash,
they'll be grand.
Put them in the wash?
The wash?
You do not put
these shoes in the wash.
Whoa! Whoa!
Whoa!
Stop!
Whoa! Wait!
Stop it!
What do I do?
Get in the car
and use the brake!
Baby!
I got you, baby!
I got you!
Baby!
Don't hurt yourself!
Make it stop!
My purse is in there!
Oh, darling.
Oh, Jesus.
My Renault 4!
Look what you done!
What I've done?
You couldn't just
wait for the cows!
You couldn't
just help me?
It's gonna cost at least
200 to tow her out.
That's not gonna come out of my pocket.
It's coming out of yours!
Oh, like hell. You will have to kill me
before I pay you a dime!
There's an idea.
Where you going?
Dublin.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
Look, this is an easy fix.
All we need to do
is find a phone,
call the garage, get a tow,
hop in the car,
back on the road and we'll be in Dublin
in no time.
Just cool the jets,
would you?
Wait! Hey!
I wouldn't
get in there
if I was you!
And I care about
your opinion because...
Fine, go ahead.
All right there, sweetheart?
Hi.
You looking
for a ride?
Yes, I'm going
to Dublin.
In Dublin's fair city
where the girls are so pretty
Yes.
Now there's a coincidence,
'cause I'm going
there myself.
Let me help you with
the old suitcase there.
That's very sweet of you.
Not at all.
And I didn't
even have to ask.
Top of the morning to you!
Oh! Morning.
That's a fancy bit of suitcase,
no mistake.
It's quality. You can see that just by
looking at it, you know?
Well, I'd say
it's been a pleasure,
but I think
we both know that...
Wait. No! Wait! Wait! Come back here!
You can't just...
They...
There you are.
Soon as I finish this,
I'll call us a tow truck.
Us? There is no us.
I am calling a real taxi.
You leave me alone.
Okay, Bob.
Excuse me.
Eoghan?
Eoghan.
Do you have a phone, please?
Please?
Thank you.
Safe home.
Yeah, yeah.
So nice of you to look after
my suitcase,
but I'll take it back.
Thank you.
Is that right, missus?
I'll call the
American ambassador.
Oh, is this his?
Well, I just...
I...
Fun's over, lads.
Give the girl her stuff back.
And who the hell are you?
Nobody. Just keeping the peace.
Yeah? Well, you can keep
your peace out of it.
That was
impressive.
Out.
Fair enough.
Hi. I just...
Should just get my things and go.
Must be something special.
Who?
Your fella.
Jeremy. He is.
He's...
He's a cardiologist.
Hi. When is the next train
to Dublin?
You're just in time.
The next train leaves
in two hours and 43 minutes.
Great.
It's a few bob
to Dublin, mind.
"Bob"?
Cash.
Money. You know?
Hey, fella.
Ballycarbery.
Mmm. Same to you.
There.
Ballycarbery Castle.
It's one of the 10 wonders of Ireland,
so I'm told.
Can only be 15 minutes to the top.
I don't want to
miss the train.
Yeah, well, that's a good point.
Don't miss the train.
No.
Only two and a half hours.
Time is going to fly.
I'll stay here.
Suit yourself.
I will.
Hi.
Declan?
Wait! I love castles.
It's beautiful.
I'm sorry you're not gonna get to Dublin before the shops shut.
I have other interests besides shopping.
I have a life.
A job.
What do you do, then?
I stage apartments.
Stage apartments,
now that's...
That's...
What's that?
Well, when somebody is selling an apartment or a home,
I bring stuff in and make it look
as beautiful as it can look.
And they get to keep all the stuff
when they buy it?
No, I take it away. I'm just presenting them
with the possibilities.
I put a sheen on it.
Hang on. So you do
your job, yeah?
Yeah.
They buy the house,
yeah?
Yeah.
And then you come along and you take all the stuff
away again, yeah?
Yeah.
You're a con artist.
No, I'm not a con...
That's just so typical of you.
You think the worst of everybody.
No.
Oh, no? I'd love to know who you have
a good word for.
I can think of a couple
of good words for you.
Riddle me this.
If your apartment's on fire,
your beautiful apartment,
what would you take?
What?
If your house was on fire
and you had 60 seconds,
what would you take?
Come on.
I...
Come on. Would it be the Chihuahua
on the duvet?
I'm not playing
this game with you.
There you are.
What would you take?
What would you take? Your lovely inn is on fire.
What are you going to take?
You know, your...
Flames coming up the stairs.
You've got 60 seconds.
The bottles of alcohol
in your pub are exploding.
What are you
going to grab?
I know exactly
what I'd "grab."
Oh, yeah? What?
Not telling you.
You can dish it, but you can't
take it, can you?
It's really...
It's a castle!
Told you.
So what's the story
with this place?
Well, hundreds
of years ago,
there was this beautiful girl
called Grainne.
Now, she was promised in marriage to this fella
called Fionn,
who was kind of a cranky old warlord,
old enough to be her father, old enough to be
her grandfather,
and therefore
she wasn't
in love with him.
Anyway, on the night
of their betrothal,
whom did she meet but a handsome
young warrior, Diarmuid.
They fell madly in love at first sight,
but what could she do?
Well, she slips a sleeping potion
in everyone's drinks,
and the pair of them run off together
across the Shannon.
Fionn wakes and there's Grainne gone.
Well, he goes mental.
Takes his army and heads off
in hot pursuit.
But it was the people, you know, the people
in the villages of Ireland,
they took pity on
Diarmuid and Grainne.
They hid them in forests and in their barns
and castles,
where they'd sleep one night
and then they'd move on.
Come on.
Is it safe?
Of course.
Sleep was all they did, 'cause Diarmuid,
good man that he was,
was suffering the old guilt
about two-timing Fionn
and out of respect for him, didn't, you know,
take it any further.
I get it.
Oh, yeah.
And then they came
to this castle
and this view.
Wow.
And 'tis said, you know, that, unable to
resist such beauty,
that here,
in this place, they...
They consummated
their love.
Oh, my God.
You're hitting on me.
I'm what?
I'm the young woman on the eve
of her engagement
that can't resist a handsome stranger?
Oh, come on.
I'm what?
You didn't honestly think
that was gonna work, did you?
Don't flatter yourself, darling.
The story's true,
but it sure as shite
ain't about you.
No?
No, you arrogant...
Arrogant what exactly?
Well, that's a tough one.
Is it American?
Oh, no. The train.
Wait! Wait,
I have a ticket!
I'm very...
You just had to take me
up there, didn't you?
One of the seven
wonders of Ireland!
Okay.
Oh, no.
Well, that speeded
things up a bit.
I hate you.
In the old days, I could have
held it for you,
but it's all "time is money"
nowadays.
Come on, now. Come on, and don't
be worrying yourself.
We'll get you to
where you want to go.
Forecast said sunny.
Here we are. The best little
BQB in Tipperary.
Come in. Come in.
Look what
the cat dragged in.
Oh! My poor dears.
You're lucky,
so you are.
Just half an hour ago, I had two backpackers
at the door
wanting the room.
But they weren't married.
Admitted it right out.
No shame.
So I sent them packing.
Right is right,
rain or no rain.
So, it's Mr. and Mrs...
Brady.
O'Callaghan.
Bradycallaghan.
O'Bradycallaghan.
We're not long married, and it's still quite
a mouthful for an American.
I come from a long,
long line of Dingle
O'Bradycallaghans.
We're praying
that one day
we'll be able to have a son and heir to help
keep the name going.
Anna, Declan to you.
Lovely. Now, let's get you
to your room.
Thank you.
After you, petal.
Thank you, sunshine.
Would you like a hand
with the bag, pumpkin?
Well, you're not sleeping in that bed with me,
Mr. O'Bradycallaghan.
Maybe you're not sleeping
in the bed with me.
Very gallant.
Gallant?
Welcome to the age
of equality.
You lot wanted the vote.
Live with it, darling.
Comfy.
We'll flip for it, darling.
Okay, fair's fair.
Heads I win,
tails you lose.
Heads.
Heads it is.
Shame. You can sleep
in the bath.
It's a shower.
You can sleep
in the shower.
Fine.
Just so long as I don't have to sleep
anywhere near you.
I'm washing in the shower
Getting mud off
Love hot water
Got a bruise there
Wait a minute. You lying,
deceiving son of a...
Get up! Get up.
Get up.
Whoa! What?
Oh! "Heads you win,
tails I lose."
You finally
got that, did you?
Good for you.
Up! Get up! This is my bed.
Liars forfeit.
And take a shower.
You smell.
You can see right
through the curtain.
Can you?
Okay,
liars forfeit,
liars forfeit!
No peeking.
Come in.
Hello, dear.
Everything all right?
Now, for dinner
we've got tripe.
Homemade. Family recipe.
Tripe.
Nothing like a bit of cow's stomach
on a rainy day.
Yum. Did you hear that,
darling? Tripe!
Right, tripe.
I was thinking,
Mrs. O'Docherty,
to thank you for taking us in
on such short notice,
why don't you
let me cook?
No, darling,
I couldn't.
Oh, you could. He's a chef.
He's very good.
It's true!
Really?
Well, that's gas.
We've got two Italians staying, as well.
Would that be okay?
No problem at all!
Thanks a million.
Good call.
What the hell are you doing now?
This recipe says
three medium carrots,
and I just think this one is a little large
to be classified as medium.
And if you look
at these two,
they're clearly medium, while this one
is slightly...
Watch.
Three medium-sized carrots.
You know, I don't think there's anything wrong
with wanting to be precise.
Okay.
Well, then
you must be very,
very precise.
Here's an idea.
Why don't you stop trying to control everything
in the known universe?
It's dinner.
Have a little faith.
It'll all work out.
Heard that one before.
Well, maybe you
should have listened.
Really? You think?
lt'll all work out. My dad was the king
of "it'll all work out."
Time shares in the Bahamas,
mobile video stores,
whatever the next
big nothing was,
all our money
went right after it.
But don't worry.
It'll all work out.
Cut to me working two part-time jobs
after school
and us getting our house repossessed on Christmas Eve.
Ho, ho, ho.
So you will forgive me
if I don't listen.
I'm sorry.
No, I'm sorry.
A father's someone you should be able
to rely on, you know?
Anyway, dinner.
We have got
cabbages, a leek,
three medium carrots.
You're not one of those
vegetarians, are you?
No.
Good.
Declan one,
chicken nil.
Sweet.
Coq au vin?
What?
Give me strength.
Don't start telling me that you've never had
chicken stew before.
Of course I have.
I'm wondering where it is that you think
chickens come from.
The freezer section.
I know, I know. I...
You just surprised me.
You keep doing that.
Give me the carrots.
Yes, carrots.
Sorry.
We build up the temperature
a little bit.
You don't need to chop them.
It's hard to hold.
That smells amazing.
Good girl. And...
So this is what you call staging,
is it?
Sort of.
Not too shabby.
Here?
Yeah.
Impeccable.
The chicken
was wonderful.
Wasn't it? And I'm usually
awful at chicken.
Jeremy always says
I make it too dry.
Jeremy?
Jeremy. Our...
Our next door neighbor.
Who sometimes
comes by for dinner.
Right, Declan?
Mmm. Yeah, yeah.
He's a lovely old soul.
Yeah.
A little bit learning difficulties,
you know.
Tells everyone he's a cardiologist.
It's a scream.
But he's a happy chap,
you know.
He's got a little thing,
bless him, for her.
Antique, Frank?
Antique, yeah. Like me.
Wedding present,
they were.
It's only 44 years,
you cheeky rascal!
See?
That's what it takes
to be married for 44 years.
The kiss.
Always kiss like it's the first time
and the last time.
Grand.
Well, come on then, son.
Show us old ones
how it's done.
Sorry?
Well, I've kissed
my wife.
Stefano has certainly
kissed his wife.
No, we're fine. We did it
earlier, kiss.
Done and dusted.
A bit of chivalry, man.
You know what I'm saying?
Oh! That's perfect.
If that was a kiss, I'm surprised you're still
wed to him at all.
No, no, they're shy,
that's all.
Yes. Really shy.
You're among friends!
You're young,
married, in love!
Anyone can see that.
Damn it, man.
Kiss the girl!
Bravo!
There you go.
Now that's a kiss!
It's quite wet.
Show a little mercy,
would you?
All right.
But one snore and you're back
in the shower.
Great.
Who'd have thought it'd take two days
to get to Dublin?
I have to charge you
an overnighter, by the way.
Surprise.
€100.
Fifty.
Seventy-five it is.
Running total €675.
Fine.
If it's all about money
for you, then 675 it is.
Good night.
Night.
I'm so sorry
I'm not there yet.
You can't imagine
what I've been through.
Worse than when they lost
our luggage in Barbados?
Like that times 10.
I just... I just
can't wait to see you.
Well, maybe this
will cheer you up.
I just heard from the board,
and we got the apartment!
What?
Yeah.
I just got off the phone
with Edith. It's ours.
Ah! Jeremy!
That is exactly what I needed
to hear this morning.
Everything is working out for us.
I'm so excited.
We'll have to celebrate in person
when you get here.
We sure will.
Hurry up already.
I miss you.
I miss you, too.
Morning.
Yeah.
Oh, is this for me?
Morning, lovebirds!
Sleep well, did you?
Yes, thank you.
So, what's on
the agenda today, then?
Mmm. Off to Dublin
for me.
Well, you can't
do that now.
Why not?
This is Sunday.
Never start a journey on a Sunday,
or a full moon.
Oh, well, I don't believe
in that superstition stuff.
How are you on train timetables?
Do you believe in them?
Sunday.
No trains.
No trains?
No.
Oh! For God's sake.
I have to be in Dublin by the 20th.
That's tomorrow.
Why is that
again, darling?
Fine. Okay.
Frank,
you have a car,
don't you?
Oh, yes.
Yes.
Okay. I could...
I would be willing to pay you
a substantial amount of money
if you would
maybe drive me.
No.
Oh! It's not
the money, girl.
It's Eileen.
She's got it.
Gone to Mass.
Then the weekly shop,
you know.
Okay, well, then
when she's back, you...
She won't be back
till all hours.
Why?
It's a fair old jaunt
to Dublin.
Where is she?
Dublin.
Bingo!
What?
Bus station's
that way.
What?
Knock it off.
It's hailstones.
Are you serious?
Ow!
Run!
Come on. It's fecking
Murphy's Law with you.
Come on!
I got Louis.
Don't worry.
Those sting!
The size
of golf balls!
Jesus Christ!
Is Lord.
Have you any just cause or impediment why
this man and this woman
should not be joined together
in holy matrimony?
No, no, Father.
You carry on.
I'm sure that they know
what they're doing.
Good. In that case, you're very welcome.
Why don't you sit down?
Come on. Dublin. We should
be making tracks.
No.
The priest is gonna
give us a ride
to the bus station
when it's over.
We can walk!
I'm not walking another four hours
in these shoes.
Besides, look how beautiful
it all is.
I kind of
hate weddings.
Why? Because people are in love?
That's so offensive to you?
Yeah.
You know,
you have all of these random opinions
and a bad attitude.
What do you know? You're clearly
not married,
and you have obviously
never been engaged.
Actually, I have.
Once.
I don't want to
interrupt a good party,
but I want to say
thank you to my husband.
I want to say, may you never steal,
lie or cheat.
But if you must steal,
then steal away
my sorrows.
And if you must lie,
lie with me all the nights
of my life.
And if you must cheat,
then please cheat death,
because I couldn't
live a day without you.
Cheers!
Are you all right?
Grand. You know,
it's just hot in there.
Do you want
to talk about it?
Listen,
Bob.
You're not
in America now.
You're in Ireland.
So, have a drink.
Shut up.
I was just
trying to help.
Help?
Yeah.
That's hilarious.
The woman who's so desperate, she's diddly-eying
her way to Dublin,
making the most important decision
of her life
based on some
ridiculous tradition,
which, frankly,
is a load of old poo.
So, thank you, but it's not I
who needs the help, okay?
It is not a load of poo.
It's romantic.
It's really,
really romantic.
I'm not good
at weddings.
They're better with
a couple martinis.
Okay, thank you very much!
We're going to do a special request
now for the bridesmaids.
Want a go?
No. No, I don't...
I don't Riverdance.
Do you never let
your hair down, woman?
Yes.
In my way, I do.
Good.
Now, this is an easy one. You'll pick it up.
Just follow them.
We're going in a circle
going that way.
No, no,
put me down!
I'm really sorry.
I was spinning.
Forget about it. At least
it wasn't my husband.
Yeah. Right.
At least it wasn't him.
I'm...
I thought
I was bad at weddings.
Aren't you supposed to be
taking me to Dublin?
Well, just tell me when. As ever,
your servant awaits.
You know what,
Declan?
Do you know
what you are?
You're a beast.
You're a real
beast.
And I cannot
stand you.
Really?
But you know what?
I'm onto you.
Is that right?
All your beastishness
is like...
It's an act.
It's a great, big,
massive cover-up.
And you growl and you snap,
but you are in...
You're in pain.
And you've got a...
You've got a big thorn
in your beasty paw.
Like a lion.
A lovely, lovely lion.
Great.
I'm sorry.
That's romantic.
Up you come. Up!
God, you're a lump.
My suitcase!
Don't worry about Louis.
I'll get him.
You're joking me.
Perfect.
You can deduct the coffee
from my bill.
Deduct away. Don't forget to add on
for a new pair of shoes,
Pukey.
Put them in the wash,
they'll be grand.
You missed your bus.
There's another one
in 20 minutes.
Oh, God. Am I still
coming with you?
I am paying you
to take me to Dublin
and you're taking me
to Dublin.
That's fine.
Thank you.
He's out.
I left a message
with the front desk.
So, Dublin.
Right on time.
So I suppose
I should pay you.
I suppose you should.
There'll be an ATM
at the hotel.
Right, so I'll be
portering again, will I?
Not if you don't
want to.
I didn't say that.
We can get a cab.
You've got legs,
haven't you, woman?
My best feature,
so I'm told.
Who told you that?
It's a beautiful city.
And I haven't seen
one backstabbing snake.
Yeah, well, it's the chancers
and cheats that you have to watch out for.
She's here,
isn't she?
In Dublin. One of the chancers and cheats.
The blonde in the photo.
Who was the guy?
So him and her...
Right.
Sorry.
We were all running the Caragh together, me, Kaleigh, Ryan.
So we bought the pub and built it up from nothing.
We really got it going.
I mean, we were flying.
And I thought that me and Kaleigh
were mad for each other.
Apparently not.
So that thing I'd grab
if I had 60 seconds,
it's my mother's
Claddagh ring.
You know, the ones with the two hands
holding the crowned heart.
Well, she's got it.
Well, you're here now. You should find her
and get it back.
I don't know.
It's your mother's ring.
Anyway, I thought
it was your ring
we were meant to be
worrying about.
Diddly-eye.
Oh, yeah. Right.
Well, I'm glad to see
you're finally on board.
It has nothing to do with me. I'm just the old bag carrier
around here.
Why should I care?
So you don't?
Would it make
a difference?
Come on.
So.
Here.
Nah, it's okay.
Declan, take it.
We had a deal. Please?
Tell you what. Why don't you just give me that one bob
and we'll call it a day?
Which one bob?
The one we flipped
for the bed.
Yeah.
Liar.
Well, best of luck.
Yeah.
So long, Louis.
Anna.
Yes?
Anna! Anna!
Hi! Finally. God.
I thought I was gonna have to call a helicopter rescue team
to come get you.
Where have you been? Hi.
Hey.
Long story.
Sorry.
It's good
to see you.
You okay? Yeah?
Mmm. Yeah.
Hi.
I'm sorry,
do I know you?
Jeremy, this is Declan.
Declan drove...
He helped me get
from Dingle to Dublin.
Oh! Okay. Yeah, yeah, yeah. Yeah, well,
I don't envy that job.
This lady is not
big on adventure.
No.
Nice to meet you, bro.
Nice to meet you.
Yeah. Yeah.
So did she
take care of you?
Did you tip him?
She paid me.
Great. Well, thanks for
getting her home safe.
Oh, God, I missed you! I missed you!
I missed you! I missed you!
I missed you, too.
No, I really
missed you.
I did. And...
And it got me thinking.
Why aren't we married?
Will you marry me?
Are you serious?
Am I serious? Yeah. Well, I'm down
on my knee. I...
I got this.
No pressure,
but it's all on camera.
Sweetheart.
Sweetie?
I... Were you supposed
to give me an answer?
Yes. Of course.
Yeah?
Yes.
Okay.
Let's try this on.
Ah! It fits!
I have champagne
waiting in the room,
so we should go on up.
Great.
Thank you.
I never thought
I'd see you in Dublin.
Declan.
Kaleigh.
There you go. And there's pints.
They're on the way.
Thank you!
You are saving the pub.
You're keeping the pans in the kitchen.
I will kiss you later.
Congratulations! Hi!
Let me see it!
Dekko.
Tom. There you are.
You're short.
But not by much.
Sorry. Come on, lads!
Oh, my God,
look at this place!
Do you like it?
Do I like it?
I want to throw you out of your own window
and take it.
Hold on a minute there.
You can show us the color of your wallet for a change.
That's all.
Drinks on the house!
I feel like your whole happy ending
is gonna be a real test
for our friendship.
I'm pretty sure she would
have been happy
with just this apartment. I don't think you needed to propose.
Oh! It was kind of
a package deal.
Really?
What, buy an apartment,
they throw in a ring?
More like
the other way around.
What do you mean?
Well, I think it was
Edith, from the board.
She called me in Dublin, probing about
our marital status.
Can you believe that? Nothing specific,
just interested, you know?
Like the residents, they're kind of old-fashioned
when it comes to issues like this.
Blah, blah, blah.
I got the message. Married, you're in.
Unmarried, you're not.
So I just said we were hours away
from getting engaged.
I just said it and it came out.
And I don't know where it came from,
but I could almost hear them
cutting our keys.
So I put down the phone
and thought,
"Well, why the hell not, you know?"
Really?
Sure. I mean,
we'd have gotten around
to it eventually, right?
Right. Of course.
Yeah.
Oh, Libby, I want
to show you this view.
Yeah.
It's gorgeous.
Okay.
Is that the fire alarm?
Really?
Okay, everybody, I guess we'd better take
this party downstairs.
The phones.
Where is the remote
for this thing?
These things are useless
without the remote. Anna!
Do you have
everything you need?
Can you just look
around for valuables?
For laptops,
cameras, whatever.
I think the cameras... Okay, here's
the video camera.
I still haven't put the proposal
up on Facebook,
so let me get that.
Oh, sweetie,
can you get the...
Anna?
We have one minestrone soup,
two quiche,
one pie beef, one pie chicken,
one green salad. Go, go, go.
Dekko?
A customer said
the chicken's dry.
The what's what?
The chicken.
It's dry.
It's a pie.
It's delicious.
Alex, you're in charge.
Don't blow anything up.
All right, which one of you bollockses thinks
my chicken's dry?
You?
Me.
What the hell
are you doing here?
Could you maybe be nice
for just a second?
I did fly 3,000 miles
to get here.
Is Jeremy with you?
What? No! No.
Jeremy and I...
It didn't work out.
Sorry.
Well,
when my 60 seconds
came around, I realized
I had everything
I ever wanted
but nothing
I really needed.
And I think that
what I need is here.
And I came all this way to see if maybe
you might think so, too.
And if you do...
Well, I don't really have any plans past that,
which is new for me.
So,
Declan O'Callaghan,
and I should probably
learn your middle name,
here is my proposal.
I propose
we not make plans.
I propose we give
this thing a chance
and let it work out
how it works out.
So what do you say?
Do you want to
not make plans with me?
I guess
that's an Irish no.
Mrs. O'Bradycallaghan.
Where the hell
are you going?
You said no.
I didn't say no.
I didn't say anything.
You walked away.
I was getting something.
Really? That was
a good time
to go get something?
Well, yeah,
it was, actually.
I was getting this.
You big idiot.
I wouldn't be
holding this ring
if it weren't for you.
I reject your proposal.
I don't want to
not make plans with you.
I want to make
plans with you.
You do?
Yeah. I do.
Will you marry me?
In all my life, I never thought
I'd see you down on one knee.
Yeah, it's getting
a bit damp down here, so...
What's it to be,
Anna from Boston?
Yes.
Yes, I will.
I'm so relieved.
For a minute there,
I thought I wasn't gonna have a place
to stay tonight.
What?
You think
you're staying
with me?
This might cost you.
Put it on my bill.
Would you
look at that!
On a Sunday, no less. It's good luck to get
engaged on a Sunday.
And end a journey.
Aye, and dig a well.
Idiot! Do they look like
they're digging a well?
You know what
I'm talking about.
I never know
what you're talking about.
Are you sure
she's gonna make it?
Remember,
she's a classic.
And she's good as new,
even after some crazy woman tried to
push her off the road.
I didn't try to
push her off the road!
I was scraping
cow poo off my shoe
'cause some rude man wouldn't help me
with the cows.
Only because someone was being pigheaded
and couldn't wait.
Shut up.
There you are.
Right.
Where to?
Just drive.
You got it, Bob.
Wait a minute.
Where's Louis?
Louis? He's fine.
Strapped him to the roof.
You strapped him to the roof?
He'll get filthy up there.
Don't worry.
We'll throw him in the wash.
He'll be grand.