Empty your mind.
No distraction.
No emotion.
Only calm and clarity.
The Yoroi Bitsu.
Our most sacred chest.
The only remaining object
of the last Koga Ninja.
It is the only final
resting place for the
weapons of ninja warriors
through the ages.
The powers they
hold are legendary.
Each piece with it's own story,
Handed down from
generation to generation...
for a thousand years.
They were created for
one purpose only.
Sudden and violent death.
With these weapons,
the ninja became...
Much more than
a mere warrior.
He become the most supreme
of the lethal dissilience.
And used them for profit
and wars.
It became an art as
pure, as it was ruthless.
Over the years...
The Ninja forged,
the deadliest poisons,
With only one antidote...
They held the power of life,
and death.
Tradition says...
That the Shinobu Katana Sword
has the power to take life.
But in the hands of
a true Koga ninja.
He has the power
to restore a life's spirit.
The Yoroi Bitsu, and and it's secrets
were pushed from the battlefield,
into the imagination.
But hidden from sight...
safe in this ancient school,
A single Yoroi Bitsu survived
and the secret of
the ninja lived on...
transforming the
disciplines of death...
into Budo... a martial
art of enlightenment.
- Masazuka.
- Yes!
- Casey!
Casey-san. Water?
Thanks, Kiko.
You are always working so late
more than anyone else.
I guess I'm not so
good at sitting still.
And not so good
at boasta, neither.
Well your father seems
to think I have potential.
So does someone else.
You know, we don't have
time for such things in the Dojo.
No. We don't.
I better get back.
It must have been
very painful, for you.
- It was in the past.
- The past...
Defines a man...
Tradition, heritage...
Your parents.
What's your point?
We have traditions.
What do you have?
A letter and a
photo from a mother,
who abandoned
her only child.
a memory of a drunk father,
who killed himself.
Masazuka!
- Casey!
- Yes!
- Masazuka!
- Yes.
Masazuka!
Sensei.
Sensei!
Welcome... brothers.
Tonight, we come together...
for another initiation ceremony.
As our ranks and power
continue to grow.
Throughout time society...
has searched for guides
from select groups of people.
Leaders, we call them.
Men of vision and action.
Do you willingly
accept the bond?
This historic agreement, lays
a foundation for a pipeline
that will reach all the
way to the Bering Strait.
Experts who believe,
that the merger of these
two Russian companies
will create sufficient capital
to win the bid
for the project.
Mr Klimitov will make a statement,
once the contract has been signed.
Please. Whatever you want
I'll give it.
Ladies and gentlemen of the press,
thank you for your patience.
In a few minutes will get a
statement from, Mr Klimitov.
Thank you.
- Tell me some good news.
- Keep watching.
Mr. Klimitov should be exiting
the theatre any moment now.
We should have a
statement, for you shortly.
Wait a minute! Wait a minute!
Something...
He's bleeding, what appears
to be from his neck.
Chaos. There's total
chaos here at Vladivostok.
Yuri Klimitov,
a Russian oil mogul,
appears to be injured.
As promised, no more merger.
- Cheers, gentlemen.
- Yes, cheers!
Greetings friends and honoured
guests from abroad.
It is a day... we recognise
by displaying a highest honour,
a sacred treasure...
of our ninja ancestry...
The Yoroi Bitsu.
After 30 years as Soke,
I must now, name a successor.
The Yoroi Bitsu must be taken
to the other side of the world.
To be guarded.
Hidden from sight.
There is a man, a scholar,
the only person I trust,
to keep it's power
from falling into
the hands of Masazuka.
Sensei.
Namiko,
You see, the Dean is
a close personal friend.
Considering the safety we need,
I thought it wise to store
it in the university vault.
This way.
So tell me, Casey,
How does a young
man like yourself...
- end up in a Japanese Dojo?
- You mean a white guy?
Well you don't exactly
fit the demographic profile.
Well, okay.
My father was a marine.
He was stationed in Okinawa,
so me and my mother,
moved there with him.
But they didn't get along to well.
She ended up leaving.
The problem was...
- She didn't take me with her.
- Oh, I'm sorry to hear that.
You see, my dad, uh...
He was a drunk.
I guess she couldn't take it any more,
He finally drank himself of the end
of a cliff in a car, when I was twelve..
So anyway a friend of the
family took me to see Sensei
rather than let them
ship me off to an orphanage
and... that's
where I stayed.
I haven't looked back since.
Masazuka.
I remember the day I met
Takada Sensei in Japan.
His technical skills were amazing.
Well I hope we
can just close the deal.
Press is already here.
I'll get back to you.
Mr. Temple, what is your reaction
to the pipeline murders in Russia?
It's a tragedy.
Isn't it true that Temple Oil shares
are up by 20 percent since,
that deal fell through?
So is the stock market.
Is there a correlation to that to?
But they were your competitors...
These were well respected men and
their deaths are a threat to all of us.
I'm willing to pledge
10 million dollars...
to anyone who can
bring in these killers.
What about the police
sources who say this is another
In a chain of killings involving
an organization called "The Ring".
I can't comment on something
I'm not familiar with.
Isn't it true, your company
has benefited each time.
I'm sorry. I gotta take this.
A friend? Didn't expect
to hear from you.
Always a pleasure
doing business with you.
Now, I must ask you
to do a job for me.
Namiko, did you
try your father again?
Still no answer.
He should be there.
I... Don't understand.
- You looking for Rebecca?
- Yes.
Are you her friend?
Sort of, she, uh...
She knew my parents.
She had a stroke.
She past away a few months ago.
I'm sorry.
Ah, Casey. Good to see you back.
Afraid, I'm just
on my way to bed.
Namiko's is still up.
I'll see you in the morning.
- Okay. Good night, Professor.
- Good night.
Did you find her?
I guess she's been
sick for a while.
Who's there?
Get down!
You know why I'm here.
Where's the box?
Are you okay?
Come on.
Go!
We need a room.
- Time's up!
- Give me five more minutes!
What?
Please.
Let's get you warm.
Rui... Akira...
- Professor.
- I know, I know.
You heard what they wanted.
- Masazuka.
- Yeah.
If he knows where we are...
That means my father...
No, no. We don't
know that yet.
Listen to me. We
don't know that yet.
The victim is Dr Paul Garrison,
He was a professor, author,
lecturer, specialist
on the far east.
We got any suspects?
Oh, yeah.
One, Namiko Takeda...
and Casey Bowman.
Still no answer.
We just keep trying.
Although we no
official confirmation...
sources tell us, it was
a gang-land style hit.
Witnesses claim
there were several victims,
including the professor.
Can we go to the police?
Police are searching for two suspects,
who were seen fleeing the scene.
A male
Caucasian, a female Asian
reportedly in their mid-twenties,
and are considered armed
and extremely dangerous.
We have to tell
them about, Masazuka.
He wasn't even there.
And people are dead.
The police... no.
They could hold on
to us, for a long time.
You heard Garrison. The Dean
knows we put something in that safe.
Pretty soon, somebody's
gonna make a connection.
- So?
- We have to move the Yoroi Bitsu.
Tomorrow.
It's okay.
We'll get through this.
Namiko?
The girl I was with,
have you seen her?
Two coffee's please
and two sandwiches.
Okay.
Hey, what are you doing?
Getting us some food.
- Sandwiches are coming up.
- Thank you.
Let me get you some sugar.
Down!
Don't shoot us!
- Come on!
- Remember. We need her alive.
Subway!
Subway.
Hey, excuse me!
Masazuka.
They could be
working for him.
Come on.
Police! Hands up!
Put your hands on your head!
Masazuka.
You have, what
I asked for, or not?
Tell our colleague,
what happened.
We found them, but
they didn't have the box.
- Where are they?
- The police arrested them.
I asked...
Where?
West 54 precinct.
But there's no way
we can get to them.
Pray I find them...
Or your next.
What are you doing in this country?
I was visiting a friend.
- The dead professor?
- Yes.
Why'd you kill him?
- I didn't.
- Then why'd you run?
Because we had to.
Those men wanted to kill us!
- Really?
- Hmm.
You have no idea what
you're dealing with here.
I'm all ears.
Sir, can I help you?
I'm here for, Namiko Takeda.
She was arrested earlier today.
- I'm her attorney.
- Okay, send him in.
I'll meet him
in my office.
- Your lawyer just showed up.
- My lawyer?
That's quite a story, Casey.
So, your saying that
this Masazuka guy,
who nobody's
seen or heard of.
or who may have heard,
is on your trail
is after you to...
retrieve a box?
The Yoroi Bitsu.
Right.
So where is it?
I can't tell you that.
Why not?
It's him. Masazuka, he's here.
I'll send him your regards.
Hey, don't leave me like this.
Hey!
Hey, what's going on?
Jesus Christ, lady. We're just
trying to get you out of here.
God! Let's go.
Let's go.
Hey, hey lady!
- On the ground!
- Where is she?
I said get on the ground!
What do you think
is happening here?
Get down, or I'll
put you down.
Some fairy tale, huh?
- Just let her go.
- Not before I kill you.
No!
Where is she?
Who did you call, your source?
Nobody.
- Who did you call?
- It's just a number to keep in contact!
I don't know who's
on the other end!
Wait! Wait!
I'll tell you where you
can find him, okay?
I'm listening.
Welcome... brothers.
We control the life and
blood of this planet.
A dedicated "Ring of Brothers".
Kill him!
Come on, stop him!
- Masazuka.
- Casey?
Where is she?
Very close.
If you've hurt her,
I swear to God...
Listen to me.
I want the Yoroi Bitsu.
Okay. You'll get it...
for Namiko.
Construction site of 49th
and church at 3am.
How many more of you?
Two.
I'm sorry, guys.
Freeze!
Is that the box?
You should believe me now.
Let's take a ride down town.
No. I'm gonna give
you what you want.
You're gonna let me do,
what I have to do.
Masazuka! Let her go!
Not until I get the Yoroi Bitsu.
Don't, Casey!
It's all yours.
Now, let her go.
49th and church.
Masazuka and Casey.
I want them both dead.
What you have, is mine.
So, come and get it.
Go! Go!
Get down!
You need this,
to keep her alive.
No!
Yes.
Such anger.
This the police,
drop your weapons.
Put your hands in the air
and lay down on the ground.
Again, drop your weapons.
Put your hands in the air
and lay down on the ground.
Namiko.
I'm sorry.
I can't save you.
I love you!
I've always loved you.
Tradition says...
that the Shinobu Katana Sword
possesses both, the power to take life
and also the life's spirit,
the power to heal.
The power to heal.
Namiko. Drink.
Drink.
Come back to me.
Namiko.
This is one hell of
a mess here, Casey.
It's gonna take day's... hell,
maybe even weeks
to clean this up.
Not that it really
matters anymore, does it?
The main thing is,
"The Ring's" broken.
Temple's in custody.
Then there's you two...
Your late for your plane.
Now get the hell out
of here, permanently.
Edited and synced by Scooby
Thanks to Florin
for the sub.