- Good morning, Miss Perky.
- Watch out, Miss Perky.
You missed!
- I've been waiting and waiting.
- Sorry.
- Every time we do this, we get caught.
- We ain't gonna get caught this time.
- If my mom f'inds out--
- She won't.
- She always f'inds out.
- That's why I'm glad I don't got a mom.
All right. Don't look.
- Why not?
- 'Cause they're hardly wearing nothing.
Come on, Billy Bob.
I never heard of one law...
says you can't watch two girls
reading magazines.
Are you so, so excited about the party?
If Billy Bob pays any attention to me.
I thought Billy Bob held your hand
at the picture show.
I thought he was going to,
but he didn't.
I think Preacher likes you.
Really?
Why do you think he gave you
that stuffed squirrel,Janice?
Maybe he just wanted to get rid of it.
Janice, what did l just say?
Stuffed squirrel.
He likes me.
- We're gonna get caught.
- No, we won't.
Hey, little brother.
- We didn't do nothing, Butch.
- You're in our f'ield, little brother.
- Since when is this your f'ield?
- Since we staked our claim.
You wanna get through,
you gotta pay a toll.
- We ain't paying you nothing.
- You don't gotta pay...
but if you wanna pass...
you gotta eat the head.
- Don't do it, Preach.
- Shut up, Billy Bob.
That was great!
What'd it taste like?
That was good.
That was the greatest thing ever.
You made Butch throw up.
So what'd it taste like?
It tasted like--
It tasted like f'ish!
How many times?
Lionel, how many times?
Always with the shortcuts.
There are no shortcuts in life, Lionel.
Lover, I'm talking to you, baby,
but I can see you're not listening.
I assure you, my dove,
I hear every euphonious word...
every golden syllable.
Excuse me, miss.
Can we help you?
I require more help than you gentlemen
could possible provide...
at your tender age.
But could you help my husband get us
the heck out of here?
Pumpkin, help has arrived.
Good day, young gentlemen.
Where in God's green Earth are we?
I'm telling you, Preacher,
I didn't hold her hand.
- I heard her say you did.
- I didn't!
You held her hand!
Preacher,just shut up.
Hi, Mr. Dixon, Mr. Trump.
We're hoping they took a look
at them crazy saucers out there...
because most experts agree
that they probably don't exist.
We're getting a lot of reports
on them from all over the country.
That's the news.
Let's get back to some more music.
Preach, look at this. '''Stan 'The Man'
Musial continues to struggle...
as the Cardinals lose a heartbreaker
to the Brooklyn Dodgers.''
Things keep on like this, we might
as well forget that trip to the Series.
Stan'll pull through, Preach, and come
October, we'll be right there...
eating Red Hots
and watching the Birds take it all.
You ever seen anything
like that, Preach?
You ever seen anything like this?
You really don't care what God says
when he looks down on you, do you?
You can't go ripping up
other people's property.
You boys...
don't be hiding back there
like a couple of criminals.
You have something you wanna confess?
Happy birthday, son.
Thirteen.
Off'icially makes you a man.
- Thanks, Mr. Dixon.
- Thanks, Mr. Dix.
- Can you make mine cherry instead?
- You licked it, Preacher.
Just barely.
Oh, my gosh, my party!
Banana-- it's just great.
Come on, Preach!
Don't slam that--
All right. Billy Bob's coming out
to pitch for the Cardinals.
Here he goes.
Jackie Robinson, and--
Strike one!
- Right here, Preacher.
- Preacher's famous knuckler.
- Gets him!
- How about a high-rising fastball?
Here we go, girls.
My special three-layer cake...
and all the tutti-frutti you can eat.
Cora Mae,Janice,
I know those ant bites are painful...
but you mustn't scratch.
- Yes, Ms. Murphy.
- I don't want it to get dirty.
What's it matter? lt's gonna
get dirty sooner or later.
I wanna keep it clean.
Is that all right with you?
Here's Billy Bob throwing his famous
fastball to Preacher Star.
Preacher knocks it out of the county.
When do you suppose those boys
will outgrow this baseball foolishness?
Boys, the Picken's County Flower Show
is less than one month off.
I'd hate to be in your place
if I have to go there empty-handed.
- Thanks a lot, Malcolm.
- There goes our clean ball.
- Go get it, Malcolm.
- Malcolm, wait.
Let the 5:00 pass.
Madam, are you
the adult of the house?
- Why, yes.
- My, what lovely roses.
Roses are so elegant and romantic.
- Don't you think?
- I do, yes.
Madam, I am Miss LilyJane Bobbit--
Miss Bobbit--
from Memphis, Tennessee.
Country children.
My mother and I have taken rooms here.
Would you be so kind
as to point out the house?
It belongs to a Mrs. Sawyer.
Why, that's it right there.
Thank you.
Excuse me, miss.
Being such a hot day and all...
wouldn't you like to rest a spell
and have some tutti-frutti?
Yes, by all means,join us.
Very fattening, tutti-frutti.
But may I see you kindly?
Come along, Mommy.
My mother has
a disorder of the tongue...
so it is necessary
that l speak for her.
She has made dresses
for the society of many cities...
including Memphis and Tallahassee.
No doubt you've noticed and admired...
the dress that I wear
before you this afternoon.
Every stitch of it
was hand sewn by my mother.
She can copy any pattern
and just recently won...
a $25 prize
from the Ladies'HomeJournal.
Please, advise your friends
and family.
Thank you.
Hello.
May I help you?
Step lightly.
From the get-go,
I don't allow smoking...
drinking or swearing.
- Hey, Speedy Thorne.
- Hey, Elinore.
I heard it was somebody
around here's birthday.
It's a bat.
Stan ''The Man'' Musial model.
That's right.
- Thanks, Speedy. It's perfect.
- You're welcome.
Boys, it's summertime.
You coming back to work for me, or what?
Yeah, we are. Only four months,
one week and two days till the Series.
I haven't given you permission
to go, son.
That's something we'll discuss
based on your behavior...
for the next four months,
one week and two days.
- Come on up and have some cake, Speedy.
- All right.
Girls, boys, have some more
tutti-frutti. Cheer up, girls.
Watch out, Reverend.
Okay, I'll tell my wife.
Thank you.
Son, don't give me that--
I hate that stufF.
- Mr. Trump.
- What?
You want to inherit my farm,
you better start showing me...
a little aptitude for the farming
business, you hear me?
Good morning, sir.
I am Miss LilyJane Bobbit.
Good morning, young lady.
I'm Pastor Daniel Williams.
I notice you have a small tatter
on your front.
As the spiritual leader
of this community...
you really ought to be flawless
in dress as well as decorum.
Well, I serve the Lord,
not high fashion.
Here you are.
- Your little girl lend you her bike?
- My wife's, Mr. Trump.
- I hope so.
- Good morning.
Much obliged, little lady.
Ma'am.
Good morning.
May I hand you one of these flyers?
Thank you, ma'am.
- Morning, Mr. Trump.
- Rosalba.
Hi, Mr. Trump.
Can we give you a hand with that?
Take these grain bags and throw them
in the back of my pickup there.
- Never mind.
- No, you don't.
Six of these... right in there.
Thank you very much.
- She went this way, right?
- Yeah, I think so.
No, wait. She went this way.
Follow me, Janice.
There she is.
Hey, look who's here.
l just hate it when handsome young men
follow me around the countryside.
Young gentlemen...
would you happen to have an automotive
repair facility here in fair Meadow?
We got the best, mister.
It's Speedy himself
over at Speedy's Garage.
- He's a war hero.
- A war hero auto mechanic named Speedy?
By golly, that's someone
I would dearly love to meet.
- She went that way.
- In case you were wondering.
- Who went which way?
- Yeah, what are you talking about?
Do we look like we just fell ofF
a turnip truck?
- What's that for?
- Under the present circumstances...
I don't feel it's proper to have this
sitting in my bedroom any longer.
And I really don't care if I ever lay
eyes on you again, Billy Bob Murphy.
- I'll go get it.
- No, leave it.
All right.
All right. Here we go.
So you're up four.
Let's shuffle them up good.
You'll be seeing double
by the time we leave.
- May I join you?
- Ma'am.
-Jeb, make room for the lady.
- Why me?
Get out of here.
Stay close, Jeb.
Gambling scares me.
Could you teach me how to play
that game? Dominoes?
Why, sure.
Well, Mr. Speedy...
what's the good word?
I replaced the fan belt.
But I think the real problem is
your battery's not holding a charge.
Is that so?
If you want my advice, you should
get you a new one as soon as you can.
You are the expert, Mr. Speedy,
so I shall take your advice.
- You want me to get on that?
- My brother is also a f'ine mechanic.
He gets very upset with me when I
take my automotive business elsewhere...
so because of family loyalty,
I'm afraid I'm gonna have to wait.
- You understand?
- You bet.
Yeah.
Lovely young thing.
Is this your beloved
or the other gentleman?
You mind putting that down?
Sports star, war hero...
f'irst-class, top-notch
automobile repairman.
Mr. Speedy, you have lived
an exciting life.
Baby doll, I think it's about time
we leave, don't you?
We're on our way, my dear.
I assume it's okay if I draw a check
from my personal bank in Birmingham?
I suppose that'd be all right.
That's $3 for the belt and labor.
- Bye-bye.
- Come and see us now, you hear?
Ma'am.
My goodness, Speedy.
You're quite busy.
It's all them old cars from
before the war breaking down.
Bad for the owners,
but it's good for me.
l'm even thinking about expanding.
You just let me know if there's
anything else I can do for you.
Indeed I shall, my friend.
Until we meet again.
Ma'am.
How you doing, honey?
Fine, thank you.
Who are they?
I believe those are the Quinces
from Birmingham.
I see.
I told you the battery's bad.
- Are the boys still here?
- They done their jobs and gone.
I paid them 50 cents apiece.
That was awfully kind of you.
The thought of turning those two loose
on the city of St. Louis...
I hate to think.
I wouldn't worry.
I don't reckon the Cards have much of
a chance with the way things are going.
Seems the boys got a crush
on your new little neighbor.
You caught that too, did you?
I told them they're
going about it all wrong.
I gave them some good advice
on how to woo women.
Well, l best get on home.
You ever feel like staying?
Twenty-f'ive cents an hour.
Anytime you want.
I'll surely think about that.
Would you focus on this game?
For heaven's sake!
Morning,Juliana.
How are you this morning?
Elinore, I'm sure there's
a logical explanation for all this.
I don't want an explanation, Speedy.
I want my roses.
Speedy Thorne,
what is that siren all about?
Oh, Mildred, it's awful.
It's just simply awful.
Elinore's roses--
her beautiful roses-- stolen!
Oh, shoot.
Nobody stole them roses.
Preacher and your Billy Bob brought them
over to young Bobbit this morning...
before they started my yard work.
I hope that boy's got on
his running shoes.
Look at me!
How dare you!
Come on! Come look at what you did!
How could you do that?
Son?
No. You treat me like a baby.
You act like a baby, I'll treat you
like one. Now come down.
I ain't never coming down.
I swear it!
Suit yourself.
That appears to be the only way
l'll get any peace around here.
And you can forget that trip
to St. Louis.
Fine! Cardinals stink anyway.
My thoughts are castles
My friends are my dreams
Please come down and eat.
I don't want any supper.
I'm gonna stay up here all night.
Son...
sometimes in the heat of the moment...
we say things that later
we realize we just did not mean.
That was very gracious of you and your
friend to bring those lovely roses.
- It wasn't nothing.
- I'm not sure your mama would agree.
The thing is...
my daddy gave her those rose bushes
before he went off to the war.
When he didn't come back,
she decided that every year...
she'd enter those roses
in a flower show.
I reckon I ruined it
for her this year...
not to mention
my trip to the World Series.
From where I'm standing,
there's only one thing to be done.
You must make moral restitution,
Billy Bob.
I don't know what that means,
but if you think it'll help--
You have to do something right
to cancel out the wrong.
What's needed here is a symbol
of your grief and regret...
at this unfortunate incident.
Yeah.
Dang! I'd sure like to buy anything.
The stores are all closed.
Perhaps if we both sleep on it...
we'll come up with
a proper solution by morning.
I'll
Be seeing you
In all the old familiar places
That this heart of mine
Embraces
All day through
In
- Mom?
- That small cafe
Your daddy was the best dancer
in the whole county.
I bet you got his dancing feet.
- I don't know, Ma.
- Let's see. Come on.
You put your right hand
at the base of a woman's spine.
And your left hand just so.
Now...
just pretend you're leading
the woman through clouds.
That's right.
You have the idea.
I'll f'i'nd you
In the morning sun
And when the night is new
Son, I know how much going to that
World Series means to you.
And I know it was something
your daddy wanted you to do...
so of course you can go.
But, darling, I want you
to listen to me.
There'll be plenty of time
for proper courting when you're older.
You're too young to be going so crazy
over one little girl.
She's so cute.
She's the cutest little dickens
I ever saw.
No. I just--
I don't think it's healthy.
To hell with it!
I'd pick all the roses in China
for that girl.
And there's nothing you can say
that'll change my mind.
Robert.
Mildred, Ada, are you all right?
It's a miracle is what it is.
My word!
The Lord has visited his grace on you,
Elinore. Isn't that right, Mildred?
I do believe we are all
witness to an event...
of great spiritual magnitude.
I think what we're witness to
is some of the f'inest work...
with needle and thread
that we may ever see...
short of a skilled surgeon.
Well, if that don't take
the whole biscuit.
Who would go to all this trouble?
It's moral restitution.
What did you say?
A symbol, Mrs. Murphy...
to cancel out the wrong.
It is the view of my late lamented
father that whenever possible...
we must balance what we ought not to do
with what we ought.
Why, how very nice of you,
Mrs. Murphy.
Now, if you are not
completely satisf'ied...
there will be no charge for the work.
Now, if you would come over here.
You'll have to tell me exactly
what's needed to be done...
on each article of clothing.
I had to see this myself.
Word sure travels fast around here.
Well, you're talkin'
about the Lord's work.
There's no stopping
tongues from waggin'.
My, look at this.
Hey, I hope you're not too mad.
l guess I gave the boys some bad advice,
I reckon, on how to court women.
Uh-huh.
No lawman should have any part
in aiding and abetting a flower thief.
Well, lucky for you
I can usually spot good intentions.
- Okay, now, put it down.
- No, I'm gonna get you.
What's that?
Good Lord, you fell for that.
Let's go, red birds.
Come on. Catch the bombs.
I got you now.
What'd you think I was pulling at?
- lf I was you, I'd run. Go!
- Don't you dare squirt me!
He's not happy.
Cardinal fans, give him
a round of applause.
I might as well.
I'll be around.
That's my job.
- When are you gonna f'ix this fence?
- Speaking of jobs--
Hey, Billy Bob...
you ever notice how Speedy's always
talking real sweet to your mom?
What are you saying?
I was saying nothing.
I was just wondering if you noticed.
I know what you're getting at,
and you might as well forget it.
It ain't never gonna happen.
Ball one.
I'm at your service, ma'am.
Take care.
- Thank you.
- As you were.
strike one. swing. Oh, boy.
Careful driving.
Oh, no, it's a foul ball.
Whoa. What's this?
-It's just old Rosalba Cat.
-What's she doing in Miss Sawyer's yard?
Just taking a shortcut from the f'ield
over yonder, I reckon.
Taking a shortcut without even asking?
It's a free country, Preach.
- A grand slam home run.
- Says who?
stan The Man has done it again.
- You want them berries?
- Gosh, Preach, what are you doing?
Are you trying to ruin our trip
to the World Series?
- You gotta pay the tariff.
- What kind of tariff you talking about?
- I'm not paying a tariff.
- Then you don't get no berries.
Gosh, don't do it, Preach!
- Gosh dang it!
- Give me that.
What's this for anyway?
You know you can't read nothing.
I can read better than you.
Preacher, leave her be!
She didn't do anything to us! Dang it!
Dang you, Preacher!
Stop that, you boys!
Stop this instant!
Don't you know that gentlemen...
are put on the face of this Earth
for the protection of ladies?
Let me help you with your berries.
Lord knows this town
has been witness...
to every kind of yours
and Preacher's mischief.
But cruelty is another thing entirely.
I am so afraid you'll grow up
to be someone I will not care to know.
You've got to be something!
Little lady!
She steal something from you?
Oh, no, of course not.
Miss, please!
Wait! Let me give you your book.
Please.
Heaven knows there's a limited supply oF
adequate reading material in this town.
- Now, are you all right?
- I'm f'ine.
Honestly, do you suppose
boys behave like this...
in towns like Memphis,
New York, Hollywood...
or Cairo of Egypt?
Here.
Blow.
It's a f'ine situation when a lady
can't walk safely in public daylight.
Rosalba Cat.
- You best be coming home with us.
- Yes, Daddy.
Where them berries
for your mama's pies?
Sir, I can speak to an event
which recently transpired...
that caused your daughter
to arrive without the berries.
Daddy, can I have
my friend stay and eat?
Not today. Come on, now.
We are sisters now,
and I don't suspect...
those boys
will be bothering you anymore.
Now, you come by our house tomorrow,
and we'll have a lovely day.
Oh, and my name's not ma'am.
It's LilyJane.
In light of the recent tragedy
that befell your mother's roses...
my mama's worked extra hard to
complete the repairs to your clothing.
I just wanna say that I'm really sorry
about Rosalba Cat.
I shouldn't have let it happen,
but I did.
I must say I was very disappointed
by your behavior.
You look to be more genial.
Yes, ma'am.
l'm genial as heck.
I hope you don't mind.
This handsome man must be your father.
I, too, understand how it feels
to lose a loved one.
Yeah. My mom said
that your dad died too.
Actually, he's not truly
and totally deceased.
Where is he?
He's not with us.
Was he the reason you came here
to live in Meadow?
I wouldn't say we ''live'' here.
Not exactly.
Not when I always
picture somewhere else...
where everything is dancing...
Iike people dancing in the streets...
and everything is pretty...
like children on their birthdays.
It's not so bad here though, is it?
Oh, goodness, no.
I know that it was the next best thing
for us to move to this town.
And the next best thing
is often the best.
Of course, my f'inal destination
has always been...
and will remain...
Hollywood, California.
You see, my plan is to appear someday
in motion pictures.
You mean movies? For real?
That's right, Billy Bob.
Can't you just feel the excitement?
I can, yeah.
Here. Why don't you play the Victrola?
It works real good.
What are you doing here?
What do you mean? I thought
we were gonna go play some ball.
Quiet. My mom's sleeping.
I forgot. I got World Series money.
You know, chores to do.
I'll see you later. Bye.
So beautiful.
Now, I'm not meddling.
At least I'd like to think l'm not...
even though l know I am.
But you're so remarkable,
and that boy of yours...
well, he needs a father.
Well, Mildred, I'll just put a notice up
on the bulletin board at church.
Good morning, Mrs. Murphy.
I believe you know Sister Rosalba Cat.
- Of course. Hello, Rosalba.
- Ma'am.
I came to discuss
a bit of business with you.
Business? ls that so?
Since it is impossible for me to pursue
my career in motion pictures here...
the next best thing for me...
is to start a small venture on the side,
which is what I have done.
A venture. I see.
Sister Rosalba and I are the sole
subscription agents in this county...
for an impressive list of magazines.
Oh, my!
Girls, as much as
I'd love to help you, I--
To be short, Mrs. Murphy,
we're not here to sell you anything.
I was thinking...
those two boys seem so idle...
and it occurred to me that they aren't
bad after all, at least in years.
Do you suppose they would make
a likely pair of assistants?
l sure do.
You'll both make equal commissions
for the subscriptions you sell...
which we will pay you
at the end of every day.
You can save your money for college.
That is,
if you want to go to college...
because neither one of you have got
the brains to win a scholarship.
- Not even a football scholarship.
- I'll get a football scholarship.
Yeah, he will.
These here are your sales packets.
Don't be getting them dirty.
Now, if you have any questions...
Sister Rosalba or I
will be happy to answer them.
- Well, go on.
- Come on, Preach.
- Preach, you know what this means?
- I reckon I do.
- We're gonna make it to the Series!
- You reckon we will?
All right. You take
all the north-side houses...
and I'll take all the south,
all right?
Whoa. We got something else
we need to take care of.
- What's that?
- You know what I'm talking about.
It's plain to see we both
can't court Miss Bobbit.
I know you've been thinking about it
just like I have.
That's foolish talk.
I can care less.
You're lying!
And I know it if you don't.
Like when you lied about having them
chores to do for the World Series dough.
All right. Fine. What are you
suggesting we do about it?
I got a way we can settle things
once and for all, like gentlemen.
- Good!
- We do the selling.
Whoever sells the most,
the other guy backs off.
- Fine!
- Good!
No, hold it. You got
three people in your family.
-They might sell you out the f'irst week.
-With what?
Stolen money, I reckon.
Fine.
Family don't count.
- Deal?
- Deal.
Excuse me.
Would you like a magazine?
Hello, Ma'am.
Would you like to buy a magazine?
What do you think you're doing? I
thought this was my side of the street.
- It is.
- We had a deal, remember?
- No, you do what you want.
- You ain't gonna win this by cheating.
You cheated f'irst.
But come Friday,
I'm gonna have me a new sweetheart.
Hello, sir.
Billy Bob, I carry 32 magazines...
and 17 comic books.
Oh, yeah.
No, sir.
Thanks a lot, Mr. Trump.
Don't slam that--
Well, thanks anyway.
Aw, Speedy.
I'm kidding you.
I always like to support a worthy cause.
Come on, Rosalba.
I am. Wait a minute.
I'm still f'iguring.
Ma'am, I got something
needs airing out.
And what might that be, Preacher?
I hope you're checking your accounts
careful, because I got more than...
a sneaking suspicion that Billy Bob
ain't turning over all his money.
Come on, Preacher.
That's a damn lie, and you know it.
You're the liar, Billy Bob,
and a cheat!
- I didn't steal nothing!
- Somebody do something!
You can't let him win, Billy Bob.
You can't.
Stop it! Look at me!
What is wrong with you?
- Aw, honey, you've got to decide.
- Decide what, for goodness sake?
You've got to decide
who's your real, true sweetheart.
Sweetheart? I should've known better
than to get involved...
with country bumpkins!
- But I was just--
- But nothing!
Now you listen to me, Preacher Star!
I don't want a sweetheart!
And if l did, it wouldn't be you!
She's a hard one, Billy Bob.
She don't want nothing
but to make trouble between friends.
Come on.
Let's go get us a pop.
- Are you working today, or what?
- What's the point?
l can't go to the World Series
all by myself.
What do you want me to do?
You can grab that jar of flatheads.
See them three fence pickets?
You can toss them
in the back of the truck.
- It's about dang time.
- Right down here.
All right.
Malcolm, you're sure that your pops
is gonna let you go...
all the way to St. Louis with me
to the World Series?
Up here at the top. Ready?
One, two--
Don't cheat. Three.
Don't cheat?
We would like to invite you to enjoy
a game of three-handed bridge...
with me and Sister Rosalba.
Have you ever played?
No,just poker with Pre--
Never mind.
That's of no importance.
We'll teach you.
- Won't we, Sister Rosabla?
- Yeah, I guess.
Can we go in your tree house?
Yeah.
All right. Calm down.
Let the girls win, okay?
- Is that good advice or bad advice?
-Just go, go!
Thanks, Speedy.
Y'all pardon the mess.
- Reverend.
- Good morning.
- How's your mom?
- Good.
Good to see you.
- Good morning.
- Come on in.
I can't believe
you got me into this.
Excuse me, Mrs. Sawyer.
We'll just squinch by you.
Billy Bob, why don't you make some room
for the young ladies and Mrs. Bobbit.
Thank you.
Excuse me.
I planned all week to speak this morning
from the book of Luke, so I shall.
Perhaps many of you are wondering
whether God or Satan...
moves among us this morning:
whether that clever deceiver Lucifer
is leading us toward the darkness.
Do you recall how Jesus himself
answered the devil's temptation?
He said unto him,
"Get thee behind me, Satan."
- Yes, Miss Bobbit.
- Pastor Williams...
I'm sorry to interrupt,
but likeJesus...
I've been sorely tempted
of the devil...
and can perhaps add some insight
to your sermon.
I'm sure the congregation agrees with me
that we can always benef'it...
from the perspective...
- from being inside another's skin.
- That's enough.
Come on, Preacher.
This is just not right.
If anybody else wants to go,
please do so now.
Do continue, Miss Bobbit.
First of all, sir...
it's easy to sit here
on a Sunday morning...
and talk about being righteous...
yet let the devil whisper
his meanness in your ear.
And it is another thing entirely
to resist the devil...
and be truly compassionate.
lf merely one person
invites him around...
the devil can whisper
through a whole town.
And suddenly everyone's lost
their sense of decency.
Even those who think
they've got him behind them...
can't get his lies
out of their ears.
If I understand you, Miss Bobbit,
I believe you're saying that...
even those who consider
themselves righteous...
sometimes need to look
in the mirror...
and see if that's the person
they want to see looking back at them.
Sir, you have understood me
perfectly.
Jesus also tells us
to love the outcast among us.
That we may become
the true children of our father.
- Amen.
- That's right.
God bless you, Sheriff.
Let us pray from the gospel
according to Luke.
"Blessed are you
when men shall hate you:
when they shall separate you from
their company for their Lord's sake.
For the whole of your reward
is great in heaven."
- Amen.
There we go.
Come on, Rosalba.
I'm gonna teach you
how to dance. Now, okay.
So you put your
hand on my shoulder.
I'll be the leading man.
And I'll put my hand on your hip.
And we'll both adjoin hands
like this.
And we go--
one, two, three.
One, two, three. Back.
One, two, three. One, two, three.
That's it. You'll be ready
for the cotillion in no time.
I've never been
to a cotillion before.
There is a f'irst for everything,
isn't there?
Well, isn't this a f'ine sight.
A white girl and a colored
dancing in the noonday sun.
Now you listen to me.
You may f'ind this type of behavior...
acceptable in the woods
where you grew up...
but in the presence
of ladies--
You ain't no lady.
Everyone knows you ain't
nothing but a floozy.
Why, Sister Rosalba.
I do believe we'll be ready
for the cotillion in no time.
I'm just a dumb colored
and that's what I'll always be.
Oh, is little Billy Bob hurt?
Shame on you.
You made old Billy Bob
bleed blood.
I'm gonna come back
and get my gun!
It's not right to treat
people this way.
Billy Bob Murphy, that was
a very brave thing you did.
- It was?
- Brave and foolish.
Now we're going to have our picnic,
and we're going to dance.
You know how l feel
about violence.
But, Ma, you should have heard all
the horrible things they were saying.
I know. Those Star boys
have been needing a lesson...
since the day
they learned to walk.
But I want you to promise me
something, son.
- What's that?
- I want you to promise me...
that you will not spend
the rest of your life...
defending the honor
of that little girl.
But Daddy always said if a lady
is in need of defending--
I know what your father said.
And... it was good advice
at the time.
But right now l am asking you
to do this thing for me.
You promise?
I can't promise.
But I'll try, Ma.
I'll see your nickel
and raise a nickel.
So what'd you do when he said
he wasn't interested, Mr. Quince?
Well, gentlemen, I simply looked
Mr. Louis B. Mayer square in the eyes...
and I said, "Sir, there's
no choice in the matter.
That little girl's gonna
be the biggest thing in pictures."
And that is how Miss Lana Turner
went from sweater girl...
to movie star overnight.
$$ "U.S. Occupation of Germany"
I'll see you
and raise you a dime, Mr. Trump.
Don't try to bluff me, sir.
I warn you.
I'll see the dime
and raise another nickel.
I believe you're the f'irst celebrities
we ever had in Meadow, Mr. Quince.
- Well, that's very kind of you, sir.
- I think a man on the cover...
of Life magazine
qualif'ies as a celebrity.
That's right, pumpkin. How can we forget
about the greasy man under the hood?
It must take a real gift
to spot talent like you do.
Who else did you discover
for Hollywood, Mr. Quince?
Well, nobody this week,
but I am hopeful.
Which gives me a little idea.
I'll see you and call.
Whoa,Jeb, too good.
Too darn good for me.
That's too darn good.
You know, I bet you got a star
in the making right here in Meadow.
You know, we could put on
a talent contest.
First prize, a trip to Hollywood...
and a screen test
with Mr. Louis B. Mayer.
- Yeah.
- What do you think of that idea, dove?
That is a beautiful idea, Lionel.
You're not joking
with us now, are ya?
Sir, I do not joke
about Mr. Louis B. Mayer.
Now we've gotta get organized.
We could do it next Monday--
No, Monday I got--
Then I got something on Tuesday.
Wed--
- We'll do it next Thursday.
- I'll get a committee together...
and we'll getup the church
like we do with the Christmas pageant.
- We'll need to let everyone know.
- Oh, I'll take care of that.
Gentlemen, it looks like
we got ourselves an event.
Now, Mr. Speedy,
you may want to sign up...
so you can showcase
your belt-tightening prowess.
"Dazzling and tremendous,
how quick the sunrise will kill me."
Talent show! Here!
Louis B. Mayer! Thursday!
- Hollywood, Lilly Jane!
- At last.
- That's a good one, Mr. Quince.
- Thank you, Mr. Dixon.
- You're welcome.
- What you get?
I never heard that one before.
Oh, Lordy.
Sir, Mr. Dixon,
now this is a f'ine cooler.
It is a perfect balance
of syrup and carbonation.
Few men could achieve
such a tangy beverage.
Well, thank you.
Thank you, sir.
Mr. Quince, I don't mean to bother you,
but these here Star boys--
and I know you can't put stock
in what they say-- but they tell me...
you might have a line on some jobs
for our young men.
Oh, I knew I couldn't
trust you boys.
- Knew it the minute l laid eyes on you.
-Just kinda slipped out, Mr. Quince.
-Just plopped out.
- Is it true, Mr. Quince?
Well, I guess the secret's
out now, isn't it? All right.
But you gotta promise
to keep it between us.
Now as you might surmise,
I have certain connections...
certain relationships and I
should not be telling you this...
but any boy of legal age
comes to me...
with $150 deposit
for up-front expenses...
shall receive a position
on one of several fruit vessels...
that make the journey from New Orleans
to the continent of South America.
I know this sounds like
a steep price to pay...
but my goodness, imagine the experience
that your boys will have...
as they sail down
to the sea in ships...
as Shakespeare noted.
Or was it the other fella
who noted that?
Who knows that?
So after a few years, he will
return home with his pockets full...
and his soul alive with tales
of living out in the high seas.
Now remember--
keep this between us.
Now, there's a limited number
of positions available...
and I, one man,
can only serve so many.
You'd have to give me
a couple of days.
I could sell an option
on my crop.
Well, you do that, sir.
Ma'am?
Great pie.
She didn't sleep a wink.
Ada, you've been saving
for that angel headstone...
since Walter passed on.
And now you're gonna give it away
to this Quince man?
- Yeah.
- We don't know anything about him.
Time is all I have left, Elinore.
I just think it's time l started
concentrating on the living.
Excuse me!
We can't clap for anybody else.
We gotta save it all for Miss Bobbit.
Now, Billy Bob,
let's not forget our manners.
Ladies and gentlemen, welcome to
the f'irst annual Meadow Talent Show.
I am your proud and humble
producer, Lionel Quince.
All right, Lionel!
Thank you very much.
First off, we're gonna meet
a young lady, Evelyn Linford...
who does her own choreography
to swan Lake.
She stinks.
Perfume from your mama.
I think l saw Billy Bob
in the audience.
That's nice.
Now, she really stinks.
"O, Romeo, Romeo,
where for art thou, Romeo?
Deny thy father
and refuse thy name...
or if thou wilst not--
And for thy name
which is not part of thee...
take all of myself."
Yes, Captain!
Mine eyes have seen the glory
of the coming of the Lord
He was wearing pink pajamas
He was driving in a Ford
Mine eyes have seen the glory
of the coming of the Lord
Captain Bryant, one moment, please.
Continue playing, son.
- Preacher Star.
- Lionel Quince does not cotton...
to the bespattering
of the American soldier.
Captain Bryant, the chorus!
Glory, glory, hallelujah
There's no place like home.
Open my eyes and what do I see
Trouble is looking right back at me
With a face that I
just love to call my own
so I turned to the mirror
to scream and shout
Please, help me, Lord
Please help me out
I don't wanna, I don't wanna
I don't wanna-- Things that don't change
Come on, honey, take a good look now
'cause trouble is coming to town
Preacher Star.
Son, you better get ahold of yourself.
- Dear mother, sweet mother
- Boo!
- Easy, Acey. Come on.
- Get off of me. l want him now.
I'll be seeing you in
All the old familiar places
That this heart
of mine embraces
All day through
ln that small cafe
The park across the way
The children's carousel
I'll be seeing you in
Every lovely summer's day
In everything
that's light and gay
If you have any respect for anyone
on God's green earth...
- I'll f'i'nd you in the morning sun
- then stop.
And when the night is new
I'll be looking at the moon
But I'll be seeing
- You
- I'll be seeing
You
- Yeah!
- Nicely done!
Yes! Great! Beautiful!
-Just beautiful!
- Beautiful!
And now we come to
our f'inal contestant.
It says here that she'll be singing
an original composition.
Please welcome to the stage
Miss LillyJane Bobbit.
Well, would you
look at that child?
What lies before me
What stands between
No one can tell me
What I have seen
some see the tarnish
I see the gleam
I have to wonder
I have to
Dream
One dream can change you
One dream can make
All the difference
One heart can take
I dream offlying
I'm in midair
I have to wonder
What's up there
The sky's the limit
Today's the day
Heavens are still there
When skies are gray
some days are better
Then they seem
Because you dream
On rainbows to rainbows
On starlight to star
To dream, isn't that what
Tomorrow is for
Only a dreamer
Knows what l know
What it's like to wonder
And then let go
On rainbows to rainbows
I know what I seem
I have to wonder
I have
To dream
Patti Page,
eat your heart out.
Well, now, folks, l don't think
there's any question, do you?
Congratulations! And you
people remember this little gal...
'cause she's gonna be somebody.
Miss LillyJane Bobbit!
Remember, everybody, you must be right
here Monday morning at 10:00 precisely.
- Don't you worry about that.
- God bless you.
A representative of the lnternational
Fruit Company will be here...
to greet you and give departure times
and boat itineraries.
And Miss LillyJane Bobbit...
since these people
are personal friends of mine...
they will also
deliver your itinerary...
as well as your f'irst-class
travel arrangements to Hollywood.
Now I shall precede you there
and prepare the red carpet.
- Bye, Mr. Quince.
- Mr. Quince.
I sure hope
l haven't misjudged you.
- I assure you, sir, you have not.
- Bye-bye, hon.
- Bye-bye. Take good care.
- Bye, Mr. Quince.
Bye, Mr. Quince.
See you next year.
- Careful.
- I'm sorry.
$$ "Picken's County Flower Show"
Well, then,
are we all in agreement?
I sometimes look at Billy Bob...
and think it was Robert who should
have come back and me that didn't.
Don't say that.
I swear, if I'm
still standing upright...
by the time those judges
make their decision...
it'll be a miracle of God.
I miss the heck out of him too.
I'm gonna take Billy Bob
f'ishin' one afternoon.
Well...
Donald, I think that's between
you and Billy Bob.
Okay.
- You'll announce it.
- Yeah.
First prize to Mrs. Murphy.
- Fine horticulture.
- Congratulations.
Thank you.
Congratulations, Mom!
Last one in's a rotten egg!
What time is it, Mom?
ls it time yet?
Two minutes till 10:00.
- Good morning, everyone.
- Good morning, Pastor.
Congratulations, LillyJane.
I thought you'd like
some reading material for your trip.
"The Devil and Daniel Webster."
Oh, that's so kind.
I've also enclosed my address,
should you care to exchange ideas.
- That's a very pretty skirt.
- Thanks.
- Is it time yet, Ma?
- It is 10:00.
- I don't see anybody yet.
- All right.
-Just now 10:00.
- He'll be here. Good to see you.
We can't give up hope, son.
Son, I think we should go home.
Can't we just stay
for a little bit longer?
It's been f'ive hours.
You know what? I bet
the fruit company guy got car trouble.
Don't you be laughing, Preacher.
Believe me, Billy Bob,
I ain't laughin'.
Folks, I got some bad news.
I just got off the phone
with the sheriff over in Dagsville.
The fruit company fella
was supposed to show up there last week.
- He never showed.
- Oh, dear.
Mom, this is so cruel.
Yes, it is.
When he hits your neck of the woods,
you beware.
And let me know.
Appreciate it.
You sure you don't know where
that Quince fella was headed?
Nope. Told you, sure don't.
Well, you keep
your two eyes out.
Good luck with that
old clunker of yours.
lt needs more than
a new battery to get her going.
- Well, thanks, Sheriff Speedy.
- You bet.
- Take care now.
- Bye-bye.
Hey, Speed.
Let me ask you something.
Why would them Star brothers buy
a battery with money they don't got...
- for a clunker ain't got no engine?
- How would you know that?
'Cause I bought the engine block from
that heap of junk week ago Thursday.
Acey, take Townline Road.
Jeb, take the river.
We're gonna f'ind this character.
I do not like being made a fool of.
- Let's go, boys.
- Let's get 'im!
Come on.
Let's hunt him down!
I think it's just a shame
about you and Preacher.
How much fun do you think it'll be to go
to that World Series all by yourself?
I don't think I'm going to be able
to count on Preach, Mom.
Mom, can I be excused?
Sure.
Take your plate, please.
Yes, Mom.
- What is this?
- It's an '"nimous" note.
What Sister Rosalba means
is that this is an anonymous note.
No, she doesn't.
That right there is an ''onimous'' note.
Anyway, we received it
earlier this evening.
What are we gonna do? Sheriff Speedy
and them left this afternoon.
Time has come to take action, Billy Bob.
Fortunately,
l have formulated a plan.
$$ "Speedy's Garage"
We're off to save the world!
I am starting
to get the hang of this.
You are. You are.
We're getting there,
and we're gonna be very quiet now.
We're gonna walk like lndians.
There he is.
Come on.
Well, Mr. Lionel Quince.
Well, if it isn't
my little starlet.
Mr. Quince,
by the authority vested in me...
by the state of Alabama
and the US Constitution...
I am placing you
under citizen's arrest.
Now, if you would please
come with me.
Citizen's arrest?
Whoo! You do have a flair
for the theatrics.
That's it?
That's your big plan?
By law, he must comply
with my instructions.
He's a crook.
He doesn't care about the law!
Your friend's right. Why don't you
listen and move along...
before something terrible
happens to you.
We're not leaving here
until you agree to come with us!
That is just not possible.
Hey, pumpkin, what's...
going on here?
We have no quarrel with you.
l trust you understand my distress.
Mr. Quince broke
his contractual obligation to me...
and many of the f'ine people
of Meadow.
Little girl, you've wasted
too much of my time.
Normally I don't make it a habit
to harm children, but in your case...
I'm gonna make an exception!
- Billy Bob, submarine!
- Submarine!
Anybody! My legs!
What are you doing?
Get me outta here!
Billy Bob and Miss Bobbit
and that other little girl are missing.
- When's the last time you saw 'em?
- Speedy, that sounds like your truck.
- Watch out!
- Look out!
- Hi, Mom.
- Billy Bob! Preacher!
Ladies and gentlemen, there's
been a terrible misunderstanding.
Mr. Quince, l'm sure we're real anxious
to hear what you got to say...
but just now,
put a cork in it.
Sheriff, got one more for ya.
There's our money!
- We want our money back!
- Hold it. You'll get your money...
just as soon as we f'igure out
who belongs to what.
The important thing is
that everyone...
will surely get
what's coming to them.
I don't think everyone
will get what's coming to them.
Seems to me if it weren't
for that little girl...
you'd all still be standing here
with your pockets empty.
It's a magical night.
A magical night.
- We didn't do nothing, Sheriff Speedy.
- You gotta believe us.Jeb, tell him.
Aiding and abetting
a felon or something.
We're still gonna get our money,
right, Mr. Quince?
Mr. Trump, could you pull off to
the side of the road? I gotta make one.
Hey, Preacher.
So why'd you send
that whole ominous note thing?
Well, I didn't f'igure
that I could do that whole...
moral restitution deal alone.
All right. You can throw
'cause you got the better arm...
- but don't miss.
- I won't miss.
"Dear LillyJane:
We give this note in hopes
it will help you achieve your dream...
of making it to Hollywood.
We ask for nothing in return
but to remain your devoted...
and anonymous admirers.
P.S. lf you try
and give it back...
we will just toss it
into the garbage...
so you might as well keep it."
Two and two the count.
Got the chance in here
with the fish scaler.
Here's the pitch to Kiner.
It's a long fly to right.
Back, back, back.
Country slaughter tries to run it down.
He's got it.l
Here we go, Billy Bob.
- With that play, the Birds stand...
- I'll get us a couple pops.
two-and-a-half games
away in second place.
And our Birds led again tonight
by stan "The Man" Musial.
His second four-hit game.
Coming back from that appendectomy...
thatjust about sunk our season.
Now, tomorrow, our Birds--
Do angels walk
Do angels talk
Do angels come along
every day
- I'm not gonna die, you know.
- Do angels stand still
Do angels fil
The empty places along the way
Heaven only knows
You'll come out to Hollywood,
and we'll climb a mountain.
And we'll all live together,
you and me and Sister Rosalba.
Heaven only knows
Heaven knows the way I feel
Tell me are angels real
- Would you do me the honor?
- lt looks like
Looks like heaven's here
Heaven, the reddest rose
Heaven only knows
Heaven knows the way I feel
Tell me are angels real
It looks like
- Looks like
- Thank you, Billy Bob.
Heaven's here
Thank you for everything.
Be careful, LillyJane.
I guess I got this for you.
I can't imagine
what it could be.
Why, it's beautiful.
Thank you.
It's only fitting that you should
be the first to use it.
Boys, those nice roses are gonna
waste just sitting over there.
Let me help you.
Thank you.
Hurry up, girls. Come on.
Have a safe trip.
Thanks.
$$ "Super"
This is Mrs. Quince's brooch.
- Where'd you get that?
- Don't ask.
No, you keep it.
Would you like to come in
for a cold lemonade?
Well, I'm not sure we have enough time
for a cold drink right now.
I do. I have time.
- Come on, Rosalba.
- See you at home, Ma.
- We'll walk her home, Miss Cat.
- All right there, you young people.
All right then.
- Billy Bob?
- Oh, right. Come on, Cora Mae.
You know, I really thought you were
a close second in the talent show.
Really? Billy Bob,
that's awful nice of you to say.
And, Janice, that tap dancing
and juggling...
I couldn't have done that.
Preacher Star, I know you left that
squirrel at the top of that bridge.
some see the tarnish
I see the gleam
I have to wonder
I have to
Dream