Find and destroy what stands in the way.
Grandfather?
This makes you weak.
Come.
I saved this for you.
What is it?
A gift.
That amulet is dangerous,
and powerful.
Things change.
A darkness covered the land.
Can not be reversed soon.
The bad is coming from the east.
What will it do us?
The people trying to dominate ...
them to bend,
for his perversity.
Grandfather.
Rachek. My friend.
Arkadi, get some wood for the fire.
Yes, grandfather.
The Red Sun
You can not ignore the forecast.
I know the better prediction
as someone else.
The boy is not ready.
We have no other defense.
The Brotherhood will never accept.
They should, Kirill is stronger every day.
The boy is not ready.
Your pride can not change his fate.
Your failure is not his.
Let him go.
I can not.
Arkadi, go back to the house.
The village is on fire.
We must help them.
The gift that I have given,
should the stones Artu
to be placed.
If I return tomorrow.
To the east, the army job.
Until you reach the tower of Ronbruck.
Look for Maxim,
an old warrior.
He will explain everything.
Rachek, until the boy.
Grandfather.
Arkadi, dive!
Grandfather no!
Arise!
Go! Do as I could.
Grandfather no!
Taci!
Listen!
Find Maxim.
Trust him.
Go! Go! Go!
Let him go.
The boy is not ready.
My men will defend.
They can not protect the west walls.
The king should act.
And he will do.
Tovar is not alone.
What is it?
Grandfather is dead.
We have confidence in a guy.
Who is the boy?
I can not say.
Its mission is to remain secret.
Call the townspeople together.
I care for mine.
Our people are now safe.
It is not long until the dragon returns.
Tell the King.
We must give our Guardian some time.
Sir ...
the Keeper is sent.
Then it's time friend.
The red sun marks our end.
But we can not have our Lord
confidence in a boy lay.
We have no choice.
We can at least ...
My whole life I have one
kingdom built.
I have protected the West.
And now, the appreciation of our
world from a boy
But surely Lord.
My men are ready to ride tomorrow.
Yes, my Lord.
Kiril Lord, may I speak.
The king arrives tomorrow morning.
The Grandfather has chosen the Keeper.
My Lord,
The boy brings news of the enemy.
Your majesty, I am by Arkady Tovar.
Who sent you?
Grandfather ...
before he died.
You may leave us.
Where did you say, you're sent Grandfather.
To Ronbruck
Maxim to find.
Then my men
this pass defense.
We will keep him
as long as we can.
Make haste.
The enemy is approaching us quickly.
You need to Ronbruck flights.
We will continue.
Forward march!
Forward!
Connect with me.
I will not be your slave.
Why destroy everything you built.
Why give up your kingdom?
Why do you force your people to such fate.
Let them live!
You will not break my spirit.
Idiot.
Where is the Keeper?
For the Keeper!
For Humanity!
What's in the bag, boy?
Tea Leaves.
Teas.
You know who we are?
We Tovar.
And we take what we want.
Not worth fighting for a mercenary.
Wait.
Where you going?
My name is Arkady,
I'm looking for Ronbruck.
Ronbruck belongs to Tovar mercenaries ...
wise if you returns home.
Wait.
Go home.
I have no home.
Destroyed.
I can not help you.
Looking for Maxim.
Who sent you?
Grandfather.
I know your name.
Katya.
Katya?
The Guardian.
Maxim?
For centuries,
harmony was held by
a group of monks ...
... called the Brotherhood.
She loved the truth.
and science.
She studied virtue.
Everyone except one.
Kirill.
For him,
harmony was not enough.
He left the Order ...
and became a master of dark arts.
He stole the stone Antiphises,
a great force against virtue.
A major threat to humanity.
So ...
... the leader of the Order,
banished the apostate.
He foresaw the virtue of the stone,
ancient relics of unprecedented knowledge.
He had success and found the
stone of patience,
vigilance and abstinence.,
calmness, generosity and kindness.
But his name was announced ...
grabbed his heart and pride.
He was blind,
the greatest gift of all:
humanity.
Thus shirk his duties.
In science
he ...
someone prepared ...
to succeed
where he failed.
Are you listening?
-Yes
I listened.
But I do not know what this
me to do.
You're a great honor conferred.
Why not take that seriously?
Because nobody asked me.
You must succeed.
If you fail
will destroy you seen
have total.
The whole world will perish in flames.
How can the stones of virtue
beat the dragon?
Excuse me ...
What am I doing?
Never turn your back on an enemy.
Why did not Grandfather
I was a Keeper?
Because you
not finished.
He said I was weak.
Then his evidence to the contrary.
A good idea,
We start here.
Have you ever learned from
a blind man to fight?
You will learn to think,
you will learn to fight,
and you will learn the proper respect.
They will first test.
You will learn the power ...
of patience.
Where are we heading?
What we are is just as important ...
as we go.
Tell me something.
By the time the stone back
in the Brotherhood,
They have lost their power.
They should be together,
not separately.
The first stone was lost here.
So all I do is here
go and tackle the stone?
Is that all?
How hard can it be?
The stone?
You can not succeed if you do not
by the rules of virtue.
Control your power.
Well, one idiot took power.
But this is only the first step.
You have knowledge of the Keeper.
Now!
Tell me his name.
Leave me!
Tell me where he is.
Leave me.
Tell me his name!
Breathe in obscurity.
Let it consume you.
I listen.
His name is Arkady.
It is led by a knight
of the Brotherhood.
He follows the river to the east,
through the valley.
Can I ask you something?
What?
Why I am the Keeper?
Just because my Grandfather chose?
Is not that enough?
Why he chose me?
You ask many questions.
Why are you not the Keeper?
Because I was not chosen.
You're not what I expected.
Then, help me.
Can I ask you,
I want this.
The sun is in motion.
We would also have.
Young man?
Hedona, my beloved ...
you know I am older ...
or whose children have kids.
Young Timmy!
Hello, Hedona.
Long ago.
And who is this being pretty?
We have a lot of lilies
need in your bathtub, tonight.
Come.
My beloved is necessary,
He will shudder as the flames cut back ...
He will have to move to stay warm.
Each of the stones has a
specic place in the amulet.
What is that?
This?
I already know I long.
The bath is ready.
Arkani, I will help you.
Do not be shy.
I made this for you.
It is hot.
Sorry.
I can not.
You still stink.
I know.
So fast, Maxim.
Hedona.
Dear, dear children.
Young man I got something for you.
You've earned it.
You are driven,
but you're a good boy.
Very respected.
What do you want?
The Guardian must be stopped.
How?
Win his heart, his mind bending ...
crushing his strength.
Yes Lord.
Good morning my friend.
The bed is not soft,
but meets the toilet.
Where are we?
In the forest.
Prisoners of Tovar.
I Arkadi.
Superboy, hé.
You may call me ..
Stranger.
Do you have news of King agmar?
You said the king.
Yes.
He and his army are dead.
Slain by Tovar,
and the dragon.
Kirill ...
He once belonged to the Brotherhood ...
let rise until the dragon.
He crushed the Brotherhood,
He and his evil men.
His army was ...
and destroyed everything the Brotherhood
and bosmensen had made.
The community they had built ...
knowledge, confidence and wisdom.
And .. and freedom.
You're crazy.
You're not my friend.
Get up.
I'm not going sideways for goats.
I said, get up, get up.
I have the keys.
Beware.
Come with me.
This way, this.
Come on, quickly.
Now is no need to
call me stranger.
We have expelled Tovar.
For here.
And if you ...
I reward you,
with a part of our treasure.
With this I can buy Tovar,
for your amulet.
Thank you
The dragon, go, go, everybody.
The dragon has burned everything ...
all villages along the river.,
between here and Sulvan.
He seeks something.
The Tovar follow him and fall
what they encounter
There is a town in the east,
not affected.
We warn them.
Go you.
I can help.
We are always the weakest,
if we feel the strongest.
No, we will go.
You should go on this way,
until you have found shelter.
You will know.
We will join with you.
Show us this way.
Katya, tell them.
What took you so long.
You make jokes.
Do you know what is in the cave?
I know.
Many people have been felled in that cave.
But not the Keeper.
- Let go.
Are you OK?
My village.
Everything is gone.
Bread, quick.
Eat this.
Thank you, thank you
There is a place not far from here.
Can you walk?
Come on, get up.
You need that way, on the mountain.
You meet the others.
They have nothing, but you're not alone.
Good luck.
Thank-you
Wait!
Take this.
Share it with others.
This was the wise man in the village ..
It belongs to him by virtue searches.
Thank you.
I sense change.
Stop.
Peaceful friend.
Remember him?
Yes, he is from my village.
Yes, yes you're Grandfather 's boy.
I'm Anson.
You may be a hot meal and
some drinking.
He will do well.
Who is he?
A noble man, a friend of Angmar.
A friend of everyone.
Arkadi.
Yes.
There is not much time.
But we must still make a camp.
A good night sleep and hot food.
Then we suited for the trip.
Go.
You've proven that you have virtue.
Remember ...
too much confidence in yourself,
the end of virtue.
Arkadi, come.
Are you not?
We will come there.
Thank you
Certainly are dark days,
as a man to use violence
to have a hot meal,
and a drink.
And you have not yet met the women.
Come bedtime.
Perhaps, I can sleep tonight.
Your strong stories fill my dreams.
Good night.
It is amazing that you've come so far.
I know who you are.
I pretended I knew nothing
Grandfather told me everything.
You're it ...
Such power and yet so young.
My companions helped.
Of course.
Grandfather and I have talked a lot ...
about your options.
Most of the stones are found,
of course.
Zoja.
Do you think it is enough to
to save us?
I hope so.
There are only a few people who
can say that they possess true virtue.
Do you believe that your virtue has, Arkady?
Come on.
This mirror can reveal many things.
Tell me what you see.
Breathe in the darkness.
Let it consume you.
Wait!
Guardian ...
You're a great warrior.
Bigger than the boy.
You are the guardians.
The virtues in the stone ...
correspond to the virtues in man.
The power ...
is in you.
My name ...
Maxim is.
I'm from the country viros.
At the foot of the mountain Drakor.
We are a stubborn people.
However, we are proud.
No!
We come as friends.
We carry the news of the knight Maxim.
This is all he left behind.
You're very gentle.
Thank you
There is not much time left.
We must go.
Why are we here?
Kirill's army passes still ahead.
We stay here until tomorrow.
The dragon will not see us.
There is a stone,
and I can find.
Arkadi trust, we must stay here tonight.
If everything fails, as long as you trust me,
then we have hope.
Katya!
Take me to Kirill.
The Guardian has failed the last
stone found.
Yes, my Lord.
You did good.
Thank you, my Lord.
Now there is nothing left in my way.
Katya!, Katya!
She has failed you, Guardian.
No!
Take her to the pit.
No, let her!
Katya!
I agree.
Katya, it's not you.
Katya Tarkadi.
It's not you.
If you insist boy ...
to prove yourself.
So you can lose your loved ones.
Your world is dying ...
and I give life.
Behold ...
my strength.
The virtue in the stone ...
corresponds to the virtues,
in man.
The power lies in you.
We did it, Grandpa.
SUbtitles edited by AiRA.Original dutch subtitles by Tinbo.
Dragonquest.2009.PROPER.DVDRip.XviD-Vomit