Windsail Key.
Your one chance to purchase the only
publicly available atoll in the U.S.
In essence, you'll be king,
or queen, of your own island.
This is but one of eight secluded coves
affording you privacy within privacy.
Half of them are warmed by
your own personal hot springs.
Completely rebuilt and upgraded,
Windsail Manor
is wired for senses
you don't even have yet.
Come on, Julia,
when have you ever known us to buy
anything without seeing it first?
Oh, I really thought my
wall would seal the deal.
Tomorrow, at 8:00 promptly, our
catamaran will leave from the marina.
You will deservedly
be the first people to set foot
on Windsail Key since its rebirth.
I'm happy to answer any
questions about the prospectus,
or the mojitos.
Enjoy.
I see you want it...
Just one second, please.
Hello?
Is anybody there?
Horatio.
This is Bill Winston.
Billionaire philanthropist,
world traveler.
And now murder victim.
You are, ma'am?
Pamela Osborne.
I can't believe this.
She lives here, called it in.
I take care of everything for
the Winstons when they're in town.
I heard a noise and found him like this.
What was the event today?
Bunch of billionaires
jockeying to buy an island.
How well did you know these people?
Only person I recognized was his lawyer.
Mrs. Winston sells
high-end real estate,
so buyers fly in from around the world.
But trust me, this isn't
a group of killers.
Well, someone was the
exception to the rule.
Where is Mrs. Winston?
I'm over here, John.
But that's not your name anymore, is it?
It's Horatio Caine.
I like it.
You know what, you can go now.
Thank you very much.
You know her, Horatio?
Mrs. Winston, Frank...
is Kyle's mother.
Team CSI
http://experts.heberg-forum.net
You've known about Kyle?
- For how long?
- Long enough, Julia.
Long enough.
I left him with my mom,
always planning to get him back.
I wasn't equipped to raise him,
and I didn't want to burden you.
Where is he now?
He's in jail.
Can I see him?
When the time is right,
we'll take care of this first, okay?
I want you to tell me what happened.
We got married in Cairo two months ago.
Just came from our house in Europe.
In a way, Bill and I...
just started to know each other.
I'm going to need
background on your guests.
Of course.
Hey, did you hear that, uh,
Alexx got in a little fender bender
on the causeway today?
No. Is she okay?
Yeah, thank goodness.
I feel like today is so weird.
Did you hear what else happened?
Julia Winston,
the victim's wife, is Kyle's mother.
Kyle, as in Horatio's son?
Yeah, and Horatio had to tell
her that Kyle was in jail.
So that poor woman got bad news
about her husband and
her son on the same day?
I know.
I feel like we should try
and get her some good news.
All right...
C.O.D. is a
single gunshot to the chest.
The defect appears
to be front to back, so
he would have been facing our killer.
Yeah, no blood.
It's not through and through, so
the bullet would still be in him.
Well, that's good news, because
if it's not too beat up,
at least you'll have something
to go on.
Got some blood here
that's been disturbed,
which means somebody took
something from our crime scene.
And it looks like he dropped a pen.
Well,
give a man something to sign with,
means he probably
had something to sign.
So they took some papers.
It's engraved-- it says,
"Larry Hopkins."
Practices law.
Who better to break it ?
I'm going to go and pay him a visit.
Mr. Hopkins,
Pamela Osborne,
the house manager,
told us that you were at the
house earlier today, is that true ?
It is.
I'm Bill Winston's attorney.
I brought him some papers to sign.
Yeah, I have a photograph here
of a void on Mr. Winston's
desk implying that some
papers had been removed.
You know anything about that ?
Bill insisted on
signing everything alone.
He said it gave him clarity.
So I was standing
outside waiting for him.
Just one second, please.
Then I heard the gunshot,
ran right in.
Bill ? Bill !
Never saw anyone go in or out.
And then what happened ?
I collected his papers and left.
You never called the police ?
No, I chose to get his affairs
in order.
Bill was a private man, and
it's my job to protect him.
Seems to me, Mr. Hopkins, that
you're protecting yourself.
You left the scene of a crime.
You can think what
you like, miss Duquesne.
Then I think I'd like
my evidence, please.
Well, even though
my client is dead,
he still has privilege. So...
you're going to
need a warrant for that.
Suit yourself, Mr. Hopkins.
I'll get one.
Until then,
don't go anywhere.
I'm posting uniforms here
and at your residence.
Your life's on hold.
As assistant state attorney,
I'll be prosecuting Kyle Harmon today,
Kathleen, in your kidnapping case.
Okay.
After Sergeant Tripp's testimony,
you're going to close
the deal for us, okay ?
Okay.
Listen.
Show your emotions,
but be strong.
I'm not strong, miss Nevins. I am...
going through a divorce I can't afford,
on top of the bills that I can't pay.
I understand that, but...
that doesn't mean that
justice shouldn't be served.
Kyle Harmon forced you from your home,
took you to a secret location
where he abandoned you.
I know what I did was wrong.
I'm really scared to go to trial.
Well, don't be.
Now, listen to me.
The victim, Kathleen Newberry,
is going to keep the focus on you,
you understand ?
Yes.
I'm going to ask you if this is
the young man who kidnapped you.
Can I just point to him ?
Absolutely.
I think about it every day.
Even though Rick Bates
put that gun to my head,
I know what I did was wrong.
Can I also tell the jury about
how my husband was behind all this ?
Your husband's already gone from
corrections officer to inmate.
So now you need to focus on
making sure Kyle joins him.
Okay.
What if they find me guilty ?
Hang on a second. Let's
not get ahead of ourselves.
We're not there yet.
Are you all right ?
I'm fine.
What do you mean ?
About the trial, you just...
- You seem really, really upset.
- No, I just want to...
I just want to make sure
you're prepared, that's all.
Excuse me ?
So, I want you to get dressed.
Dad ?
Are you going to be there ?
Of course I will.
Now get dressed.
All it needs is your signature.
Wanted to make sure everything was
on the books before
Kyle's trial.
I appreciate that, Frank.
Who is this woman ?
She's Kyle's mother.
That's not what I'm asking.
Who is she ?
John Walden is a cover
name I used 16 years ago.
I did some special task
force work in Pensacola.
That's when I met Julia.
Was it serious ?
It was for me.
Custody's a big step, Horatio.
Yes, it is.
Alexx, I got your message.
How are we doing ?
Recovered the bullet between T7 and T8.
It's mangled, distorted.
Projectile entered through the sternum,
passed through his aorta, up
to the thoracic vertebrae.
That would mean that his lawyer
could've walked in and shot him.
But not face-to-face,
like we thought.
As I was going through
his clothes, Eric,
it hit me.
There's no blood on it.
And no defects.
Based on the wound pattern
there should be something on the tie.
There was a pen on the ground, right ?
Papers missing.
He was getting ready to
sign something which means...
he was leaning over.
Okay, no way the killer
was lying on the floor.
Bill would have seen him.
Killer wasn't on the floor.
The killer was under it.
But there are no basements in Miami.
Alexx, money can buy you
a basement, if you want.
This is the very first wine
cellar I've seen inMiami.
They had to have dug it right
out of the coastal ridge.
This had to have cost a fortune.
It cost him his life.
I've positioned a bendy
where Bill Winston stood.
With the laser, let's see what we get.
This is the A.C. vent.
Winston must have liked
it real cold at his desk.
And the shooter stood right here.
Now confirm that with the laser.
Bingo.
There it is.
Thanks.
What's that right there ?
Do you see it ?
It's blood and hairs.
Maybe we got lucky. Maybe our
shooter was clumsy and hit his head.
Yeah, let's hope so.
Hey,
I need the results of that hairs.
I collect it, I run
it, and you're anxious ?
Yeah.
No. I'm not done yet.
Hey, did you hear that
Kyle's case is up today ?
Yeah, that's right.
Horatio's headed
over to the courtroom this afternoon.
That poor kid.
He's been used by everybody
his whole life
and now he might spend
the rest of it in jail.
Well, I think if he gets acquitted,
Horatio's going to get custody.
Yeah, but even that might change now
that the mother's back in the picture.
I trust Kyle to make the right decision.
Yeah, me too.
I expect nothing less from H.
Oh, here we go.
We got a CODIS hit.
Rob Mason.
He's in here for white-collar crimes.
Looks like Rob just made
it to the big leagues.
So, how did you guys figure
out I was in the cellar ?
Because you left your hairs behind.
You guys...
are good.
I racked my head on that ceiling.
See.
Serves me right, I guess.
Why were you in the basement ?
Do you like fine wine ?
This place is like
the Tiffany's of wine.
Bill always talked about
his 1905 Rothschild Bordeaux.
So you had a taste ?
I wish I had the guts.
Just wanted to say I'd seen it.
Why open the vent ?
Okay.
You got me.
So I wasn't there for something vintage.
Bill's always in that room.
I was hoping to get a hot tip.
Insider trading ?
You don't bank billions
playing by the rules, lieutenant.
Besides, he never said a word.
So you shot him.
Why don't you slow down there.
Okay, I've never fired a gun
in my life.
There's an easy way to prove that.
Now I'm no scientist,
but if I were guilty,
that should have
changed color, right ?
Right.
Guess I'm out of here.
Excuse me.
Don't go far.
Time to find out if
you're guilty, Mr. Hopkins.
That's a search warrant for the papers
you took from Bill Winston's office.
Okay, well, I have some
clients coming in shortly,
but I will take a look at this...
do it now or I tear your office apart.
Do it now.
These are annulment papers, H.
Bill was going to dissolve
his marriage to Julia
based on the grounds that
Julia had committed fraud.
That's right.
Just after they got married, Bill
asked me to look into her.
So you stumbled onto her past.
She claimed to have
made millions in google,
but she didn't have a dime.
And we uncovered at least five different
identities that she used in the past.
What tipped him off ?
The windsail key deal.
She cut their honeymoon
short to close it.
He figured anyone that concerned
with the payday must really need it.
So, she was using him.
In his world, everyone uses everyone.
But the playing field's
gotta start level.
Why go through with
windsail key auction at all ?
He was going to publicly
out her in front of everyone,
so she couldn't dupe anyone in private.
And she would be penniless.
There appears to...
be a lipstick smudge on those.
You don'T...
no.
Must be Julia's then.
That means she knows that he
was going to end their marriage.
And that is called motive.
Uniforms went to the
house, and Julia's not there.
What about her cell phone ?
It's turned off.
Turned off.
Okay. I've got an idea.
Thank you, Mr. Wolfe.
Yes, this is lieutenant Caine.
Kyle Harmon please.
Lieutenant, he's got a visi tor.
Okay, what is the name
of the visitor ?
Julia Winston.
Keep her there.
I always knew you'd come back.
I whispered that promise in your ear
the last time I saw you.
Really ?
I'll never leave you again.
I can't believe no one
taught you how to do this.
Yeah.
Well, I've never really worn a tie.
Brings out the blue in your eyes.
I'll teach you how to
do it when you get out.
That's if I ever get out.
I don't want to hear that.
Everything is going to be fine.
You didn't hurt anybody, did you ?
No, but I...
and I'm sure that woman
understands that you made a mistake.
We all make mistakes, don't we ?
Yeah, I guess.
Look at that.
So handsome.
Like your father.
Could I have a word, Julia?
Of course.
Outside, please.
Don't forget my promise.
Okay.
What are you doing?
I'm visiting our son.
You failed to mention his trial today.
I wanted to support him.
And you failed to mention you've used
five aliases over the last 15 years.
When I met you, you were
undercover for a living.
But I'm a police officer.
You found out about the
annulment, didn't you?
I stopped by the lawyer's last night
to go over the deal for the island sale.
Saw it on the table.
I'm going to go get some coffee.
- Would you like some ?
- Please.
And it was at that moment
that you realized
that you were about
to lose everything.
what are you implying ?
You called, Horatio ?
Check her car, please, Frank.
You bet.
You really think i killed
my husband ?
I guess we're going
to find out, aren't we ?
Horatio ?
I have no idea how that got there.
Hook her up, please.
Yup.
You're wasting your time.
Why is that ?
Because you still love me.
I heard Horatio may have
found the murder weapon.
Yeah, in Julia Winston's Mercedes.
How diabolical.
You know, if her husband
had signed the annulment,
she wouldn't have anything, and
now, she's a wealthy widow.
Hang on, Calleigh, okay ?
Let's just see what
the evidence tells us.
Okay.
Now, I got some pressure
distortion, there, but,
think I've got
enough to make a comparison.
I know that Julia is a savvy con artist,
but I'm thinking, she's
probably a rookie killer.
You're so sure of yourself that
I am going to let you confirm it.
My pleasure.
Ten-card's right there.
Okay, this print that you
gave me is not Julia's.
I said it. Told you she was framed.
Want to widen the search, run
it through afis, see what we get.
I got something.
Rob Mason.
The guy in the basement.
Thanks.
I'll bring him in.
Positive for gunshot residue.
That's got to be wrong.
Stand up, please.
Turn out your pants pockets inside out.
That's positive twice, Mr. Mason.
I was tested earlier, it was
negative. How could that happen ?
You put your hand back in your
pocket after you fired the weapon.
Then you scrubbed your
hands before you came in.
now that everything's out
on the table,
why'd you do it ?
Things were starting to come apart.
What was coming apart ?
I spent years bribing and embezzling
my way into the inner circle,
and I'm finally rubbing
elbows with billionaires,
and the help goes and screws it up.
Tim Gilbert.
Sorry. You must have me
confused with someone else.
Come on, Tim.
We worked at Ellicot house
cleaners, remember ?
That was a long time ago.
Yeah.
What are you doing here ?
What does that have to do
with your killing Bill Winston ?
Julia came to me with a deal.
She would not out me
as a fraud
if I did her a favor.
You want me to kill your husband ?
The gun will be here, Bill
will be upstairs.
I don't know. I can'T... i
can't do this. I'm not a killer.
Now, calm down.
He'll never even see you.
One
clean
shot.
Then leave the gun, and
I'll take care of it.
When you're done,
get back to the party.
What makes you think
I would kill someone ?
You lied your way in here so
you could be one of the big boys.
so be one.
she left me no choice.
Why don't you tell me what you
did with the gun after that ?
I left it there for Julia.
She said she'd take care of it.
By hiding it in her own car ?
I don't think so.
I'm telling you, Julia's the
one behind this entire thing.
You may be telling the truth, Mr. Mason,
but we have no physical evidence
tying Julia to the crime, so
unfortunately for you,
she's played you perfectly.
The young man surrendered
without resistance
and has complied with all
that's been asked of him since.
But he did take her to
a secondary location.
That's correct.
and to reconfirm, that is the
man who abducted Kathleen Newberry.
Yes, it is.
These questions have
been asked and answered.
If there's nothing else,
let's move on.
Thank you, Sergeant Tripp.
That's all.
Witness is excused.
Thank you, judge.
Miss Nevins, your next witness ?
The victim in this
case, Kathleen Newberry.
She's scheduled for 11:30.
Let's proceed.
Your honor, as her testimony
promises to be long,
the state requests we break
for lunch before calling her in.
Court will resume in 90 minutes.
The defendant is remanded into custody.
so, Kathleen Newberry's a no-show, huh ?
Yeah. No one can find her,
which helps Kyle, of course.
I'll send my team up there right now.
Thank you, Horatio.
Did I hear her say her
witness is missing ?
You did.
Where's Kathleen, Julia ?
Why are you asking me that ?
I'm asking you because
you petitioned for custody
this morning hours
before this proceeding.
Of course I did.
I'd do anything for him now.
And that's my point.
Looks like Mrs. Newberry
was having a rough go of it.
There's a foreclosure here.
Some past due bills.
Kathleen, this is assistant
state attorney Nevins.
But you know what?
There's no sign of forced entry.
There's no blood anywhere,
there's no signs of a struggle.
What about the voice mail ?
Yeah.
There are, uh...
there are over a dozen of them.
Most of them are from asa Nevins.
Looks like she packed in a hurry.
Hey, come check this out.
She left one bag behind ?
It's a currency band.
$10, 000.
Yeah, she could've fit a
hundred of those in here.
So it looks like Kathleen
Newberry just became a millionaire.
Something oily on the bottom of the bag.
Hopefully trace can tell us something.
Like where all that cash came from.
My guess, it's from someone who
benefited from her disappearance.
I'm sorry, Mrs. Winston
isn't available right now.
She's had a very difficult day.
Well, actually, I came to talk to
you because you run the house.
In exchange for living
here when they're gone.
I do everything when they're in town.
Well, we found a bag today
at Kathleen Newberry's house,
and it had traces of acrylic
polymer and butyl carbitol.
What are those ?
They're cleaning solvents for marble
floors, which Kathleen doesn't have.
But you do, in every room.
We're not the only home in Miami
who has them, Miss Boa Vista.
No, but you're the only one with
motive for Kathleen to disappear.
Mrs. Winston's been in court all day.
She couldn't have had
anything to do with it.
Well, see again, that's why
I wanted to talk to you
because since your boss
just inherited millions,
I think she sent you
to pay off Kathleen.
Not that I did, but what would
be wrong with such kindness ?
Giving a woman who's fallen on hard
times a chance at a fresh start.
Someone did her a great service.
"Someone" ?
I think you're behind it.
The best charity is anonymous.
That might be true, but I
doubt that it was charitable.
Do you have a body ?
Are you saying there is one ?
If I have done anything, then
I helped a woman in need.
If you want to talk about this more,
I'll be in court looking after my son.
Criminal court, Department B
is now called to order.
All rise.
Okay, Counsel.
Your next witness.
Your honor, permission
to approach the bench.
Sidebar.
I have been informed by assistant
state attorney Nevins that
the prosecution's key
witness is unavailable.
Then the state is not able to proceed.
I therefore have no choice but to
dismiss this matter without prejudice.
So I'm free ?
You are, Mr. Harmon.
Upon discharge from the
Miami-Dade department of detention,
you are released to your parents,
both of whom have filed
separate petitions for custody.
So I have to choose ?
Yes, son, you do.
Court adjourned.
I'm no lawyer, but if
Kathleen Newberry doesn't show up,
Kyle can't be retried, right ?
That's correct, but
I'm going to find her, Julia.
And when I do, we're going to have to
start this whole process over again.
Why would you want to put
your own son back in jail ?
I'm, uh...
not actually
talking about my son.
Hey.
Do you have a twenty on Tripp ?
I can't seem to get ahold of him.
No, but Manchester and missing
persons got a court order
to access the department
of transportation records.
Turns out Kathleen has
a sunpass in her car.
So there are records at every
toll plaza of her sailing through.
She's in a hurry, too.
She's hit a lot of them.
She's north of Boca Raton,
which means she's headed
way outside our jurisdiction.
So what if Julia's telling the truth
and Kathleen did take the money and run ?
Maybe, but I've got a bad feeling.
Man, it feels so good to be out.
Let's keep it that way, okay ?
Son...
I can't tell you not to do this.
My whole life, I've been
moving from place to place.
Okay, with nothing,
not even a photograph.
All I have is what I can remember.
Kyle, that's not true.
You have your freedom now.
I suggest you take care of it.
You loved her once, right ?
I just need that chance to try.
I understand.
You stay in touch, though.
I will.
You take care of him.
I'm his mother.
Transcript : www.ydy.com
Team CSI
experts.heberg-forum.net