* I feel in my heart
* Our love has been
roaming apart
* And when
I try talking to you
* See what
you're going through
* It's hard to know
where to start...
* I know in my heart
* I can make it all
up to you
* This feeling of love
doesn't know
* If it has a chance
to grow
* Time will tell
versus what you do...
* I feel in my heart
* Love dreams,
so it seems...
Ladies and gentlemen,
it gives me great pleasure
to introduce my best friend...
best-selling author--
ladies and gentlemen,
a big round of applause
for Wes Wilson.
Thank you.
Making my way up to the stage.
Yes. Yeah. Thank you.
Thank you. Yes.
Hey. What's going down?
You're smooth.
Boy, yes! Thank you, thank you.
Thank you,
thank you very much.
Just wanna say it's a great
honor to be here this evening
and it truly does warm
my heart and soul
to see these gorgeous couples.
It just makes me think,
"Man, I am one heck of a writer!"
Yes!
- That you are!
- Now seriously, I remember...
way back when... when this was just
an idea floating around in my head.
And I talked to my agent here,
Martin Rivera,
who told me to forget all about it.
Way to go, Martin!
No, seriously, relationships--
the key is commitment, time
and, most importantly, honesty.
Yes. No, but seriously,
honesty-- honesty is the key.
And if that fails, role-playing.
All right. Perfect.
Thank you very much.
Hold it up there.
Right. Yeah.
We did it!
Oh, yeah.
Here we go, ladies.
Thank you very much.
Thank you, thank you.
Thank you very, very much.
Yes! Role-play, role-play!
Okay. Thanks.
Thank you very much.
Be whoever you want to be.
Enjoy yourself.
All right, let's have plenty of people
on the dance floor.
- Ladies.
- Pleased.
- That look is working for you.
- You're better looking in person.
Thank you, darling.
Hey, can I have a vodka
and tonic, please?
Coming right up.
- Hey.
I have kind of seen
you around.
I'm-- I'm Wes.
I'm a writer.
- No kidding.
- You probably saw the speech there.
I got...
a national best-seller.
I'm actually working
on a new book now.
Really? What is it about?
It's all about
how to talk to women,
but I'm only on page 10.
How am I doing?
No, seriously,
you are absolutely gorgeous,
and, just purely
for research purposes,
is there anything I could say that
would get you to come up to my room?
- No.
- Why not?
Because you're just a writer.
Okay.
A challenge.
You kicked your shoes off.
They're over there somewhere.
Hey, buddy.
Creepy.
- Nice dress.
- Thank you.
I'm on my way.
- Hey, do you wanna dance?
- Okay, this one's for the lovers.
Just follow me.
Samantha?
Yes.
- Would you marry me?
Yes!
Happy day, darling!
They're getting married!
You love doing that,
don't you?
I plan on doing it
the rest of my life.
* Feel the heat
* Then you'll see
I never say goodbye...
Thank you very much!
Mrs. Wilson,
ladies and gentlemen.
Now then,
let's get out of here.
- Hey.
- Marty? Marty Marty Marty.
This is the girl I was telling
you about. This is Samantha.
Samantha, this is Marty;
Marty, Sam.
Nice to finally meet you.
He said you were beautiful
and he wasn't lying.
This is amazing. Hi.
- Thank you.
- So, engaged? Already.
- Yes.
- That's very quickly.
Congratulations.
- It was love at first sight.
- Yes, it was.
Well, when you know, you know?
Hey, that's actually
a good title for another book,
maybe a follow-up to this. All right,
you guys, this is uncomfortable.
Um, you know what? There are
a couple of people I want you to meet.
Marty, I love you.
We'll do it another time, okay?
- Hold your body close to me...
- See you soon, Marty!
Later.
Okay.
Let's get you home.
Chilly, yeah.
Here you go, sweetie.
- Thank you.
- My God!
What a night. What a night.
- I had a great time tonight.
- It was pretty perfect, wasn't it?
Oh my God. I gotta tell you,
you just look absolutely gorgeous.
You are the most beautiful...
Baby.
Wes!
Alicia,
where have you been?
Where are my diamonds, Alicia?
Maybe I didn't explain to you
our retirement policy...
there isn't one.
Leave him alone.
What's it like to lie
to the man you love?
Hey, what's going on here?
Go to hell!
Last chance, Alicia.
What's it gonna be?
Let him go.
I will get them for you.
Fuck! Son of a bitch!
I'm gonna fuck you up.
Wes!
You idiot! Put her in the car.
Sam!
Where the hell
are you taking her?
Dude, what happened?
- Sir, hang in there, sir.
- 911. What's the emergency?
There has been a robbery.
Someone's been mugged.
- Are you with the victim now?
- God.
Yes.
Okay, I'm gonna
need your location.
732, copy.
Service road 54,
under the I-90 overpass.
I've got a possible 10-29 Victor.
Be safe, 732.
Um, I'm really sorry
that it's taken me
so long to get
this together for you,
but it's,
it's pretty standard, Mr. Wilson.
By Washington state law,
her assets will remain in trust
until either a year passes
and the court declares her dead,
or her body is recovered.
That's it right there.
Uh, Mr. Wilson,
do you understand?
You okay, buddy?
- Yeah, go ahead.
- Okay. Well...
you can continue to live
in the house that you both shared.
She also had a checking account
at First Savings Bank in Seattle,
and a safety deposit box
at Washington Trust in Spokane.
- You, of course, get--
- Spokane?
Uh, yeah. You--
you didn't know about that?
Until you called,
I didn't know she had a lawyer.
I guess we all have
little secrets, right?
D-d-do you have
any other questions?
How long have you been married?
I don't know, 11 years, I guess.
Do you love your wife?
Yeah, very much.
Well, cherish every moment.
Um, okay. Well, listen,
thanks so much for coming in
and please just feel free
to contact me.
- Thank you very much.
- Sure.
Here you go.
- I'm going on lunch, okay?
- Yeah.
I'll tell you anything
that you want.
Um, look, he-- he--
he gets the house,
he gets some cash
and a-- and a--
and a box.
- A safety deposit box.
- When does he get access?
Um, in a-- in a year,
when the court gives
its full authorization to the bank.
It's all-- it's all right here
and it's all legal.
Sir, listen to me,
I swear to God...
I won't say a word to anybody.
I promise.
I really don't give a shit.
Every person you tell,
I'm gonna send a piece of your wife,
a piece of your kids--
a ear, finger, an eye.
- It doesn't matter to me.
- Okay, you know what?
They-they don't--
I'm telling you right now.
I-I-- listen to me.
Listen to me, okay?
Look, I-I already told you I'm not
gonna say anything to anybody.
No, no.
Attention, shoppers.
Today at the mezzanine level,
we have a book-signing
with self-help author Wes Wilson.
His best-selling book,
"Finding Love in the 21st Century,"
is on sale today only
at 40% off
suggested retail price.
- Hey, there's my guy.
- Hey.
How is the sequel coming?
- Great. Just great.
- That good?
I'm just having
a hard time getting motivated.
That would get me motivated
right there.
Nah. She doesn't really look
like the relationship type.
Who said anything
about a relationship?
All you need is to go...
in and out.
It's actually a good possible title.
Remind me to write that down.
Look, it's time for you to start
thinking about casual dating again.
- Yeah, I'll start thinking about it.
- You'd better start thinking about it!
Because I literally live vicariously
through you. If you're not having sex,
I'm not having sex. I'm getting
pretty fucking horny over here.
I can tell.
A couple of nights out
with some chicks like this
will straighten you right out.
You can maybe have that one
or that one.
Hi.
As a motivational speaker, you really
leave something to be desired.
You just gotta give me some time.
I know it's been a year,
but I was really madly in love
with Sam. It's how it is.
I'm not asking you to stop
thinking about her.
I'm just saying
every guy needs a little...
I'm taking care of myself.
Sure you do. All right,
I'm gonna go have a smoke
- and leave you with some people.
- I thought you quit.
Ah, good health is only gonna
keep me in bad marriage.
Yeah. Hello.
Wes-- Wes Wilson.
There we go.
Good luck finding love
in the 21st century.
Hi.
Thank you.
Oh! Excuse me. I'm sorry.
Whoa, hey! God.
Everybody okay?
- Okay, yeah.
- No, I'm fine.
Pick up a few of these things.
I'm Wes.
I am Nicole
and I know who you are.
Of course, well, there's a huge
standee of me there.
Look,
I'm just gonna put it right there.
I am a big fan
and I write for the Seattle
"Woman's Book Weekly"
and I would just love
to do an interview with you.
Oh, well, thank you very much.
I'm flattered.
You're welcome. Not many writers
get a best-seller their first time out.
Ah, beginner's luck.
I read it twice.
Some really good stuff in there.
Thank you very much.
Thank you.
So did it help?
Are you married?
- Uh, no-- no wife.
- Girlfriend?
No-no, just me...
all alone.
- So what's wrong with you?
- Pretty much everything.
It doesn't look like it from here.
Uh, thank you.
Step right up.
Uh, so the interview?
Does this weekend work?
I'm kind of busy
this weekend, actually.
- What about tonight?
- Tonight?
- Well--
- No time like the present.
Here's my address.
Um, okay. Yeah, tonight.
Tonight could be good.
Great.
So we meet around 7:00?
- 7:00! 7:00. Nice to meet you.
- Okay. Nice to meet you.
- Hi there.
- Hi.
There you go.
Good luck.
- Hello, sir.
- Hello.
Your book is very inspirational.
I've always said
it's not just for women.
I was in a relationship--
well, I thought I was in a relationship.
But then I read your book.
It was like you opened up
my mind and my eyes
- and I saw things in a whole new light.
- Thank you very much.
This girl I was seeing, well--
she wasn't the girl
I thought she was.
Well, I'm sorry to hear that.
What happened?
She just disappeared.
Uh, well, would you
like me to sign it?
I can dedicate the book,
if you like.
I want you to make it out
to my new girlfriend.
- Okay.
- Audrey.
I want you to put, "Diamonds
are a girl's best friend..."
"Diamonds are...
a girl's best friend.
Wes Wilson."
There you go.
I'll make sure
this one doesn't disappear.
Nice, huh?
Fan base is expanding.
This is big. This is really big.
Hello?
Dude, I know you're there,
sitting there watching the machine
as I talk, little bastard.
Look, remember, this is just
an interview with a super hot girl
with a super hot body,
all right?
Just have fun.
Maybe she'll inspire you.
Don't forget to tell me all about it.
- You know I love this shit.
- All right.
- Wes?
- Hi.
You can see me? Hi.
- Come on up.
- What do I push?
Hi.
How long have you been
out there?
Feels like my whole life.
You wanna come in?
- Sure. Yeah.
- Come in. Get out of the rain.
Well, let me get you
out of these clothes here.
Don't you think we should talk first?
- I mean--
- You'll find a robe behind my door.
- Are we going out though?
- It's a mess outside.
I thought we'd stay in.
Okay.
Oh, gosh.
- It's a nice place you have here.
- Thanks. It's a rental.
- What?
- You in that robe.
Oh. It's cozy.
- Let's open some wine.
- Thank you.
- I take it you don't date much, huh?
- It's been a little while.
Is there a reason?
Uh, well, it's kind of a long story.
I was in this, um--
uh, well, I'm writing
a new book and--
- Oh, really? What is it about?
- I don't know.
Hey, you should laugh.
I'm completely lost-- writer's block.
- Well, you know what they say.
- What do they say?
- Write what you know.
- I don't think
anybody would be too interested
in my dull life.
You'd be surprised. I mean,
my readers are sure interested.
Right, right, the interview.
After dinner...
when we're more relaxed.
Good?
Yummy.
So I didn't really wanna be a writer.
I wanted to be a teacher.
Yeah? Well,
what's something only your closest
friends would know about you?
I'm a hell of a dancer!
- Really?!
- Yeah.
I'll show you some love here.
Yeah, here we go.
Big moves.
Ready?
Okay. Hey, yep!
- Look at that-- skibbitydoo!
- Impressive.
Spinning! Oh, shit.
- Are you okay?
- Yeah, I think I just hurt myself.
Okay, okay.
- Wes?
- Yeah?
Are you ever gonna
put your clothes back on?
No.
Well, in that case...
Whoa, easy.
Afraid I'll take advantage?
I'm horrified at the thought
of not remembering.
Oh, trust me, you'd remember.
All right, um,
I'll go get my notebook
and maybe your clothes.
What...
the hell?
Hi, Wes. The interview
we did was published today
and I'll bring home a copy for you.
I thought we could celebrate.
I'm gonna pick up some stuff tonight.
Do you want pasta or fish...
or I don't know,
maybe you wanna go out.
Maybe you're tired of my cooking.
Hello?
Are you there?
Wes?
Anyways we can decide later. All right,
I'll see you soon, honey. Goodbye, babe.
Oh, Jesus!
I forgot that stupid cat.
Hello?!
I have a gun.
Wes, where are you, buddy?
Yeah, I'm down here--
in the cellar.
Where are you, man?
Oh shit.
- I'm in here. Get in here!
- Yeah.
I got the check for the thing.
What the hell is this?
I have absolutely no idea. Sam got
this house from some little old guy.
As far as I know, she hated guns,
hated small spaces.
Maybe he was one
of those weapons wackos,
like the guys who sell knives on the
home-shopping network or something.
I think this is a little high tech
for that little old guy.
Somebody was just in here.
Sam, what the hell were you into?
Is there anything
you're not telling me, man?
I'm just as much in the dark
as you are.
What am I signing here?
It's just a release form.
And in it you will find
Samantha's death certificate,
an authorization letter
and the key to her safety deposit box.
You will need all 3
to gain access.
Also in there is the final papers
and the deed for your house.
That's, that's everything.
- I can't believe it's been a year.
- Well, I guess time flies, doesn't it?
Uh, well--
What happened to your finger?
Uh, well, I-- I have
a bit of a woodworking hobby
- and I cut it with a table saw.
- Ouch.
Um, Maggie, would you
excuse us for a second?
Mr. Wilson,
how well did you know
Samantha?
Because I actually
never met her.
See, I had her will on file
with instructions to contact you
if anything
should happen to her.
Well, in February
I went to pay her taxes,
but her Social came back
as non-existent.
I tried to contact her
at her workplace-- Atlantic Traders.
I just-- I tried again thinking
that maybe I had the wrong number.
Mr. Wilson, Atlantic Traders--
it doesn't exist.
Um, well, I-I--
I guess that's it.
Well, be careful
with that table saw.
Hi, honey.
Wes, what happened?
You know, I can't find a single thing
to tell me who she was or--
her job didn't exist,
her name didn't exist!
- Baby.
- "Finding Love in the 21st Century,"
by Wes Wilson-- fraud!
I couldn't tell you the first thing
about the woman
I was gonna marry!
Wes, I've always had this belief
you can spend a lifetime with
someone and never really know them.
Oh, God, is that supposed to help?
Nic, I'm sorry. I shouldn't have
said that. It was rude.
- It's okay.
- No, it's not.
This has nothing to do with you.
If you want some answers,
why don't you just go to Spokane
and open that safety deposit box, okay?
I mean, who knows what can be inside?
I'll go with you.
This doesn't concern you.
Baby, everything about you
concerns me, okay?
I care about you.
I worry about you.
Please. Okay?
I really wanna thank you
for coming along with me
on this journey.
It's been great.
So what do you think
is in the box?
I don't know.
It could be more guns.
Crazy, I don't know what
she was doing with that arsenal.
I guess I really didn't know her
all that well.
Oh, yeah.
Just a little nervous.
We just gotta go slow.
It's been a little while.
This is very--
Yeah, this could be
a long session.
All right.
- Shit, get off me!
- What? What?
Someone's on the balcony.
- What are you talking about?
- I'm serious.
What are you talking about?
I don't see anyone.
I tell you
somebody is out there.
Well, it's a good thing
they left.
I could have shown you
how tough I am.
Just how tough are you?!
Yes, you are a tough woman.
Uh, it's been so long
since I've been with a--
- Hey, you know what it says here?
- What's that?
That "all relationships
should be based
on a certain kind of commonality."
- A what?
- Commonality.
That "the opposites may attract,
but in reality it's the very attraction
that leads to the demise of the same
relationship in the long run."
Like 2 fucking potheads
can stay together forever, right?
Yeah yeah, this guy is smart.
Listen to this: "If one likes
camping in the outdoors,
and the other is inclined
to like room service,
the relationship could be put
under constant stress
because both parties
don't share a common interest."
- Sounds like a contract.
- That's is what it says.
"Because ultimately
all relationships
are like a contract."
I ought to write a fucking book.
Yeah.
"Both parties have to agree
whether consciously
or subconsciously
to be there for each other."
Fucking deep. This guy's got
some head on his shoulders.
Yeah.
This girl I was seeing,
well, she wasn't the girl
I thought she was.
She just...
disappeared.
Mr. Wilson.
Hey, "diamonds are
a girl's best friend," right?
Your book helped me
get in where I fit in.
- Oh, good.
- My name is Isaac Kahn.
I'm here on behalf
of Atlantic Traders.
- Really?
- I take it Samantha never mentioned us.
No, no, she never mentioned
anybody she worked with.
Well, we're here to help.
Why don't you get in the car
and we'll talk?
I don't think so.
Mr. Wilson, we're very sorry
about your loss
and are here to assist
in any way we can.
So what is this about?
Several small matters have
been brought to my attention.
Inventory she handled for us
has been mixed up
in her personal assets.
What kind of stuff
did she do for you guys?
- Assorted buying and selling overseas.
- Really?
Alicia--
Samantha was one of my best employees,
a major loss to the company.
So a year later with condolences?
Where were you when I called last year?
Well, I do travel a lot
and I never received any messages.
My sincerest apologies.
I really needed answers last year.
So, thank you,
thank you very much.
Have some coffee.
He's gonna regret that one.
Excuse me, ladies. Sorry.
Oh, shit.
- Easy!
- Watch out!
Get the fuck out of here!
Come on!
- Up here.
- Hey, hey!
Wait!
Over there!
- Yeah?
- Do you have him yet?
- We lost him, boss. Sorry.
- Of course you did.
- Meet me in the alley.
- Let's go!
Hey!
Shit.
Don't kill him.
Get me out of here, Chauncey.
- Yes, sir.
- Hey!
After him!
Hey, where is he going?!
You put me
in a peculiar spot, Mr. Wilson.
Oh, shit.
You chose to be rude
when I tried to be nice.
So now we do it this way.
- You will go to the bank--
- What?
a simple withdrawal.
Your fiancée stole something from me
and I want it back.
No!
I trust we will see you
at the bank at 11:00 AM?
And if you and your lady friend
wanna make it home in one piece,
you'll do as I say.
Wait, wait, wait...
This is crazy.
Samantha couldn't
have stolen anything.
My dear boy,
you have no idea.
Why don't you tell me then?
Oh, my ribs.
Oh, God.
Hey, watch it, man.
He's been gone way too long.
I understand.
Someone's at the door.
I gotta go.
Nicole?
Oh, sh--
Jesus Christ, don't shoot me.
I just went to get some breakfast.
Jesus, baby, what happened?
Oh, shit, yeah.
Some guy from Sam's work--
not so nice.
He said she stole
something of his.
He thinks it's
in her safety deposit box.
What? This is crazy.
We should call the police.
No! No, no, he knows where I live.
He knows all about you.
- Me?
- Yeah. He called you "my lady friend."
Now I'm scared.
What are we gonna do?
He wants me to go the bank,
give him whatever the hell's
in the safety deposit box.
You see this?
It's only gonna get worse.
- I'm just gonna do what he says.
- They really worked you over.
You should see the other guys.
They're perfectly fine.
Listen,
I really don't think
you should come with me.
- Why?
- Clearly, it's not safe.
After this, you're not leaving me
here alone, okay? I'm going with you.
All right. Oh, Christ,
I'm just a writer.
It hurts.
My head, it--
- Somebody wants to see you.
- Oh, come on, let's get--
Oh, Jesus!
Get off him! Get off him!
Enough!
Let's go.
So...
okay.
Inside the car, please,
Mr. Wilson.
I'm getting out of there!
Okay.
Once again for me,
if you will, Mr. Wilson.
I go into the bank,
get the contents of the box,
put it in this bag
and hand it over to you.
And if you don't do as I ask?
- You will kill Nicole.
- And who else?
- Me.
- Excellent student, Mr. Wilson.
- I'll be back as soon as possible.
- Okay.
What the hell is this?
Mr. Boone will
accompany you inside.
- Why?
- Insurance, Mr. Wilson.
The girl isn't enough?
They rarely are.
See you in a minute.
Hi, what's your name?
Excuse me.
Miss, where are the boxes?
- What?
- Sorry. The...
safety deposit boxes.
I need to get in there.
- I need to see your key.
- Oh, right.
I also have a letter
from the court
authorizing me.
And the death certificate's here.
- Passport.
- Right.
Passport. Hang on.
- There it is.
- Please have a seat.
Sign here, please.
You know that book you wrote talking
about gender roles and relationships?
You know, the guy should cook
for his wife once a week?
Any recipes you recommend?
Mr. Wilson, how do you do?
- I'm Jeff McKenzie.
- Yeah, hi.
Well, then,
- I'm very sorry to hear of your loss.
- Thank you.
If you will.
- You're welcome.
If you need anything else...
Okay.
- Open it!
- I'm opening it.
Okay.
Come on, let me just-- just let me
have a look inside the thing.
Damn thing.
Come on, man.
- This belongs to us. Thank you.
- Yeah.
Psycho, psycho, psycho.
Come on, let me just have
a look in the box. Come on!
Hey. No!
- Wes.
- Shit.
- Are you all right? Come here.
- Get what he wanted?
- I don't know. There was a case.
- Honey, what was in it?
- I don't know. He just took it.
- Anything else?
- Mr. Wilson?
- That was it.
You left your bag in the vault.
Is everything all right?
Just keep it.
All right, let's just get
out of here. Come on.
Ah, thank God
they didn't hurt you.
What are we gonna do?
Let's go back to the hotel,
pack and get out of this nightmare.
They got what they wanted.
Sam is gone.
I just wanna move on
with my life.
Yeah, maybe you're right.
Sam would have wanted it that way.
She's trying to fuck with us.
I won't let that happen.
I've got an idea. We make this whole
thing move a little bit faster.
Why don't you go get the car,
I'll get the bags?
Okay, I'll see you in a minute.
Okay.
Wes.
- Oh, holy shit!
- I'm so sorry.
Oh, this is crazy. This is not
happening. Who the hell are you?
- I have put you through so much.
- You've put me through so much?
You have no idea what the hell
I've been through. This is insane.
Wes, you need to listen.
I don't have much time.
What the hell
are you doing here?
Please. This is just crazy. Tell me--
tell me this is a dream, please.
It's not.
I'm only here to warn you.
But you're a little late.
Wes, this is really important.
I need you to meet me under the bridge
near the clock tower, alone.
Now hold-- hold on.
You've been dead for a year.
I've been chased around
by these fricking weirdoes.
Now you want me to follow you
to God knows where?
I mean, didn't you care
about me at all?
Of course.
I was trying to protect you.
Well, you're doing a hell of a job.
I've barely been gone a year
and you're already screwing around.
Oh, no. Time out, time out.
You were supposed to be dead.
That woman you're with
wants what Isaac wants.
That's insane, completely insane.
I know I have
a lot of explaining to do.
- You think?
- But the less you know the better.
So then it's true.
You did steal from him?
Look, meet me by the clock tower
in the park. And lose the girl.
What?
- Oh my God.
- I have to go.
- What?
- We need to split up.
Remember, clock tower,
lose the girl.
Yeah, he's upstairs.
Okay. I'll wait for your instructions.
All right.
Hey, honey.
How have you been?
Good, just pretending
to be dead for a year.
Get down!
Oh, Jesus!
Let's go!
What the hell?
Oh, Jesus.
Come on, this way.
Get out of the way!
- Watch out! Wes--
- The gun--
- God, he's shooting.
- Get out of my way.
I've got him!
- Hang on.
- Hold him back.
You're going down!
Wes, get down.
You killed him!
- What the hell is going on?!
- I worked for Isaac.
- Wow, I didn't know you at all, did I?
- Look,
I stole $10 million in diamonds
and a list of Isaac's special contacts.
He wants it back.
What the hell kind of business
is this guy in?
He smuggles guns,
weapons, jewels-- whatever.
- So what? He thinks I have the gems?
- Well, we will.
And he won't stop
until we're dead and he has it all.
So what? What-what-what
what do we do?
So lose the girl
and meet me where I said.
I have a plan.
Just trust me.
I'm just a writer!
- Honey, do you have the keys?
- Yeah, I do.
It's a nice spring day.
Cops. And I've got
the murder weapon-- perfect.
Check it out.
Coffee, please. Black.
Thank you.
I love this town.
My dad used to bring me here
when I was little.
Was he in the spy game as well
or did you just
fall into it yourself?
He sold refrigeration equipment.
Believe it or not,
that was my next guess.
Wait, is that code
for "He iced people"?
The only icing he did
was for restaurants.
You made it sound
like they were dead.
They are.
That wasn't a lie.
You know, I never
really lied to you.
- I just never--
- Never told me the truth.
Don't even try it.
Come on, please.
- I was in love with you.
- Please, Wes,
just try to understand.
So how have you been,
asides from being
a thief and a liar?
- I don't like your tone.
- You don't like my tone?
Oh, I'm sorry. You'll have to excuse me.
I'm not used to having conversations
- with my dead fiancée every day.
- Are you done?
I'm not-- I'm just getting started.
Do you understand
you just killed
another human being?
- It's not the first time.
- Jesus Christ!
- You know, I went to the bridge--
- You were followed.
- Followed?
- Where's the girl?
She's got a name, by the way.
Her name is Nicole.
- And I ditched her like you told me to.
- She's not who she pretends to be.
Oh, you've said that already.
Please. She's a nice girl.
She's got nothing to do
with any of this.
She'll leave you
when she gets what she wants.
Hey, listen, honey,
not everyone is a liar like you.
- Wes.
- 'Cause I'm-- I'm a dead man.
Isaac knows where I live.
If he can kill me here,
he can kill me there.
I mean, there's-- there's no escape.
- I can protect you.
- Oh, please.
- Look, you have to believe me.
- I can't even believe my own eyes.
Oh, shit.
Nicole, how's the Bureau?
- How does it feel to be alive?
- You two know each other?
She's been tracking me
for years.
So, Wes, anything
you wanna tell me?
Me?
Who the hell are you?
She's a fed.
Wait, wait a sec. You both are in
on this? I don't believe it.
- I told you. She wants the diamonds.
- No, we want the list.
I've cared about 2 women in my life
and they've both lied to me.
Not little white lies, but big,
huge get-me-killed kind of lies.
I have to go.
Come on, girls. Girls!
Oh, nice!
Ladies, please.
Leave him alone.
That was my pint!
Oh, Jesus Christ.
Crazy fricking women.
Taxi! Hey, taxi!
Oh, come on.
Oh, come on, what the hell?
Hey, that's my beer.
Guys, come on.
Listen, listen.
I have had it with this.
I cannot-- come on.
Hey, please don't put me
in this trunk.
Please. Come on.
I'm claustrophobic.
I don't care what kind
of disease you have.
You son of a--
help me, please. Help me, please.
Oh, God. Oh, God.
Help! Come on!
Let me the hell out of here!
Oh, God.
Wes, let's go.
Wes?
- Come on, girlie.
- Hey, hey!
Where are you going?
Hello? Hello?!
- Where are you?
- Sam. Sam! Sam!
I'm in the truck of a car!
- Well, what are you doing there?
- Oh, this is my thing.
It's what I do.
I'm just relaxing.
- Where are they taking you?
- They failed to mention that
- before they threw me in here.
- This is very, very bad.
I don't even understand.
Why did you even leave?
- Because you're both insane!
- Nice. That's very funny,
very cute.
Oh, God, I'm a dead man.
I'm a dead man!
Okay. Well, just relax.
Do you have any idea
where you are?
I don't know, I hear traffic.
- What happened? Are you okay?
- We just hit a bump.
Major pothole.
Drive a little safer, would you?
- Jackass!
- Shut up!
You almost gave me
a heart attack.
Oh, wow. Jesus,
I'm so sorry to hear that.
The guy drives like a lunatic.
You have no idea
what I've been through.
Are you actually gonna
guilt-trip me right now?
Wes, if I hadn't died that night,
we would both be dead right now.
Oh, what? So you're gonna say
you did all this shit for me?
- Thanks a lot.
- No. Don't you get it?
I stayed dead
for the both of us.
Hey, hey, while we're at it,
one question:
"Why were you even with me?"
I had enough of your bullshit.
Huh? God!
I felt normal
when I was with you.
You know, I--
I never had to pretend.
I could just be myself.
Oh, Christ,
I don't have any bars!
Wes, say something.
Wes?!
Damn it!
Come on, let me out of here!
- I said shut the fuck up!
- Damn it!
My book!
Son of a bitch has no respect.
Come on, Wes!
God, where are you?
Shit.
Where are you?
Oh, God.
- Which ear, the right or the left?
- Please. You don't have to do this.
I won't tell anybody
about you guys' existence. I swear.
Did she honestly think there was
anywhere on this entire planet
- that she could hide from me?
- You seem like nice fellas. Come on.
- Kill him.
- No, no, no, wait, wait.
- No ear?
- No. Listen, listen.
I'll put in my next book.
How does that sound?
Like having my balls licked
by a porcupine.
Kill him.
You kill me, you get nothing.
Can I get that?
I know that hurt.
Wes?
No, Alicia.
Or is it Sam?
Let me talk to Wes!
I know my diamonds are nearby.
Shall we go get them?
- And no, that is not a question.
- I need him to get the package.
So many problems and distractions.
Okay. Come to the corner
of Washington and First.
And please don't make me
hurt him.
I swear to God, Isa--
God damn it!
Hello?! I'm actually
quite good in here now.
Very comfortable, quite cozy.
I said shut the fuck up!
You've been
a very naughty girl, Alicia.
Where's Wes?
What? No kiss?
What? Come on, come on!
- Let me out of here, you--
- Wes, we're gonna get you out.
- He has to go in alone.
- Is that you, Sam?
Get me the hell out of here.
Hi, honey. There's some good stuff
in here. You should read it.
All right, what the hell is going on?
- Sweetie, you have to go in the bank.
- Another bank?
What am I supposed
to do in there now?
Look, everything you need
is inside.
Don't be a hero, Mr. Wilson,
or I'll put 2 more holes in her,
and I don't mean the good kind.
I can't believe I signed
a book for this guy.
Stay close, sweetheart.
This is unbelievable.
Oh, okay.
Good morning, sir.
Hi. I need to get in
to the safety deposit box.
- Passport.
- Right. Of course.
My fiancée, she passed away.
She died, yep.
Rest in peace.
Put your right hand
on the screen, please.
Right.
High tech.
- Your key.
- Thank you.
You're welcome. This way.
Jackass.
"Dearest, I will make
this up to you in ways
you cannot even begin to imagine.
I always knew I loved you.
And this time I promise
never to let go.
Most importantly, my love,
please walk out the back door."
Sir? Sir? You can't go
that way. Sir.
Shit!
There he goes.
Open the door.
Get out of the car!
What the fuck, you son of a--
No, no, no, you simple bastard.
Go after him!
Bring me my diamonds!
I haven't shot anyone
in a long time.
Wes, what are you doing?
- God!
- Hey!
- What are you doing?
- Hey, come back here!
Yeah!
Let's go.
Come on! Come on!
Aye aye.
Come on!
Holy shit.
Sam, what the hell
are we doing?
Oh my God.
- Where's the list?
- What list?
I was hired to get
a list of Isaac's clients.
What clients?
Who are you people?
I can't leave empty-handed.
- Sorry, babe.
- So now you're gonna shoot me.
I don't believe it. Here, look.
See it for yourself. There is no list.
- Wes, grab the case.
- Thank God.
- Give me that.
- Here.
- So you don't go away empty-handed.
- The list?
Names, numbers--
it's all there.
I never did those things
your people said I did.
I was the thief. Once I figured out
what else was going on,
that's when I tried to get out.
I'll pass that along.
Get down here.
I'll cover you guys. Go!
Let's go.
Go!
Ah, see there?
There's Nicole. Stop the car.
Come on, you gotta pick her up.
She gave us cover.
- Stop the car!
- Okay, fine.
You can't just leave her
out here.
Thanks.
All right, we're all together.
Let's go. Go, go, go!
Thank you, Nicole,
for the cover there.
Look, why don't you drop me off
on the next corner here?
I can go for a latte
and a deep-tissue.
Shut up, Wes!
Sweetness just keeps pouring
right out of you, you know that?
He's right behind us!
- Check the glove box.
- Perfect.
Hold on!
Jesus, she's crazy!
I'm gonna be sick!
God, no!
Whoa! Hey!
Watch it!
Hold on!
I think we've lost him.
Just do me a favor.
What do they say in mob terms?
- Just take me out.
- That would be getting whacked.
- Whacked, wiped-out, whatever.
- Look, just tell me one thing,
- are you in love with her?
- Love is a beautiful thing.
People meet. They fall in love.
They have normal relationships.
- She's using you.
- Just sit back there
- and enjoy the ride, missy.
- Girls, girls,
didn't you learn anything
from my book?
Chapter 7: "Communication Is
the Key to Any Successful Relationship."
- Jesus!
- Get down!
I'm gonna kill
these sons of bitches!
Look out!
I don't care anymore!
Cut them off!
Do it!
- What are you doing?
- I'm going in the park.
What!
Don't go in the park!
Stay on them!
To the bridge.
There's pedestrians everywhere.
You're gonna kill somebody.
You know what?
Just a little support would be nice.
I don't like anything you do-- nothing.
Nothing! Shit!
You got 'em!
Get down!
Shoot him! Shoot him!
I think you lost 'em!
Nice driving.
Fuck you!
Nice work, honey!
Oh, Jesus.
We gotta get out!
Shit.
I'm alive!
Wes, help me.
- Come on, honey.
- The case.
Just leave it.
Oh, come on! Nicole!
I'm a big girl. Just go.
Up this hill, come on!
Get back. What are you doing.
Come on, let's go.
- Come on!
They're getting away!
Up here.
Get through there.
Come on.
Shit, he's coming.
Come on!
Go go go!
Oh God.
Shit!
Come on, let's go!
Wes!
Ah! I'm shot!
- Oh, God!
- Drop it!
I'll finish him.
- Drop it.
- It stings.
God!
- Wes?
- God.
Somebody get an ambulance!
We need help!
Call an ambulance!
- Somebody help!
- God! The pain!
Apply pressure.
- Right here.
- I got it, I got it, I got it.
- Oh, guys!
- Okay. You're okay.
You're okay.
Just relax. Just relax, Wes.
Don't get up. Don't get up.
I've never seen my own blood.
It's too much!
- Where is she going? Oh my God! Jesus!
- Just relax. You're okay.
You're okay. You're okay.
- You're okay, Wes.
- The pain!
- It's fine, okay.
- Jesus.
I'm passing out,
I can feel it.
Nice to see you again, Isaac.
Seat belts must remain fastened
until we reach
our cruising altitude.
I had a dream once
and you took that from me.
So now I'm gonna take all of yours.
Hope you took
your flying lessons.
You wonderful little--
Pull up, pull up!
Terrain coming.
Pull up, pull up.
So in the end
Isaac's plane crashes
- and Sam parachutes to safety.
- Okay.
So Sam is still alive
leading a double life.
This is good stuff.
All right, check this out, man.
"She stole millions of dollars worth
of gems from a relentless madman.
Now he will hunt her to the ends of
the earth and beyond to get them back."
This is good.
You know what we should do?
Let's change Spokane to Paris.
I think it's much better.
I don't know, Marty.
Real life can be pretty
damn exciting sometimes.
Is this about the check?
Where are you going?
Excuse me.
Oh, I'm sorry. I thought
you were somebody else.
* I know in my heart
* I can make it all
up to you
* This feeling of love
doesn't know
* If it has a chance
to grow
* Time will tell what you do...
I'm Sam.
I'm a spy.
No kidding.
Is there anything
I could say
that could get you
back to my place?
- No.
- Why not?
Because you're just a spy.
You know,
I'm not really just a writer.
No?
Isaac was right.
Diamonds truly are
a girl's best friend.
Subtitles: Arigon
I couldn't help but overhear
you guys talking.
- I understand you're an agent?
- That's right.
I got this idea for a book.
It's a cookbook with recipes
for couples in trouble.
- Who else knows about this?
- Nobody.
Well, a few, but they're
not around anymore.
Let's keep it that way.
Martin Rivera.
Nice to meet ya.