Getting to work on a project like this,
to be a part of a story that's
on the scope that this is on...
As an actor, it's a dream come true.
I've been making movies
since I was five years old,
and I've never seen anything like this.
The whole project,
the process from the very beginning
has just imbued all of us, I think,
with a sense of respect for what
these guys have gone through.
Get off the beach!
Keep moving!
It became a bigger project
than just making a movie,
and I hope we honor these men
the way they should be honored.
As far as the story of
the second world war goes,
there's two very
different perspectives.
The European theater which
we've examined before,
with "Band of Brothers,"
had a different D.N.A. to it
than the war in the Pacific did.
When "Band of Brothers" came out,
many people who
fought in the Pacific said,
"What about us guys?
"We did something too.
We made a major contribution."
Colonel Puller, where you heading?
Tokyo. Care to join us?
I don't know. It's a ways, sir.
Write us when you get there.
I will.
It was very important for us
to show how this war
affected these men.
During the war, after the war,
that really is something that we didn't
get into as much in "Band of Brothers."
But it's really a more personal and
intimate story than "Band of Brothers."
It's much more experiential.
When we began working on "The Pacific,"
We wanted to cover the entire war,
but to do it in a way that was
personal and compelling and dramatic.
Stand by the bow ramp.
Go go go go!
Our miniseries focuses on three guys:
Eugene Sledge, Robert Leckie
and John Basilone.
Eugene Sledge wrote arguably the
best memoir of combat anywhere,
called "With the Old Breed:
At Peleliu and Okinawa."
He was just a kid
who loved war stories.
And when this war came around,
he ended up getting a real taste
of what war is really like.
John Basilone got the
Congressional Medal of Honor
and his life and his exploits
were very well documented for us,
and so we could follow them.
Do you wanna live?
Get off the beach!
Move!
Robert Leckie was a writer
before the war.
He wrote a magnificent piece of prose
called "Helmet For My Pillow,"
which was about his experiences
at Guadalcanal and Peleliu.
It's an honor to
spend time on a character
who was here and who lived it,
and it's an honor to
try to tell this story,
and try to tell this story properly.
We wanted this to really be based on,
you know, real people
and real situations,
because the marines were also fighting
malaria and all kinds of the elements.
The natural environment
was just as debilitating.
One advantage that
we have on "The Pacific"--
we had it on "Band of Brothers"--
is the commitment of the actors.
They had a sense that they had a
moral responsibility to get it right.
And part of getting it right is the
research that we prepared for them,
but also our military advisors
and the boot camp that they went to.
* We are proud to claim the title *
* of United States Marines. *
They went through a
brutal period of training.
It was designed to be that way,
just so they would understand what
maybe the people they're portraying,
to some extent, what they endured.
Boot camp was probably the
most intense experience of my life.
- One, two, three.
- 9!
- 10!
Just stop. Just stop!
What's the matter with you?
Captain Dye said it when he goes,
"You're gonna hit walls out there."
We never say the word "movie."
We never say the word "actor."
We use "the mission."
I just remember saying to myself,
"Am I training for a movie or
"am I actually training
'cause we're going to war?"
Fire!
I was a college athlete,
and I've been an athlete my whole life,
and I've never had
a stretch of nine days
that was as brutal on my body.
Not too long into it,
you forget about being an actor.
And then you forget who you are.
And then you just
get into the discipline
of all the different stuff
that you have to do.
They came out of that boot camp
different people.
I was there before they went in--
You know, Goatees, long hair.
They went in there and
they came out different.
I'm telling you
You feel invincible.
You feel like you can
get through anything.
If you can get through that,
you can get through anything.
Fire!
You can't buy this kind of experience.
You know,
given the nature of this project
and how important
it is to tell the truth...
Oh, sorry.
Vera.
Bob Leckie.
I'm your neighbor
from across the street.
I know who you are, Bob.
The miniseries, "The Pacific,"
starts a few days after
Pearl Harbor in the United States
and spans four years
from from 1941 to 1945.
I joined the marines--
Thought I'd do my bit.
Take care of yourself.
We wanted to be able to
incorporate the home front,
life at home,
both before and after the war.
Because we had several
characters that allowed us,
we get a chance to see back home.
That had not been possible
with "Band of Brothers,"
because the material didn't address it.
What have we done?
We've gone respectable.
What John Basilone went
through on-- at home--
It's a great story.
It's damn good drama.
I've reenlisted.
They can ship me out
whenever they want.
The first battle that
we examine is Guadalcanal.
Nothing prepares you for
the moment that they say "action,"
and the jungle at night lights up.
The noise is actually thunderous.
And the flashes of light are blinding.
Here we go. Positions, everyone.
The night battle on Guadalcanal was
the night that John Basilone
and just a few hundred marines
were going up against an onslaught
of thousands of Japanese
who are gonna be crossing
into their encampment.
Japs!
Japs! Start falling in!
We do a massive amount of research,
so that we can try
and get at the truth.
We really went through
every inch of that battle,
and everything that was
written about it or known about it
and tried to make that
as authentic as possible.
And the shooting of it was
rather intense, to say the least.
Action!
And doing fights like this,
you don't wanna do the TV version.
You wanna make it--
as every part of this project is--
as authentic as possible.
J.P., cover me.
John, wait, what are you doing?
John, what are you doing?
( shouts in Japanese )
With all the research
that they had done,
they pretty much had it down
to exactly how it happened.
Then to actually be shooting it,
to be in the middle of it,
there are some moments when
you could almost feel the presence
of these men there with you.
It was pretty, you know,
it was pretty intense.
Peleliu--
The battle that we're filming right here
was one of the most brutal and
misunderstood battles of the Pacific War.
Here we go, boys!
Peleliu is a battle that's so key to
what our vision of "The Pacific" is
that it took three episodes
for us in order to tell it.
We're out here today
on the ocean shooting
AMP tracks which would have
troops and guns on them,
coming off to do the
attack on the beach.
Load and lock, gentlemen!
Now the "colossus" that
you're seeing in the background
is actually a working barge.
And onto the barge, we've built
the partial back end of an L.S.T.
Because we were able to find this barge
that had the ramp in the back of it,
we can actually have
the AMP tracks driving out,
going into the water--
you get all the natural sounds--
And we're shooting inside them
so you see the troops reacting
the way they really would.
So it's gonna lend a tremendous sense
of reality to what we're doing,
which is really what
we're trying to do here,
is make something that
is real and accurate to
what the true war in
the Pacific was as we can.
Go go go. Move out!
This is our Peleliu beach set,
which is up in Far North Queensland
at a location called Rocky Point.
This end of our Peleliu
beach landing is
where Leckie comes ashore
in his AMP track.
And Leckie has to land on a very
heavily coraled area of beach,
which is accurate to history.
- We gotta get off the beach!
- I know, I know!
- Leckie, we gotta move!
- I know. We gotta get off!
The other end of the beach
is what we call the
Sledge end of the beach,
which is much much sandier,
much less coral, in fact.
Action!
What I've wanted to
do with Sledge's landing
is to give you about three or
four minutes of actual time
that he experiences on that beach,
knowing that the battle is
going on before he landed,
and will rage on for hours
after he's passed from the
beach on into the airfield,
so that the audience can
identify with his experience
and to share the fright.
Sledge, god damn it,
you gotta get your ass
out of that hole right now.
Move it!
- And cut!
- Cut!
We're trying to prepare
this stretch of land for Peleliu,
the beach of Peleliu,
which is one of the worst engagements
which marines had to face
in their Pacific campaign.
The beach that we're actually
filming on is very sandy,
so we have to build all our coral
and dress that into
the location as well.
Also, you can see that
we have a fortified bunker on
the Leckie end of the beach,
which is angled to strafe the beach
as the soldiers come ashore.
The only way to stop this Jap artillery
is to get into those hills,
and the only way into those hills
is across this airfield.
When we move,
do not stop till we get across.
- You got it?
- Aye, skipper!
This is a recreation
of the airfield at Peleliu
that the Americans came across after
they'd come up through
the scrub from the beach.
These are recreations of
buildings that were actually there.
We have the airstrip.
We have the power station,
the administration block,
air raid shelters,
some bombed out timber buildings.
Third platoon, move out!
We've got decorators
who are researching different
ways of making craters,
and how to make them, dress them,
and make them look real.
If you're gonna draw a pencil sketch
of what life in Hades is like,
I think you could do it from a
photograph of the battle of Peleliu.
Corpsman! Hey, corpsman!
And action!
Get off the beach.
Keep moving!
Iwo Jima is the site where
John Basilone voluntarily
returned to combat.
Even when he received
the Medal of Honor,
he never looked at himself
as above his men,
so much so that he demanded
to go back and fight
when he didn't have to.
You tell that tank to follow me.
- Aye, aye!
- Move!
Let's go!
And cut!
When I was first told that
I'd be shooting the battle of Iwo Jima
on the side of a mountain inland at the
You Yangs National Park in Melbourne,
I said to myself,
"How are we gonna do that?"
But they carved off
the side of a mountain.
They brought in, I was told,
$1 million worth of volcanic ash,
and basically set up the exact
replication of the mountain
with respect to the various
tiers of the volcanic ash.
And then of course, the larger shots
of ships and so forth was all something
that was done visual effects-wise
in post effects.
But the majority of the shots
worked without having to touch 'em.
The smoke and the
intensity of all the fire
and all the things that were going on--
you really felt like you were there.
I'm more proud of the Iwo Jima battle
than anything I've
ever been involved in.
Action!
Clear the back line!
Third platoon, get up on the rocks!
You know, if you were gonna
take the twin campaigns
for the island of Iwo Jima
and the island of Okinawa,
you could probably say those were
the absolute worst of the entire war.
K Company, cease fire!
Not only the horror of
actually being under fire,
but everything else about that island
was just absolutely miserable.
The battle of Okinawa presented
a lot of challenges for the production
because of the terrible conditions
that the marines fought under.
Spread out! Spread to the left!
The Okinawa landscape
was something that we had to
research very carefully--
Everything from the architecture
through the color of the soil,
the kind of rock geology that
we see exposed through the earth.
We built a Japanese village.
We dressed it all out,
and then we wrecked it.
We burned it, destroyed it
before even the crew got there.
And after that, it was all about mud,
pumping in water and making thick mud.
Every morning we would drench the set
and then drive tractors over the mud
just to churn it up and till it.
So it was a mess.
And then at night and
sometimes in the day,
we had rain towers,
so it was always raining.
It was always muddy.
Okinawa was part of Japan.
They were viewing themselves
as defending Japan,
and the only way in order to
get through the battle of Okinawa
is to take every day that it requires
and spend every life
that it was going to take.
That was the only way to do it.
Okinawa had a profound
effect on all of us.
It's a very intense episode.
It affected everybody.
And it particular affected the actors,
and their performances reflect that.
Cease fire!
Cease fire, God damn it!
I told you to cease fire.
You're supposed to be observing.
I see you with a goddamn sidearm.
We were all sent here
to kill Japs, weren't we?
So what the hell difference does
it make what weapon we use?
I'd use my goddamn hands if I had to.
We're telling the story the way it was.
I feel we get inside
our marines' heads,
and hope that we tell the story that
we would want them to have us tell.
I want you to meet some of the reason
that we're doing what we're
doing every day out here.
When the veterans come on set,
they bring home the
sense of responsibility.
The fact that we're doing this today
and going over all of this again
is really startling to me.
I just can't believe it's happening.
I am so proud and so thrilled
that they have decided
to make this thing.
I'm-- I can't express how I feel.
We'd all given up that this story
would ever be told--
The real true story.
'Cause it was a nasty war, man.
War is a part of the human condition.
The question we ask in "The Pacific"
is, "What did it do to its participants?
"How can you survive?
"How can you see what those guys did
"and expect to just
move on with things?"
It's not about America versus Japan.
It's about war
and how horrific it
can be for everybody.
Every single person that
had to go through that
deserves to be remembered,
and their story deserves to be told.
I can't imagine any human being
going through a greater struggle
than what these guys did.
It's brutal and it's honest
and it's right there in your face,
as it was for them.