[SOUND OF SNIFFING]
[BRUSH RUSTLING,
RUNNING FOOTSTEPS]
[GRUNTING]
[FOOTSTEPS FADING]
[GRUNTING LOUDLY]
[SPITS]
HEY, WHERE'S MINE?
WHERE'S McCALL?
THEY SHOULD'VE LANDED
10 MINUTES AGO.
UMM...
WHAT ARE YOU
WAITING FOR?
CALL HIM.
[CELL PHONE RINGS]
McCALL.
Man, on phone: PLEASE
HOLD FOR MRS. MANNING.
HEY, WHERE ARE YOU?
McCall: HOW MANY
ASSISTANTS DO YOU HAVE?
NOT ENOUGH.
PLEASE TELL ME YOU LANDED.
I'M ON THE TARMAC NOW.
Carla: GOOD.
CHANGE OF PLANS.
DON'T COME TO BASE CAMP.
WE FOUND BETTER ACCESS
THREE MILES DOWNRIVER
FROM HERE.
LIN'S GOT MR. VARGAS' MAPS.
SANTIAGO'S GOT THE BOATS.
HE'LL TAKE CARE
OF WHATEVER YOU NEED.
THAT SOUNDS TOO EASY.
YOU ALWAYS THIS PREPARED?
Carla: THAT'S WHY
I NEED MORE ASSISTANTS.
SIT TIGHT.
HELP HAS ARRIVED.
TU, UH, DOCTOR?
EN REALIDAD SOY
UN ANTROPOLOGO Y LINGUISTA.
YEAH, I'M A DOCTOR.
I'M AN ANTHROPOLOGIST,
AND HE'S AN ARCHEOLOGIST.
[TAPS ON SCREEN]
[SPEAKING SPANISH]
WHAT'S HE SAYING?
HE THINKS
YOU'RE A TERRORIST.
WHAT WAS IT,
THREE TOURS?
THAT'S A LOT
OF MIDDLE EAST STAMPS.
Santiago:
HEY, SHUGIE!
HEY, WHAT'S THE PROBLEM?
PARDON ME.
UN MOMENTO.
THESE ARE MY PEOPLE.
VARGAS EXPEDITION, HUH?
YOU DISRESPECT ME AGAIN?
SORRY. I APOLOGIZE,
MY FRIEND.
OKAY, COME. VAMANOS!
WE HAVE
A LONG JOURNEY, HUH?
I HOPE YOU GOT A.C.
OF COURSE. OF COURSE.
THE FREE KIND.
SO OUR GOOD BOSS,
MR. VARGAS,
HE'S SURE GOING
TO A LOT OF TROUBLE
FOR A RUSTY OLD KNIFE,
NO?
Lin: IT'S NOT THE DAGGER.
IT'S THE PEDIGREE.
THE QUAYIN DAGGER
ONCE BELONGED
TO PEDRO ARIAS ALVARADO,
ONE OF THE MOST DECORATED
CONQUISTADORS OF ALL TIME.
BY DECORATED
HE MEANS RUTHLESS.
Lin: TOMATO. TOMAHTO.
HARRY FANCIES HIMSELF
A MODERN-DAY CONQUEROR,
SO HE SQUANDERS MILLIONS
COMBING THE WORLD
FOR ANY VESTIGE
OF SPANISH IMPERIALISM.
IF IT'S SO DISTASTEFUL,
WHY LOWER YOURSELF
FOR A PAYCHECK?
HEY, HIS MONEY'S AS GOOD
AS ANYBODY'S, NO?
LOOK OUT!
[MEN MUTTERING
IN SPANISH]
THEY JUNTA?
NO JUNTA
THIS FAR NORTH.
THEY'RE GUERILLAS.
GENERAL GOMEZ'S MEN.
DON'T WORRY.
[BOTTLES CLANKING]
WE'RE LIKE BROTHERS.
HE DIVORCED MY COUSIN
LAST YEAR.
QUE PASO, PRIMOS?
SO WHO EXACTLY IS WINNING
THIS LITTLE WAR OF THEIRS?
HOW AMERICAN OF YOU TO BELIEVE
SOMEONE ACTUALLY WINS IN WAR.
IF THEY DIDN'T,
WE'D ALL BE BRITISH.
PRIMO!
HEY, OH! HEY!
[REBEL LAUGHS]
[CHUCKLES]
[REBEL SPEAKING SPANISH]
GRACIAS.
PUT IT ON.
WHAT'S THIS?
LITTLE GIFT
FROM CARLA
SO SHE CAN
KEEP TABS ON US.
LOOKS LIKE IT CAME OUT
OF A CEREAL BOX.
YEAH?
WHAT'S WRONG WITH IT?
IT'S CALLED A HIDDEN
TREASURE FOR A REASON.
'CAUSE THERE'S NO MAPS.
THERE'S A MILLION ACRES
OF UNCHARTED LAND
OUT THERE.
WITHOUT THAT MAP,
WE'D WANDER AROUND
FOR 10 LIFETIMES
AND NEVER SEE
THE SAME TREE TWICE.
WHERE DOES HARRY
GET HIS INTEL?
Lin: HARRY NEVER REVEALS
HIS SOURCES,
BUT TRUST ME,
THEY'RE RELIABLE.
Felicia: HEY, LIN,
WHAT'S AT THE BOTTOM
OF THIS YAMBALLI STELE?
IT'S CALENDRICS.
OR GLYPHS--INSTRUCTIONS
OF SOME KIND.
NO, THEY'RE
ASTROLOGICAL SYMBOLS.
THE ONES AT THE TOP,
BUT THESE GLYPHS
ARE NONSEQUENTIAL.
ALL RIGHT, SHOULD I BE
TAKING NOTES, OR WHAT?
WHAT'S A GLYPH?
TRIBAL WRITING,
LIKE EGYPTIAN HIEROGLYPHICS.
THAT'S HOW
THEY PASS DOWN STORIES.
BORING DETAILS LIKE
GRAIN INVENTORIES, BIRTHDAYS.
TRIBAL CUSTOMS
OR WARNINGS.
YES, ANCIENT SECRETS,
MYSTERIOUS CURSES. BOO!
IT'S BEEN WELL DOCUMENTED.
HE'D KNOW IF HE BOTHERED
TO READ.
WHAT'S THAT SUPPOSED TO MEAN?
FIGURE IT OUT.
IT'S ON THE QUIZ.
Carla:
JOHN, GET IN HERE.
JOHN,
I NEED TO SEE YOU NOW.
[COOING SOUND]
[COOING]
[MUTTERING AND COOING]
[SOFTLY SNORTING]
[COOING]
[SCREAMING]
[WHISTLING]
GET DOWN, GET DOWN,
GET DOWN!
WHAT?
GET DOWN.
I SAID GET DOWN.
ALL RIGHT, LET'S GO.
DON'T YOU THINK ALL THE WHISTLES
AND CLENCHED FISTS
MIGHT BE A BIT
OVER THE TOP?
YOU WANT TO GO TOE-TO-TOE
WITH HEAVILY ARMED GUERILLAS,
YOU BE MY GUEST.
Santiago: JUST WATCH OUT
FOR THE JAGUARS.
AND DON'T FORGET
THE ONE-ARMED MONKEYS.
I THOUGHT YOU SAID
WE HAD A GUARANTEED
PERIMETER FROM GOMEZ.
WE DO.
WHAT'S THAT?
TRACKS LIKE THAT
WOULDN'T SURVIVE A STRONG RAIN.
YOU. COME HERE.
WHERE'S MAKAI?
HMM?
YOU TELL HIM
TO PICK UP HIS MESS.
WHERE AM I SUPPOSED
TO LOOK?
SO, DOC, WHAT KIND
OF WARNING SIGNS
SHOULD WE LOOK OUT FOR?
IT'S OKAY, CAPTAIN,
YOU DON'T
NEED TO PLACATE ME.
I LOOK LIKE THE KIND OF GUY
THAT PLACATES PEOPLE?
AND IT'S SERGEANT.
COULD BE
PRETTY MUCH ANYTHING.
INVOCATION OF DEITIES
TO WARD OFF THEFT.
KEEP EXPLORERS FROM
TRAMPLING ON THEIR GRAVES.
INVOCATION.
YOU MEAN LIKE CURSES?
SOMETHING LIKE THAT.
WOULD THEY HAVE
DEVISED DEFENSES?
YOU MEAN LIKE BOOBY TRAPS?
SOMETHING LIKE THAT.
Lin:
IT'S ONLY IN THE MOVIES.
NOBODY ASKED YOU.
WHATEVER.
HO.
HEY, CHECK THIS OUT.
NO, THANK YOU.
NO, NO, I'M SERIOUS.
COME HERE.
I PULL MY ZIPPER DOWN,
I USUALLY GET LUCKY,
BUT NEVER LIKE THIS.
Felicia: WOW.
A REAL CONQUISTADOR.
IN THE FLESH...
AND BONE.
THIS THING'S GOTTA BE
500 YEARS OLD.
SELVA DE LOS MUERTOS.
Felicia:
"JUNGLE OF THE DEAD."
THAT'S WHAT THE YAMBALLI
CALL IT.
DON'T YOU MEAN
CALLED IT?
THEY'RE EXTINCT,
REMEMBER?
WHY "JUNGLE OF THE DEAD"?
'CAUSE IT'S CURSED.
HAS BEEN FOR CENTURIES.
A LOT OF SPANISH EXPLORERS
CAME TO THIS PART OF THE WORLD.
NOT MANY LEFT.
THE NAME STUCK.
BASTARDS.
THOUGHT THE WORLD
WAS THEIRS TO CONQUER.
IT WAS 500 YEARS AGO, MAN.
LET IT GO, HUH?
McCall, on phone: LIN
CLAIMS IT'S AUTHENTIC.
SOUNDS LIKE YOU'RE
GETTING CLOSE.
ANY REPORTS OF GUERILLA
MOVEMENT IN THE AREA?
Carla: HOLD ON.
[tapping keyboard]
LATEST INTEL HAS THEM
40 MILES EAST. WHY?
McCall: OH, NOTHIN'.
JUST A HUNCH.
LET ME KNOW
IF YOU HEAR ANYTHING.
[phone beeps]
[GROWLING]
YES. WELL, I DON'T CARE
WHAT HE THINKS.
I PAID FOR RESULTS.
LOOK, IF HE CAN'T DO IT,
GET THE MONEY BACK
AND FIND SOMEONE WHO CAN.
[phone beeps]
GOOD NEWS, MISS MANNING.
THAT'S ALL I HAVE TIME FOR.
Carla: HAPPY TO OBLIGE.
I UPLOADED A PHOTO
THE TEAM JUST SENT THROUGH.
IT'S ON THE SERVER,
AND I THINK YOU'LL FIND IT
VERY ENCOURAGING.
I'M BOARDING NOW,
SO GIVE ME A MINUTE.
MORNING.
GOOD MORNING.
EXCELLENT.
UH, SERGEANT McCALL'S
CONCERNED ABOUT THE GUERILLAS,
BUT I ASSURED HIM--
NO, I THOUGHT
WE BOUGHT A WINDOW.
WE DID. 48 HOURS.
BUT GENERAL GOMEZ DOESN'T
EXACTLY HAND OUT RECEIPTS.
OH, HO, THERE IT IS.
THERE IT IS.
YOU KNOW, THAT BRAVE MAN
COULD VERY WELL BE
ONE OF MY ANCESTORS.
Carla:
I THINK WE'RE CLOSE.
WITH ANY LUCK, WE'LL BE
OUTTA HERE IN EIGHT HOURS.
THERE'S NO SUCH THING
AS LUCK, MISS MANNING.
ONLY DETERMINATION
AND PERSEVERANCE.
[CHUCKLES]
Lin: GUYS!
I THINK THIS IS IT.
Santiago:
NO, NO, NO, HOLD ON.
NO ONE SAID ANYTHING
ABOUT ROBBING GRAVES.
THE YAMBALLI
CONNECTED EVERYTHING
TO CIRCADIAN RHYTHMS,
SO ALL THE TOMBS
SHOULD FACE EAST.
CIRCADIAN RHYTHMS?
MOST TRIBAL CULTURES
BASE THEIR CUSTOMS
OFF THE PATTERNS
OF MOTHER NATURE:
MOON, SUN, PLANETS.
LOOK FOR THE ONE
THAT RUNS NORTH-SOUTH.
YOU JUST SAID
THEY ALL FACE EAST.
NOT THE ONE WE'RE AFTER.
HEY, WAIT.
RESPECT THE DEAD
OR THEY
MAKE TROUBLE FOR YOU.
RELAX, MAN.
WE'RE NOT DIGGING UP
RANDOM GRAVES.
ALL RIGHT?
I'LL KNOW IT
WHEN I SEE IT.
EVERYBODY
JUST FAN OUT.
WHAT KILLED THEM OFF,
THE YAMBALLI?
THE USUAL SUSPECTS:
GERMS, GUNS, STEEL,
WHITE PEOPLE BASICALLY.
YEAH, NEXT YOU'LL
BE BLAMING GLOBAL WARMING.
I WAS GONNA ADD
MULTINATIONAL CORPORATIONS,
BUT I KNOW
YOU'RE A STOCKHOLDER.
THAT'S RIGHT, BABY.
NEXT TIME YOU REACH
FOR A LIFESAVING DRUG,
REMEMBER IT'S
FROM A MULTINATIONAL.
HEY, GUYS?
NORTH-SOUTH.
YEAH,
THIS LOOKS PROMISING.
THESE ARE, IDEOGRAMS...
GLYPHS.
[BLOWING]
"ONE HEART...
FOR ALL HEARTS."
COME ON. LET'S GET
THIS SUCKER OFF, HUH?
SHOVEL!
HOLD ON, HOLD ON.
LET ME READ THIS FIRST.
WHY, YOU STILL WORKING
ON YOUR DISSERTATION?
COME ON, SHOVEL!
JUST GIMME A SECOND.
YOU REALLY THINK
THEY'RE GONNA WARN US
IF THE THING'S CURSED?
COME ON, VAMOS!
I DON'T KNOW.
WHAT IF SHE'S RIGHT?
YOU DON'T KNOW
WHAT'S IN THERE.
THIS ISN'T
AN ANTHROPOLOGY EXPEDITION.
IT'S ABOUT ONE THING
AND ONE THING ONLY,
AND NO ONE GETS PAID
TILL WE DELIVER!
HELP HIM OUT.
Lin: ON THREE.
BACK UP, BACK UP.
COME ON.
READY? ONE...
TWO...
THREE.
[GRUNTING]
[STONE SCRAPING]
[GAS HISSING]
[COUGHING]
GOOD, GOOD, GOOD.
UH...ALL RIGHT.
COME ON, NOW PUSH.
READY. READY.
[STONE SCRAPING]
GO!
Lin: OKAY, THAT'S GOOD.
THAT'S GOOD, THAT'S GOOD.
AHH!
ACES OVER KINGS.
HEY! HEY, HEY.
JUST KEEP IT
IN YOUR PANTS.
LEMME READ THIS BEFORE
YOU DO ANYTHING STUPID.
YOU DON'T HAVE
TO JUSTIFY YOUR PAYCHECK.
LET'S JUST GET THIS THING
AND--
HEY, THIS DOESN'T MAKE SENSE.
WHY WAS
A EUROPEAN CONQUEROR
FORMALLY BURIED
BY HIS ARCH-ENEMIES?
McCALL, TELL HER.
LET HER TAKE A LOOK.
AWW!
"CHOK," THAT MEANS
TO PUT OR KEEP.
"MASKAB" IS "BLADE,"
BUT THE NEXT WORD
IS TOO WORN DOWN.
I CAN'T READ IT.
McCall:
INSTRUCTIONS?
Felicia: POSSIBLY,
OR A WARNING.
HEY! NO, NO, NO!
RELAX,
RELAX, IT'S NO BIG DEAL.
GOD, WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
THAT WORD RIGHT THERE
MEANS "DEATH."
THIS IS A WARNING.
YEAH, WELL,
NOBODY'S DEAD, RIGHT?
LIN, HOLD IT UP.
[camera phone clicks]
AHEAD OF SCHEDULE,
I'M IMPRESSED SERGEANT McCALL.
WELL, YOU GAVE US THE MAP.
I ALMOST FEEL GUILTY
TAKING YOUR MONEY.
MY GOODNESS, IT'S EXQUISITE.
McCall:
IF YOU SAY SO.
WHAT'S LIN THINK?
HANG ON...LIN?
CARLA.
YOU SEE IT?
Carla:
IS IT THE ONE?
DEFINITELY.
THE BLADE IS A LITTLE OLDER
THAN I THOUGHT,
BUT THE HANDLE'S
VINTAGE 14th CENTURY.
WAIT, HOLD ON.
Carla: WHAT IS IT?
WELL, IT'S THE...
THE STONE ON THE HILT.
IT'S NOT OBSIDIAN.
IT'S...
OH...[laughs]
IT'S A RUBY.
A RUBY?
ARE YOU SURE?
Lin:
YEAH, IT'S GORGEOUS.
IT'S GOTTA BE 30 CARATS,
MAYBE MORE.
I'VE NEVER SEEN
A STONE THIS BIG.
Carla:
SEND ME A PICTURE.
OKAY, HOLD ON.
[CLICKS]
HOW MUCH YOU
THINK THAT'S WORTH?
MORE THAN YOU OR I
COULD EVER SPEND.
[WRITING]
LIN, LET ME TALK
TO McCALL AGAIN.
YEAH?
LISTEN TO ME
VERY CAREFULLY,
I DON'T WANT ANYONE
GETTING ANY CRAZY IDEAS
OR RENEGOTIATING
THEIR CONTRACTS,
SO YOU TAKE THAT DAGGER,
AND YOU KEEP IT SAFE.
DO IT NOW.
YES, MA'AM.
HAND IT OVER.
BOSS'S ORDERS.
GOT IT.
Carla:
GOOD. NOW TURN AROUND,
[LOUD RUMBLING]
HEAD STRAIGHT BACK
TO CAMP.
DO NOT STOP
FOR ANYTHING OR ANYONE.
I WANT THAT DAGGER
IN MY...
WHAT'S WRONG?
[RUMBLING]
Carla:
McCALL, TALK TO ME.
[SCREECHING]
Carla:
WHAT'S HAPPENING?
McCall: UH, I DON'T KNOW.
UH, GUYS?
NOBODY MOVE.
[BRUSH RUSTLING]
WRAP IT UP. THAT WAY.
LET'S GO.
WE CAN'T JUST LEAVE.
YES, WE CAN!
STAY TOGETHER!
[WHOOSH, SNAP]
AAH! AAAH!
HEY! HEY!
SANTIAGO, FIND
THE RELEASE POINT!
YOU, STAY WITH HER!
DON'T MOVE!
AAH!
CALM DOWN!
CUT HIM DOWN!
SANTIAGO, COME HERE,
COME HERE, COME HERE!
GIMME A HAND!
LIN! LIN! RELAX!
RELAX!
Lin: HEY!
[SHOUTING]
[PORTER GROANS]
[GASPS, SCREAMS]
Lin: HELP!
[SANTIAGO SHOUTING]
Lin: HELP! HEY!
GET LIN DOWN!
WHAT? NO!
Lin: CUT IT!
NO! NO, SANTIAGO, HELP ME!
[GRUNTING]
HELP!
HEY, GET ME DOWN!
WAIT! SA--
WAIT!
[CELL PHONE RINGS]
[RINGS]
GO.
Carla: SORRY TO DISTURB YOU,
MR. VARGAS.
WE'VE GOT A SLIGHT PROBLEM.
THE EXPEDITION WAS ATTACKED,
AND WE LOST CONTACT
WITH THEM.
ATTACKED?
ATTACKED BY WHOM?
WE'RE ELIMINATING
POSSIBILITIES.
GOMEZ SWEARS HIS MEN ARE
NOWHERE NEAR OUR PEOPLE.
OKAY, HOLD ON.
AND THEY FOUND
THE DAGGER?
YES. I'M
UPLOADING AN IMAGE NOW.
ALL RIGHT,
WHERE'S THE TEAM NOW?
LAST CHECK HAD THEM
LEAVING THE GRAVE SITE.
WHEN FIGHTING BROKE OUT,
WE LOST GPS TRACKING.
Harry: THERE IT IS.
THEY FOUND IT.
THEY REALLY
FOUND IT.
YES.
IT'S EXQUISITE, ISN'T IT?
WAIT A MINUTE.
WAIT A MINUTE,
WHAT IS THAT?
IS THAT A RUBY?
YES, SIR. YOU FORGOT
TO MENTION THAT BEFORE.
WELL, IT ISN'T DOCUMENTED.
I DIDN'T KNOW
ANYTHING ABOUT IT.
OH, MY GOD, THIS
CHANGES EVERYTHING.
I'M SORRY?
HOW DO YOU KNOW FOR SURE
THAT THE TEAM
WAS ATTACKED?
I MEAN, HOW CAN
YOU BE CERTAIN?
WELL, I HEARD GUNFIRE--
WHOSE GUNFIRE?
I ASSUME
IT WAS ENEMY FIRE.
I PAY YOU FOR FACTS,
NOT ASSUMPTIONS!
THEY TOOK IT.
THEY TOOK IT!
I CAN FEEL IT.
I'M COMING THERE!
NO, HARRY, WAIT.
JUST GIVE ME A CHANCE
TO GET SOME INFORMATION.
YOU HAVE HAD YOUR CHANCE.
[PHONE BEEPS]
YOU TELL THEM TO TURN
THIS PLANE AROUND RIGHT NOW!
[GASPS]
[PANTING]
[BRANCHES SNAP]
[WATER SPLASHES]
[GROANING AND PANTING]
PSST! SANTIAGO.
DID YOU GET IT?
WHAT WAS IT?
WHERE'S LIN?
CALL CARLA, TELL HER
TO GET US OUTTA HERE.
YOU JUST LEFT HIM,
DIDN'T YOU?
CALL HER.
GO BACK, CUT HIM DOWN!
I'LL FIND FELICIA.
DON'T MOVE
TILL I GET BACK.
WHAT ABOUT THE DAGGER?
WHAT ABOUT IT?
WELL, WE DON'T GET PAID
TILL WE DELIVER.
MAYBE I SHOULD HOLD IT,
IN CASE YOU DON'T
MAKE IT BACK.
I'LL MAKE IT BACK.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
[DIALING]
I'M GETTING US
OUTTA HERE.
GIMME THE PHONE.
YOU'RE NEVER GONNA FIND HER!
SHE'S PROBABLY DEAD ALREADY!
GIMME THE PHONE!
THEY KNEW
WHAT THEY SIGNED UP FOR!
WE'RE ALL EXPENDABLE.
[DIALING]
UNH!
YOU STUPID...
NO ONE GOES ANYWHERE TILL
WE GET OUR PEOPLE BACK,
YOU HEAR ME?
WELL, I'M NOT
GOING BACK ALONE,
SO YOU CHOOSE.
LIN OR THE GIRL?
[LIN WHIMPERING]
HELLO!
McCALL?
FELICIA!
AAH.
OH, MAN, THIS REALLY BLOWS.
[GRUNTING]
HEY, WHO'S THERE?
[GRUNT]
HEY!
[GRUNTING]
WHO'S THERE?
STAY AWAY!
DON'T COME ANY CLOSER!
I'M ARMED!
[SNAP]
AAH!
[GASPING]
[FOOTSTEPS]
[MUTTERING]
LOCK THEIR LAST POSITION,
AND RUN A SIMULATION
TO TRACK THEIR MOVEMENTS,
BASED ON TIME AND TERRAIN.
WHERE'S MY EXTRACTION TEAM?
I COULD SEND MY GUYS,
BUT THEN WE'LL BE
UNPROTECTED.
WHAT ABOUT THE LOCALS?
THEY'RE SPOOKED.
ONE OF THE WORKERS IS MISSING.
NOW THEY'RE CONVINCED
SOMETHING'S OUT THERE.
I'LL PAY DOUBLE. TRIPLE.
YOU JUST GET ME
SOME REAL MEN.
Santiago: THE LOCALS
HAVE LEGENDS ABOUT THEM.
THAT'S WHY THEY STAY AWAY.
WHO'S THEM?
THE BEASTS.
THEY'RE RUTHLESS.
SHAPED LIKE MEN,
BUT WARPED, LIKE ANIMALS.
IT'S GOT A HEARTBEAT,
I CAN KILL IT.
THEIR CLAWS,
THEY CUT THROUGH THE TREES,
AND THEY
TALK WITH THE JUNGLE.
LOS OSCUROS QUIENES
HABLAN CON ARBOLES.
I DON'T SPEAK JUNGLE.
WELL, IT DOESN'T
TRANSLATE EXACTLY,
BUT "DARK ONES
WHO SPEAK WITH TREES."
YEAH, WELL, I DON'T BELIEVE
IN FAIRY TALES, DUDE.
[BRANCH SNAPS]
[GASPS]
WHAT IS THAT?
YOU SEE ANYTHING?
McCALL?
McCALL!
[CRACKLING NOISE]
[BRANCH SNAPS]
[CRUNCH]
AAH! AAH!
[WHIMPERING]
WHAT HAPPENED?
IT GRABBED ME.
THE TREE,
ONE OF ITS BRANCHES.
THE TREE GRABBED YOU.
I'M TELLING YOU.
IT GRABBED MY ARM!
[GRUNTING]
[PANTING]
[GROANS]
[GRUNTING]
[SHOUTING]
AAH!
[RUMBLING]
[GROUND CRUNCHING]
[FRIGHTENED GRUNTS]
[SCREAMING]
AAH! AAH! AAH!
[SHOUTING]
[SCREAMING]
NO, GET AWAY!
[MACHINE GUN FIRE]
AAH!
[FELICIA WHIMPERING]
FELICIA,
ARE YOU INJURED?
LET ME SEE.
WHAT WAS THAT THING?
McCall:
LET ME SEE.
WE GOTTA GET OUTTA HERE!
PLEASE.
IT'S HERE.
[PANTING]
WHO ARE THEY?
YAMBALLI.
I THOUGHT THEY WERE
SUPPOSED TO BE DEAD.
THEY ARE.
Felicia: THERE'S
SOMETHING ELSE OUT THERE,
SOMETHING WORSE.
COME ON,
WE GOTTA SAVE LIN.
[LIN GROANING]
COME ON,
YOU CAN'T DO THIS.
I'M AMERICAN!
HEY! JUST
LET ME DOWN NOW!
DEJAME! DEJAME!
LET ME GO NOW!
[GROANS]
PLEASE!
PLEASE. COME ON!
I'LL GIVE YOU CIGARETTES,
HUH?
Felicia: I'M TELLING YOU,
THERE'S SOMETHING OUT THERE
THAT EVEN THE YAMBALLI
ARE AFRAID OF.
IT CHASED ME
AND GRABBED ONE OF THEM
AND DRAGGED HIM AWAY
LIKE A RAG DOLL.
WHAT'D IT LOOK LIKE?
IT'S GONNA SOUND CRAZY,
BUT IT--
IT WAS THIS SWARM
OF VINES AND ROOTS,
LIKE--LIKE THE JUNGLE
ITSELF WAS ALIVE.
THE LEGEND. I TOLD YOU.
THEY'RE NOT CREATURES.
THEY'RE MEN IN SUITS,
FLESH AND BLOOD.
NOT THEM.
IT'S THE JUNGLE.
IT'S LIKE IT'S EVERYWHERE,
NOWHERE.
ONE OF THE TREES
GRABBED ME TOO.
Felicia: LOOK AT THIS.
THOSE MARKINGS ON THE TOMB,
THOSE WEREN'T CALENDRICS.
IT'S A WARNING.
WHAT'S IT SAY?
"THE JUNGLE FEEDS ON
THE BLOOD OF THE INVADERS."
[HELICOPTER]
[RADIO CHATTER]
MR. VARGAS, WELCOME.
WE GOT YOUR TENT
ALL SET UP.
HAVE YOU LOCATED THEM?
WE'VE NARROWED DOWN
THEIR LOCATION
AND ARE PREPPING
A TEAM FOR EXTRACTION.
I BROUGHT MY OWN MEN.
JUST SHOW ME WHERE THEY ARE.
I REALLY THINK YOU SHOULD
LET MY MEN DO IT.
THAT DAGGER IS MINE,
AND I'M NOT GONNA LET
SOME SOLDIER OF FORTUNE
STEAL MY BIRTHRIGHT.
WE DON'T KNOW
THAT'S WHAT'S HAPPENED.
SERGEANT McCALL
COMES HIGHLY RECOMMENDED.
AND I'VE SEEN BETTER MEN
GIVE UP FAR MORE FOR FAR LESS.
HARRY...
IT'S TOO DANGEROUS.
WE DON'T KNOW
WHAT'S OUT THERE.
JUST--
JUST GIVE US SOME TIME.
CARLA,
WHERE ARE THEY?
LAST POSITION'S
SIX KILOMETERS DUE EAST.
QUADRANT 64-N.
THANK YOU.
WAIT!
TAKE THIS.
[SCREECHING]
[YAMBALLI GRUNTING]
[GASPING]
HEY. HEY...
LOOK, I DON'T--
I DON'T MEAN YOU ANY HARM.
PLEASE JUST--
JUST LET ME GO
AND I PROMISE
I WON'T EVER COME BACK,
NEVER!
EVER!
Woman, weakly:
WATER.
AAH.
[WOMAN GROANS]
WHAT'D THEY DO TO YOU?
Woman: WATER.
Lin:
I--I DON'T HAVE ANY WATER.
DID YOU COME HERE
TO RESCUE ME?
RESCUE YOU?
NO, I'M A...
I'M A--
I'M AN ARCHEOLOGIST.
I WAS SENT HERE
ON AN EXPEDITION.
BY HARRY VARGAS?
YEAH.
DID YOU FIND IT?
THE DAGGER?
WHO THE HELL
ARE YOU?
DR. EMMA KIRKPATRICK.
TWO WEEKS AGO,
HARRY SENT US HERE
TO FIND HIS PRICELESS
FAMILY HEIRLOOM.
WAIT, WAIT, WAIT.
"US"?
ARE THERE MORE?
WHERE ARE THEY?
DEAD.
I DON'T SEE HIM.
WAIT HERE.
DO YOU THINK HE'S DEAD?
THERE'S NO BLOOD,
THE ROPE'S BEEN CUT.
MY GUESS IS THEY TOOK HIM.
WE CAN'T JUST LEAVE
HIM OUT HERE.
BASE CAMP...CARLA'S
GOT ALL OUR WATCHES
LOCKED INTO HER GPS NETWORK.
Bodyguard: MR. VARGAS,
WE SHOULD REST.
I'LL REST WHEN I'M DEAD.
THERE.
THEY CAME THROUGH HERE.
YOU HEAR THAT?
HEAR WHAT?
THE SILENCE.
NO BIRDS, NO CRICKETS,
NOTHING.
THE AIR,
IT'S SO THICK,
YOU CAN TASTE IT
IN YOUR MOUTH.
[WHISPERING
IN NATIVE LANGUAGE]
[CRYING]
NO, PLEASE.
PLEASE, NO!
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
AAH!
Lin: HEY, LET HER--
LET HER GO!
[SCREAMING]
LEAVE HER ALONE!
DAMN YOU!
PLEASE!
AAH!
WHAT ARE THEY
DOING?
[CRYING]
PLEASE LET ME GO.
[GRUNTING]
[CRYING]
NO!
[WHISPERING]
B'ACK'A'CHAN!
XALA...
B'ACK'A'SHAN.
[MOANING INCANTATION]
[EMMA CRYING]
PLEASE.
XALA! B'ACK'A'SHAN!
[WHIMPERING]
Lin:
WHAT'S HE DOING?
[SHAMAN WHISPERING]
WHAT'S HE DOING?!
B'ACK'A'SHAN!
Lin: HEY,
YOU LEAVE HER ALONE!
[CRYING]
LEAVE HER ALONE!
XALA.
B'ACK'A'SHAN!
XALA! B'ACK'A'SHAN!
[YAMBALLI WHISPERING
IN NATIVE LANGUAGE]
[EMMA CRYING]
HEY!
HEY, HERE YOU GOIN'?
AAH!
WHERE YOU GOIN'?
COME BACK HERE.
HEY! HEY!
YOU GET HER DOWN!
PLEASE!
[LIN GROANS]
GET HER DOWN
FROM THERE!
HEY! HEY!
[RUSTLING]
[RUMBLING AND CRUNCHING]
[WHIMPERING]
HEY!
[EMMA GASPS]
[WHIMPERING]
[VINES CRACKLING]
[SCREAMING]
AAH!
[GROANS]
HELP HER!
AAH!
HEY, HELP HER!
HELP HER! AAH!
[COUGHING, CHOKING]
JEEZ!
[EMMA CHOKING]
[GROANS]
[FLAPPING WINGS]
[SNIFFING]
WHAT IS IT?
[SNIFFS]
THERE.
NATIVES.
WHAT DID THIS?
SHH.
THEY KNOW WE'RE HERE.
[RUSTLING]
[BRANCHES SNAPPING]
OHH!
THERE!
[GROANING]
CHARLIE!
[YAMBALLI SHOUTING]
[MACHINE GUN FIRE]
AAH!
OHH!
[GROANING]
[EXHALES]
NICK! NICK!
HANG ON, NICK! HANG ON!
HARRY, GET OVER HERE!
HARRY!
HANG ON, BUDDY.
GONNA BE FINE.
GIMME YOUR SHIRT! WE NEED
TO PUT SOME PRESSURE ON THIS!
[NICK COUGHING]
HE'S NOT GONNA MAKE IT.
YES, HE IS!
WE JUST NEED
TO STOP THE BLEEDING!
TOLD YOU HE'S
NOT GONNA MAKE IT.
DON'T.
DON'T LET YOUR EMOTIONS
CLOUD YOUR JUDGMENT.
YOU'RE A SOLDIER.
ACT LIKE IT.
McCall: I JUST DON'T
SEE HOW THE YAMBALLI
COULD SURVIVE
WITHOUT ANYONE KNOWING.
THEY'RE NOT EXACTLY
LETTING PEOPLE GO HOME
TO TALK ABOUT IT.
YOU BLAME THEM?
IT'S THEIR TERRITORY.
WE COME IN,
DISTURB THEIR PEACE,
TRAMPLE THEIR GRAVES.
WHAT IS IT?
THIS ISN'T LIN'S.
THEN WHOSE IS IT?
[COMPUTER BEEPING]
HARRY, WHERE ARE YOU?
WE'VE JUST BEEN ATTACKED.
WHAT?
ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
PREPARE THE CAMP
FOR IMMEDIATE EVACUATION.
NO, THIS IS CRAZY.
I'M SENDING IN A TEAM.
WE'RE PULLING YOU OUT.
GO, NOW.
NO, DON'T WORRY
ABOUT ME.
IT'S MY JOB TO WORRY.
WHO ATTACKED YOU?
DON'T WORRY ABOUT ME.
HARRY,
WHO ATTACKED YOU?
TALK TO ME.
HARRY!
YOU EVER NOTICE
THE AIR OUT HERE?
HARRY?
IS THAT BLOOD
ON YOUR FACE?
IT'S INVIGORATING.
HARRY.
[TAPS COMPUTER]
HARRY!
[POUNDING KEYBOARD]
[STATIC BUZZING]
YOU HEARD HIM.
BREAK IT DOWN,
ALL OF IT.
ALERT THE CHOPPERS.
WE NEED AN AIRLIFT
WITHIN THE HOUR.
[GUNSHOT]
Man: ATTACKING!
ATTACKING!
[GUNSHOT, MEN SHOUTING]
Man:
YAMBALLI! ATTACKING!
[SECOND MAN
SPEAKING SPANISH]
Third man:
NO, NO, NO, NO, NO!
[MEN SHOUTING IN SPANISH]
AAH! AAH!
[SHOUTING]
NO! LET ME GO!
LET ME GO!
HEY!
[GUNSHOT]
AAH!
[SHOUTING]
LET'S GO!
GET UP!
LOOK OUT!
[EXPLOSION]
AAH!
[GROANS]
[YAMBALLI SHOUTING]
[GRUNTS]
OH!
Santiago:
BOATS ARE THRASHED.
HOW WE GONNA
GET OUT OF HERE?
LET'S WORRY ABOUT THAT
AFTER WE GET OUR PEOPLE BACK.
WELL, IT'S
AT LEAST A WEEK BY FOOT.
WHY WOULD ANYBODY
DO THIS?
SANTIAGO WAS RIGHT.
WE INVADED
THEIR TERRITORY,
ROBBED THEIR GRAVE.
Felicia:
IT'S MORE THAN THAT.
I'VE SPENT YEARS
WITH INDIGENOUS TRIBES,
AND I'VE NEVER SEEN
ANYTHING LIKE THIS.
ATTACKING IN DISGUISE,
UNPROVOKED.
MERCILESS.
IT'S GOTTA HAVE SOMETHING
TO DO WITH THE FOLKLORE.
SELVA DE LOS MUERTOS.
THE CREATURE.
OH, COME ON!
WE'VE BEEN OVER THAT.
YOU DIDN'T SEE IT.
WE DID.
YOU WERE UNDER ATTACK.
YOUR STRESS LEVEL
WAS OFF THE CHARTS, OKAY?
BATTLE ALTERS
PERCEPTIONS,
ESPECIALLY IF YOU'RE
NOT USED TO IT, TRUST ME.
I'VE BEEN THERE.
HE'S NEVER GONNA
BELIEVE US.
NOT TILL HE SEES IT
WITH HIS OWN EYES.
I'M TELLING YOU
I KNOW WHAT I SAW.
IT DOESN'T MATTER.
IT DOESN'T MATTER
WHO'S OUT THERE,
WHAT I BELIEVE.
WE'RE STUCK.
SO YOU WANT TO SURVIVE,
WE HAVE TO FOCUS,
WORK TOGETHER.
OKAY?
LET'S DO IT.
Carla: LET ME GO!
PUT ME DOWN!
PUT ME DOWN! NO!
LET ME GO!
NO!
[RUMBLING]
[WHISPERING
IN NATIVE LANGUAGE]
[WHISPERING EXCITEDLY]
[BRANCHES SNAPPING]
[WHISPERING]
[MAN GASPING]
[BRANCHES SNAPPING,
GROUND RUMBLING]
[YAMBALLI COWERING]
[SHOUTING IN NATIVE LANGUAGE]
[GROANING]
[CARLA CRYING]
NO!
HELLO? HELLO?
DOES ANYONE HEAR ME?
DOES ANYONE EVEN KNOW
WE'RE OUT HERE?
McCall: I GOT IT.
I NEED BATTERIES
OR A PORTABLE POWER SUPPLY.
HOW DOES IT WORK?
THE WATCHES
CARLA GAVE US.
THEY'RE ALL CONNECTED
TO A MASTER GPS NETWORK.
IF I CAN GET JUICE IN THIS,
WE CAN LOCATE
ANYONE WEARING ONE.
GUYS, LOOK AT THIS.
LOOKS LIKE
HARRY'S BEEN HERE.
HOW DO YOU KNOW?
A PASSPORT. LAPTOP.
GREAT. HE'S PROBABLY
DEAD, TOO.
OH, NO.
NO. NO, NO, NO, NO, NO.
WHAT?
"MATT BAKER. LINGUIST.
"DAYTON RILEY,
MILITARY SPECIALIST.
"DR. EMMA KIRKPATRICK?
ARCHAEOLOGIST."
THERE WAS
ANOTHER EXPEDITION TEAM.
THAT EXPLAINS
THE BLOODY T-SHIRT
AND THE BOOT PRINT
IN THE MUD.
WHY DIDN'T THEY TELL US?
'CAUSE THEY'RE
PROBABLY ALL DEAD.
[WHIMPERING]
TAI'K!
LIN.
[PANTING]
LIN!
[WHISPERING]
WHAT HAPPENED?
ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
NOT REALLY, NO.
NO.
I THOUGHT THE YAMBALLI
DIDN'T EXIST.
WHY DIDN'T YOU TELL ME
ABOUT THE OTHER TEAM?
WHAT?
EMMA KIRKPATRICK,
ANTHROPOLOGIST?
SHE WAS HERE.
I WATCHED HER DIE.
WHAT ARE YOU
TALKING ABOUT?
DON'T LIE TO ME!
JUST DON'T!
THOSE ARE HER HANDS
OVER THERE!
YOU'RE SICK.
YOU SENT US ALL
IN HERE TO DIE.
LIN, PLEASE.
PLEASE LISTEN TO ME, OKAY?
I SWEAR I DIDN'T
KNOW ANYTHING ABOUT THIS.
YOU HAVE TO BELIEVE ME.
I'M HERE JUST LIKE YOU.
PLEASE.
WELL, THEN HARRY
SCREWED US ALL.
THIS IS IT.
THIS IS WHERE
THEY FOUND IT.
A GREAT MAN LIES HERE
WITH NO LIMITS BUT THE SKY.
IT'S A FUNNY THING
COMING FACE TO FACE
WITH YOUR ANCESTORS.
YOURS IS THE GLORY.
MR. VARGAS, THIS IS
A NEEDLE IN A HAYSTACK.
WE'RE NEVER GONNA
FIND THEM LIKE THIS.
WELL, THAT DAGGER
BELONGS TO ME.
I WILL FIND THEM.
WHERE DID YOU GO, HUH?
THERE'S FIGHTING HERE.
AND DEATH.
IF McCALL
WENT THAT WAY,
WHY IS THERE SUCH
A STRUGGLE OVER HERE?
TAKE A GUESS, MR. VARGAS.
SERGEANT McCALL
IS SMART ENOUGH
NOT TO WAVE HIS EXIT LIKE A
FLAG.
LISTEN.
[LOW GROAN]
THE JUNGLE IS TRYING
TO TELL US SOMETHING.
IT'S ANGRY.
YEAH. THAT MAKES
TWO OF US.
[GROWLING]
CAN YOU FEEL THAT?
[BRANCHES CRACKLING,
GROANING]
HUH?
CAN YOU FEEL THAT?
FEEL WHAT?
[MUFFLED] HELP!
HELP!
[GROWLING]
[CHOKING]
HELP!
[GROWLING]
[GRUNTS]
HARRY! HARRY!
HARRY, HELP ME!
AAH!
I SHOULD'VE SEEN IT.
IT WAS TOO EASY
AND FOR TOO MUCH MONEY.
VARGAS PREYS ON WEAKNESS.
HE SET US ALL UP.
WE DON'T KNOW THAT.
THOSE PEOPLE COULD BE
SIPPING MARGARITAS
IN CABO RIGHT NOW
FOR ALL WE KNOW.
YOU BELIEVE THAT?
HARRY'S AN OPPORTUNIST.
HE'S NOT HEARTLESS.
HIS DONATIONS HAVE KEPT
MY FOUNDATION GOING
FOR THE LAST TWO YEARS.
SO WHY ARE YOU
DEFENDING HIM?
I'M NOT.
I JUST CAN'T BELIEVE
HE'S THAT DUPLICITOUS.
OR WE'RE THAT GULLIBLE.
Santiago:
IT'S LIKE YOU SAID,
HE'S A CONQUISTADOR.
HE'LL DO ANYTHING
FOR HIS TREASURE.
[current crackling]
WELL, HE'S NOT MOVING,
BUT THAT'S LIN.
CUT ME A PIECE.
LOOK. THERE'S TWO MORE.
ONE'S MOVING DUE EAST
BY THE GRAVES.
IF HARRY'S HERE, MAYBE THAT'S
HIM OUT THERE LOOKING FOR US.
IF HARRY'S HERE, HE'S
ONLY LOOKING FOR ONE THING.
HERE.
IN CASE I DON'T
COME BACK.
WHAT?
WHERE ARE YOU GOING?
TO FIND LIN AND SEE WHO ELSE
IS OUT THERE.
I SUGGEST YOU TWO
START TO WORK
ON THAT TWO-WAY RADIO.
NO. I'M GOING WITH YOU.
I CAN'T ASK YOU
TO DO THAT.
THAT'S TOO DANGEROUS.
I'M NOT GOING ANYWHERE.
OUR BEST CHANCE
OF GETTING RESCUED
IS STAYING RIGHT HERE.
WELL, THIS MISSION
ISN'T OVER
UNTIL WE'RE ALL HOME,
INCLUDING LIN.
TRUTHFULLY, I SUGGEST
WE ALL STAY TOGETHER,
BUT THAT'S UP TO YOU.
WHAT IF YOU
WERE OUT THERE?
WHAT WOULD YOU
WANT US TO DO?
[SPEAKING
NATIVE LANGUAGE]
Carla: LIN.
LIN, TALK TO ME.
THEY'RE GONNA
KILL ME NOW.
DON'T SAY THAT.
SOMEONE'S GONNA
FIND US.
LISTEN!
IN A MINUTE, SOMEBODY'S
GONNA COME OVER HERE
AND UNTIE ME,
AND WHEN HE DOES, I'M GONNA
SHOVE HIM ON TOP OF YOU.
NO, NO, NO.
DON'T MAKE THEM ANGRY.
THEY KEEP KNIVES
STRAPPED TO THEIR LEGS.
OKAY, YOU JUST TRY
AND GRAB IT.
I CAN'T.
YES, YOU CAN.
YOU JUST GRAB THE KNIFE.
YOU JUST GRAB IT.
YOU GRAB IT!
WAIT, LIN!
LIN, WAIT!
WAIT.
[GRUNTS]
[MAN SHOUTS
IN NATIVE LANGUAGE]
[LIN PANTING]
OHH!
CARLA, DID YOU GET IT?
I GOT IT!
[STRUGGLING]
[SPEAKING NATIVE LANGUAGE]
JUST LET ME GO, PLEASE!
[SHOUTING
IN NATIVE LANGUAGE]
Shaman, whispering:
B'ACK'A'SHAN!
[MOANS]
XALA!
B'ACK'A'SHAN!
[WHISPERING]
PLEASE DON'T DO THIS.
JUST LET ME GO.
DAMN IT.
[WHISPERING
IN NATIVE LANGUAGE]
WAIT!
XALA! B'ACK'A'SHAN!
WAIT! DON'T--
DON'T GO!
WAIT! JUST--
JUST JUST STAY HERE!
WAIT! DON'T GO!
JUST--UNH!
JUST STAY HERE!
WAIT!
[PANTING]
[VINES CRACKLING]
PLEASE!
CARLA!
[LOW GROWLING]
GET OUT HERE,
YOU SICK BASTARDS!
HELP HIM!
[CHOKING]
NO!
OH, MY GOD.
OH, MY GOD, NO.
[LIN GROANING]
[GRUNTING]
[BRANCH SNAPS]
[WHIMPERING]
[SPEAKING NATIVE LANGUAGE]
PLEASE. PLEASE
JUST LET ME GO.
[SPEAKING NATIVE LANGUAGE]
PLEASE?
I KNOW YOU
UNDERSTAND ME!
YOU KNOW
THIS IS WRONG.
[SPEAKS NATIVE LANGUAGE]
SHH!
IT'S OKAY, PLEASE.
PLEASE JUST LET ME GO.
LET ME GO, PLEASE,
OKAY?
IT'S OKAY.
[SPEAKS NATIVE LANGUAGE]
[SHOUTING
IN NATIVE LANGUAGE]
THIS IS CRAZY.
FEEL LIKE EVERY BRANCH IS
GONNA JUMP OUT AND GRAB ME.
SELVA DE LOS MUERTOS.
WHAT IF IT'S NOT
THE JUNGLE THAT'S CURSED?
WHAT IF IT'S THAT DAGGER?
EVERYTHING WAS CALM
TILL WE TOOK THAT THING
OUT OF THE TOMB.
WHY WOULD THE YAMBALLI CARE
ABOUT THE WEAPON
OF A CONQUISTADOR?
YOU TELL ME.
HEY, SANTIAGO,
LET ME SEE THAT DAGGER.
IT'S DEFINITELY SPANISH
IN ORIGIN.
AT LEAST THE HILT IS.
HUH.
WHAT?
SO THIS ISN'T
THE ORIGINAL BLADE.
THE HANDLE
CAME FROM SPAIN,
BUT THE BLADE
IS FROM SOMEWHERE ELSE.
IS THAT WRITING?
LOOKS LIKE THERE'S SOMETHING
HERE UNDERNEATH THE HILT.
[POUNDING DAGGER]
HEY, WHOA!
WHOA! WHOA!
WHAT?
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
I'M TRYING TO SEE IF THERE'S
SOMETHING WRITTEN UNDER THERE.
OKAY, I AGREED
TO HELP FIND LIN,
FINE.
BUT WE'RE NOT GONNA
DESTROY THIS KNIFE, OKAY?
IT'S OUR TICKET
OUT OF HERE.
HEY, WAIT A SECOND.
SOMEONE'S MOVING...
FAST.
[BRANCHES CRACKLING]
AAH!
[MUFFLED SCREAM]
SHH.
IT'S ALIVE,
THE JUNGLE.
IT'S A LIVING,
BREATHING ENTITY.
[WHIMPERING]
JUST LIKE YOU AND ME.
YOU KNEW.
YOU KNEW ALL ALONG.
SICK SON OF A BITCH!
BE QUIET.
QUIET! QUIET!
NO!
YOU'RE DISTURBING IT!
LET GO.
QUIET!
GET OFF OF ME!
CARLA!
CARLA, LISTEN TO ME,
CALM DOWN.
NO! NO!
NO!
QUIET!
McCall: VARGAS!
HANDS UP.
I SAID HANDS UP.
WHY SO TESTY, SERGEANT?
WE'RE ALL
ON THE SAME TEAM.
YOUR WEAPON--
PULL IT OUT SLOWLY,
THROW IT AWAY.
YOU KNOW,
I WAS HOPING
TO MEET
YOUR DAUGHTER ONE DAY
AND INSPIRE HER WITH
TALES OF YOUR HEROICS.
Felicia:
WHAT'S HAPPENING OUT HERE?
IF I KNEW THAT,
I WOULDN'T NEED YOU.
OR
THE OTHER TEAM?
THEY ALL DIED,
DIDN'T THEY?
AN UNFORTUNATE
NECESSITY.
YOU BASTARD.
YOU SENT US OUT HERE
KNOWING FULL WELL
THIS WAS A SUICIDE MISSION.
I DIDN'T KNOW.
I SWEAR, I DIDN'T KNOW
ABOUT THE OTHER TEAM.
I NEVER
WOULD'VE SENT THEM!
IT DOESN'T MATTER!
THERE'S A MONSTER
OUT THERE,
AND WE'RE STANDING
AROUND ARGUING.
WELL SAID.
WE'RE WASTING TIME.
GIVE ME MY DAGGER.
SAT PHONE, HAND IT OVER.
NO. THE DAGGER FIRST,
THEN THE PHONE.
HOW ABOUT I JUST SHOOT YOU
AND TAKE IT
FROM YOUR DEAD HAND?
WELL, GET ON
WITH IT THEN.
SHOOT ME!
[RUMBLING]
GET BACK. GET BACK!
GET BACK!
[GUNSHOTS]
YAH!
AAH! AAH!
HELP! AAH!
[CARLA WHIMPERING]
NO! HELP!
HELP!
LET'S GO!
LET'S GO, GO, GO!
AAH!
COME ON!
COME ON! COME ON!
COME ON, COME ON,
COME ON!
AAH! NO, WAIT!
I CAN'T. I CAN'T!
GET UP!
IS THAT THE THING
YOU SAW BEFORE?
KIND OF,
ONLY 10 TIMES BIGGER.
BULLETS DIDN'T
MAKE A DENT.
HARRY PUSHED HER.
HE PUSHED HER
INTO THAT THING...
[GASPS]
TO SAVE
HIS OWN ASS.
YOU BELIEVE US NOW? HUH?
I DON'T KNOW
WHAT TO BELIEVE.
HOW DO THE YAMBALLI
SURVIVE OUT HERE
WITH THAT THING
RUNNING AROUND?
MAYBE THEY DON'T JUST
TALK TO THE JUNGLE.
MAYBE THEY CONTROL IT.
WE GOTTA GO BACK
AND GET HARRY'S SAT PHONE.
IT'S THE ONLY WAY
OUT OF HERE.
McCALL.
WHAT?
[VINE CRACKLING]
McCALL, LOOK OUT!
WHAT?
AAH!
GET IT OFF!
[GRUNTING]
GET IT OUT!
UNH!
McCall: KEEP RUNNING!
KEEP RUNNING!
McCall: LET'S GO!
[SCREAMING]
[GROWLING]
[GROANING]
YOU STUPID BASTARD.
SINCE WHEN ARE YOU
THE HERO TYPE?
WHO KNEW?
[GASPING]
I NEED TO STOP
THE BLEEDING.
GIVE ME A BELT
OR SOMETHING.
DOUSE IT
IN FRESH WATER.
I ALWAYS THOUGHT
THE DOCTOR TITLE
FOR ANTHROPOLOGISTS
WAS B.S.
YOU WORK IN ENOUGH
THIRD WORLD WAR-TORN COUNTRIES,
YOU LEARN HOW
TO DRESS A WOUND.
SANTIAGO, I'M GONNA TIE THIS
REALLY TIGHT.
IT'S GONNA HURT, OKAY?
BITE.
ONE...
TWO...
THREE.
[MOANING]
[CRYING]
DID YOU ALWAYS WANT KIDS?
COUPLE YEARS AGO,
AN EX-GIRLFRIEND SHOWED UP
ON MY DOORSTEP
WITH A 3-YEAR-OLD GIRL.
SAID, "I'M GLAD YOU'RE ALIVE.
NOW IT'S YOUR TURN."
SHE HAS YOUR EYES.
WHAT'S HER NAME?
AMBER RENEE STARDUST McCALL.
WOW. THAT'S SOME NAME.
I WASN'T THERE
WHEN THEY FILLED OUT
THE BIRTH CERTIFICATE.
HER MOM'S KINDA--
UNIQUE?
I WAS GONNA SAY PSYCHO,
BUT, YEAH, UNIQUE'S ABOUT RIGHT.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
CAN'T KEEP RUNNING
FROM THAT THING.
WHATEVER IT IS,
WE GOTTA KILL IT.
WITH WHAT?
HOW DO YOU
KILL A TREE?
YOU CHOP IT DOWN?
OR YOU BURN IT.
THIS ISN'T
JUST A TREE.
IT'S SENTIENT.
IT THINKS
LIKE WE DO.
WELL, GOOD. THEN
IT'LL FEEL PAIN LIKE WE DO.
[COUGHING]
THIS THING'S GONNA GET
INFECTED OUT HERE.
THERE'S A MEDICAL KIT
AT CAMP.
IF WE GET BACK,
CAN YOU SLOW THAT DOWN?
YEAH.
CAN YOU WALK?
HELP ME.
[GROANING]
McCall: I JUST DON'T SEE
HOW A GIANT KILLER PLANT
COULD WREAK HAVOC LIKE THIS
WITHOUT ANYONE KNOWING
ABOUT IT.
WHO KNOWS.
MAYBE IT WAS ON
A SICK LEAF.
[LAUGHS]
CARNIVOROUS PLANTS ARE RARE,
BUT NOTHING NEW.
I'VE SEEN A NEPENTHES
RAJAH SPECIMEN
OVER THREE FEET TALL.
IT KILLS FROGS,
BIRDS, AND EVEN RATS.
WELL, THIS ONE'S A LOT
BIGGER THAN THREE FEET.
TRUE, BUT THE RAIN FOREST
IS CONSTANTLY EVOLVING.
HALF THE SPECIES OUT HERE
HAVEN'T EVEN
BEEN CLASSIFIED YET.
YEAH, WELL, SOMEONE
SHOULD'VE MENTIONED THAT
IN THE BRIEFING.
[BREEZE BLOWING]
[RUMBLING]
[DEEP GROAN]
STAY HERE.
[TREES CRACKLING]
[LOUD CRACKLING]
Santiago:
McCALL, WHAT'S OUT THERE?
[TREES CRACKLING]
SEE ANYTHING?
NOTHING.
[RUNNING FOOTSTEPS]
Santiago: McCALL!
SANTIAGO,
LIGHT YOUR TORCH!
LIGHT IT! LIGHT IT!
GIVE IT TO ME!
WHAT WAS IT?
[SNAP]
AAH!
[FELICIA SCREAMS]
HOLD ON!
GOD!
GET IT OFF ME!
OH, MY GOD!
BURN IT! BURN IT!
GET IT OFF ME!
HOLD ON! HOLD ON!
AAH! AAH!
BURN IT!
[SANTIAGO GROANS]
GET IT!
McCall: YOU'RE OKAY.
YOU'RE OKAY.
[SANTIAGO GROANS]
[WHIMPERING]
Santiago:
WHAT DO WE DO NOW?
McCall:
QUIET. JUST STAY TOGETHER.
WHAT IF IT COMES BACK?
SHH! WHAT'S THAT? LISTEN.
LISTEN.
[YAMBALLI SPEAKING
NATIVE LANGUAGE]
McCall: WHAT IS THAT?
[GRUNTS]
HUH.
[FELICIA GASPS]
[GROANING]
HEY, YOU ALL RIGHT?
EVERYTHING'S BLURRY.
OH, NO.
WHAT?
LIN'S WATCH.
I DON'T THINK
I CAN DO THIS.
YES, YOU CAN.
HEY, LOOK AT ME.
I'M GONNA SEE
MY DAUGHTER AGAIN,
AND I'M GONNA DO
WHATEVER IT TAKES
TO GET YOU BACK
TO SAVING THE WORLD,
BUT YOU GOTTA STAY SHARP.
YOU UNDERSTAND ME?
NO MORE DOOM OR GLOOM,
OKAY?
OKAY.
[GROANS]
HEY!
LEAVE HIM ALONE!
TAI'K! TAI'KA' RAK!
HUH.
HE UNDERSTOOD YOU.
IT'S K'ICHE,
A MAYAN DIALECT.
MAYBE IT'S CLOSE
TO THEIR LANGUAGE.
S'IK BOW, JUN KAMIKAL.
EL-ES-AJ Q'ATOBAL.
B'TAK AWAJ NIMALA-J K'ULEL.
WHAT'S HE SAYING?
WE TOOK THE BLADE,
AWOKE THE PROTECTOR.
THEY CALL THAT THING
A PROTECTOR?
THE WARNINGS
AT THE TOMB.
SO IT'S OUR FAULT?
I THOUGHT THEY CONTROLLED IT?
NIM-JA-LA
KU'EL-EL KAN-OOK?
NABE KANOQ NIM-ALA-J K'ULEL
PETIK PA ULEW.
IN THE PAST, INVADERS
ATTACKED THEIR LAND...
[SPEAKING NATIVE LANGUAGE
AS FELICIA TRANSLATES]
TRIBAL ELDERS PRAYED,
SUMMONED A PROTECTOR.
HE FED ON THE BLOOD
OF THE INVADER,
BUT HE DIDN'T STOP.
HE ATTACKED THEM,
SO THEY CREATED A...
A TALISMAN,
PART YAMBALLI, PART INVADER,
TO STOP THE BEAST.
A TALISMAN?
[SHAMAN SPEAKING
NATIVE LANGUAGE]
Felicia:
THE DAGGER.
WE'RE SUPPOSED TO FIGHT
THAT THING WITH A KNIFE?
NAK'IK K'A
CH-PAM ULEW,
TIO-XA-LAJ ULEW!
NO.
HE'S PINNED IT
TO THE EARTH,
AT THE SACRED PLACE.
THE TOMB.
AAH!
AAH! WHAT IS THAT?!
WHAT IS IT?!
IT'S INSIDE OF ME!
GET IT OUT!
S'IK BOW PAQ'!
JUN YAWABIL 'OL TZEM!
GET IT OUT OF ME!
CANTE EH CANTE.
A HEART...
FOR A HEART.
CANTE EH CANTE.
NIMALAJ K'ULEL TE!
I DON'T KNOW.
MAYBE HE SAID
IF THE PROTECTOR DIES,
WE CAN SAVE SANTIAGO.
McCall:
WE HAVE TO KILL IT.
THAT SOUNDS LIKE
A REALLY GOOD PLAN.
I'LL DO IT.
GIVE IT TO ME.
THE KNIFE.
HEART FOR A HEART.
I'LL DO IT.
TELL HIM!
CANTE EH CANTE.
[SPEAKING NATIVE LANGUAGE]
[GROANING]
Warrior: EK.
EK A MUQ-UL WI! BAI HI!
Santiago: PLEASE,
GET IT OUT OF ME.
[HEART BEATING]
McCall:
WHAT IS THAT?
Felicia:
IS THAT BEATING?
CANTE EH CANTE!
MA-I'IH!
CHUQ' CANTE OH K'ULEL!
HEY, WHAT ARE THEY SAYING?
SOMETHING ABOUT
HEART OF THE INVADER.
[DRAWS DAGGER]
STAND BACK.
AAH!
[LOUD RUMBLING]
[SHOUTING
IN NATIVE LANGUAGE]
[SECOND WARRIOR
SHOUTING]
[LOUD CRASHING]
[FRIGHTENED YAMBALLI SPEAKING
IN NATIVE LANGUAGE]
WHAT'S HAPPENING?
I THINK WE
PISSED IT OFF.
MAYBE WE
SHOULD TAKE IT OUT.
NOW!
[YAMBALLI SHOUTING]
[FELICIA SCREAMS]
AAH!
RUN!
GO! GO! GO!
GO! GO!
[SPEAKING NATIVE LANGUAGE]
I DON'T UNDERSTAND.
IT SHOULD'VE WORKED.
WE'RE MISSING SOMETHING.
LET ME SEE IT.
[DAGGER CLANKS]
THERE'S SOMETHING WRITTEN
UNDER HERE.
IF I COULD JUST GET
THIS THING APART.
HERE.
[DAGGER CLANKS ON LOG]
COME ON!
LET ME SEE IT.
McCall:
WHAT'S IT SAY?
"ONE HEART
FOR ALL HEARTS."
THAT'S WHAT THE SHAMAN SAID,
WHAT IT SAID ON THE TOMB.
NO, HE SAID,
"A HEART FOR A HEART."
HE WASN'T TALKING
ABOUT SAVING SANTIAGO.
HE WANTED TO SACRIFICE HIM.
AND I VOLUNTEERED.
THAT'S WHY THE CONQUISTADOR
WAS IN THE YAMBALLI GRAVE.
THEY KILLED HIM
TO IMPRISON THE CREATURE.
A HUMAN SACRIFICE.
[BRANCH SNAPS]
[GASP]
[YAMBALLI PANTING]
GIVE ME THAT.
I GOTTA LEAD 'EM AWAY,
GET 'EM OFF OUR SCENT.
DON'T LEAVE.
STAY HERE. DON'T MOVE.
I'LL BE BACK.
[FELICIA WHIMPERING]
AAH!
YAAH!
THAT SUCKS.
OHH!
AAH!
[GROWLING]
[PANTING]
AAH!
[GROANS]
[GROWLS]
CRAP.
TA'IK MAK BOW!
[GASPING]
HEART OF THE INTRUDER!
THIS HAS GOTTA END.
I'M SORRY.
Felicia: McCALL, DON'T!
I'M SORRY. I TRIED.
BA-TAK OL-NEK!
LET HER GO!
I'LL KILL HIM!
BA-TAK OL-NEK!
OL' A WINIK!
I'LL DO IT!
Felicia:
IT WON'T WORK!
THE SACRIFICE HAS TO BE
AN OUTSIDER!
THAT'S WHAT
THEY KEPT SAYING!
[WARRIOR CHOKING]
YOU WANT ME?
[GROWLS]
DO IT!
[GUNSHOT]
[FELICIA WHIMPERING]
HAND IT OVER,
McCALL.
Felicia:
HARRY, YOU DON'T KNOW--
GIVE ME MY DAGGER!
DON'T DO ANYTHING
STUPID, HARRY.
Felicia: HARRY!
HARRY, THE CREATURE
AND THE DAGGER ARE CONNECTED!
BE QUIET!
AAH!
OH!
WHY, YOU SON OF A BITCH!
UNH!
OH!
[LOUD RUMBLING]
AAH!
AAH! AAH!
NO!
THAT DAGGER'S
RIGHTFULLY MINE!
GET AWAY FROM IT!
DON'T TELL ME
WHAT TO DO!
I DON'T WORK FOR YOU
ANYMORE!
AAH!
[LOUD RUMBLING]
[CRYING]
[SHOUTING IN NATIVE LANGUAGE]
[LOW GROAN]
[WARRIOR SHOUTING]
[SCREAMING]
[GROANS]
TIME TO DIE, SERGEANT.
[LOUD CRASHING]
OH!
[GROANS]
OHH! OH!
AAH! AAH!
YOU FIRST.
AAH!
[VINES CREAKING]
[GRUNTING]
AAH!
[MOANING]
[TREE MOANING]
IS IT OVER?
TELL ME IT'S OVER.
[FOOTSTEPS]
IT'S OVER.
CAPTIONING PERFORMED BY
AEGIS RAPIDTEXT