READY TO RUN
Where is the microphone?
I am wearing, Bob?
I was called
disaster in the White House.
I had an appointment
with a guy tonight ...
We are ready?
And my teeth?
It turns ...
Hello. Signed by Bullwinkel
on the roof of the White House ...
where run
very strange rumors.
The President would have been eaten
by a sort of giant flying nose ...
There was a ceremony honoring
Jensen, astronaut disappeared
and then everything went wrong ...
My hair!
What is ...
Looks like a gadget space
Giant has just landed.
I shall approach ...
Excuse me, I'm on TV.
I see a door that opens
and soldiers
encircling the capsule.
A cute little squirrel comes
out of this strange spaceship.
I do not know what happens ...
It's hell!
Do not do it ...
it's my producer!
My cameraman is dead!
How long ...
I'll shoot!
THE SPACE MUTANTS
TWENTY YEARS EARLIER
Good luck, Earl.
Thank you Dr. Frubar.
Dad.
Goodbye, Josie. I love you.
Goodbye, Dad.
7 ...
6 ...
5 ...
4 ...
3 ... 2 ... 1 ...
Fire!
Successful ejection. It is in orbit.
EJECTION OF FUEL
Control station, the dial
indicates a fuel leak.
It was she who supported
button!
Remove this girl away.
Let me go!
This is not me!
Earl, by Dr. F.
As you can see,
- You're dry.
- How?
I fear that Josie has pressed
the eject button on the fuel.
We try to find a solution.
Send help!
Impossible, Earl.
Here's the situation.
You can not save you.
Open your secret pocket.
Flash Special Live
the space capsule ...
Here Earl Jensen
from interplanetary space.
Hello, America,
My name is Earl Jensen.
I learned that I have no
fuel and I can not
return to Earth.
But do not pity me.
It is an honor
to give his life
for his country.
Now the flag.
The great visionary leader
Department of Space,
Dr. Frubar,
did everything
in his power to save me.
Under his leadership demanding
and stimulating
we will continue
conquer and control
interplanetary space.
You can do something.
If we had enough money
for our operations,
I would have been safe
in space ...
So please, open
your hearts and wallets.
Send your contribution
Department of Space.
And never a tragedy
like this will not happen again.
Wait ... I see ...
I almost.
Goodbye. God will sell out.
Earl is "God bless you" ...
Damn!
What a terrible tragedy ...
Goodbye, America
and goodbye
Josie darling.
I will return, Dr. Frubar.
You can count on.
Darby.
One minute
I'm supposed to work.
But then Josie,
we love.
Josie, has a good time.
Think of your reputation.
Josie, enjoying life.
It is so short.
This is the way
of evil and sin ...
Listen to your heart,
He said: "Kiss me, kiss me!"
You wanted him, Josie!
No, you're scared! Your heart tells you:
"Save yourself, be wise!"
Do not live in trouble
and solitude, little sister!
Listen to me, Josie. I know what
is best for you and your dear soul.
Men want a wife pure.
You do not buy a cow
if the milk is free.
What bullshit!
Who wants to marry a cow?
Your father said:
Either we live or we die.
What do you know?
You're a whore,
a trail,
an alley cat,
a hussy!
And you a prude,
an icicle, a lesbian,
bouffeuse a tuft
who donned carrots!
You insult me!
You go roast in hell!
You are the devil!
And you a penguin rampant!
Sodomite, pig,
loose woman!
Frigid dyke,
ass full of cobwebs!
Drag, sucking, sperm bank,
bag fuck, whore of Satan!
Grazers carpeting,
pubis polar ice queen!
Bitch, bitch, drag,
runner, whore ...
In addition, you have fake boobs!
Bitch!
Darby Okay, I'm ready.
What's this?
It's incredible!
It's fantastic.
It is not possible.
- But yes!
- Come, Josie.
Your big bang is there waiting for you.
DEPARTMENT OF SPACE
Hello beauty.
- Are you married?
- My wild beast ...
Your hot lips ...
I burn! It takes me a fireman!
Darling!
Turn off me with your big hose!
Sir,
advertisers are there.
Department of Space.
The Department of Space?
Josie Jensen of the Centre.
Listen, Josie, get married
and stop bugging us.
Listen to me.
Check the details
6245 and 71102.
Well, if you insist.
What a magnificent sight.
Come, gentlemen.
I have something to show you ...
Look at the screen.
SATPUB
You are gallant company
and a screen as big as Oregon
suddenly unfolds ...
Brad, you have bad breath!
For breath
fresh mint,
use toothpaste and Smiley
send a kiss to your problems.
Fucking machine!
Gentlemen, SatPub!
My little heart.
What I like you ...
Sir,
advertisers expect.
I check your details ...
On the big screen!
What's this?
- A new sun?
- A new planet?
No, it's a fucking asteroid!
And headed towards us!
- You have to call Dr. F.!
- Not me!
Gentlemen, this is for you
the opportunity to participate in early
adventure advertising
The most dramatic history.
So who is starting for as little
one billion dollars each?
POST EMERGENCY
Who has the balls
appropriating the world?
It is a unique opportunity.
Who wants to take a percentage?
Dr. F. here Tomkins, radar.
Hopefully it's important.
We have identified a meteorite.
He heads back to Earth.
Make the jump!
Well, sir.
It is not possible!
But if!
Stop the missiles!
Why?
Yes, why?
Because it has a green tail!
And then?
Yes, so what?
The green tail indicates
the presence of metal.
And then?
This is the spacecraft
my father! Stop it!
Do not quit.
I repeat, do not quit!
If you do that,
you're fired!
I'm waiting!
Are you kidding me?
I'm hosting my father!
Wait for me!
Where is he?
There has to follow the trail.
Sinners!
You can not ignore Jesus!
You can not forget Jesus!
You can not live without Jesus!
It's impossible, impossible!
No, you can not!
You can not!
We can not fight with Jesus!
Can not
and we will not!
We can not fight with Jesus!
This is the way to hell!
1st ... Press the mushroom!
2nd ... It goes too fast!
3rd ... It will fly!
4e ... Say goodbye!
You can not play rock
with Jesus, even to laugh.
You can not play rock with
Jesus is a bastard!
Come on, Jesus!
Sinners, sinners!
Repent now!
And now, sinners,
close your eyes guilty
and look up to heaven.
Lord, take me now!
Warning!
Who is this old?
- What is he doing?
- He has a gun!
Warning!
This is blasphemy!
Dad!
It is the devil!
I beg you ...
I must make my report
Dr. Frubar.
What happened,
Mr. Jensen?
No, I must see Dr. Frubar.
What happened?
How did you survive?
I drifted further and further
in space ...
- This is nonsense!
- I do not believe it!
Inventions!
Please
Give me water.
Josie, Let's get him. He is delirious.
Wait.
Those were wonderful years.
It worked.
We had fun.
We loved each other.
It multiplied.
We had never been happier.
And then ...
They came back.
And here I am.
Hello America.
Here is my friend Allen the Alien.
Next week
we meet the President
and Dr. Frubar.
I look forward to the present
Dr. Frubar.
Ladies and gentlemen,
President of the United States!
Thank you.
I will begin
some preliminary remarks.
You know, although I grew up
in poverty,
we ignored
we were poor.
My dear and holy mother
be sacrificed,
she had three jobs,
but we are preparing meals
full of love and tenderness,
never reprimand
or a slap.
My God!
Bag of shit!
I am pleased to welcome
the adventurer, explorer,
the astronaut
this great American
Earl Jensen.
It is a pleasure to be here,
before the whole of America.
But I was told
that would be great Dr. Frubar
to introduce myself.
I know you're there, Dr. F.
Come share my glory.
If you do not show,
I'll get angry.
Calm yourself, Earl.
Everything will be alright.
Come quickly, Dr. F.
The life of your President
is in danger.
- Hurry, or else ...
- It can not, it's the President!
Mr. President, stand firm!
It's a trap.
Boris, come back!
The President was eaten
by a nose!
Check the rules!
Come quickly,
or the President is screwed.
Come, Dr. F.
- What's going on?
- Release the President!
Help!
What the hell, God?
Boris, idiot!
Take off immediately!
I do not know what you cook ...
but it will not work.
He
who has emptied your tank!
And you, you little bitch
Where is my finger?
America, this is the real Dr. Frubar.
He dropped into space ...
Well done
for our brave heroes
Earl Jensen.
America needs both
to this great man.
On the other hand,
I am proud to announce
launch
my most formidable achievement ...
the SatPub!
Hurry!
Take off! Position helicopter!
You're fired!
If we want
job well done ...
Idiots!
You pull my limo!
Dad!
Drop them!
Dr. Frubar!
Damn.
They escape!
Dad, who are these monsters?
Come, Josie, we must start from here.
Dad, what's going on?
Who are these creatures?
They saved my life
in space.
Now we must help them.
Look!
Warning!
Look, it's Darby!
You're crazy!
Trapping the dome
and let out the aliens.
You're crazy!
They are killers!
You love me?
You know I love you ...
I wish we had
a deep and normal.
You want depth?
You love me, Josie?
You do not use it just me?
Come, Darby,
do not talk nonsense!
Come, Darby, c'mon!
Save the aliens!
I do not know
if the time is right, but ...
Darby, wake up!
Cease fire!
You pull my SatPub!
Climb!
I can not, I have vertigo!
If we get to the clouds,
we are saved.
Dad, what's going on?
Who are these creatures?
Remember, long ago,
when I was drifting in space ...
EARL OF FAREWELL SPEECH
Find him and kill him!
Kill! Kill!
I had to put confidence in Frubar
in order to get revenge,
so I invented
Planet of the story of Nez.
Dad, you're hurt!
II you need a doctor!
Promise me you'll take care of the aliens.
No, Daddy!
I love you!
Earl, why did you do that?
You could become a rich hero.
And you ...
Dr. Frubar ...
could have become a human being,
by moving people
before profit.
Remove this wreck!
Today ...
America weeps.
This great American
Earl Jensen
gave his life for his country.
He wanted to protect us
these extraterrestrial murderers.
This morning, we found
his body shredded
in their lair.
He is now en route
to the large infinity ...
space.
We decided to dedicate
the launching of large SatPub
to his memory.
I'm sure it's
what he would have liked.
As for those aliens
evil ...
we will return
to where they came from.
See you tomorrow at noon
to participate
in history!
Promise me you'll take care of the aliens.
Is closed.
You must go.
Come on, hurry up!
What's happening?
What happens, God?
I give him a bandage.
Help me.
There is little time.
I do not know ...
Come, Darby!
Stand there!
Your last meal on Earth.
Thank you. Authorized access.
Good day.
Come, Darby! Shoot!
I will not go over
As you would not have said
whole story.
Dad told me everything
Just before he died ...
Hello, handsome.
You're cute.
What's this?
A surprise?
A big surprise!
Come to mommy.
Demon!
My beast ...
What ecstasy!
Dr. Frubar,
advertisers are there.
Come in, gentlemen.
Dr. F. Awaits you.
Darby, quick!
The sun will rise.
Then finished the history of aliens.
Trained to fight,
eager for battle ...
The bait was in place.
And then ...
I've seen it happen to Earth
sparkling.
You are not in advertising!
Hello gentlemen,
I hope you have the money.
It's amazing.
According to the report,
these extra-terrestrials
does not come from space, but ...
by ... Earth.
They're off!
They escaped!
Wait ...
LOCK
Ladies and gentlemen,
is a great day
for the progress of humanity!
We are here
for the inauguration ...
A little to the left.
That's it. She is in position.
Remove the lens cover.
Now, right!
This is Boris, I'll catch it.
Ye have ever
band nerds!
I am safe
in my SatPub.
These people fool you
disarticulating member after member
while you are only
Children of laboratory animals.
They do not realize
you're just a bunch
unnecessary guinea poor.
Dr. F. Said: "Firing."
No, idiots,
not "Firing"!
Dr. F., do not forsake me!
Tickle it!
Again, again, voila!
Goodbye, Josie.
We are alive!
- Boom!
- Fit.
The time is surely a misnomer,
but as we
short time to live ...
I wanted to give you this.
It is a minitélescope.
You can see ...
Take the wheel!
I have a crazy idea!
I! Relayed to me.
I jump up truck.
The Tensor is what you need.
The Tensor wonders
for the abdominals and buttocks.
... Of humanity.
Ye have ever
band nerds!
These people fool you
disarticulating member after member
while you are
that children
laboratory animals.
They do not realize
you're just a bunch
unnecessary guinea poor.
No, idiots,
not "Firing"!
Kill!
Give me the ring now.
Wait for me!
ZOO OF ALIENS
PET
Adaptation:
Martine Leroy-Battistelli
Subtitle TVS - TITLE FILM