(ROLLER COASTER PLAYING)
(PEOPLE CHATTERING)
(PEOPLE WHOOPING)
No, no, no. No. Come on. Come on.
No, no, no. I can't. I gotta go!
All right. All right.
Cheers. Come on.
(CHEERING)
(SCREAMING)
- Mary! Come on!
- Come back.
Take me on a, take me on a
Take me on a roller coaster
Oh! Mary, what's this?
You slipping out on me?
No. I was looking for you. I just...
I have to go home, Rick. I'm exhausted.
Come on, Mary. It's fucking spring break.
No, Rick. I'm wiped, okay?
I have to go home. I'm sorry.
You can watch me dance.
I got a new move.
Oh!
(LAUGHS)
Yeah, that's funny.
(HORN HONKING)
MAN: Get out of the fucking road!
Hey, learn how to drive,
you fucking prick!
Fuck you!
Hey. Hey! Forgetting something?
Okay, Rick, I really have to go.
- What's with you tonight?
- Rick...
Look at me, I'm exhausted. I just...
I have to go home, okay?
I'll call you. I promise.
- Sure you're good to drive?
- Yeah.
Yes. I'm fine.
All right.
(WHISPERING) Take care.
Okay.
WNPC, New Jersey.
Hey, you kids out there on joyrides,
spring break is here!
This is Eddie the Spaz
coming to you this Friday night,
and the countdown begins right now
to a nonstop weekend Spaz-a-thon,
with me, the Super Spaz.
No sleep, no breaks,
just me and you, my little rodents.
Meanwhile, the weather just in
from Mexico City,
chilly tonight, hot tamale.
- Yeah, baby.
- Oh, dear God.
(SWITCHING STATIONS)
(FLOATON PLAYING)
Yes.
(SINGING ALONG) I drove my car
into a cop car the other day
Well, he just drove
off whatever, it's okay
- I ran my mouth off a bit too much
...a bit too much
Oh, what did I say?
Well, you just laughed
it off it was all okay
And we'll all float on okay
And we'll all float on anyway
Well, a fake Jamaican took
every last dime with that scam
It was worth it
just to see that sleight of hand
Bad news comes don't you worry
even when it lands
Good news will work its way
to all them plans
We both got fired
- on exactly the same day
...exactly the same day
Well, we'll float on
- Good news is on the way
...is on the way
And we'll all float on okay
Shit!
(LAUGHS) Damn.
Shit. Come on.
(KEYS CLATTER)
(WHISPERING) Shit!
Mary, honey, it's Mom.
Dad's boss invited us to his boathouse
for the weekend. Couldn't say no.
We'll be back on Monday.
Have a great weekend. Love you.
MR. MURDOCK: Honey, parrots?
MRS. MURDOCK: Oh, don't forget
to pick up the parrots tomorrow.
(MACHINE BEEPS)
(FLUSHING)
(CREAKING)
(CLATTERING)
Hello?
(CREAKING)
Shit.
(GASPS)
(GAGS)
(SHUDDERING)
Hello?
(MAN MOANING)
(WHISPERING) Hi.
I'm going to help you.
(MOANING)
Can you hear me?
What?
(MOANING)
Yes? Yes? You can hear me?
(MAN MUMBLING)
(MAN GURGLING)
I'm going to help you, okay?
(SCREAMS)
(ROARING)
Get off me.
(SNARLING)
(MARY PANTING)
(RETCHING)
(GAGS)
(MARY GRUNTING)
(SOBBING)
(GRUNTING)
(SHOWER RUNNING)
(SOBBING)
(ALARM BUZZING)
(WHISPERING) Shit.
Ladies and gentlemen...
NEWSCASTER: This morning, the town
of Baltimore is trying to come to terms
with 24 hours of...
MAN: What the hell? All right...
NARRATOR: Murder, mayhem
(GUNSHOT)
and aliens...
NEWSCASTER:
Now here's Dick with the sports.
Morning, ma'am.
Can I help you?
My bumper's dented, can you check it?
Sure.
Let me guess. Cell phone.
That's quite a bit of work there.
Can you leave it overnight?
No, no, overnight, that doesn't work.
Well, there's a garage over on First Street.
You could try them.
They're not gonna tell you
nothing new, though.
So, you want me to fix it or not?
Listen, why don't you get out
and just leave it to me?
You know what, I'm gonna come back later.
(CELL PHONE RINGING)
- Hi, Mom.
- Mary?
I've been trying to get you all morning.
Is everything okay?
Yeah, I'm fine. Everything's good. Why?
- You sound a little funny.
- Mom, I'm fine.
Did you pick up Grandma 's parrots
at the airport?
(STAMMERING) Uh, no, it's not a good day.
I'll do it Monday, okay?
Sweetheart, no, no, no,
you really need to pick them up today.
Right, yeah, okay. I'll go.
I need you to pick them up right now,
as a matter of fact.
It's Saturday, and the
place shuts at 1:00.
Right, Mom, I know. Okay.
I'll drop everything. I'm going, okay?
Mary, you sure you're okay?
Yeah.
Sorry, it's just...
It was a late night.
All right, sweetheart, I love you.
Love you, too.
(STIFLING SOB) Fuck.
(CHUCKLES) Five more minutes
and these babies were on their way
to the tweet-tweet orphanage.
MAN: Nice talking to you, too!
Come on, come on, come on.
- Sorry, my nerves are just a little raw.
- PARROT: Okay, sugar.
Fuck. Come on.
What's the best way
to cover a small dent?
Make a bigger one, right?
Cover the first collision?
(SQUAWKS)
(PARROTS CHATTERING ANIMATEDLY)
Okay, Mary,
you're losing it.
You're losing it, okay?
(CRYING) You're losing it, okay? Just...
Fuck. Okay, just...
Stop, Mary, just think.
Think, okay? Okay?
The trout season officially opened
this weekend in Colombo.
All the old hands
will try their luck
hooking a trophy
specimen again this year.
Me? I guess about the only thing
I'll catch is the cold.
Thanks, Julia. Speaking of cold, John,
what's the weekend weather forecast?
Sadly, the kindergarten teacher was
reported missing by his wife Friday night.
I gave him a kiss good night,
and the next thing I know, he's gone.
His cell phone, his watch,
his shoes are still by the bed.
Timothy, if you're out there,
please come back, please.
I love you. Andy misses you.
We both miss you so, so much.
Detectives were canvassing
hospitals last night,
providing Mr. Emser's description.
Emser is a well-respected teacher
for the past five years at the
Colombo Elementary County School.
CHILDREN: (SINGING)
... little lamb, little lamb
Mary had a little lamb
its fleece was white as snow
And everywhere that Mary went...
(ROCK MUSIC BLARING)
(HORN HONKING)
(CAR DOOR CLOSES)
Hey, where you been, man?
You've been raging since last night, huh?
Why didn't you call me?
What's wrong with you?
What, you got another guy in here? Huh?
Yo, asshole, show your face!
(LAUGHING) You wouldn't be that stupid.
Look at you.
- What?
- Well, you look like shit.
What's up with you?
Nothing.
(SCOFFS)
What do you mean, nothing?
I know you. Something's up. What...
(EMPHATICALLY) Nothing.
- Where'd you go last night?
- Nowhere, nothing. It's just...
- So you came back home?
- Yes, I was at home.
Okay, then why didn't you
answer my calls?
I just... I was just... I was...
- Who were you with?
- Stop it. Nothing.
- Okay, so then why didn't you call me?
- Nothing! Okay, I killed a man!
All right, well, if it's just that,
I know a great place upstate
where we can go and no one will find him.
I'm not joking.
- Not a joke.
- Enough, all right? It's not funny anymore.
The schoolteacher, the...
What are you talking about?
The fucking... The schoolteacher!
Why aren't you listening?
I am listening to you.
You're not making any fucking sense.
The schoolteacher!
His wife is, like, all over the news,
like Elmer, Ester,
I don't know, just someone!
You're talking about the guy on TV,
singing with the kids
and the nursery rhymes and shit?
- Huh?
- Yes, I...
I killed him.
Okay. Okay, cut it out, all right?
You know...
What's the matter with you?
That's not funny.
I'm not... He was...
(STIFLING SOB) He was in the garage
and stuck to the car,
and I hit him and I...
I killed him.
You hit him?
Look at me.
You're not fucking around with me, right?
(MARY STIFLING SOBS)
(MARY GASPS)
That's some heavy shit, Mary.
I killed him.
All right, just... Just...
- I killed him.
- Okay, okay, all right.
(SOBBING)
Okay, okay.
- I didn't see him and I killed him.
- Okay, all right, all right.
- Stop. Stop. Okay, okay.
- I killed him!
- I know, I know.
- I killed him.
- I didn't mean it. I didn't mean it.
- I know. Okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay.
MARY: I just...
I told him I was gonna help him,
and then he just...
He started attacking me, so I just...
I hit him with a golf club.
You hit him with a golf club?
Oh, my God. You're fucking nuts.
Don't yell at me.
I'm not yelling at you,
but I need to know what happened.
All right, Mary? You want to know why?
'Cause you're gonna need my help.
Trust me on that.
I just...
I just panicked.
He was just lying on the bumper like some
demented, dying animal,
and he was just screaming at me,
and he just...
He started to, like, attack me,
and he just wouldn't stop, and so,
I just grabbed the first thing I saw
and it was a golf club,
and I didn't mean it. I didn't mean it.
You have to believe me.
I did not mean it. I didn't mean it.
Mary, of course I believe you.
Okay? How long have we been going out?
Two years, right?
I believe every word
that comes out of your mouth, okay?
Okay?
All right, so, what,
this dude's still in the garage?
Mary, if I'm gonna help you,
you're gonna have to talk to me, okay?
(QUIETLY) I buried him.
You buried him?
No, please. You have to understand,
I was... I was so scared. I was so...
I know I probably should have
called the cops, but I didn't...
I didn't know what to do. Please, Rick.
- Please, just help me, just help me.
- Okay, okay, okay, okay.
Okay, I just need to think, all right?
We need a plan.
- What kind of plan?
- One that works.
Okay? One that we've gotta stick to,
and it's gotta be rock solid.
Okay, but what do we do?
Okay, okay.
No one, nowhere, no how,
can know about this, okay?
I know you want to vent right now,
but the most important thing you can do
- (ENUNCIATING) is keep your mouth shut.
- (WHISPERING) I don't think I can.
And then we move on one day at a time.
No mouthing off,
no loose ends, no haircuts,
nothing that brings attention to yourself,
Mary, and I mean nothing.
This will pass, okay? I promise.
This guy will get his 15 minutes of fame
and then bam, he ain't shit no more.
They'll find someone else to talk about.
That's the plan.
You on board?
Okay, come here.
(MARY CRYING)
RICK: You feeling better now? Huh?
Come on. Come on.
(RICK GRUNTS)
What?
I heard something.
- (CHUCKLING) What?
- Just go check it out.
- I will, in a sec. Come on.
- No, now.
It's probably not...
(SCOFFS)
Fuck.
(SIGHS)
- It's probably nothing.
- Just check it.
Rick?
(CLATTERING)
(RICK CACKLING)
Fucking jerk, you're lucky
I didn't stab you with this!
(CHUCKLING) Whoa!
Whoa! Easy there, girl.
(WHISPERING) That would be
murder, Mary.
Oh, fuck off.
Come on.
(FOOTSTEPS STOMPING AWAY)
(SIGHS)
Hey, little fucker, what's up? Huh?
Hey... Jesus!
Little bitch.
I'm sorry.
Just relax, all right?
Take some of your dad's meds,
it'll take the edge off, and just go to bed.
- I'll see you later.
- Where are you going?
I gotta go, Mary.
You know, my head is pounding,
I got to be up in,
fuck, like, four hours.
You know, I can't think straight.
I gotta get some sleep.
So do you, okay?
(PHONE RINGING)
Hello?
Rick?
(CELL PHONE RINGING)
(GROANS)
- (SLEEPILY) Mary?
- Rick, I'm scared.
(GROANS)
- It's 3:30 in the fucking morning.
- I can't help it, Rick. They know.
(STAMMERING) There's a flyer.
- A flyer?
- Yes. It has his face and everything.
They know.
(SIGHS) Mary, it's probably just a cop
or a volunteer or something, all right?
- That's what they do.
- At 3:30 in the morning?
Okay. These guys work
around the fucking clock, all right?
There's probably one
under my door right now.
Can't you come over?
And do what, huh?
What are we gonna do?
Sit around and worry?
Trust me,
it's only gonna make things worse.
(RICK SIGHS)
Listen, Mary, all right?
I'm counting on you.
You need to calm yourself down.
All right, sweetie?
Yeah, I know, I know.
You're probably thinking,
"That's easy for you to say."
Fuck me, right? Yeah, but...
Look, I'm in this with you now, all right?
All the way.
So go take another downer, you know?
And if they're fives, take two,
wash it down with some booze
and get some sleep. All right?
Now, I need you to hold yourself together
for the next couple of days, all right?
And don't let this flyer thing
fuck with your mind, all right?
It's just routine. Okay?
Oh, yeah, and another thing,
don't drink and dial, all right?
That's how you get snared,
talking shit on the phone. All right?
- Hey.
- Thanks.
EDDIE ON RADIO:
Hey, there, you children of the night,
almost 36 straight hours
into the Spaz-a-thon,
and I'm feeling like a dead rat
slept in my mouth.
It's 3:45 EST.
I'm not talking Eastern Standard Time,
I'm talking Eddie the Spaz Time.
(PARROT SQUAWKING)
PARROT: Step out.
You scared the shit out of me.
PARROT: Step out. Step out.
Who taught you that? Grandma?
Smart birds.
- Mary, don't go crazy.
- PARROT: (SQUAWKS) Crazy.
- Shut up!
- PARROT: Crazy. Crazy.
(SHRIEKING) Shut up! Shut up! Shut up!
Today, police divers searched the
waters of Spring Lake without success
for the kindergarten teacher
who mysteriously vanished
from his home, late Friday night.
Police now believe his fragile mental state
may be behind his disappearance.
Emser was recently diagnosed
with bipolar...
(MUTED)
EDDIE ON RADIO: Hear about the two kids
who kissed in the fog?
They missed.
(SHRIEKING) Oh, yeah!
Whoo! Suffering from some serious
sleep deprivation here, man,
so don't hold me accountable
for my actions.
Stepped out of the studio
for a little air intake.
Ooh! Tell you, man,
it is a real blanket of fog out there.
Fuck!
(WHISPERING) Fuck.
(CELL PHONE RINGING)
(GROANS)
Oh, you gotta be fucking kidding me.
- Mary, go back to bed. Fuck.
- Rick.
- Rick, the blanket.
- What blanket?
The blanket.
I wrapped the body in a blanket,
and if they find that, the fibers...
They're gonna be on me in a second.
I'm fucked. Rick!
- You wrapped him in a blanket?
- Yes!
(GROANS)
That was a dumb thing to do.
- You gotta go back there and get it.
- No.
Uh-uh. No. No.
I can't go back there. I can't.
(RICK GROANS)
I get it. You want me
to go back there with you, right?
Yeah, well, right now
I'd rather cut off a nut.
Please, Rick. Please.
- Where?
- Okay. Right on Clover Road,
all the way until you hit the woods.
I will be there in 20.
What?
- Don't leave me hanging, all right, Mary?
- Yeah, I won't. Promise.
(SIGHS)
Fuck.
Where is he?
Rick, it's me. Where the hell are you?
I can't believe this.
Rick?
(PANTING)
Come on. Just fucking call.
Fuck.
Rick? Rick?
Oh, fuck, Rick. Rick!
(GASPS)
(SOBBING)
Rick.
(SOBBING) This isn't...
Rick, I'm sorry. I'm sorry. Oh, my God.
(CELL PHONE RINGING)
Hello?
MAN: (SINGSONGING) Bloody Mary.
(GASPS)
(CELL PHONE RINGING)
Hello?
Who is this?
I'm gonna call the cops.
(PHONE RINGING)
MAN: (SINGING) Mary had a little lamb
Stop it, please. Just...
Little lamb
Stop it. Just stop it.
(DOOR BANGING)
(CLATTERING)
(GROANING)
Oh, fuck!
(PARROT SQUAWKING)
PARROT: Bloody Mary.
Bloody Mary. Bloody Mary.
(SQUAWKS)
(SCREAMING)
(BULB BUZZING)
(GASPING)
(ENGINE STARTING)
(MUFFLED SCREAMING)
(CRASH)
(ENGINE STOPS)
(MUFFLED SCREAMING)
Hey, hey! This is full service only.
Hey, fella.
Hey, wait a second.
(MUFFLED SHOUTING)
ATTENDANT: I know you.
Aren't you that teacher on TV?
The missing guy?
Emser.
Hey, it's okay now. It's okay now.
I'll get cops, okay?
(GLASS BREAKING)
(MARY SCREAMS)
(GURGLING)
(MUFFLED SCREAMING)
(ENGINE REVVING)
(MARY WHIMPERING)
(CRYING)
(HISSES IN PAIN)
Tim? Tim? Oh, my God.
(SOBBING) Oh, my God. Thank you.
Oh my... Jesus Christ.
(STAMMERING) What happened?
Look at you.
(CRYING) I thought you were dead.
Oh, my God.
You need to get to a hospital.
Tim, do you hear me?
Why don't you let me help you?
I don't understand. What is going on?
Why can't you tell me what happened?
Please talk to me.
Andy, do not come in here. Go to sleep.
I'm not sleepy.
Dad, can I stay up, please?
Just a little bit longer, I'm not that tired.
Can I go to the garage
and get my laser gun?
- (SHARPLY) No.
- Daddy said no, now go to bed.
(GROANING)
(CHAINS RATTLING)
(GASPS)
- Did you brush your teeth?
- Yes.
(WHISPERING) Mom, is Dad gonna be okay?
(WHISPERING) Yes, honey,
now close your eyes.
Please, Tim, take your medication.
Why are you doing this to me?
Fuck!
All right, fine, be that way.
It's because you didn't take it,
this whole thing happened.
God damn it. I can't stand it anymore.
You don't want me to take you
to a hospital, you're covered in blood,
you disappear from the face of the earth,
and you expect me to act normal?
I saw you send the letter to the school.
What are you talking about?
I saw you fucking send it.
Tim, you're imagining all this.
It's in your head, Tim.
What must they be thinking now?
That I'm gonna come down there
and slash their throats from ear to ear.
I'll bet that's what they're thinking.
That bitch couldn't kill me.
Kill you? Who?
That bitch.
(STAMMERING) I'm calling the police.
(GASPING)
JANE: Andy? Andy, are you in there?
WOMAN: Hello, this is 911 operator.
Hello?
(INSISTENTLY) Hello?
Are you okay? Hello?
Hello?
Okay, we're sending the police.
(GRUNTING)
(TOY LASER GUN FIRING)
(MARY GRUNTING)
Mom!
JANE: Andy, are you in there?
Oh, my God.
Who are you?
My husband did this to you?
Thank you. Thank you.
Could you please untie me?
- Yeah, yeah. I will. I will.
- I'm really hurt.
- Please, just... It really hurts. It hurts.
- Okay, it's all right.
- All right. Here, here.
- Thank you. Thank you.
(JANE SHUSHING)
You're gonna be okay.
My husband, he's not well. It's his head.
I'm gonna call the police.
(JANE SHUSHING)
(ROARING)
(SCREAMING)
No!
(STARTS ENGINE)
(TIRES SCREECHING)
(SCREAMING)
(TRUCK HORN BLARING)
(MARY SOBBING)
Please.
No, no! Don't!
(WHIMPERING)
(SCREAMING)
(MARY SOBBING)
(GROANING IN PAIN)
(GROWING SNARL)
(BARKING)
(SNARLING)
(WHISPERING) Could you hear
the bones breaking when you hit me?
Could you?
- Could you?
- No, I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry I didn't see you.
I didn't see you.
- It was an accident?
- Yeah.
- It was no accident.
- It was.
- It was. I'm sorry.
- You...
When you found me in your garage...
When you found me in your garage,
you stank. You stank.
I'm sorry.
You stank like alcohol.
(SOBBING) I'm so sorry. I didn't mean it.
I'm so sorry. No.
I'm gonna do something
really, really bad to you.
No, please.
No!
(CRYING) I'm sorry! Stop it!
(MARY GASPING)
Hail Mary. Say "Hail Mary."
Hail Mary. Hail Mary.
Full of grace...
You don't even know it.
(SHOUTING) You don't even know it!
You don't even know it!
Because you don't believe.
You don't believe.
(WHISPERING)
You don't believe in anything.
It's time to go.
(SCREAMING)
(SCREAMING CONTINUES)
(GASPS)
Fuck.
(ENGINE REVVING)
Son of a bitch.
(SNARLING)
(ROARING)
Get the fuck off me!
(ROARING CONTINUES)
Get off me!
Fuck you!
Oh, my...
(BELLOWING) Fuck you!
(LAUGHING CRAZILY)
(SPITS)
(GROANS)
EDDIE ON RADIO: WNPC, New Jersey.
It's 7:00 a.m. on a
perky Sunday morning.
We did it, my little rodents,
the weekend Spaz-a-thon is done.
History! We made it
in one piece, baby!
We did it.
Next stop, home, sweet home.
You kids out there,
Eddie the Super Spaz, signing off.
Stay out of trouble.
Have yourselves a great day.
Excuse me.
Can you take a look at my car?
I think the bumper is...
Gone?
Let me guess. Cell phone?
Can you fix it
or do I have to find somebody else?
Yeah, I can fix it. If I find the right match,
I'll have it ready today.
- Come back at 3:00.
- Okay.
Is there somewhere I can wash my hands?
To the left.
Hey, you okay?
(MUTTERING) We're almost there.
We're almost there.
(SIREN WAILING DISTANTLY)
I don't think I need that bumper anymore.
(STIFLES LAUGH)
(LAUGHS)
(LAUGHING)
(SIREN APPROACHING)
(CAR STOPPING)
(CAR DOOR OPENS)
(CAR DOOR SLAMS)
(ROLLER COASTER PLAYING)
Ooh!
Rock boys rock my world
I like to play with all my girls
But money makes me hard and tight
I love to bathe in cash and pearls
Rock boys rock my world
I like to play with all my girls
But money makes me hard and tight
I love to bathe in cash and pearls
Throw it up
Up, up, up
Smoke it up
Pump it up
Up, up, up
Kick it up
Lick it up
Up, up, up
Eat it up
Get it up
Up, up, up
Fuck it up
Throw it up
Up, up, up
Smoke it up
Pump it up
Up, up, up
Kick it up
Lick it up
Up, up, up
Eat it up
Get it up
Up, up, up
Fuck it up
Up, up
Take me on a, take me on a
Take me on a roller coaster
Ride it
Take me on a, take me on a
Take me on a roller coaster
Ride it
Take me on a, take me on a
Take me on a roller coaster
Ride it
Take me on a, take me on a
Take me on a roller coaster
Ride it
Going down is a rush
Don't look now, hush, hush
Get me hot, get me high
All I need's an alibi
Got no alibi
Going down is a rush
Don't look now, hush, hush
Get me hot, get me high
All I need's an alibi
Got no alibi
Throw it up
Up, up, up
Smoke it up
Pump it up
Up, up, up
Kick it up
Lick it up
Up, up, up
Eat it up
Get it up
Up, up, up
Fuck it up
Throw it up
Up, up, up
Smoke it up
Pump it up
Up, up, up
Kick it up
Lick it up
Up, up, up
Eat it up
Get it up
Up, up, up
Fuck it up
Up, up
Hard and tight
Subtitles by LeapinLar