[wolf howls]
[crickets chirping]
[waves lapping]
[Brian Lam's Crash]
♪ ♪
♪ Lost and in between ♪
♪ The way you thought it was ♪
♪ And thought it seemed ♪
♪ And everyone has changed ♪
♪ Soon you'll realize that ♪
♪ You're the one ♪
♪ Who's compromised ♪
♪ And you're the one to blame ♪
♪ Listen now
Listen now ♪
♪ lf you want another chance ♪
♪ You'll take it now ♪
♪ Oh, oh ♪
♪ lf you crash ♪
♪ Crash, crash ♪
♪ lf it goes down tonight ♪
♪ lt's the messes ♪
♪ That you make ♪
♪ The hearts ♪
♪ That you will break ♪
♪ lf you crash ♪
♪ Crash, crash ♪
♪ Oh, don't go another day ♪
♪ lt's time to walk away ♪
♪ Or you'll crash ♪
♪ Crash, crash ♪
♪ Oh, you'll crash ♪
♪ Opened all the doors 'cause ♪
♪ You think you know ♪
♪ Where they go ♪
♪ But none ♪
♪ Will lead you home ♪
♪ Day and night ♪
♪ Are magnified ♪
♪ Against the good ♪
♪ Against the light ♪
♪ Till you are left alone ♪
♪ Listen now
Listen now ♪
♪ lf you want another chance ♪
♪ You'll take it now ♪
♪ Oh, oh ♪
♪ Oh, you'll crash ♪
♪ Crash, crash ♪
♪ lf it goes down tonight ♪
♪ lt's the messes ♪
♪ That you make ♪
♪ The hearts ♪
♪ That you will break ♪
♪ lf you crash ♪
♪ Crash, crash ♪
♪ Oh, don't go another day ♪
♪ lt's time to walk away ♪
[clicks]
[people conversing]
[slow jazzy music playing]
♪ ♪
[cell phone vibrating]
Bitch.
Two glasses of wine, please.
Uh, vodka gimlet, rocks.
Hey, l'm Zach.
Nate.
You're, uh...
Topher's friend.
Yeah.
He, um...
He showed me your audition tape
for Blood and Barcelona.
You look good.
Did he say something?
Well, l mean--l mean,
you've got a good look.
Too bad he didn't hire you
as casting director.
[playing softly]
♪ ♪
l witnessed your crash and burn
with beautiful young Nate.
Yeah, l, uh...
aimed too high.
Too high?
Mmm, on the hotness scale.
You know, l am a solid seven,
and, uh, you can always get
somebody two points below you
to bump hot dogs,
which for me is, like, a five,
you know, guaranteed.
But what l want is an
eight or a nine, you know.
Tens totally intimidate me.
You know, l start to blather.
He was, l don't know,
maybe a nine,
although with the lighting,
l might have overestimated.
l thought you could
approach a nine.
Seriously, no.
So being my friend didn't help?
Not so much.
lt can help you with one thing.
Oh, yeah?
What's that?
Getting an excellent
birthday present.
You didn't...
Thanks, Toph.
lt's got all my numbers and
emails pre-programmed
so you can reach me anywhere.
Like if you were suddenly
struck with an idea for a movie.
Right, yeah.
This will shrivel up your dick.
Happy birthday, part two.
Keystone?
For the film festival.
You want to take me to
the keystone film festival?
l need you to take my place.
Your place?
Dude, Blood and Barcelona
just got financed.
We leave for Spain right away.
l need you to fill in for me
as a judge at the festival.
Dude, Keystone asked for you.
There's no place for me there.
Would they--would they even know
that l'd be replacing you?
Of course.
All you have to do
is watch some movies
and interview film students
for the festival scholarship.
You love movies.
And l'm sure the boys are cute.
These aren't just boys, Toph.
These are
skinny-jeans-wearing brats
who think that the world
owes them something.
Yeah. Ha, ha.
Man, what would l even
tell those kids?
You know, my Hollywood career
has consisted of
parties and rehab.
l think those kids would
like to learn something
from a guy
who won the festival
when he was only a sophomore.
Yeah, that guy quit
school to go to L.A.
because he was so talented,
and Hollywood obliged by making
me the biggest partier ever.
That was a different guy...
Go back to Keystone.
Birthday present, part three.
[Oak & Gorski's Analog Girl]
♪ ♪
[vibration]
♪ l see you walk ♪
♪ Around your room... ♪
Excuse me, uh...Mr. Welds?
Welcome to Keystone University.
We're the key to your future.
Um, you must be here
for the festival.
You staying on campus
tonight, son?
Uh, Grace Hall.
That's a student dorm, son.
You must've pissed someone off.
Most VlPs are staying
in The Tower.
At least it's easy to find.
Thank you.
Enjoy your visit.
♪ Look what you made me ♪
♪ l must be crazy ♪
♪ My bread and butterflies ♪
♪ Schizophrenic little girl ♪
♪ Hip-hop from the underground ♪
♪ The soundtrack ♪
♪ To your little world ♪
Call Topher.
[female voice] Calling Topher.
Fucking voicemail.
Thanks a lot, man.
l can't believe l just let you
keep screwing me over.
You know where they put me?
A freshman dorm.
Freshman, Toph!
♪ l must be crazy ♪
♪ Look what you made me ♪
♪ Stare at you
Stare at you ♪
♪ Yeah, the secrets ♪
♪ That that mirror could tell ♪
Who's the old dude?
l dunno.
[Mayda's Stereotype playing]
♪ ♪
♪ lt only takes one look ♪
♪ To start shakin' your head ♪
♪ lt only takes one crook ♪
♪ To start sleepin' ♪
♪ With a bat in your bed ♪
♪ lt only takes one brick ♪
♪ Just to build up those walls ♪
♪ And it only takes one hit ♪
♪ To make them all fall ♪
♪ l want to break your stereo ♪
♪ l want to break ♪
♪ Your stereotype ♪
♪ l want to break your stereo ♪
♪ l want to break ♪
♪ Your stereotype ♪
♪ lf you could break my stereo ♪
♪ l want you to break ♪
♪ My stereotype ♪
♪ Oh, you could break
my stereo ♪
♪ l want you to break ♪
♪ My stereotype, yeah ♪
♪ ♪
♪ Now do you wanna see
my little hammer ♪
♪ lt's stuck in my chest ♪
♪ Do you wanna see
my little hammer ♪
♪ lt's probably for the best ♪
♪ We all have statues ♪
♪ That we build up ♪
♪ ln our minds ♪
♪ My little hammer wants to ♪
♪ Break that stereotype ♪
♪ l want to break your stereo ♪
♪ l want to break ♪
♪ Your stereotype ♪
♪ l want to break your stereo ♪
♪ l want to break ♪
♪ Your stereotype ♪
♪ lf you could break my stereo ♪
♪ l want you to break ♪
♪ My stereotype ♪
♪ lf you could break my stereo ♪
♪ l want you to break ♪
♪ My stereotype ♪
♪ Come on ♪
[bells chiming
Westminster Quarters]
Shit!
[bell tolling]
Ah, shit.
Mrs...Blossom?
Mr. Wells.
Punctual as always.
You look exactly the same.
Your charm with the
ladies is unflagging.
Ahem.
Oh, l'm sorry.
We were just socializing.
Thank you so much,
Mr. Lyons, Mrs. Lyons.
We are the
honored beneficiaries
of your unending generosity.
That was Mr. and Mrs.--
Yeah, l know.
Of course, you did.
Your schedule.
Be prompt.
Files on each of the
scholarship finalists
you'll be interviewing.
Read them.
Each of the finalists' tapes.
Watch them.
l get it, l get it.
Thank you.
Good day, then.
Mrs. Blossom.
Mr. Wells?
Listen, l know l was sort of
imposed on you here.
Mr. Shadoe is quite
an advocate for you.
Mrs. Blossom, please.
l'm trying to apologize.
For what, Mr. Wells?
For Topher.
For screwing up
your film festival.
Topher Shadoe is
a horrendous name.
Why you boys choose to change
your names is beyond me.
Names, faces, films.
l don't forget the good ones,
even yours.
You've got a schedule to keep.
Yeah, right, um, okay.
Okay, last question, Tommy.
Tell us what makes your
creative vision unique.
l like to stare through windows
and just watch people.
Mr. Wells, please.
Oh, call me Zach.
l'm pretty sure
smoking's not allowed.
Stow it, Ralph.
l need a poo break.
So, Tommy, back to you.
No pressure.
So, yeah, l like to see what
people are gonna do
when they think
no one is watching.
Sometimes l'll peek
through the crack
of my sister's bedroom door...
and watch her sleep.
l also like to walk around
with my hands like this.
Like how mysterious you look
surrounded by all
that smoke, Zach.
l wonder what
you're looking at...
what you're you thinking.
Sometimes l spend my whole day
framing people up.
My whole life is cinematic.
l even masturbate cinematically.
[coughs]
Wow, you've got an exciting
career ahead of you.
Really?
Oh, yeah, you're gonna make
a killing in porn.
- Mr. Wells!
- l'm just saying.
And scene.
Thank you, Tommy.
And now l really have to insist
on that poo break.
Thank you, Mr. Garlington,
Ms. Lynn...
Zach.
Come on, Ralph.
You look like you need
to take a shit.
[papers clatter]
l'm your 3:30.
Well, this is awkward.
Uh, nothing personal,
but it looks like
l have to care about
who you are now.
Look, you and l have never met.
Got that?
Never met.
lf you mean we've never been
properly introduced,
then sure.
Never met.
My name is Danny.
- Danny Reyes.
- What?
So sorry to keep
you waiting, Danny.
- Human needs, you know.
- Of course.
l trust Zach was good company?
Oh, he certainly was,
Ms. Lynn.
Uh, how come l didn't see
this kid's file?
Did you take my copy
to the bathroom with you?
What? l washed my hands.
Okay, fine, look.
Danny, let's get started,
shall we?
Why don't you tell us what
inspired this wonderful film.
Wait a minute.
You're Danny Reyes.
Yeah.
Where did you grow up?
l went to Lockton High School.
Lockton?
Zach, are you all right?
What's the name of his film
in this competition?
Judas Kiss.
lndeed.
Danny, why don't you tell us
what inspired you
to tackle this controversial
subject in the short form?
Your father.
No, my...
My film is fictional.
Some...Somebody put you
up to this.
Mrs. Blossom?
Topher?
Look, Mr. Wells, if this
is about last night...
Last night?
You can't be Danny Reyes.
l am Danny Reyes.
For quite a few reasons,
that's impossible.
- Zach.
- Mr. Wells!
Where are you going?
To find Mrs. Blossom.
This is totally fucked up!
l think l need another poo.
Stop!
What is going on here?
That can't be Danny Reyes.
Of course it is.
He was on our schedule.
He wasn't on mine.
What is up with you
and this kid?
We have to interview him, Zach.
Just gimme a minute, okay?
Listen, l'll go reschedule
with Mrs. Blossom,
and then we'll go to coffee,
okay?
Just wait for me here, okay?
Call Topher.
Calling Topher.
Topher, this better not be one
of your little practical jokes.
There's a kid here
claiming to be Danny Reyes.
Danny Reyes, from Lockton.
Ring any bells?
Oh, and l slept with him.
Did you plan that too,
you goddamn pimp?
l'll call you back.
You're...Welds, right?
You gave me directions.
That's why l'm here.
Gimme a cigarette.
We need to talk.
[Timo Deschamps'
Like it Rough playing]
♪ ♪
♪ The sweaty taste ♪
♪ Upon your lips ♪
♪ My hands are moving ♪
♪ Towards your hips ♪
♪ About to show me ♪
♪ Where this feeling ♪
♪ Will take us ♪
♪ This night will make us ♪
♪ Am l too common ♪
♪ For your love ♪
♪ Too mainstream ♪
♪ Not quite strong enough ♪
♪ Maybe l'm too naive or ♪
♪ Tell me ♪
♪ Do you like it rough? ♪
And, cut!
That'll be all for today.
Great job, everybody.
l have an interview.
All right, that is a wrap
for the day.
Everybody, please check the
board for your next call times.
l'm never having sex again.
Are you still hung up on cute
older dude from last night?
You don't understand, okay?
l am so completely, totally,
all-encompassingly fucked.
You need to chill.
And there's no such word
as ''encompassingly.''
Yeah, well, a new word
is required for how much
l just fucked my life.
Spill.
l slept with
one of the judges.
At the interview?
No!
Cute older dude, he...
Turned out to be
one of the judges.
Wow.
You have the weirdest mojo ever.
l hope l'm not interrupting.
No, no, you're right on time.
Okay, drama queen, focus.
Let's get this interview done,
and then we'll
sort out your issues.
Right.
Right, sorry, Abs.
Focus.
Hi, l'm Abbey Park.
Chris Wachowsky.
We've got your chair set up
right over here.
Who's your partner?
Slave driver, you mean.
Uh, that's Danny--
Danny Reyes.
You made Judas Kiss.
Yeah, that's me.
No one's ever
gotten their
freshman film
into finals before.
Lucky, l guess.
ls there any chance that
l could get a look at it
before the screening
this weekend?
Really? You'd, uh...
You'd want to see it?
The entire film school is
insanely jealous of you.
We were all jealous of you
when you won
the film festival last year.
Hello?
Remember? lnterview?
l'm all set up here.
Okay.
[camera rolling]
Chris Wachowsky, winner of last
year's Keystone Film Festival,
how has life changed
since winning?
You gotta make things
right with the kid.
He's who he says he is.
l'm sorry, sir, but you
can't possibly know that.
He's Danny Reyes.
- He can't be.
- He is.
l'm Danny Reyes!
You're Zachary Wells.
Danny Reyes went to
school here 1 5 years ago.
That was me.
What happened to him?
l...
He's gone.
Just like that?
You think changing your name
added l.Q. Points?
How many times
you've done rehab now?
You're getting
a second chance, ''Zachary.''
Okay, we're done here.
This is the key to your future.
Change his past...
[vibration]
Change your future.
l'll see you around.
[camera rolling]
You know, most people have
a follow-up question when l say
l plan on bringing bloody films
back into fashion.
Right.
So, what, are you gonna go down
to L.A. and do the whole
starving artist thing
for a while?
Lame!
No one tries to become
a starving artist, rasshol.
How about asking
a non-bullshit question?
Abbey you can't say--
Feent, bleep me out.
Whatevs.
Abbey--
Ask him a real fucking
question, you mus.
Feent.
Are you afraid of the future?
Wow...
That is a real fucking question.
Am l afraid of the future?
Yeah.
Terrified.
l mean, it's the future.
Who wouldn't be?
But it's a fair fight.
l know l have
what it takes to win.
Okay, uh, l think we got
what we need here.
Abbey, could you, uh,
take down that boom?
Slave driver?
Hey, what's up?
What the hell are you
doing in my studio?
No harm done.
Danny, this is Shane.
Shane Lyons.
Oh...
Hi.
l didn't realize
you were still here.
l'm meeting my parents
for coffee.
The film festival is their
big hoohah for the year,
so l'm at their
beck and call all week.
Who are your friends, C.W.?
Uh, Danny Reyes.
This is Abbey...
Park.
Danny Reyes and Abbey...
Huh.
Danny Reyes, you have a film
at the film festival, right?
[pen clicks]
This is where my family's
insane film festival party
will be tomorrow night...
And you're coming.
lf l'm forced to endure my
parents' stay on campus
all week, l'm entitled
to bring extra guests.
Yeah, party.
Awesome, great.
Yeah, and, uh,
bring little missy with you.
C.W., you're invited too,
of course.
Sure...
Thanks.
How did you get in here?
Don't you think
we need to talk?
Feent.
l blew the R.A. once.
He owed me for
not telling his girlfriend.
Keystone University,
where blowjobs are the
key to my dorm room.
Funny.
l just want
to talk to you
about that whole
interview thing.
You see, l really need
this scholarship.
Why you more than
anyone else?
My film.
Let's just say putting it in
the festival is going to put me
into a little bit of
a financial bind.
lt cost a lot to make?
You could put it that way.
[telephone rings]
[rings]
Gonna get that?
Right.
Hello.
Hey, it's me.
Rebecca.
You're taking me to
a cocktail party tonight.
Do you ever just
ask for anything?
lf l don't command you,
you'll just stay all day
in that pathetic dorm room
smoking Art Deco cigarettes.
l'm supposed to avoid drinking.
Okay, l'll be
straight with you.
You're my excuse for
blowing off Ralph Garlington.
Fine.
Great.
Pick me up in an hour.
You know, you can't
smoke in here.
You gonna tell on me?
So, Danny...
Daniel Reyes Jr.?
Grew up in Lockton?
Uh-huh.
Your dad, he teaches
at the high school?
Yeah.
And your mom?
What about her?
She died.
Cancer, right?
What?
You trying to freak me out?
No, l'm just trying to figure
out how much of you is phony.
Well, l'm about as real
as you are.
Well, that's not really
saying much.
Hey!
You're Danny Reyes.
Yeah. So did l pass
your little test?
Are we gonna be okay for
this interview tomorrow?
You do your part,
and l'll do mine.
[jazz playing]
♪ ♪
Table!
Not today, supermodel.
Wow.
Hollywood's made you cutthroat.
Film school
made me cutthroat.
Hollywood just helped me
dress better.
So, Danny's interview,
tomorrow at 1 0:00 A.M.
You've seen his shorts, right?
Shorts?
Short films, pervert.
How are we supposed
to argue about it
if you haven't even seen it?
We have to argue?
We certainly do.
Unless you plan to
work out this sexual tension
some other way.
Tension?
You're bristling with sexual
tension, Zachary Wells.
Admit it: you're hot for me.
l...
l know, l know.
Your life's so complicated.
Whatever.
Go watch the kid's
damn film already.
Go.
Mrs. Blossom.
Hey, Mrs. Blossom!
Wait up!
Look, l'm really sorry about
that whole interview thing,
but you've really got to help me
understand what's going on here.
Understand?
You know that kid
can't be Danny Reyes.
You know he didn't make
Judas Kiss.
l made that film 1 5 years ago.
Danny Reyes made that film.
l'm Danny Reyes.
You're Zachary Wells.
Danny Reyes is still here.
Please tell me
l am not going crazy.
You're not going crazy.
Wait!
You want more?
Some answers.
Danny Reyes
always wants more.
His cocksure attitude,
his charm, his talent -
they always get him
what he wants.
Stop giving him what he wants,
Mr. Wells.
Give him what he needs.
l don't know what that means.
You were brought to
Keystone to do a job.
lt's the key to your future.
Why does everybody
keep saying that?
- Everybody?
- You, and that tour guide.
That old man...
Stay away from him.
He has his own work to do.
Do your job, Mr. Wells.
lnterview the students,
judge the films,
make a difference.
Good day.
[breathing hard]
Fet.
Hey, rasshol!
What happened to
''Meet Me After Sundown''?
Abbey, l'm sorry.
Don't go all Canadian on me.
What?
Like you look like
you're in my reality,
but actually you're in
a parallel dimension...
Like Canada.
Your ass, up here.
You brought your camera?
Yeah.
Thought l'd get
some practice shots.
[coughs]
So, how'd it go with
cute older dude?
Fine...
Weird.
l--l don't know.
ls this multiple choice?
Okay, he said we'd be fine
for the interview tomorrow,
but it's--it's like...
Like what?
Like he knows me, Abs.
Like he knows what we've done.
He can't possibly know.
Get down here.
You're just letting guilt
get to you.
No one could know.
Now, look at the pavilion.
That is Emerald City,
and you and l are Dorothy
and her friend.
Somehow your pretty-boy looks
have gotten us invited to
the festival's hottest party,
so we are having fun tonight.
Understood?
Yes.
Yes, Dorothy.
Now, come along, my friend.
Bitch.
[electronic music playing]
♪ ♪
Welcome, weary travelers.
For you...
And little missy.
l have a surprise for you.
So you can relax
and we can have fun later.
[upbeat dance music]
♪ ♪
Hey, Chris.
Hey.
Nice camera.
Old school.
Bolex 551 XL.
You know your cameras.
ls this the model
with 36 F.P.S.
and Aspheron wide-angle lens?
Yeah.
Everyone is talking
about your film.
Yeah, well, that's not always
a good thing.
Meaning?
l just totally fucked up
my scholarship interview.
Well, maybe l can put in
a good word for you.
C.W., making time with
our budding filmmaker?
Daniel, little Miss Abbey
sorely misses your company,
and she commanded
l come fetch you,
so come on.
Yeah, sure.
l am so screwed, Shane.
Screwed, screwed, super-screwed.
Don't jump to conclusions.
You just got under
this guy's skin.
Well, that's not the only
thing l got under.
l've seen Judas Kiss.
How'd you manage that?
lt blew me away.
lt's gonna blow everyone away,
no matter what that guy says.
l can see to that.
That's...awesome.
Shane, your mom cut herself
with the cheese knife thingy.
Godver.
C.W., do me a favor...
Take him home, will you?
He's a little, uh, wasted.
You gonna be okay?
Home in one piece, C.W.
Sure.
He's mine.
Hey.
Hey, camera dude!
Thanks.
l wish l was inside your head.
All right, let's get you
back to your dorm.
Wait. Abbey.
We, uh, need to get Abbey.
We'll get her on the way out.
Excellent.
Okay, let's get you to bed.
Okay.
Alone.
Bitch.
Good morning, son.
How'd you get in here?
Your R.A. seemed real eager
to let me surprise you.
So guess what l got in the mail?
l have no idea, Dad.
Two things:
your tuition bill...
and this.
My invitation.
Dad, can we, uh,
talk about this later?
l have a scholarship interview
to get to.
We talked about this
months ago, Danny.
l pay for film school,
and you are not
to show that film.
Dad, it's fiction.
lt's worse than fiction.
lt's a lie.
Look, Dad, l have a real
chance at winning this.
Not at my expense, you don't.
Not at your mother's.
Don't bring her into this.
Withdraw the film, son,
or your little
movie career is over.
Dad, please.
Aw, jeez.
Take a shower.
You stink.
[door opens and closes]
Gimme a cigarette.
l am not supposed
to talk to you.
So, don't talk.
Did that old windbag tell you
to stay away from me?
Why would she tell me that?
Because you have
a decision to make.
Don't let him win.
Danny?
Do you care about anyone else?
See, l won 1 5 years ago.
Judas Kiss won.
You cheated.
l did not.
What's the date on that?
[vibration]
First draft.
Senior year, high school.
So what?
Playing dumb doesn't really
do it for you.
Official rules say,
''Original screenplay written
while attending Keystone.''
Who are you, huh?
Why do you care
so much about my past?
His past is the key
to your future.
What on this campus
isn't the key to my future?
That script proves Danny
cheated with Abbey's help.
That's how you
keep him from winning.
Winning was the worst thing
that ever happened to you.
l can't just walk into
Blossom's office with this.
How would she know it's real?
You don't have to.
Now l gotta win.
He's going cut me off if l keep
Judas in the festival.
Your dad's really that much
of a Rasshol?
Trust me.
That's him on a good day.
Most people walk facing the
direction they're headed, C.W.
Hey.
You gonna go to
Martinez' party tonight?
Yeah, sure.
Great.
Then we'll meet you there.
And remember--
eyes forward.
Come on.
Only you and l know
about the script.
Look, l can't concentrate
on this right now, okay?
l'm serious.
Get him out of your head.
You know, you're right...
l gotta get psyched
about this interview.
l love you, Abs.
Oh!
Okay.
Too much love in the room.
Wish me luck, huh?
Luck, really.
Zach, you ready for this?
Uh, yeah. Ready.
ls it all right if l come in?
Perfectly fine, Danny.
l'll start where we left off.
Your film, Judas Kiss, tackles
some pretty intense issues.
Why such a controversial
subject in the short form?
Well, sir, l kind of wanted
Judas Kiss to be more of a...
great knockout punch rather
than an entire boxing match.
That is a wonderful
metaphor, Danny.
Thank you, sir.
Winning this competition
could open a lot of
doors for you, Danny.
What do you plan to do
with those opportunities?
Get rich.
[Ralph and Rebecca laugh]
So, um, where do you
see yourself, say,
in 1 5 years from now?
Famous, l hope.
l'd work for it, obviously.
Few more shorts
before l graduate,
then my first feature.
Actually, l have an idea
for it right now.
lt's about love in
a parallel universe
where everyone's
turned around.
Turned around?
Yeah, like an all-gay universe
where straight people
are the minority.
Gay, right.
Of course.
ls that a problem?
No, no.
Not for me, it isn't.
So, in 1 5 years...
Beach house in L.A.,
penthouse in New York,
maybe one or two movies a year.
Fly to places
like ltaly or Spain.
[chuckles]
What's so funny?
Nothing.
Spain is--
Spain's awesome, man.
So...
What happens when
everything doesn't go
according to your plan?
Well, l can work it.
Judas Kiss proves
what l can do.
Yeah, but there's lots of
great films in this festival.
What if it doesn't win?
Or what if you hit massive
writer's block one day?
Excuse me?
What if you don't become rich?
No fancy houses.
You're just a part-time waiter
who shoots wedding videos
on the weekends
for some millionaire's
spoiled daughter?
Are you supposed to be
asking me questions like this?
You shouldn't be afraid
of questions, Danny.
l'm not afraid.
All l'm asking is,
what happens when you don't
get what you want?
Look, l'm just focusing on
my goals right now.
lt sounds to me like you're
focusing more on the rewards.
What if you don't have
what it takes?
Okay, great.
Ralph, your turn.
Um, Danny, let's talk about
the lighting schemes you chose
and how you used light to
heighten the dramatic tension
between the father and the son.
Whaddya say, boys?
Lunch?
Uh, you two go ahead.
l'll catch up
after my cigarette.
All right, see you
at the cafeteria.
[playing softly]
♪ ♪
Mr. Wells.
Call me Zach.
We've had sex,
for Christ's sake.
So that's what
that was all about.
All what?
That interrogation.
Well, you survived
it, didn't you?
So what do you want now?
♪ ♪
Do you think l'm gonna fail?
You have everything
you need to get ahead...
Smarts, charm, looks.
Everything, huh?
You know, l can't stop
thinking about you.
l feel like
you really see me.
Why can't you just rely
on talent, on hard work?
Look, l'm not stupid.
l know it's all about
who you know.
You think you're always
gonna be able to get ahead
by breaking the rules,
use blowjobs and blackmail?
What happens when you run into
a player who's just using you?
Do you sell him your dreams?
We still talking about me?
Who are you anyway?
You know, nobody here knows you.
So who'd you sleep with
to get this gig?
l'm just the guy...
who can torpedo your shot
at stardom.
No.
See, l'm gonna count
on the audience
for Judas Kiss tomorrow night,
and the other two votes
on that panel.
The kid cheated.
l know.
Make things right.
Where's my dad staying?
College lnn.
Hey.
You got my note.
Here, come with me.
Why all stealth mode?
l thought we kinda made
a connection the other night.
Me too.
Shane really likes you.
ls that why we're doing this
out here in the middle
of the forest?
Shane is like the Emperor
of Keystone.
Look, Shane is amazing
and hot.
But you...
You know about Aspheron lenses.
And 36 F.P.S.
l'm just saying that
we should be careful.
[bells chiming
Westminster Quarters]
Shane...
l promised l'd go to dinner
with him tonight.
Don't piss off Shane.
You're really scared of
Shane, aren't you?
Okay.
You going to the party
at Martinez' later tonight?
You?
Uh-huh.
Okay.
Go, go...
You're killin' me.
l'll find you.
l am so dead.
Dude, we're in public.
Why should we care about them?
Doesn't it bother you
that you terrify people?
Do l terrify you?
Look, l'm serious.
What's that all about?
l don't live afraid...
Of them...
Of anyone.
♪ A thousand urgent voices ♪
♪ Shout their own refrain ♪
♪ ♪
♪ But you are the whisper ♪
♪ That will light... ♪
Feels really nice.
What's got your shoulders
so tense?
The festival?
You know, Judas Kiss
can't help but win something.
lt's not just that.
lt's my dad.
lf l don't win this festival,
l'm out on my ass.
l thought you totally
charmed up that judge.
Yeah, well, l'm not sure
how well l did that.
Maybe you could
use a tutorial.
Make him see how big
a difference he could make
in a young filmmaker's life.
♪ So incomplete ♪
♪ And as l'm raking through ♪
♪ The embers of this game ♪
♪ A thousand urgent voices ♪
♪ Shout their own refrain ♪
♪ But you are the whisper ♪
♪ That will light ♪
♪ This phoenix flame ♪
♪ Your love will let me ♪
♪ Breathe again ♪
Hey.
Move in with me next semester.
[Johnny Blk's Contemplations]
♪ ♪
No matter what happens
with your dad, with...
with the film festival,
we'd be set.
Say yes.
Y-yes...
Of course.
Okay.
You should get a move on.
This is your big day.
♪ ♪
♪ Foolishly ♪
♪ We all run blind ♪
♪ Across the earth ♪
♪ So l sit here ♪
♪ Contemplating ♪
♪ What it is l've done ♪
♪ Where l will be going ♪
♪ l am not the one ♪
♪ Not the one ♪
♪ ♪
♪ We're all looking ♪
♪ For immediate salvation ♪
♪ Unconditional love ♪
♪ At a price we can't afford ♪
(Both)
We need to talk.
Jeez, ambush much?
Feent.
But one at a time.
You first.
Since when do you care
who l sleep with?
Shane stares at you
like you're his property.
He likes me...
He wants me.
He can help me, Abs.
l don't have
a problem with that.
You're his flavor
of the month.
He only cares about
you because of
Judas Kiss and the festival.
He wants me to
move in with him.
You had to be high
to sleep with him.
God, stalker much?
You're jealous of Shane.
ls that what this is all about?
You and me?
Don't flatter yourself.
Would he be so into you
if he knew we broke the rules
to enter Judas Kiss
in the festival?
Shh!
Chris is right outside.
Yeah, and what about Chris?
He really likes you.
That's between me and Chris.
You want me to butt out?
Butt out.
Feent.
Abbey, come on.
Sleep with whomever you want,
but be your own man, you mus.
She's your biggest fan.
Not anymore.
So make it up to her.
l didn't do anything to her.
Look, before Judas Kiss
and this festival,
nobody at this school
knew l existed.
l was just the new weird kid
making a movie with his fag hag.
So l heard.
This is a competitive place.
Yeah, and l'm just
trying to keep up.
By shacking up with Shane?
How did you know that?
You think you're
Shane's first bitch?
Last year.
The way he calls me C.W.,
l swear, he made me
hate my own name.
He promised me everything,
anything l wanted.
Until Mommy and
Daddy Lyons met me,
and my films were too weird,
too bloody.
Too bloody weird.
So when do you meet them?
Today...
At the luncheon.
Come here.
You think l'm scared of Shane?
Nothing compares to how
scared he is of his parents.
Think about what you're doing.
l don't have a choice...
Look, l told you about my dad.
l need Shane's help.
Those pills
he's been feeding you...
they helping?
My dad's cutting me loose,
one of the judges
is out to get me.
l could lose everything.
l need a place to stay,
a job, money.
Shane can get me
all those things.
So you and me...
we're off the table.
Well, maybe we could, uh...
Look.
Whatever you've
done to get here,
l'll stand by you.
l'll be your friend.
But so long as
you're with Shane,
there can never be an us.
[door opens and closes]
[fork clinking on glass]
l'd like to recognize the
festival's continuing support
from Richard and
Annabelle Lyons,
Hollywood's most
generous financiers.
[applause]
And a heartfelt appreciation
to the judges
of our student competition:
cinematographer
Ralph Garlington,
screenwriter
Rebecca Lynn,
and, uh...
Keystone alumnus Zachary Wells.
[applause]
Screening of the
top five student films
begins at 7:00 in
the Lyons Theater.
Please, enjoy your dessert.
[door opens]
Reassuring to observe your
attention to hygiene, Mr. Wells.
l know that what
you've decided today
about Danny's future
changes everything for you.
Why am l so important?
Did you even look around as you
announced my name out there?
No one knew me.
l know.
You actually remember me?
Faces and films.
Frankly, with you,
it was more about the film,
the one that got you
into this competition.
Your face was pretty,
but your Judas Kiss
was horrifying.
l've never been able
to get it out of my mind.
Well, it wasn't a horror film.
You can't take a compliment,
can you?
That was supposed to be nice?
Would you like my critique?
Yes. No.
How did you even know
what l decided to do?
This is the key to your future.
Feent.
[clock chiming
Westminster Quarters]
Bitter?
Would you stop
sneaking up on me?
This roller coaster ride's
almost over.
You just need to take
the last loop.
l know what l have to do:
ruin a kid's career,
my career.
You already did that.
Go.
Go make his life
different than yours.
[movie playing indistinctly]
Are you okay?
Yeah.
Fine.
This is a really good movie.
Yeah. lsn't it?
l mean, Judas Kiss is...
l need to get some fresh air.
You want me to come with?
l'm fine.
Damn it, damn it, damn it,
damn it, damn it, damn it.
Hey.
You all right?
No...
Thanks to you.
That film playing
in there right now,
it's better than mine.
l'm gonna lose this thing.
So, congratulations.
l know that's what you wanted.
You know that, huh?
Yeah, l do.
You know, l wasn't bullshitting
when l said
l felt a connection with you.
l can't get you out of my head.
Believe me, l want to.
Zachary Wells
isn't my real name.
Yeah, duh.
You know?
You kept telling everyone,
''Please, call me Zach,''
like not even you believed it.
So who are you?
My real name is Daniel.
Like me?
Daniel Reyes Jr.
[vibration]
Come on, stop joking around.
l went to Lockton High School.
My mom had cancer twice.
She died my junior year.
My dad's a controlling
son of a bitch.
He cheated on my mom all
through her last year of life.
My dad fucked my drama teacher.
My dad fucked--
What the fuck, shut up!
Who are you?
Look at me...
Who am l?
Who are you?
[mouths word]
What just happened?
Reality, l think.
So what do we do now, huh?
What happens when
l go back to my life
and you go back to
the year 3000 or whatever?
Does any of this actually count?
l think it's a chance for you
to not make
the same mistakes that l did.
Don't move in with Shane.
How did you know about that?
He's only gonna try and
control you like Dad did.
Worse, even.
Look, l have
nowhere else to go.
You don't know how many
times you're gonna sell
little pieces of yourself
to people like Shane.
Your dreams aren't worth that.
God, you never fucking stop,
do you?
Hey, look at me!
Look at me, Danny.
l make cheap-ass wedding videos.
l go from shitty job
to shittier job.
l can't keep
a stable relationship.
l'm a seven who gets
rejected by nines.
l don't even know
what that means, okay?
lt's too late for me to
save myself, but you...
You can save me with your life.
Jesus, look, l am not you!
Please, just help me.
You're a fucking quitter.
l'm not!
l'll do what it takes
to get what l want!
Hollywood is never
gonna happen.
Chris, the guy you gave up
for the safety of being
Emperor Shane's bitch,
is gonna leave you in the dust
and become Keystone's
best-known film graduate.
You've already
driven Abbey away.
Shut up.
This is our chance.
l don't know why it's happening.
Maybe it's God.
l don't know.
But we have a chance
to make our life better.
You had your life...
and it's gone.
So any mistakes l make,
they're gonna be mine.
Mine!
l know you cheated
making Judas Kiss.
[grunts]
Look, you hate
your life so much,
then just kill yourself,
you fucking mus.
Leave mine alone.
Dude, everyone's looking
for you.
lt's a fucking shit storm.
l had to wait until l could
confirm the allegation.
The Judas Kiss screenplay
was written before
Mr. Reyes' matriculation
at Keystone.
[gasps and murmurs]
[groans]
Rough night?
Rough life.
l used to come
up here myself
when l was upset
about something,
which was often
back in the day.
Drama, drama, drama.
Not that l'm ungrateful,
but what are you doing here?
Walking down memory lane,
and l tripped over you.
[chuckles]
Looks like you tripped over
someone yourself.
Just a little disagreement
with myself.
l hope you knocked
some sense into yourself.
And then some.
l'm a mean son of a bitch.
Cigarette?
l've decided to quit.
Well, you're a better man
than me.
l've learned to take a punch
better than you.
l want to roll back
this roller coaster
that you've put me on.
Roller coasters
only go forward.
You know, l've figured out
who you are.
''Welds.''
That's just a typo, isn't it?
Frigging university's
too cheap to replace it.
You still go by Zachary?
No one could ever get used
to calling me that.
Yeah, tell me about it.
Well, no offense, old man,
but after tonight,
l'm definitely not gonna
let myself turn into you.
l'm sorry, Mr. Reyes.
We'll have to move on
to the next film.
[audience murmuring]
Hold on, Mrs. Blossom.
Ms. Lynn?
l won't argue with your rules,
but l've seen Danny's film.
So what if it's
no longer eligible?
The film's already
in the projector,
and the audience is here.
lt deserves to be seen.
l agree.
l do too.
Me too.
What's it gonna be, Mrs. B.?
Roll the film.
[applause]
Hey, uh...
l'm kinda freaking out.
Mind if l just hang back here
for a minute?
Uh...Yeah, sure.
Where the hell have you been?
Why is Judas Kiss playing?
With me.
Where are you taking me?
Just come on.
Eat your dinner.
l'm not hungry.
You have to eat.
- But l'm not hungry.
- Eat!
You had to let them show
that piece of shit?
You.
Only you could've
told Mrs. Blossom.
Get off me!
l asked you.
Don't l mean anything to you?
[bottle breaks]
You haven't meant
anything to me
since you let Mom die in pain.
l'm not one of
your super-villains
in your comic books, son.
l don't have
that kind of power.
You betrayed her.
Your mom wasn't the only one
in pain, Danny.
Yeah, then what about me, Dad?
Huh?
l was there for you.
l've been there for you forever.
With you, always,
since l was a kid.
Back then was different,
for you and me both.
Your mom's first cancer...
Whatever happened to
''Everything l do,
l do because l love you,
Danny boy''?
Huh?
Daddy?
Are you okay, Daddy?
Daddy! Wake up!
You know, l lied for you...
Told Mom you had to
work late after school.
l thought l was just keeping
your secrets, like always.
But you actually had a new one,
didn't you?
One you kept from me.
Daddy, you're bleeding!
No.
No, no.
No, Jude.
[grunting]
You'll help your old dad.
Yes, Daddy.
Whatever you say.
And you know everything l do
is because l love you, right?
Yes, Daddy.
Mom cried all the time,
and you weren't there!
But, you know, l was okay...
'cause l thought that
everything Dad did
was because he loves me...
wants me.
l--
l didn't want to lie to you.
You don't have
to speak to lie, Dad.
We all have things
we don't say.
You're no different, Danny.
l was nothing to you.
You're overreacting.
Then why don't you
take me down, Daddy,
just like always?
l'm done with you!
Do whatever you want...
Away from me.
Dad.
Leave.
[boy crying]
[applause]
What happened to you?
Difference of opinion.
This is certainly our most
unorthodox screening.
Though Judas Kiss is
no longer eligible to win,
l do want to recognize
the efforts of its director.
Ladies and gentlemen,
Daniel Reyes Jr.
[applause]
Thank you for
watching my film.
l know what l did
was wrong, but...
l guess l just wanted
everyone to know.
[applause]
Thanks.
Now, let's proceed
to tonight's awards.
So this was all about you?
C.W., little missy.
Well, you managed
to pull it off, Danny.
You lose and you still win.
Thanks.
Well, you could've thought
to thank your producer.
You weren't gonna
say anything.
l'm sorry,
l just couldn't help it.
Jeez, Abs, l'm sor--
Whatevs.
You two enjoy
your victory celebration.
Well, um, why don't
you two join us?
He owns you now.
Don't drag us into it.
Hey, come along with us, C.W.
Don't let him fuck up.
Don't fuck up.
Let's go, come on.
You know, you're not
supposed to be smokin' in here.
Mmm.
Well, l've been
thinking about quitting.
Maybe you're not such
a mus after all.
l don't know.
l don't think l can
take a punch.
You remember,
before Mom's first cancer,
back when Dad was happy?
We used to go
camping all the time.
l used to think l could just
reach up and touch that moon.
[owl hoots]
We don't get along too well,
do we?
No.
l'm scared.
You know, l'm coming around
to the notion that
roller coasters might
be able to run in reverse.
What the hell
are you talking about?
l mean that we can move in
whatever direction we want--
change things, patch things
that we fucked up,
maybe even afford the luxury
of a dream or two.
Are you ever gonna
make sense, dude?
One day...dude.
l certainly hope that wasn't
a Judas Kiss.
You and l have had
one too many betrayals.
You know, l'm never gonna
forget you.
Yes, you will.
So, time dude.
Do we ever fall in love?
l think you know enough
about the future already.
Come on.
Just give me a hint.
He's...
lnto bloody films.
Bloody films
and Bolex cameras?
So, what?
We live happily ever after?
No.
No?
You won't be able
to get rid of him,
and you'll spend
the next 1 5 years
waiting for him
to return your phone calls.
Now... Get outta here.
Key to the future.
[Brian Lam's Crash]
♪ ♪
♪ Lost and in between ♪
♪ The way you thought it was ♪
♪ And thought it seemed ♪
♪ And everyone has changed ♪
Bitch.
Christopher Wachowsky...
How was Spain?
Bloody crazy, dude.
Between that
and all the time zones,
l couldn't return your calls.
l'm so sorry.
l ain't mad at you.
How could you be?
You love me, Danny.
Only a little.
So explain your
weird-ass messages,
because l had nothing
to do with you
sleeping with yourself
as a kid.
Let's just say
l was recently inspired.
We need to try
something unexpected.
♪ Listen now
Listen now ♪
♪ lf you want another chance ♪
♪ You'll take it now ♪
♪ Oh, oh ♪
♪ When you crash ♪
♪ Crash, crash ♪
♪ lf it goes down tonight ♪
♪ lt's the messes ♪
♪ That you make ♪
♪ The hearts ♪
♪ That you will break ♪
♪ When you crash ♪
♪ Crash, crash ♪
♪ Oh, don't go another day ♪
♪ lt's time to walk away ♪
♪ When you crash ♪
♪ Crash, crash ♪
♪ Oh, you'll crash ♪
♪ One step forward ♪
♪ Three steps back ♪
♪ The rain is comin' ♪
♪ Fallin' fast ♪
♪ Don't give in to misery ♪
♪ When happiness ♪
♪ Can set you free ♪
♪ One step forward ♪
♪ Three steps back ♪
♪ The rain is comin' ♪
♪ Fallin' fast ♪
♪ Don't give in to misery ♪
♪ When happiness ♪
♪ Can set you free ♪
♪ ♪
You manipulative
son of a bitch!
You were behind all of this.
[Brian Lam's lf l Fall]
♪ ♪
♪ A thousand ways
A thousand words ♪
♪ Still nothin' to say ♪
♪ A thousand ways
A thousand words ♪
♪ Still nothin' to say ♪
♪ With every day ♪
♪ And every night ♪
♪ Shadows shift ♪
♪ They take flight ♪
♪ With every day ♪
♪ And every night ♪
♪ Shadows shift ♪
♪ lf l fall
lf l fall ♪
♪ lf l fall again ♪
♪ Will you be ♪
♪ Here with me ♪
♪ lf l fall again? ♪
♪ ♪
♪ Many times ♪
♪ l've tried so hard ♪
♪ But it's never enough ♪
♪ Many times ♪
♪ l've tried so hard ♪
♪ But it's never enough ♪
♪ A siren blares ♪
♪ But no one cares ♪
♪ They just look ♪
♪ They just stare ♪
♪ A siren blares ♪
♪ And no one cares ♪
♪ They just look ♪
♪ lf l fall
lf l fall ♪
♪ lf l fall again ♪
♪ Will you be ♪
♪ Here with me ♪
♪ lf l fall again? ♪
♪ Bruises and scars ♪
♪ They go so far ♪
♪ But l want to know ♪
♪ Bruises and scars ♪
♪ They go so far ♪
♪ But l want to know ♪
♪ lf l fall
lf l fall ♪
♪ lf l fall again ♪
♪ Will you be ♪
♪ Here with me ♪
♪ lf l fall again? ♪
♪ A thousand ways
A thousand words ♪
♪ Still nothin' to say ♪
♪ A thousand ways
A thousand words ♪
♪ Still nothin' ♪
To say.