[Horns honking]
¶ Better watch your back ¶
¶ Three rivers is murky ¶
¶ Run up the jibs
get touched in a hurry ¶
¶ Lucky if you live to see 20 or 30 ¶
¶ With no holes in your body
or your throwback jersey ¶
¶ These hos ain't dirty ¶
¶ Homeys do your dirty ¶
¶ My city is green ¶
¶ Everybody stays thirsty ¶
¶ I'll let you know
that my city ain't safe ¶
¶ I got friends still living
with holes in they face ¶
¶ Wheelchair homeys can't move
below the waist ¶
¶ Don't be misled about the PGH ¶
¶ The haters in the water
and it's all about waste ¶
¶ When the Jake bangs a cutty
it's a open-shut case ¶
¶ Everybody's broke in the ghetto ¶
¶ We cut throats ¶
¶ Steel City triggers
we ain't easy to approach ¶
¶ Folks in my city
keep toasting the coat ¶
¶ Beefs escalate you know
for coke and the dope ¶
¶ Still city killers
everybody's below ¶
¶ From the Village to the North Side ¶
¶ Guns we tote ¶
Since kindergarten,
I had this brotherly connection
with my four closest friends.
- What's up, guys?
- What's going on?
Five bucks a head.
There's my main man, Kevin.
Five bucks?
What's up with that?
We got our own shit, bro.
Yeah, man, well, you know, we got
three kegs and a DJ to pay for
so it's five bucks.
Oh, man, that's whack.
I'm gonna be right back, okay?
Yeah, well, whack or not,
it's five fucking bucks.
What are you gonna do, man?
Hey, spot me five?
Yeah, man.
There you go.
All right.
Go have some fun, huh?
Have a good time, guys.
[Jumping hip-hop music]
[People laughing and talking]
There's crazy Chris.
Cool tat.
Can I see the rest of it?
Okay, switch.
There's smooth Darick.
Dude, this is your mom's house.
You can do whatever you want.
You know what?
I don't know what to tell you.
Everybody paid five bucks.
Steady Eddie.
Oh, man, that's whack.
Now I owe Porter five bucks.
Look, man, you want to buy an Island?
Yo, yo, yo, homes.
Give me a shot on that.
Back up, man, back up.
My bad, my bad, my bad.
We're cool.
And then there was me.
I was the catalyst of the group.
We had one common theme.
It was the basis for numerous conflicts
within each of our lives and,
I suppose, stunted our growth
from being the responsible people
others expected us to be.
It was money.
It wasn't always parties, though.
During football season
we took bets from our friends
on the college games.
You in on that?
Look at him coming down.
He's at the 10.
He's at the 5.
Touchdown!
No!
Yes!
It was all small-time,
but your standard
bookmaking operation, nonetheless.
The only problem was,
some of our money-making ideas
cost more to put on than they brought in.
Who did that?
Oh, come...
all right, hang on a second.
All it would take is one
moderate disaster to wipe out
a week's worth of hard work and profits.
So some jagoff stole the keg pump.
We're gonna lose a $100 deposit on that.
Perfect.
Already down this week.
That's good.
- Good, all right.
- Yeah.
What are you doing with your life, huh?
There's a lot of people willing
to bend over backwards to help you.
Did your mom catch you
in her underwear drawer again?
I was trying to look pretty
for you, buddy.
I don't know who looks better
in those things, you or her.
Me for sure.
I've been doing that Buns of Steel
your mother taught me.
Tell your mom
you're gonna be late tonight?
Why do you think she's screaming
at me all the fucking time?
"Aiee!"
Yo, boys, I'm getting laid tonight
like wall-to-wall carpet.
You say that every time we go out.
Does that shit ever happen?
I'm trying to psych myself up, all right?
You can do all the positive
thinking you want.
No one's going home with you
till you pop that fucking zit
on the side of your face.
Hey, hey.
Leave it.
Damn it.
- Why you got to give him shit like that?
- 'Cause he's good-Iooking.
- He's better looking than you are.
- Nobody's better looking than me.
Marc Anthony,
that's a good-Iooking guy.
Whoa, I would switch teams for him.
[Laughs]
Hey.
How you doing?
What?
Oh.
Fuck you.
Prick.
Hey, what are you doing?
I came out for a smoke.
It's freezing out here.
Yo, yo, yo, check it out.
Check it out.
Are those hookers?
No, you jagoff.
They're Girl Scouts.
Hey, do me a favor.
Go over there and get me
a box of Thin Mints.
Look at those tits.
I'm gonna break them off a ten spot,
see if I can get a piece.
Yeah, yeah, do it, do it, do it.
All right, I'll see you in a minute.
What's up?
Hey, guys.
What's going on?
Where you girls from?
I haven't seen you around before.
Oh, well, we just moved
into this joint.
My name's Sienna.
And this is my girl Jasper.
Yeah, yeah, well,
who you hiding from?
'Cause nobody comes
on North Side
unless they have to.
So you guys want to do something?
I'm a really fun date.
Tell me something.
What can I get for $10?
How about a kick in the dick?
[Laughter]
That ain't exactly
what I had in mind, sweetheart.
You know what?
I'd like to apologize for my friend.
Just to let you know,
if I had the money,
I'd spend it in a second.
Aw, that's sweet.
Hey, I don't know if you guys
are busy or not.
But, you know,
can I buy you guys both a drink?
I mean, come on.
It's, you know, it's our bar.
We're always in there.
It's cold outside.
Ten minutes, come on.
All right.
Yeah?
All right, come on.
[Heels clacking]
What do you guys like to drink?
Whiskey.
[Twangy blues music]
¶ ¶
All right, Jasper.
This is Eddie.
Hi, nice to meet you.
This is Sienna.
- Hi.
- Hi, nice to meet you.
Look at that punk.
He's such a punk.
He doesn't even like playing darts.
Don't get bent just 'cause
you ain't got no game.
I got game.
Hey, guys.
What have you got, another pitcher?
Oh, this one's done.
I'll go get another.
Excuse me.
I want the good stuff, huh?
Here you go.
Yo, when you gonna
get rid of that jacket, Bob?
You ain't Terry Bradshaw.
No, the glory days are over.
At least I had glory days.
Ooh.
Yo, he just beat me to the punch.
Bitch of it is;
I saw them first.
Yo, yo, what did you talk about?
What you talk about?
Not a whole lot.
Well, the pigtail's kind of tough.
Someone probably nailed her
in the ass when she was 12
and fucked up her head.
Like what happened to Eddie
on that camping trip?
Whatever, moron.
Hey, Bobby, you got that
pitcher coming?
Oh, man, I got to go.
Kimberly's due back.
Hurry back.
We're gonna play
hide the kielbasa with Eddie later.
Bring your sleeping bag.
[Funky music and singing]
¶ ¶
What's up, player?
Got another smoke?
Uh, yeah, man.
Yeah.
Sure appreciate it, my man.
I forgot to go to the store
and buy a pack before it close.
You know?
I like them shoes too.
They clean.
Yeah.
I like 'em.
And right there I got the idea.
Shit, yeah, here he goes again.
Hold up, y'all.
I've been giving this a lot of thought.
Those hookers last night...
seriously.
Here are girls who live
in a shitty-ass apartment
and smoke crack all day, right?
That is a business opportunity
waiting to happen, y'all.
Yo, you okay with him pimping
out your new girlfriends?
[Laughter]
Shut up.
Yo, they're gold mines
waiting to be discovered.
Your average hooker for hire
is doing what,
like, two, three dudes a night?
You know those hos
do more guys than that.
All right, all right.
Make a point here.
Let's say three.
They're charging something like
$200 an hour.
Now, granted, guys don't keep them
for more than an hour.
But that right there?
That's $600 a night.
Yo, there's no way those two girls
are making six bones a night.
Exactly my motherfucking point,
'cause I'm not talking about
your average back-alley ho.
I'm talking about
call girls, y'all.
They make $200.
Now check this.
$200, $600 times seven days a week...
Do these chicks get off on each other?
Oh, I never make it this far.
Equals $4,200 a week, a week y'all.
[Women moaning]
Times four weeks in a month
equals $16,800.
That's almost $17,000 a month,
y'all, per girl.
Per girl, y'all.
What if they want a day off?
Fuck that.
They don't take a day off
doing drugs, do they?
[Woman moaning]
Hey.
You're not even paying attention.
Are you suggesting
that we become pimps?
I would rather not use the term "pimp,"
rather the term "investors,"
'cause you got to figure
it's gonna take a little seed capital
to get this thing going.
I mean, we've got to buy them
new clothes and stuff,
get their hair did,
manicures, pedicures.
I figure all, like, $200 apiece.
Whoa, wait a minute.
Hold up a second.
It was one thing when you wanted
to raise rottweilers
in my backyard.
But this, this is another story, Brian.
You're talking about prostitution here.
Yeah.
So?
Eddie, this is prostitution.
I'm sorry.
You like working at the brewery?
Take a look at us, man,
all of us.
In a couple years, y'all,
we're gonna be 30.
You know what we're gonna have
to show for that?
Nothing.
I work at a hardware store,
and I'm 26 years old,
and I make $7 an hour.
And all I got waiting for me
at the end of this
is a shitty-ass 401(k).
And a bad back.
You work at a video store.
The garage, man.
Electronics store;
you hate that place.
No offense, fellas.
We fucked up.
All right, and none of this shit's
getting any better
unless we make it better now.
I may not like it,
but it pays the bills, you know?
Okay?
I know, man.
I know, Eddie.
And look, if all that you want out of life
is to pay those bills, man,
then so be it.
But I don't want to live
on the Upper North Side
of Pittsburgh my whole life.
I want to cross that bridge, y'all.
And I don't want to come back
unless I choose to.
Y'all know what I'm saying at all?
It's a great idea, Brian.
Really, it is.
But it's illegal, you know?
Like hardcore illegal.
Thank you, Darick.
Y'all, so are sports bets,
poker games, and marijuana.
But y'all don't got a problem with that.
Yo, I'm not asking you to kill somebody.
This ain't even like robbing a bank.
This is consenting adults.
It's a victimless crime.
Just... just... just think about it.
Think about it, y'all.
That's all I'm saying.
Huh?
The decision to start
our new business was unanimous.
Well, almost unanimous.
Are you kidding?
No, no.
You know, I wouldn't get it otherwise.
Look, you can do your thing.
It's just not for me.
What do you mean, man?
Because it's not right.
I mean, it's exploiting someone
who is down on their luck.
Oh, come on, Eddie.
Look, I want to go back to school and...
[laughs]
School?
Eddie, come on, man.
That's the whole thing.
You ain't gonna have to go
to school, baby boy.
Yeah, but I want to go to school.
Come on, man.
Brian, I want to get my degree.
Okay, so instead
of making fat cash now
and enjoying your life,
you really want to torture
yourself through school?
That makes a lot of sense, Eddie.
I dig that.
I'm gonna go to school.
All right, look.
You do you.
Okay?
Come on, man.
It's like that?
It's like that.
And with that, Kevin, Darick, Chris,
and myself made a pact to become...
well, lack for a better word, pimps.
¶ Got pimping in my blood ¶
¶ Hustling in my bones ¶
¶ Guess who did that ¶
[singing]
So that's your business idea?
Well, yeah.
It does sound like a pretty good idea.
We're fine.
We don't need a pimp.
We never have, never will.
Clean up your shit.
You do know that we are not
criticizing what y'all do.
I love what y'all do.
Most definitely.
It's just the way in which you do it,
it could be better for you, for you.
I think that we can agree that jumping
in cars with random scumbags
just ain't safe, right?
Okay, that's it; thanks, guys.
We're willing to spend money.
Yeah, we're all gonna chip in here.
Right, guys?
$200 a piece.
Or more, you know,
probably more.
Girls, we're willing to do
whatever it takes to make this happen.
Okay?
Just talk to us.
You must have been smoking crack.
A cut of the business
and buy their drugs?
Who's the lamb that's gonna do that?
'Cause I know it ain't gonna be me.
Relax.
I can't relax.
That wasn't part of the plan, man.
Relax.
[Giggles]
Whoo!
Ow!
Come on.
Why don't you use
your cell phone, man?
Why don't we use yours
so that they could
trace it to you, you jagoff.
Darick's weed supplier, Marty,
arranged a meeting
with this dude named Nate...
He knows that we're coming?
At what time?
All right.
A self-made cat who dealt
in all matters of cocaine.
We're on.
Cool, cool.
¶ ¶
¶ Yeah ¶
¶ Uh-huh ¶
¶ Money on the mind ¶
¶ Hustling all the time ¶
¶ All about the paper
'cause the younging on his grind ¶
¶ Younging on his grind ¶
¶ Young, younging on his grind ¶
¶ Money on the mind ¶
¶ Hustling all the time ¶
¶ All about the paper
'cause the younging on his grind ¶
¶ Younging on his grind ¶
¶ Young, younging on his grind ¶
[door creaks]
What's up?
Uh, we're here to see Nate.
I'm Darick.
I'm Marty's friend from...
Yeah, I know who you are.
You the party from the North Side.
Get your dumb asses inside.
Don't be naming names
on my porch, motherfucker.
Take your hat off.
Daryl, come here, son.
Go help your Mama.
Take your toy.
Baby?
Come on, Daryl.
Let's watch TV.
Come on, come on.
He ain't never seen that many
white boys together at once.
[Chuckles]
[Sighs]
So tell me.
Why the sudden interest
in the crack cocaine trade?
Well, Nate, we don't...
We don't.
Really think that that matters.
With all due respect, man.
You know, the situation is
that we're gonna be needing,
like, a fairly large quantity of product
on a fairly regular basis.
I didn't mean to sound like a dick.
We're not really asking
where it's coming from,
you know, so I don't really
figure it should matter
where it's going, right?
What's your name again?
I'm Brian.
Okay, Brian.
Let me tell you something.
You best start caring where
the stuff comes from.
Dig?
'Cause shit rolls downhill,
if you know what I'm saying.
And I don't run
that kind of program.
My supplier knows
the intricacies of my business,
and I know the intricacies
of those I do business with.
Without that,
we ain't got shit to talk about.
All right, all right.
I mean, that makes sense.
You got to know.
Right.
The deal is, we got some girls
who are willing to date guys
in exchange for crack.
Y'all got what willing to do what?
Girls, hookers willing
to date dudes for crack.
[Laughs]
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Whoa, man, wait a minute.
Wait a minute.
So what you telling me is,
y'all are pimping hos.
Is that it?
That's what you said.
You white motherfuckers
are pimping bitches?
For real?
Damn, a nigger can't have shit no more.
[Laughs]
I'm a pimp.
What?
I am, right?
[Laughs]
Oh, damn.
Yo, man.
Y'all cool with me.
Come on.
Y'all make yourself at home, pimps.
Yeah, I remember back in the day,
I was a pimp.
[Chuckles]
See, the pimp game,
that's about getting the bitch
to sell that ass and give you money,
not half of it, not 3l4 of it, all of it.
But in your case,
you're in partnership
with the bitches' first love,
which is crack cocaine.
So you take on those bitches,
you take on their habits.
It could be costly.
How much shit you talking?
That's where we're running
into a little confusion, man.
You know, we...
we don't know how much
that translates to on your end,
but the girls are saying...
Whoa, whoa, whoa,
wait, wait, wait.
First off, any female
who suck dick for a living,
she ain't no girl.
My wife's a girl, a lady.
Them hos you get?
They bitches.
All right.
The bitches.
There you go.
Now all y'all say it.
All: The bitches.
Mm-hmm.
My niggers.
All right, man.
Well, the bitches say they're
smoking about 20 rocks a day.
I don't know what that...
They're probably buying $10 rocks.
That's $200 a day.
Multiply by two bitches.
They're your bottom bitches.
You're gonna get more bitches.
Shit, man.
You talking about a sizeable
amount of stuff,
especially if you talk about
buying month to month.
Like how much?
Mm, somewhere
in the neighborhood of 15 Gs.
Well, you know, we were wondering if,
you know,
we could get a volume discount.
[Laughs]
What?
A volume discount.
A volume discount?
What the fuck is a volume discount?
Do I look like
a motherfucking flea market?
No.
No, I don't give out no discounts.
My prices are fixed.
What you pay for a gram last week,
you pay this week.
I don't fluctuate.
And I sure as hell don't give
out no motherfucking discounts.
Sorry.
[Sighs]
I tell you what.
Look, I ain't got no time to be making
no extra group of rocks for your hos.
Y'all got to do that yourselves.
So you give me 15 Gs...
no, fuck that.
Give me 12 Gs.
I'll go to my supplier, get a kilo.
You let me cut it up.
I take four ounces off the top for myself.
We call it even.
All right, well, we're not
gonna have that kind of cash
right off the bat.
It's all still new to us, man.
So we're gonna have to be
buying smaller amounts
till we get things rolling.
You gonna show us
how to make the rocks?
You get your bitches
to give me a volume discount?
We could work something out.
Deal, baby.
Let's go.
Welcome to the lab, fellas.
This here, that's a kilo.
Back in the day,
I got a bitch going to jail
stuff that up her ass.
Glass broke.
Bitch got high off it.
Her ass sucked it up.
Crack ass.
Show you how to make this shit.
You got to get 2l3 cocaine
with 1l3 baking soda.
Put some water in there.
You let that simmer.
Stir this.
Ah.
You know that aroma?
Just smell it in.
Go ahead, smell it.
Yeah.
And Chef Nathaniel creates his famous
crack cocaine souffle
with Arm & Hammer seasoning spice.
Ta-da.
And Chef Nate can cook it, can sell it.
But most important rule,
don't partake in the product.
Makes a motherfucker lose focus
and fuck everything up.
Y'all feel me?
Yeah.
Keep this up.
That's how it's done.
Then you chop it up into little pieces,
and you get rocks.
See that there?
That sell for 20 bucks
on any street in America.
The American dream.
Mm, small little thing, ain't it?
It's so cute.
Yeah, it was great.
I mean, Bozeman was like,
"Darick, you're late.
Your shift started two hours ago."
I was like, "Hey, my bad, dog.
"You know, I thought I was off.
I just thought I'd come down
and let you eat my ass."
That's my boy.
Hey.
Did I just hear what I think I heard?
Hey, look.
I got it covered, all right?
Yeah, what do you mean,
you got it covered?
I mean, I got a handle on it.
Just relax.
I'm not gonna do anything
to hurt James here.
I don't know, Brian.
Chris, don't puss
out on me now, all right?
I need you to do this.
Why can't Darick or Kevin do it?
Because I need you to do it.
The girls can't be alone
right now, all right?
We got to have somebody with them
24 hours, seven days a week.
We got to keep an eye
on our investment, man.
I don't know.
Chris, everybody is doing their part,
baby boy.
And this is what I need
you to do, all right,
in order for this to work.
You need to do this.
You're gonna be living
under the same roof
with 24-hour,
seven-day-a-week pussy, man.
Come on.
All right.
Yes.
You're gonna be rich.
Okay, so there's this documentary.
Yeah, it's about this German director.
Basically they have, you know,
they hired two different actors
for the same scene.
And the first actor is like
this English rock star guy.
And he's like,
"It's pretty cool, right?"
And then it's horrible, obviously.
We're just like,
"Whoa, that's crazy."
And then you see, like, all the people
down at the bottom of the bell tower,
and they're all like,
"What the fuck?"
[Laughter]
It's amazing.
It's my favorite thing.
You guys want a beer?
- Yeah.
- I can take one.
Sure.
Get your shit out of my bathroom.
Hi.
So what was that in there?
What?
I kind of sense you vibing me
a little bit.
Oh, really?
Vibing you?
Maybe you weren't?
Maybe.
"Maybe," huh?
What, "maybe" is not good
enough for you?
Yeah, "maybe" is good enough.
Shit, I haven't had a "maybe" in a while.
So when was your last "maybe"?
It's been a couple months.
What about you?
[Laughs]
When was your last "maybe"?
Yesterday.
Did I ruin it for you?
I don't know.
Got me thinking.
Thinking about what?
You're a smart girl.
You're cute, cool to hang out with.
I just don't get it.
What don't you get?
That you could sell your body
to some scumbag you never even...
Don't fucking touch me.
You understand me?
You're not my daddy.
I already have one of those.
Believe me.
Hey.
Where's your partner at?
Oh, she's up in the apartment
trying some stuff on.
Right on.
Check it out.
[Laughs]
Now, you see,
that's what I'm talking about.
None of these sluts know how
to market themselves.
Look at this shit.
"White European female, 25,
alcohol only."
What does that tell you?
Nothing.
That doesn't tell you shit.
Look, the key to this business
is marketing.
You got to be explicit.
You got to say stuff like, you know,
"Hot blonde likes it up the ass,"
or "Empty your nuts in my mouth."
[Crashing]
You guys are laughing,
but I'm fucking serious, okay.
[Glass clinking]
That's how you get their attention.
All in the marketing.
What's our ad say?
Oh, ours is nice, man.
Homegirl wrote most of it.
"Tandem Greek freak
specializing in BDSM,
water sports"...
That's pissing.
"Role-play.
"Let your fantasy become reality.
One blonde, one dirty, 23, 24,
alcohol only."
Boom.
Tandem Greek freak?
Jasper, you wrote that?
No, no, no.
That part's my contribution.
Hey.
Kevin's phone's been ringing nonstop.
With dudes?
Yeah, man.
We got, like, ten calls in the last hour.
Well, let's start
calling them back, right?
Schedule in some shit.
What am I supposed to say to these guys?
Homey, you ain't got
to say anything, man.
Just ask them what time
they want to party.
All right, give me this.
Hey, y'all.
This is it, what it's all about,
right here, right now.
Yeah, did you call this number?
Yeah.
Yeah, this is the escort service.
Oh, we got two girls;
a blonde and a dirty blonde.
You can have one,
or you can have them both.
Ah, 200 bucks an hour for one
or 300 bucks for the both,
which is, you know, my friend,
it's obviously a better deal.
Okay, just one?
Which one?
The blonde?
Yeah, okay.
Yeah.
Holy shit.
What?
It's just a wig.
No, no, no, not a problem.
Everything's fine.
Uh-huh.
Okay.
No, no, no, sure.
It's not a problem.
No, I was talking...
The guy just hung up.
Give me that before you hurt yourself.
Press Send again.
Hey, baby, you just call?
Hi.
Yeah, my name's Jasper.
What's your name?
Hi, Don.
How can I help you, baby?
Yeah, I can do that.
Mm-hmm.
All right, I'm gonna
pass you over to my assistant.
He's gonna get directions.
All right, see you soon, baby.
Damn!
That's like some straight-up
hottie fly shit.
Shh.
All right, no problem.
Make sure you get a tip.
Just keep it to yourself.
[Rapping]
¶ I like the way she drop it
down to the floor ¶
¶ Break it off
wiggle it a little more ¶
¶ She got a nigger hard up... - ¶
Yes.
Yes, yes.
Get in there, get in there.
Way to make an outfit.
My man, could you... real quick?
Appreciate that.
[Rapping]
¶ ¶
¶ When I came in the door ¶
¶ I seen her before ¶
¶ Dropping that ass all the way
down to the floor ¶
¶ Yeah, I like what's going on
over there ¶
[slapping]
¶ Oh, I don't think
the girl really know ¶
¶ How she got the whole club
moving in slo-mo ¶
¶ When they can't keep up ¶
Six months into our little business,
things could not have been going better.
Early on, I got this idea to offer
the Johns cocaine and weed
in addition to the girls,
kind of like a party package.
That turned out to be more lucrative
than the girls themselves.
For a bunch of half-assed guys like us,
we had a pretty air-tight operation.
Nate grew to be an invaluable resource,
providing us with any quantity
of shit we needed
so long as he got his cut,
four ounces from every kilo
we ordered,
which became almost two keys a week.
That was all Darick's job.
He was in charge of everything
that had to do with cocaine:
Buying it, transporting it, cutting it,
making the rocks,
and most importantly,
keeping our girls fed
with their daily needs.
I had Darick move into the girls
apartment just for convenience.
Every day, he'd deliver crack
for the girls
along with any other packages
that the Johns
might have ordered
for the upcoming night.
It was perfect.
Trick or treat, ladies.
Let's get it going, all right?
With the help of Jasper,
who turned out to have
quite the mojo for business,
we recruited three more girls:
Tiara...
Here, Tiara.
Moira, and Sebastian.
Here you go, Sienna.
Looking good.
And the beautiful thing
was how the transactions took place,
because none of us were dealing
directly with the Johns.
The risk to us was minimal.
It was the girls who had
their asses on the line,
because they were the ones who
were actually making the transactions.
Drugs for money and sex on top of it.
If any of the Johns turned out to be cops,
girls' asses that got busted, not us.
[Balls crack]
Our only contact with the customers
was through Kevin.
He was in charge
of setting up the dates.
It was ingenious.
The Johns would respond
to the call girl ad
by calling Kevin's prepaid cell phone
so it couldn't be traced.
Then after one of the girls
has sex with the John, and only then,
will Kevin proposition
the guy next time,
ask him if he wanted any blow.
Jasper?
No, she's not available right now.
Oh, well, how about this?
How about I send over this
hot little blonde number for half price?
How's that sound?
Yeah, very.
Very.
Uh-huh, okay.
All right.
Yeah, I'll have her at your
doorstep ready to party
in less than an hour.
All right, man.
[Phone ringing]
After Kevin got the order
for coke and the girl,
he'd call Chris and give him
the John's address,
tell him what the order was for
along with which girl he wanted.
Not a problem.
Chris would then let Darick know
so he could fill the coke order
kind of like a pharmacist
and bring it down to his place
later for delivery.
And just as a precautionary measure,
Darick would then call Kevin back
to confirm the coke order
and the quantity.
Not that I didn't trust any of my guys,
but I didn't want to leave any loopholes
just in case anybody
got any ideas, you know?
As for me, well, I probably had
the best job of them all.
I was quality control
and general manager
of the whole operation.
Every week I would pass out the cash
so Darick could buy his coke,
give Chris money for rent and gas,
and gave Jasper funds
for the girls' clothes and makeup.
A few bills for Kevin's cell phone
and the adult ads.
Everybody got their cut.
How much are you spending
on clothes per day?
This goes to my girl.
She's earned it.
My man, good.
Now, this is for you,
if you brought something in.
But you don't.
I can't be having you come in...
I personally was pulling in
about 20 grand a week.
Not bad for a high school dropout.
Hell, I would have been
fine with that in a year.
I guess that's the irony of destiny.
¶ ¶
Is this too gaudy?
Beyond gaudy.
It's John Gotti.
You know,
I got a few new threads,
but you guys,
you guys are nuts.
Yo, say hello
to my little friends.
Holy shit.
- Is that a...
- M16 with a 403 grenade launcher.
Yes it is.
Why do you have that?
I think the question
should be, "Why not?"
Fair enough.
Yo, I'll catch y'all later.
I'm gonna go get that 60-inch plasma.
Work it out.
Yeah, yeah, it's good to see you.
Darick, what did you do?
Where do you keep getting
this kind of money?
Don't start.
It's not like that.
It's not stolen.
I swear.
It's all hundreds.
Buy whatever you need.
And get something
for your mom too, okay?
Look, I know I haven't been
the best father for James.
You and I,
we've had our problems.
I'm gonna change that, all right?
I just need a little more time.
Okay.
You know it's not
about the money, right?
James needs his dad.
I'm trying here.
Okay, I am.
I'm trying.
I just need you to hang in there
with me, okay?
Huh?
Okay?
Okay.
And all this stays?
Absolutely, as is.
Do you smell that?
No.
What is it?
It's pussy.
I'm sorry?
Look at this place, man.
The kind of joint where panties
come right off.
Oh, yes.
You want to know
what I'm gonna put right there?
Hmm?
A panty basket.
Hell yeah.
Have you seen Snoop?
None of them cats
with a panty basket in their crib.
I'm gonna be the first motherfucker.
Does that mean we have a deal?
Yeah.
[Jumping hip-hop music]
¶ ¶
Any of you guys want an Island?
[Laughs]
Oh, yeah, no, I know.
But it's just like a temporary thing.
You know, what I really want to do is act.
You know, like in regular movies,
like a romantic comedy or something.
Yeah, so I got a few more
prerequisites to finish,
and then I can enter that program.
You know, I got a full boat this semester.
Oh, that's great, man.
That's great.
Yeah.
Hey, have you seen Jasper any place?
No, no, I haven't.
I haven't seen her.
Well, I'll see you in a minute, all right?
[Jumping hip-hop music]
¶ ¶
¶ Hit me up and we can ball today ¶
¶ I'm from the hood in the city ¶
"Like a rose caught in a book
"on which pure women
may not look,
"for its base pages claim control
and crush the flower
within the soul."
That was my sister
Jenny's favorite poem.
You know, she was only 13,
and I was 14,
when we moved out here
from Wisconsin, just the two of us.
Where's your sister now?
You can only self-medicate for so long.
And about six months ago,
she just didn't wake up.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Thanks.
I wish I had known.
I never would have let that happen.
I don't want to do this anymore, Kevin.
I don't know.
I thought I'd do this business
with you guys,
and that would be my ticket out.
But I'm scared,
because this life is,
you know, all I know.
What is it that you want to do?
I don't know.
It's okay; it's okay.
[Laughs]
My nigger.
[Phone ringing]
Thanks for the shamrock, man.
Does this make me Irish now?
Nah.
You know, you blowing up, man.
Yeah, you a real player now.
Oh, thank you, brother.
Thank you.
Thing is, though,
I ain't the only one who notice.
You moving a lot of shit.
That many K flowers in a week
ain't no joke.
That many K flowers in a month
You got bitches.
You got the D flowers.
You got websites.
Seems like you on the tip
of just about everything.
And the powers that be,
they're starting to ask questions.
Well, what you talking about, brother?
Who's asking questions?
[Laughs]
Nigger, you think I grow
these D flowers
in my backyard?
No, they is they.
And they are putting you on notice.
They gonna start taxing your ass.
From here on out,
the going rate for a K flower
is gonna be 30 Gs.
You feel me?
Made payable directly to they.
30 grand?
That's fucking nuts.
[Laughs]
Hey, baby, baby, don't trip, man.
I don't like it either.
That's the cost of being a baller.
So just roll with it.
That's all you can do.
What if I decide to start getting
my shit from someplace else, man?
Huh?
What happens then?
You don't want to know the answer
to that question, dog.
Yeah?
On real, don't get it twisted, baby.
So just be cool.
Keep everything together.
And look at it this way.
You made it, dog.
Oh, yeah, you're a big-time baller,
because they don't come knocking
unless you're a bona fide player.
So you be cool.
Peace out.
Good thing gonna be all right, baby.
And thanks for the shamrock.
Happy birthday to me.
Rule number one.
Never partake in your own product.
You remember that?
Hey, man.
It's your birthday.
People are looking for you.
They're gonna bring out
the cake in a minute.
I'm gonna be down
in a second, all right?
Darick.
Shh.
Check this shit out, man.
Boom.
Oh, man, that it tight.
You like that?
That costs more
than your car right there.
That cost more than my life.
Hey, man.
Hey, sweetie.
Yo, here he is.
All: Happy birthday!
Kevin, Kevin.
Where's Darick?
Where's Eddie?
Eddie, Eddie.
How you doing, my man?
I'm good, man.
I'm good.
- Happy birthday, buddy.
- Happy birthday, dog.
Thank you, man.
For sure, for sure.
Eddie, thanks for coming, man.
Come here.
- Hey, let's get this picture.
- Let's get this picture.
For us.
[Camera shutter clicks]
[Cheers and applause]
It's fucking bullshit, Kevin.
What kind of fucking punks do they
think they're dealing with, dude?
I'm not somebody you fuck with, Kevin.
I did not work this fucking hard
to be disrespected.
I swear to Christ, man.
Ever since we been coming up,
the walls have eyes and shit, man.
I've been seeing strange dudes
around my place.
I don't even feel like this
fucking cell phone is safe, man.
[Sniffing]
Are you gonna wait for me?
Yeah.
Tiara and Moira are at the hotel
for a couple more hours.
I'm here.
All righty.
You are so freaking cute.
God, all right.
I'll see you in 30 minutes.
¶ A place I never been before ¶
¶ 'Cause all I know
it's hard out there ¶
¶ And y'all know it is ¶
¶ So tell me ¶
¶ Show me a place that we can go ¶
¶ Some place I never been before ¶
¶ 'Cause all I know
it's hard out there ¶
¶ And y'all know it is ¶
You want to smoke some crack?
¶ Left behind where the sun
it just shines ¶
¶ And we find our own spot
in the shade ¶
[crashing]
[Muffled screams]
[Running footsteps]
Police.
Open the door.
Police;
open the door.
Step out, hands up.
Step out, step out.
Come on out, out.
Out.
Up against the wall.
Go over there.
Against the wall, against the wall.
Put your hands on the wheel!
Put your hands up!
Up, up!
Now!
[Water running]
[Sighs]
[Phone ringing]
Hello?
What?
Hold on, hold on.
Slow down.
I'll be there in 20 minutes.
[Phone beeps]
Hey.
So who the hell was this guy?
Some white-collar computer nerd.
He's used us three times.
He always asks for Sienna.
This time, well,
I guess he flipped his lid
and fucking killed her.
So what's going on with Chris?
Hey, asshole.
Did you hear what he just said?
Some fucking shitbag killed her.
Sienna is dead.
Thank you for that, Darick.
I already heard that part.
What is it that you want me
to do about that?
You want me to cry about that?
Is that what you need?
You need me to tear up a little bit?
Is that what's going on?
You're losing it, man.
What the fuck is going on with Chris?
You're slipping.
Um, he said they booked him
for possession and intent to distribute.
They found Sienna's gig bag
in the back of his car
with all her clothes and shit
and started thinking about charging him
with pimping and pandering as well.
They're holding him without bail, Brian.
You want to fix this shit,
or should I?
I'll fix it, like I fucking fix
everything, dude.
Okay.
My stepbrother, huh?
That's a good one.
Yeah, well, you know,
I wasn't sure who all could
come see you, so...
Thanks.
Yeah.
So...
what exactly do they know?
About what, you guys?
Uh-huh.
Nothing.
So you didn't tell them anything?
Not yet.
Whoa, what do you mean, "not yet"?
Listen, man.
I'm in serious,
serious trouble here, Brian.
They got me on possession
of a controlled substance
and possession of cocaine
with intent to distribute,
and they're trying to stick me
with pimping and pandering too.
They know
what I was doing there, man.
I'm lucky if I escape by with just that.
Even then I'm looking at
mandatory jail time.
And I'm telling you straight out,
I can't go to prison.
I can't even stand it here.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, baby boy.
Nobody said anything about you
going to prison, okay?
You got me.
What?
Brian, there's nothing you can do or say
to get me out of this.
I'm in fucking jail, man,
on two felonies.
And I'll probably be charged with
two more before the day is over.
I know.
I'm just saying,
you telling them about us ain't gonna
help out your situation any.
That's all I'm saying.
I mean, just know that.
I'm not planning
on telling them about you guys.
I know you wouldn't.
What they want to know is
where I got the cocaine from.
The attorney they gave me
is trying to work a deal
with the deputy DA
to drop the charges
if I tell them who and where
I got the coke from.
Okay, Chris.
Listen to me, all right?
Do not let them sucker you in
to that bullshit.
Seriously, man.
Don't.
If you tell them about Nate,
it'll fuck everything up.
Everything is already fucked up, Brian.
Look at me.
Look at where I am.
Hey.
Thank you.
Chris, sit down.
Sit down now.
Look, it's Sienna, man.
Don't worry about that right now.
Now, listen to me.
Listen to what I am saying to you.
Guys like you don't go to prison
for things like this, Chris.
It doesn't happen.
This being your first offense,
you know, overcrowding, baby boy,
they're gonna let you go.
They're gonna give parole,
send you home,
maybe some community service
or something, okay?
Oh, yeah?
Yeah.
Well, what if they don't?
What if they don't send me home?
What if they send me to the state pen
with a bunch of gang banging butt pirates?
What if that happens, Brian, huh?
I am telling you that they won't.
They're trying to scare you, Chris.
That's how these
fucking people operate.
Don't let them.
I'm sorry if it's gonna
fuck up your business,
but right now,
Nate is my only ace in the hole.
And what then, huh?
Huh?
What do you think's gonna happen then?
You think that shit's
not gonna come back on all of us?
You think Nate's gonna be
a hospitable fucking guy
after you fucking backstab him?
He won't know who told on him.
The cops will just act like
it's a routine drug bust
or something.
Christopher.
Come on, man.
You think Nate's stupid?
Only a matter of time, baby boy,
until he finds out
you got picked up.
And then... -
then we're all gonna be fucked.
All of us, Chris.
I would rather take my chances
with Nate than go to prison.
I don't know what else to tell you.
I'm sorry.
Time's up, Collins.
Chris, listen to me.
I don't think you understand
how dangerous this situation is, okay?
You got to give me time to figure it out.
Chris, don't say anything to anybody.
Chris.
Fuck.
Yeah, have them meet
at the girls' place.
Tonight.
Yeah.
Hey, Kevin, um...
I'll see you tonight, all right?
All right.
There he is.
Hey.
Hey, did you see Chris?
We good?
Yeah.
And what's the deal?
He's gonna be out like
tomorrow or the next day.
Something like that.
What do you mean
he's gonna be out tomorrow?
I got it taken care of.
Ladies, I need you guys go in
the other room.
Go, go, go.
Come on, come on, come on.
Go.
I took care of it.
What do you mean you took care of it?
I mean I took care of it, homey.
Okay, he's gonna be okay.
We're gonna be okay.
Nothing's gonna come back on us.
A little faith, huh?
Kevin, a little faith?
All right, all right.
Now it's back to business, okay.
We got to get things on track.
Brian, I wanted to talk to you
about that.
You know, I've been thinking.
You know, with all the shit
that's gone down lately,
you know, it seems that,
you know,
maybe it's time
we get out of this life, bro.
You know, I know that we planned
all this shit.
You know, but we never really
talked about how
or when we were gonna end this.
Maybe now is the time.
And then what, huh, Darick?
Then what happens?
We end it tonight.
What happens?
Then we go on with our lives.
Go on with our lives?
Just like that?
Yeah.
Yeah?
Why not?
Tell me something, man.
Could you go back,
working that 9:00 to 5:00,
having somebody tell you what to do
after you've been making
20 grand a week for the past year?
I wouldn't need to go back
to a 9:00 to 5:00 gig, man.
I've got money saved.
You got money saved.
Yeah.
Yeah, yeah, I got money saved,
you know, unlike you,
who went out and bought
a fancy apartment and all your toys.
You know, my life hasn't changed
all that much.
How much money
you got saved, Darick?
I got enough.
Don't worry about me.
You got enough for what?
For what?
To not work the next 10, I don't know,
man, maybe 15 years if you milk it.
Then you're gonna be
middle-aged, Darick,
and you gonna be back
at the fucking garage.
No.
No, I'll go back to school
or something.
School.
I can just see that shit now, dude,
drug-dealing pimp
enrolled in Carnegie Mellon.
I'm not a drug-dealing pimp, all right?
You're not a drug-dealing pimp?
No.
You got a kilo of coke stashed
in your garbage disposal at home.
And you're in a house
with three hooker whores.
And you got nothing to do with it?
You got equal share in this bullshit like
the rest of us, Darick.
Yeah, well, that's the whole thing.
Ain't it, Brian?
I don't want to stake my claim in life
as some drug-dealing pimp.
Not anymore.
Oh, and Sienna?
That's our responsibility, Brian.
That's our fault.
What am I supposed to say to my kid
when I'm behind bars?
See, that fucking kid,
that's your problem.
This shit is way out of control.
What a little fucking bitch.
Huh?
I'm done too.
What?
Yeah, I'm done too.
Kev...
I told the girls to go to their room.
I told the girls to go
to their fucking room.
Kevin.
About four months now.
[Sighs]
Couldn't find a bitch some place else?
I mean, really?
I'm in love, man.
[Disbelieving laugh]
[Laughing]
Listen to me.
We got money, huh?
We got more money
than we ever imagined
we'd have as kids.
This is getting bad, man.
Chris just got busted.
People are dying.
We got to get out of this.
You know what I'm saying?
We got to be done with this, get on,
try and find like,
some normal life or something.
This is my life, Kevin.
This is our lives, man.
This...
It's everything that we ever wanted
since childhood, man, since...
since we were kids.
Come on, get up.
Just go.
Go.
What up?
You remember my boy Chris?
Yep.
He got arrested a couple nights ago.
A lot of shit went down, man.
One of the...
one of the fucking hos got killed, dude.
Cops came through, scooped him up.
He had a bunch of fucking coke,
a lot of fucking crack in the car.
Go on, chill.
I think he gonna snitch.
Why didn't you tell me this
from the get-go?
We could have nipped
this shit in the bud.
I didn't know.
I didn't know it was gonna go
like this, dude.
Those are my boys.
Well, it ain't over till it's over.
Don't worry about it.
You got an established clientele.
Bitches are dime a dozen.
And you got me pinch-hitting.
Don't worry about it.
Now we gonna have to make
some drastic moves.
The peeps above would have it
no other way.
You feel me?
Yeah.
Have a seat, G.
Bye, Daddy.
See you tonight, baby.
Come on, Daryl.
Let's go.
How you doing this morning,
young man?
Could be better.
I heard that.
Need to use the john
before I start cleaning it?
No thanks.
Eh, just thought I'd ask.
Fella yesterday waited
till I cleaned the whole thing
and sprayed diarrhea
all over the bowl.
You don't seem the kind of fella
to do something like that though.
I can't do this.
This your first time in jail?
Yep.
Hopefully my last.
You said a mouthful there.
Don't wind up like me now,
old and decrepit,
always being told what to do.
That ain't no way for a man to live,
especially a young fella like yourself.
This ain't me.
Just go home.
Go the fuck home, man.
Go home.
This is crazy.
How long you been incarcerated?
Eh, shoot.
I've been in and out
of correctional institutions
for most of my adult life,
for a good portion of my adolescence.
You have a wife and kids?
No, sir, can't say I do,
at least none that I know about.
[Laughter]
Maybe in the next life, huh?
Hey, what was your name?
Chris.
Pleased to meet you, Chris.
I'm Rudy.
All clear.
Your regular programming
with this late-breaking news.
Police need your help
identifying possible suspects
in connection with a citywide
prostitution and drug trafficking ring.
The suspects appear to be based
out of the Brighton neighborhood
on the North Side of Pittsburgh.
If you have any knowledge
of an individual...
[snorting]
Fuck.
Help in this case,
please contact North Side detectives
And as always, any information
will remain confidential.
Come on, babe.
Let's go.
[Engine revving]
What's he doing?
He's got a gun!
[Gunshots]
It was Nate's idea to replace
Kevin and Darick
with a couple of dudes
he did time with upstate.
My end of the deal
was to take out Kevin,
for one, prove to Nate
I was down for the long run;
for two,
set up this insurance policy
so there wouldn't be anymore
of this tattletale bullshit.
[Gunshot]
If all went well,
I would have shit on Nate,
and he would have
shit on me.
Condemning one another
would seal our own fate.
When I told Nate about Chris,
he assured me
he had the situation handled.
Had I known he was gonna use
a geriatric janitor for the job,
I never would have agreed.
He stabbed him everywhere
but the head, heart, and lungs.
I'm no doctor,
but everybody knows
those are the kill zones,
not the stomach.
Why... why are you bleeding?
Why are you bleeding?
We got to go to the hospital.
No, no, no, no.
We have to get on the plane.
- No, I'm not getting on the plane.
- We're going to the hospital.
No, you have to get on the plane.
You can't go to the hospital.
They know what you look like.
I'm gonna send somebody
to the hospital to get you, okay?
Okay.
You'll come meet me in a couple days.
You sure it's all right?
Mm-hmm.
Are you sure you're all right?
Yeah, yeah.
I'm fine.
[Snorting]
I love you.
[Phone ringing]
Yeah?
What's up?
Are you with Kevin and Darick?
No, why?
Chris' parents just called, and, look,
someone tried to kill Chris, man.
And he thinks that you set him up.
Man, he signed an affidavit
all about your business.
[Sighs]
Had a good run, huh?
Hey, man, you...
you remember when...
when my father was still alive,
and he used to put on those
puppet shows
in the front yard?
You and me, we would...
we would...
we would play Fatty and Skinny.
And you used to make
my mother laugh so hard.
You remember that?
Listen, you...
you got to do me a favor, Eddie, okay?
If anything happens to me, man,
you got to...
you got to promise
to take care of her, okay?
Eddie?
Promise me, man.
Sure.
[Doorbell rings]
North Side police have just reported
that the suburban shooting
in the Shaler area this afternoon
seems to be connected
to the ongoing investigation
of a North Side mafia group.
The gang is involved with prostitution
and drug distribution,
including such street-level
substances as heroin
and crack cocaine.
The leaders of this organization
are believed to be working
out of the Brighton section
of the North Side.
They are deemed armed and dangerous.
Do not attempt to approach
these individuals.
Police are asking that any information
that may help in the apprehension
and conviction be forwarded to them.
Help keep our neighborhoods safe.
[Electronic beeping]
[Toilet flushes]
Come on, come on.
Come on, come on!
Sir, the water's off.
[Helicopter blades thudding]
Freeze!
Put your hands behind your head.
Don't move.
[Sirens wailing]
[Gunshots]
Let's get that bird out of here.
Get your men up on that roof.
[Sirens wailing in distance]
[Gunshots]
[Chamber clicking]
Ward, take the back.
Go, go!
[Sirens approaching]
[Woman talking over radio]
[Phone rings]
Hello?
Mama.
Hey, hey.
Uh...
I, uh...
listen.
I was wondering if maybe
that you could forgive me for this?
You know what I mean?
You know, Mama, it's okay.
It's okay.
[Static]
Secure the perimeter.
Make sure this place is taped off.
I see him.
He's on the patio.
Suspect is on the patio.
Hold your fire.
Let's take this son of a bitch alive.
You, drop the gun!
Drop the gun!
Drop the gun now.
- Put the gun down!
- Do it now.
Put it down.
We will shoot you!
Put the weapons down.
[Men shouting]
Put the gun down and get down.
On the ground now.
Do it now.
Hands on your head now.
Drop the gun!
Hands on your head!
We will shoot you.
Put the weapons down.
Get on the ground!
Get down on the ground.
Put your gun down and get down.
- Now!
- Do it now!
Get down on the ground.
Hold your fire.
Hands on your head now.
Hands on the back of your head now.
Put your hands behind your head.
- Do it now.
- Let's go.
Do it now.
- Now!
- Do it now!
[Gunshot]
Who fired?
Cease fire.
They is they, motherfucker.
Let's get the wagon in here.
[Siren wailing]
The day we buried Brian and Darick,
Kevin called to give his condolences.
He and Jasper had made it
safely out of the country,
but he didn't say where.
He couldn't say where.
Brian and the organization
made a combined fortune
of $7.3 million in the course of a year.
And it was all gone.
They wanted to leave
their mark on the world,
leave something for others
to remember them by.
Hey, it's Pittsburgh, the city of bridges,
a town where your neighborhood
defines your destiny.
These guys were my best friends.
But they took a road
that I wasn't willing to follow.
And though they were flying high
for a while, in the end,
what they didn't realize
is that they were flying off
the bridge to nowhere.
[Stirring orchestral music]
¶ ¶