...to find the best ideas to
celebrate this very special day?
Me! Me!
Well, yesterday the staff
selected the winning idea
and it came from this class.
The winner is our own...
Lucinda Embry.
Come on, everyone.
We'll be closing our
dedication ceremony
with the burial
of the time capsule.
What's the time capsule?
This is a time capsule.
Now I need you to put your
thinking caps on because I want
each of you to draw what you think
the future is going to look like.
Then we'll put the pictures in the
capsule, and 50 years from today,
a group of children,
just like yourselves,
will open it up to see
what you drew.
Doesn't that sound exciting?
-Yes, miss Taylor.
Lets begin.
That is a lovely spaceship there.
Time's up.
Everyone hand your work in.
And make sure you write
your name on the envelope.
Lucinda, you need
to finish up now.
Oh, Lucinda.
The assignment was
to draw a picture.
This was your idea.
Okay, I want you all
to finish, please...
Welcome to all our friends
and esteemed colleagues.
We, the students and faculty
of William Dawes elementary,
hereby bury this time capsule
in dedication of our new school.
And we charge our descendants
to open this vault of history
50 years from today.
To the future and
the promise that it holds.
Lucinda!
I'm certain that Lucinda is
simply playing somewhere...
Please, help find her.
The cloakroom.
Check the cloakroom.
Lucinda?
Lucinda!
Oh my God!
Make them stop.
Please, make them stop.
Caleb! Take a look at this.
There you go.
What is it? -Saturn's rings
await for your approval.
Has anyone found life on
other planets? -Not yet.
This is just us for now.
Okay, then how manys that
might have life? -Well...
If you count the number of stars
similar to our sun in this galaxy,
then you factor in the probability
that they have Earth-like planets
orbiting them... -There are
10 million possible worlds
with 4 million mature enough
for life to evolve.
Why do you even ask? -Just
making sure if you're listening.
Where are you going?
-To watch that Discovery program.
But it's dad's famous sunday night
hot dogs on the run... time!
I can't consume that.
I've decided to become a vegetarian.
When were you planning on telling
the guy who buys the groceries?
Are you deaf?
I just told you now, dad.
Off. -No, it's almost over.
You're not gonna be able to
concentrate in class tomorrow.
We don't have a class tomorrow.
It's the 50th anniversary, remember?
I remember.
Caleb...
When I said it was
just us out there...
you know I was talking
about Space, right?
I didn't mean Heaven or anything.
I'm sure wherever mom is...
Dad... we don't even
believe in heaven.
I never said that, Caleb.
I just said we can't know
for sure. That's all.
If you wanna believe,
you go ahead and believe. OK?
Okay. Bed time.
Hey... you and me, together.
Forever.
I love you.
-I love you too.
I'm gonna pose a topic
to get you thinking
along the right lines
for your term paper.
It has a subject of randomness
vs determinism in the universe.
Who is jumping in? Jessica.
Determinism says that occurences
in nature are causally-decided
by preceding events
or natural laws.
That everything leading up to this
point has happened for a reason.
That's right.
That's what determinism says.
Spencer! Tell me something
about the sun.
-It's hot.
-Elaborate.
Temperature is about
10.000 degrees F on the surface.
27 million degrees at the core.
-Good.
Stacey!
A word or two
about the composition.
Mostly hydrogen, also helium.
With some carbon and nitrogen
turning there. -Excellent.
Now, I want you to think about
the perfect set of circumstances
that put this celestial
ball of fire at just...
the correct distance
from our little blue planet
for life to evolve.
Making it possible for you to be
sitting here in this riveting lecture.
That's a nice thought, right?
Everything has a purpose.
An order to it.
Is determined.
But then, there's the other
side of the argument.
The theory of randomness.
Which says it's all
simply a coincidence.
The very fact we exist is nothing
but the result of a complex,
yet inevitable string
of chemical accidents
and biological mutations.
There is no grand meaning.
There's no purpose.
What about you,
professor Koestler?
-What?
-What do you believe?
I think shit just happens.
But that's me.
Class dismissed.
That's some very heavy shit for
early morning by the sounds of it.
Since when does the cosmology
department honor my lectures?
Since my esteemed colleague
in astrophysics owes me a latte.
Er... what's on your
scientific mind today?
Do you remember Kim's little sister?
Ph double Ds... remember her?
Is it ethical to say things like
that about your sister in law?
It's factual. It's peer reviewed.
It's like... anyway, whatever.
She's in town this friday.
-Okay.
And she thinks that you're intriguing
which I thought was code for "gay"
but apparently not cause she's asked
if you would join us for dinner.
-I... I don't know.
-Oh, come on, John.
Come on! You owe me for last
time you skipped out on me.
-Caleb was panicking...
-Yeah, look, I know.
And the time before that he had
a sore throat. -Oh, no!
Damn it! Damn it! -What?
-Caleb's ceremony. I'm sorry, Phil.
Hey! Hey! Friday!
-I'll think about it.
50 years ago the students and
faculty of William Dawes elementary
imagined what the
future might hold.
Today we unveil their legacy.
Now I'd like to introduce you
to someone very special.
Miss Priscilla Taylor.
Since miss Taylor was there
for the original dedication,
it's only fitting that we
have her do the honors today.
You almost forgot again.
-Made it in time to hear you sing.
You were the best one up there.
-You could not hear it.
I could. I swear.
Gotta go. It's starting!
Easy, don't push it. -Everyone is
going to receive an envelope.
Open them gently now.
It's really old.
Lucinda Embry
Hey, what did you get?
Boring! Everyone else
got a picture.
Caleb, could you please
watch where you put this?
I don't want you
to lose another one.
-It's making funny noises.
-Try turning the volume down.
Hey dad, remember that kid
Jason from soccer practice?
He's having a sleepover
this weekend.
And he was wondering if
I can come. -Sounds like fun.
They have a boat.
Jason's dad said he even might
take us out on the lake.
-I'll think about it.
-That means no.
It means I'll think about it.
What are you doing with this?
You're not supposed to bring this
home. It belongs to the school.
But maybe it means something.
Like a map or sorta
something like that.
Yeah, that's good, I don't know,
but it's not ours to keep.
You'll return this as soon as you
get to school tomorrow. Got it?
Now lets go. Bed time.
Good night, baby.
Good night, mom.
Nine eleven 01?
In memory of the 2996 lives
that were lost that day.
- 2996.
C'mon!
What the hell is this?
Dad!
Dad, we're gonna be late!
Thanks for the ride, mr Koestler!
Dad, are you sick?
-I am fine.
Don't you think you're acting
kinda awkward today?
Am I awkward? I just had
a lot of work to do last night.
Okay. Bye, dad!
Bye.
Look at this. Look at the
numbers beside the dates.
2996. That's how many people
died in the attacks that day.
Stay with me. I know how
this sounds, but I've matched
these numbers to the dates
of every major global disaster
for the last 50 years
in perfect sequence.
Except for 3, and these events haven't
occured yet, starting with this one.
So, tomorrow,
somewhere on the planet,
this number string predicts
that 81 people are gonna die...
in some kind of tragedy.
Whoa. Have you listened
to yourself? -I know.
It sounds pretty crazy. -I know.
-I mean... even for you.
What's this?
-Open it.
Why are you showing me this?
The day Allison died in the fire.
It's on the list too.
On the piece of paper that's been
buried in the ground for 5 decades.
Can you explain that, Phil?
I was up all night going over this.
I went through that list
again and again and I tried
to fault it. And I couldn't.
-Maybe someone's playing a
really shitty joke. -Right! Right!
Except I saw them dig it up!
I watched them pull the capsule
out of the ground and hand
that sealed envelope to my kid.
-OK. Let me ask you this then.
All these uncircled numbers?
What do they mean?
I don't know yet. Maybe nothing...
-Maybe they all mean nothing.
Phil, hey, can we just start over?
I'm not saying that 81 people
are gonna die tomorrow, okay?
I'm just trying to understand
why this is saying they will!
Okay! It's spooky. I'll grant you,
it's more than spooky.
But just step back, alright?
You have all these uncircled
numbers with no sequence to them.
Numerology, Kabbalah,
Pythagorean cults...
There are systems that
find meaning in numbers.
But they are a dime a dozen. Why?
Because people see
what they want to see in them.
That's really what
you think I'm doing?
Yeah, I think that losing Allison
has spun you off your axis a little.
And I think it has clouded
your judgement.
I'm just saying it has clouded
your judgement. Don't you think?
Where are you going?
-Off campus.
Yes?
You do remember her?
-Oh yes. I remember Lucinda.
She was such a sad little girl.
Would you like some iced tea?
-Oh, no, no, thank you.
Do you remember the day your
students buried the time capsule?
Oh yes! The children
were so excited.
And what about Lucinda?
Later that day
we couldn't find her.
She was hiding in the closet
under the gym.
Scratching at the door with her
fingernails like some kind of animal.
Scratching at the door?
Why was she hiding?
-I'm not sure.
She was holding up the class.
Writing all those silly numbers.
I had to hurry her along.
Then we found her.
And I knew something had
frightened the poor dear.
But we never could get her
to tell us what it was.
Miss Taylor, my son got
Lucinda's time capsule message.
Do you remember this?
Is this what she wrote?
Oh, professor, you are testing
an old woman's memory.
Can you believe it's been 50 years?
-It's a long time.
I believe that's it.
Oh, how rude of me.
I never offered you a drink.
Would you like some iced tea?
-No, thank you. I'm fine.
I thought maybe I could meet her.
I'm sorry. Lucinda passed away
several years ago.
I said I'm Caleb Koestler's father.
I'm calling to find out the names
of the two janitors that pulled
the time capsule out of the ground
yesterday at the ceremony.
I'm not sure I understand why
that would be a problem for you.
Caleb!
Who was that?
-I don't know. Just some guys.
-What did they give you?
-Just this. Kinda cool, isn't it?
What did I say about
talking to strangers?
Have you done your homework?
-I need 10 more minutes of practice.
I don't want to have to
ask you twice, Caleb.
Hey, stranger! -At what age
do we learn to knock?
I said I was gonna drop by. On my
way to graveyard shift, remember?
Didn't you get my message?
-I've been busy.
Do not play with my things.
-You're always busy.
Yes! Yes.
How's my nephew?
-He's become a vegetarian.
-A what?  -Why? You got
a problem with that?
You're not feeding him dad's famous
sunday night hot dogs again, are you?
You know, if you want someone
to take him off your hands
for the evening so you can go out,
you know, like normal people do...
I appreciate the offer,
but we're fine.
And believe it or not, Caleb and I
have got a good thing going there.
So, you can report that
back to headquarters.
Mom says hi.
So does dad.
Grace! Don't.
I get that you don't like
being the son of a pastor.
-I am the son of a pastor.
-That's fine. You're still his son.
Can't you let it go?
-Can't he?
He asks after you every time
I see you. He worries about you.
-He said that?
-He doesn't have to. -Right.
You're gonna have to speak
to him one day, you know.
This can't go on forever.
You know it's what Allison wanted.
For Caleb to have a grandfather.
And vice versa.
Okay. I'm going.
I'm going.
By the way, Grace, how are you?
How's your life?
What's going on for you?
Thank you, John, for asking.
I have to get up
early in the morning.
What do you have going on?
I'll say a prayer. -Please...
...don't. -Okay.
Experts say solar flairs
this weekend may interrupt
cell phone communications.
-Experts...
The price of oil may
hit another record.
Another fire burns
out of control in the Gulf.
Eighty one.
An explosion on a soon to be
decommissioned oil rig
triggered a fire which burned for
3 hours before it was extiguished.
Officials don't yet know the
exact cause of the explosion,
but believe a malfunction in the
cooling system may've been at fault.
Due to the prompt response
of the rescue unit,
the structure was evacuated
with no loss of life.
Farmers across the Midwest...
...and here's Karl Witherman.
Looks like a scorch is on the wind.
That's right, Bob.
The forecast shows more high
pressure moving in later this week.
It seems our indian summer is
set to last a little while longer...
Hallo. -Dad, where are you?
You're on the car pool
this afternoon.
Caleb, I'm so sorry.
I'll pick you up in ten
minutes, okay? -Okay. Bye.
William Dawes elementary school.
Alternate routes:
no alternate routes available.
This is Phil and Kim. We can't
get to the phone right now.
Please leave the message.
-Hey, Phil, it's John.
I am sorry about yesterday.
I kind of freaked out on you,
didn't I?
Look, I'm not ready to meet anyone
in any kind of special way.
But I would like to take you up
on your offer for dinner.
I think it would be good for me
to just get out of the house and...
The uncircled numbers
are locations.
This location.
What's going on?
Do we get through or what?
Hi! Is everything okay?
I'm sorry sir, but you need
to get back to your car.
-Anybody hurt? -A couple of
injuries, but nothing serious.
Get down!
Hey! Hey!
Help me! Please!
Help me!
-Are you okay, sir?
-Step back, sir. Step away.
...one of the worst days
in recent US aviation history
when four planes crash-landed
across as many states,
from Maine to Miami.
Can you go upstairs
while I talk to your dad?
You didn't tell him anything?
-Of course not.
First estimates put
the presumed dead at 81.
We need to talk.
I just...
I just wanna sleep.
What happened, dad?
What's going on?
My car broke down
on the highway.
It's more than that, isn't it?
I'm going to bed.
Get your homework done.
Then you should go to bed too.
No TV tonight.
Why? I always watch an hour of TV.
-No more questions, Caleb.
I can ask questions when you tell
me things that don't make sense.
You won't let me play soccer,
you won't let me stay over at Jason's
and now you won't tell me
what's going on
and why you're acting
so weird all the time?
I'm not a kid anymore.
Oh my God! John!
You were there?
The date, the number of dead,
the GPS coordinates.
Latitude and longitude.
Why didn't I see that?
It wasn't a coincidence.
I drove past at the exact moment
the prediction came true.
It's not a coincidence.
-OK, John, I didn't say it was.
So, what are we calling this?
Synchronicity?
Two unrelated events, digging up
time capsule, plane crash...
combine to create a significance
with the subject, you?
I keep seeing their faces.
Burning...
Oh, man...
Okay, look. We are way beyond
the boundaries here, John.
We don't have
a frame of reference.
There could be multiple
meanings to consider.
There are two disasters left.
What are you saying?
Numbers are warnings
meant for me.
They might just as easily be
a warning to stay away.
You could've been killed today, John.
Caleb would've been orphan,
and you wanna go put yourself
back in harm's way?
Two disasters left.
Right now my scientific mind
is telling me
to have nothing more
to do with this.
And yours should too.
Caleb! It's all right.
-Dad!
It's okay.
It was just a bad dream.
Just a bad dream.
Hey!
You stay away from us, you hear?!
Want some of this?!
Caleb, why don't you
check out the animals?
I'll catch up with you, okay?
-Okay.
Do you know that all wolves
are born deaf? -Really?
Did you know that
when they get older,
they can hear another wolf's
howl from ten miles away.
-Wow. How do you know that?
-I read it in National Geographic.
Hi. -Hi.
Is that your daughter?
Yeah, why? -Why?
Uh... that's my son.
And they look like they are
already best friends.
Yeah, Abby is probably
telling him about the animals.
Even as a baby she was
completely fascinated with them.
Yeah, he's the same.
He likes extinct animals.
I'm John.
Hi, Diana.
What are they doing now?
Caleb is showing her
something in sign language.
-I'm sorry, I didn't realise...
-He's not.
His sounds just...
get jumbled up sometimes.
He has a hearing aid which
helps, but he's not deaf.
He is an expert
in sign language.
It's very hot in here.
Air conditioning must be out.
Dad, can we get a drink?
-Can we get one too?
Hey, would you and Abby
like to join us?
Sure, that'd be nice.
Abby, this is John.
-Hi. -Hey, Abby.
It can be tough sometimes,
cause, you know, I'm by myself.
-I know how you feel.
-You're a single parent too?
Yeah.
I left him years ago. He couldn't
keep his hands to himself
so I decided he couldn't
keep me to himself either.
Well, it is... it's his loss.
And you? You're separated?
Diana...
We didn't meet here by accident.
I need to talk to you
about something.
Ask you something
about your mother.
My mother?
What about my mother?
Did she have some kind of...
...ability? -Ability?
A gift of some kind?
Who are you? -Yeah, it's
awkward, you don't know me.
I'm John Koestler, I teach
astrophysics at M.I.T.
My son goes to
William Dawes elementary
which is the same school
your mother went to.
50 years ago, she put
this in a time capsule.
It's a list of dates, events...
...that, I think,
she believed would happen.
Look, I don't what
any of this is about.
I thought if I could talk to you or
your father... -My father is dead.
I think it's possible
that there are people
like your mother, Lucinda, who can
see things before they occur.
Abby, we're leaving! Honey!
I followed on your mother's
predictions, and I watched
81 people burn to death
in that plane crash yesterday.
When she said it would happen.
Where she said it would happen.
And there was nothing
I could do about it.
She says 170 people will die
tomorrow in New York City.
And in 3 days time,
october 19th, 33 more.
Stay away from me.
And my daughter.
Abby! Lets go, honey. C'mon.
Stay right there. Diana!
Diana, I think this has
something to do with my son.
I don't know how or why,
but I think he's in danger.
So I'm asking you please,
please help us.
I can't.
... possible terrorist plot. The
department of Homeland Security
raised the national threat
level from elevated to high,
after intelligence report
suggested that an attack
on the major East Coast
city may be imminent.
Police have urged citizens
to stay vigilant.
FBI New York.
How may I direct your call?
The attack will
take place tomorrow
at the corner of Lafayette
and Worth streets.
Corner off the area after midnight.
Are you clear on that?
Sir, let me pass you
through to our...
Please! Do exactly as I say
or many people will die.
This is not a crank call.
You said you'd take him
off my hands.
I know there's something
you're not telling me.
Don't let him watch the news.
Why hasn't this intersection
been sealed off? -Excuse me?
I said why hasn't this
intersection been sealed off?
Sir... please calm down.
If you'll accompany me, we'll
get this matter taken care of.
Sir! Stop!
Out of the way!
Let me through!
Get off the train.
-Why? What is wrong?
Just take the baby and get off.
-What's your problem, pal?
Hold it right there, sir.
Transit police!
I'm asking you to stop!
That's him!
You have to stop him!
Transit police!
Turn around!
Now! Get your hands up!
Please! Please, I won't
do it again, I promise.
I'll give it back!
Move back! Move back!
Federal Aviation Administration
official said that it's possible
that an electrostatic burst
might have caused
the Lexington air disaster
of two days ago.
NOAA, the National Oceanic and
Atmospheric Administration,
remained silent tonight.
But with the devastating
subway crash in Manhattan,
power cuts in Long Island...
Grace, I got held up by work.
I'll be over in 30 minutes.
No, I'm fine.
I'll see you in 30 minutes.
Caleb, go inside.
Hey! -Hey.
Wanna check out the house?
-Sure.
You said october 19th?
My mother used to talk
about that day all the time.
She said that was the day
I was gonna die.
All my life I've had this
thing hanging over my head.
And Abby's.
I just don't believe that
anyone can predict my future.
And what does it matter anyway?
We all die in the end.
I don't wanna know
what my future holds.
Last year my wife was on
a business trip to Phoenix.
Couple of days before
my birthday, and...
a fire started in her hotel
at four in the morning.
The investigator said that
Allison died of smoke inhalation.
Died in her sleep.
She wouldn't have known
anything about it.
While she was dying, I was
at home, in the front yard.
I always thought
you're supposed to sense
when the people you love
are in danger.
I didn't feel anything.
Nothing.
I was just...
blowing leaves off the lawn.
I'm so sorry, John.
My point is that from
then on, I decided...
that no one can know
what was coming.
And life is just a...
string of random
accidents and mistakes.
And then I got that list.
If that had come to me
before Allison left,
I would've saved her life.
I need to know.
It's still here.
What's this?
Have you seen this?
Abby used to do this sometimes.
Write things backwards.
That last number.
I don't think it's 33.
It's EE.
EE... initials.
Someone she knew?
I don't know.
I was nine when she overdosed.
The only time I ever came
in here was with my father.
We identified her body.
She willed the property
to me, but...
I never came back
for any of her things.
When I was little,
my mother used to tell me
that she could hear voices.
Whispering to her.
Telling her horrible things.
Then one day my dad came
and took me away from her.
He said she was sick.
She said she moved
out here to get ready.
I never knew what
she meant by that.
I've made this for her
one Christmas.
I never knew she kept it.
She used to stare
at this picture for hours.
That's where they found her.
In there.
Have you seen enough?
Yeah. Okay, we'll go.
Abby? Abby!
EE isn't just one person.
everyone else
Abby, no!
What? What?!
It's okay! It's okay.
They were here.
Who? Who was here, Caleb?
Did they hurt you?
No. They were talking to us.
-What did they say?
I don't know.
They were all talking at once.
They said we can go with them.
If we chose to.
Who did? Abby, who?
The whisper people.
Hey! Lock the doors.
What do you want with my son?
Answer me!
I just know they've been
following us for days.
I think someone's been
following me and Abby too.
That's why she didn't write
any coordinates down
after the final date. There isn't
a single location this time.
Are you telling me that my mother
could see the end of everything?
That we're all gonna
die tomorrow?
She was disturbed, John.
She could've just...
...made it all up.
-She's been right so far, Diana.
About everything.
Abby is all I've got, John.
I can't let anything
happen to her.
Caleb, you really need to sleep.
I can hear them whispering
to me sometimes like Abby can.
Could Lucinda hear them too?
Yeah I think she did, yes.
Are me and Abby gonna die?
No. I will never let
that happen, Caleb.
Do you hear me? Never.
You and me... together.
Forever.
Abby, what do you like
to eat for breakfast?
Abby?
What are you doing, honey?
It's the sun.
There's something I need to check.
Get Abby, you're coming with us.
Caleb!
Hey, John, what happened?
Hey!
Talk to me! What happened?
I've been calling you
off the hook ever since
I've heard about the subway.
John...
Do you remember that paper on
extrasolar activity I published?
-Yeah, sure I remember.
-I found evidence of the series
of superflairs from the
star in the Pleiades.
Right. Readings were off the chart.
We were both wrong.
The numbers are a warning,
but not just to me or
any random group.
They are a warning to everyone.
Okay, you're officially scaring
the shit out of me right now.
The superflair.
In our own Solar System.
100 microtesla wave of radiation
that will destroy our ozone layer.
Killing every living organism
on the planet.
We have to let everyone know.
We have to call the NOAA...
They already know. The announcement
will come any time now.
I thought there was some
purpose to all of this.
Why did I get this prediction when
there's nothing I can do about it?
How am I supposed to stop
the end of the world?
Go home, Phil.
Be with Kim tonight.
Diana...
It's so stupid.
I spent my whole life
knowing that she was right,
and pretending that
she was insane.
If we hide underground
we got a chance, don't we?
It's possible.
I know some caves.
Off route 40, past Groton.
Hardly anyone knows about them.
I used to play there as a child.
We could try there, right?
Okay. -Okay.
Caleb, put some clothes and
shoes into your backpack.
Diana, load all the non-perishable
food, any water you can
into the truck. Lets try to be
outta here in 10 minutes.
Allison wanted me to call you.
The day she left for Phoenix
she wanted me to promise her
that I'll call you.
I know, John.
We haven't spoken in so long.
I don't really even
know why anymore.
I need to tell you something.
Yes?
That sermon you preached
every year at Pentecost,
about the gifts of the spirit?
One was the gift of prophecy.
1 Corinthians 12.
Yes, I remember.
The Church should
respect the prophets.
I have a prophecy.
It's about to be
proven accurate.
I need you to respect it
and receive it as the truth.
This heat we're experiencing
isn't gonna get better.
It's gonna get worse.
Much worse.
I need you to get mom and Grace,
and any supplies you can,
and get below ground tonight.
The basement, the sewer,
just get as deep as you can
and as fast as you can.
And that will keep us
safe from this heat?
I don't know, dad.
But we have to try, right?
I'm sorry, John, but I'm afraid
I'm not going anywhere
tonight or any night.
I appreciate your concern,
but if it is my time,
it's my time.
I'm ready whenever
the good Lord calls me.
And you... -Dad?
John? -Dad!
Caleb, lets go!
Caleb?
Caleb!
Caleb, stop!
What were you doing?
Did I do that?
This isn't the way
to the highway.
Everybody wait here.
John!
John! Please!
Why are we back here?
John, please. What are you doing?
We have to get to the caves.
We're not going to the caves.
-What? -She knew the
coordinates for this last event.
She tried to write them down.
Teacher said she was
interrupted. Ran out of time.
So she scratched them
into this door.
She tried to tell us
where to go.
You're not making any sense. Look
at you. Look at what you're doing.
The numbers are the key.
To everything.
Please! Please, John,
we need to leave!
We're taking my car. C'mon.
Lets go. Take your things with you.
They are here.
They better be here.
Throw them in the back.
What about dad? -He is just
gonna finish what he's doing.
He's gonna follow us. We're
getting a head start, okay?
Diana!
Caleb!
Where are we going, mom?
Are we hiding from the
whisper people? -Yes, my baby.
They won't find us
where we're going.
Mom, they know where we are.
How do you know that?
-They told us so.
You've seen them again?
No. They just talk to us.
How, Abby?
How do they talk to you?
They whisper into our heads.
Oh, God...
I wanna call my dad.
-The phones are down!
I promise he's right behind us.
We'll call him when we get there!
Stay right here.
Number 5.
This is an emergency
broadcast transmission.
This is not a test.
This is an emergency
broadcast transmission.
Turn that up!
...lasted longer and
caused more damage
to our infrastructure
than we originally thought.
We're recommending that people
stay indoors until further notice.
Get your pets inside,
stock up on extra water,
and if possible seek out
4-5 feet underground shelter.
Where is the President?
-The President and his staff
are currently to be transported
to a secure location.
Hello? -Dad!
Caleb! Are you okay?
Tell me exactly where you are.
We are at the gas station.
I don't know where.
The damage information regarding
the distructing power of flairs...
Caleb, get back to the car, now!
John? -Where are you?
-We're in Westford.
I'm sorry, I had to do this
for Abby and for Caleb.
I'm taking them to the caves.
I've found the numbers!
They are the location
of your mother's mobile home.
That's where we gotta go!
-Don't do this to me. Please.
-I know how it sounds.
You want us to head
towards the place
where this is supposed to happen?
Are you insane?
It's the kids we gotta take,
or we're all gonna die!
Stay where you are.
I'll be right there.
No! If we go to the caves,
we have a chance.
You said the sun
can't reach that far.
The caves won't save us!
Nothing can! The radiation
will penetrate a mile into the
Earth's crust! Do you hear me?
Our only chance is to go
where your mother told us to go!
No! I don't believe you!
I'm taking the children.
We have to save the children!
That isn't your call, Diana.
Caleb is my son!
Diana! Caleb!
Are you there?
Abby!
They took my daughter!
Damn it!
Where did she go?
Same thing happened with Y2K.
They are gonna wake up tomorrow
morning, feeling pretty stupid.
20 minutes ago there was
a woman here, she was screaming!
She was with a kid. He was on your
payphone. A nine year old kid!
Some guy took the lady's car with
the kids inside. Drove right off.
-The woman, where did she go?
-That way.
Stop that!
You gotta pay for it!
Where are the children?
-We can't help you now, sir.
Charge.
Clear.
Again. Clear.
-You can call it.
-12 midnight, exactly.
There's a man down.
We need help.
Diana...
I'm sorry.
Caleb!
Where is he?
Where is Caleb?
I want my son!
Now!
Dad, dont!
Are you hurt?
What did they do to you?
It's okay, dad.
I'm okay.
This is my friend.
They said that I can keep him.
Caleb, I want you to come with me.
We're going now.
But we have to go with them.
They won't hurt us.
Abby, are you okay?
Your mom wanted to
be here, honey. -I know.
The whisper people told me
that mommy is safe now.
They've been protecting us
all along, dad.
They sent a message ahead
of them. To prepare the way.
And now they've come for us.
Who are you?
It's time to go, dad. They've
chosen us so we can start over.
So everything can start over.
What do you mean?
I don't understand!
Why is he saying that, dad?
What?
What is he saying, Caleb?
He's saying...
only the children must go.
Those who heard the call.
Please...
I can't go with you, Caleb.
I can't go with you.
But they've chosen us to go.
They haven't chosen us, Caleb.
They've chosen you.
Both of you.
Caleb, you have to
take care of Abby now.
You have to be strong for her.
No. I don't wanna go
without you.
They could've taken you
away from me, but they didn't.
You have to make
this decision yourself.
But you promised.
You said that we'll be
together forever.
We will be.
I'm not leaving you.
But you gotta go with them.
You gotta go.
You gotta go with them.
Listen to me, Caleb.
Stop, stop... listen to me.
We're gonna be together.
We're all gonna be together.
And mom is gonna be
with us too. I know it.
I know that, Caleb.
I know it.
Look... here, take this.
Take this with you.
One day you'll know
what it means.
I love you, daddy.
Where's Caleb?
Caleb's safe.
We're going to stay on air
for as long as possible.
All we can say is what we've
been repeating all morning.
Get to any kind of
underground shelter.
This isn't the end, son.
I know.
Transcript AP