Twenty questions. Go.
You're a man. Are you in politics?
Warm beer. Tastes like piss.
It's your turn, babe.
Dead or alive?
Don't you think that's
a really stupid question these days?
You know, he's kind of an asshole,
but if you need me
to take care of him, I will.
I can hear you.
He's the one in the family
with all the brains.
Is that right?
All right, the interstate's coming up.
What do we do?
Don't get on it. Stay on this back road.
How come every time you say that,
we end up in a three-hour scenic tour
in the middle of nowhere?
Look, we agreed on the rules, didn't we?
And by taking it, we're breaking what?
The rule that says
we shouldn't take the interstate.
"I guess we wouldn't want
to break any rules," he said,
drinking his beer
as he drove the stolen Mercedes
ridiculously over the speed limit,
and, look, no hands!
- Babe, don't!
- Stop!
- Stop it, you moron!
- Don't!
- All right, smartass, I'll read the map.
- Can you? It has actual writing on it.
Very funny.
Hey, hey, hey, hey!
Hey, guys.
All right, windows, everybody.
What the hell is this guy doing?
My daughter and I, we ran out of gas.
All right, sir,
please move your car out of the road.
We left Denver yesterday morning.
Last gas we got was Colorado Springs.
I'm sorry, we can't help you.
Now move your car!
Look, all we need
is just a little bit of gas.
Yeah, I'm sure you do.
You and everybody else.
Stay where you are!
We can trade you for it.
We got food and water.
- Brian, we have more than enough.
- More than... How do you know that?
- I said do not get any closer!
- Brian, he looks clean.
Or he could be incubating.
Think about it for a second...
Guys! She's got it.
Shit!
Come on, come on, come on...
They'll die out there.
Everyone dies.
The rules are simple.
At least, that's how my brother sees it.
One, avoid the infected at all costs.
Their breath is highly contagious.
Two, disinfect anything they've touched
in the last 24 hours.
Three, the sick are already dead.
They can't be saved.
You break the rules, you die.
You follow them, you live.
Maybe.
Hey. Look what I found.
Great.
Hey, if you happen to find a brand-new
factory-issued oil pan, holler.
- Are you sure you can't fix it?
- It's blown, lvy Boy.
- Brian.
- What?
All that car needed was gas.
Wait, what? No. No, no, no way.
- Lf we sit here, we're just gonna die.
- We won't if we go back?
You saw the girl.
You saw the blood, the rashes.
Bobby, come on, you saw her.
- Am I the only one here?
- Kate, we do not have a lot of options...
They're your rules!
Danny, tell your girlfriend
to get her shit together.
- I'm not his girlfriend.
- She's not my girlfriend.
All right, then tell me, tell me.
Why the hell is she here?
Why didn't we let her sit tight
in her McMansion,
- waiting for the looters?
- Okay.
Could we just calm down and try
and think this thing through? Please.
- Yeah.
- So what about the car?
I don't know, Danny. I'm trying to think.
- Well, we need that car...
- I know that!
Shit!
All right, put your masks on, guys.
Frank Holloway.
We're gonna need your car.
Yeah, I figured as much.
Do you really want to splatter
your brand-new vehicle
with the insides of someone who,
for all you know, may be infected?
We got loads of Clorox.
- Cleanup is not my chief concern.
- Brian, that's all right.
- That's close enough.
- I picked up a radio transmission
from a school outside of Farmington
last week.
People from all over the state
are traveling there.
For what?
The CDC, they set up some kind
of emergency response center.
They've got a new serum.
That's one hell of a story, man.
I don't think I've heard that one yet.
Are they getting results?
No, they're not getting any results, Kate.
They've got a new treatment, and I am
taking my daughter there in this car.
Now, if you're onboard with that, great.
If not...
This is a fairytale, and he knows it.
It's the Baltimore vaccine all over again.
It's a bunch of retrovirals
that don't work for shit.
So go ahead, Brian.
Shoot him in the head.
Wait! Hey.
I got an idea.
Hey.
Want to know a secret? About boys?
Their bark is worse than their bite.
- You know what I mean?
- No.
- It's okay.
- Don't listen to her, kiddo.
- Trust me, she loves it when I bite.
- Why don't you eat me, Brian?
- I think we can arrange that.
- Jesus, Brian! She's, like, eight.
Yeah, well, mentally, so is he.
Adiós, Road Warrior.
You crap piece of shit.
But Godless governments have fallen,
and the armies of man
have perished by his hand...
Pattycake, pattycake...
... for this pandemic is the flail of God
and the world his threshing floor,
and, implacably,
he will thresh out his harvest
until the wheat is separated from
the chaff, the righteous from the sinner.
And make no mistake about it,
there shall be far more chaff than wheat.
Few chosen...
Come to think of it,
I haven't seen much weed around lately.
- Very funny.
- What?
Just show some respect.
For what?
That God's punishing my daughter?
Who's he rewarding? Who, you?
- That's not what I'm saying.
- What are you saying?
Some people locked themselves away,
piled up food,
didn't even pick up the phone.
They were dead in a week.
Me, I worked at the stadium,
digging those mass graves for 400...
- 400 bucks a day!
- That's exactly right.
You can laugh all you want,
but I was up to my knees in that shit,
and here I am.
So you're immune or chosen
or something?
I'm here and they're not.
So, then, I guess you won't mind
kissing my daughter good night for me,
huh, Brian?
I didn't think so.
So much for being chosen, huh?
That's hysterical, huh, lvy League?
Where'd you go to school, Danny?
- He got a scholarship to go to Harvard.
- Yale.
- It was Yale, actually.
- It doesn't really matter, does it?
A little something shut the place down
before freshman orientation.
- Watch it, Brian.
- How's that for a knee-slapper?
- Why do you have to be such a dick?
- Come on!
Watch out! Watch out!
You! You stay in the back, you hear me?
Hey, I will if you keep your eyes
on the goddamn road!
Hey, you can get out anytime!
You can get out right now!
- Okay. Okay. Okay.
- Kate! Kate!
The tape held.
You don't have to worry about it.
Are you okay? What is it?
Damn it.
I think she knocked a filling loose.
I weep for you.
It's locked.
Danny, be careful.
It's okay.
Shit.
Hey, are you all right? Danny!
What happened?
Jesus!
Just get the gas and let's go.
Hey, kids, we'll be back in 20.
Yeah, we'll be back in more like five.
Shit.
Bobby! Baby?
- What's that?
- That?
Well, Brian and I,
we had a dad, too.
He was just like yours.
And every summer, when we were little,
he would take us to this place.
It's Turtle Beach.
And we could swim and surf,
and we'd fish
and eat these soft-shell crab
sandwiches that were soaked in mayo.
Were there lots of turtles?
Lots? God, there were thousands
of them! They were everywhere.
I mean, you could barely put your foot
in the water without stepping on one.
Sometimes they'd be stacked up
on top of each other.
- That's impossible!
- It is possible.
- They were everywhere.
- Can we go to Turtle Beach with them?
Time to sleep.
What makes you think
you're gonna be safe there?
It's an old motel.
The place has been abandoned
for years. We'll go on scavenging trips
and quarantine ourselves
every single time we get back,
- and wait.
- Until they come for us.
Until... Until the disease dies off.
The disease or the people?
It's the same thing, really.
Bobby, I love you,
and you know
what a dipshit I can be sometimes...
What's the big deal?
I think we should see other people.
If that's the way you feel.
It is the way I feel.
- You can be such a dipshit sometimes.
- I know!
Probably the biggest in the world
at this point.
Do you ever think of Yale?
Yeah. Sure.
That, and all those things
you think you'll get to do someday.
Jesus!
- Put it out! Put the fire out!
- Go, go, go, go, go!
Where do you think you're going, boy?
- Hurry up.
- Hurry.
Just keep it down. Keep it down.
Put it out.
- Okay, I'll be right back.
- Daddy.
Honey, I'm just going in there
to make sure
there are no monsters under the bed.
If there are monsters, you shouldn't go.
Okay, now listen to me.
There's no reason to worry. All right?
I'll be back before you can say
Captain Feathersword.
You're too smart for me, you know that?
I'll stay with her.
Bobby.
Look, now is not the time, okay?
The girls need some alone time
to talk about boys.
I am serious.
Do not get too close to her.
I'm serious. Just go. It's gonna be fine.
You know, you are always doing
whatever the hell you want.
That's why you love me!
Hello?
Looks like your hospital
ran out of patients, Frank.
Come on. Let's get out of here.
Where's Kate?
- What is she doing?
- Kate?
- We have to go. There's nothing here.
- You don't know that.
Kate, they failed. Let's go.
There's a whole wing
we haven't checked yet.
You see? There are people here.
Wait!
No way.
Oh, my God. They did it.
- Sir. Sir!
- Yes?
- Are you in charge here?
- No, you want Dr. Lindus.
His office is on the second floor
of the old math building.
But you won't find him there.
He died on Thursday.
Doctor, we've come all the way
from Colorado.
We heard that you had a serum here.
It's my daughter, she's...
My daughter is very sick.
- How long?
- A little over a week.
- Is she bleeding from her ears yet?
- No.
Well, bring her in.
Okay, kids, these nice people
are gonna take you to your parents,
who are all waiting outside.
So, as soon as we finish our medicine,
we'll all be right as rain.
What are you doing to these kids?
What's that? Where's the serum?
The serum? Yes, we had a serum.
For three days it stabilized the patients.
A few actually improved.
Three days.
That's the best that we could do,
or anyone else in the world
as far as I know.
Staved off the virus for three days.
Prolonged sickness and pain
for 72 hours.
Well, I'm not prolonging it anymore.
- What's in the punch?
- Potassium.
Lots and lots of potassium.
Now, if you'll excuse us.
No! No, stop! You can't do this!
Kate, they're sick. They're already dead.
Let's go.
- Brian, they are kids.
- Who's dead? My daughter's alive!
She's not dead!
- There are other places...
- Stop pulling the goddamn curtain!
Please! Please.
- Give me your gun.
- Frank, stay where you are!
- Give me your gun, Brian.
- Frank, you know I can't do that.
Give me the gun!
Danny!
Stop. Stop! Stop, goddamn you!
Stop it! Now!
Put that down.
- Put it down!
- Look around you.
We lost power two weeks ago.
We sucked the town dry of gas
just to run the generators.
There's nothing left.
Don't. Please don't.
Sometimes choosing life is just
choosing a more painful form of death.
You're telling me your favorite cartoon's
name is Mop-Face Circle-Shirt?
- No!
- Brush-Bill Soup-Jeans?
No! SpongeBob SquarePants!
Spoon-Lips Boxer-Shorts!
Frank! Frank!
Okay. You're gonna be okay, just...
Okay, listen. Breathe slow.
Okay, okay.
We're getting out of here.
What happened?
Nothing. She took it off.
She had problems breathing, I think.
- Come here.
- Daddy? I have to go.
- Number one or number two?
- Number two.
Can you hold it?
Well, how about if I get you, like, a potty
or something, can you do it here then?
No.
All right, now. I need you to be
a very big girl for me right now.
Okay? I need you to be really brave.
You see those little blue huts
over there?
I need you to go over there by yourself,
and I'll be waiting
right here for you, okay?
- Can you try that for me?
- Okay.
- Good girl. You ready?
- Ready.
Come on.
I'll be waiting right here for you, okay?
- Okay, honey. It's okay.
- Daddy.
- I'm sorry.
- No, I'm sorry.
You did great. I'm very proud of you.
Now Daddy will take you, okay?
You strike me as a good man, Daniel.
We'll be back in a minute.
Come on, honey.
Get in.
- Get... Get in the car!
- We can't leave them here. Not here.
Look, we brought them here.
That was the deal.
Now, it's time to drop the fairytales
and move on.
You heard what that doctor said.
There's nothing here. There's nothing!
You already put us in danger
once back there.
Bobby? Bobby, say something.
Hey, what was that song... What was
that song Miss Stevens taught you
- that you used to sing all the time?
- Itsy Bitsy Spider.
The ltsy Bitsy Spider, yeah.
Do you remember how to sing that?
Ltsy bitsy spider went up the waterspout
Down came the rain
and washed the spider out
Out came the sun
and dried up all the rain
And the itsy bitsy spider
went up the spout again
How long till the beach, Danny?
At least two days. Why?
Anyone for 18 holes?
If we're gonna stop somewhere
for the night, might as well be high-end.
Right?
- What do you say, Bobby?
- Do whatever you want, Brian.
Hello!
The service here is for shit.
Hey.
- You all right?
- Yeah.
Hey.
Look, what happened back there...
I'm just trying
to get us to the beach alive.
- You know that, right?
- Yeah, I know.
We all agreed on the rules.
And the sick, they're dead.
There's nothing we can do for them.
Right.
- All right, I should go check the back.
- Okay.
Okay. Knock it off, stupid, you're fine.
Hey, Danny! I found the pool!
You want to play Marco Polo?
- Shit!
- Help!
Help!
Oh, Jesus Christ! Danny!
Let's play some golf.
Jesus! Yeah!
Hey, are you okay?
I thought golf was for old people.
- Fuck.
- Jerk!
Come on down here, baby.
- What?
- Help me out of here.
Come on, it'll be just like the time
we broke into Forest Oaks.
Remember how the groundskeeper
booted us out?
Yeah.
Well, this time we're members.
They can't touch us.
It's nice and soft.
Just come out of there. Come on.
Just give me a hand.
- Come over here! Get over here!
- Brian! Stop it!
Come on! Don't!
What?
- I'm gonna get all dirty!
- It's sand!
Yeah, sand is dirt, asshole!
Okay, ladies and gentlemen,
it's the 18th hole, and
young Brian Green steps up to the tee.
He needs a hole in one here
to get to the Masters,
but what he's really worried about
is people finding out that he's gay!
God damn it!
Dude, my advice to you
is put the club down, wait 10 minutes,
and just never pick it up again.
If it's so funny, show us what you got.
Thanks, but I think I'll use
an actual driver.
It's getting down to the wire, folks.
- Katie, Kate, whatever her last name...
- Shut up!
- All right!
- Nice.
Shit, the girl can swing!
Fairfield Country Club
Junior Champion three years in a row,
thank you very much.
Tiger Woods can kiss my ass.
Yeah!
Oh, shit.
Larry?
Larry, come in.
Can you hear me?
If you're there, pick up.
We're coming back. Do you hear me?
We're coming back.
What are you doing?
What the hell are you doing?
All day long, every single phone!
The phones are dead.
So, I just gotta try
and get in touch with my parents.
They're dead, too.
- You don't know that.
- I don't? Where were they?
Their cruise ship was quarantined
in Piraeus.
- Then they're dead.
- How do you know?
- You don't even know where Piraeus is!
- It doesn't matter where Piraeus is!
Everyone, everywhere, is dead,
your parents, my parents.
Soon you and I will be dead, too.
Kate, what happened?
- Leave me alone.
- Please.
What did she say to you?
Brian?
- That's not Brian.
- No.
- Shit!
- We got them!
This way!
Up on the second floor!
It's a mess up here!
Who are you,
and what the hell are you doing here?
Who are you?
Maybe we'll be able to talk
once we get rid of this.
No! Don't touch me!
Please, don't touch me!
We've been out a couple of days
scouting for supplies! We just got back!
Let him go!
Now.
We got everybody?
- I think so.
- There's nobody else.
Tom!
- My space.
- What?
They breached it. It's not safe.
I can't... It's not safe!
That's what you get
for living in a condom, man.
- You get...
- Screw you.
Hey, leave him alone!
We just wanted to spend the night here!
You sons of bitches.
What have you done with Larry?
How the hell do I know, man?
Maybe he got in a fight
with a shower curtain
like the rest of you guys.
Larry. He was guarding the place.
They killed him.
- He was like that when we got here.
- Yeah, right.
You expect us to believe that?
Why don't you go in the pool,
check out the cause of death
for yourself?
- What, no volunteers?
- Shut up.
Tom, he must have been sick
when we left and didn't say anything.
That's impossible.
You know that's impossible.
The system is perfect.
- Why? Because you thought of it?
- He didn't seal up his suit properly.
He made a mistake.
He didn't follow procedure.
Whatever gets you through the night.
You know, I just met you
and I'm already sick of you.
- I have that effect on people.
- Brian, cut it out! Jesus!
I want all of you out of here. Now.
Hey!
- Please, we need that.
- So do we.
Get in.
- Not you.
- What? Danny.
What the hell are you doing?
Let the girl go.
- The girls stay.
- No!
- Yeah, they stay.
- Get your hands off me!
- Don't you touch her, you son of a bitch!
- Don't move!
Get back!
If we keep the girls,
what are you gonna do with the guys?
Kill them?
We're not that kind of people.
Yeah?
And what kind of people are we?
The kind that just sits and waits to die?
Wait.
Screw you, Tom! This isn't the mill.
You're not in charge anymore.
Let the girls go.
We have to check them out.
Make sure they're clean.
Right.
Strip.
- Please, no.
- I said strip!
Shit, shit, shit, shit!
- What's going on?
- Oh, my God! Back off! Back off!
- Somebody tell me what's going on!
- Stay away from her!
- What the hell is going on?
- I said go!
Shit!
Get the hell out of here right now!
I said, right now!
This one's locked.
- I'm gonna look inside.
- I'll go check the back.
Danny?
Do you want to end up like them?
We will if she stays.
Talk to him.
- Brian?
- Help me out, will you?
We need to talk.
The key to the pump
has to be here somewhere.
- Brian, we need to deal with...
- Where the hell is that key?
Get in the car.
Get in.
Any luck?
Brian.
Get out.
I said get out.
- I'll get in the back.
- That's not what I said.
Brian, please let me stay.
Brian, please don't!
Brian, do not do this!
- There's a town down that road.
- These are just bruises.
I've been bouncing around
in the back of that
- stupid car for days.
- I'm sure there's plenty of water in town,
- but here's half a gallon.
- Of course I have bruises, but I am fine!
- Lf you ration it...
- I love you.
...it should last a few days.
- You love me, don't you?
- The same goes for the food.
- Brian, I'll wear a mask. I didn't know.
Like hell you didn't know!
- I...
- Don't you do that!
Don't you lie to me!
I wasn't sure.
Please don't leave me here!
Please, won't you help me?
When you get to town,
you find a comfortable place,
you know, with a good bed.
And get yourself a blanket,
even if it feels hot now.
And lots of water.
Do it before you're too weak.
Brian. Brian!
I warned you about the girl.
- You...
- I told you to stay away from her.
Why the hell
couldn't you have listened to me?
She was choking. She couldn't breathe.
- Brian.
- Hey, hand me a beer, will you?
Warm beer.
Tastes like piss.
- What are we gonna do?
- I don't know.
- It's almost gone.
- I know that!
Car.
- I see it.
- We gotta make them stop.
Yeah, we'll just wave politely
and ask for help.
Brian. Brian!
Hey! I'll deal with this.
- Stay where you are!
- Don't come any closer!
I'm gonna stay right here.
We just need some gas.
- Sorry. We don't have any to spare.
- I know. I understand.
But I was just hoping
that maybe as a fellow Christian,
- you might be able to help us.
- Please don't do that.
You see, my wife in the car,
she's pregnant.
We're just looking for a cool place
to have the baby,
- see this thing through.
- Go in reverse. Let's go. Let's go.
Good luck.
- Go, go, go.
- Ma'am.
- No, I can't.
- Please.
I'm begging you!
No, Brian!
Get out!
Get the gas.
Oh, God.
What are you doing?
They weren't gonna give it to us, Danny.
Help her out.
You don't talk to me. You hear me?
You don't tell me what to do!
Don't walk away from me,
you son of a bitch! I'm talking to you!
- What the...
- I am talking to you,
and I'm telling you what to do,
you self-righteous shit!
It must be nice sitting on the sidelines
while your dumb brother
wades in shit for you.
- No, I don't...
- Somebody had to do it.
- Was it gonna be you, Danny?
- You didn't have to...
You remember...
You remember our last day at home?
It wasn't you who went up to Mom
and Dad's room to get his gun, was it?
It wasn't you! It wasn't you
who had to go up there and lie
and tell them not to worry,
that you'd be back real soon.
- They were alive? Alive?
- You knew they were.
They were? You... You told me...
- What you wanted to hear.
- You asshole! Asshole!
Come here. Come here.
I'm an asshole for what?
Tell me, Danny, asshole for what?
For what?
For letting you walk by
with a clean conscience?
Well, that's what you like, Danny.
Remember Bobby?
You remember Bobby?
I was the one that had to drag her
out of the car
while you just sat there
watching me do it!
Bobby was right.
You got all the brains.
Danny.
Hey. Brian.
Stop here.
Brian. Brian.
We're gonna stop at this house, okay?
We're gonna find something
to dress your wound with.
Whatever you say, Doc.
Danny. There.
A little closer.
Keep going. Okay, stop.
Hello?
Hello!
If you can hear me,
we just need medical supplies.
Someone's hurt.
We're not infected,
and we don't mean you any harm.
We're...
We're just gonna take what we need,
and we'll leave.
What happened? Oh, shit!
What's on you?
It's not contagious. It's not human blood.
It's dog blood.
- You had me worried, little brother.
- I'm sorry.
Sorry.
Hey, don't take this the wrong way.
Can you pull down your pants?
Hey, so much for being chosen, huh?
I'm sorry.
He's got it, doesn't he?
Shit!
I don't know if there's anybody listening,
but my generator is dying.
So, if there is someone out there,
this is my last song.
This is Laura Merkin,
last survivor of Corpus Christi, Texas,
saying goodbye.
Can I see those?
Bobby had this crazy idea.
She wanted to be a mom.
Can you believe that?
Why not?
With me?
There are some things
I'm just not good at, man.
Where did she get...
A baby?
Who knows?
Maybe I would have been good at it.
Hey, Danny. Danny?
I gotta tell you something. It's a secret.
You want to hear a secret?
- Sure.
- At the stadium,
some of those people, they were...
They were still alive, Danny.
We were gonna dump them in the grave
and then...
Some of them would move.
I'd look at the supervisor,
and he'd pretend not to see, so...
So we'd pretend not to see them,
but we did.
We did, and we'd bury them anyway.
- There were so many bodies, Danny.
- I know.
- So many.
How the hell did we get here?
- I don't know, Brian.
- You know.
We both know.
We both...
Where you going, Danny?
Where you going, man?
We're leaving, Brian.
- Come on.
- Come on, come on, come on, come on!
- Shit!
- Oh, my God.
I need those keys, Brian.
Sure.
And I need a ride.
- You know I can't.
- Come on, Danny.
The ocean, you and me, one more time.
You remember how it was.
Hitting those waves
before everything turned to shit.
Just give me the keys.
You want them?
Shoot me or take me with you.
- Brian, don't do it.
- I'm not gonna end up like them, Danny.
Rotting alive, alone.
You can't tell whether they're alive
or dead.
Please, Brian. Don't.
- It's what we decided.
- I'm dying, Danny!
I don't give a fuck about the rules.
You made them.
My little brother.
I taught him everything he knows.
I drive and wait for a storm to come
and wash us all away,
but it doesn't.
It's a beautiful day.
And it shouldn't be a beautiful day.
I wait,
but nothing happens to me.
And for the first time,
I feel like I am alone in the world.
We made it.
Two strangers with nothing left to say.
Brian and I used to love this place,
the hotel, the beach.
They still look exactly the same,
but they're just places now.
Brian! Danny! Come on!
I don't know what'll happen next.
I don't know how long I'll live.
But I know I will be alone.