MALONE:
Getting shot's never easy.
[ Gunshot ]
Bullets tend to hurt, a lot.
[ Man screams ]
MALONE:
If they go straight through, fine.
That you can deal.
It's messy, and it's over soon.
[ Gunshots ]
Sometimes they take care
of themselves.
Sometimes they need a hand.
But if they glance off a bone,
get up in the ribcage,
they tend to bounce around
your insides
like dice in a backgammon cup.
Getting knifed isn't any better.
[ Gunshot ]
Even if you're dealing with a pro.
Someone who severs
a carotid artery.
Punches one through the heart.
You'll be lucky if the lights go out
inside three minutes.
Funny thing is,
sometimes these punks take care
of my business for me.
Without even knowing it.
My name's Malone.
In my line of work you have to knife
before you're punched
and shoot before you're knifed,
because there's one golden rule
that can never be broken.
Once you're dead, you stay that way.
Oh, fuck!
Okay, okay, okay! You win!
SCUMBAG: All right?!
SCUMBAG: Hey, look.
There's my gun, all right?!
You can have it.
I'm coming out now, so don't shoot!
So, don't shoot!
Look, there's my gun.
So, you can take it.
I'm cool, man. All right?
I'm cool.
Cool, huh?
Mine. See you in hell.
[ Gun clicking ]
Shit!
STACHE:
I got the case! I got the case!
Fuck!
MALONE: Some men are harder
to kill than others.
Fortunately,
I'm one of the hard ones.
Woah!
[ Screams ]
Fuck me. Shit.
[ Grunts ]
Hey! Walk away, wino!
[ Screams and grunts ]
Fucking drunk!
Ow!
Walk it off!
Pink? Goddamn, Pink.
Ta-da!
God, Malone!
Whoa!
Don't worry, kid.
I'll get your keys back.
[ Laughs ]
[ Screams ]
Thank you.
Here's your keys, kid.
[ Gunfire ]
Try to keep the screaming down.
It upsets the other guests.
TV INTERVIEWER: Listen, I know
there are millions of women
out there watching right now.
They get asked out
by that guy, they're afraid to say no.
But they're just all so terrified
they're gonna get stuck
on a two-hour long date with
somebody that's just really creepy.
What is proper etiquette
for, you know,
giving someone a brush off
these days?
Wow.
Well, the proper etiquette is...
Mom?
Why, why are you yelling?
I'm right here.
Hey, Ma.
Malone!
Ow, ow, ow!
Not so hard, Ma.
You were supposed
to come by last week.
Esther's granddaughter was here.
She looks fertile, Malone.
Wow. You got a hell of a way
of selling a gal.
Maybe you should start
writing personals.
Maybe I will.
Not that I could sell you.
You look like hell.
What did you do?
Get in another fight?
Ugh. Fight's when the other guy
has a chance.
Oh, ever since you were 6,
you were fighting with the other boys.
Fights at the playground.
Fights at the bike racks.
-Ah, to do no harm.
-Oh, no, no, no.
-Easy. Whoa, Mom.
-What's step one? What's step--?
Buckle your shoe.
Hey, Ma. Come on. I deserve it.
You deserve a smack across the face.
That's what you deserve.
Now, say it with me.
I admit I'm powerless over alcohol.
And my life
has become unmanageable.
See how unmanageable
your life has become.
You don't know what you've got
'til it's gone, Malone.
If you weren't so hardheaded,
you'd know that by now.
MALONE:
Say it again, Ma.
You're hardheaded.
It's a family curse.
Oh, no. Before that.
You don't know
what you've got 'til it's gone?
Right now, I've got it.
MALONE: What the hell were those
guys killing themselves over?
Don't mumble, Malone.
It makes you sound uneducated.
What the hell would you throw
yourself out a window for?
You threw yourself out a window?
No, Ma.
A guy with a mustache.
Oh, please don't grow a mustache!
Your father did,
and it looked like a rat curled up
and died under his nostrils.
You know, weaker men than you have
dealt with tragedy without the booze.
GLORIA: How many bullets
do I have to pull out of you
before you live again?
You know, you can quit the booze.
You just need support.
Someone to prop you up
and help keep you on your feet.
Malone?
GLORIA:
Well, I guess I should be grateful.
If it wasn't for these lovely
shoot-outs, I wouldn't see you at all.
[ Man screaming ]
It's her birthday tomorrow.
Buy her something nice.
Sir, I'm gonna need to see some I.D.
SECURITY GUARD: Ugh!
[ Keypad beeps ]
[ Security guard grunts ]
Next time there's a new guy,
tell him let the big, bad, black
motherfucker go.
There's a blot on this city.
It's as if God came along,
hiked up his robe,
and took a big holy shit
right on top of downtown.
Or, maybe it was you, Boulder.
You're nearly as big as,
you know --
Ah, it wasn't me, Boss.
Well, the point is...
...the city has lost its sense
of structure,
and without structure, without order,
it's hard to be king.
I heard Stache's little pick up
turned into a blood bath.
We had some uninvited party-goers,
and he didn't get the case.
No.
Who did?
Malone.
Malone? Just one guy?
Well, go get him, Boulder.
Go crush him.
Well, it's not that easy, Boss.
Malone's hard. Real hard.
Word is he turned
from private dick
to gun-for-hire after what
they did to his family.
They killed his wife...
...his son, his brother...
...his brother's family...
...tried to stamp
his gene pool into extinction.
Personally,
I can't wait to hurt him.
Boulder, do you have any idea
what Malone's probably done,
now that he has that case?
Opened it.
Goddamn right he's opened it.
And now that he's seen what's inside,
I want Matchstick in on this.
WHITMORE:
You got a problem with that?
Boss, the guy's a sadist.
Little sadism might come in handy.
Speaking of sadism,
call in The Mauler, as well.
The Mauler? Have you seen
where she keeps her knives?
Boulder, you're a killer.
You're the bloodiest son-of-a-bitch
I know,
and I pay you very well too, don't l?
Yes, sir.
But that's not why you do
what you do, is it?
My wife's gonna pull out of it.
I'm sure.
Then as long as you
keep working for me,
I'll keep floating her medical bills.
I learned something early on
in my career,
and I've never forgotten.
Men will work
very hard for good money.
But they will absolutely
kill themselves for love.
I'll find The Mauler.
And put Malone's face
on a baseball card.
Wake up every thug
in this entire city.
I want everyone to know
I'm paying big money.
Five million dollars.
But, most importantly,
get me that case.
Yes, sir.
[ Elevator dings ]
And, Boulder... ripped out
a man's heart and ate it?
The physics of punching
through a man's sternum alone
make that an impossibility.
Next time,
spare me the hyperbole.
Yes, sir.
Son of a bitch!
Don't you ever knock?
What's this?
Was it just me, or were we paid
a hundred grand
to recover what was inside the case,
not just the case?
It was a set-up, Murph.
They knew I was coming.
No way. No way. Not possible.
I checked it all out.
I did my homework.
It was legit. It was quiet.
Just you and the client.
I need to know who hired me, Murph.
Now, you know we follow a formula
around here. Don't ask. Don't tell.
Nobody's the wiser.
What's a couple of bullet holes
over a sound financial future, huh?
What was in the case?
You miss the part
about it being a set-up?
What's wrong with you?
I never seen you like this before.
What was in the case?
It was the meaning of love, Murph.
Now, cry me a name.
You're looking at her.
Evelyn, Malone,
Malone, Evelyn.
He's a swell guy.
When he's not roughing people up.
I hope your man's better at delivering
goods than looking pretty,
'cause he sure as hell
ain't much of a looker.
Yeah, well, Evelyn, Malone
was just telling me that he, uh,
ran into a little speed bump
when he was picking up the case.
Said it was some sort of a set-up.
You were paid to get the case,
not open it.
What did you do
with what was inside?
Never mind about that.
I had ten goons trying to make me
dead over that damn thing.
So, let's skip to the part
where you explain, sister.
I'm not your sister.
You ain't the client either.
Talk. Or I'll make like you're my
daughter and bend you over my knee.
Promises, promises.
You think a dime-store hussy like that
came up with this much cash?
No way.
Um, my apologies, Evelyn. He's not
accustomed to polite conversation.
Can it.
That's all right, Murph.
I don't expect manners
from a talking animal.
Yeah, I'm much better at biting
and scratching.
And hunting and killing,
I suppose.
That's why they pay me.
Okay, the gorilla wins.
I'm not the client.
What?
So much for the job being legit.
Look, all I know is that I'm supposed
to pick up the case and deliver it.
Tonight.
To who, lady? Who wants it?
I need a name, goddamn it.
A gorilla wouldn't understand.
Something I said?
Look...
They have my brother, Sammy.
I got a letter saying if I don't
deliver the case tonight,
they're gonna kill him.
MALONE: Where?
Hey, darlin', we're closed
for the night. You lost?
Where's your parents?
Parents?
Guess they left me here.
All by my lonesome.
Are you lollipop69?
I got your e-mail.
At first, I thought it was a joke,
you know, spam.
But you're here.
You're really here.
Now, what are you going
to do about it?
If they find out there's nothing
in the case, they'll kill him.
I'll have your brother
before it gets that far.
Just keep it closed.
When we get a little closer,
I'm gonna have you drive.
Okay.
This one turns on the sound.
This one turns on the lights.
And this one...
...makes the horsies go up and down.
I thought that's
what this one was for.
This might be easier if you took
that lollipop out of your mouth.
It might get in the way.
You know?
Agreed.
[ Zipper unzips ]
Ah, pretty, pretty,
moist and pretty--
I've got your case!
[ Carnival equipment whirs ]
[ Man groans ]
Where's my brother?!
EVELYN: Oh, my God!
Sammy!
I like to cut the soft ones.
Please.
Malone!
Sammy! Sammy!
Shit!
Who grabbed you?
Who grabbed you? Huh? Who?
Sister.
Talk to me, damn it!
Who grabbed you?
Damn it.
[ Creepy laugh echoes ]
[ Man whispers ]
I'm watching you.
Malone?!
Ring around the rosie
[ Giggles ]
MALONE: Evelyn?!
Malone?
-Where the hell is she?
-I don't know.
Help me.
[ Carnival music plays ]
[ Child singing ]
Which way?!
If you see yourself, turn.
Let's get the hell out of here.
MALONE:
Two questions, sister.
You say you were told to deliver
a case tonight,
or they'd kill your brother.
And now he's dead, thanks to you.
How'd you know where the case
would be in the first place?
The letter.
And how'd you find Murph, huh?
He shoot you out of the sky?
Also in the letter.
Where'd you get this
goddamn letter?
From my goddamn mail box.
Please, slow down!
Listen up, lady.
Not only did you almost
get me killed tonight,
you also blew any chance of me
finding out who hired me.
Let alone who killed your brother.
So, unless you've got
some helpful bit of information
in that overwrought hairdo of yours,
I suggest you get the hell
out of my life.
Out of your life?
You told me you'd save my brother,
you son-of-a-bitch.
Get out. Get out.
Where am I supposed to go?
Here. Take a cab.
Wait. I've got the letter.
Who gave it to you?
Eddie the Cheese.
Right after they grabbed Sammy.
After who grabbed Sammy?
I asked Eddie. I even said please.
Maybe you can be more persuasive.
Lady, you ain't got to persuade
a fella. If you know how to push.
-What?
-Go on.
Here.
Don't leave me.
Please. Please! Malone!
[ Music playing inside ]
[ Crowd screaming inside ]
Matchstick.
You gotta burn every place you rob?
Disco should have died
when ABBA broke up.
[ Explosion ]
I'm just helping it along.
Damn.
[ People screaming ]
[ Knock on door ]
They killed Sammy.
Look, um,
I'm sorry as hell about Sammy.
But you can't stay here.
I need Malone.
If they killed Sammy,
who do you think's next?
Please, Murph. Where is he?
I can't tell you where he is.
You know, we have
a simple formula around here.
Don't ask, don't tell.
Nobody's the wiser.
[ Knock on door ]
Malone.
No, he doesn't knock.
Upstairs.
MURPH:
Uh, what are you doing here?
[ Glass shatters ]
[ Groans ]
Up awfully late, Murph.
Yeah. Yeah.
Well, I was just, uh, cataloging
my stamp collection, you know.
Hell of a Friday night, Boulder.
I don't see any stamps.
You always were
the astute one, man.
Never could get a nickel by you.
Still for the life of me can't
remember why I fired you.
You didn't fire me. I quit.
-Oh, really?
-Really.
Is that right?
'Cause I seem to remember
you sitting me down one day
and saying, "Murph,
I got trouble paying my bills,"
and I said, "Yeah, of course you do,
pal, because you're fired!"
Is that antique?
Uh-huh.
I quit!
Where's Malone?
MURPH: Malone?
Never heard of him.
Can I get you a cup of tea?
Ugh!
Next time, it's your face.
Now, me and Malone
used to work together.
Just like you do now.
So, I'm willing to bet
you know where he is.
Where is he?
Huh?
What?
Where is he?!
Unlike my genetically
malfunctioned associate,
I would like to take this opportunity
not to wage war,
but to play nice.
You see, life hasn't always
been kind to me, Murph.
Yet, still I've always made it
a moral prerogative
to turn the other cheek,
so to speak. You know?
To look at the bright side.
Especially when life is at its worst.
Or, in your case, most stubborn.
Now, before things start
getting heated up in here,
I think it would be very nice of you
to give us Malone's whereabouts.
Okay. There's no need
for that here, all right?
We're all businessmen, right? Let's
just do a little business, shall we?
Okay.
Let's do a little business, Murph.
How 'bout the business of kerosene?
You see, it's a very
deceptive substance.
It looks like water,
and it feels like water.
The only difference is when
kerosene is kissed with flame, Murph,
then it burns like hell.
Okay, I don't know anything,
all right?
He came in here screaming
about the meaning of love
being in that case,
and then he beat the hell out
of here, that's all I know, okay?
The meaning of love.
Like in a fairy tale?
Once upon a time,
there was a bad little boy
who loved playing with matches,
you see,
because fire was his only
and best friend,
but then after the accident,
he learned to respect fire, Murph,
because fire, though it's beautiful,
it's consumptive, you see.
It's powerful, and if you're not
careful, Murph, fire will hurt you.
Do you understand what I'm saying?
So, as the house
was burning down,
the little boy's Mommy
and Daddy scream.
They sounded like music to his ears
because now there was nothing
to get between the bad little boy
and his heart's desire.
Fire.
Okay, corner of Compton
and Sycamore, Apartment 318.
Sycamore and Compton. 318.
Let's go, Matchstick.
Thanks, Murph.
Oh, now that we're friends,
can we--?
Can we just forget about this whole,
uh, torching-the-parents episode?
I miss Mom and Dad dearly,
I really do.
And, uh, tell you the truth,
I'm still working it out in therapy.
Therapy?
You should be in a dog kennel,
you fucking freak!
[ Grunts and moans ]
[ Screaming ]
All right.
Where are you?
Come here. Doc says you gotta take
your medicine, or else--
[ Cat screeches ]
Little fucker. Come here.
Ow.
[ Muffled voice ]
Don't hit me again, okay?
Whatever's left of my good looks
can't take it.
You know who I am?
You're Malone.
Your family was murdered, and
now you rip out people's hearts
with your bare hands.
Sometimes.
Sometimes I weld their eyelids
together. Depends on my mood.
Today's been pretty shitty,
so I'm gonna ask you one more time.
Who pinched Sammy Smalls?
Where'd you get that fucking letter?
They'll kill me.
They'll kill me, Malone, you know--
[ Muffled coughing ]
[ Talking through towel,
indecipherable ]
Huh?
[ Talking through towel,
indecipherable ]
What was that, you say?
[ Talking through towel,
indecipherable ]
It's Jerry. He runs a hooker joint
called The Trade Winds Motel.
Okay?
He sent the money.
He wrote your letter.
Jerry?
I didn't know he was literate.
[ Knock on door ]
EVELYN: Malone!?
No.
I can't breathe. I can't--
Quiet. No talking.
Come on!
[ Gun cocks ]
If somebody ever got to me or Murph,
we had a plan.
Give up the address
of our neighbor, see?
That way, there'd be time enough
to even the odds.
Put up the gun, doll.
I'm in a mood.
Okay.
Come on.
That's a good girl.
Wait a minute.
This is Murph's gun.
I gave it to him.
How the hell did you--?
Aw, hell.
That's right, Malone.
They killed him.
They killed him
because they were looking for you.
I can't stop seeing Sammy
with that knife in his chest.
Everybody dies.
It was just his turn.
Those men who killed Murph,
that girl who killed Sammy,
they think I'm with you.
You have to help me, Malone.
Scotch.
Good scotch like this
you're supposed to sip,
but in light of the circumstances,
I don't think history will judge you
too harshly if you shoot it.
The meaning of love.
Murph said something about it before
they burned him like a bad steak.
What is it?
It's a lonely thing, killing a man.
Once you start,
once you kill somebody
someone cares about...
...pulling that trigger
becomes a way of life.
No one cares about you.
You sure about that?
You pull that trigger, you start
to build a wall of corpses around.
The higher you stack 'em,
the safer you feel.
So you just keep pulling
that trigger. Bang.
MALONE:
Bang. Bang.
It's a cold world, Evelyn.
But at least I know
how to stay warm in it.
Scotch is far easier, trust me.
I'm powerless over alcohol.
My life has become unmanageable.
Just finished cleaning it.
It's a good thing
you didn't pull the trigger,
I wouldn't have wanted you
to embarrass yourself.
[ Knock on door ]
My guess is when Murph
spilled that address,
there were more ears listening
than just yours.
Damn it. No bullets.
Open it.
Don't be stupid.
Think it's gonna do us any good?
Buy me some time. Go on!
Damn it.
[ Knock on door ]
EVELYN: Who is it?
[ Pounding on door ]
Okay. Okay. Okay.
Can I help you?
Malone.
Boulder, what are you doing here?
I thought Murph fired you.
For the last time,
I told you, I quit.
I see you're still
on the rot-gut, huh?
Yeah. I would never start
what you can't finish.
Before I surrendered,
I did a lot of bad things.
Terrible things.
But I've managed to mend a lot
of emotional fences since then.
You could, too.
BOULDER: We have a meeting
at the "Y" every night of the week.
I already got a mother.
Where's the case?
[ Gasps ]
Mother, mother, mother.
Oh, how I wish I still had a mother.
MATCHSTICK: Mother would have
loved you, sweetheart.
Yum-yum.
Hey, easy, Sparky.
Save that book for the bedroom.
The name's Matchstick.
I'm surprised you haven't
heard of me,
seeing as how we're both
wayward souls,
wrought in the ashes of our
respective families' demise.
Take a seat, pussycat.
You see, the story I heard was
you had to decide who would die.
MATCHSTICK:
Your wife or your son.
Hell's bells, Malone.
What a dilemma.
And then, after you chose the wife,
they killed both of them.
Oh, Hell's Bells, what a tragedy.
Kiss my ass.
Oh, Malone. I doubt that would be
pleasurable for either of us.
You see, I have precious little
sensation in these "smackeroonies."
Where'd you get Psycho Boy?
Whose payroll you on anyway?
I'm in business for myself, Malone.
Just like you. I'm my own man,
captain of my own ship.
What, Murph wasn't
good enough for ya?
Hard to be good for anyone
when you're dead.
That wasn't smart, Boulder.
Killing Murph.
Now I'm gonna have to
rip out your heart.
Now, let's not confuse the facts,
gentlemen.
It wasn't the oversized baggage
that did your friend Murph in.
No. It was flames.
Smoke. Heat. Immolation.
We're here for the case, Malone.
Where is it?
Yeah? Who wants it?
Doesn't matter who wants it.
All that matters is who gets it.
Murph said it was
the "meaning of love."
It is.
We know you opened that case, and
we know you have what's inside of it.
Now, where is it?
Why don't you ask him?
Easy, big man.
That way. Come on.
Back up. Go on.
You mind? I just had that area
waxed, it's pretty sensitive.
Sorry to cause you discomfort.
Go on. That's it.
Come on.
Go ahead. Go ahead.
You gonna shoot? Shoot.
Go. Go.
Go ahead. You gonna shoot?
Shoot me.
Yeah. I would,
but I'm all out of bullets.
Here! Come on! Come on!
Oh, shit.
Shit!
Come on! Come on!
Sorry if I don't know how to load guns
and shoot people.
-Come on!
-Freeze! Police!
Against the wall.
All right.
-IN SPANISH: She's the crazy one!
-Back inside, sir!
[ Chaotic noise ]
What is that?
You're not gonna like what's gonna
come through that door.
Hey, hey, hey!
You stop right--
[ Fire alarm sounding ]
[ Gunshot ]
[ Neck cracking ]
Here. I want you to go
to the liquor store on 5th Street.
Buy me a pint of whiskey.
They give you any trouble,
tell them you're with me.
You coming?
These guys aren't
gonna quit 'til they're dead.
I'm gonna make them that way.
Go on.
I'll meet you at the Tradewinds Motel.
On 5th, all right?
Where is it, huh?
Where is it?!
Closed.
It's for Malone.
I'm Malone's girl.
Malone?
Yes, Malone.
Whiskey.
Yes. Whiskey.
Oh, God!
Not the booze!
Come on, Malone! Come on!
Malone!
Who put out the reward on the case,
who wants it?
Go blow, Malone.
Why do they want it?!
Goddamn it!
Go blow, Malone!
Come on!
I'll be back for that thing
in your chest.
Why aren't you at the hotel?
You didn't notice,
they were about to kill you.
When I tell you to do
something, you do it.
Are you nuts?!
I need a drink.
Be right back.
Come on!
[ Moans ]
Boulder, you had one job.
Get Malone.
What? Slow down.
I don't care if he's got
a bad attitude.
I'm not asking you to invite him
to a coffee klatch.
I'm telling you to jam him in the boot
of your car and haul his ass in!
No, no, I didn't realize that a
'69 Mustang has limited trunk space.
[ Phone beeps ]
Hold on. Yeah?
What? What?
What do you mean, they're gonna
kick her out of the country?
Doesn't she have her visa?
She never got one?
None of the girls got their visas?
You're goddamned right it's bad!
Take an awfully long dick to fuck
one of them from across the Atlantic!
Who is responsible?
Frankie the Crooner? You sure?
Well, find out!
Boulder, call me back
in five minutes.
No! He couldn't actually rip
your heart out. Christ!
[ Bell dings ]
Can't you see the sign, man?
I'm out to lunch.
Malone?
Malone!
How the hell are you?
What's it called when you're out
to lunch at two in the morning?
Munchies?
You're sweating, Jerry.
What's the matter?
It's just me, your ol' pal from the
neighborhood looking for a room.
With two beds.
You mean, she's not a--?
I don't know. Are you?
What does your cheek say?
My cheek?
JERRY: Hey, I can see you've got
needs, and you're in luck!
I got the best room in the house.
Complete with complimentary
prophylactics and earplugs.
What's my ol' pal
from the neighborhood
doing packing his dirty laundry?
Does he know Eddie the Cheese
got pinched?
If Eddie got pinched, then he might
rat him out about a letter
sent to a girl named Evelyn.
Huh?
Whose payroll are you on, Jerry?
Whitmore. Okay? Christ!
I got paid to write the letter
by Whitmore!
Whitmore.
Here. Watch something
a little less confusing.
Come on.
Christ, I'm aroused.
Too bad there's not a man around.
I'll be sure to call if I see one.
Why bother?
You finally got what you wanted.
Earplugs?
Me. In your room. With a bed.
We don't have time to sleep.
Jerry's working for Whitmore,
which means Whitmore hired me
to get that damn case,
means Whitmore killed your brother.
Problem is,
nobody knows where he lives.
He went underground years ago.
Goddamn mole.
We gotta dig him out.
What about what was
in that case?
Why do you think
he wants it so badly?
Forget about that.
Whitmore went
through a lot of trouble
to make sure it ended up
in my hands.
Not yours.
Don't confuse yourself.
Whitmore used you
to get that case for him.
Not to keep it for yourself.
Now, what was in it?
I told you, it was the meaning of--
Of love?
Bullshit.
Why don't you just give it
to Whitmore
before someone else gets hurt?
A lot of people got hurt
in this town, lady.
I just happened to be first.
Do you think you want it rough,
Malone, but you don't.
You want it soft.
Just like the rest of us.
Now, if you don't mind,
I feel sticky.
It's been a dirtier night
than I expected.
Get some rest!
No one knows where we are.
Few hours now won't kill us.
Oh, ladies,
with a performance like that,
you more than earned your stay
in these great United States.
You deserve what I usually reserve
for panty-dropping moments,
but since yours have all ready fallen,
consider those desserts.
Huh?
Ah-la-la-la-la-la-la! Hu-hu-hu!
Hey! Here's the fun.
Yeah! Ooo!
Well, well, well. Good evening.
Welcome, everyone.
[ Reverb from amp ]
Son of a bitch.
Sorry about that.
Good-looking crowd.
All right!
Let's get down.
And let's get sexy. Huh?
Oh, yeah.
Well, good night, ladies
That's right
Ladies, good night
[ Cell phone ringing ]
It's time--
[ Cell phone ringing continues ]
I'm just gonna--
All right, you know what?
This had better be good,
because I'm right in the middle
of entertaining the people.
WHITMORE:
My visas.
Mr. Whitmore?
Oh! Hi, Mr. Whitmore. Hi.
Yeah. Um, what?
Where the fuck are my visas?
Uh. Well, uh. I don't, uh, I don't
really know, uh, Mr. Whitmore.
This is the first
I've heard about this.
Well, I just found out
that they disappeared
from our warehouse last night.
Meanwhile, I got some tramp
from Brazil
claiming you gave her one
for a blowjob.
Uh, well, I mean, you know, I mean,
don't insult me, uh, Mr. Whitmore.
You know. It's not like I need to, uh,
bribe hookers to get pussy, you know?
I mean, I'm a working musician.
Got the, got the ladies falling
from the trees, as they say.
I have to wear special wading pants
just to wade through them.
WHITMORE:
Working? [ Laughs ]
The only paying gig you've got is
singing at fucking nursing homes.
WHITMORE: Well, if you didn't steal
them, you better fucking find them.
Or you're gonna get your nuts jerked
out through your asshole.
[ Phone beeps ]
Okay.
[ Dial tone ]
All right, well, then, I will play
at your birthday party, Mr. Whitmore.
It would be my pleasure.
Get off your knees.
OPERATOR:
All circuits are busy now.
If you would like to make a call,
please try again later.
Okay. Just contact my agent.
All right, bye-bye.
Good night, ladies
Ladies, good night
It's times like these I'd much rather
be drowning in a sea of sex.
[ Laughs ]
Look at those happy shmucks.
Three hundred dollars,
and they're king for an hour.
Meanwhile, I'm a paying out millions
of dollars a year in payroll
to a bunch of two-bit crooks
who make me feel
like a fucking court jester.
Present company excluded,
of course.
What the hell's wrong with you?
Don't tell me I hurt your feelings.
I've been mending a lot
of emotional fences lately.
I can't work for you anymore.
I have to be my own man.
Captain of my ship.
Now, I need you to give me a loan
for medical expenses,
and I'll pay you back, with interest.
Can you believe this guy?
He's a sap.
And he's terrified of fire.
Aren't you, Leslie?
Name is Boulder.
Oh.
Leslie. Boulder.
Whatever the hell your name is.
We got a mutually beneficially
situation here, remember?
You do what I tell you,
and I make sure that your wife's
life-support machines keep pumping.
You should be more gracious.
Murph sure as hell
wasn't floating her bill.
You lose me, and she blinks out.
Like a light.
Ah! I, I heard the doctors say
that there's no chance
of the poor woman's recovery.
No, she's gonna pull out of it.
No. I heard she's brain dead.
Don't look at me like that.
I mean, I'm not the one
who wrecked that car.
Children! Enough!
The case. Did you find it?
The Mauler found it
at the amusement park,
but it was empty.
Well, then, go find Malone.
Bring him back to me.
We'll beat it out of him.
Malone!
You have to get to the hospital.
You're bleeding really bad.
Come on.
Brockwood.
-Malone?
-Brockwood Retirement Home.
Where?
Brockwood Retirement Home.
Take me there.
EVELYN:
Okay.
FRANKIE: Fa la la la la la la
Hup hup hup
Hey, here's the fun.
[ Laughs ] Yeah! Woo!
Oh, my goodness! Yes!
What a good-looking crowd, huh?
Thank you.
Yeah, thank you, thank you.
It's good to be young, huh?
Well, I mean, to be vital. You know?
Well, hey, to be alive.
Actually, it's probably not good.
Little hot?
FRANKIE: Hey, you could probably,
uh, just stop with the light show.
It's not Pink Floyd.
Enough with the lights!
Deaf motherfucker.
FRANKIE:
Okay, let's get this going.
Which way?
FRANKIE:
So, let's swap pills.
Crank up the oxygen.
Let's get down.
And let's get...sexy.
[ Music plays ]
Well, good night, ladies
Oh!
Oh! Are you feeling it?
Ladies, good night
Ha, ha! How!
[ Audience laughs ]
Oh, you've got to be shitting me.
Excuse me.
Yeah, get me Whitmore.
[ Malone screaming ]
[ Malone groaning ]
Don't you got a retired
anesthesiologist around here?
You finished?
Oh! Is she with you?
Yeah, she's a client, Ma.
That's all.
Come in, come in.
Thank you.
You've changed.
Yeah, so has your underwear,
if you wear any.
How do you know my boy?
I told you. Mom, Mom!
She's a client.
Murphy's client.
Was Murph's client.
Anyway, we're not really
supposed to know each other.
It's complicated.
I think she's perfect!
You've been drinking?
What's the matter with you?
It's a special day.
Not that you'd remember.
[ Knock on door ]
Oh.
You shouldn't have.
I didn't.
That's the sweetest, nicest thing
that anybody ever did for me.
Oh, you love your Mommy.
Say it with me!
You love your Mommy!
Keep her inside.
Lock the door.
Hey. Where's the squawker?
I don't know. Made a phone call
and took off out of here real fast.
Still trying to breastfeed
in kindergarten.
I felt like the only cow
in Switzerland.
Oh, Malone! Your friend here's been
asking all about your childhood.
Sounds so idyllic.
I'm green with envy, Malone-sy.
Put the gun down.
That's it.
Now, give me the meaning of love,
or I make "she" as pretty as me.
She's a pretty as she needs to be,
you creep!
Ow!
[ Screams ]
[ Fire alarm beeping ]
Okay, Mom. Let's go.
Come on.
Malone!
You just lit that man on fire!
Come on, Mom!
Malone.
Oh, wow. You're big.
Wouldn't hit a guy in front
of his mom, now, would ya?
Get in the car!
Give 'em hell, Malone!
I need the meaning of love!
Where is it? What is it?
Ask your mother.
Are you all right?
Start the car! Start the fucking car!
Okay! Okay, let's go!
Go! Go!
Come on.
You know Poco Rio,
about 60 miles south of here.
Here.
Poco Rio?!
I don't want to go to some place
I've never heard of!
Ma, here.
Find a nice spa.
Treat yourself like a queen.
I'll see you in a week.
-What the hell was that for?
-Just in case you don't....
Get in the car.
Watch your head, watch your head.
Come on.
Here. Go! Go!
Yeah, no,
don't worry about it, Maurice.
I got it, you lazy motherfucker.
Tony Bennett didn't have
to do it like this.
I have to do it.
Oh, my goodness.
Hey, there, dollface.
I haven't seen you around
here before.
Frankie the Crooner, right?
Yeah, born and raised,
except for the crooner part.
You know?
That you gotta earn.
So, ah, look, five grand
gets you a free stay
in these great United States
for a year.
Or if you don't have the cash,
we could work out
something a little more--
[ Implies sex ]
[ Gun cocks ]
Malone.
Hey. Oh, l, uh, isn't she a...?
I dunno.
Why don't you ask her?
Aren't you a...?
What does your nose say?
My nose?
Yeah.
[ Frankie coughs ]
-Who did you call, Frankie?
-Suck my Sinatra.
Fuck! Okay! Okay!
FRANKIE: Stop the car,
you motherfucker!
Hey! Stop the car!
Fucker!
FRANKIE: I'll talk!
Whitmore! All right?
Whitmore!
God! Unbelievable!
You know, I gotta tell you, Malone,
there is a lot of money
out there on that case, all right?
And I hate to bruise your ego,
but it's not even about that anymore.
I mean, Whitmore is up to his gills
in shit water from his own guys,
stolen visas, lieutenants
skimming off the top.
All right, it is unreasonable.
So he called a meeting
at the carnival tonight.
But the fucked up thing is,
is that Pencil,
they're gonna double cross him.
You lying to me, Frankie?
Let me tell you something.
Whitmore only travels
one way, in style.
You can see his limo
coming from a mile away.
If it don't cross over that bridge,
you come back and kill me.
All right, you know where I sing, and
you keep the princess away from me.
Uh, oh, it must be a hell of a thing
to be an only child,
ooh, every day is yours.
She's not an only child.
Whitmore killed her brother,
Sammy Smalls.
Sammy ain't got no sister.
What?
I played at every one of his birthdays
for the past ten years.
He sure as shit ain't got no sister.
Someone taking you for a ride, pal.
You got a goldfish.
What did he say?
What are you doing?
[ Tires squealing ]
Driving fast.
Malone, stop!
Oh, my God!
I take back all those mean things
I said about you.
I was just trying to be smart.
Yeah, you're smart, all right.
Try physics, specifically inertia.
Why did you hire me
to get that case?
He was gonna kill my brother.
Sammy's last words were "sister",
as in "not my sister".
You know why?
'Cuz you ain't.
I might survive.
You definitely won't.
Come clean. Huh?!
MALONE:
Come clean!
I'm pregnant!
[ Tires screeching ]
Okay, lady, spill.
Whitmore picks his girls
from overseas.
He keeps his favorites for himself.
But if you ever lose enthusiasm,
or you get pregnant, you're out.
That means he sends you
to work the alleys,
the back-rooms, the sex clubs.
I did it until I decided it was bad.
Bad. For what?
Whitmore's baby.
Sammy Small wasn't my brother.
He was my lover.
When Whitmore kicked me out,
Sammy took me in.
Whitmore didn't know.
So Sammy's working for Whitmore?
Sammy told me Whitmore was gonna
blackmail you with that case.
Why? Huh?
What's he want with me?
Sammy didn't know,
but he said once you got the case,
you'd run straight to Whitmore,
so I convinced him to let me
get the case from you.
Whitmore found out,
so he had Sammy killed.
I made up the brother story
to try and save him.
Where the hell is he?
Where do I find this son of a bitch?
Christ, Malone,
I was his trick, not his date.
How should I know?
Why did you do it?
To meet you.
Like it or not,
you've got a reputation.
No, I mean, really, why?
'Cuz I'm gonna kill Whitmore.
I'm gonna put a bullet
through his filthy, rotten heart,
and I need you to get me to him.
-Nobody kills Whitmore.
-Why?
-'Cuz they need him alive.
-No, Malone, I mean, really, why?
Is it the meaning of love? Huh?
What? Think a lady like me
wouldn't understand?
Well...
That was special.
I'd go with you,
but your seat belt's broken.
I couldn't live with myself
if you get a traffic violation.
What are you doing?!
Come here.
Get away from me!
Get away from me, you creep!
Malone, put me down!
Put me down, you dumb, ugly ox!
Put me down!
What about the cops? Huh?
This seal means
they're done investigating.
Get your hands off of me!
Easy, sweetheart.
Whitmore's men might not be
stupid enough
to come back to the scene
of a crime.
But a damsel in distress
might change their mind.
Come on.
Happy?
It's too tight. It hurts.
What if I have to go
to the bathroom?
Fertilize.
Come on!
[ Knock on door ]
Quiet.
I never heard of Poco Rio.
Hey.
I hate carnivals.
Check it out!
Whitmore wants to have a talk about
how we're running our operations.
Might help if he made
an appearance.
BUCK TOOTH: Well, maybe
he's still miffed about you
losing that case to Malone.
Fuck Malone and fuck that case.
Whitmore's got no respect
for the men I lost.
49% of me wants to show him
just how sorry I am,
so he better do nothing
to push it into the majority.
You were mean about as well as that
ridiculous mustache of yours.
Shortchanging Whitmore's
the flavor of the week,
and you're the only one out here
who hasn't had the spine to do it.
[ Gunfire ]
[ Balloons popping ]
We're not alone.
Gee, you think, pretty boy?
[ Bell dings ]
Hey, you schmoes, check out...
Where the hell are you two going?
It might be Malone!
-Whitmore's here.
-What?
You two look for Malone!
I gotta talk to Whitmore!
Whoa, Stache,
are you fucking with us?
Only when I'm on top.
Hey! Whitmore!
Where the hell's Whitmore?
Okay, first of all,
let me just say that I didn't
want to double cross you.
He caught me with the visas.
Okay, he made me.
He... I don't like violence.
I'm a singer.
Sure you are, Frankie.
Where the hell is he?
[ Tribal music fades up ]
Sometimes I like to go tribal.
Tired already?
[ Laughs ]
What the hell?
Who the hell's back there?
[ Girl humming tune ]
It's just the meaning of love
The meaning of love
[ Giggles ]
It's just the meaning of love
The meaning of love
Do you know
how I learned how to count?
Tallying up elementary school
rejection slips.
You've killed a lot
of dangerous men, Malone.
Did that give you pleasure?
You're gonna give me a rash, lady.
Did you finally get your revenge
for what they did to your family?
I heard you like fairy tales.
Once upon a time,
this guy had a gorgeous wife
and the most adorable little boy.
But one night while Malone
thought he was on the job,
the job was in his home.
They had a good time
taking turns with his boy
and then taking turns
on top of her.
Then when they were all spent...
Bang! Bang! Bang! Bang!
It's not fair!
You had such a happy family...
...and I can't even get a date.
[ Gasps ]
Do you think it's my personality?
Nah, it's probably your face.
Girls...
You know what
they say about fire?
It's cozy.
Ah, Malone, so pathetic.
You still haven't learned
the lessons of fire.
It's rebirth, the phoenix rising
from the ashes.
Don't give me the poetic crap.
The only lesson you should have
learned is don't play with matches.
Oh, but then, I wouldn't have
had any friends as a child.
And that would have been
a lonely existence.
Ho, ho, ha, ha.
Wow, Sparky, went a little heavy
on the skin peel there, pal.
[ Laughing ]
Let's play nice, Malone-sy, okay?
I'll give you the name
of my plastic surgeon.
You give me
what was in that case.
Yes. Yes...
What do you say, Malone-sy?
You hand over the meaning of love,
or it's Mauler's turn again.
MALONE: Why don't you
invite Boulder, too?
If I had known the three of you
were working for Whitmore,
I'd have had you all over for tea.
Look, my hands,
they're a little shaky.
Ooh, the loss of motor skills
is rather debilitating.
Oopsy. Oh. Oh.
Apologies, Malone-sy on your nice,
nice, beautiful suit.
It's just like they have
a mind of their own.
Oops! Oopsy!
Oops! Oh, Malone-sy! So sorry!
Oopsy again, Malone-sy!
And again! And again and again
and again and again
and again and again and again!
Oh, how 'bout a drink, Malone-sy,
huh? I know you're thirsty.
Parched. Yeah.
There you go, Malone-sy.
How's that taste?
Now...dah, dah, dah, dah.
Don't move. Don't move.
In this light,
you look just like Murph.
[ Screaming ]
Always take the gun.
Toasty! Oh, oh, yes, yes!
Nice, toasty!
[ Laughs ] Oh!
You think this looks painful,
imagine what Whitmore
is doing to your woman.
Burn in hell, you fucker.
Shit.
What the hell?
Mom! Mom!
What?! What?!
Why are you yelling?
I'm right here.
Where's Evelyn?
The whole place has been tossed.
What happened?
I dunno.
I had a little nap,
and then I had a second nap,
and then the third was pretty good,
but I don't remember a fourth.
Anyway, I fed your cat his medicine.
How the hell'd you manage that?
Well, I had to feed you, didn't l?
I wonder if A.A.
has a family discount.
And yet another reason
why sobriety's overrated.
If you were still drinking, I would
have never found out where you were.
Now, I want you to
take me to Whitmore's cave.
Understand? His hovel.
His apartment.
[ Elevator dings ]
They seem to know you here.
Hello, Malone.
I thought you were done
living dangerously.
Hell, I thought
you were done living.
So, this is it, huh?
You were Whitmore's
pigeon all along.
What did he promise you?
Castle in the sand?
Something more permanent.
Uh.
Not bad for someone
who started off as his trick.
Come on, baby.
Put the gun down.
You came to kill Whitmore, not me.
Where is he?
Buying flowers.
From the moment you sweet-talked
your way into my life,
you were playing double.
You lied about being the client,
and that phony letter
led me to Eddie the Cheese.
Being kidnapped when nobody else
knew where you were.
And Sammy, he wasn't your lover,
or your brother.
He was just a dupe, just like me.
Hell, there was no way to know
I'd go after Whitmore
unless you knew exactly
what this was.
I didn't know it was your kid's toy.
I swear, Malone.
I never told you it was.
[ Toy drops ]
You set me up. Lead me here.
To Whitmore. Why?
Maybe I haven't been
straight with you.
Straight?
Lady, you're a goddamn zigzag.
Now you're gonna help me
get my family back, see.
I let you kiss me, didn't l?
[ Gunfire ]
You're a hard man to kill.
My family.
Your family doesn't want
anything to do with you.
But you already know that.
Don't you, Malone?
Malone's family's dead, Boss.
Yes.
Let's talk about the elephant
in the room, shall we?
Let's talk about the meaning of love.
That's the meaning of love?
Malone's family's not dead.
He made up those stories
so no one could get to them.
See, he knows in our line of work,
the best way to hurt a man
is through the people that he loves,
so he started
moving them around years ago.
But then one day you showed up,
and she was gone.
She didn't even bother to leave you
a note, did she, Malone?
Or were you just too drunk
to read it?
Truth is, they're worth
a whole lot more to you
than you'll ever be to them.
That may be.
But unless you prove my family's safe,
your little carrier pigeon gets it.
Nobody's worth that much to me.
Wrap him up, Boulder.
WHITMORE:
Boulder, you hear me?!
Okay, Whitmore, so you got me.
Why the runaround if all you were
gonna do is kill me, huh?
You've already done it.
You see, you've now murdered
everyone who's ever worked for me,
which means I'm finally free
to take my business legit.
Fuck!
You can't buy respectability,
but you can kill everyone who
knows you've ever been bad.
You murdered my entire syndicate,
took my hapless,
right-hand man hostage,
forced your way
into my humble abode,
even murdered the love of my life.
Now your corpse
is gonna take the fall.
You are a hard man to kill.
But lucky for me,
hard is not the same as impossible.
My wife's no longer around,
so you can't blackmail me anymore.
Boulder!
I quit!
Your son's favorite toy.
You wanna know where I got it?
Huh? You wanna know
where they are?
They're safe, I swear.
I'll prove it to you. I'll prove it.
Give you the rest of the number
when you're out of the ZIP code.
You hear that?
What? Hear what?
Flies.
Blackmailing son of a bitch.
Well...
To not being dead.
-Huh?
-Nah, I got my reasons.
I don't.
See you, sweetheart.
Malone!
So you never really ripped
anyone's heart out?
Let's hope you never find out,
Boulder.
[ Coin slides into pay phone ]
[ Ringing ]
OPERATOR: Please insert 25 cents
for another minute.
We're sorry, your call cannot be
completed as dialed.
Please check the number
and dial again
or call your operator to help you.
The number you have reached
is not in service.
Please insert $1.25
for another eight minutes.
Please be sure you--
[ Woman speaking Japanese ]
Information, how may I help you?
I'm sorry, there's no answer.
Please try your call again later.
[ Ringing ]
CHILD:
Hello? Mom?
WOMAN:
Hello? Hello?
Who's this?
Hello? Malone, is that you?
Hello? Malone? Is that you?
Please say something.
Is that you?
Please, Malone.
Is that you? Hello?