(COUNTRY MUSIC PLAYING ON RADIO)
MOTHER:
You poor, poor young thing.
Running out of gasoIine
on such a hot day.
Yeah, that's my own fauIt, ma'am.
How's that?
WeII, I got a IittIe wasted Iast night.
I did a stupid thing.
- WeII, I got shit-faced.
- Ha-ha-ha.
I stoIe that truck.
Uh....
Went on a IittIe joyride.
A drunk and a thief?
Now, Father.
Let he who is without sin....
You need...
- Ha.
- ...a guiding hand.
You need a famiIy.
You need...
...a thing caIIed Iove.
I need a snapshot.
FATHER:
Oh, for chrissake.
MOTHER:
No.
Scotty?
Scotty, come out here.
Bring your camera.
(GRUNTS)
MOTHER:
Oh, God.
You Ieave Scotty aIone.
Come on, baby, up.
They didn't mean it.
Oh, my baby.
You don't mind, do you?
WeII, actuaIIy, if, uh....
A memento.
FiIthy.
Uh....
MOTHER:
Say cheese.
(SINGING)
Yes, Jesus loves me
Hey, settIe down, boys.
Don't you yeII at me.
- Sons--
- Don't yeII at me.
Where's your mother at?
(SCOTTY BABBLING)
(RV CREAKING)
Oh, fuck.
MOTHER (SINGING) :
Give me that old-time religion
It's good enough for me
Oh, God. Oh! Oh, God.
- Oh, God. Honey, honey, heIp me.
- You son of a....
- You fiIthy sinner.
- HeIp. HeIp.
- HeIp, honey. HeIp.
- You fiIthy sinner.
Oh, yeah. Get him.
You defiIed my souI mate.
Give it to him, baby!
Yes.
(LAUGHING)
- Fornicator.
- Yes, yes, yes!
Oh, baby, do it for Jesus.
(SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY)
MOTHER:
PIease forgive me, Jesus.
(GRUNTING)
Oh, baby, teII him.
FATHER:
We're just doing his wiII.
The Lord Jesus wants us to cIeanse you.
To cast out the demons
that have tainted your immortaI souI.
DRIVER:
You son of....
Sweet Iamb of God!
And if thy hand causeth thee
to faII into sin...
...cut it off.
Yes, Jesus!
(DRIVER SCREAMING)
FATHER: And if thine eye causeth thee
to faII into sin...
...cut it out.
MOTHER:
SmiIe for the camera.
- I am feeIing the spirit, Scotty.
- So sweet.
Come on, boys.
MOTHER:
Oh, come on, boys.
Here we go, boys.
MOTHER:
Come on, pick it up.
SmiIe.
What...?
Oh, my God.
(INAUDIBLE)
GIRL:
Check him out.
I Iove a man in a uniform.
You didn't come back from the fucking
war to party with your parents, did you?
You know, I used to heIp him
with his homework.
Yeah.
Oh, God.
I don't know.
A Iot can happen in 18 months.
Tommy, I know I keep saying this...
- Go ahead.
- ...but we're proud of you.
Thanks, Dad. Mom.
TOM:
Don't worry, IittIe brother.
I will find you.
(MUSIC PLAYING)
MAN: That's crazy.
AII right, I will check you Iater, man.
This is sweet and shit,
but none of this wouId be there--
PeopIe don't have a sense
of history anymore.
Oh, hey. You take this.
Yo, Tom.
(IMITATING GUN FIRING)
WeIcome home,
Captain Shock-And-Awe.
- WeII, thanks, man.
- Yeah.
So, uh, how was it?
Now, come on. No, teII me.
What? Did you get shot at?
You kiII somebody,
eat their heart?
- What?
- AII the above.
JARED:
Yeah.
Wow.
So you and MariIyn...
...together again?
Of course.
Jared, you don't know anything,
do you?
About my IittIe brother?
Oh, no, no. I mean, I know
what everybody eIse does. Right?
Like, Jesse and Nicole...
...took off for Hollywood a year ago,
and they haven't been heard from since.
If you don't get me out of here
right now...
...I am going to go CoIumbine.
Oh.
I am going tomorrow.
What? Where?
CaIifornia.
I got 10 days' R and R. Time enough
to get to HoIIywood and back.
Tom...
...baby, they're dead.
We don't know that.
NicoIe was my best friend.
She wouId have caIIed me.
And your brother,
he wouId have caIIed you, right?
Think you're going to find them?
Cops couIdn't, their parents couIdn't.
They're not me.
Listen, Jesse is my IittIe brother.
I aIways Iooked out for him.
If I wasn't overseas, I--
I'd have gone after him
the minute I heard.
I want you to go with me.
GIRL:
I found him. Come on, guys.
Jeez, dude. I haven't been up this earIy
since high schooI.
WeII, it's good for you.
Anyway, I want to make EI Paso today,
maybe even Las Cruces.
Yes, sir.
(CAR APPROACHING)
MARILYN:
Oh, no.
PIease. No, no, no.
No, Tom.
He's so not coming with us.
I heard that.
Tom is my best friend
and I just want to heIp out.
You are not his best friend.
No, no. I said he's my best friend.
I can't controI who Tom Iikes.
- Like you, for instance.
- I don't mind.
We got a Iot of ground to cover.
We couId use another vehicIe,
but that piece of shit?
Shh. She's going to hear you.
Come on. She can make it.
I know that she can.
If she dies,
you are not riding in this truck.
If she dies aIong the way,
you can bury me with her.
DeaI. Let's get out of here.
I taIked to my cousin, Jake.
He Iives in L. A.
I think he was the Iast
to hear from Jesse.
- WeII, what'd he say?
- Not much.
Jess was Iooking to crash
at his pIace.
ToId him he was on something
caIIed the OId Highway.
I Iooked on the map.
There's nothing caIIed
the OId Highway.
It's weird.
What the heII are you doing?
Enjoying myseIf.
What are you doing?
Jesus Christ, MariIyn,
we will get puIIed over.
Don't be a dork.
I am a corporaI in the U.S. Army,
sweetheart.
You know what couId happen to me
if I got arrested?
Why don't you want to be over here
with the other dinosaurs?
(IN GRAVELLY VOICE)
I don't Iike it with the other dinosaurs.
I don't Iike it at aII. I am going to eat
him if he's over here with me.
That's what I am going to do.
He's asIeep.
It's about damn time.
The kid hasn't shut up
since high schooI.
Oh, it's nice of him to heIp.
You know why he's reaIIy here, right?
Why?
Jared's had a hard-on for NicoIe
since, Iike, second grade.
He thinks if he finds her,
he will finaIIy get Iaid.
(CHUCKLES)
- Oh, good goddamn Iuck.
- I am not kidding.
- MariIyn...
- Hmm?
...are you, uh, gIad I am back?
What do you think?
It must have been heII for you.
Must have been so IoneIy.
You know, I'd understand if, uh,
you partied some whiIe I was gone.
I want you to know that.
Don't worry.
I was a good girI.
I went to this store in DaIIas
and bought a diIdo.
I wrote your name on it
with a marker.
- You didn't.
- I did.
You want to see it?
I packed it.
(MOANS)
(CAR ENGINE REVVING)
(''AMAZING GRACE'' PLAYING ON CAR STEREO)
- Who is this guy?
- I don't know.
- What was that about?
But you get your ass back in bed.
That's an order.
(HUMMING)
Hey, NicoIe.
Big daddy's coming to rescue you.
Yeah.
(CAR BACKFIRES)
(ENGINE RATTLING)
Hey, guys, it's me.
I am burning oiI Iike MariIyn
through a case of beer.
Fuck you, you dweeb.
Oh, whenever you're done with Tom.
Hello?
AII right, there's a gas station up ahead.
We will puII over.
It was just a joke.
I didn't think it was funny.
He didn't mean anything.
I am not some kind of fucking drunk.
He didn't say that.
What do you think?
Ha. I don't even want to
have this conversation.
MAN:
Zip it up, boys.
Zip it up.
Hey, how you doing?
I don't know.
Listen, we're on our way
to CaIifornia.
My buddy here needs some oiI.
Suppose we couId use a fiII-up too.
MAN:
It's seIf-serve.
I never touch the pumps unIess I have to.
Causes cancer in the testicIes.
Thirty-weight, over there.
Bathroom's in the back.
Try our snack bar.
Something tasty for everybody's taste.
- Uh, sh--?
TOM: I will pay for it.
Listen, we're Iooking for somebody.
Might have come through here about a year ago.
They were in a bIue convertibIe,
headed for HoIIywood.
One of them was my brother.
I was hoping you might remember.
MARILYN: Come on, Tommy.
Let's get out of here.
Yeah.
Yeah, I remember.
I remember them aII.
(SIGHS)
Young dreamers, young Iovers.
Heading for the coast,
heading for a new future.
But them.
Them, I remember.
They're stuck in my memory
Iike gum under my chair.
Young.
So young.
But, hey...
...for 22.95...
...I will teII you everything.
MARILYN:
Oh, for God's sake.
Tom, can we pIease
get out of here now?
Just teII me what the fuck you know.
They were Iost.
Babes in the woods.
Lambs to the sIaughter.
I tried.
I tried to steer them away.
I did.
I reaIIy did, I swear.
What did you teII them?
I toId them I'd seen a Iot of shit,
and they'd better watch their asses...
...or they'd end up shit
under somebody's shoe.
And what did Jesse say to that?
My brother, what did he say?
He toId me to have sexuaI reIations
with myseIf.
TOM:
That's not a bad idea.
JARED:
This is hers.
I swear. This....
This is NicoIe's.
I remember when she won this for riding.
We were, Iike, 11 .
MARILYN:
You remember?
Yeah, I remember.
Ugh. Dude, you're such a joke.
Where did you get this?
I don't know.
Where?
Where did you get it?
You know what? I do remember.
I know, yeah.
I, uh--
About a year ago,
I found it on the OId Highway.
What OId Highway?
There's no OId Highway on the map.
You got to know where it is.
WiII you show me?
Sure.
It's about a miIe up that way.
You can't miss it.
JARED:
How much?
It's on the house.
Thanks.
Tom, come on.
Who's the most awesome guy?
Jared's the most awesome guy.
(GRUNTS)
(STOMACH RUMBLING)
Hey, yo, it's me. I got to puII over.
TOM:
Fuck, Jared. Not more oiI.
No, I have to, uh, go to fudge town.
(LAUGHS)
A IittIe too much information, dude.
(JARED IMITATES FARTING)
JARED:
Oh, sorry.
Oh, it's terrible.
We're cIose to a rest stop.
I just saw a sign.
It can't wait.
Breakfast gave me the McShitties.
I will catch up with you.
Oh....
(GRUNTS)
My gosh. Shit.
Shit.
(YELPS)
TOM: The next services
are miIes up the road.
I am betting they at Ieast
made a pit stop here.
Yeah, weII, if I know NicoIe,
she sure wouIdn't pee in the dirt.
- Hey, Tom?
- Yeah.
Nothing.
Shit.
LiteraIIy.
KIingons, perfect.
(CAR APPROACHING)
The fuck?
What the fuck? Fuck, dude.
Sir?
It's occupied.
Jesus Christ.
(ENGINE REVVING)
Oh, shit.
Oh, fuck.
Damn it.
Jesus Christ.
It's occupied. It's occupied.
I am aImost done. I am aImost done.
I swear it.
(GASPING)
As soon as Jared gets here,
you think we couId find a moteI?
I couId use a IittIe minibar action.
AII right. I guess I will use the faciIities.
(DOOR OPENS)
Tommy?
(WOMAN CRYING)
Hey, are you okay?
(TOM READS SIGN)
(''AMAZING GRACE'' PLAYING IN DISTANCE)
(ENGINE REVS)
WOMAN:
Jesse.
I am so sorry, Jesse.
I am so sorry.
Did I hear you say Jesse?
(MARKER SQUEAKING)
NicoIe?
What the fuck?
''KZL-303.''
''NicoIe''? Oh, my God.
(CRASHING)
(WOMAN GRUNTING)
What the fuck?
Tom?
Tom.
I don't Iike this.
(BEEPING)
(''AMAZING GRACE'' PLAYS OVER PHONE)
What the fuck?
Oh, come on. Come on.
Just steIIar.
Guys, it's Jared.
Can you hear me?
It's Jared. PIease come in.
Thanks for the ride.
Oh, my....
NicoIe. Oh....
What happened to you?
It's been, Iike, a year.
Nobody's heard anything.
Oh, you Iook Iike shit.
What happened?
YeIIow truck.
The driver....
He took me to the bus.
Who the heII are you?
You're getting yourseIf
into a shitIoad of troubIe.
You know that?
You hear me?
You hear me?!
Look at me, you fuck!
What do you think you're doing, huh?
What do you think this is?
Did you do something
to my brother, you fuck?
Say something to me,
you sack of shit!
I said, say something!
What the...?
(TOY GUN BEEPING)
Ah.
AII right.
Here we go.
Let me take a Iook.
''KZL 303.''
- What the heII is that supposed to mean?
- I missed you.
ReaIIy?
I missed you too.
I have aIways missed you.
Ever since the sixth grade...
...when you sat next to me...
...I have aIways kind of Iiked you.
I thought you Ioved me.
Of course. I just never thought,
in, Iike, a miIIion years...
...that you and I
wouId ever have a chance.
Oh, Jess.
Uh-- He was a good guy.
Is. Is a good guy.
I mean, Tom and MariIyn,
they're out Iooking for him right now.
But I came because of you.
And whoever did this to you
is one sick fuck.
Pardon my French.
I will kiII him.
Huh?
The driver, we will kiII him
for what he did to you.
The bathroom thing?
No, no. That's, Iike, nothing
compared to what he did to you.
We will kiII him.
First, we got to get you to a hospitaI.
- Then we're going to go to the cops.
- No, no, no.
I tried the cops. I tried everything.
- Don't you see?
- Uh-huh.
Ends here.
- Ends here.
- Shh.
Ends here, ends here.
NicoIe. NicoIe.
Hey, easy, easy, easy.
Come on, come on.
(SOBBING)
I will protect you.
Jesse.
Uh--
You know what we have to do?
We have to go. We have to go.
Tom and MariIyn,
they're Iooking for us.
They're at the rest stop.
(GROANING)
Hey.
AsshoIe.
Listen to me.
I am a corporaI in the U.S. Army.
They're going to be Iooking for me...
...and they're going to find you...
...and you're going to be fucked.
You understand?
So you better Iet me go right now!
Hey, I am taIking to you.
(GRUNTING)
(DRILL WHIRS)
My brother was here, wasn't he?
Jesse, my IittIe brother.
You hurt him, didn't you?
Just teII me, you fucker!
Did you kiII my brother?
TeII me!
(WHIRS)
(CHUCKLING)
Then you better kiII me, fucker.
Don't you fucking dare!
You hear me?
No.
No, no, no.
I will kiII you-- No!
Fuck! Fucker!
(SCREAMING)
I wiII fucking kiII you!
Jesse.
It's Jared.
Oh, Jesse.
NicoIe.
Jesse.
Oh, my God.
He's got Tom too.
He's got Tom in the bus.
What?
Ends here.
Ends here, ends here, ends here.
NicoIe.
Oh, Jesus.
Jesus! Jesus!
NicoIe?
NicoIe? Wh--?
Okay.
Everything's going to be okay.
(ENGINE SPUTTERING)
Goddamn it.
You're Ietting me down, bitch!
So far, this trip sucks.
(CAR APPROACHING)
Hey, hey. Hey, pIease, pIease, pIease.
Thank you.
Wow.
My car just, Iike, died back there.
The smeII, I am so sorry.
Uh, I feII....
This guy, Iike, tried to kiII me. I....
- PopsicIe?
- No, no, thank you.
Such a hot day.
Be nice to have something cooI
to suck on.
Better take it, son.
Sure.
Scotty, PopsicIe.
Thanks, Scotty.
MOTHER:
There, isn't that nice?
You said someone
tried to faciIitate your demise?
Yeah. Um....
This dude in, Iike,
a big yeIIow truck and--
FATHER: YeIIow truck?
- Mm-hm.
Did you see
who was behind the wheeI?
- Did you see?
- No, not reaIIy.
It was some Dukes of Hazzard reject.
Then you must be a sinner, boy.
Otherwise he wouIdn't be on your ass.
- He was one too.
- What?
The one behind the wheeI, the driver?
He was a sinner once, Iike you.
A fornicator.
His souI as bIack as coaI.
- We cIeansed him.
- He got what he deserved.
And then he gave us
what we deserved.
(LAUGHING)
Look, aII that I know is that
some asshoIe tried to kiII me, okay?
Hey, I think we're reaIIy cIose
to the rest stop now.
You can just Iet me out,
I will go find my friends.
(FATHER LAUGHING)
He's going to Iike you, boy.
You're a dirty boy, aren't you?
Dirty boys must be cIeansed.
It onIy hurts for an instant.
What onIy hurts?
What are you taIking about?
Show him, my sons.
And if thine eye causeth thee
to faII into sin, cut it out.
Thanks for the ride, you freaks.
Jared, what are you doing?
That's our ride.
No, I don't think so.
It's a bunch of wackos.
I don't care.
I just want to get the heII out of here.
- Where is Tom?
- He's gone.
What do you mean, gone?
I went into the bathroom,
and when I came out...
...Tom, the car, just vanished.
- WeII, that's fucking weird.
- Yeah.
And that's not the onIy thing.
I can't go in there. It's the girIs' room.
You're not going to suddenIy sprout tits,
aII right, Jared?
Oh....
You know, I didn't know
that girIs couId be this yucky.
AII right, Iisten to me, okay?
I don't think that this is how it is.
I think that this is how it was.
What the fuck are you taIking about?
Look, the first time that I came in here,
it was nice and cIean and new.
And I thought I saw NicoIe, okay?
I thought I saw her tag this staII.
Look at it.
Jared, Iook at it.
What do you think,
I am drunk off my ass and seeing shit?
No, I don't.
I saw her too.
(GASPS)
(GRUNTING)
Fuck.
(GROANING)
(GRUNTING)
Fuck!
What the fuck?
What the fuck? We're seeing ghosts.
- Why is that so hard to beIieve?
- Yeah, Iike, a ghost bathroom?
Jared, aII I can do
is beIieve what I saw.
Okay? This bathroom is as reaI
as NicoIe was.
And she was so reaI,
you couId reach out and touch her.
You know what I am taIking about.
Are you fucking bIushing,
you IittIe weenie?
Oh, my God, you are.
What did you do with her, dude?
It's nobody's business.
Wow, you finaIIy get Iaid,
onIy the chick's dead.
I don't want to taIk about it.
It's personaI.
Wait, she toId you
Tom was on the bus?
- What does that mean?
- I don't know.
WeII, she wrote
that some psycho took Jesse.
The driver.
- Maybe the bus is his IittIe pIaypen.
- CouId be.
But she didn't say where it was?
''Ends here.''
That's what she said, ''Ends here.''
We got to find that bus.
We got to save Tom.
No, wait, wait, wait.
We're going to wait right here...
...untiI somebody comes aIong
and caII the poIice.
That gas station, remember?
With that crazy oId guy.
- We can waIk there.
- No, that's, Iike, 60 miIes from here....
Come on, it's just over here.
The road goes around these hiIIs,
but it's reaIIy just over there.
TeII me you're not thinking
about hiking.
It's the middIe of the night.
Don't be a fucking pussy.
I am not being a pussy,
there are snakes.
There are tarantuIas.
There are inbred zombie cannibaIs.
God knows what eIse is out there.
Fuck it.
MariIyn, there couId be
another expIanation for aII this.
- Like what?
- Here, here.
Maybe it's, Iike,
some kind of mass psychosis.
You and me got, Iike,
a mind meId going.
Read my mind, Jared.
Shut the fuck up.
I can do that. Sure.
(MAN GROANING)
- Shh. Jared, Jesus.
- Sorry.
HoIy shit.
That's the fucking truck.
- What the heII is that?
- I took it out of Tom's, come on.
So, what are you going to do?
You're going to, Iike, shoot the driver?
Yes, if we have to.
MARILYN:
There's nobody in there.
Maybe he ran off.
No, maybe he's in there. Come here.
Jesus, he kiIIed him.
- What?
MARILYN: Aah! Jesus.
Goddamn it. You just scared
the shit out of me, you asshoIe.
You're the asshoIe.
- You fucked my nap.
- AII right, sorry, sorry, sorry.
Cash register's open. Uh....
Take everything.
Just don't hurt me, okay?
We're not here to rob you. We want to
know where that customer is outside.
Customer? I got a customer?
- Where is he?
MARILYN: That's what we want to know.
- I think he took my boyfriend.
- He tried to kiII me on the toiIet.
- You're shitting me.
- No, he's not.
So he didn't come in here?
You haven't seen him anywhere?
You're the onIy one to disturb
my sIumber and my supper.
Fuck your supper.
He's got to be here somewhere, right?
I mean, do you have a bathroom?
- Locked, out back.
- Do you have a phone?
Our ceIIs are dead.
Yeah, got a pay phone.
In the garage.
(CLICKS)
HeIIo. HeIIo.
MAN: Hello?
- Yeah, is this 911 ?
(MAN LAUGHING)
- Is this 911 ?
- 911.
- Great. Okay, my name is Jared Schnoz.
- Schnoz.
We're at a gas station,
right near the CaIifornia border.
My friends and I think that, um,
our friend might have been kidnapped.
Friend? Kidnapped?
Yes, his name is Tom.
- Tom HiIts.
- Tom.
Is this reaIIy 911 ?
- Who the heII is this?
- Tom.
Tom.
- Listen, fucker.
- Do you know something about this?
- Fucker? Ha-ha-ha.
Yeah? WeII, fuck you.
Where's Tom?
What did you do with him?
Fuck you. Ha-ha-ha.
(MAN GROANING)
Jess?
- Jesse.
- No!
It's me. It's me. Jesse, Jesse.
It's Tommy. It's big bother.
It's Tommy.
It's me.
I found you, you IittIe shit.
I knew you weren't dead.
I wouIdn't Iet you be dead.
Tommy? Is that...?
- Is that you, Tommy?
- Jess.
Are you Tommy? Is that you?
What did he do?
(YELLING)
- What are you hoping to find?
- I don't fucking know.
This fucker's Iicense, registration,
maybe the address for that fucking bus.
- I wouIdn't do that if I was you.
- Yeah.
What if he comes back?
What if he finds you messing around
in that truck? What if he gets mad?
That's what this is for.
He gets mad,
you bIow his fucking baIIs off.
PIease, pIease.
That's private property.
Put it back. Right now. Put it back.
Son of a bitch. He took Jesse.
He took NicoIe,
and now he's got Tom.
(KNOCKING ON WINDOW)
MariIyn.
- What?
- Check it out.
There's bIood.
- Oh, my God.
- What?
- Jared, show me.
I saw this on Court TV
about seriaI kiIIers.
They take trophies. They're fetishistic.
- This is Iike some sexuaI thing.
- Ugh.
You're right. He probabIy
just spanked aII over that stuff.
Gross.
Oh, Lord. Oh, Lord.
Oh, the eyes.
- The eyes.
- What?
What are you taIking about?
What about the eyebaIIs?
Nothing, I don't know nothing.
JESSE:
He said that I was a sinner.
The driver?
No, the preacher.
Preacher? Who the heII is he?
I don't know. He seemed to work
for the driver, I guess.
So I'd wake up and there they'd be.
The preacher, his wife...
...and their kids.
He brought his famiIy...
...to fuck you up?
They'd aIways stand around and pray.
They said they were heIping me.
HeIping you what?
Get to heaven.
And how the fuck
were they going to do that?
I never knew when they were coming,
and then you'd hear the Winnebago.
- Winnebago?
- The famiIy's.
And then he'd bring me casseroIes.
I fucking hate casseroIes.
(CHUCKLES)
- And then....
- Fuck.
The driver wouId
drag me out of here...
...and the preacher wouId start praying,
and then the fun wouId begin.
Don't buIIshit me.
You know something,
something about the eyebaIIs.
Try our snack bar. Tasty.
For everybody's taste.
You know everything
that goes on, on this road.
I will bet you know aII about this driver--
Where he is, what he wants.
....and you're going to teII me.
No, I swear.
TeII me everything.
Everything you know,
or I wiII shoot your fucking ass.
Do you understand?
I try to warn them. I try.
But he hears.
He knows.
I got to be carefuI.
I got to be very carefuI.
- Who the heII is he?
- It's not who.
It's what.
There's an oId Indian Iegend.
If you're buried
without your eyebaIIs...
...your spirit is cursed
to wander the earth.
RestIess, Iost, in pain forever.
You're saying
that the driver's a ghost?
And that someone
took his eyebaIIs too?
That's exactIy what I am saying.
You know, I tried to find them one day,
his baby bIues.
I wanted to find them.
I wanted to put him to rest.
Put him to rest?
Burn the eyebaIIs.
The smoke wiII rise to heaven.
His spirit wiII foIIow.
AII right, we got to find Tom, find this
bus. Do you have a car that works?
Yeah.
- Tow truck.
- Get it.
Take us to the next town,
we got to get the cops up here.
I hate to say it, but I toId you so.
Get the tow truck.
- Where the fuck is the truck?
- I don't know, Jared.
There's not even any tire tracks.
MARILYN:
Ghost driver, ghost truck.
Whatever. We're going to get the fuck
out of here, right? Doesn't matter.
(MAN YELLS)
(CRASHING)
Oh, shit.
Wait, wait, wait.
If it is a ghost, do you think a gun...?
Come on, Scooby-Doo,
Iet's find the mystery bus.
I think it was a van.
Hey, mister?
HeIIo?
Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
MARILYN:
Oh, shit.
He's here somewhere. AII right.
There, there, there! There he is!
(MAN MOANING)
Did you get him?
No, it's not him.
It's the gas-station guy.
Then who's this?
Jared?
(GRUNTING)
You aII right?
JESSE:
That's yours.
That's your truck.
- Come on, Iet's go.
- Shit.
I got you.
Oh, no.
Oh, God.
Okay. Good.
Uh....
He wants you to understand.
- Understand what?
- Your duties.
Look, pIease,
just pIease don't Iet him hurt me.
No. No, don't you get it?
No, he doesn't want to hurt you.
He....
He wants you to hurt her.
MARILYN:
No.
What?
(SOBBING)
He thinks she's a sinner.
- And he wants you to cIeanse her.
MARILYN: No.
No. No way. No fucking way.
He knows she was unfaithfuI, okay?
When her soIdier boy was off at war...
...she took soIace in drink...
...and in the company of men.
I won't hurt her.
I was afraid you'd say that.
No, pIease.
(SCREAMING)
(SOBBING)
TOM: I wish the goddamn ceII phone
worked.
I can't wait to caII Mom.
It's been reaIIy hard on her,
you know.
I thought about you every day, man.
Once, I couId have sworn I saw you.
We were running a checkpoint
in Buhriz.
It's just outside of Baghdad.
A car goes through,
I see you sitting in the back seat.
(CHUCKLES)
You don't think moments Iike that.
What the fuck
wouId you be doing in Iraq?
It was, uh, just a kid.
Had a jacket Iike yours.
You know, the red one?
You shouId have saved me.
Huh?
You're my brother.
You shouId have saved me.
I did save you, shithead.
What are you taIking about?
(SOBBING)
You're not going to, Jared.
You're just not going to do it.
JARED:
Oh, my God.
Jared, you're not going to.
You're just not going to.
Oh, my God.
Jared, pIease. Jared, pIease.
You don't have to do this.
- You don't have to do this.
JARED: I am sorry. I am sorry.
Leave him aIone!
Jared, don't you fucking dare do it.
Jared, don't you dare.
Jared, don't you dare!
- I am sorry.
- Jared, no!
- No, Jared.
I can't. I can't.
(GASPING)
- I can't.
- Fuck you!
Jared, no, no.
(SCREAMING)
JARED:
Oh, my God.
I am so sorry.
AII right!
(JESSE COUGHING)
You aII right?
I prayed for you...
...to save me.
- You never came.
- What the fuck are you taIking about?
Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
Jess.
Jess. Jess, hoId on.
- I will get you to a hospitaI.
- You shouId have saved me.
What?
Jesse!
(SOBBING)
MariIyn?
- MariIyn?
- Tommy.
- I am here, baby. I am here.
- You were on the bus?
- Yeah.
- Is there any sign of your brother?
- My brother's dead.
So is NicoIe.
And they took Jared. I am sorry.
TOM:
We got to get you some heIp.
I am going to be fine.
Let's just get home, okay?
- Oh, my God.
- What is it?
Oh, my God.
This is it. That's what NicoIe
was trying to teII Jared.
Ends here.
- This is it. This is where we shouId Iook.
- MariIyn.
- They must be here somewhere.
- What?
- His eyes.
- The fuck you taIking about?
The driver. Burn his eyes
and we can put him down.
(CAR APPROACHING)
- I got this guy.
- Tom.
Tom.
Jared?
Jared, what happened to you?
The famiIy made me dinner.
It's casseroIe.
Okay, Iisten to me, okay? Jared.
Jared, Iisten.
The driver's eyes--
Look at me!
....they're here somewhere.
Okay, we have to find them
and burn them.
Jared, you check out here.
(CLICKS)
Oh, shit. I think I might have it,
I think I might.... Ugh.
Oh, God.
- You find anything?
- Nothing.
Me either.
How do you burn
somebody's eyes, anyway?
That will do.
Wait, how am I going to Iight that?
- Wait.
- Jared, just find them.
Fuck.
What the fuck?
- He's gone. He's just fucking gone.
- Tom!
- What?
- They're there. Here's a picture of them.
JARED:
The twins.
The twins have the eyes.
Tom, Iook out!
Open up.
(YELLING)
Thanks for the fucking ride.
Tom.
Tom. Baby, it's over.
Come on.
(MUSIC PLAYING ON HEADPHONES)
What the...?
Goddamn it.
Maybe he went on ahead.
It's just not Iike him.
And that car of his....
I drove practicaIIy the whoIe way back.
It's weird.
(MARILYN SOBBING)
MariIyn.
I know this has been heII for you.
We did the right thing.
We stopped the bad guy...
...even if this whoIe thing
was compIeteIy fucking crazy.
MariIyn, pIease stop crying.
You shouId have saved me.
(''AMAZING GRACE'' PLAYING)
The fuck?
You shouId have saved me.
I don't fucking beIieve it.
Tom, heIp me.
MariIyn.
MariIyn!
(ENGLISH SDH)