Shared by http://DJJ.HOME.SAPO.PT/
That one's not ours.
You sure?
I authorize all cadavers
and associated research.
He's not ours.
People donate their
body to science,
end up submerged in a pond?
Cram med in a car?
Body farm; creepy.
A body farm
is not creepy.
It's a controlled study of
situational decomposition.
All in all,
a very helpful place.
Tell that to Slim
hanging from the tree.
Whoever placed our victim here
knew that the body farm existed.
What they didn't know
is each body
is tracked by
a bunch of scientists.
Can't just slip a card
into the deck.
Well, he's not in rigor.
TSD is under six hours.
I'll move him as soon as
you're finished.
- Any I.D.? - None.
Okay, then move him.
Gunshot wound to the chest.
Well, look.
One of your friends.
It's a carpet beetle.
It shouldn't be here.
Vic seem more like a hardwood floors kind
Carpet beetles are the last
to arrive at a corpse...
when it's almost a skeleton.
I mean, this guy's still fresh.
David, get this body
out of here now!
We got cross-contamination!
Wow! You got to go
to the body farm?
Yeah.
I've always wanted
to go there.
What was it like?
Quiet.
I hear Grissom
goes there all the time.
Like, even on his nights off.
Why does that
not surprise me?
Man, something stinks
in here again.
What, bad milk?
Cottage- cheese bad?
Worse. It's all
over my sandwich.
Smell that.
Yeah.
He's got one of his
experiments in there.
You're kidding me?
Bugs or blood?
Not bugs.
Oh, that's so not cool. That's a community
Someone has got to talk
to Grissom about this.
Talk to me about what?
You leaving your
experiments in our
refrigerator.
The lab fridge was full. I put in last night.
I'm going to test for horizontal motion
on bloodstains.
Vis-a-vis surface
textures.
Hey, any of you guys got
any linoleum at home?
That blood
is rank, man.
That's why the Red Cross
gives it to us...
'cause it's past
its expiration date.
Anything new on the
body farm victim?
I gave the prints
to Identification.
They're running through
the base s now.
Okay.
I'll be in autopsy. Let me know.
Way to go, Nick. You really told him.
I told him. He just...
doesn't hear it.
Yeah.
Well...
the entry wound tells me
the body sustained a projectile.
A bullet.
But there's no bullet
fragments in the tissue,
and no exit wound.
So, how do
you explain that?
Bullet wounds usually
leave bullet evidence.
There's no evidence
of a bullet in this wound tract.
So, let's excise it.
Do a more
localized search.
That was my next suggestion.
What's your best tool for excising the tissue
of our Mr. Doe?
Oh, it's not a John Doe anymore.
Database says
that our victim
is Mike Kimble,
age 38.
He has a townhouse
in Summerlin.
Brass is going to
meet us there along with the rest of the unit.
My bet says that it's
the primary crime scene.
Good.
Aren't you coming?
We're excising
a wound tract.
Sounds fascinating.
It is.
Is that Mike Kimble's house?
That's it.
Seems like somebody
beat us here.
You think?
Neighbor called it in.
She smelled the smoke.
Thought he was barbecuing
in his living room.
Where's his neighbor now?
Over there talking to Brass.
Um... no, I didn't hear any
noise coming from Mike's place last night.
But, um...
I was wearing my headphones,
doing my workout.
Did Mr. Kimble have many
visitors to his house?
Other than his clients,
just, um...
just his fiancé, Jane.
Uh... but they usually
stayed at her place.
Do you have the full name
and address of the victim's fiancé, Jane?
Yes, actually, I do.
It's in my kitchen.
As soon as they let me back in,
I can get for you.
Something...
a metal fragment.
It's not like any bullet
I've ever seen.
Titanium...
maybe a pin.
From the ribs?
Oh, here's
the manufacturer's number.
I should've bought stock
when I first started finding
all these medical implants.
Bovine.
Excuse me?
Genus Hypaderma.
These are normally found
in the intestinal tract of cows.
These maggots aren't
found in humans.
Foreign tissue. Cow.
Makes absolutely no sense.
The body farm also studies
animals, not just humans.
This more of your
cross-contamination?
Only one way to find out.
What up, Doc?
Hey, there you are.
Sorry I'm late.
D.A. Wanted an update
on my robbery case.
Oh, it's all good. I'm just starting
my walk-through.
The desk is crispy.
There's a burn pattern for you.
Fire burns upward.
This is moving downward.
Defies the laws of physics.
Fire's draw n to fire.
Well, you know
what we got to do.
Check out the upstairs?
Well, the guy
who started the fire
wanted to make sure the
bedroom got it worse.
How do you know it's a guy?
Why are you jumping the gun?
Well, according to Sara,
94% of all arsonists
are male.
Yeah, that sounds
like Sara.
The fire burned longest here.
It's the point of origin
right here.
I don't smell any accelerant.
Could have burned off.
Fabric would have fueled it.
I don't know.
It doesn't make any sense.
Afire burning downward?
Must have found an accelerant.
Furniture polish.
Warrick...
Is that blood?
Oh, man.
Something bad happened here.
This fire is just a cover-up.
Are you serious?
Hold on a second. Hi.
I'm Detective Jim Brass.
Is Jane Bradley in?
She's in the kitchen.
Really? No.
This can't be happening.
Mike is dead?
I don't know how
I'm going to tell my kids.
They love Mike.
You and Mike were engaged?
The wedding was supposed to
be in a week at the Tangiers.
No sweets after 10:00.
What's the rule?
Oh, come on, Mom,
I'm starving.
Have an apple.
He's growing
like a weed.
What was your
fiancé's business?
He was a photographer.
He did weddings, events.
We argued over who'd
do our wedding because
he didn't trust
anyone else's work.
Hi.
How many times have I said you have to
You can't just
barge in this house.
Maybe as many times
as I've asked you
to have the kids
ready and out front
on my nights?
You must be the ex-husband.
What's going on?
Are the kids
all right?
Is Jake in some kind of trouble?
No.
Mike Kimble was
killed tonight.
Are you serious?
Would you mind
showing us your hands?
My hands? Why?
To see if there's any gunpowder
or evidence of a burn on them.
Sure.
Look, uh... I don't
want to be rude, but...
I stop paying alimony the day
Mike and Jane get married.
I mean, I'm the last person
who would have killed him.
If we wanted to get in touch
with you,
how would we reach you?
You can reach me at any of my four grocery
Anytime.
We'll be in touch.
I'm going to get the kids,
if that's all right.
They're in the den.
Accelerant.
Hey.
Yeah, Warrick said
the fire was orange,
so low-temperature fuel.
Something accessible...
gasoline, kerosene...
I thought you
were in post.
I was.
So, anyway, this is where
the fire started.
Victim's bedroom.
Grissom...
Gris...
Sometimes it's about
where the fire
isn't.
Sometimes I hate this job.
We have evidence
that Mike
may have had
an inappropriate
relationship
with your daughter.
What kind of evidence?
Photographic
and definitive.
That the man
I was going to marry
somehow sexually...
No, I don't believe that.
Things like
this happen...
sometimes right
under our noses.
We're going to have to talk with your
Jody, we found pictures
in Mike's house
of you posing.
Tell her Mike would
never do anything
to hurt you.
In some of the pictures...
He truly was like
a father to both kids.
I wish you would
just listen once.
In some of the pictures,
you're wearing a bathing suit.
Do you remember
Mike taking them?
Jody...
Anything that he did to you
was not your fault.
You can tell me
if Mike took
those pictures.
Jody?
Honey?
I loved Mike
and he loved me.
The daughter clammed up.
Seems to be in the
protect-the-abuser trap.
I'm going to take her
over to the hospital
for a SART exam.
What are the chances Mom knew what her
I've seen it happen.
As a mother,
I hope not.
Yeah, right.
I'm going
to look into it.
Well, our photo guys tell me
those pictures were taken
with Mike Kimble's
type of camera.
Yeah?
Yeah.
What are you
doing here?
A thousand points
of light,
and I only need one
to clear up this picture.
The blur equals
the length of the light.
If I can compress this light
back into a point,
then the rest of the picture
gets clear.
That's how they got
Hinkley's image
when he was shooting the prez.
What is that...
there...
bottom right corner?
Is that a finger?
Yeah, I think so.
Well, that's unusual, isn't it?
A professional photographer
gets a finger in the shot?
Maybe his good hand
was otherwise engaged.
I'm going to work
on that for a while
and see if I can get
some ridge detail.
Maybe even a fat print.
I'll... I'll see you later.
All right.
So this is your experiment, huh?
So, because you found beef in
the wound tracts of the victim,
you think the meat might be
from one of the body farm cows?
Did the fly find
the beef in the wound
and lay its eggs,
or did it bring
the beef with him?
I did an experiment similar
to this in San Francisco,
except the cross-contamination
was blood.
Wasn't a murder case,
but it was instructional.
None of these
beef particles
are as big as the tissue found in Mike
Kimble's
And I found out
the ex-husband
is the proud owner
of a registered handgun.
Hmm. What
does that mean?
It means I need
to see that gun.
Uh... Grissom?
Aren't you going
to tell me anything?
About?
The case, the meat,
what you found...?
I'm working it.
I thought I was
working it with you.
Yes.
You're right,
you are.
So, take some photos
of the experiment for the D.A.,
and then get rid
of that stuff.
That meat... the raw meat... me?
Yeah.
How many meals
have we shared together?
I don't know.
Take a guess...
over a year working together.
.30
I'm a vegetarian.
Everyone here knows
I haven't eaten meat since we stayed up
It pains me to see ground beef;
forget about cleaning it up.
Okay.
Have Nick do it.
You're telling me
this bastard took
pictures of my daughter?
We found them
in his house.
I never liked the way
he looked at Jody.
I never liked it.
How did he look at her?
Touchy - feely.
It wasn't normal.
I told Jane when
she started seeing him,
he's not a good guy.
He's not good for our family.
But you can't control
who your ex-wife dates.
Russ Bradley,
Gil Grissom, CSI Lab.
Thanks for coming in.
Is this your gun?
Yes.
May I take a look at it?
Please.
It's been cleaned.
Of course.
You never store
a dirty firearm.
May I ask what kind
of ammunition you use?
A.38 special.
It takes.38s.
Whatever's on sale.
There you are.
Got something
for you from Trace.
Sara?
Almost finished.
They isolated
the accelerant
used in the fire.
It's alcohol-based.
Acetone,
methyl methacrylate?
Nail polish remover.
Guess that's
the six percent
no one talks about...
female fire-starters.
What's this... a burn?
Yeah.
How'd that happen?
On a curling iron.
I'll give you
a prescription
for antibiotics.
Let's do the last portion
of your exam now, okay?
Excuse me.
Okay, lay back.
Scoot back
a little more.
Just a little more.
Very good.
Take a deep breath.
This won't
hurt at all.
It's melting.
Sara's not going
to be too happy
with that
experiment
in the fridge.
I'm putting it
in the freezer.
The doctor finished
the exam on Jody Bradley.
Physical findings:
Scarring,
chronic sexual abuse.
Well, have Brass get a warrant for the
Check the evidence we recovered from the
They stayed in both places.
Listen, there's a good chance the
She had second-degree burns on her wrist.
One thing at a time.
Right.
You coming with?
I can't.
Take Nick.
Right.
Experiment.
That's the girl's
nightgown.
We've got some samples coming in.
They're priority one.
What is that... what did you find?
Child Services will be remanding Jody to a
Was my fiancé involved in any way?
He's not your fiancé.
Not anymore, anyway.
Jim?
I just got back from the events office at the
where you and Mike were supposed
to be married.
You canceled your wedding five days ago.
I even have your
credit card receipt for the ten percent
You didn't like the way he looked at your
No. I just got cold feet.
Convenient timing.
Look, when Russ and I got
married 20 years ago,
you couldn't find
two happier people,
and now we can barely stand to be civil.
I didn't want to make another mistake.
It wasn't that you sensed
what was going on?
Mike would not do
what he's being accused of.
Believe me.
I'll believe the DNA.
Feels like blackjack, you know?
You guys all fanned around the table,
waiting to see which card I'll reveal next.
Greg, this is an abuse case
involving a minor.
Right. Sorry.
So, I have DNA samples from every male
that lives with Jody Bradley,
full-time or weekends.
First, I have Mike Kimble, the fiancé
Dead fiancé
"Match not found."
You got to be kidding me.
Sorry, Captain.
The guy has naked pictures of her in his
The mother called off their wedding.
DNA takes a pair.
So whose is it, the father?
"Match not found."
Third and last.
Give me that.
How did we miss that?
No. No, I never did
anything like that to my sister. No.
How do you explain your semen on
I can't... I can't.
The county automatically
provides your son
with an advocate.
We can't proceed
until he arrives.
You getting anywhere with the print?
I'm still trying
to enhance it.
It's kind of frustrating,
that, uh...
this picture puts us at the very moment of
but we can't see
what she's seeing.
They say the eyes are the window to the
Yeah, my grandma used to say that all the
In a way, it's true.
The aqueous fluid and the
vitreous in the human eye
allows for an image to be reflected in it.
Well, maybe... if I enhanced the reflection in
with the right combination of algorithms...
I think my Popsicles are ready.
Jake, did you take pictures of your sister
and plant them in Mike Kimble's house?
No.
You do have keys
to his house, though. Right?
I mean, your mother told us that both you
Yes, but I didn't
plant anything.
He didn't take the pictures. He didn't plant
He has no idea how his DNA got in his
Yeah, maybe a little hobbit put it there.
That's it, we're done.
All right, hold on.
You mind if I talk to Jake alone?
To what end?
I have a hunch.
Everyone does it, Jake.
You just... feel like you're the only one.
Then, when you don't do it,
it happens in your sleep anyway, right?
Yeah. And then you go to take a leak,
dust off the equipment,
you just grab the first thing that's handy,
It was just... on the hamper.
Your sister's nightgown?
The next thing I know, I'm getting, like...
questioned by the police
and my parents are looking at me
like I'm some sort of...
pervert.
Yeah, that's rough. Rough.
Well, listen, in the future, dude...
even if the situation's
embarrassing,
the truth's probably the best policy there.
Yeah.
Hey, listen, you
ever notice your mom's boyfriend
acting weird around your sister?
Like a little, uh...
too friendly,
too forward?
Mmm, no.
No. I mean, my sister is
the one that's kind of weird.
Really?
Yeah.
How?
She's just always just,
you know,
"Mike's coming over.
I can't wait
till Mike gets here."
Mm-hmm. Yeah.
You like the guy?
When, uh... my parents
were getting divorced,
my mom, she cried,
like, every day,
and, uh, Mike showed up
and she stopped crying
so, yeah. I guess.
What are you doing here?
Isn't this your day off?
On the day you plan
to expend a meat bullet?
Frozen?
Yeah, I had to freeze it with
a touch of liquid nitrogen.
Well, I'm ready
to watch history.
Bullet-like entry wound.
The meat disintegrates.
Lost in
the soft tissue. Hmm.
You're quite
a marksman, Russ.
And inventive... you managed
to build a bullet made of meat.
The meat from the projectile
was visually indistinguishable
from the victim's
stomach tissue.
We know that
your gun was clean
but it turns out
that your reloader wasn't.
Yeah. We got this from
your garage on a warrant.
We figured a gun enthusiast like yourself
Packs gunpowder
into used shell casings.
Cheaper than buying
new rounds, right?
The material that
was on your reloader
is consistent with
the material we found
in the victim's wound tract.
Ground beef.
A father knows.
He was giving her gifts...
you know, cameras.
He gave her a camera?
And the wedding was,
like, a week off,
and he was going
to be living
under the same roof as
my children full-time.
When I went over there,
you know, I was just going
to set him straight, right?
You know what he says?
Hey, I can't help it
if she likes me.
I guess it's like
mother, like daughter.
You touch my little girl,
and I will kill you.
Too late.
That's when I lost it.
Then you dumped him
at the body farm.
Your grocery chain makes
regular meat deliveries there
for experimental purposes.
Then what?
You arsoned his place
to cover up the murder?
Grabbed the nail polish remover
from the bedside table,
poured it all over the place?
I'll tell you the truth.
I...
I feel relieved.
I'd like to make
a formal confession.
He can confess
to the homicide,
but we're still examining
evidence in the arson.
The guy wants to take the heat
for his daughter on the arson.
Well, where's
the harm in that?
Well, the harm would be
to the justice system
unless I misunderstand
our place in it.
Don't you think that little
girl's been through enough?
What I think, and what
the evidence proves,
are possibly
two different things.
What is this?
It's, uh... just what it says:
It's a request
for a leave of absence...
six months... year, maybe.
Why?
I was thinking
of checking out
the federal government
system... FBI...
We have the best lab
in the country.
I need a different
work environment.
What does
that
mean?
One with, um... communication...
respect.
Everybody here respects you.
You don't.
Is this about
that hamburger thing?
No. Grissom...
this is not about
that hamburger thing.
I-I-I don't believe you.
How can you reduce
everything that I've said
to some kind
of single quirk?
Do you think the problem here
is just about me?
If you don't sign my leave,
I'm going to have to quit.
Hey, Sara?
The lab needs you here.
Great.
Did you hear the dad
copped a plea
on the murder,
and the D.A.
Expedite d it?
Voluntary man,
first offense.
Out on bail.
Free in four.
No jury was going
to convict a father
for killing
his daughter's abuser.
What do you have?
Accelerant.
Identical to the type
found at the arson.
Police got it out
of Jody's gym locker.
Well, looks as if Jody
was probably telling the truth.
She did burn herself
on a curling iron.
So who started the fire?
Hey.
You get anywhere
with those fingerprints?
Back burner.
I've been working
on this reflection in her eye.
You see
what I'm seeing?
No.
Come on.
I've been working on this
enhancement all night.
Look closer.
What is it?
A clock? A mirror?
It's got a latch...
a lock.
A porthole?
It's a porthole?
Yeah.
These pictures
were taken on a boat.
Miss Bradley.
Yes.
Warrick Brown.
Your fiancé Mike...
did he own a boat?
A boat? No.
No?
Did he borrow one
or rent one?
He wanted to borrow
my ex-husband's boat,
but he was
too proud to ask.
Your ex-husband
owned a boat?
He bought one
after our divorce.
I've never been on it.
Okay. Thank you.
Jody...
we know that Mike
gave you his camera.
We suspect that
your father used it
to take pictures
of you on his boat.
We believe that
he then placed
the camera back
at Mike's
to implicate him,
along with the pictures.
He said I was like my mom
when she was young
and they were happy.
He said having me was
like having his family back.
Did you ever
tell your mom?
I tried.
I don't want to go to Dad's.
You know what the judge said:
Two weeks with Dad,
two with me.
Jody, we have strong forensic evidence
But cases like this are
very difficult to prove.
A victim testifying
makes all the difference.
He told me if I ever talked
he'd kill me.
Jody, if you don't talk...
I told Mike...
and he was going to fix things.
And my dad killed him...
okay?
Catherine.
What is this?
Found it on the boat.
DNA just ran it.
She's under 14, right?
Yeah. 12.
He didn't take pictures
of his daughter.
He never touched her.
He's a loving, devoted father
who works hard
at his chain of grocery stores
to keep her in good schools.
Except when she's on his boat,
right?
This is your sleeping bag
we took off your boat.
Our lab turned it
inside-out.
The discoloration you see
is a mixture of vaginal
and seminal fluid...
your daughter's and yours.
Okay.
Don't say a word, Russ.
He doesn't have to.
The sleeping bag's talking
loud and clear.
Brad, make me a deal.
I can't.
What do you mean, you can't?
You got me four years
for murder.
I can't.
You can get me something.
No, he can't.
In the state of Nevada
we're all bound
by a legal statute.
The sexual assault of a minor
age 14 and under
is a mandatory life sentence
with no possibility for parole.
Excuse me.
Could I talk to
you for a moment?
Why don't you wait
over there, sweetie.
Okay.
I owe you an apology.
I have an eight-year-old
daughter.
It's okay.
You were
looking out for mine.
Tough case, huh?
Just give me a straight ahead murder any
Well, you wouldn't
be human if it
didn't affect you.
I heard about you and Sara.
Sara... you know,
she gets very emotional.
Are you in denial?
No, that's... no, no.
Way too analytical.
Wow, you got
burned bad, huh?
Welcome to the club.
I got third-degree burns
from my marriage.
Happens to everybody. Everybody just
Good.
Let's move on.
But you have
to deal with it.
You have to deal
with it first.
You got to deal with it
before it goes away.
You are the supervisor.
You have responsibilities,
and people are making
a family around you
whether you like it not...
whether you give them
permission or not.
We don't have to go
to the Grand Tetons together.
Just... every now and then,
you got to lift your head up
out of that microscope.
Yeah.
Yeah, hi. I'd like to get
some flowers for a girl.
No, no. Not flowers.
A plant. A living plant.
She likes vegetation.
Yeah, that'd be fine.
To a "Sara Sidle."
Deliver it at the CSI Division,
Las Vegas Police Department...
the one out
on North Trop Boulevard.
Yeah, you can bill me
at the same place.
Gil Grissom.
The sentiment?
Oh. Oh. On the card. Yeah.
Um... uh...
Have it say...
Have it say, uh...
"From Grissom."
Thank you.