My son's story
begins in the ocean.
A place full of secrets.
Somewhere beautiful,
somewhere dangerous.
Its mysteries have baffled
mankind for centuries.
None were solved in the Bermuda Triangle.
But in order to understand the Triangle,
you must understand my son.
Although he lives among you, he was
born in the darkest regions of the sea.
I hoped to teach him
the ways of the world.
How to live a good life
and become a good man.
But then...
I was taken from him.
Turtle 1,
Turtle 1.
Tempest Key coast guard to Turtle 1.
Atlana, you're out there ?
Flying High and free.
All the hatcheries were undisturbed.
You missed me ?
More than I can say on an open frequency.
How do you know researches system turn out ?
He's got something to tell you.
Dad, Mum let me take the biggest sea turtle.
It was the coolest thing ever..
And dad, I hold my breathe
under water for almost five minutes.
Hey, that is incredible, kido.
I swear, you must be part of fish.
Hey, we left in an hour away.
You wanna grab a pizza and meet us?
Tom ?
Tom, can you read me ?
Oh, my God.
Atlana, sweetheart, I lost you.
Atlana ?
Arthur, back off.
Honey, get your seat.
Aaron, do we get a storm doing out there ?
No, sir.
Blue sky for 500 miles.
Hold on.
Mommy !
Mommy help me !
Mommy.
I'm stuck. I can't get out.
They're coming for you.
You have to get to the surface.
Do good with your life.
I will find you again, I promise.
I love you, Oren.
Mommy ?
Mom ?
Morning, A.C.
You had a busy night...
Come on, get out of here.
What'd I do this time, sheriff?
Oh, it depends on where you were
at ten o'clock last night?
I don't wear a watch.
I can't tell you.
Didn't you bring in Neptune?
World and free five dolphins?
- I'm the wrong man...
- Is that so ?
All right....
How do you explain these Kodak moments ?
Sir, come on.
Any ten years old and a PC could have
photoshoped those pictures.
Come on, AC.
Look, you're under arrest for breaking
an entering and an animal endangerment.
Endangerment ?
Come on, I've seen port-a-potty that were
cleaner than this thin park.
I was doing of those dolphins a favour.
Yeah, the world is full
of misunderstood heroes.
Come on.
Thanks for bailed me out, dad.
I promise I'll pay you back.
A.C, I know your heart is
on the right place,
but come on this is the third time this year.
I guess this is the day
when you wish you never would...
- ... to sign the adoption papers.
- Hey, kido.
No matter how many time you screw up
and you're definitely gone for the records here,
I'll always be your father
All right, I gotta go to work.
You know, it's ten years today
since Mom disappeared.
AC, please, don't.
Don't do this to yourself.
We were flying over the Bermuda Triangle.
She called me Oren
She said she had so
much to tell me.
Didn't she also said do
good with your life ?
I don't see you fix it
her on that.
You should be in Stanford right now,
not worrying about being incarcerated.
I'm not leaving Tempest Key until
I'll find out what happened to mom.
Look, I missed her too.
But you're not a teenage anymore.
You have so much potential.
I hate to see you gotta waste.
Look I'm messed up.
I'm Sorry.
If you're really sorry.
Pull your life together, kido.
I'll see you later.
For Sale.
Rough night ?
No... No, then that was fine.
But this day keep sucking
more and more by a minute.
Why are you putting a
for-sale sign on my boat?
Technically, the boat
is still mine.
I figured it was time for me
to cut my losses.
Eva.
I know you are mad about the chargers
I blew off this morning.
You know, there's something ironic about
watching five cardiologist,
have a heart attack when you tell them
their diving instructor is in jail.
Technically, it was a holding cell
and the plan was not to get arrested.
You know, that's what you said when you swam
above the cruise ship and went out the bar tab.
It was a wedding.
You know, I got caught up in the moment.
I've run everyone around.
For the record, the bride's maid did said that
my toast was incredibly romantic.
Well, maybe one of them should have wired you
the money to cover the bill.
You're not really gonna sell
my boat, are you ?
AC, come on, we're supposed to be
business partners.
Why did you pick last night
to go Greenpeace on me?
You wanna know the real reason
why I freed those dolphins?
It's because I felt like
they were calling to me.
So what do you say, you can talk
to fish now ?
Dolphins are mammals and...
No, it was more... They, huh...
Weird empathy...
If you want, I can call a friend
of the dolphin rescue
and we can set up a legal defence fund.
Ok...
Ok. Thanks.
Don't worry.
And get to work.
Get inside and
staring at these bottles.
Anyone around here wants
to afford me a drink?
Little early for happy hour,
don't you think?
You're Tom Curry's boy.
I've seen you diving Mercy Reef.
Then I realize I have a fan club.
You don't.
You're in a light house with endless point.
Goals of nothing on my view.
It sounds beautiful.
I remember the day your mother's
plane went down.
That cloudless Caribbean’s sky.
God couldn't have painted a prettier picture.
Then I don't know where it came this storm.
I'm sorry, who are you ?
My name's McCaffery.
Keep the change.
Arthur...
If you look hard and long
enough into the deep.
Something is going to start looking back.
Watch yourself.
Mercy Reef
25 miles off Tempest Key.
This is cost guard rescue.
We have a possible ship break victim.
We got an unidentified man, may twenty's.
- ...He's hypothermic.
- Vitals aren't responding.
They're coming.
I mu... I must warn Oren.
Take it easy, buddy.
Take it easy...
We're taking you to the hospital..
This is unit 66. We are on road
to the Mercy Reef hospital.
Tempest Key Naval
Air Station.
Don't forget to take the left in Cuba, Torres.
You think, I'm taking advice from you Munts?
You'd get lost in a two lane highway.
- Lieutenant Torres.
- Commandant Alley.
You've got a new mission...
Coordinated in your NavCom.
You'll flying over Mercy reef.
- Permission to speak freely.
- Go ahead.
Sir, if you're giving me an easier assignment
because you don't believe
I can handle the rigour of this program
you're at 100%...
This is not the LPGA, Torres.
You tee off with the men.
These orders come from way above my head.
They told me to put my best pilot on it.
They need a clean sweep of the area.
Now if I blow enough sunshine every backside.
You're ready to fly?
- Yes, sir.
- Good.
Now, the coast guards have pulled a
John Doe off the Reef.
No boat, no I.D and no idea
where he came from.
*** to fed is up food chain.
If you see anything out of the ordinary,
you let me know.
Lieutenant Torres reporting
as ordered.
I'm flying over Mercy Reef,
there's nothing out there, guys.
Wait a second, something below
the surface is following me.
It's coming on fast.
Hang on... It's just dropped back.
I'm gonna circle around.
There is a disturbing...
There's a light... It...
- It's you...
- Welcome back.
Doctors said I can wait here until you wake up.
I hope the Navy’s doesn't have
"You break it, you bought it" policy.
You remember anything?
Just a flash light.
Then I was flying through the water.
And you were carrying me.
And we were going so fast.
You know, when you're drowning,
your brain misses oxygen
And you start to see things they’re unreal.
Maybe you should rest.
Is that your way of saying that I'm crazy?
Your plane crashed at 700 miles an hour.
So I'm gonna reserve judgment
until the painkillers were off.
I'll better go tell to the nurse, you're awake.
Wait...
What's your name?
It's not important.
You saved my life.
It's important to me.
AC...
Oren?
They know, you're here.
They know you survived.
Why did you call me that?
Where did you get this necklace?
They're coming... For you...
- Who are you?
- Visiting hours are over.
Who the hell are you?
This badge means I'm the only
one asking questions.
Where are you taking him?
I said where're you taking him?
I asked you a question.
Where are you taking him?
We got him.
When did he wake up ?
Five minutes ago.
Is he displaying violent tendencies like the others?
No, Sir... This is the file you
requested from the NAVY archives.
The dental records match our John Doe.
This is Hansen Gus Thompson. Member of flight 19
who disappeared December 5th.
1945... Bermuda Triangle.
Welcome home Hansen Thompson.
Where the hell have you been
for the last 60 years?
This Tom's caller son, it's about the man he pulled
over Mercy Reef this morning.
...That's the bitch. I tell you when I got the
perfect spot in the house for the lady. Right above....
Easy.
I've already told them to dock some place off and
I'll report the boat, tomorrow, to the Fish and Wildlife.
Fines not gonna stop these guys.
I just gonna go remind them about the catch and release policy of marlin.
AC, kicking the crap and have a bunch of issues
means that all gonna lead you back in jail.
Okay ?
It's amazing how cruel people can be.
Yeah... It bothers me more and more.
That marlin should be in the ocean and not
hanging at some moron's fireplace.
Maybe some day, the fish will get their revenge.
I don't know, I think rednecks
make pretty ugly trophies.
I'm Nadia.
I heard you're pretty amazing under the water.
If you would like to take me diving,
I'm free tomorrow.
I was hoping
we could do something...
- Let's get out of here.
- Great idea.
- Let's go for a swim.
- That's still in my mind.
You're not bad under the water yourself.
Years of practice.
You know, we met a long time ago.
Are you sure about that ?
You got different when I remember of you.
Let me refresh your memory.
Nadia ?
Ok, You're already starting to freak me out here.
I hate those damn things.
What the hell was she ?
Get your clothes on.
We need to talk.
Once a siren has you in her game, there's nothing a man can do.
Siren ?
Of course.
You act like you see them all the time.
I've seen my fair share.
Unfortunately my hands are a little rusty.
The only way to kill those scary bitches is
to nail them between the eyes.
Who are you?
An exiled like you and your mother.
Exiled from where?
It's called different names by different cultures.
You probably know it by its most famous.
Atlantis.
Atlantis ?
Next time you're in Atlantis,
Could you say Hi to Captain Nemo
and to Little Mermaid for me ?
You think, I wanted to be the one to tell you ?
No, I think you need to lay off the booze, old man.
It psyched out your brain.
You can't run away from you true calling, Oren.
So let me get this straight...
My parents were the rulers of Atlantis.
So I guess, technically, that would make me...
A prince.
You know, the fact that you can say that with
with a straight face is impressive.
Let me ask you a question.
Does Atlantis have a retractable dome?
Or does everyone just swim around in
there like a bunch of fish?
Don't mock me.
You think I don't know how absurd this sounds?
But you saw that siren.
Was that a joke?
Okay, so if Atlantis exists...
Then how come...
..our sub sonar or deep sea probe
hasn't been able to discover it?
because it's cloaked in a shroud no more
than technology can penetrate.
The Bermuda Triangle.
Your father was a man of peace.
They were others who wanted to
wage a war against the surface world.
Your father resisted.
And so what? They killed him?
Now they want me dead too.
A man should get you and your mother out.
The only place you would be safe was up here.
You were found on Mercy Reef,
by a young coast guard Lieutenant.
My dad.
Then he knows.
No.
Your mother insisted that we said nothing.
She probably thought
she could hide you from you true destiny.
Yeah, and what's my true destiny, huh?
To defend this world you've embraced as your own and protect the ocean from what you were born.
You want me to fight sirens
and standards oil.
Is that it?
You know what? Forget it.
Find somebody else.
I'm not interested.
You can't avoid your responsibilities, Oren.
It's in your bones and you know it.
This is insane.
I'm a dive shop owner.
I'm not the protector of the Seven Seas.
Destiny is like a riptide.
You never know what's pulling you in
until it's too late.
So this girl, Nadia, is actually a
killer mermaid who...
... wants to take you out because you're some
sort of under water royalty?
I'm quite sure, yeah.
Well, they all look so funny on the Starbuck's cups.
Well, I didn't believe it either until that
siren tried to kill me.
She's coming back for me.
Then I suggest a road trip to the desert
with a truck full of Evian.
Eva.
I think she is the creature that attacked my mom.
I have to face her.
You're really serious about this.
You should close up for a couple of days...
Head out of town.
I don't want you cut in the middle of this.
And what about you?
I'm taking the Quint to Atlas Point.
McCaffery got weapons there.
Well, it looks like a storm is coming anyway.
Maybe I'll go and visit my sister in Tempa.
Look, I'm sorry about all this insanity.
Yeah, well, being a friend of yours always require a leap of faith.
Besides, some day you'll make it up
to me give me a cool title like...
"Duchess of the Deep"
I don't know how you escaped from Atlantis.
But thank you for leading me to Oren.
It's good to see you back on your feet,
Lieutenant Torres.
Thank you, sir...
But I'm confused.
I already went over the accident
report with commandant Alley.
I understand that but
I'm the one who ordered the mission.
I wanted to debrief you myself.
And who exactly do you work for?
Top of the all lieutenant.
Commandant in Chief.
I was curious about that flash of light that
you saw like before you lost control.
To be honest sir,
I was disoriented.
That could've been a sun flair.
You wanna placate me.
I won't think you lost your mind.
After all, you were flying
over the Bermuda Triangle.
With all do respect, sir,
that's just a myth.
I used to share that sentiment.
And you changed your mind.
Why don't I show you?
Last year, this man, boarded
an oil platform...
...in Golf of México and
attempted to blow it sky high.
He was killed before he succeeded.
His name was Evan Corday.
He disappeared along with his yacht.
Off the cost of Bermuda.
On July 6 1905.
It's impossible... It must have been a descendant
or somebody who looks like him.
I'd agree with you, except that the finger
prints were perfect match.
And he's not the first one to come back.
Come back from where?
That's what the project Nova
aims to find out.
I want you to join us Lieutenant.
Help unlock the mysteries
of the Bermuda Triangle.
Sir, I'm a pilot... I don't know
if I had any experience I could offer.
You have more experience than any of us.
You witnessed something extraordinary out there
and you lived to tell the tale.
I don't believe a pilot with your impeccable
record can be taken out of the sky
by a sun flair or a freak mechanical failure Lieutenant.
Sir, I'm doing that to fly jets
and served my country.
Not chase windmills.
This is not a fool's crusade.
This is a matter of national security.
All these files contain pictures of people who
vanished in the Bermuda Triangle.
They are MRA's in an invisible war.
And Tempest Key is the final line.
Yeah?
I'll be right there.
If you want to see how real this is
come with me Lieutenant.
Eva you need to hit the road or you're never gonna
to make you out of here before the storm.
Once it's locked down, I'll go.
I don't want to come back and find out
our restaurant under water.
I got it, I got it...
So I want you taking care of business and...
...We should talk to the bank about
a lender upgrade to your boat.
Oh, great.
Power lines have blown over.
No, it must be the circuit breaker.
Light is still on the cabin Jack's.
- Are you sure you know what you're doing?
- Yeah, trust me.
Would it kill you to hold the flash light steady?
It's very funny, Eva.
Good night forever, Oren.
Eva.
Sorry about your friend.
But I'm more concerned about your life now.
McCaffery...
She got you, too?
Where is she taking us?
Home. To Atlantis.
To be executed.
Why haven't she got us already?
You're a symbol of hope, Oren.
If they kill you,
that hope dies too.
- I need water.
- My flask, it's in my boot.
Smash it!
- How do we take her down?
- We are doing anything.
You're getting off this boat.
No!
No! That thing took my mom
and attacked my friend.
I'm not going anywhere until she's dead.
I promised your father on his dying breath
that i will project you.
I'm not breaking my word now.
Do you have any weapons?
Nadia!
Your aim's got better.
- Where is Oren?
- Roast in hell you jelly bitch!
Now... Where is Oren ?
I'm right here.
Your mother can't protect you this time.
What did you do to her?
You'll find out.
You're coming home, Oren.
Oren?
No!
Well done, Oren.
Your father would have been proud.
I'm sorry, Eva.
Feliz 1936 - Club Havana.
How much do you remember Lieutenant Torres?
You know, that siren was just the beginning.
There're creatures in the deep you couldn't imagine
in your worst nightmares.
Oh, that's reassuring.
Thanks a lot.
I'm not here to make you feel good.
I'm here to prepare you for the worst.
Look, we should've started your training years ago.
And let's then do it.
It starts now.
I'm ready.
A birthday gift.
I kind of feel it's like a book.
I'm not really much a reader.
Just open it.
Henry the 4th :
Part 1 and 2.
I didn't really know Shakespeare
was in sequence.
I expect for you
to read them by next week.
I gave up book reports
in sixth grade.
This is a part of your training.
Right, see, when you said training, I thought, you meant...
You know, wielding tridents, and
doing cool stuff in the water.
All in due time.
Don't worry, there's plenty of sex and violence
in there that'll keep you interested.
Could you just say the highlights?
And tell me how it ends?
The lesson isn't in the end, Oren.
It's in the journey.