Hello
Hello?
Oops! Where are you?
In celebration
Well
The association''senior police officers
invites you to attend AGM.''
''Unveiling of this year's retired
Welcome to new members''
''Buffet with dancing. Ystad Saltsjöbad''
Go on like that?
I have done that in 30 years
of tradition and duty
-Need help?
-Yes
LDAG is in Ystad.
It does not look good if I am absent
I have not seen you as a man
of tradition and duty, right.
-Who are you going with?
"I was not going to torment someone else.
I would not torment you ...
I have nothing special for me today.
That's
fucking boring tilställningar.
To an outsider, they are deadly.
-Is it champagne?
-Yes, I think.
If you are unsuccessful, then?
I would not be in uniform on the street
after 20 years.
If everyone was so vain that you ...
"It's not wrong on their uniforms.
-Jo.
Okay, it is quite ugly. But seriously ...
If everyone thought like you
would the police come.
Some must of course palla
to work in real life
Yes, and who should thank them?
-How much do Svartman?
"It is not about the
-Wallander serves no fortune.
-No, but a bit more.
He of course do not have a uniform.
-What the hell!
-The barely visible.
Stop being such a fucking wimp.
All right
All right, fine horse.
Calm, take it easy
But God, what is that?
There is something in the water.
Thank
-Hey.
-Yes, heels.
-Yes.
A glass of
I think I need soon.
Nämen! Kurt!
-Hey
"It was not yesterday.
Katarina. Sven, defectors
now in the security industry
-This is my wife Mette.
-Catherine.
Yes, I am a defector
and damn glad of it.
I still get invited here -
and said Mette wanted to go to a party.
Where is you?
"We just got.
-V was thinking well that ...
Over there, perhaps?
You kidding, it's Maundy Thursday.
Martinsson is on duty.
Then'll have someone to talk about it
for Martinsson.
Wallander is on leave
and does not answer his phone.
lsabelle and Pontus is on course.
What should I do? Go there yourself?
You may well take it on the road?
I eat lamb with mother in law.
The family is sitting in the car.
Sure, I can stop at a corpse
on the way to the mother.
-You are the best in the world.
-Tell that to my wife!
Ha ha!
-Stop it, Linda.
Now the father.
Soon we are at grandma.
-That 's it.
-Dad will!
We should just stop on the road.
A job thing.
- What job thing?
- You know, the job thing.
It goes fast.
-No, I have never looked back.
-Good.
Being the police are equally appreciated
which will be patching lisa.
No one tackaar
and salary, we will not talk about.
-It may well be other reasons.
-Look around in here.
How many had chosen to become police officers
if they could choose again?
-Are you in security?
-No, I have stopped working.
Sven serves so well.
Of my salary was the only tax.
Sven will also end soon.
We plan
to obtain a place south.
Wow, it sounds fantastic.
Where did you have in mind here?
Do not know, just warm.
It might be something for you? Kurt?
You are a meritorious police
and can get any job you want.
I can hear myself.
After a few years, you can take the wife
on perpetual vacation.
Oh, no ... We are not married.
Colleagues.
And neighbors.
It is only today
I am "and".
-Then you are police, too?
-No. I am a prosecutor.
You can not park there!
Hey!
Here you can 't stand? Hey!
What the hell was this?
We have two burning vehicles
cenrala in Ystad.
3701, we are on the E65
just west of Skurup.
-Do you have addresses?
-Great Square at the corner of Harbor Street.
-Have Wallander come?
-No.
Where the hell is the fire?
Martinsson. What, another one?
We have three burning vehicles
in central Ystad.
Kurt Wallander?
There is someone Ebba looking for you.
What the hell is it now?
Yes, minister
Yes, you do not need to yell.
I will. Relax, I'm on the road.
We must go. You too. Sorry.
-Yes, it's just so.
"We may well see you again? Take Sven's short ..
It says our numbers.
Okay, thanks. Hello.
-What happened?
"We are taking it on the road.
Strangely, just run like that.
-No, something happened.
-What the hell! Road construction? Check it out.
"I check.
It should not be something here Down!
Out! Out of the car!
Out! Out with you!
-What the hell was that?
-A Turn of the robbery.
3701, we are on the E65
just west of Skurup.
We have witnessed a robbery
against cash.
-3701. Hello?
-Bring your camera. You must take pictures.
-Stop and wait for reinforcement
-3701
Stop and wait for reinforcements.
Yes, it is understood!
Where the hell are they somewhere then?
Now drag the. They stick.
What are you doing?
We would wait for reinforcements.
What the hell do we do then?
They will of course be excluded.
Do not be such a fucking pussy,
what we said. Okay?
But take it easy!
-Slow down.
-Calm down. Pull yourself together!
-Watch out!
-What the hell is he doing?
-Slow down!
-When will they escape.
-What the hell is happening?
-Back! Back off! Back off!
And when the horses began to react ... ?
Yes, they were frightened
and began to fuss
-Come on.
-Stay in your car.
-Yes, but Linda must pee
-Yes, yes.
Okay ...
-You got the horses.
-Yes.
You went up and touched the corpse?
-Did you know if he was alive?
-No.
Were you in front and went on ...
-... or, you held your distance?
-Yes.
It is good to say
to our engineers ...
- Investigating brottsp atsen
Shoulder-Nom now
No, come here. Not there.
Okay, you saw nothing else?
No one other man?
No.
-Can we go now?
-Yes, the way your car. I will.
-Then I'll take your name and number.
-Jonna.
-0739 ...
-... 88 ...
-... 10 32.
-Okay.
Hello.
Now I want to
you sit perfectly still.
-What should you do?
-I will take up a hole.
Then I go into
with a camera and watch.
Pacific.
Move a bit, so.
It looks good. It is quiet.
It is quiet.
It is quiet, my friends.
It was professional done
Exact amount
to bring up the doors.
Of tracks apparently loaded the above
in a box car and drove west.
We have set out roadblocks
in all directions.
"They have a fucking head start
-25-30 Minutes.
They had just
the burning cars in the skull.
MOBILE CALLING
Yes? Kurt.
Can you talk more?
-Okay, I will.
-What was that?
lsabelle have collided
Pontus and is missing.
Hello. Glad you came,
then we can go further.
-Family with you? Cozy.
-V will have dinner with mother.
Ak you. I'll take over
Hope it will be good.
-Where have you body?
-On the other side the hill. Goodbye.
"It was not a moment too soon
"I'm sorry.
I can not just say
I do not care it.
lsabelle! How are you? Where's Pontus?
Check out the car. The car! The camera in the car!
"There are going well. Be calm.
"We have to go.
-Nyberg. Nyberg!
-Yes.
-Camera.
-Yes, that's it.
Damn, they saw the robbery.
They followed.
-Is the last picture?
-Yes. It is the last picture.
All the fucking fire is already extinguished.
I want all the police cars are out
until we have found Pontus.
Yes, it's good. Thank you. Hello.
Fucking idiots!
-Did you find something more?
-Yes, I do well always.
There is no indication
Pontus that was shot here.
-Mobile have you called?
"Yes, five hundred times. No response.
MOBILE CALLING
Wait, please call again!
Do it!
MOBILE CALLING
What the hell?
Help! What the hell, then!
What the hell!
Help!
MOBILE CALLING
Kurt.
Yes. How is he?
Is he going to the hospital?
Good. Yes, that's fine. Hello.
Hello.
You fucking pussy.
-Hey.
I would like to submit these.
But first a question ...
What was it that really happened?
You were well clear instructions
whether to stay and wait?
Or is it something we've missed?
It was my fault.
They were on their way out and I ...
You received an express order
to stop and wait for reinforcement!
Did not you?
-Yes, but it would take ...
-So you heard!
But you acted exactly the opposite
Is that correct understood?
-Yes, but
-No, but damn!
You understand what could have happened?
Damn kids!
What I wanted to say is ...
... I'm very happy
n that's okay.
-Thank you.
Thank you.
Shall we go out and walk? When we do so.
-Do we know how much they came over?
15 million under SkandiGuard
And this murder ...
Is it something related?
-It 's not what we see.
-Then, we separate investigations.
The body was badly
according to Karin Linder.
He is shot in the head.
Svartman was the first place.
-Where is he?
-Available.
Damn, we manage two investigations
and the two men short.
Call Svartman.
As you know, took some pictures Pontus
with his camera phone.
Here we Marko Lehtinen.
It is hogerhanden
to this guy -
-Leonard named Belker
He sat at Kumla in eight years,
then ran away and he is wanted.
He is probably active.
July 28, 2002 in Märsta,
a raid on eleven million.
-Svartman are going.
-Thank you. August 25, 2005 in Hallunda.
15 million.
Four days later Akalla, 19 million.
"There are no amateurs.
-What is interesting is how he works.
Robberies twice
every few days.
First staging something spectacular
so the police are busy.
"When chaos is worse, turn it into.
-Then we can wait one to robbery.
There will we be prepared for.
-Hey.
-Aren 't you leave today?
I thought it,
not to speak about my wife.
-What?
-Oh, nothing.
"It was a sour old man.
-Bye.
Bye, Ebba. We are on the phone.
-Take care of Jussi.
-You say it.
-Hey.
-Svartman! Hello.
Be precise body found
in the watercourse?
There. Eggelstad.
Theoretically, the scene of the crime lie
well upstream.
Be Linder fast on
if there is a link to the robbery.
She is ready for lunch
and found a thing on the discovery site.
-A little thing.
-The offender was a minor.
It seemed like an entire kindergarten
had barging around there, "she said.
She told me to hand over
it Svartman.
I do not understand why.
Then you health Linder
I was free.
-Would I have locked the kids?
-Come on.
It is a major setback.
Last year, we laid down
enormous resources on security.
-What did you do?
-A major analysis of our procedures.
Here is a long list.
You can follow me.
Is there anything else you can come to me.
Ystad police want to ask some questions.
Of course. Mike Sterner.
- You set the schedule for shipments.
-Yes, just to the south of Sweden.
Counted as Ystad in southern Sweden?
-Should I be honest ...
"There, we assume.
-This kind will not be possible
"It does.
Like, it does not matter
how secure a system is.
-Can you explain how you work?
-Yes.
We run three cars, two of which are empty.
Körsohemat encrypted
individually to the drivers.
They do not know themselves
if they are running with empty boxes.
You are responsible for the encryption
Southern Sweden?
I'll tell you about a competitor.
A few years ago
were subjected to the raids.
They improved their methods,
but the robbers were always the right car.
It was a town that was leaking.
He felt the encryption?
Arena had studied at KTH
and was an expert in cryptography.
How does it himself?
You have increased resources for security
the last year.
I have a new lock
and we have video surveillance.
Can you see the recordings
from the last month?
It can be difficult.
I do not think they will save the links.
Sorry.
This should be
throughout the last month.
-Fine, thanks.
-Thank you.
The bullet penetrated through pannbenet
and penetrated the left hemisphere.
It went out through the back of the head
-How long has he been dead?
-One week, plus or minus two days.
Nothing of water in the lungs,
so he was probably dead before he came in.
Could he have been murdered somewhere else
and floated to Eggelstad?
It is possible.
Identification will not be easy.
Fingerprints
there was no code.
Dental impressions are analyzed.
It takes time.
I understand.
An athletic man, around 55 years.
That is what I can say.
Something more?
This was in the pocket.
Hello.
-How does it work? If you find something?
-Nothing.
That's him all the time.
Not a visit to two weeks.
-What is he doing?
Jobs.
Can you play at normal speed?
Damn, that's of course Internet poker.
Damn, I thought he was working.
-How long has he been doing?
-All the time.
Is he a compulsive gambler?
Gambling debts?
Then he has a damn good reason.
We can not pick him for it.
He is the only one who knows
driving schedule before it is encrypted.
Does he have gambling debts -
-is it reasonable that he is open
for every conceivable proposal.
I think we should wait
until we find something more.
Look what I got today.
There are more than Sven and Mette
with foreign plans.
A colleague and his wife
skaa move to the south of France.
"Provence,
two kilometers from the salt bath. "
A fantastic house.
-How the hell did you afford that?
-Free sector.
He switched to corporate law.
-Maybe you should change jobs?
-No.
He defended a construction company
who used a float trowel -
-who had given every tenant
tracheal problems, especially the children.
-A clear conscience is the best pillow.
"Yes, let them rotate in insomnia
They have all fa
a fantastic house.
400 gross square meters of stunning.
You may well bite on Sven's proposal?
Then you buy a house
and invite me down
-See you.
-Yes.
Svartman!
A woman called five times -
-on a car that is on her land.
-Could you take it?
-No, I'm going to lunch.
You may well take something on the road?
-Thanks, you are ...
- ... "The best". I know.
Damn.
-Hey. Johan Svartman, Ystad police.
-Christina Tham.
It is my land you spill on.
Here it is.
-Fine!
-UGLY. Take it now?
-Now?
"I was clear on the phone.
I demand to scrap heap moved
from my chips today.
"I do not know if this is possible.
"This is exactly what will happen ..
Vil talk to my lawyer?
Black Brandt called you?
No, Svartman.
Sven ...
MOBILE CALLING
Kurt.
Hey, Svartman.
You may ask her to call the municipality.
Explain politely
that she can stop her lawyer ...
An Amazon?
-Hey.
-Have you checked license plate numbers?
No, I have not had time.
Is it your car, drive it away.
The car does not move
until I say so.
You can go. We will contact you.
He managed
had these keys.
Contact Nyberg and vehicle registration office.
The car is registered on
Harald Claesson, Guresgränd 1A.
Good, then we will go there.
Kurt! Come.
He has selected a route on the map.
That cross,
that was where we found the Amazon Basin.
He has been out and oriented,
so anything happening here.
He is shot, body dumped
in the water and float -
-down here to Eggelstad
where we found the body.
The question is
what happened along the road.
I could go the way
and check out a bit.
It is good that you suggested yourself.
That takes a day.
One day the forest is what I need.
I talk a job now.
No fucking picnic.
No, of course.
"It's good. We heard.
-Yes
-Hey. Oh, hey you.
-Hey.
-Molly!
"She felt I uktar dog.
Is Sven-home?
-Yes. He sits in the sauna.
-You can get along nicely.
-I am not complaining.
Not really.
It was not
for money, I ended -
-but it does not hurt
when they roll into.
It was time. How do you say?
"Only the rich
prevailing over their own time. "
And it makes you?
-Yes, now.
I work more than rarely.
As police worked, I continued,
evenings, weekends ...
I know.
The marriage went down the drain.
It was my fault.
So we sat there without life
in addition to the job.
The compromise I do not like
with Mette.
I got a second chance.
She deserves everything I can give her.
What about you? Have you not thought of
to marry again?
The idea may well beat sometimes.
Did you make safety analysis
on SkandiGuard?
That's right. About a year ago.
We look at them
in connection with robbery
Yes, it was their transportation.
I went through
their internal practices.
Is there a gap ...
Did you hear about
by Mikael Sterner?
Yes, he did a little for himself -
-but he seemed serious
-You do not suppose ...?
-No.
"We believe nothing yet.
-Here is Mette.
-Hey.
-Come here. Come.
Come and visit.
Come and visit me.
She knows that I uktar dog.
-Were you a good hand?
-Excuse me?
It must be difficult to fold
when you sit on a good hand.
"I do not understand.
- No?
Bells on my Saagar
"Poker" and "addiction"?
I am not an addict.
Do you have gambling debts?
No, I do not.
On the contrary.
Poker gives me
a steady side income.
lnom one years, I say me
to become professional players.
You can see my bank accounts.
I have no secrets.
There were no gambling debts?
He earns more in poker
than the three of us are doing together.
Perhaps it is to do
so you can move south.
-What you talking about?
-No, nothing.
Okay, back to square one.
-Hey, Nyberg.
-Hey.
-How does it work?
-Joda.
The lab has sent the report
the explosive from the shipment.
There were no sensations.
It was a primer, remote ...
Yes, on a signal.
Is it the type
which has been used in the other wafers?
Yes, but it does not mean anything.
The military uses the dough.
It is easy to obtain.
One thing that was weird ...
The amount of dough and apteringen
was nasty like.
-Okay. Thank you for so long.
-Thank you.
You ... What would you do
-If you had unlimited
money during the holidays?
Purely hypothetical?
I would do what I do.
Two weeks in Iceland,
excavation and fishing.
It is expensive to snuff
If they called and said
that you had received an inheritance
-from an unknown aunt in America,
what would you do?
I would probably go home
and devote myself to what I like.
How do you work?
I met a colleague from the past.
He has a lot of money.
He would take early retirement
and do not give a shit.
It sounds like shit.
-Had he inherited?
-No, he has worked them together.
-Yes, he may not have been the police.
-No, you're right in.
I'll call when I get a moment.
It is good.
Now I am not ...
Were not you told to rest?
"It was a prescription
-You were told to go home and rest.
I know, but we would look up
one thing about cars.
-There must have been witnesses.
"We heard them, we could get in.
We thought somebody shot
and laid out on the web.
Right. Check it out, then.
Then you go home and rest.
-Is not it beautiful?
-What are they doing here?
Lame and sick, they are lagging here
to work.
-They 're sick. Slot, then?
-What the hell are they to do with it?
"I can check it out.
-Fuck it.
Wait, wait! Check.
All watching the fire,
but he is about to leave.
It's a Vespa Elite, an old.
Fucking-eye you have.
-My dad had one of those.
Check it out.
Elite-e at the end.
"I know.
Scanian scooter club.
-Maybe he is a member.
-There you have membership.
What did you do
between 13 and 15 on Thursday?
I and the girl was on lunoh
with her sister.
-You were not out there with vespan?
"I have not started yet
Do you have names
and phone to his sister?
-Did he have an alibi?
-Easter Dinner.
-How many are there left?
-Atta, if v holds us to Ystad.
-Shall we take the entire southern Skane ...
-Yes, if necessary.
-Shall we?
-Yes.
Do not be so fucking pussy!
Hello?
Hello. Pontus Hoijer, Ystad police.
Is that your scooter outside?
-What d'ya?
-A bilbrand.
Yes, I read something in the newspaper.
-What did you do last Thursday?
- No fan tutte I fire on a car.
Me and the wife was with my parents
and ate dinner.
Do you have names and phone numbers?
Helge and Birgitta Karlsson.
0414-12 12 32.
You, in which the helmet ...
Freeze! Freeze!
Lie still! Lie still!
A witness saw you get out
a blue Ford Fiesta before the fire.
-Do not want to cooperate?
-You can interpret it how you want.
I just drove a car into the square.
And after that?
"I left the car and pulled.
Once you had set fire to it?
I had no idea
that they would blow up the car.
I was in hell on the road
to emphasize the self.
Who are "they"?
He knows nothing. He received 12 000
to drive a car at the square.
They work
in cells isolated from each other.
We must have something more going on.
Anything!
-Martinsson?
-Yes.
This with lntrSafe
and SkandiGuard.
What do you think lntrSafe bill
for his work with SkandiGuard?
Security analysis, reporting, ...
... surveillance, video cameras,
lock code, and the whole balunsen.
Well, 150 000 ...
200 000 at least.
Okay.
-Hurry up! We go now.
-Yes.
Damn!
SHOOT
-Where is he?
"I do not know.
MOBILE CALLING
Hello? Yes.
Yes, we will now.
Shit, we need to go back.
Doorbell CALL
-Hey.
-Have you Sven at home?
-No, sorry.
"He does not answer the phone
-Yeah.
-Was it important?
-Yes.
"I ask him to call.
-Yes, it is important.
-How are you?
"I was kind of rush a headache.
-I'll call him later.
-Should I get a tablet?
Yes would you do it?
Hall, it is Svartman.
Svartman. I was fired.
-Svartman have found their hiding place.
-Ah, hell!
Good. Hello. They have their headquarters here.
They shot at me.
-How does it work?
-I have a simcard hair.
There is an encrypted message.
D-J-4-3-A,-B.
There's something for Nyberg.
MOBILE CALLING
Yes? It's only half the money.
It was not what we agreed.
I deliver no information
until I have all the money.
What? I've looked in the envelope.
But what the hell ...
What the hell?
A new voicemail.
Hey, it's Kurt Wallander.
Can you come tlll station?
I would like to ask some questions
as soon as possible. Hello.
Imagine that each letter
have a number in this alphabet.
A is a, b are two and so on.
We can apply p us one.
A becomes B, B becomes C.
Then comes the hard part -
and I have transferred the
to this machine.
It may be here
and chew a few hours.
-Snack?
-Absolutely.
I'll just have this conversation,
I will.
Yes, it's Kurt.
Are you off now?
Good. Hello.
I would just like to ...
-How are you?
-Yes.
It is good.
I want to ask some questions
if SkandiGuard.
I love Mette.
She sought protection for all the shit
she has been through.
About two years
I could give it to her.
Now I have thrown her out
insecurity again.
It's so fucking stupid.
She is not involved.
It's just me.
I ...
... going to take my punishment.
Okay.
-So it is you who is the leak?
-Yes.
They contacted me
when I had just met Mette.
Just as if they had figured it out.
At first, I said flatly no.
Then the firm could not so well
I had hoped
The implication
to encounter all the time.
Yes, it was said that it was.
It is good.
What do you know about the next robbery?
6718 is in place.
Unit an on-site.
Get ready for action.
Yes, now it is best that you are right.
Well, damn. It should match.
Nyberg. Two
than a passenger bus.
-Should I reject them?
-No, let them go.
The shipment value is in the pipeline.
-Is it alone?
-No, a bus will follow.
-The robbery is running. Run!
"We will.
All ready. All units on site.
-Out! Out!
-Down with you!
-What are you doing?
-Go away!
Was in Belker? Where's Belker?
-Where the hell is he?
-Kurt! The shipment is empty.
How are you?
Satan.
Molly! Come on now, so there.
So, stay there.
-What the hell is he doing?
-Get out of the car. Rappa on!
Out of the car. Throw the radio n the car.
Rappa on. Mobiles.
Go away! Rappa on!
Here we have the sharp.
-Can you see where they are?
-Yes, the GPS is on.
"They are brand new. There.
-Coast road.
Port.
"We've got to go.
-What are you wearing?
Come, I'll take your bags.
What are you doing?
Sven? What are you doing?
We can talk then
SHOOT
Mette. Mette. Mette.
-Stick!
Sven, put the gun down.
Get out of here!
"She will die. I shoot.
-No! Nobody shoots.
-Can you not leave us alone?
-You can not get out of here
"They have to deal with Mette.
"I take care of Mette!
I take care of Mette.
MOBILE CALLING
Martinsson.
Okay. Thank you.
They found great value shipment,
blown and exhausted.
He almost made me feel
it was me who had chosen the wrong.
Come on.
-Have you heard anything about Belker?
-Not a trace.
He took enough
Tue Germany or Poland.
lnterpol is plugged in, so we'll see.
What good they are together.
How long do you want her?
To on Monday.
Mette is of course when printed.
-Do not you think that she knew something?
"I do not know.
She knew enough
that something was not right --
-but she did not grasp it
of course, money poured into.
-One can guess that it is over when
-Yes, so did the dream to pieces.
F yttÃ abroad and stop working ...
Inconceivable that he took risks like that.
He must have taken
that he would be discovered.
He was in love, Kurt.
All burns not for his job.