( haunting music playing )
( wolf howling )
( police siren wailing )
YOU WANT 1 OF THESE
DEEP-DISH GREASY-ASS DONUTS ?
I'M YOUR PARTNER
HOW MANY YEARS,
AND YOU FORGET
I'M A DIABETIC ?
THAT'S RIGHT,
YOU'RE MY PARTNER, MAN.
WHAT EVER HAPPENED
TO HELEN,
YOU KNOW, THE BABE
WITH THE FUNNY HAIR ?
WHAT'S UP WITH HER ?
SHE'S GOOD.
I DON'T WANT HER LIFE STORY,
I JUST ASKED YOU A QUESTION.
WE'RE GETTING MARRIED.
YOU'RE BULLSHITTING ME.
NO.
YOU'RE BULLSHITTING ME !
NO, OVER THE WEEKEND,
I POPPED THE BIG Q.
SHE CAME BACK WITH THE BIG A:
SEX ON A REGULAR BASIS.
WHAT ?
YEAH.
CONGRATULATIONS, MAN.
THANKS, MAX.
HEY, MAX, I'M GETTING
OUT ON 3 QUARTERS.
HELEN, SHE'S GOT SOME SAVINGS,
I THINK WE'RE GONNA BE FINE.
YOU KNOW, I'M GETTING
TIRED OF THIS SHIT,
I CAN'T TAKE IT ANYMORE.
I'M GONNA GET A REAL JOB,
YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN?
WHAT ?
I'LL MISS YOU, MAN.
PFFFF !
I'M NOT GOING TO MISS YOU
THAT DAMN MUCH, THOUGH.
YOU'RE THE ONE LEAVING
THE BROTHER STILL IN THE 'HOOD.
HEY, ME AND HELEN,
WE WROTE--
JUST GO GET MARRIED--
ME AND HELEN, WE
WROTE OUR OWN VOWS,
YOU WANT TO HEAR?
OH, MAN ! DOES
THIS SHIT RHYME ?
NO. NO.
"BECAUSE I CARE ABOUT YOU,
I WANT TO BE WITH YOU."
THAT'S IT ?
YEAH.
THAT'S ALL ?
WE WANTED A SHORT CEREMONY
SO WE COULD GET GOING.
YOU'RE CRAZY, MAN.
YEAH, I'M CRAZY,
BUT I'M HORNY.
Unit 17, come in.
UNIT 17, GO AHEAD.
Code 3, Club 0 at
Crescent and La Cienega.
Hostage situation, subjects
armed and dangerous.
( siren wailing )
( tires screeching )
6-W-17, CODE 6.
HEY MAX, 20 MEN.
GOT DETECTIVES DOWN THE SIDE.
BUILDING'S
LOCKED UP TIGHT.
SOME CRACKHEAD'S
THROWING A BLOOD PARTY.
( gun firing )
( screaming )
YO, YO, JIMMY, MAN...
GET OVER THERE.
YOU FEEL LIKE
DANCING ?
DON'T FUCK AROUND,
LET'S WAIT FOR SWAT.
( window shattering )
LET'S GO, MAN.
SHIT.
I GOT THE DOOR.
IT'S LOCKED.
( gun firing )
THERE'S GOTTA BE
ANOTHER WAY. GOTTA BE.
FIRE ESCAPE. COME ON,
JIMMY. COME ON.
OH, SHIT.
I'M GETTING TOO
OLD FOR THIS.
I THINK WE GOT
SOMETHING HERE.
WHAT ?
OH, YEAH.
WHERE WE
GOING ?
HELP ME OUT.
( Jim straining )
THIS IS THE AIR DUCT.
WE CAN DO THIS.
OH, MAN !
I'M FUCKING CLAUSTROPHOBIC,
LET'S WAIT FOR BACKUP.
( gun firing )
WHOA !
MAX, PLEASE.
I'M GOING IN, MAN.
ALL RIGHT, I'LL TAKE
THE OTHER ONE.
FIGURES, I GET THE
THIN ONE. THIS SUCKS.
( loud rock music playing )
( 1st man )
$1 MILLION, MAN !
( 2nd man )
DOWN, YOU FUCKING...
JESUS !
( 2nd man )
GET THE FUCK DOWN !
( 1st man )
AND, AND A PLANE.
YEAH, IN FACT,
A FUCKING LEARJET,
RIGHT OUT ON THE STREET.
FULL TANK, CHECK
THE OIL AND THE TIRES.
BUT, BUT WE CAN'T--
WE CAN'T GET YOU ALL THIS.
( glass shattering )
STOP !
WOOO !
DO YOU LIKE ME ?
HUH ?
I THINK SHE DOES.
YOU'RE NOT SCARED
OF ME, ARE YOU ?
AHH ! AHHHH !
AHHH !
LEAVE HER ALONE,
YOU BASTARD !
EXCUSE ME, DID YOU
SAY SOMETHING ?
YOU KNOW SOMETHING ?
RED LOOKS GOOD ON YOU, BABY.
SHIT.
WHERE IS MY
FUCKING JET ?
( duct creaking loudly )
( audio equipment screeching )
( loud music stops )
UHHH !
NO !
FUCK YOU !
( screaming and moaning )
( EKG beeping )
IT'S NOT FAIR, MAX.
( Max )
IT'S NEVER FAIR.
I'M GONNA GET ON
HOME TO ANNA.
I'LL CALL YOU LATER.
( Helen sobbing )
WHAT ABOUT YOU ?
WHAT IF HE
WAKES UP ?
IT'S, UM...
IT'S JUST THAT HE'S CHANGED
SINCE WE GOT MARRIED.
WELL, PEOPLE--
PEOPLE CHANGE, EVERYTHING
CHANGES, SEASONS CHANGE.
IN FACT, CHANGE IS THE ONLY
PERMANENT THING AROUND.
ISN'T THAT RIGHT, DOCTOR ?
DIDN'T, DIDN'T YOU KNOW THAT ?
IT'S IN ALL THE PAPERS.
YOU DIDN'T KNOW THAT ?
HE'S ANGRY ALL
THE TIME, TOO.
WHAT MAKES YOU
ANGRY, MAX ?
WHAT MAKES MAX ANGRY ?
WELL, AH, BAD GUYS.
THE "BAD GUYS" ? MAX,
WE'RE TRYING TO TALK HERE.
CAN'T YOU EVER STOP
ACTING LIKE A COP ?
THAT'S WHAT I DO, BABY.
I'M A COP, OKAY ?
I CAN'T JUST DROP
MY LIFE OFF ON,
ON THE WAY HOME TO
GET DRY-CLEANED.
YOU CAN GET
ANOTHER JOB.
YEAH, LIKE WHAT ?
I DON'T KNOW.
SOMETHING.
SOMETHING THAT I DON'T
ALWAYS HAVE TO LISTEN TO.
YOU DON'T WANT
TO HEAR IT,
NO ONE WANTS TO
HEAR IT. WHY AM I HERE ?
WHY AM I HERE ?
( Anna )
THERE'S A REASON
FOR THAT.
TRY US, MAX.
REASONS NOT
TO BE CHEERFUL, WELL...
AH...
HOW ABOUT
FOR STARTERS MY...
MY FRIEND AND
PARTNER'S DYING.
AH, WOULD, UH, SOME OTHER
EXAMPLES BE HELPFUL, DOCTOR ?
WE ALL LOSE
PEOPLE, MAX.
YEAH, WELL,
I THINK COPS LOSE
JUST ABOUT
EVERYBODY.
I LOVE YOU,
MAX.
BUT I DIDN'T SIGN
ON FOR WAR DUTY.
THIS IS ONLY OUR, OUR
THIRD YEAR TOGETHER.
THINGS ARE GETTING
WORSE AND WORSE.
I KNOW.
I GUESS THE THINGS I SEE
IN THE STREET SOMETIME...
THEY KINDA MAKE...
DON'T MAKE
ME FEEL LIKE...
BABY, IT'S ME.
NOT YOU.
OH, HI, OFFICER.
( EKG beeping )
( accelerating EKG beeping )
HEY, MAXI-PAD !
HA-HA-HA !
HA-HA !
YOU TOOK 4
BULLETS IN YOU, MAN.
WHAT THE HELL ARE
YOU DOING HERE ?
HEY, MODERN MEDICINE,
WHAT CAN I TELL YOU ?
AT LEAST I'M NOT PISSING
OUT OF MY ARMPITS, YOU KNOW ?
LOOK, I GOT HIT, I WOKE
UP IN THE HOSPITAL.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT
THE FUCK THEY DID.
BUT WHATEVER THEY
DID, IT WORKED.
WHATEVER IT WAS,
IT WAS PRETTY FUCKING
WEIRD, MAN. LOOK AT YOU.
ARE YOU SURE
YOU'RE ALL RIGHT ?
I'VE STILL GOT A COUPLE
OF BANDAGES ON,
BUT THEY'LL BE
OFF AFTER AWHILE.
HOW ABOUT YOU AND I GOING
OUT AND GETTING SOME BAD GUYS ?
WHAT DO YOU SAY ?
WHAT ?
THERE'S NOT ENOUGH
SUGAR IN THIS DONUT.
IT'S 1 OF OUR
DIET DONUTS.
DIET ? I ASKED FOR A
DONUT WITH SUGAR !
JIM, COME ON, MAN.
DIET DONUTS ! WHERE DO
YOU THINK I COME FROM ?
THERE'RE ENOUGH SPRINKLES
ON THE DONUT, MAN. LET'S GO.
HEH-HEH-HEH !
JIM, LET'S GO.
GO WHERE ? I'M GONNA
GET MY DONUTS !
YOU GO ! I'LL BE
RIGHT THERE.
( Jim yelling )
EVERYBODY, DOWN !
GET DOWN !
( screaming )
GET IN THE CAR, JIM !
COME ON.
DAMN !
( horns blaring )
( siren wailing )
( growling )
RIDE'S OVER !
SHIT !
AHHH !
YOU HAVE THE RIGHT
TO REMAIN SILENT.
IF YOU REVOKE THAT RIGHT,
ANYTHING YOU SAY...
FUCK !
JIM !
WHAT HAPPENED ?
FOR CONSPICUOUS BRAVERY
AT THE CLUB 0 ARMED TAKEOVER,
CONGRATULATIONS,
OFFICER DIRE.
ANOTHER MEDAL TO ADD TO
YOUR REMARKABLE CAREER.
( crowd applauding )
LADIES AND GENTLEMEN,
THESE ARE YOUR
MEDAL OF VALOR
RECIPIENTS FOR 1993.
( crowd applauding )
HEY, DICK TRACY,
WAIT UP !
WHERE'S THAT KILLER
PARTNER OF YOURS ?
YOU GOT MORE MEDALS
THAN I GOT BUTTONS.
KNOCK YOURSELF OUT.
( labored sighing )
ANNA ?
( answering machine rewinding
and beeping )
Hi. This is Detective
Adam Garou
calling for
Officer Max Dire.
When you have a chance,
please come by my office.
We should talk.
( beeping )
( Anna )
Hi. I'm in Houston, with Mom.
I don't want you to
worry. I just need
some time, Max, you know,
to think about things.
I'm sorry. I'll talk to
you in a week or so, okay ?
I love you. Bye.
( beeping )
COME IN.
ADAM GAROU.
MAX DIRE.
THANKS FOR COMING,
PLEASE.
YOU'VE BEEN HAVING
A ROUGH TIME LATELY.
YEAH, A LITTLE BIT.
CONFUSING. ALL
THIS STUFF WITH JIM.
YEAH. MM-HMM.
HOME LIFE ISN'T
TERRIFIC EITHER.
SHE'S...
NOT HAPPY.
HOW THE HELL WOULD
YOU KNOW THAT ?
I'M DETECTIVE IN CHARGE
OF OFFICER CRISIS COUNSELING.
HAVE BEEN FOR
SOME TIME.
I THOUGHT YOU MIGHT
WANT TO MEET
WITH SOME COPS WHO'VE
HAD SIMILAR PROBLEMS.
THERE'S BEEN MORE THAN
1 COP HAD
HIS PARTNER BLOWN INTO ICU,
AND CAME OUT ACTING LIKE
1 OF THE BIONIC X-MEN ?
I MEAN MORE
THAN 1 COP'S
HAD A ROUGH TIME
DEALING WITH JOB STRESS.
SOMEONE LIKE YOU.
WHAT DO YOU MEAN
SOMEONE LIKE ME ?
MAX...
YOU'RE 1 OF THE BEST OFFICERS
ON THE FORCE, NO QUESTION.
YOU'RE SMART.
YOU'VE GOT NERVE.
A COMBINATION WE
CAN'T AFFORD TO LOSE.
WE KNOW YOU'VE GOT
SOME PROBLEMS, MAX.
WE JUST DON'T
WANT YOU TO QUIT.
SO, WHY IS THE DEPARTMENT SO
INTERESTED IN MY PRIVATE LIFE ?
IT'S OUR BUSINESS
TO KNOW.
TO CARE.
SOMETIMES IT'S GOOD TO
KNOW YOU'RE NOT ALONE.
OKAY, MAN,
WHAT'S THE DEAL ?
A GROUP OF COPS
MEETS TWICE A WEEK.
I SIT IN, SORT OF
STEER THINGS.
YOU KNOW, ANNA AND I
ALREADY TRIED THERAPY.
DID IT WORK ?
SO, YOU AND YOUR COPS,
YOU GET TOGETHER
AND YOU TALK ABOUT
YOUR PROBLEMS
AND YOU
KICK IT, RIGHT ?
NOW, HOW'S THAT ANY
DIFFERENT FROM WHAT
I COULD DO RIGHT DOWN
THERE AT THE BLUE NIGHT ?
MAX...
WHAT HAVE YOU
GOT TO LOSE ?
THERE'S A MEETING THIS
THURSDAY, A FEW SELECT COPS.
I HOPE YOU'LL
BE THERE.
WELL, I'LL TELL
YOU WHAT.
WHY DON'T YOU LET
ME THINK ABOUT IT ?
I'LL BE HERE.
( rhythmic beeping )
SO THE FUCKING PERP
SHAKES THE BANK,
STICKS THE MONEY
DOWN HIS PANTS AND RUNS.
HE GETS MAYBE 50 FEET BEFORE
THE DYE CARTRIDGE GOES, "POW !"
( Stratton )
WORST PAIR OF
BLUE BALLS EVER.
OH, MAN ! THAT SHIT'S
GOT TO HURT, MAN.
I HATE WHEN THAT HAPPENS.
FUCKING WAR
OUT THERE, MAN.
TOOK DOWN A HOMEBOY
THE OTHER DAY--
GODDAMN HIP-HOP
WITH A LAUNCHER
IN HIS TRUNK.
THE KID IS 14.
WHEN I WAS 14 YEARS
OLD, I WAS WATCHING
SOME  HAPPY DAYS ,
FONZIE-TYPE SHIT.
THAT SHOW'S A LITTLE TOO
COMPLICATED FOR STRATTON, HERE.
HEY, GO FUCK A CAT.
HEY, MAX.
HOW'S JIM DOING ?
MAN, HE WAS READY
TO PACK IT IN,
GET MARRIED, EVERYTHING.
GOES INTO THE HOSPITAL,
COMES BACK OUT ACTING LIKE
DIRTY HARRY
ON CRACK, MAN.
IT HAPPENS, MAN.
TOMBSTONE COURAGE.
NO, THIS IS WEIRD.
IT'S LIKE HE'S BACK,
BUT HE'S BIGGER
THAN LIFE.
WAY BIGGER.
( sergeant )
LIKE RAMON, MAN.
( Stratton )
YEAH.
PEREZ, HE'S A
HELL OF A COP, MAN.
SAME THING HAPPENED--
GOT GUNNED DOWN IN LINCOLN
HEIGHTS ABOUT A MONTH AGO.
( Max )
NO, MAN, I HEARD IT
WASN'T THAT BAD.
IT WAS BAD. HE'S BACK
IN UNIFORM IN, LIKE, 4 DAYS.
I MEAN, THAT
CAN'T HAPPEN, MAN.
HEY, HOW YOU DOING,
LAZARUS ?
I'M NOT MARRYING
HELEN, MAX.
OH, MAN ! COME ON,
THAT'S BULLSHIT !
YOU HAD A LITTLE ARGUMENT ?
I TELL YOU WHAT,
HAVE NO FEAR,
LET YOUR PARTNER,
MAX, BUY YOU A BEER.
COME ON, PUT YOU
IN A GOOD MOOD.
I WANTED TO THANK YOU
FOR BEING A GOOD PARTNER.
BEST COP I
EVER KNEW.
WHAT'S UP, JIMMY ? YOU
KNOW YOU CAN TELL US.
I'M OUTTA HERE.
ARE YOU
RETIRING ?
YEAH, I'M RETIRING.
YOU'RE CONFUSING THE SHIT OUT
OF ME. COME AND PLAY SOME POOL.
YOU'RE CONFUSING
ME, OKAY !
I'M GONNA BEAT YOUR ASS
AT SOME POOL. RACK IT UP, MAN.
LET'S SHOW THIS
BOY WHAT'S UP.
YOU CAN'T PLAY ANYWAY,
PUT THE BALLS TOGETHER.
LET'S DO IT.
I'VE GOT MONEY.
JIM!!!
THANKS FOR
COMING BY, MAX.
ANYTHING YOU WANT...
I KNOW JIM WOULD
WANT YOU TO HAVE IT.
I...
I HAVEN'T BEEN
IN HERE SINCE...
( Helen vomiting )
( doorbell ringing )
MAX...
GLAD YOU
COULD MAKE IT.
HEY, MAN, THIS IS
NOT A BAD PLACE
ON A DETECTIVE'S SALARY.
A FEW INVESTMENTS,
MONEY COMES IN.
I'VE BEEN SAVING
FOR A WHILE.
I'M SORRY
ABOUT JIM.
YOU MAY NOT KNOW
EVERYONE HERE.
THEY'RE NOT ALL
FROM YOUR DIVISION.
EVERYBODY,
MAX DIRE.
HI, MAX. WELCOME
TO THE CAUSE.
CASEY SPENCER.
HEY, NO, NO. YOU, YOU I KNOW.
YOU'RE, AH, RAMON PEREZ.
HEY, MAXWELL HOUSE.
QUE PASA ? QUE BIEN.
DOUG CRANE.
UH, NICE TO MEET YOU.
THIS GUY CAN
CHANGE YOUR LIFE.
IT'S KILLER STUFF.
YOU ALL HAVE 1
THING IN COMMON.
EACH OF YOU HAS
AN OUTSTANDING RECORD.
YOU'RE WARRIORS.
THAT'S WHAT YOU ALL WANTED TO
BE WHEN YOU JOINED THE FORCE.
BUT IT GOES DEEPER.
YOU ALSO WANTED TO STRIKE BACK
AT THE EVIL DECAY OUT THERE.
WE'VE ALL SUFFERED IN THE LINE
OF DUTY, MAX. YOU AREN'T ALONE.
MY SISTER,
MI HERMANITA .
WRONG PLACE,
WRONG TIME.
DRUG WAR CROSSFIRE.
AND I'VE BEEN SHOT. NO
FUCKING FUN, BOYS AND GIRLS.
LOOK AT THIS SHIT.
BEAUTIFUL LA !
I TRIED TO STOP A PIMP FROM
WHIPPING UP ON HIS WHORE.
THE BITCH STUCK A
BLADE IN MY BACK.
I WAS A DESK JOCKEY
TILL I MET ADAM.
NOW I HAVE MY
LEGS BACK.
( Garou )
DOUG LOST
SOMETHING, TOO.
LET'S NOT GET INTO
IT TONIGHT, OKAY ?
SAVINGS.
HOUSE.
GAMBLING.
YEAH, WELL, MY PARTNER
SHOT HIMSELF IN THE HEAD.
IT'S BEEN A GOOD WEEK.
YOUR WIFE
LEFT YOU ?
YEAH, THAT TOO.
SO WHAT, I GET IN
THE CLUB NOW,
OR I GOT TO FUCK
A CADAVER OR SOMETHING ?
( laughing )
DEEP DOWN, ALL OF
YOU BLAME YOURSELVES.
DON'T.
SOCIETY WANTS THE STREETS
CLEAN, QUIET NIGHTS...
BUT BY ITS RULES.
ARE CRIMINALS
RESTRICTED ? FUCK NO.
SO WHAT SHOULD WE DO ?
CIRCULATE A PETITION ?
THEY SAY WE'RE THE LAW.
I SAY, IF WE'RE THE LAW,
LET'S FUCKING BE THE LAW.
WHOA, WHOA,
WHOA, WHOA !
WHAT ARE YOU GUYS
TALKING ABOUT ?
THEY MEAN MORAL
CRIME VS. TECHNICAL.
MAX, IS IT MORAL TO LET
ANIMALS RULE THE STREETS ?
MORAL TO LET A
KILLER WALK BECAUSE
YOU FORGOT TO
READ HIM HIS RIGHTS ?
NO FUCKING WAY, MAN,
HOSE IT OFF THE STREETS.
CLEAN THE FUCKING
PENDEJO  SCUM.
UH, NOW, HOLD UP, ARE WE
TALKING LIKE SOME SORT OF
PSEUDO-CHARLIE BRONSON
VIGILANTE SHIT HERE ?
WE CALL IT JUSTICE.
LAW AND ORDER.
ADAM, I GOT TO
TALK TO YOU.
LATER.
NOW.
CASEY, TAKE GOOD
CARE OF MAX.
SURE.
MAX ?
YOU DON'T WANT TO
GO OUT TONIGHT.
WHY ?
'CAUSE, UM, MY MOTHER'S
SICK, UH, DOWN IN SAN DIEGO.
I GOT A-- I GOT A
FLIGHT IN AN HOUR.
YOU'RE LYING.
I DON'T LIKE THIS, ADAM.
I GET THE SHAKES,
NIGHTMARES.
I WANTED TO KNOW
WHAT IT'LL BE LIKE,
YOU KNOW, IN 5 YEARS.
YOU KNOW THAT COP,
MAX'S PARTNER ?
I WENT TO THE
HOSPITAL.
HE'S GONNA DIE
ANYWAY, RIGHT ?
SO I DOSED HIM WITH IT.
JUST, JUST, JUST TO SEE
WHAT WOULD HAPPEN.
I DON'T WANT TO BURN
OUT LIKE THAT, MAN.
IT'LL NEVER HAPPEN.
HE WAS PUMPED
FULL OF JUNK:
DEMEROL, MORPHINE,
CODEINE.
DRUG INTERACTION,
IT TIPPED HIM OVER.
THIS OPERATION WILL
BE OVER IN A WEEK.
YOU'RE YOUNG,
YOU CAN HANDLE IT.
DON'T BACK OUT
ON US NOW, DOUG.
WE NEED YOU.
HEY !
I CAN'T STAND
BEING IGNORED.
I THOUGHT THIS WAS
GONNA BE ABOUT
A LOT OF COPS TALKING
ABOUT THEIR PROBLEMS,
BUT OTHER THAN
THE ROMANTIC COUPLE
OUT THERE, NO
ONE'S TALKING.
YEAH, WELL...
WE TALK
SOMETIMES.
BUT... SOMETIMES WE
DO MORE THAN TALK.
LIKE WHAT ?
( Perez )
ANOTHER ONE OF TEAGUE'S
GUN-SELLING PARTIES.
( Liza )
YEAH, BULLETS
AND BUTTHEADS.
HEH-HEH, HEH-HEH.
RINGSIDE SEATS, MAN.
ODDS MAY BE A
LITTLE 1-SIDED,
MAYBE WE SHOULD CUT
HIM SOME SLACK, HUH ?
CAN I ASK YOU
GUYS A QUESTION ?
WHAT THE HELL ARE
YOU GUYS DOING ?
( Garou )
PROTECT AND SERVE.
HEY, MAN, I'M GONNA PROTECT
MY ASS ON OUT OF HERE.
I DON'T NEED TO BE A PART
OF THIS HALLOWEEN SHIT.
JUST WATCH...
THEN DECIDE.
( Doug )
YOU BETTER BE
CAREFUL, PEREZ.
YOU'RE GETTING
HITCHED TOMORROW.
YOU DON'T WANT TO
GET YOUR DICK SHOT OFF.
HEY. HEY, HEY !
WHAT IS THAT SHIT ?
VACCINATION.
FLU SEASON.
NO, IT'S NOT ILLEGAL
RIGHT ?
THAT SOME VITAMIN B12 ?
WHAT IS THAT SHIT, MAN ?
NOT EVEN CLOSE.
SHALL WE ?
( grenade exploding )
( machine guns firing )
RAMON.
THIS BETTER BE GOOD.
OH, IT'S GOOD.
I HATE THE HEAT.
WE GOT US A PROBLEM.
WHAT ?
I SAW GAROU AND HIS
LITTLE TEAM OF SUPER-COPS
TAKE OUT AT
LEAST 50 PEOPLE.
AND THIS IS GONNA
SOUND CRAZY,
BUT THEY WERE ON
SOME WILD DRUG.
AND IT HAD THEM
SO PUMPED UP,
THEY LOOKED
LIKE MONSTERS.
REALLY ?
YEAH.
WELL, MAYBE WE SHOULD
PUT STAKES THROUGH
THEIR HEARTS, OFFICER
DIRE, HOW ABOUT THAT ?
I'M SERIOUS, MAN,
I SAW WHAT I SAW.
I THINK I SHOULD
WRITE OUT A REPORT.
DETECTIVE GAROU
HAS REQUESTED
YOU BE PUT ON
SPECIAL ASSIGNMENT.
UNDER HIM.
IT'S QUITE AN HONOR.
A CAREER MOVE.
I'D THINK CAREFULLY ABOUT WHAT
I'D SAY OF HIM IF I WERE YOU.
AND, UH...
I WOULDN'T BE WRITING UP
ANY REPORTS ABOUT MONSTERS.
( speaking Spanish )
SINCE IT IS YOUR INTENTION
TO ENTER INTO MARRIAGE...
( speaking Spanish )
JOIN YOUR RIGHT HANDS
AND DECLARE YOUR CONSENT
BEFORE GOD AND HIS CHURCH.
( speaking Spanish )
DO YOU, RAMON PEREZ,
TAKE FOR YOUR
LAWFUL WIFE ESTRELLA
MALDONALDO,
TO HAVE AND TO HOLD
FROM THIS DAY FORWARD ?
( speaking Spanish )
FOR BETTER,
FOR WORSE...
( speaking Spanish )
IN SICKNESS
AND IN HEALTH...
( speaking Spanish )
UNTIL DEATH
DO YOU PART ?
NO.
I CAN'T !
( speaking Spanish )
( shouting in Spanish )
I DON'T WANT TO
GET MARRIED, OKAY !
YOU'RE JUST NOT
MY LIFE ANYMORE !
MAX.
HE'S DONE THE
RIGHT THING.
REALLY.
DON'T WORRY.
THEY'RE BEAUTIFUL,
AREN'T THEY ?
MM-HMM.
BEAUTIFUL ANIMALS
LOCKED AWAY IN A CAGE.
YOU GONNA ANSWER
MY QUESTIONS ?
SEE, A WOMAN LIKE YOU
MAKES ME CURIOUS.
MAX GETS CURIOUS,
HE DOES A LITTLE INVESTIGATING
LOOKS INTO THE OLD FILES.
AND GUESS WHAT I FIND ?
NOTHING IN THE COMPUTER.
NOTHING FROM THE TIME
WHEN YOU MET GAROU.
YOU GONNA TELL ME
WHAT'S GOING ON ?
JUSTICE, REAL KIND.
JUSTICE.
I GOT A FEELING THERE'S A LOT
MORE THAN THAT GOING ON.
AND A LOT MORE
THAN THAT WITH YOU.
I WAS LIVING OUT
IN CHATSWORTH,
IT WAS A HOME
INVASION.
THEY... KILLED MY
HUSBAND, FRANK.
TOOK $200 AND
SOME JEWELRY.
SOME TRADE, HUH ?
YOU KNOW, I HATED BEING
A WOMAN THEN.
SMALLER
AND WEAKER.
I WAS A COP, BUT I
COULDN'T DO ANYTHING.
6 MONTHS AGO,
I MET ADAM.
HE MADE ME PART
OF THE PACK.
THE PACK ?
YEAH.
YOU CAN BE
PART OF IT, TOO...
IF YOU WANT.
I LIKE YOU, MAX.
JOIN US.
( growling )
JOIN ME.
( snarling )
MAX !
YOU GOT A HALL PASS ?
LISTEN, BOB-MEISTER...
NOW, YOU KNOW THAT
WORKUP ON JIM, RIGHT ?
I'M GONNA NEED--
I'M GONNA NEED TO SEE THAT.
TAKE A NUMBER,
DRAGNET.
BOB-MEISTER, LISTEN TO ME,
NOW, I NEED TO SEE HIS BODY.
JESUS, HAVEN'T YOU EVER
TRIED ANY HERB TEA, MAN ?
COME ON, SHOW
ME THE BODY, MAN.
COME ON.
SO MANY DEAD.
TAKE OUT THE SLUG.
SCREW UP THE EVIDENCE CHAIN ?
YOU'LL GET ME A DETENTION.
IT'S A SUICIDE,
EVERYBODY SAW IT,
HE SHOT HIMSELF
IN THE HEAD.
TAKE THE SLUG OUT.
OKAY.
BUT I DON'T KNOW WHAT YOU'RE
TRYING TO PULL HERE, MAN.
GAROU TOLD ME
NOT TO LET ANYONE
DOWN HERE TO
TOUCH THE BODY
UNTIL HE LOOKED
AT IT HIMSELF, YOU KNOW ?
HIS SILVER DOLLAR.
IT'S HIS GOOD LUCK PIECE.
SAVED HIS LIFE ONCE.
IT WASN'T IN HIS POCKET WHEN
HOMICIDE CHECKED THE BODY.
YOU LOST ME, MAN.
PUT HIM BACK.
QUICK.
( banging )
MAX !
WHERE'S GAROU ?
HE'S NOT HERE.
WHAT DID GAROU
DO TO JIM CASEY ?
MAX, UM...
ADAM WOULD HAVE TOLD
YOU SOONER OR LATER, HE'S--
TOLD ME WHAT
SOONER OR LATER ?
WELL...
ADAM ISN'T
JUST A DETECTIVE.
YOU KNOW, HE'S
ALSO A SCIENTIST.
A BIOCHEMIST.
AND THAT STUFF YOU
SAW US TAKE, THAT SERUM.
ADAM CREATED IT.
WHEN WE TAKE IT, MAX, WE
CAN DO JUST ABOUT ANYTHING.
YOU KNOW, WE'RE
FASTER, STRONGER...
BETTER.
WHAT THE FUCK
DOES THAT MEAN ?
THOSE ASSHOLES ON THE STREET,
THEY'RE REVVED ALL THE TIME.
WE CAN'T COMPETE
WITH THEM.
NOT WITHOUT
AN EDGE.
YOU KNOW, YOU SAW RAMON
GET SHOT AND HE LIVED.
WITH IT, WE HEAL
IMMEDIATELY.
NO, NO, YOU DON'T
UNDERSTAND.
THIS STUFF IS POTENT.
FIRST ONE'S FREE.
NO, I DON'T PUSH SHIT
LIKE THAT IN MY BODY.
JESUS, MAX, WE'RE NOT
TALKING COCAINE HERE.
YOU TAKE FLU SHOTS ?
VITAMINS ?
THAT'S ALL THIS IS.
A SUPER VACCINE.
LOOK.
THE ANSWER IS "NO."
YES.
YOU HAVE TO.
NO, I DON'T.
ONLY 2 THINGS I HAVE
TO DO: GET OLD AND DIE.
( moaning )
( snarling )
MMM.
MMMM. MAX.
MAX.
WOULDN'T YOU
LIKE TO TEAR INTO
EACH OTHER LIKE
THAT EVERY NIGHT ?
YOU KNOW WE JUST BROKE
ABOUT 30 PENAL CODES ?
I HAVE THIS ANIMAL
MAGNETISM.
BE PART OF
THE PACK, MAX.
LOOK, IF YOU DON'T LIKE IT,
YOU'RE STRAIGHT
BACK ON REGULAR
ASSIGNMENT.
BE A CHRISTIAN SCIENTIST
IF IT MAKES YOU HAPPY, BUT...
AT LEAST TRY IT.
YOU KNOW WHAT ?
I THINK I'M GONNA
HAVE TO "JUST SAY NO."
PLEASE, MAX,
JUST ONCE. PLEASE !
I DON'T MIND YOU ASKING,
BUT THE ANSWER IS "NO."
I GOTTA GO.
MAX ?
I'M SORRY.
( vase shattering )
UNHH !
AHHHH !
IT'S DESTROYING WHAT
IT DOESN'T NEED.
( growling )
NOW DO YOU
UNDERSTAND ?
SHIT !
LET'S GO FOR A RIDE.
HERE'S HOW
IT WORKS:
THE FIRST TIME YOU
TAKE IT, IT CHANGES YOU.
NO SHIT.
YOU NEVER GO BACK
TO HOW YOU WERE BEFORE.
IT REVS YOU UP.
IT'S A MIRACLE CURE.
HEALS THE SICK.
YEAH, AND RAISES
THE DEAD.
TAKING MORE JUST
MAKES IT BETTER.
WE USUALLY DOSE UP
JUST BEFORE WE GO OUT.
IT REALLY HELPS YOU WIN
FRIENDS AND INFLUENCE PEOPLE.
YEAH, ESPECIALLY
WHEN I.A. FINDS OUT, HUH ?
YOU WORRY TOO MUCH.
NOW REMEMBER, WHEN YOUR
ADRENALIN RISES, YOU'LL CHANGE.
LOOK LIKE SOMETHING
OUT OF A THEME PARK.
IT'S KIND OF
COOL, ACTUALLY.
IT SCARES THE SHIT
OUT OF THE BAD GUYS.
ONE OF TEAGUE'S
ICEHOUSES, HUH ?
LET'S DO IT.
HEY !
YOU ARE GONNA
BUST THEM ?
THAT WAS HER IDEA.
HMMPH, YOU WANT TO
LEND ME YOUR KEYS ?
YOU NEED TO TAKE YOUR
NARROW ASS ON HOME.
WHAT THE HELL ARE
WE GONNA DO NOW ?
IT'S A GOOD THING WE TOOK
THAT DYNAMIC TENSION COURSE.
OH, YEAH.
( wolf howling )
FUN, HUH ?
( Casey grunting )
( growling )
FUCK !
OKAY, STRIKE 3.
THAT ASSHOLE'S FUCKED WITH
MY DEALS FOR THE LAST TIME.
MY PEOPLE INSIDE TELL
ME HIS NAME'S GAROU.
HE'S HEAD OF SOME
SPECIAL TEAM.
SPECIAL TEAM ? THEY
WERE FUCKING ANIMALS.
YOU KNOW, I THOUGHT
IF I LEFT HIM ALONE,
MAYBE HE'D
JUST GO AWAY.
LIKE THE FLU.
YEAH, MR. TEAGUE,
BUT WHAT IF THESE GUYS
DECIDE TO SCREW UP
THE CONVENTION AT
THE DOCK NEXT WEEK ?
EXCUSE ME ?
I DIDN'T GET IT.
HANDLE IT.
HANDLE IT ?
YOU MEAN LIKE I CAN
PLAN IT, HANDLE IT ?
THINK SNEAKERS:
"JUST FUCKING DO IT."
OH !
BEAUTIFUL.
NO PROBLEM.
HEY, DON'T WORRY,
MR. TEAGUE.
STEPHAN'LL TAKE
CARE OF EVERYTHING.
IT'S UNDER CONTROL.
I'VE BEEN HEARING LOTS OF TALK
ABOUT SAFE STREETS, GAROU.
BUT I HAVEN'T
SEEN RESULTS.
APART FROM
THAT TAKEDOWN
AT THE BEACH PARTY
THE OTHER NIGHT.
CHANGE TAKES TIME.
I'VE GOT NERVOUS
PEOPLE IN CITY HALL.
WITH ANOTHER ONE OF
TEAGUE'S ARMS DEALS
GOING DOWN IN A FEW DAYS,
THEY WANT RESULTS.
I GET RESULTS... MY WAY.
YOU KNEW THAT GOING IN.
TALK TO P.D. IN DALLAS,
MIAMI, DETROIT.
ASK THEM IF THEIR CITIES
WEREN'T SAFER WHEN I WAS DONE.
I DON'T CARE ABOUT THEM,
I CARE ABOUT LA.
IT'S NICE TO SEE
YOU CARING, CHIEF.
YOU'RE A REAL PRICK,
AREN'T YOU, DETECTIVE ?
IS THAT A DESPERATE
CRY FOR LOVE ?
( growling )
( door opening )
SOMEONE'S BEEN BAD.
YOU TOLD ME TO DO
WHAT I HAD TO.
I'M SORRY
I SHOT HIM.
I DIDN'T KNOW HOW
ELSE TO GET HIM ON IT.
I DON'T GIVE A SHIT
THAT YOU SHOT HIM.
I DIDN'T TELL YOU
TO FUCK HIM.
DIDN'T YOU HEAR ME ?
YEAH.
THEN YOU MUST
HAVE FORGOT.
'CAUSE YOU'RE ONLY
SUPPOSED TO FUCK ME.
I'M TOP DOG.
REMEMBER ?
DO YOU LIKE HIM ?
YES.
( snarling )
( growling )
DO YOU LIKE HIM ?
NO.
NO, I...
I DON'T LIKE HIM.
( snarling )
( growling )
( all )
SURPRISE !
( applauding and chattering )
GOOD TO SEE YOU.
HAPPY BIRTHDAY, MAX !
THE BIG 3-0.
( applauding and cheering )
NOW LISTEN,
I HEAR YOU GUYS
ARE DOING SOME
GREAT STUFF DOWN THERE.
SO...
I THINK IT'S TIME YOU TAKE
YOUR SILVER MEDAL BACK.
( applauding )
AH !
( rapid heart beating )
HOW WAS HOUSTON ?
UM, A LOT OF GUYS
IN BIG HATS.
FLEMING CALLED AND THOUGHT
THAT I SHOULD BE HERE.
I MISSED YOU.
BABE, YOU LOOK
TERRIBLE.
WHAT'S THE MATTER WITH YOU ?
LOOK AT YOUR FACE.
I'M OKAY.
NO, YOU'RE NOT OKAY.
COME ON, TELL ME
WHAT'S...
I'M COOL.
IT'S ME !
MAX, TELL ME.
BABY,
I LOVE YOU.
WHATEVER IT IS, WE'LL
GET THROUGH IT TOGETHER.
DON'T,
IT HURTS !
DAMMIT !
( rock music playing )
MAX, YOU KNOW
THAT THING
I DIDN'T DO TO
YOUR DEAD PARTNER ?
WELL, I RAN A CBC ON HIS BLOOD,
MAN. HIS CRIT WAS HIGH.
THE EOSINOPHIL COUNT
WAS WAY UP THERE.
WHAT I'M TRYING TO SAY IS,
THERE'S SOMETHING IN HIS BLOOD.
WHAT'S UP, MAN ?
HOW YOU DOING ?
HAVE A BEER, MAN !
WHAT'S YOUR PROBLEM ?
IT'S YOUR BIRTHDAY,
LET'S GO ! LET'S GO ! HEY !
WHAT ?
HEY, LOOK, MAN. HERE COMES
YOUR NEW BUSINESS PARTNER.
( eerie music playing )
HEY, IT'S
PRESENT TIME, MAX.
HEY, HAPPY BIRTHDAY,
MAXIE !
JUST WHAT YOU ALWAYS
NEEDED THERE, BUDDY.
COME ON, OPEN IT UP.
HEY, DON'T BE SHY.
CAREFUL, YOU'RE GONNA BUST IT.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING ?
HA-HA-HA !
WE HAVE TO GO, MAX.
I HAVE A VERY SPECIAL
PRESENT FOR YOU.
NICE PARTY, POOPER.
I NEVER SHOULD'VE
COME BACK.
ANYTHING THAT FEELS
THIS GOOD, MAN,
CAN'T BE GOOD FOR YOU.
IT HASN'T HURT ME
AND I'VE BEEN
TAKING IT A LONG TIME.
YEAH, HOW LONG ?
LONG ENOUGH.
SINCE FRANCE.
FRANCE ?
I GREW UP THERE.
WHEN I WAS A KID, MAX, IT WAS
SAFE TO WALK THE STREETS.
YOU COULD LEAVE YOUR HOME
AND NOT FEEL LIKE PREY.
YEAH.
LOOKS GOOD.
IT'S GOING TO BE
A CLOSED CASKET.
( snarling )
WE NEED GUNS.
TOUGH GUYS, HUH ?
FUCK.
WE NEED GUNS.
( helicopter hovering )
( glass shattering )
WE NEED A
NEW VEHICLE.
CHIEF WANTS TO
SEE YOU. NOW.
OH, YEAH, MAX,
THERE'S SOME PIECE OF SHIT
DOWN IN HOLDING.
HE'S RANTING
ABOUT GAROU.
YOU MIGHT WANT
TO CHECK IT OUT.
( door slamming )
I HOPE TO HELL YOU KNOW
WHAT YOU'RE DOING.
SOMETHING WEIRD
ABOUT HIM, MAX.
YOU WANT ME
TO STAY ?
I GOT IT.
I'M FROM GAROU.
WHO ARE YOU ?
PART OF HIS TEAM.
( laughing )
I DON'T WANT UNDERLINGS.
I WANT HIM.
( growling )
( sniffing )
YOU'RE ON IT.
GET OUT WHILE
YOU CAN, BRO.
WHO THE FUCK
ARE YOU, MAN ?
DETECTIVE TOM DAVIES.
MIAMI P.D.
WHO DID THIS
TO YOU, MAN ?
IT'S YOUR BOSS.
HE'S A FUCKING
MONSTER.
WHEN ?
2 YEARS AGO.
( sniffing )
YOU'RE HOLDING. GIVE ME !
HEY !
WHAT DID HE
DO TO YOU ?
DO TO YOU !?!
I DID THE JOB FOR HIM,
CLEANED UP CITY.
AND THE REST OF
YOUR PACK ?
DEAD.
I'M THE ONLY ONE LEFT.
HE KILLED THEM. I GOT AWAY.
HEH-HEH.
YOU FOLLOWED HIM HERE
TO GET SOME MORE OF THAT STUFF.
FUCK NO!
I CAME TO KILL HIM !
IT'S A GODDAMN CAVE !!!
( snarling )
RELAX !
I TOOK IT
TOO MANY TIMES.
I CAN'T GO BACK.
IT STRIPS YOUR GLANDS.
IT LEAVES YOU
UNEMPLOYABLE.
( snarling )
MOTHERFUCKER !!
WE'VE GOT WORK TO DO.
I'M TIRED, MAN. I'M GONNA
TAKE A LITTLE BREAK.
JESUS, WHAT
THE FUCK HAPPENED ?
NOBODY'S ALLOWED
A GUN IN HERE.
HE ATTACKED OFFICER DIRE.
I HAD TO SHOOT.
YEAH, LIKE
THE MAN SAID.
MAX !
MAXIE !
WHAT THE HELL
HAPPENED, MAN ?
THIS IS MY BRAIN.
THIS IS YOU
ON MY BRAIN.
ANY QUESTIONS ?
YOU GOT US ALL HOOKED
ON YOUR OWN BODY, MAN.
LOW OVERHEAD.
YOU'RE A MOTHERFUCKING
WEREWOLF.
WAS. THERE'S NO WORD
FOR WHAT I AM NOW.
MY FAMILY WAS
HUNTED DOWN LIKE ANIMALS.
PREYED ON.
I HATED BEING AT THE MERCY
OF THE LUNAR CYCLE.
IT'S SO PRIMITIVE.
IT'S PATHETIC.
I LEARNED TO
DIRECT IT.
BIOFEEDBACK.
DRUGS.
I REFINED IT.
MADE IT MINE
TO CONTROL AND TO GIVE.
NO, NO. UH-UH.
HE'S ONLY SUPPOSED TO
CHANGE ON THE FULL MOON.
FULL MOON ?
YOU'RE A ROMANTIC, MAX.
SO WAS I IN THE BEGINNING.
WHEN I CAME TO AMERICA,
THIS WAS THE GREATEST
COUNTRY ON EARTH.
I WANTED TO GIVE SOMETHING
BACK, SO I BECAME A COP.
PUT TOGETHER SPECIAL TEAMS
TO START CLEANING THE CITIES.
AND IT WORKS.
HE'S INFECTING
ALL OF YOU, HUH ?
THIS NEO-NAZI,
SUPER-COP BULLSHIT ?
LOOK, YOU'RE SWALLOWING
HIS INSANITY RIGHT NOW.
GO AHEAD,
SHOOT UP, MAN.
SHOOT UP !
WAIT.
TAKE IT.
( snarling )
MAX, NO !
YOU SICK MOTHERFUCKER.
TONIGHT, WE TAKE BACK
THE STREETS.
YEAH, YEAH. TAKE BACK
THE STREETS, HUH ?
I DID A LITTLE RESEARCH
ON YOU, GAROU.
FULL ECLIPSE
EACH TIME, HUH ?
EVERY CITY YOU WENT TO:
DETROIT, DALLAS, MIAMI.
EXCEPT FOR
ONE LITTLE THING
I BET YOU DIDN'T TELL
THE REST OF THE TEAM, HUH ?
EACH TIME, YOU'RE
THE ONLY ONE LEFT ALIVE, MAN.
EVERYBODY ELSE IS DEAD...
EXCEPT FOR YOU.
YOU'RE SMART, MAX.
WHY DO YOU THINK
I CHOSE YOU ?
THE PROCESS DOESN'T
END WITH ME.
I NEED SOMEONE TO CARRY ON
AFTER I'M GONE.
IT'S A HELL OF A GIG.
YOU SURE YOU DON'T
WANT SOME ?
OR DO I EXECUTE
ANOTHER TRACHEOTOMY ?
NOT TODAY,
MOTHERFUCKER.
CASEY !
OHHHH !
COME ON. WE GOT TO
GET SOMEWHERE SAFE.
TO THE BEACH.
HE CAN'T PICK UP OUR SCENT.
IT HASN'T BEEN THAT LONG
SINCE WE SHOT UP.
WE'RE GONNA HEAL.
( coughing )
WHAT'S WRONG ?
I HAVEN'T BEEN TAKING IT.
I TRIED TO DRY OUT.
THAT FALL HURT ME BAD.
YOU GOT SOME. GO AHEAD,
DOSE UP OR YOU'RE GONNA DIE.
YOU TAKE IT. HEAL YOURSELF.
DESTROY GAROU.
AHHHH !
( growling )
( Perez )
WHERE WE GOING ?
SAN PEDRO.
THE CONSORTIUM'S MEETING.
I THOUGHT WE WERE
JUST TAKING OUT TEAGUE.
WE ARE.
HE'S JUST
THE SYMPTOM.
TONIGHT WE BEGIN TO
PURGE THE DISEASE.
IT'S OVER, GAROU.
I'VE HAD ENOUGH OF YOU
AND YOUR COMMANDO TACTICS.
YOU AND YOUR PEOPLE
ARE OFF ASSIGNMENT.
WHAT THE HELL'S
HAPPENED ?
I'LL GET BACK TO YOU
ON THAT.
HEY, LISTEN, WHERE'S
GAROU ? DO YOU KNOW ?
HE'S UP ON THE ROOF.
SOME HUSH-HUSH OPERATION
ON THE DOCKS.
ARE YOU OKAY ?
Air 54, you are not
cleared for takeoff.
Repeat. Air 54, you are
not cleared for takeoff.
CHIEF !
NO !
( gun firing )
Hey, Bob-meister, listen,
I need a favor.
FAVOR ?
WHAT KIND OF FAVOR ?
Silver nitrate, you know,
the liquid kind,
I need a mixture, man.
OKAY.
And I need it with
some other drugs.
ALL RIGHT.
Yeah, morphine,
Demerol, anything.
IF I CAN.
Just make it strong.
ALL RIGHT.
( Teague gasping )
YOU WANT TEAGUE ?
( Teague )
TELL THIS ANIMAL
TO LET ME GO.
LET THAT
MOTHERFUCKER GO.
TAKE HIM.
YOU FUCKING
BASTARD.
A SILVER BULLET.
SO CLEVER.
GO AHEAD,
MAKE YOUR DAY.
( Perez )
YOU KILLED HIM.
OUCH.
DIDN'T YOU
GET MY MEMO ?
A FULL ECLIPSE PROTECTS
ME FROM EVERYTHING.
INCLUDING SILVER.
NOW, YOU WANT TO SEE
SOMETHING REALLY SCARY ?
NO !
( crane engine starting )
( growling )
( crane engine chugging )
( wind howling )
SUPER-COP SILVER
COCKTAIL ! CHEERS !
HEY, MAX.
MAX...
DON'T LET IT ALL...
END HERE.
LIE DOWN...
IN MY BLOOD.
TAKE MY POWER.
PROTECT THE INNOCENT.
HEY, PRETTY LADY,
YOU KNOW WHAT ?
HI. WHAT ?
ALL THIS GOOD AIR'S
BAD FOR MY HEALTH.
BUT I THINK I'M STARTING
TO LIKE IT HERE.
GREAT.
UNTIL WE HAVE
TO MOVE AGAIN.
HEY, I GOT ANOTHER
CONVICTION TODAY.
YOU'RE SUCH
A GOOD COP.
OUCH !
MMMM.
I GOT WORK TO DO.