23.976 English
Snohomish. Snohomish.
Everett next.
Hey, gorgeous.
Hey.
How you doing?
How was the funeral?
I can't talk about it yet.
Well, I'm glad you're back.
Did you miss me?
Good.
- How's the office?
- Boring without you there.
No office intrigue? I wouldn't want
to miss anything.
Well, let's see. Jerry switched
from regular to decaffeinated.
Oh, Erica went out with some guy in
a rock band who bit her ass all night.
- Interesting.
- She thought so.
She's seeing him again.
And Ben Jordan was released
on parole.
Don't tell me they relocated
him in Snohomish.
Well, there's good news,
and there's bad news.
What's the bad news?
They've relocated him
to Snohomish.
- What's the good news?
- He's your case and not mine.
Dorothy, your husband's missed
our last five sessions.
He obviously doesn't
want to change.
Or can't change.
I think it's time to consider
going to the shelter.
Miss Mathews, that's my home.
That's where I get my mail.
That's my phone number.
I'm not saying he's a monster.
I'm saying he's sick...
...and he needs help. I know it's hard,
but if you press charges...
...the court will make him
get the help he needs.
I have to go.
Before I miss my bus for work.
All right, Dorothy.
I'm making an appointment
for your husband...
...for next Wednesday at 3.
If he doesn't show, I'll be
at your apartment Thursday...
...and we'll settle it one way
or the other.
Miss Mathews, thank you.
I heard a couple of new jokes
while you were gone.
They're really offensive.
So, what else is new?
Okay. You wanna hear
the dead-baby joke or the sexist joke?
What? No black jokes?
Yeah, I got a racist joke,
but those aren't funny anymore.
Give me the...
Give me the sexist joke.
Good. What's the difference
between a whore and a bitch?
Gee, I'm not sure, Steve-O.
What is the difference?
A whore will sleep with anybody, and
a bitch will sleep with anybody but me.
Oh, God.
How you doing? Good to see you.
- We still on for dinner?
- I'll see you later.
- Can I help you?
- Yes, they say you can. Is this you?
How old?
Four, maybe.
The eyes.
They're very pretty.
What can I do for you?
I'm here to see my social worker.
My parole officer told me
to see you right away.
Ben Jordan.
You really should have called...
...and set up an appointment.
All right.
Since you're here,
you might as well sit down.
Do you like mysteries?
What?
The book you're reading.
I like the Travis McGee novels a lot.
Maybe you should try David Goodis.
He wrote a book called The Burglar.
It's excellent.
I'll keep an eye out for him.
I've been reading your file.
Good reading?
As a matter of fact, it is.
Hundred and forty-six IQ.
You're a pretty smart fella.
Oh, I don't know.
Ted Bundy had 150.
Mr. Jordan, I'm not here
to judge your past.
I'm here to help you with your future.
What you did in prison was
impressive, but I'm not gonna lie.
With your record, it's not gonna
be easy getting you work.
Right now, the best you can expect
is minimum wage.
Certainly nothing up to your
capabilities, but if we work together...
Miss Mathews?
Is it all right if I smoke?
What?
It helps ease the frustration.
You're not taking this very seriously,
are you?
Can we skip the therapy?
I'm seeing a shrink for that.
I need a job.
All right. I'll give you a referral
to EDD before you leave.
Can I have it now?
All right.
Ask for...
...Walt Deeter.
Good. It's a start.
Are we done?
I guess.
Ben, what did you do
when you arrived in town?
Went to see my parole officer.
After that.
Went for a walk.
I tried calling my mom.
Bought a pair of socks.
Oh, and I had pizza.
How did it taste?
The best cardboard pizza
I've ever had.
I can imagine.
No, you can't.
What did you think of Jordan?
What do you mean?
Did I think he was cute?
Ever since I saw him today,
whenever I go pee, I just get...
Look, I was surprised
when I saw him...
...and I was wondering if you had
the same reaction.
No, I think, for a serial killer,
he is a damn fine-looking guy.
He's not a serial killer.
Right. He only kills
the ones he loves.
Look, I didn't talk to him. You did.
What do you think?
Good.
I think maybe he's changed
over the years.
I read all the paperwork on him.
He deserved that parole.
He's intelligent.
He has a kind of charm.
He got his master's degree
in psychology while he was inside.
I don't think he's the same man
he was 15 years ago.
Look, if a kid robs
a liquor store, okay...
...and he shoots the guy behind
the counter...
...I can believe that, after 15 years,
that kid might not do it again.
Whatever it was that made Jordan
pick up that knife, slaughter his wife...
...and his unborn baby
scares the hell out of me.
Why?
Because I don't like
how it makes me feel.
How's that?
Like they should have executed him.
Yeah, he's back inside.
Hauled him out of the house last week
with a couple of keys.
- Mr. Samuels?
- Yeah.
Hi. Laura Mathews.
Ben Jordan's social worker.
Look, my man, I'll call you later.
Damn. Old Ben ain't do too bad
for himself, did he?
Most social workers I seen,
they look like...
Well, you know.
Well, now, let's see...
Jordan. Jordan.
I have some questions I need
answered in order to find...
...Mr. Jordan work
in my community.
Fine.
- Is it Mrs. Or Ms.?
- Ms.
Well, Ms. Mathews...
...l'll help you, but you ain't gonna find
that boy a job.
What makes you say that?
Well, if I owned a hardware store
or a little gas station somewhere...
...I wouldn't want that sick S.O.B.
On my property.
I'll find Ben work, all right.
I'm very good at my job.
Well, go ahead and do that then.
And good luck to you. I mean that.
So, what can you tell me
about the Kathy Tudor murder?
On the night of August 4, 1975, Ben
Jordan took a kitchen carving knife...
...and stabbed his better half
30 times.
- Thirty-six.
- Oh, my mistake. She was...
Six months pregnant.
Now tell me something I don't know.
There was a witness...
...who heard the girl scream
around 11:30.
She didn't think much about it, and
went back to watch Johnny Carson.
Then a little past midnight,
she hears something else.
So she goes to her window and sees
Jordan stagger out of his house...
...with what looks like
a carving knife in his hand...
...toss it on the front lawn,
get in his car and drive off.
The cops found him passed out drunk
in his car a little before dawn.
The knife was the murder weapon.
His prints was all over it.
And...
...the movie camera he filmed
the murder with was his own.
What movie camera?
Cops found a Super-8 movie camera
at the scene.
Jordan filmed the murder.
It's in the police files in Ellensburg.
Way I understand it, it makes...
...Nightmare on Elm Street
look like Charlotte's Web.
Still want to find him a job?
I'm sorry I'm late.
Could I sit down?
Sure. Make yourself comfortable.
I...
I have a lot I'd like
to talk about.
Good.
Where would you like to start?
I heard you were
at Lee Samuels' office.
You were nosing around, weren't you?
I wish you wouldn't.
I don't think you're in a position
to tell me how to do my job.
It might not be much,
but it is my life.
Did he tell you about the film?
- Yes.
- Do you want to know why?
- Sure.
- So do I.
You want to talk about it?
I'm only here because I have to be.
If you can get me a job,
I'll be grateful, and I'll walk.
Would it make you feel better
if I told you I didn't kill her?
- Did you?
- Are you saying you'd believe me?
Give me a chance.
Gee, I don't know.
You've built up some pretty good
defenses, haven't you?
Yeah. Avoidance, denial.
I know the terms. They don't apply.
- You sure?
- Yes. Are you?
You know what we're doing?
A little yard-bird sparring.
You mean you're playing games.
I don't pry into your past.
I have to know who you are.
You have my file.
I can't help you if you won't let me.
Let me tell you something.
If we were to have this kind
of an exchange in the joint...
...one of us would end up
with a shank between the ribs.
That isn't funny.
No, it isn't.
This was the stuff on the reel
he shot first.
They found a shitload
of these little reels.
Jordan was quite
the home-movie nut.
And I don't mind telling you...
...this film was a bitch to get.
Perfect picture of American
white-trash marital bliss.
- What happened?
- His camera must have run out of film.
- So he didn't actually film the murder.
- Not for lack of trying.
But you never see Jordan
actually kill her.
Disappointed?
You made this film sound
like proof positive that he did it.
What do you need?
To see the knife jabbing her belly?
Yeah, that is what I need.
That's what I was expecting to see.
I was confused before I watched this,
and now I'm even more confused.
Confused?
Confused about what? His guilt?
Kathy not only knew the murderer,
she was comfortable with him.
She offered him a beer.
She did this little dance for him.
I seriously doubt she'd act
that way for just some burglar.
Maybe it was somebody
else she knew.
Yeah. You can say "maybe"
all goddamn day...
...but I don't think you
really believe that.
I'm playing devil's advocate here.
That wasn't a crime of passion.
That was planned,
something a serial killer might do.
He planned to kill her,
he even filmed the event...
...and after he did it,
he got blind stinking drunk?
First, he uses method,
then he's out of control. Come on.
Maybe you give too much credit.
Maybe he isn't a natural-born killer.
Maybe he got himself all drunk
because what he did freaked him out.
- Now who's Mr. Maybe?
- Yeah, maybe so.
But my "maybes" is better than your
"maybes." I gotta get my butt home.
Lee, I sure appreciate you getting
a copy of that film for me.
Like you said,
we're working together.
Would you mind too terribly
if I borrowed it for a while?
Would you mind if I ask you why?
Good night, Ms. Mathews.
Good night, Mr. Samuels.
Hello?
Yeah. Hi, it's Ben.
Ben Jordan.
How did you get my number?
Oh, from the phone book.
There were two L. Mathews.
One of them was a dentist.
But I've been thinking...
...maybe I haven't been fair.
You're only trying to help,
and I've been slapping you around.
Are you still there?
Laura?
Yes.
I'm calling...
...to say I'm sorry.
That's all.
Good night.
If you'd committed a crime and
the evidence was against you...
...how long would it take
to bring a guilty verdict?
- Laura.
- I'm just asking.
A day or two.
Look, don't get emotional
about this one.
Are you being protective?
Yeah. I'm being a little protective.
Well, bless your heart.
Okay, Nancy Drew, listen.
You know, one of these days, you're
gonna realize that this platonic shit...
...is for the birds
and that it has been me all along.
But that glorious and magical day...
...is not going to happen
if Ben Jordan kills you.
Did you ever suppose
that he might be innocent?
Yeah.
A man goes to trial...
...and he is innocent
until proven guilty.
And then he's convicted, and he's
guilty unless proven innocent.
So don't make me to be some
narrow-minded jerk...
...because you're being naive.
There are things
that don't make any sense.
Yeah, I'm sure there are.
But you're not a detective.
You're a social worker. So...
...talk to him, give him advice,
find him a job. Speaking of which...
...I think I got him one.
- You did?
- Where?
- H & R Meats.
Swing shift. Strong back stuff,
strictly donkey work.
That's okay. He just needs a job.
Did you tell him?
No, I figured he'd rather
hear it from you.
Thanks for the help, Steve.
Sure. But if somebody ends up
hanging from a meat hook...
...I am not taking responsibility.
I wanted to give you something...
...for your help.
I got it...
This is beautiful.
Did you do this?
I noticed you like flowers.
You should really thank Steve.
When I get a chance, I will.
It's been a while since I had a drink.
I must admit I'm surprised.
- About the job?
- That we're having dinner.
I'm not exactly your mother's idea
of a date.
You don't know my mother.
Anyway, this isn't a date.
Oh, what is it?
Support for the poor
and misguided?
You should put that on your wall.
You're not making this easy.
I didn't know it was supposed to be.
I'm sorry.
I'm doing it again.
I've been away too long.
I forget how to behave sometimes.
You want to talk about
something else?
What about you?
Who is Laura Mathews?
Or does it only go one way?
I don't think I want to play.
I don't mean bare your soul.
I mean...
...little stuff like...
...where were you born?
Who would your mother approve of?
Another time, maybe.
Avoidance?
Denial.
I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to scare you.
Door was open.
Would it make you feel better
if we had some more light?
I'd feel better.
This is good work.
My father did it. He died
before he could finish it.
- Well, it's nice.
- What are you doing here?
I've been trying to understand
your interest in me.
I've been turning it around in my head.
It doesn't make any sense.
I mean, maybe it's this angel-of-mercy
picture on your wall.
Or maybe you really
do like mysteries.
So I thought I'd ask.
We'll talk about it tomorrow
in the office.
I don't think you're being honest.
Please.
I'm making you nervous.
Yes.
All right.
Give me a second.
You want to know if I'm innocent?
The last time I was innocent
was 15 years ago in court.
Innocence doesn't exist in prison.
It doesn't matter.
And nobody cares.
If you care...
...stay away from me.
Don't ask me out to dinner.
I get confused.
You can't go out in that.
I'll give you a ride home.
Rain's never killed anybody.
Here. Take this.
Angel of mercy.
Who the hell are you?
- Mr. Tudor?
- Yeah. That's me.
Hi. My name is Laura Mathews.
I'd like to talk to you
about Ben Jordan.
Hey, I'd love to talk
about that cocksucker.
You want some cocoa?
Oh, no, thanks.
Five years early for good behavior.
What the fuck is good
about his behavior?
It's a slap in the face
to my daughter...
...to me, to the whole community.
Could you tell me a little
about Kathy's friends?
She had a few girlfriends.
Not too many.
How could I get in touch with them?
They got married and moved away.
Besides, I was Kathy's best friend.
It wasn't like the normal
father-daughter relationship.
We were good friends.
The best.
You look tired.
I'm a little tired.
Well...
...I have got the cure for that.
Magic hands.
No, thanks. I'm ticklish.
Do you have Kathy's high-school
yearbook or anything?
It's buried somewhere in this stuff.
What paper did you say
you work for?
I'm not a reporter.
I'm with Social Services.
Up in Snohomish.
Where they sent Ben Jordan?
Yeah. I'm Ben Jordan's
social worker.
Get out of here.
- Please...
- Get the hell off my property!
Do I have to call the authorities?
I guess I do.
No, you don't.
Thank you very much for your time.
Oh, you're a pretty lady, aren't you?
Hello. I'm Laura Mathews.
Hello. My name is Larry, and I am very
happy to make your acquaintance.
Well, Larry, I'm very happy
to make your acquaintance too.
I came here to ask you
some questions. Would you mind?
- No.
- Good.
A long time ago you were at a trial.
It was a murder trial for Ben Jordan.
You told all the people that you saw
somebody else go into that house.
Do you remember that?
Yeah, but that...
Yeah.
L... I was...
Well, that was when I was just a kid.
It was a long time ago. I was hoping
you could tell me what it was you saw.
Do you remember that night, Larry?
Sort of.
Did you know Ben Jordan?
He was...
He was a friend of my brother's.
Ben Jordan
was your brother's friend?
But it wasn't Ben.
It wasn't Ben you saw
go into the house?
It was somebody else?
You sure about that?
Well, I swore on the Bible.
And you can go to hell if you swear
on the Bible and it ain't the truth.
What did the other person look like?
Well, he was... He was older.
He was bigger.
Well, I don't remember too good.
Well, Larry, it's been
a pleasure talking with you.
Likewise.
Thanks very much.
Listen, lady...
...if you wanna talk to somebody
around here, you talk to me.
- What?
- Larry is very happy here.
I take good care of him,
and he takes good care of me.
Mr. Canipe, I think you have me
confused with somebody else.
- You're a social worker, aren't you?
- I am.
Jesus Christ! How many fucking times
are you people gonna come out here?
I'm not here about you
or Larry or your farm. L...
- The county didn't send you here?
- No.
I'm Ben Jordan's social worker.
He's living in Snohomish now.
I thought I'd come down here and
find out what I could about his case.
You came down here
to talk to Larry about Ben?
Yeah.
Sorry. I owe you a big apology.
Oh, boy. I'm sorry.
I didn't mean to scare you.
Well, I did mean to scare you...
...but you're not the person
I wanted to scare.
I'm a trucker, and every so often
I have to go off on long hauls...
...and leave Larry by himself here.
Well, that's okay because Larry
can take care of himself.
Once in a while they send somebody
to give us a hard time about it.
- It's okay. I understand.
- Did Larry help you out?
Sort of. He said that
you and Ben were friends.
Me and Ben were friends, all right.
He was a real hell-raiser.
- I got him out of a lot of trouble.
- Yeah? What kind of trouble?
I'm making it sound worse than it was.
Just kid stuff. Wildness.
Do you think he killed Kathy Tudor?
I don't want to. I don't know.
That was a long time ago.
At the time, I knew he didn't do it.
But now I don't know whether or not.
If you thought he didn't do it,
do you have any ideas who did?
I don't know.
The guy Larry saw, I guess.
It could have been anybody.
- Well, thank you very much.
- Sure.
I appreciate it.
If you're Ben's social worker,
you're gonna see him, right?
Yeah, I'll see him.
Would you tell him that Todd says...?
Oh, what does Todd say?
Tell him Todd says good luck,
and he's an ugly son of a bitch.
- Sure.
- All right. Thank you.
Oh, Lord have mercy, I sure didn't
help Ben much during that trial.
I was, at the time,
a little full of myself.
Well, I've learned to loosen up
just a little since then.
Here. It's Ben's file.
Here we go. Ben's unemployed.
Been drinking.
He has got
an 0.18 blood alcohol level.
0.18. I mean, that's a heavy load
we're talking about.
We're talking like
falling-down drunk.
- The way I see it, Ben comes home...
- Excuse me for interrupting.
But how'd you know Ben got drunk
before he got home, instead of after?
The clerk that sold him the booze
saw him guzzling it out in the car.
All right. Listen to this.
Say I'm Ben, and you're Kathy, okay?
I'm trying to stab you. All right.
As drunk as I am, my thrusts are gonna
be all over the place. Am I right?
They weren't.
All of them were straight in.
Dead center.
- Sorry. Am I upsetting you?
- I'll manage.
Good. There's another thing.
Why in the hell the home movies?
- Yeah. That's what I've been thinking.
- Then there's Kathy. Sweet Kathy.
There she sits, smiling.
Her husband comes home tanked...
...and she's gonna offer him
another beer?
You're right.
It doesn't make any sense.
You know what?
It never did make any sense.
All they ever had on Ben
was circumstantial evidence.
The bottom line to this is Bill Tudor,
a very powerful man in this town.
Member of the Moose Lodge,
Masons.
You see, he wanted action. Some
bastard had murdered his daughter...
...and he wanted
some bastard to pay for it.
- You saying Ben was framed?
- No, not intentionally framed. No.
I mean Ben could have done it.
And that was good enough for them.
They said you were gonna be
back this afternoon.
- Called your office. You mind?
- That's okay. Sit down.
I just got back from Ellensburg.
- I talked with people.
- You did what?
Carlton Daniels.
Larry and Todd Canipe.
- I asked you not to nose around.
- Ben, I know you're innocent.
I know you didn't kill Kathy.
It was somebody else.
Why don't you leave me alone?
I don't need to go through this again...
...so you can feel like
the angel of fucking mercy! Damn!
What's the big deal
about trusting me?
Why do you want to go on hiding?
You'd rather feel sorry for yourself...
...than clear your name
or find out who killed your wife.
What are you trying to do?
Or does it feel safer
to stay behind bars?
None of your damn business.
You wanna stay there,
I won't stop you.
Oh, psychology. Give me a break.
Ben...
...you didn't do it, did you?
I know the truth.
I don't need to prove it to anybody.
I don't care. I really don't.
I do.
I guess I'd better go.
Following me is a little melodramatic,
don't you think, Steve?
I'm not following you, okay? What
the hell do you think you're doing?
I know our relationship hasn't
exactly been what you want.
You think I'm jealous?!
Give me more credit than that!
Look, if you were fucking a milkman,
I would be jealous. But you're not.
- Jesus Christ, this guy is dangerous.
- Not to me.
Because he hasn't left you
in a pool of blood yet?
- You're melodramatic.
- Fucking-A, I'm melodramatic.
- He wasn't guilty.
- It'd be nice if it was true, but it's not.
Look, Steve, you don't know anything
about the trial, the case or the man.
I know the facts, and I know my heart.
And they say he's innocent.
Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
I got it working.
I felt like doing something.
I also wanted to say
I'm sorry for the last time.
Don't worry about it.
You have hands like my father's.
Strong and beautiful hands.
Like they're carved out of stone.
- Morning.
- Hi.
- Are you okay?
- Yeah. I had a nightmare.
I woke up, didn't remember
where I was or how I got there.
I watched you breathe for a while.
- How long has he been there?
- Since I got up.
It's what he does.
I know.
Jordan, come here.
- Mr. Lundy.
- I want to talk to you.
The boss is watching.
Listen. I want you
to understand something.
I am watching you. You do anything
to violate your parole...
...and I mean anything, you are
back inside. Do you understand that?
If anything happens to Laura,
you're not gonna make it to trial.
I guarantee it.
Mr. Lundy.
Thanks for the job.
The second he steps out of line,
I want to be the first to know.
- Where did you meet her?
- In a bar.
The kind of place
where the floor is covered...
...with sawdust and busted teeth.
Real romantic.
What about you?
You must have had guys, like Steve.
- Steve is...
- Just a friend?
Not always. We had an affair.
It lasted about a month...
...before I decided
we were better off as friends.
That figures.
- Were you ever married?
- Once.
He had an affair,
and so I threw him out.
He did something, knowing if I found
out I'd be hurt, and he did it anyway.
Are you wondering
if this is a mistake?
Do you know what these taste like?
Come here.
Oysters.
How do you know it's not poisonous?
You first.
Me second.
Like oysters, huh?
You're right.
It's delicious.
Your turn.
No.
I'm gonna have some of yours.
- Hi.
- Hi. Northwest Parcel.
- Can you just sign right there?
- Sure.
- Who's it from?
- Got me.
- Great.
- Thanks. Bye.
- Something wrong?
- Just some more stuff of my dad's.
- I'm sorry. I gotta run.
- Okay.
- Want some coffee?
- Oh, great.
Thank you.
So...
I'll see you later.
- You call me.
- Sure.
Got your gift the other day.
Am I supposed to say thanks?
- What gift?
- Come on. Stop acting like a baby.
The way you tried to deliver your
message was incredibly insulting.
I don't know what
you're talking about.
I can't be responsible
for your heart...
...when it's out in the open
on your sleeve like that.
Okay.
Hi. Thanks for coming.
Yeah. No trouble.
Glad I can help you out.
Get you anything while you wait?
A cup of coffee?
No, I'm fine.
- Mr. Canipe, what are you doing here?
- I came to talk to you, ma'am.
Sit down.
- What about?
- Well...
It's about my brother's testimony.
Larry was lying.
He was nowhere near that house
the night Kathy died.
Why would your brother
perjure himself like that?
He did it because I asked him to.
Why?
I guess it seems silly now, but
at the time, I was doing Ben a favor.
I was his best friend, and nobody with
good sense was gonna listen to me.
You know, I hoped the fact...
...that Larry was a kid and slow
would give him sympathy.
Instead, the lawyers
just used it against him.
Why didn't you tell me this
in Ellensburg?
You came to the farm and asked
questions, and I just stuck to my story.
Then, well, about a week ago,
Mr. Lundy there...
...he came to the farm, and he said
you might be in some trouble.
I got spooked.
Well, thank you very much
for telling us your story.
Have a pleasant trip back
to Ellensburg.
- Good day, Mr. Canipe.
- So long.
Let me call you back.
- You think you're pretty clever.
- You are mad now.
- Goddamn right I'm mad.
- You wanted the truth. I got it.
I got the truth.
I got the truth about you.
There's not a goddamn thing
you won't do!
You want me to be the asshole?
Okay. I'm the asshole.
Ben is innocent.
I don't care if you bring 100
Todd Canipes through that door.
Just stay the hell away from me
from now on!
H & R Meats.
- Ben Jordan, please.
- Jordan?
He hasn't been here
in over a week.
Hello?
Then...
...that's it, isn't it?
Yeah.
You know, if you don't mind
my saying it, I'm a little surprised.
Didn't you think of using anything?
At that moment
I wasn't thinking at all.
Score one for passion, huh?
Are you all right?
No.
No, I'm not.
This is the residence
of Laura Mathews.
I'm not home,
but if you leave a message...
...I'll return your call right away.
Wait for the beep.
Oh, damn it, Laura!
What the hell's going on?
I know you're there.
Pick up the phone.
Laura?
Call me. Okay?
I miss you.
Laura?
Are you there?
Pick up the phone. Please.
- Hello?
- Hi.
I was worried. How have you been?
I've been busy.
Yeah, me too.
Oh, yeah? You been busy at work?
No. Not exactly. I'm just...
Listen...
...I need to talk to you.
Okay. Give me a couple of minutes.
I'll be right there.
No.
Not here.
- Just coffee, thanks.
- The same here.
I'm sorry I lost my job.
I was gonna tell you,
but you didn't give me enough time.
It's not important.
So, what did you
want to talk about?
Laura?
I'm pregnant.
You keeping the baby?
Are you?
I don't know.
Why not?
You afraid it's gonna
be a psychopath?
I don't know what I'm afraid of.
You think I killed her.
What changed your mind?
You know what I think?
I think you've been slumming,
and now you're getting scared.
God, are you lucky I didn't get drunk
one night. I could have killed you!
Oh, stop! Please!
Look at me.
All right.
I'll stop.
Laura? You all right?
My God! Steve, what are you doing?
I got a little worried when you
didn't answer your phone, so...
So here I am. Good excuse as any for
a little early-morning fishing, I guess.
Think there's ever gonna be
a time when you don't hate me?
Steve, I don't hate you.
It's just that right now,
I'm pretty pissed off at you.
But I'm also kind of spooked,
so I'm glad you're here.
Would it be all right if I talked to...
...Miss Mathews for a second?
Hi.
Miss Mathews, I'm
Detective Allan Tobias.
I know you've been through a lot, so
I'll make this short. I need to ask...
...do you know anyone
who might have reason to...
...kill Steve Lundy?
All right.
We'll try it again. Where were you?
My room.
At the motel?
- Yeah.
- You didn't leave your room all night?
You got it.
What did you do last night?
- I slept.
- How about this morning?
I was still sleeping.
Oh, you slept all night.
Didn't get up to take a piss
or anything, right?
Yeah, once.
I don't suppose you have
any witnesses to that, huh?
I piss alone.
Ben, what'd you think
of Steve Lundy?
I'm gonna miss him.
- Hi.
That was a... That was
a very nice service.
- Jordan was released this morning.
- He was what?
Public defender said that we had to
show cause if we wanted to hold him...
...and well, we didn't have any.
I just thought I'd let you know.
Miss Mathews...
...you don't have anything
to worry about...
...because I have the man
staked out 24 hours a day.
Oh, there's something
else I'd like to ask.
People have been saying that there's
something between you and Jordan.
Now, I know it's none of my business,
but it might help if I knew.
There was something.
Laura!
Would you let me in?
No!
Before the cops get here.
Laura, you believed in me.
You were the only one.
Open this damn door!
You stay the hell away from me!
I've got a gun!
It was pouring rain that night.
I'd gotten laid off a week before,
so I was out looking for a job.
Not having any luck.
So I stopped off...
...picked up a couple of six packs...
...and just sat in the car, drinking.
Trying to work things out
in my head.
We were young.
I was thinking...
...maybe I wasn't ready for the baby.
That I'd be a lousy father.
Anyway, I tied one on.
About 11, I figured I'd
better be getting on home...
...while I could still drive.
I found her.
I didn't kill anybody.
I just didn't.
- Hi.
For the baby.
You're a little early, but thanks.
Come on. Let's get out of here.
You go ahead. I'll be a few minutes.
- Can I ask you something?
- Sure.
Why are you having the baby? I mean,
I know it's none of my business.
But why?
Because...
I guess because...
...in the middle of all this death...
...it's a life.
Thanks for the present.
No!
Dogs lost the scent.
We can't see a damn thing.
Nothing so far.
We're gonna call it a night.
Gonna leave a couple of men here.
I think you'll be fine.
- Lf you need me, call me.
- Okay.
- Thanks.
- See you in the morning.
- Good night, boys.
- Good night, sir.
- I'll be in the studio.
- You want one of us to go with you?
I'd rather be alone.
This is the place...
...where I fell in love with you.
- Ben...
- I don't want to hear your voice.
When you turned on me, the
first thing to go was your voice.
You believed in me.
I wonder...
...why did you stop?
Laura...
...when I found my wife...
...she was lying in a pool of blood...
...eyes staring.
God, I remember calling her name...
...sitting there on my knees,
holding her.
The knife...
...was still in her belly.
I had to pull it out.
I just had to.
Nothing else I could do.
Come on.
They got him, huh?
Yeah.
They...
They got him.
What are you doing here?
I was out there with them.
The others left because of the rain...
...but I thought I'd try a little harder.
I'm chilled to the bone.
Could I have a cup of coffee?
- Hello?
- Laura? Tobias.
I'm sorry he got as far as he did...
...but at least we got him
before he could do anything.
- Daddy.
- What?
So glad you called.
All right, I hear you. If you're
in trouble, find a way to say yes.
Yeah, very much.
And I always will.
Hang in there. I mean it, Laura.
Hang in there.
Help's on the way.
I have to go now.
Love you.
My father.
I know.
- Would you like some more coffee?
- No.
Thank you very much.
Please.
No.
Please, please, please.
I got them, Ben! I got both of them!
Now you stay right there.
You'll be safe.
I'm going back in,
and I'm gonna take care of her.
Todd! No!
Christ!
Laura!
You should have blown
his head off like I said...
...and we could have
avoided all this.
Laura!
Help me! Help me!
Ben! Help me!
Turn it on.
Look at her. Look at her!
She offered me a drink
and everything.
Why not? I'm Ben's buddy.
Ben came home...
...30 minutes after I killed her.
I just hid in the bedroom.
He came in,
he saw her on the floor...
...and he ran out.
Poor Ben.
Poor Kathy.
There were others before her.
And they all had these bellies.
These big, round bellies.
But don't misjudge me.
I'm not a sex maniac.
I'm not some Son of Sam asshole.
I don't hear voices.
It's not like I have to...
...kill somebody every week.
The first time Mama
made me put it in her...
...I felt sick.
Then as her belly swelled...
...and she climbed on top of me...
...it got so I couldn't breathe.
I held my breath...
...till she went away again...
...and left me alone.
No!