Game three of the 1985 series
is just underway...
Kansas City trailing by one.
The first pitch by Rosenthal...
is hit on the ground
towards second base!
Wexler's got it!
Fires to first...
and we've quickly got one out.
In 1985, his average
was two-fifty for the season.
Mom?
Hi, darling.
This is for your tea party.
Thank you.
Go on and play now, girls.
Mama's got work to do.
Ivy, go take your sister
upstairs.
Come on, Violet.
Let's go get Joy.
Would you like any tea,
Madeline?
Careful, it's hot, very hot.
There you go.
And a cookie.
-Can you play, Joy?
-Mm-hmm. Come on.
Oh, goodie, tea.
You pour some more tea, Violet.
Your daddy's home, Joy.
There's gonna be fireworks.
Catherine?
Honey?
-Who the fuck are you?
-Don't!
I don't want
to fight you, all right?
Just get the hell out!
Becca?
Go.
Baby, let me get you
some ice for that.
Ivan, wait!
You don't understand!
Ivan, please,
would you listen to me?
How many others, Rebecca?
Grocery boy? The mailman?
How many?
And in my house!
You think this is easy,
sneaking around your wife...
and pretending
there's nothing between us?
You're home.
How long...
have you been sleeping
with my husband right here...
in my own house?
Ivan, tell her to get out.
Ivan, tell her.
Where are you going?
Whore.
I am not a whore.
Then what are you?
He told me what you're like
between the sheets.
Is it any wonder
he needs a woman?
It's happening again.
Oh, no.
I'm giving you twenty minutes
to get out of this house.
And if you're not gone...
I will call the police
and have you removed.
Violet, take Madeline.
I'll try to write to you.
Thanks.
May I help you?
Is this still
the Greers' residence?
Yes, it is.
I'm here to see Joy.
May I tell her who's calling?
Violet?
I can't believe it's you.
Thank you, Mrs. B.
It's hard to believe
it's been eleven years.
Daddy refuses to believe
I'm not ten years old anymore.
I just moved back here
from Arizona.
I thought maybe I'd get
a waitressing job part-time...
and maybe start some summer
classes at the junior college.
That's wonderful.
It makes me long
to be twenty again.
Being twenty is hard.
Not as hard as being eight...
but then, life wasn't meant
to be easy, was it?
Have you found an apartment?
Not yet, but I put my name up
on the board at school.
Why not stay here?
I--I couldn't.
But we have so much room.
It's not a problem.
Joy, can I have a word with you
in the kitchen, please?
Come here, you crap.
Joy, having Violet stay here
is out of the question.
-Why?
-Well, for many reasons.
It's been a long time.
Things have changed.
Dad, Violet was my best friend.
When she and lvy were here,
it was like having sisters.
Seeing her today
was like nothing had changed.
I know that, sweetheart,
but where is she going to sleep?
We have an extra bedroom.
That was
your mother's room, Joy.
I know that.
What do you think, Mrs. B?
Maybe the girl
could use a helping hand...
if you know what I mean.
I promised you
we'd be home again.
Welcome home, Madeline.
Seventy-six, seventy-seven...
seventy-eight, seventy-nine...
eighty, eighty-one...
eighty-two, eighty-three...
eighty-four, eighty-five...
eighty-six, eighty-seven...
eighty-eight, eighty-nine...
ninety, ninety-one...
ninety-two, ninety-three...
ninety-four, ninety-five...
Just a minute.
Ninety-seven, ninety-eight,
ninety-nine, one hundred.
Oh, my gosh.
I'm supposed to be in training.
You must be good.
I'm proud of you.
Who is this?
Michael.
-We're going to get married.
-Married?
In the fall.
Daddy wants us to wait...
but Michael wants me to apply
for a transfer to Yale...
so we can be together next year.
Yale? Is that far away?
Connecticut, silly.
Michael will be home from school
next week.
I can't wait for you
to meet him.
He's very good-looking.
Remember when we were little...
and we used to dress up
like we were brides?
You made a veil
out of a petticoat.
And you made one out of
a whole roll of toilet paper.
What about your dad?
What's he going to do
when you get married?
I don't know.
Sometimes I'm afraid
he'll end up alone.
He doesn't date?
There's a woman named Gwen
he talks about.
Mrs. B and I keep hoping he'll
find the time to ask her out.
It wouldn't bother you
if he got serious or anything?
Why should it?
He's been alone a long time.
He deserves to be
with someone nice.
But I don't think
he'll ever get over my mother.
You've probably noticed
how her room is still the same.
After all these years...
Dad still can't bring himself
to change it.
You must really miss her, too.
I do.
A lot.
I really need her sometimes.
Connecticut?
No, thank you, Mrs. B.
How's Yale this year, Michael?
Good, sir.
I'm developing
some important relationships.
Good.
Michael's fourth in his class
this year.
That's very impressive
for freshman year.
It's very impressive
for any year.
We're looking forward to you
at the bank this summer.
See you on Monday?
Absolutely.
I'm looking forward to it.
Good. You've got the house
to yourselves tonight...
-because I've--
-Got a meeting.
That's right.
-Good night, Dad.
-Good night.
-Good night, sir.
-Good night, Michael.
It's party time.
Michael, you should've been
at the club for drinks.
There's some new blood.
All in good time, my brother.
All in good time.
Scott, what's up?
How's Princeton?
A bitch.
The classes or the girls?
To uncompromising women.
Hear, hear.
So, I hear you're tearing up
the courts.
Got my last Division One
Tournament on Friday.
-Then hello lvy League.
-lf I win.
No ifs. You're in your prime.
Jaimie, am I right?
We have lived on that court
for the past two months.
If she could eat and sleep
out there...
that's where we'd be right now.
You're Violet, right?
What are you doing this summer?
She's taking classes
at the junior college.
Ooh!
The junior college.
My maid took
English classes there.
Is it a tough school
to get into?
Oh, no. They'll accept
just about anybody...
as long as your welfare check
doesn't bounce.
No, thanks.
No. I have to go to work.
Right now?
Yeah.
I drew the late shift tonight.
You know,
new kid on the block and all.
Well...
See ya.
Oh, baby!
You guys leave her alone.
She's had it pretty tough.
What was she doing here
in the first place?
Her mother was their maid.
She was my best friend.
Stop it!
Damn it, Joy,
what's the matter now?
I told you.
I have a lot on my mind.
I have an early practice
tomorrow.
I'm just not in the mood.
If your mother
was this uptight...
no wonder your dad
fooled around.
How dare you say that to me.
I confided in you about that.
I can't believe
you would throw it in my face.
Look, I'm sorry.
How about I come by after
your practice tomorrow, OK?
Oh, my God!
You think it was Daddy?
You scared me half to death.
That's some...
some outfit there.
Where did you say
you worked again?
Denny's.
In Hollywood.
It's under new management.
I--I guess I've never eaten
there before.
Would you like to?
You should see
the look on your face.
Look, it's kinda late.
I gotta go.
Come on. It's a joke.
Look, l...
I think we got off
to a bad start.
I see we have a little
unfinished business.
Stock market's up...
and I see
we're a major stockholder.
Just a minute!
Come in.
I wanted to apologize
for my friends tonight.
They can be pretty
annoying sometimes.
Don't worry about it.
It didn't bother me.
Well, it bothered me.
I'm sorry.
Can I talk to you
about something?
Sure.
You never get...
urges or anything?
I do. A lot.
But when it comes down to it,
I just...
get tense.
I don't even want him inside me.
I've never had an orgasm
with him.
I've never even had an orgasm.
I think my mother
was the same way.
I mean, she did sleep
in this room most of the time.
What if I'm just like her?
The first time
I was with a guy...
I was thirteen.
I was known
as the school slut...
by the time I was fourteen.
But then I got smart.
I stopped going to school.
Excuse me.
Where did you get that?
This? Why?
It doesn't belong to you.
Now, how would you know that?
Because it belonged
to Mrs. Greer!
She's not using it, is she?
More coffee, Mr. Greer?
No. No, thank you, Mrs. B.
"Dearest Joy...
"I've kicked. I'm clean.
"I'm ready to make amends for
all the hurt I've laid on you.
"Love, Michael."
So...
old Michael had
a little drug problem, did he?
That honking for you?
Yeah, it's Jaimie. We've got
a practice doubles match.
When will you be back?
Probably late.
I was hoping we could spend
the day together.
I've gotta practice.
Last Division One Tournament...
is the day after tomorrow.
I gotta win.
You don't gotta win, Joy.
Yes, I do.
You know,
you're really hard on yourself.
You don't have to be perfect
all the time.
If I were, I wouldn't work
twice as hard as everyone else.
Jaimie and I will be
practicing here this afternoon.
You should come watch.
Oh, goody.
What are you doing?
Well, in case
you hadn't noticed...
I am the housekeeper here.
This is what I do.
I would appreciate it if,
from now on...
you'd let me know when
you're going to come in my room.
Larry's been a naughty boy.
My time is your time.
Where do you want to meet?
What are you in the mood for?
That'll cost extra, you know.
Really?
They didn't tell me that.
I can't believe that happened.
-That's crazy.
-I need to play a real set.
In a minute, OK?
You're supposed to be
my training partner.
All right, I'm coming.
I'm gonna go get a drink.
Do you want anything?
Anything. Just hurry up.
Listen, I have to go, OK?
No, really. I have to go.
You guys look like you could use
something cold to drink.
Excellent!
Throw it in the blender.
Add a little ice...
and you got yourselves
something tropical.
A little extra kick never hurt.
I suppose not.
What did you put
in those drinks?
The teeniest shot of rum.
I swear--the teeniest!
Play to win, ladies.
I don't believe it.
Come on, Joy.
Joy, sit up.
Hey, there.
What's goin' on?
They're both drunk.
That's weird.
When's Mr. Greer get home?
Probably any minute.
Why?
Are you kidding?
He's a total fascist.
If he sees Joy like this,
he'll freak.
Come on.
Help me get her upstairs.
We'll just tell him
she's got a headache.
Yeah.
That won't be a lie.
We'll have to come back for her.
Michael, I'm gonna be sick.
Oh, God, just hang on, OK?
Wait.
Hold it a second.
Are you crazy?
Oh, man.
Mr. Greer, how goes it?
Where's Joy?
She went upstairs
with a headache.
She was on the court all day,
and I guess she overdid it.
-I'd better look in on her.
-No. I'll do it.
All right, Michael.
Thank you.
Man.
Get the lights.
That's good.
I just don't understand
what Joy was thinking.
She knows she needs every second
of practice she can get.
This could screw up everything.
-Maybe that's what she wants.
-What?
Never mind.
It's not my place.
Did she say something to you?
Well, the way she talks...
it sounds like she thinks things
are moving a little too fast.
Getting married,
moving to Connecticut--
But we already decided.
She thinks maybe you're pushing
a little too hard.
She thinks maybe you guys should
try dating other people.
What are you talking about?
Are you saying she's been
seeing other people...
while I've been away
or something?
Shit!
Who is it?
I can't believe it.
I can't believe
she's cheated on me...
after I've been faithful
this whole time.
Except for last night.
Listen...
you just stay away from me,
all right?
You didn't have any dinner.
Thank you so much, Violet.
That's so sweet.
What is this stuff?
It's nothing--spreadsheets.
No wonder your eyes hurt.
Is all this stuff
really part of your job?
I'm afraid so, Violet.
Keeps me out of trouble, though.
Maybe a little trouble
isn't such a bad thing.
Excuse me?
It just seems to me
like you're avoiding something.
Joy told me that you've...
never really gotten
over Catherine's death.
You know...
there's nothing wrong
with having feelings, Ivan.
I can call you Ivan?
If you feel something...
go with it. You know?
I mean...
don't be afraid
to follow where it leads.
Otherwise...
what would be the point
of living?
Spreadsheets?
Well...
don't work too hard.
Good night.
Oh, my God.
Where are you going?
Wait, don't leave yet.
Joy'll be right back.
Oh, my God!
Do you always swim in the nude?
Did you enjoy that?
Not as much as you did, I bet.
Actually, l...
didn't even know
you were still here.
I'm not leaving until l
straighten things out with Joy.
Have you decided
what you're going to say to her?
Not exactly.
Maybe this will help.
I don't do that anymore.
I made a promise to Joy.
Aren't you a good boy?
I just thought it might help.
I'll bet you've promised
yourself all sorts of things...
where Joy is concerned...
but promises were meant
to be broken, Michael.
Look, this did not happen.
Play to win, Michael.
You know...
my old mother used to say...
that house guests and fish...
start to smell
after about three days.
And what is that
supposed to mean?
Oh, nothing.
You know,
I was wondering...the "B."
Short for "bitch"?
I feel like I've been
hit by a truck.
Drink this.
Does my dad know?
Actually, he thinks you went
to bed early with a headache.
I can't believe Jaimie...
getting me drunk
and then splitting like that.
I'm so angry at her.
She seemed
a little upset herself.
I'd like to strangle her.
I have exactly twenty-one hours
until the tournament...
and I can't even see straight.
Well, I'll keep
the coffee coming.
Michael left his jacket
in my den, and this fell out.
I can't allow this
in my business...
and I will not allow it
in my family.
Do you understand me, Joy?
It's gotta be a mistake.
The only mistake
is me allowing you to date him.
Shouldn't we give him
a chance to explain himself?
I know you'll do
the right thing.
He promised me never again.
He lied to me.
Nothing's more important
than the truth, Joy.
But I guess you can't
expect that from a druggie.
He's not a druggie.
He's just...
He's under
a lot of pressure, and...
What am I gonna do?
Listen...
Everything's gonna be OK.
Everything's gonna be just fine.
I promise.
Jaimie doesn't want
to see me anymore.
And she doesn't want
to be partners, either.
I'm not surprised.
I knew from the minute
I met her...
she was only into you
for what she could get.
You think so?
She's nothing but
a social climber.
It's Michael.
I'll go down and talk to him.
Thanks.
I want to talk to her about it.
Michael, you're really starting
to hurt my feelings.
What are you talking about?
You can't keep pretending
we're not sleeping together.
I mean, I thought we had
something special going.
You told her about last night,
didn't you?
-You bitch.
-I didn't tell her anything.
I didn't have to.
You did this all by yourself.
His pupils were totally dilated.
He wasn't making any sense.
He thinks the reason you won't
talk to him is because of me.
It's just like him
to blame everyone but himself.
Don't help him, Joy.
Fuck him.
All right.
I have to stop
making excuses for him.
I have to be tough.
He has to take responsibility.
Michael just doesn't give up,
does he?
They're not from Michael.
They're for Gwen,
your dad's date for tonight.
He finally asked her out?
Yes, he did.
How do I look, Mrs. B?
Mr. Greer,
in my humble opinion...
you are beyond handsome.
Thank you, Mrs. B.
Could you get the flowers
for me?
Hi, honey.
Hey, Dad.
Wow. Very handsome.
Thanks.
Where are you off to?
Meeting my coach to practice...
one last time
before the big tournament.
Honey, with everything
happening around us...
I realize I haven't been
that supportive of you...
but I want you to know
there's no doubt in my mind...
you're going to win
that tournament.
Thanks, Dad. I just hope
I don't let you down.
You're a Greer. We deliver.
-Here you go!
-Mrs. B, thank you.
All right.
You got some lint
right on your shoulder.
Let me get my brush.
That's gonna have to stay.
I've got to get out of here.
Come on, Joy, Let's go.
-Hello?
-Hi, this is Gwen Randall.
-Is this Ivan's daughter?
-Yes, it is.
Listen, Joy.
Has your dad left yet?
Shoot.
Can you get a message to him?
Absolutely.
Could you have him meet me
outside the courthouse...
and not at my office?
In front of the kiosk.
-You've got it.
-Thanks, Joy.
No problem. Thanks.
Hello,
this is the Greer residence.
Will you please leave a message
after the tone?
Ivan, what happened?
I stood outside the courthouse
for nearly an hour.
To say I'm pissed off
would be an understatement.
In fact, do me a favor...
and lose my number.
I love champagne.
Violet, you're not legal.
I won't tell if you won't.
Why are you so dressed up?
Party.
You're home early.
She didn't like them?
Actually, she stood me up.
-I'm sorry.
-I'll live.
You know, in all my life...
I don't think
I've ever gotten flowers.
I just wanted to feel pretty
tonight.
Maybe dance a little.
Laugh.
Feel good.
I know that must seem silly.
I know.
Dance with me?
I'm not much of a dancer,
Violet.
It's all right.
We can't do this, Violet.
I want you to feel good, too.
Shouldn't you be wearing
your glasses, Mr. Greer?
I cannot do this with you,
Violet.
Don't make me go.
Don't do this to me.
I will win. I will win.
Please let me win.
Joy, you're gonna have
to speak to me sooner or later.
Michael,
I want you to leave me alone.
That's not fair.
Fair?
God, you are driving me crazy...
and I've got the tournament
this morning.
I know.
I want to be there for you.
I love you, Joy.
I don't know, Michael.
All right, we'll talk.
After the tournament,
I'll meet you...
at the coffee-house on campus.
I gotta go.
Good luck.
Thanks.
Greer residence.
Hello, Gwen!
No. His daughter's in a tennis
tournament this morning...
but I'm sure he'll be
in his office later on.
Can I take a message?
You did?
How many messages did you leave?
I see.
Well, I can guarantee you...
that he never received
any of your messages...
but I'm pretty sure who did.
Going somewhere?
I don't know what you think
you're up to, little girl...
but I'm gonna put a stop to it
right now.
I don't think so.
You bitch.
I got a call from Greer telling
me not to report to my job...
because they found
another intern.
You set me up, you got me high,
and you seduced me.
If that's what
you need to believe...
so you can live with yourself...
it's OK with me.
You're setting them up
just like you set me up.
They're my family.
I would never do anything
to hurt them.
They're not your family!
Your family's dead.
Yeah. That's right.
I did a little checking.
That junior college
never even heard of you.
Then I find out your sister lvy
threw herself out of a window.
-Shut up.
-Let's not forget your mother.
I said shut up!
I bet you don't even work
at Denny's, do you?
Now what?
I'm gonna tell Joy
who she's really living with.
You're gonna tell her
you're fucking me?
I'm gonna tell her the truth.
That'll be
an interesting approach for you.
Think she'll buy it?
I don't think it's gonna be
too hard to convince her.
Look, I'm going to meet her
at two o'clock.
That'll give you enough time
to get out.
Well, she won't be there.
She never planned to meet you.
-You're such a liar.
-Really?
Then why did she tell
your good buddy Scott...
to pick her up at the house
at one thirty?
Fuck you.
You're gonna be so sorry.
Curiosity killed the cat.
Right now, Joy's sitting
somewhere waiting for you.
Guess you let her down again,
Michael.
Do you know what kind of people
like pain?
Let's see, there's doctors...
and lawyers...
I even have a judge
for a client.
But you know, it's not the pain
that gets them off.
It's the feeling of someone else
being in control.
I'm in control now, Michael.
You know,
this whole thing with Joy...
was really just about
Daddy's bank...
wasn't it?
I got a really big chuckle
out of your pathetic rambling.
Kiss-kiss.
You really should have
kept your promise to Joy.
Stayed away from the drugs.
This is the shit
that killed you.
I guarantee...
you've never felt
anything like this before.
Bye-bye, Michael.
You all right?
I played like I never held
a racquet before in my life.
I just...I couldn't
concentrate, you know?
It's Michael's fault.
He totally distracted you.
He didn't even show up.
He didn't call again, did he?
Come by?
I've been here all day.
I wanted to teach Michael
a lesson...
not make him go away.
Made a mess of everything.
You don't see it.
It's not you.
It's them.
But I want them to love me.
You think they care?
Well, they never will.
They'll just use you
and throw you away.
It's the same
for both of us, Joy.
We're the same in so many ways.
Sometimes...
I just wish the rest
of the world would fade away.
Where did you get those?
Those are my mother's.
I just came across them.
I didn't think you'd mind
if I borrowed them.
They were in her jewelry box
in the back of her closet.
Please put them back.
Fine.
It's not that big of a deal.
Yes, it is, Violet.
I think things are getting
a little too tense around here.
What are you trying to say?
I think maybe...
it would be a good idea...
if you started thinking about
another place to live.
Don't worry, baby.
I'll fix it.
I promise.
Oh, my God, he was here.
She lied to me.
I...
I brought these for Joy.
I know she's feeling upset
about...
Losing the tournament.
Well, I'm sure she'll love them.
I talked to Gwen today.
You pretended you were Joy,
didn't you?
You didn't give me her messages.
I didn't give you
the messages...
because I was jealous.
Joy was wrong.
About what?
It wasn't Catherine
I couldn't get over.
It was your mother.
God, you look so much like her.
I told you, I just can't do this
with you, Violet.
But you already have...
only I'm not gonna let you
turn away from me...
Like you did her.
No. This is his father.
Mr. Beckett.
I was just looking for Michael.
I'm afraid I have
some bad news for you.
What?
Michael's been found dead.
They're not sure yet,
but it seems like...
he might have been murdered.
Daddy?
Oh, my God!
Untie me.
Joy, please don't leave.
Oh, God.
Stop it, Violet.
Ivan, everything's gonna
be all right.
I should never have
taken advantage of you, Violet.
You've got to go,
and you've got to go now.
Go?
You fucked me...
and now you're throwing me out?
Just like my mother.
You promised
to take care of her...
and that she would be
provided for.
I told you I wouldn't let you
turn away from me.
I meant it.
Just get out.
If you'd like to make a call,
please hang up and try again.
Help me.
Mrs. B, I need to come in.
The breaker box
is in your closet.
Daddy.
Oh, my God.
-Where's my father?
-He's gone.
What have you done with him?
He did it to himself.
What are you talking about?
Here. Put this on.
I don't think I want to.
I want you to.
Besides...
you can't go like that.
Go? Go where?
We're going together...
but we have to be dressed up...
so, here, put it on.
All right.
You're really
freaking me out, Violet.
Now, sit...
and I'll pour tea.
I don't want to sit, Violet.
I'm very scared.
Don't be scared.
I told you
I'll take care of everything...
and I will...
but you have to trust me.
Now...sit down.
Where's my father?
You killed Michael, didn't you?
You're so lucky I'm your sister.
Who else would have gone
to all the trouble for you?
They didn't want us
to be together...
but now they can't stop us.
We'll be together forever.
What do you mean?
Here.
Hold this.
Take it!
Now...
all you have to do is drink.
You'll drink first...
and then I'll hold you
until you fall asleep.
I'll have to hold you tight...
to stop you
from thrashing around so much.
Then I'll drink.
And I'll lay down beside you...
and hold your hand.
Now...drink.
You bitch!
I tried to make it easier
for you...
but I guess
we'll have to do it your way.
Help!
-Help!
-Grab my hand.