Shared by http://DJJ.HOME.SAPO.PT/
No watch, no wallet, no shoes.
This guy was picked clean.
In this neighborhood, he's lucky
to have the fillings in his teeth.
Still there.
This guy was well-groomed.
I don't care if he was
lemon-scented and martinized,
if he was on Washington
and D, he was copping.
He should have just said no.
Maybe somebody wouldn't
take no for an answer.
CSI 4x16 Getting off by Kornifex
So, Detective Cavaliere how
long have you been in Vegas?
Couple of weeks.
Welcome to Tranny-town. This
is where the hustlers come.
Yeah, I can see why. It's very romantic.
This is new.
Don't get territorial. It's
for my own personal collection.
Whatever blows your
skirt up. Burn me a copy.
There's a small cut on the forehead.
Yeah, it looks like he's wearing
makeup. Blush on the cheeks...
lipstick.
Transvestite. Fits the profile.
Honeymoon suite's across the way.
Anonyms sex becomes anonymous sex crime.
Murder usually personal.
Maybe whoever had the last
dance left behind a corsage.
I'd settle for his clothes.
Hey, I'll give you a hand.
You think a hacksaw's
going to do the trick?
No. But that's why
god invented sawzalls.
All we got is a decapitated doll.
That's still legal in Nevada.
Dave, what's up? You find something?
I was just thinking I wouldn't
be caught dead in those shorts.
Yo, baby, look, why're you rushing
the day? We got plenty of night left.
I'm working, lady.
See, that's something we already got
in common, 'cause I'm working, too.
Oh, yeah?
mm-Hmm.
Were you working him?
Him? No. No, sir. But I tell you
one thing. Good-looking white boy
like that? I know plenty of women
who'd be tripping over their platform to
get a little somethin' somethin'. But
no, sir, he wasn't nobody's customer.
Really?
This guy get here on
foot? I don't see a car.
They haven't found one yet.
I suppose nobody saw it drive away.
They were all in the bathroom.
Multiple stab wounds. The deepest
of which transected the thoracic
aorta and the right mainstream bronchus.
Anything else?
His name is Ed Burnell. Matched
his prints, prior for possession.
And it's not the first time he stared
death in the face. Our man had a double
dose of cirrhosis. That takes work.
Years of hard-core alcohol abuse, plus
hepatitis, probably
acquired by dirty needles.
In Chinese medicine, the
liver is the organ of anger.
Addicts and alcoholics medicate their
anger, consequently, destroy their liver.
Actually, half the
liver is pretty healthy.
The new half.
Oh... a graft from a less angry donor.
Organ recipient procedure is pretty
clear. They only do transplants
on people who test clean for a year.
Well, he probably got his new liver,
figured he could, uh, start all over again.
Is that what you think? That
once an addict, always an addict?
Don't let the scope touch
the garment. You don't want to
contaminate the evidence.
And work systematically.
Up-down,
left-right, what?
Oh, whatever works for you.
Just don't miss any spots.
All right, hang on. What
do those look like to you?
Semen stains.
Yes.
Which, on a man's underwear,
aren't exactly probative.
No.
Can't tell you how long they've been
there, or how often the guy changes
his shorts. You know, I knew guys that
could go up to four days on one single
pair of tighty-whities.
Thanks for putting that
picture in my brain.
All right, so...
I want you to outline each
individual stain with dots. But keep
them at least an eighth of an inch
from the edge to avoid contamination.
And then, cut out the swatches
and send them to myself in DNA.
You got it.
A fiber in his nose.
Yeah, I'll get it to trace.
Petechial hemorrhaging.
I would've thought he was strangled
during some kind of rough sex-
play, but there's no marks.
Suffocation maybe?
That's why undertakers
love smother-victims.
He's got something under his nails.
Looks like silver paint.
Vegas brow. A showgirl
thing. Eyebrows thin out from all the
plucking and waxing and filling in.
Well, we can kind of rule
him out as a showgirl.
Yeah.
And, you know, he's hairy
for a drag queen. Hey, David?
Yeah?
Could you hit the lights?
Wow that's noit beauty
make-up his face looks painted.
Kinda looks like a clown.
Yo, man, get these spiders off
my face, man! I gotta beam up
outta here. I need my medication.
I'm a CEO of a five-bag-a-day
corporation, you know that?
- Uh, come on. Let's go.
- Thank you.
Y'all look like cartoons,
man. Okay, thank you.
Whoa, whoa, whoa. Take it easy,
pal. You're not running the four-
minute mile on those pins.
Nice shoes.
It's all good, it's all good.
Whoa! Who gonna pay for
that hole in my ride, man?
Your ride? This was never your
ride. This car belongs to Ed Burnell.
Finders keepers, baby.
I gotta bag me some ho's.
What drug is he on?
I don't know. Whatever it is, he
either took too much or not enough.
Just 'cause the guy looks like a
clown doesn't mean he is a clown.
Description didn't match anyone
in missing persons. If you've got a
better idea, now's the time.
I'd say we're in the right place.
Yeah. Either that or they're
casting a John Wayne Gacey revue.
And you can tell that putz
that Buddy Ween doesn't send
cruise ship talent for bar
mitzvah wages. You got that?
Uh, strippers are down the
hall, girls. This is clowns.
No kidding.
I'm Catherine Willows. This is Sara
Sidle. We're with the crime lab.
Well, why didn't you say so?
We do lots of police parties.
The party has already happened.
What am I supposed to do with this?
Identify the body. Did
that man ever work for you?
Well, let me put it
this way: I rep clowns.
That's Flappy, that's
Flappy Junior, that's Allen
...he doesn't work that much... Popo...
get it? All I do is book the face.
I don't care what's underneath.
If our victim was a professional
clown, would he be in this book?
Uh-huh.
What are these numbers for?
That's the national clown
and character registry.
How do you register a clown?
Well, not the clown. The look,
the face. Each one is unique.
It's like snowflakes.
We're going to need
to take this with us.
You got a warrant? I'm kidding.
Okay, it's just a loaner, though.
I know you stealin' my medication.
I am in pain, damn it! Bring me
some stuff!
What are you two ladies lookin' at?
Uh... Jamal...
we're with the Las Vegas crime lab. It
seems you were driving a dead man's
car when you got in your accident.
Half the peoples I know be dead. It
don't mean they can't own a vehicle.
Hey, Vanilla Ice... at this point
you're lookin' at a murder rap,
which may end you up on death row, and
I'm not talking about the record label.
Nurse, this be cruel and unusual!
Look, pal, right now the evidence
tells us that you killed the man
whose car you were driving.
You want to explain that?
Explain what, B?
I was laid up shootin'
speedballs all day. Look, man,
when I get off, I'm gone. Feel me? I
can't see nothin', I can't hear nothin'.
Wherever high is, that's
where I take the elevator up.
Oh, you damn cow! Took you long enough.
When I call you, you
come, you understand me?
Why you got to do me like this?
That's right. Man's dead.
What difference it make how he got
there? Now, if you'll excuse me,
I got a date with Mrs. Jones.
Man's already dead. Why he
be needing shoes, anyway?
Was that a confession?
I think a plea of insanity.
DNA results on the blood from
Jamal's clothes. It's his own.
Well, the blood spatter's consistent
with a front end collision.
So he didn't kill him in the car.
Doesn't mean he didn't kill him.
What I want to know is how's a
strung-out junkie like Jamal get a
guy out of the car with just his knife?
Yeah, and why stab him six times?
Well, let's just say for argument's
sake that Jamal is telling the
truth and that Burnell was already dead when
he took his wallet, his shoes and his car.
Well, if the motive wasn't
robbery... what was it?
Maybe this'll tell us.
Heroin?
Negative on
marquis-mecke-froede.
So, if it's not an opiate, what is it?
I don't know. I've never seen it
before. I ran a color and crystal
test. Take a look.
All I can tell you is
it's an indole alkaloid.
Did you run it through the GCMS?
Yeah, but it's not in the library.
That's Doodles. A.K.A. Donny Zanko.
So you know him.
There are two kinds of clowns:
There's your ex-circus pros,
washed out of Ringling
Brothers, Barnum and Bailey,
and then there's your
basic chuckleheads.
Which kind was Doodles?
Basic chucklehead. You know, buy
a getup, learn some tricks, and
grab some scratch boring the crap out
of nine-year-olds. He was a good birthday
man, except when he, uh...
So, he made money boring kids?
Parents throw parties. They like
clowns because they think their
kids like clowns.
Mm-hmm. Lindsey's fourth... bad scene.
Oh.
So, what was the last
gig you booked for him?
Uh... car wash, couple
of weeks back. Why?
Mr. Ween, he's been dead less than
48 hours and he was wearing his makeup
when he was killed.
That son of a bitch. He was
working off the books. I never
thought Doodles would try to stiff me.
He, actually, was the
one who got stiffed.
So, it turns out Burnell's tox
report was clean. Not only that, he
works at some sort of recovery center.
Well, that makes sense.
It does?
Well, the substance we found
in his car was ibogaine.
What's that, the stuff that grows hair?
A choline-esterase inhibitor that
acts as a stimulant in the central
nervous system.
In the liver, it converts to an
active metabolite... noribogaine.
Noribogaine locks onto
addiction receptors...
blocking the feedback loops that
reinforce dependency.
In human speak?
Well, apparently, in some cases,
one dose of ibogaine can cure
physical addiction.
Does it come with a
free set of steak knives?
It comes with a free trip. Curing
physical addiction is a side
effect. Its intended use is to
facilitate visual, tactile, and auditory
experiences of alternate realities.
So it's an hallucinogen.
Mm-hmm. Used by the Bwiti tribe of
Central Africa. It comes from the
powdered bark of a tree
growing in Cameroon.
No kidding.
Many ethno-botanists believe that
the iboga is what the bible is
talking about when it refers
to the tree of knowledge.
The Bwiti consume the powdered bark
as part of an initiation ceremony.
After the ritual, a man is called
baanzi, one who has seen the other world.
No way it's legal.
Not in the U.S.
So, Ed Burnell was a drug dealer.
Well...
He's either dealing in the addiction
or the cure, and a dealer's a
dealer. And this guy's
dealing out of a halfway house.
Well... I can see why Doodles drank.
So, if he's hooking up in
Tranny-town, you'd expect to find some
man-on-man
porn.
All we've got is
varying flavors of juggs.
Hmm.
Looks like Doodles was
working out some animosity.
Oh, an answering machine with messages.
Friday, 11:02. AM
Hey, Doodle-pie. I can't stop
thinking about your enormous feet.
You know what they say about big feet.
... 02 P.M.
Okay, paddle boy, you want a war, you
got one. And just so you know, I do
appreciate the irony of
me leaving you a message.
Interesting.
Hey, Mr. Doodles, your taxi's here.
Yeah, yeah, cool your
jets. I'll be right down.
He took a cab ride two days
ago... and his costume's not here.
Makes sense if he's out of town
on a job. I'll call Detective
Cavaliere and have him
pull the phone records.
Burnell worked here for about
a year. This is a halfway house.
We provide a safe place to live. I mean,
if they're going to do ibogaine, I'd
rather have them do it in
here than out in the street.
And despite the fact that San Quentin
is your alma mater and you have a
record as long as my leg, you
wouldn't do anything illegal, right?
I wouldn't do anything to
jeopardize this place, and we don't
give out illegal drugs. We
do a lot of good work here.
You know, if ibogaine is such a miracle
cure, wouldn't it make your life easier?
The drug doesn't promise
anything. You got to earn it. If a
user doesn't realize why he used in
the first place, I mean, no power in the
world is going to make him stop.
Right here is a good case in point.
So, you're going?
Yeah.
You sure that's what you want to do?
Yeah. This place just
reminds me too much of Ed.
Look, I really wish you'd
stay here a little longer.
I can't.
You did a good job here, Mindy.
I'm still doing it.
What's her story?
Ed got her clean. Let me show you
what she looked like two months ago.
What are you doing here, Mindy?
Wanna get off.
I... I don't got another
run in me, but I can't stop.
My name is Ed Burnell. I'm
here to help you, Mindy.
This place is nice. Can I stay here, Ed?
Yes.
'Cause you're gonna
take care of me, right?
Yes, I'm going to take care of you.
So, was it the ibogaine or
the months she spent here?
You don't believe in ibogaine?
I don't believe in miracles.
But Ed did?
Look, when Ed first came here,
he was an asset to the place. And
then he got... religious about it.
You know, there's a reason why Mohammed
kept his ass on the mountain.
It was safe there. The
thing about recovery is
it only works for those who want
it, not for those who need it.
But Ed came down from the mountain,
and he brought the ibogaine with him.
Yeah, and he started pushing it
on everyone. Sometimes he won,
sometimes he lost.
From one addiction to another.
I can't believe Doodles is
dead. When did it happen?
We're hoping you can help us find out.
Yeah, according to Sunburst Taxi
one of the drivers dropped off
the clown here two days ago.
Yeah, that's right. My
son was having a birthday.
It's my own little tradition.
Birthdays, special occasions, I
always hire a clown. The kids love them.
Except this time, I think maybe
we should've gone to Circus Circus.
What do you mean by that?
Well, we hired a clown
- squirting flower, big floppy shoes and
all that
- what we got was a smackdown.
Doodles was going through
his clown bit, and, uh, then
this mime comes through our kitchen, which
at first we thought it was part of the act.
What the hell are you doing here?
So, uh, I jumped in and broke it
up and dragged the Mime into the
kitchen. I was going to call you guys...
Mmm.
...But he apologized and said
that, uh, there was bad blood
between him and Doodles. And he gave me
a hundred bucks for the damages, which
I thought was a pretty stand
up thing to do, so I let him go.
Did you get his name?
I did better than that.
He, uh, told me he'd give me great rate
if I ever wanted to upgrade from clowns.
And what time did Doodles leave?
The kids were really upset after
the fight, so I took them out for
ice cream.
Doodles stuck around to help me
clean up, and then he asked me
to call him a cab.
Do you remember the name of the
taxi company or the time of the call?
Well, he'd been such a good
sport that I offered to give him a
ride home. I dropped him off
at his place at around 8:30.
Hey, excuse me.
Take a look.
Look, you do have the right to
remain silent, but unless you
want a trip to the station,
I really wouldn't keep it up.
You want to talk about Doodles, fine.
Take a look at what
that skeek did to me.
You got that at Maguires'?
Stick a mime and a clown in the
same place, it's like a cobra
and a mongoose.
You crashed Doodles' party, he kicked
your ass, and now Doodles is dead.
I didn't kill him.
You left a threatening message on his
answering machine. You declared war.
Look, the creep was a parasite.
When he wasn't bad-mouthing me,
he was horning in on my gigs. Every time
I line up a job, "ring-ring," Doodles
calls the mom, gets her to hire him,
too. That's money out of my pocket. So,
yeah, I figured a little
payback was in order.
Yeah, what did you do
after you left the Maguires?
I had a strip mall opening out of town.
You didn't stop by his house? You
know, wait for him to come back?
No. I got two hookers in
Pahrump who can verify.
We found prints belonging to three
separate people in Ed Burnell's
car: His, Jamal the thief, and Mindy.
He could have given her a lift.
Except we found her print on a condom.
Well, she said she loved Ed.
Yeah? How much, I wonder.
We're looking for information on Mindy
Dupont. This was her last known address.
Yeah, she's here.
Mind if we talk with her?
You got a search warrant?
You don't need a warrant just to talk. But
if you want, we'll go get one and come back.
Hey, it's a free country.
Yes, it is.
Mindy Dupont. We heard
you cleaned yourself up.
I tried so hard.
He said I would feel again.
I never wanted to feel.
Ed saved my life.
How do you repay a favor like that?
I tried.
We're going to clean you up.
What if I don't want to be clean?
No. I'm going to help you.
He was an angel.
He gave me that stuff.
And you didn't want to get high anymore.
Did you come here to
remember or to forget?
Well, the mime's alibi checks out. He
took polaroids, with the hookers. Strip
mall opened at 7:30. He didn't
leave Pahrump till the next morning.
Uh-huh. So that leaves us with what?
Nothing.
Hmm.
What about timeline? Mrs. Maguire gives
Doodles a lift, getting
him home around 8:30.
As far as we know, he didn't
have another job that night.
Doodles goes home, having performing
all day for kids, wrestling with
mimes. His costume would've been a little
skanky, yet he doesn't change out of it?
Maybe he never got inside.
And he walks around town in his
clown suit until he gets killed?
Okay, what are the
knowns? Um... Doodles was
suffocated. We found
yellow fibers up his nose.
Greg analyzed the semen
stains on his boxer shorts
and found an unknown vaginal
contribution in the sample.
Mrs. Maguire was the last
person to see him alive.
The night Ed Burnell was killed you
never checked into the halfway house.
Mindy, we found a knife in your basket
of clothes with Ed Burnell's blood on it.
Help us connect the dots.
We all have this secret,
terrible cave in our hearts,
and the more we try to escape it,
the deeper we drive
ourselves inside of it.
This isn't the halfway
house, Mindy. You're looking
at a murder rap, so
let's talk specifics.
There were fifty-seven
micrograms per milliliter
of monoacetylmorphine in your urine
sample. That means you
were using for a while.
Ed gave me ibogaine.
That was months ago. Where were
you the night Ed was killed?
It was like Adam and Eve
taking you to the movies except
the movie was your life and you were
watching it and in it at the same time.
Why would you have a
knife with his blood on it?
I think Ed Burnell knew you were
using again and he was out
there that night looking for you.
The spirits... they protect you.
Well, you better hope so, because you're
under arrest for the murder of Ed Burnell.
Sara. Excuse me. Could
you, uh, help me out?
Yeah, with what?
A woman. I need you to process
a female suspect for me.
Sure.
Palms down.
Thanks. You can get dressed now.
Samples from your suspect. There's
nothing but a few track marks.
No defensive wounds, no bruising.
Junkies usually bruise if
you breathe on them too hard.
She is a pile of twigs, very frail.
What?
I haven't seen you for a while, have I?
You see me every day.
It's all yours.
Thanks.
So, we're looking for clown sex...
...and clown murder.
This fabric is consistent with the
fibers we found in Doodles' nose.
You notice how everything matches
except this one pillow sham?
Yeah.
The white-faced clown
with a pillow covering
his face. There must've
been some transfer.
If a pillowcase like that had grease
paint on it, would you throw it out?
I'd clean it first.
You lied about driving the clown
home. He was in your bedroom.
DNA on his boxer shorts indicates
that you had sex with him.
We checked with the Buddy Ween Agency,
and, uh, you hire clowns on a fairly
regular basis: Four,
five, six times a year.
That's a lot of clowns.
I already told you. I like clowns.
I think you like them
more than most people.
Mr. Maguire, I hate to tell
you this, but while you were
off driving the other kiddies
home, your wife was doing the clown.
We figured you must've walked
in on them... in flagrante.
My wife!
You stripped the body and
dumped it in an area frequented
by transvestites, hoping
that it would just... go away.
Another forgotten sex crime.
You covered your tracks. You
cleaned the house. You washed
that pillowcase. What I
don't understand, though...
why did you keep the clown suit?
You don't understand. Merrill and
I have been married nine years.
We have two kids.
Not much left to get excited about?
I love my wife.
When Al wore the suit...
it worked... and it was good.
If you found something
that got you off...
wouldn't you keep it?
Man, there is something so heartbreaking
about a woman with raggedy drawers.
Mm-hmm.
Grissom. We've gone through
all Mindy's stuff twice.
There's no trace of blood.
It doesn't make any sense
if she disposed of the
clothes, she's not just
gonna forget about the knife.
Hey, guys, got a male DNA skin
sample collected from Mindy's hair.
Burnell?
Yes and no. The blood is Burnell's,
but the skin belongs to another guy.
Do we know who?
The gods of CODIS have blessed
us with a hit: Riley "Boom-Boom"
Renaldo, proud owner of
two assault and battery
charges and a possession
with intent to distribute.
Current occupation: Apartment manager.
What do you bet Boom Boom's estate is
on the corner of Washington and D Street?
Renaldo was Mindy's landlord?
That'd make her a bag-bride...
a strawberry. Paid her rent
horizontally. As long
as a dealer keeps a
strawberry high, the strawberry
does whatever the dealer wants.
Las Vegas Police. Open up.
Riley... you said I could have
a taste when we were done. Riley!
Shut up, sunshine.
Nice. We keep Mindy for a couple of
hours, and you've already moved on.
What's the matter? Lose faith in
Mindy? She always comes back to you.
Guess Burnell was bad for business, huh?
Yeah, old Ed gets enough people in
the 'hood clean, you get no love.
Riley... I need it.
I said shut up.
Mindy didn't need it anymore, right?
That's why you helped her remember.
I don't need that anymore.
What do you mean, you don't need it?
Just one more, and that's it.
Burnell wasn't hard to find, was he?
Yo, man... that jackass who be
messin' with Mindy is back...
You've got nothing on me.
Yeah, we do: Burnell's
blood on your skin.
So, come on, let's go, let's
go. Come on, you have the
right to remain silent.
Anything you say...
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
It's her choice, right?
Unfortunately.
What do you want to
do, take her to lock up?
Lateral move. She's already there.
One guy's dead. One guy's going to jail.
Well, you're free to go.
Go where?
You got my message.
Yeah. You sounded hungry. I was
thinking... dinner at the Bellagio.
All right.
What are you in the mood for?
Room service.