( whining )
Woof, woof !
Woof, woof, woof !
Nice try, fleabag.
Zeus !
Get outta here !
Blcch,
Dog germs !
Do I smell
some dinner ?!
Breakfast.
I knew that.
You've been up
all night again, huh ?
Sorry,
it's just that
I've been working
on this Melody
And it's somewhere in there.
I just can't find it.
What's this ?
Breakfast burrito.
Cool, thanks.
Let me see
your face.
Excellent, b+.
So, what's in
this burrito ?
Eggs, refried beans,
onions, jalapeños,
Peanut butter,
mozzarella cheese,
pineapple chunks.
Oh, yeah,
and lettuce.
So it's nutritionally
balanced.
Oh, shoot !
My burrito !
Ugh !
( whispering )
Zeus, psst.
C'mon, c'mon.
Good boy,
eat it up.
Thank you,
thank you.
Oh, good,
you finished yours.
I'll go get you
another one.
Woof !
And you two stay
At the enrichment program
all day, okay ?
( in robot voice )
you-are-understood-mother.
Ditto.
I'm not in the mood for
the principal calling me
Telling me
that you two--
( cat shrieking )
What is that ?
Lovely.
Jordan, cow bone !
Woof, woof, woof !
Hey !
Ahh !
Cow bone.
Cow bone,
cow bone !
Zeus, cow bone !
Zeus !
Cow bone !
C'mon, go on !
Go on !
Pfft...
I'm so sorry.
Let me help.
No, that's okay.
Oh, jeez.
Here, let me help.
Just how do you
propose to do that ?
I'll put your flowers
back in the ground here.
Wait, wait, no.
Actually, I have a very
particular way of doing this.
I like to put the roots
in the ground.
Oh...
Very...
You new in
the neighborhood ?
Yeah.
Just renting
for the week ?
Actually we'll be here
'till the end of July.
Great !
I'm Terry Barnett.
Mary Beth...
Dunhill.
Mary Beth.
Right.
I'd love to stay and chat
in my present state
But I'm late
for work.
That's okay,
I'll just replant
your flowers.
Oh, no, that's alright.
Is there anything
I can do ?
Uh, no.
How 'bout
your laundry ?
I'm a great
ironer.
If you can just
restrain that...
Zeus.
Yes !
Thank you.
Me, Terry, you ?
Judith.
You ?
Nora.
( groaning )
You're late.
I've been frantic,
don't ask.
What if Roxanne’s
not there ?
We've never been
late before.
What if she gets
eaten by a shark
Sitting there
waiting for us ?
What if I'm sorry, Becky,
I had a rough morning ?
Oh, yeah ?
Well, it's about
to get rougher.
We've been rejected
by the Pason Foundation,
And the manheim,
And the delphi.
Great !
That leaves
the Rockland Grant.
If I don't get that,
I'll be--
Stocking goldfish
at the local store.
Very funny,
Claude.
I wasn't joking.
Perhaps we should strive
for that grant together.
"the sum of the parts
being greater than the whole."
I don't think so.
Somehow I think our
research philosophies
are slightly different.
Oh, I didn't know
I ever had one.
Let me know
if you change your mind.
He should be
working with sharks.
He'd feel
more at home.
If I don't get
major funding soon
Roxanne's gonna
be in a pool
Doing sound recognition tests
for the rest of her life,
Probably for him.
Good morning, guys.
Hey, Phil.
Let's play the sounds of
the other dolphins for Roxanne
And see if
she runs away.
Okay, Roxanne,
I'm comin', sweetheart.
( dolphin chirps )
We'll do a body check,
check for rake marks.
We'll see if she's been
playing with other dolphins.
These are from our
last session, right ?
Right.
( sniffing )
Burritos ?
Do you smell
burritos ?
Yeah.
( loud burp )
You.
You're so cute !
No, this dog
is not cute.
This dog is
the hound from hell.
C'mon, you Zeus,
whatever your name is.
Get up here,
sit down, sit !
Sit, stay.
Stay.
( Jordan )
Zeus !
Yo, Zeus !
I think
I got Roxanne.
Great !
I'm cursed.
He's so cute.
He's not cute.
You stay
right there
Or you're gonna get
a free swimming lesson !
He's giving me
a face like that.
Zeus !
We've got her.
Roxanne,
sorry I'm late.
C'mon,
that's a girl.
Good morning
to you too, Roxanne.
How are you ?
C'mon.
Very good.
Woof, woof !
Thanks a lot, Zeus !
( Zeus barking )
Maybe if we give him
some food he'll calm down.
Maybe if he becomes food
he'll calm down.
She did not
mean that.
Yes, I did.
( Mary Beth )
we're outta here.
Zeus,
where are you ?
C'mon, Zeus !
Zeus !
Zeus ?
Lost the dog.
Great.
My new neighbor's
gonna think
I've shanghaied his dog
and fed him to the sharks.
Zeus ?!
( Mary Beth )
C'mon.
Oh, my gosh.
C'mere !
Get the camera.
I got it.
7:10,
2:15,
Off location six.
We have a canine Zeus,
we have Roxanne.
Woof, woof, woof !
What are
they doing ?
Talking to
each other.
They're
communicating.
They are talkin'.
I think...
We're witnessing
Inter-species
communication.
Mary Beth.
What ?
You're gonna get
that Rockland Grant.
Yes !
I love this dog.
I've always
loved this dog
From the minute
I saw that dog.
Linda, what have
you got ?
Mother and calf.
Yes.
Let's separate these two
for the next 24 hours.
Begin the sonar
recognition test series
And increase the volume
of the masking sounds
Until mother and calf
can no longer communicate.
The baby
needs to feed.
"the baby
needs to feed."
The sacrifice is for
the good for all mankind.
For science.
Yeah, for
Dr. Claude carver.
Swing it around.
You got it ?
Hold it steady.
( Mary Beth )
great submersible.
Look at that.
I could really use
something like that.
How'd you get it ?
Oh, I pulled
a few strings.
Perhaps you'd like to
take her down sometime.
Oh, yeah, sure !
Solo.
I keep telling you
Two keen scientific minds
are better than one.
Yes, but neither
are any good
Without the
essential ingredient.
What might
that be ?
Heart.
Sure.
Hey, hey !
I'll drop kick you
from here to Miami !
( Mary Beth )
no, you will not.
C'mon, Zeus,
let's get outta here.
Phil, get my bag,
will you ?
There you go.
You deserve it.
( boy )
let's go !
Great.
Okay, so let me
get this straight.
You don't want us to have
any fun over the Summer.
I don't want you
hanging out with
borderlines.
Craig isn't
borderline, mom.
And ditching your
enrichment classes.
Well, we're just--
We were just--
Rescheduling.
Yes, right.
Grounded.
This block,
one week.
Oh, no, mom.
Zeus !
Zeus.
Where'd you guys
find him ?
Actually he found me,
and you are ?
I'm Jordan Barnett.
I'm with him.
I see you and Zeus
have become friends.
Well, miracles
sometimes happen.
What's that ?
Some photos
I took this morning.
What ?
I can't
believe--
Oh, my God !
( Mary Beth )
charming.
Looking good, mom !
Working on
two weeks.
Here.
Your house has
a satellite dish,
doesn't it ?
Yeah.
Mom ?
Okay, but not
all the channels.
C'mon, Zeus !
Your dog was on the boat
with me all day.
Really ?
I'm sorry, I won't
let that happen again.
No, actually it sort of
seemed to suit him.
Really.
I'd like to
take him out again if --
Sure, you can take him
on a cruise to Antarctica,
But he's Jordan's dog.
Would you mind
If I just ask
him something ?
Go right ahead.
Gimme that !
Can I just watch this
for a minute ?
Girls, girls,
time out.
Where's Jordan ?
In there.
What are you
watching ?
( Mary Beth )
hello.
Oh, hi.
Hi, can I come in ?
Yeah, sure.
"braveheart".
Wow !
Did you do
all these ?
Yeah.
That one's gonna be the cover
for my dad's opera score.
Your dad
writes opera ?
It's a rock opera.
Most of the time
he does music
For commercials
and really tall elevators.
It's only
to pay the bills.
( woman on TV )
we have now brought the
psychic friends network...
Love that
satellite dish, huh ?
This is gonna
sound really lame,
But we don't even
have one TV in our house.
We're like a media
impaired family.
Oh.
Hey, is this
your mom ?
Yeah... She died.
Sorry to hear that.
You must miss her a lot.
Can I talk to you
for a minute ?
Yeah.
I think Zeus is
a very special dog.
What do
you mean ?
Well...
I think that Zeus
is capable of--
Inter-species
communication.
What's the big deal ?
I talk to Zeus all the time.
Ah,
But Zeus is talking
with my dolphin.
You own
a dolphin ?
I don't own her,
Roxanne lives in the bay,
But I kinda
take care of her.
She used to
live in a tank.
We're reintroducing her
into the ocean.
Now the problem is,
That she doesn't really
take to other dolphins.
But she seems
to like your Zeus.
So I was thinking,
It might be
really interesting
To get the two together,
Zeus and Roxanne,
And just see how things
go from there.
What do
you think ?
Well, this has to be
Zeus' decision.
Alright.
So, Zeus, would you like
to go out with Roxanne ?
Woof, woof !
Is that
a "yes" ?
Woof !
Yeah.
Great.
You like
our mom ?
Yeah, sure I do.
Enough to
go out with her ?
How 'bout
Saturday ?
Alright.
It's okay.
Okay,
new behavior.
That's it.
What is she doing out there
with that dog ?
Havin' fun.
No.
I'll tell you
what she's doing.
She's trying to
steal my grant.
That's just not
gonna happen.
No, sir !
Hey, watch where
you're going !
I was and I am.
You're driving too fast.
There are kids around.
Oh, I'm sorry.
I was in a hurry
to visit with Miss Dunhill.
Apparently
so were you,
And failed to look both ways
before crossing the street.
Thank God
for anti-lock brakes.
What are you
doing here ?
These are the manuals
for the submersible.
It's yours whenever
you want it.
Really ?
( man )
invite me in,
I'll go over them with you.
Alright.
Terry, did you
need something ?
Oh, no,
it's not important.
Alright.
Never is.
So, this is
a surprise.
It is ?
Bye, mom.
We're goin'
for a test ride.
I thought you two
were grounded.
Just around
the block.
With Zeus
and Jordan.
Please, mom ?
Come on mom !
One block.
I love you !
Thank you,
mommy.
Bye, mom !
You should think about
boarding school for those two.
Now, where were we ?
The catch.
No catch.
Boy.
This is it ?
This is it.
I don't know
about this.
Woof, woof !
Hey, get out
of there !
( sirens )
This is definitely
getting out of hand.
Okay, hold it
right there.
Judith ?
What's going on ?
Judith and Nora
are getting busted.
This is probably
their first offense.
I can probably get them off
with a stern warning.
Mm-hmm.
C'mon.
So, am I
to believe
That cute little dog
and your dolphin
Are actually talking ?
Incessantly.
Wow.
I have all this communication
skills data on file.
Perhaps you might
wanna reconsider
About pooling
our research
And applying for that
Rockland Mammal Grant together ?
The catch !
What, what catch ?
I'm sorry,
I'm sorry.
I already applied
for my grant.
But thanks
for the mini sub.
It was very
unselfish of you.
Hey, thanks for
talking deputy dog
Out of serious
jail time.
You're welcome,
youngster.
What's
the catch ?
Probably a lecture,
right, Jordan ?
No, he's not
too good at those.
But, I'm gonna try.
( motorcycle approaching )
( Terry )
that's it, all off
who are gettin' off !
Just around
the block ?
Do you two girls even know
what time it is ?
Yeah.
It's time for the
marlins-reds game.
Huh ?
On your
satellite dish.
It's been real !
( Jordan )
did I miss something ?
Tell me they weren't
robbing a bank ?
They weren't
robbing a bank.
Thank you.
They're still
talking ?
Probably
busting us.
Not Terry.
Give me those !
I can read lips.
"live to ride."
"ride to live."
A way of life.
"a way of life" ?
That's just a logo
they use to sell the bike.
Who cares about reading lips ?
I'm reading body language.
And they are talking
a mile a minute.
Oh, yeah.
What are
they saying ?
She's asking
him out.
( Judith )
no way.
Way.
Woof, woof !
Whoa.
Okay.
You can--
Right.
¶ it was
a teen-age wedding ¶
¶ and the old folks
wished them well ¶
¶ we could see
that Pierre ¶
¶ did truly love
the mademoiselle ¶
Wow.
Killer.
Cool, mom.
See, mom ?
You can look good when you try.
Dad.
Yes.
Terrence Barnett.
It won't bite.
¶ c'est la vie
say the old folks ¶
¶ it goes to show
you never can tell ¶
¶ they had
a hi-fi phono ¶
Put your feet on.
If you'd like,
you can hang onto the back
Or you can put your hands
around my waist.
Okay.
Whatever you like.
Jordy, you listen to
Mrs. Rice, okay ?!
Yes, father, sir !
( starting bike )
You okay ?
Woof, woof !
We are good.
¶ c'est la vie
say the old folks ¶
¶ it goes to show
you never can tell ¶
( Judith )
we think you spend too much
time alone, Jordan.
We've gotta do
something about it.
( calypso music )
Oh, he put it--
I don't know
how to play poker.
That's okay, Jordan,
we'll teach you.
The main thing
you need to know
Is you have to
bet something.
But I don't
have any money.
That's okay, too.
I'm sure we can
think of something.
Maybe we can
bet chores ?
Chores !
What kind of chores ?
Stuff your parents make
you do around the house
So they feel
you're useful.
You know,
chores.
I do all the chores
around here.
You won't have to.
If you win, that is.
Deal.
This Claude guy--
Do you see him ?
Every day.
Oh, really ?
Really and
unfortunately.
He's the head honcho
at the institute.
I used to be
his assistant,
But we had
a parting of the ways.
Oh. Would it be tactless
to ask over what ?
Third party.
Oh, I apologize,
never mind--
A dolphin.
"a dolphin."
I happened to think
that the dolphin
Was more important
than his career.
I agree.
( man )
hey, c'mon,
join us !
C'mon !
You have three of a kind.
That's excellent.
Yeah, but I have
the two of clubs.
Two of clubs
beats anything.
Sorry, man.
Gonna have to
clean my room for a month.
( Judith )
sorry.
Whoa !
Let's see, Jordan,
you've got tens and jacks.
That's two pair.
That's real good--
But, I have a three,
a five,
A seven, a Jack
and a Queen.
Cutthroat straight.
That beats you, sorry.
You're gonna have to
water our plants for...
Two weeks.
We better
get going.
We will...
Eventually.
You said that dolphins
are telepathic.
How about people ?
Some people.
Your bet.
Double
or nothing.
I'm your slave
for the rest of the Summer
Or we're back
to even.
You sure ?
I like to live
on the edge.
Well, you just
crashed and burned.
I have
a straight flush.
Oh, yeah,
oh, yeah.
And you know what ?
This is
the two of clubs.
No.
How'd you
do that ?
It's all
in the wrist.
I had
a great time.
You sound
surprised.
I am.
I mean,
no, no, no,
Please,
I don't mean
That I'm surprised
that I had a good time.
I'm...
For...
She's really
into it.
( Jordan )
give him a break,
he's a little Rusty.
More than
a little.
Yes !
Woof, woof,
woof, woof, woof !
Hey !
Shh !
Shut up !
Get outta here !
You get, get !
Get out !
Stop it, stop it,
stop it, stop it !
Woof, woof, woof,
woof, woof !
Zeus !
Zeus ?
Damn.
Okay, here I come.
Zeus.
What are
you doing ?
Okay,
You're a weird dog.
It's the creature
from the black lagoon.
Yeah, dressed
like Dr. Carver.
Get me a towel !
Creature, sir !
( guitar riff )
I think
they hear you.
That's where
Roxanne should be.
With them.
Cool fish.
I think you've
got yourself a band.
Good job, mates !
Rehearsal tomorrow,
same place, same time !
Everybody sober !
You know
dolphins.
Yeah.
I don't wanna
lose you, Terry.
lose me either.
When are
you leaving ?
I gotta go
to Boca Raton...
For a week,
mix my tracks,
Then it's off
to Boston
And a regular job,
Jordan's in school.
How 'bout you ?
I'm here through the Summer
if I get my grant.
And if you don't
get the grant ?
Minnesota aquarium
tour guide.
Ugh !
Mary Beth won't share,
will she ?
Neither will I !
Inter-species
communication.
I'll show her
inter-species communication !
Let's start with her.
She looks sickeningly
cute enough.
( whimpering & yelping )
( snoring )
See ya.
I'd like to
thank you.
Really, for what ?
'cause we're going
down in the sub ?
I should be
thanking you.
No, I mean thanks
for helping Terry.
He hasn't been able
to write in a long time.
( Jordan )
Roxanne’s
so graceful.
( Jordan )
oh, cool.
( Mary Beth )
uh-oh, drift nets.
They kill thousands
of dolphins every year.
Where do they
come from ?
Illegal fishermen.
C'mon, let's lead
Roxanne outta here.
( Jordan )
we're gonna have to
leave next week.
There's a new
family moving in.
You could stay
at our house.
What about my dad ?
( Judith )
we have two extra rooms.
Perfect.
Hey girls,
what brings you here ?
You've burned
the school down.
Then, why are
you here ?
Thank you.
This looks good.
Okay, why are you two
eating salads ?
You always
eat salad, mom.
Why can can't we
eat salad ?
I'm sorry,
no satellite dish.
They're too expensive,
we can't afford it--
No, mom,
it's not a satellite dish.
It's really that
Terry and Jordan
Need a place
to live for a while.
We want them at our house.
We have two extra rooms.
Yeah,
c'mon, mom.
Whoa, whoa.
Why do you think
they're even interested
in staying at our house ?
Well, Jordan does.
And so
does Terry.
Says who ?
Jordan told us.
He told us
lots of stuff.
Curious
to know, mom ?
What exactly
did they say ?
Okay, well--
It started out...
The rest of
the Summer ?
You sure this was
Mary Beth’s idea ?
And where are
my Twinkies ?!
I made you
a fruit salad.
It's in
the refrigerator.
And of course,
it was her idea.
You're sure.
Absolutely.
And dad,
use a spoon ?
Mm-hmm.
Right here,
I knew that.
Now, before
we do this,
There's a few things
you gotta know about me.
Uh-oh.
You one of these guys that
howls at the full Moon ?
I'm afraid so.
Oh, dear.
It's a little late
to be reticent now.
After all,
this was your idea.
My idea ?
Mm-hmm.
Jordan said
it was--
it was your idea for--
No, the girls told me
that you said--
No, I--
We've been set up.
By world-class
professionals.
Well ?
What are we gonna do,
professor ?
Well...
I suppose...
If you stayed that I could
continue my work with Zeus.
Mm-hmm, and...
I could finish
my second act.
So, I guess we'll
just have to
Make the best of it.
Man, we're good.
Woof, woof !
Should I take this stuff
next door now ?
Just put it
outside first.
Why ?
'cause I said so.
Jeesh !
Lemonade ?
No, thank you.
What happened ?
Nothing.
What didn't happen ?
Jordan ?
It's gone south.
What are we doing this for ?
Are we doing this for us ?
Are we doing this for
the Rockland foundation ?
Are we doing it
for the kids ?
What ?
All of the above.
I don't know.
It's okay, just--
Take as much time
as you need.
( Jordan )
it's time
to go, Zeus.
I don't
understand.
If a dog and a dolphin
can get along
Why can't our mom
and his dad ?
( Zeus whining )
Woof, woof !
Zeus, please.
I feel
badly enough.
Then why don't you
turn around ?
I wish I could.
I don't see
anyone else driving.
Jordan !
Hey,
good morning, boss.
Hey, you alright ?
What's wrong ?
They're gone.
So is Zeus.
They're just gone.
Men and dogs, huh ?
C'mere.
It's okay.
Oh.
I could almost cry.
Tears of Joy.
That dolphin
is fair game now,
Track her.
C'mon, Zeus.
Zeus, c'mon.
Zeus.
C'mon.
What is she doing ?
I don't know.
She's running away.
She won't let us
near her anymore.
So much for inter-species
communication.
That's what happens
When you work with these
animals in the wild.
They can walk out on you
whenever they want to.
If we can bring Roxanne
back into the lab--
Dr. Carver,
It's illegal to catch
a dolphin in the open sea.
Excuse me, Phil.
You know
he's right.
I'll replace Roxanne
with one of the simpletons,
Perhaps even two.
As scientists
we have to circumvent
These ridiculous
bureaucratic regulations.
( man whistling )
Girls, dinner !
Feeding time at
the enrichment program.
I resent that.
Why do you treat us
like your little Einsteins ?
What do
you mean ?
Did your parents
ever send you
To an enrichment
program ?
No.
C'mon, mom,
it's the Summer.
Enjoy it !
You're right.
I guess I'm just trying
to rush everything too much.
I'm trying to rush you
into being little adults,
I'm rushing Roxanne
back to the wild.
Probably rushing Terry into
I don't know what.
Oh, no, mom,
We'll take
Some of the blame
for Terry.
Actually, mom...
We'll take
most of the blame.
( Judith )
alright,
all of the blame.
I was so close.
I was so close
To reintroducing
Roxanne into a pod.
And then--
What happened
to Roxanne ?
She's gone.
She'll be back,
don't worry.
No, she won't.
She misses Zeus
too much.
Mom.
Zeus !
( phone rings )
Hello ?
It's me.
Yes ?
I see.
( Jordan )
anything ?
Nope, nothing.
I just know he's
trying to go back.
That is
unbelievable.
That's like scary.
I think it's time to take
Jurassic measures.
I agree.
What do we have to lose ?
Alright,
who is that ?
Hi.
Can you please
hold on a second ?
Dad.
It's for you, mom.
Who is it ?
It's Jane freeman
From the
record company.
It's somebody selling
cemetery plots.
Mom, get the phone.
Hello ?
Hello, gorgeous.
I had a dream about you
last night.
You did ?
Oh, yeah.
We went all the way,
positively platinum.
Oh.
I had a dream about
you too last night
And we went
resoundingly tin.
Hello, Terry.
They don't give up
too easily, do they ?
No, they do not.
I heard about Zeus.
I heard
about Roxanne.
She's pretty hurt.
So is he.
I mean, I think
she'll get over it.
Maybe...
We can give it
a little more time.
We'll talk.
Yeah.
Tomorrow ?
Yeah, tomorrow
would be great.
Alright.
Okay.
Bye.
Hello ?
Goodbye.
Okay, bye.
Hello.
Alright,
you hang up first.
Mm-mm.
How 'bout we
hang up together ?
I'll say bye
And on one, two, three,
we hang up.
Okay, bye.
One, two,
Three.
Hello ?
( dial tone )
She hung up on me.
Breakfast.
Jordy !
I woke up and
I wanna smell the coffee !
Jordy ?
( Jordan )
hi, dad, it's me.
I've gone to
look for Zeus.
Hi, dad, it's me.
I've gone to
look for Zeus.
( PA In background )
the white zone is for
Loading and unloading
of passengers...
Oh, shoot.
( phone rings )
Hello.
Mary Beth,
it's Becky.
I know it's Sunday but I thought
you should know about this.
Know what ?
I came to the office to
check up on a few things and--
And what, Becky ?
Claude carver
was just in.
He said they found a dolphin
caught in drift nets...
Dead.
It's not Roxanne.
I've gotta
find her, Becky.
Right.
No more
Mr. Nice guy.
Look who's back.
Now Roxanne
is ours.
No, Dr. Carver.
Yours.
We quit.
No, you don't.
You're fired !
We got a date
with a dolphin.
Excuse me, sir !
How would you like to be part
of scientific history ?!
Can I interest you
in a case of rum ?
Enjoy your flight.
Next in line.
( Jordan )
do you have
standby ?
What ?
Do you have
standby ?
And do you have a good reason
for being here ?
Uh-oh.
Take us to 0-3-5
full throttle !
This mongrel
is the perfect bait !
Roxanne will
come to us !
( beeping )
Yes !
We got her !
Ah, my foot !
You know, Jordy,
We're gonna do everything
we can to find Zeus
But it's extremely unlikely
he made it down here.
Dad,
Zeus is an
extremely extreme dog.
That he is.
( Jordan )
he's also in love.
( Terry )
an extreme emotion.
Why don't you
try it sometime, dad ?
It's okay.
( Judith )
Jordan !
C'mon !
Cab's waiting.
Let's go.
Mind if I
tag along ?
C'mon !
Becky.
There's something
you should know.
It's about
Dr. Carver.
Hey, girls,
Terry,
What are you
guys doing here ?
Where's my mom ?
Her boat's gone.
She's out
looking for Roxanne.
C'mon, Roxanne.
Ready the net.
( Zeus barking )
Ready...
Now !
You missed,
you idiot !
Get it back up !
Get it up, fool !
C'mon, move, move !
Get me out !
You stupid dog.
Mom ?
Mom !
( Nora )
mom !
Mom !
( Jordan )
flags up,
she's down in the sub.
How long can she
stay down there ?
45 minutes
I think.
Roxanne.
( Mary Beth )
yes, Roxanne.
I think she wants you
to follow her.
Get me a knife !
You okay ?
Roxanne.
( Jordan )
c'mon !
( Claude )
good dog,
yes, yes,
That's a good dog.
No !
( Claude )
you mongrel !
Stay, stay.
What are you doing ?
No, no, no !
Officer,
arrest this dog !
Oh, we will.
Free Dr. Carver,
and then arrest him.
I confess,
it was all him !
What are you talking about,
you idiot ?!
I'll kill you !
Atta boy, Zeus.
( man across street )
I'm waiting !
How do you like
your new neighbors ?
I liked the
old ones better.
I'm gonna
take a shower.
make some coffee.
Don't do that
again, okay ?
We believe that with
all that's happened
It's clearly
established that
You do
like our mom.
Of course I do.
Enough to marry her ?
How 'bout
next Sunday ?
Where do you
keep the coffee ?
At this point,
if there's anyone here
That has any reason
that this marriage
Between Mary Beth Dunhill
and Terrence Paul Barnett
Shall not
take place,
Speak now or forever
hold your peace.
( man )
wait !
Wait !
Sorry, they told me to bring
this down here right away.
Better offer ?
It's the grant !
( Jordan )
good going, Mary Beth--
I mean mom.
Now I suppose
you can kiss the bride.
What's going on ?
I think...
He's telling her
it's time.
Go on, girl.
It's your turn.
}}