Okay. . .
Honey, didn't we settle on this dress?
lt's got straps.
lt makes me look chunky.
lf you were any thinner, you'd
crack in two and blow right away.
No, Mama.
My tushy's a little cushy.
Honey, your tushy's just like your
mama's, and that means just fine.
Take that, Mama.
Okay, sleeves or no sleeves?
What do you think?
Oh, l don't know.
l still like this dress.
Well, mother,
it doesn't matter what we like.
[ Camera clicks ]
Well, question is. . .
What would Silas like?
BOSS: Silas!
There's somethin' in the pool!
RADlO:
That was ''Angel yes''
and you're listening to WQQG
here in Wilmington, Kentucky.
Comin' up, we'll talk about...
Hey! What the hell
is wrong with you?
Didn't you hear me?
We got a floater.
[ Rat squeaks ]
[ Grunts ]
Now, what the hell
did you do that for?
lt wasn't dead.
Well, get it out of there.
l want this pool clean.
That must be askin' too much.
Am l askin' too much?
Hey! Hey, dumb-ass!
Am l asking too much?
Yes.
BOSS:
Hey!
l had to beg for weeks
to get you that job.
Talked him into a dental plan --
full family coverage.
How you gonna
cover a full family now?
Silas, you gotta be more dependable.
You're marryin' my little niece.
You're joinin' our family.
Now, l know you're a decent fellow
deep down inside,
but you gotta ask yourself,
what are we all seein' on the outside?
Ah, we'll work on it.
You buy the ring?
Now, see, that's part
of that bein' dependable thing
we were talkin' about.
She has a ring.
And you did buy it for her, right?
l assume she didn't
buy it for herself.
[ Phone rings ]
Niagara Falls - da da da dum!
Look how big it is.
lt's huge!
And did you know
that 6 million cubic feet of water
goes over the edge every minute
1 70 feet straight down?
Did you know that?
lt's in the pamphlet there,
if you wanna have a quick look-see.
Cammy?
Why are you still doin' this?
Because, Raymond, you should know
that Niagara Falls
is the place for lovers.
CAMlLLE:
l mean, that's the slogan.
Yeah, it's printed
right there on the pamphlet.
Look, see?
Oh, poop, Raymond.
l think Silas
has served his debt to society.
Honey, he's on parole.
He can't leave the state.
-Well, says who?
-The state. lt's the law.
Well, then,
we'll keep it our little secret.
And it's more fun that way.
Niagara Falls is where people go
when they're in love,
and that's the real law. . .
. . .the law of love.
Oh, honey, you look so beautiful.
l want to remember today,
just the way it happened,
the way l look, the way l feel.
l always want it to be this good.
Smile.
[ Camera clicks ]
l wonder how Silas is feeling.
[ Throwing up ]
Silas, don't screw this up.
Happy. Happy. Everyone's happy.
[ Organ plays ]
[ Wedding march plays ]
Darling! l love you!
And do you, Silas,
take this woman, Camille,
to be your lawful wedded wife, to love
and honor, in sickness and health,
in loving holy matrimony
till death do you part?
lt's your turn, Tiger.
You can do it.
Do you want me
to repeat the question, son?
You just say yes, hon.
Say yes.
You just say yes.
Yes.
-Yes.
[ Laughs ]
[ Clapping and cheers ]
Oh, wait!
Oh. . .
Oh, jeez. . . the rice.
l forgot to get the rice.
We have to throw the rice.
The rice is for good luck.
-Cammy. . . it's okay.
-Well, didn't anyone bring the rice?
-Baby, it's all right.
-lt's okay.
Okay.
[ Church bells ]
[ Music plays ]
PRlEST:
Congratulations, Silas.
Not dancing with your pretty bride?
l can't dance.
Well, it's your weddin' night, son.
Nobody's gonna care how you look.
l can't dance with her.
lt's Camille.
Sometimes l just feel like. . .
Like you have doubts.
-Like l wanna punch her! Wham!
-Good Lord.
Tell me about it.
l mean, that girl can talk.
That's all she does is talk.
Talk, talk, talk, talk, talk!
-But you just married her.
-Preacher. . . l need a word with Silas.
Tell me about it.
You're a lucky man, Silas.
Boy, that girl would do
just about anything for you.
Silas!
Come on out here, Tiger!
Except maybe shut up.
Oof!
You know. . .
every marriage
has problems the first year.
Yours just happen to be
in the first couple hours.
l know you'll work through it,
'cause. . .
well, if you don't, l'm gonna
have to send you back to prison.
Three strikes,
and you'll never come out again.
Come on, Silas.
Come on.
-A sidecar!
-What the hell is that?
And here's somethin'
for the trip to Niagara Falls.
For you and all your pictures.
Thank you, Uncle Raymond.
Thanks for the sidecar.
You're the best. l love you.
-Bye, everyone!
-Remember, be good. Both of you.
Smile, everybody!
That's my little niece
you've got there. Be good.
-Take care of her, Silas.
-Goodbye!
Goodbye, cruel world! Bye!
Bye, honey!
[ Music plays ]
Niagara Falls!
Niagara Falls, here we come!
Did you see my book?
''Make Your Honeymoon Perfect''!
You don't see that every day.
How about some bathrooms?
We've been on the road
since Covington.
l told Silas a girl
just can't hold it forever.
Whoa!
You've got a kitty on your head, man.
You've got a kitty-cat.
But seriously, nice sidecar, dude.
-You like a warm-up, Cowboy?
-Lookie there.
Aren't those some pretty creatures?
You know, when it comes to horses,
l'm kind of a philosopher.
Suppose you're wonderin'
what l mean by that.
Hey, Tiger, over here!
We got company.
Look.
Silas got a good chunk
of his sentence cut
for showin' such good behavior.
l mean, that's what Raymond said,
good behavior, it's true.
-Don't tell them that.
-But it's true!
l'm not ashamed to tell them.
-Camille. . .
-Just shows how worldly you are.
You served your time,
and now you're mine.
l would go see him during visitation.
He looked so cute
in that orange jumpsuit.
All the guards
said we made a perfect couple.
-Ahhh. . .
-l've known Silas since l was six.
-Show them your tattoos, Tiger.
-No!
He didn't have those back then.
He's such a rebel, isn't he?
l mean, nobody smokes anymore.
Wow. Are truckers really this nice,
or are we just in good moods?
You just have to tell them
everything about everything.
l think the dress
sort of gave me away.
Besides, rule number 1 5
in the honeymoon guide book says,
''Always tell people
that you're newlyweds.''
''They will sometimes
offer you special discounts.''
-Why don't you just invite them along?
-Don't be grumpy, Tiger.
l'm not ''grumpy, Tiger.''
l'm mad.
Why do you have to be
so damn happy all the time?
lt makes us both look stupid.
You know, l'm sick of your damn
honeymoon guidebooks
and your Niagara Falls stories
and all your talking!
That's all you do is talk!
Can't you just shut up
for once in your life?
Please. Please.
Just try and keep
your mouth shut once.
Please.
Can you do that?
Don't do it.
They have hash.
l never had hash before--
Please.
Shut up.
Have you had hash?
Ma'am?
Are you okay?
Yeah.
Once we get to the Falls,
we'll be okay.
We just both
want to get there so badly.
lt's just that Silas
is the strong, silent type
and l sometimes
talk more than he's used to,
but he doesn't mind, really.
[ Motorcycle engine rumbles ]
See?
He's just itchin' to get there.
Talk, talk, talk, talk, talk!
Talk!
Talk, talk. . . !
A horse will be scared
of the smallest things --
a flower bush,
a puddle of water.
He'll see the puddle,
but he can't understand it.
So he'll rear back, afraid.
Now. . .
Thank you.
Now, we people,
we can see it for what it is.
lt's just water.
So why should we be scared?
Are you following me here, ma'am?
l'm sorry.
Somethin' about horses. . .?
Yes, ma'am.
Just somethin' about horses.
[ Motorcycle engine rumbles ]
Well, l guess this is it, then.
Thanks for the company,
Mister Cowboy Bob.
Hey. . . you two are gonna make it.
l got a sense.
You got that connected kinda feelin'.
Good.
Goodbye, ma'am.
Bye.
Yeah.
Come on.
We can't miss
that big freakin' waterfall.
Silas, do you love me?
l married you, didn't l?
Tiger, please.
You do love me, don't you?
Well, that wasn't really
the question that l meant to ask.
You know, it just
sort of came out wrong.
l don't mean, l don't mean ''love,''
''love me'' --
well not yet, anyways.
l mean, people grow to love
each other, so we got lots of time.
Camille!
Get on the bike, please.
Please get on the bike!
[ Camera clicks ]
[ Motorcycle engine rumbles ]
[ Crying ]
[ Clanking ]
Silas, my ring!
l dropped my ring!
[ Honking ]
Silas!
Hey. . .
Don't sit so close to the new TT.
You'll go blind.
Here you go.
Looks like Daddy
forgot his wallet again.
A phone!
-You, you're covered in--
-A phone! l need a phone!
-Who's he calling?
-l don't know.
9-1-1.
What's your emergency?
Hello? Hello?
Please don't hurt us.
We don't have anything.
l killed her!
-l don't care what you've done, okay?
-l killed her.
-We won't say anything to anyone.
-l killed her!
You just go on. Just. . .
Here. . . just take the money.
Please don't hurt us.
Camille!
Camille?
Oh, there you are, Tiger!
You okay?
Yeah, l'm here.
l'm a little mucky.
l don't think they're gonna
take my dress back.
My neck's a little sore,
but you can touch it.
l thought l killed you.
Tiger, look at your shirt!
You look awful.
l'm gonna have
to get you to the doctor.
What happened?
We wrecked.
l don't remember much.
l just. . .
Tiger, you're shaking.
Are you okay?
l thought you were gone.
l'm not goin' anywhere.
Except to Niagara Falls with you.
You sure you
don't remember anything?
Well, l remember the wedding
and getting in the sidecar.
Did we stop somewhere?
That part is a little fuzzy.
Oh, right. Here.
Oh, Tiger, you found it.
Oh, Tiger, your poor bike.
Should we go to that house?
Maybe they'll give us a ride.
No. That's a bad idea.
Farmers.
[ Police sirens ]
-Tiger. Hey!
-Camille! Get down!
Hey! Hey!
They didn't even beep, Tiger!
l'm on parole!
Oh, Camille!
l almost blew it!
[ Honking ]
Hi.
Did he say who he was calling?
No.
He didn't actually talk to anyone.
He said, um. . . he said he killed her.
And he seemed
real upset about killin' her.
And he was wearin' that tuxedo,
which l guess seemed peculiar.
-Did he say who he killed?
-He killed our damn TT!
We already established that, son.
Hey, Sheriff!
Got this.
Run a check on those.
See what we get.
Hey, Camille!
You all right in there?
-Can you hear me? Camille?
-Be out in a minute!
[ Phone rings ]
-Raymond. . .
-Silas?
Silas, what's goin' on?
-Somethin's wrong with Camille.
-ls she okay?
Well, yeah, she says she's okay.
She wants to keep goin' , but. . .
somethin's wrong.
Not now.
You got a call from some sheriff
in Ohio investigating a robbery.
-Says he's gotta talk to you pronto.
-All right. All right. Silas, listen.
l want to talk to her,
but you tell Camille if she's sick,
turn around, come home.
She's got her whole life to see
the Falls. Will you tell her that?
Now, now, hold on.
Yeah, Foster.
What?
Get in bed, Tiger!
After a hot shower,
l'm a frisky kitty.
[ Growls and meows ]
l've decided
no more poutin' from Camille.
lt takes two to tango.
l'm gonna make this fun for you, too.
Co-o-m-me. . .
C-o-o-m-me
to m-m-e-e-e. . .
Tiger?
Tiger.
[ Phone rings ]
Good morning.
This is your wake-up call.
Camille?
Wake up. . .
Wake up time.
Camille!
[ Neighing ]
Tiger. . .
l just had this dream.
Whoa. . .
Look at you.
You're all dressed.
-Yeah.
-What's the story, morning glory?
l get a kiss this mornin'?
That was a handshake, not a kiss.
-l've got to take a shower.
-But you're all dressed.
l know.
CAMlLLE: You know, whenever
l'm in a new place like this,
l always think, what if l lived here
instead of home, you know?
l mean, what if l always lived here?
And then l think,
l never would have met Silas.
What if you lived somewhere else
and we never met?
Then l think, l would have met you
wherever l lived. l was meant to.
Love is a powerful thing, Silas.
lt's the thing that keeps me going.
l could use some color.
You look. . . nice.
-Really?
-Yeah.
Listen, you wanna try on some more?
l'll buy as many as you want.
Okay!
-Okay?
-Okay.
May l have that hat, too, please?
Okay. That will be $959.29.
How do you wanna pay for all this?
Okay. . . Wayne.
Silas!
Oh. . .
-lt's our honeymoon.
-Oh.
Right this way.
How can we afford this?
l didn't budget for chandeliers
and Olympic pools.
Hi.
-Hi there. l love your place.
-Thank you. l'll take that bag.
Oh, thanks.
Okay. Here we are.
The honeymoon suite.
Oh, my God!
Maybe we should
let some fresh air in here, huh?
-Yeah.
-Oh, this is gonna be fun, Tiger!
lf there's anything you need,
don't hesitate to call the front desk.
-Thank you.
-They will send someone.
-Bye, Leslie!
-Bye!
Thanks!
-l've gotta take a shower.
-Again?
You like me
to come in there with you, Tiger?
No!
Oh, shit.
Camille?
Camille!
l brought you a robe.
l'm fine in here, thanks.
Come on.
You've been in there long enough.
You could come in here
with me, Tiger.
No. Come on.
Tiger, why are you being
so nice to me?
l mean, l appreciate it. But l wanna
know, is there somethin' wrong?
You wouldn't believe me.
Well, try me.
You're dead.
Oh, my God!
Tiger, look!
-Come on!
-You saw a blue horse?
Yeah. l think it went this way.
lt sounds crazy,
but l've seen this horse before.
Look. . .
Oh, my God, is this real?
Well. . .
Look what the horse dragged in.
l was hopin'
we'd see you again someday.
Figured you'd be
up to the Falls by now.
Oh, but we took a few wrong turns,
but Tiger got us back on track.
Right, Tiger?
Why would you. . . paint a horse?
COWBOY BOB:
Well, it all started with a dream.
But l'll tell you, it sure makes
their teeth look brighter, don't it?
-Sure does.
-She's not very strong.
Well, that's Maggie.
l told you about her.
-You don't remember that part, huh?
-No.
Well, Maggie knows you.
l told her all about you.
Ain't that right, Maggie?
Didn't l tell her?
Maggie likes you.
l like Maggie.
Tiger, you're turning green.
l should have warned you.
Maggie's been so sick lately,
l've been experimenting
with a special feed.
COWBOY BOB:
l like to try out new recipes.
l can't hardly smell anything anymore.
l got used to it, l guess.
You need it in this business.
ln the cowboy business?
No, ma'am.
The cowboy business
is dead and gone.
This here is. . . show business.
Show business. . .
You know, Maggie's about
the smartest horse l've ever known.
COWBOY BOB: One day she just
wandered in and found me.
Don't know why.
COWBOY BOB: But l knew
there had to be a reason for it.
l could see it in her eyes.
And ever since then, l've just been
tryin' like heck to keep her goin'.
You know, l'm not
one of them New Age cowboys,
but l believe in fate.
That's beautiful.
Silas, isn't that
the sweetest thing you ever heard?
COWBOY BOB: lt's comin' to the end
of the trail for Maggie.
l know that.
Well, Roy Rogers
had Trigger preserved after he died.
Least, that's the story l heard.
CAMlLLE:
Do you smell somethin'?
COWBOY BOB:
l can't smell anything but horses.
Silas, do you smell that?
-Yes.
-CAMlLLE: lt's weird.
l wonder what it is.
lt's you.
CAMlLLE:
Silas Parker, l don't smell!
Do l?
Yes.
Hey. . .
-Where you goin'?
-You stay.
Obviously, l need to go.
Well, she didn't smell.
How much?
Roger that.
We'll be up there.
Mark!
-l'm gonna stop that asshole.
-RAYMOND: Hey, now.
We won't need that.
SHERlFF STElNER:
The family he robbed
said he carried on about killin'
somebody.
SHERlFF STElNER: We're lookin'
at a parole violation turned robbery
turned possible homicide.
-That's a red flag.
-He's not even capable of murder.
Silas steals things.
Little things.
Once he stole a microwave
for his mama's birthday.
You know, that's kind of sweet.
RAYMOND:
Now, look. l know the boy.
Deep down inside,
he's a decent fellow.
And that's why
you let him jump parole?
Because deep down,
he was not on parole?
Come on! lt's their honeymoon.
Besides, you don't know Camille.
She always gets what she wants.
She's wanted him
practically her whole life.
SHERlFF STElNER: Well, l found this
in the cornfields yesterday. . .
near the accident site.
l'll say he was pretty prepared.
-This is their honeymoon money.
-They're not on a honeymoon.
They're runnin' for the border!
Hey, l understand she's your niece.
You can tag along.
But like it or not,
this is my honeymoon now.
The missus seems kind of tuckered.
She's dead.
Oh, yeah. Yeah.
l know what you mean.
When l haven't slept well,
l can hardly get started the next day.
No, she's not tired.
She's dead.
ln what sense?
She's decaying, fallin' apart.
lt gets worse every minute.
-She doesn't seem too upset about it.
-She doesn't know.
l mean, how are you supposed
to tell someone that they're dead?
Hmm. . .
Exactly.
[ Alarm rings ]
[music] Pull in the club [music]
[music] We hear the bang bang [music]
[music] Roll through the door [music]
Bob!
Bob?
[ ''Four on the Floor'' plays ]
Got ten gallons of formaldehyde.
Go!
[music] Do what you came to [music]
[music] You can't numb that feeling
of that four on the floor [music]
l can't believe l did that.
That was great, Bob.
Destruction of private property.
l feel like an outlaw.
[music] D.J. is really wicking [music]
[music] He got that old school mixing [music]
[music] The fellows' heads are spinning [music]
[music] All the girls are finger licking [music]
[music] We got the public bubbling [music]
-Bob! Bob! Bob!
-Whoa!
Bob!
COWBOY BOB:
Hold on! Hold on! Jesus!
Come on!
-Let's roll, buddy.
-Yeah.
[music] Four on the floor [music]
[music] Feel the beat in your soul [music]
COWBOY BOB:
l know it's none of my business,
but what are you gonna do to her?
Just clean her up, tell her the truth.
SlLAS: Formaldehyde
will get rid of the smell.
How will you break it to her?
l don't know.
My wife usually does all the talking.
You sure are an unusual couple.
Yeah.
[ Lock clicks ]
l'm home.
[ Crying ]
Camille?
Silas. . .
What's wrong?
[ Crying ]
Hey.
[ Sobbing ]
-CAMlLLE: Don't, Silas. Just don't!
-lt's okay.
Don't, Silas!
Don't look at me!
lt's okay.
What's happening to me?
l don't understand it.
Everyone can see it.
l look so terrible.
Why is this happening?
l think you're dead.
What?
That's not possible.
-How can that be?
-l don't know.
lt doesn't make any sense.
Come here.
-But, Tiger, this is our honeymoon.
-Shh. . .
l got you somethin'.
Ta da!
lt's red.
Yeah. Red.
Yeah.
Don't look at me. l get shy.
l said not to look at me!
[ Laughs ]
[ Hums a tune ]
What are you doing?
Just bein' stupid.
Do you like it?
lt's the most beautiful thing
l've ever seen.
You really think so?
Yeah.
Thank you, Tiger.
What are we gonna do, Silas?
CAMlLLE:
Just tell me l'll be okay.
l'm not really dead.
Okay?
All right.
And we're gonna make it to the Falls.
We're not gonna stop now,
not for anything.
We can make it.
lf it's the last thing l do, Camille,
l promise you
l'll get you to Niagara Falls.
SHERlFF STElNER:
Damn bagel is two weeks old.
She used to plan her whole schedule
around his parole meetings
just so she could
get a glimpse of him in my office.
-You didn't talk her out of this?
-RAYMOND: l tried.
l showed her surveillance tapes
the night we picked him up on a B & E.
All she could talk about was
how cute he looked in that sweater.
How can you stand in the way
of somethin' like that?
l would have shot the guy.
[ Whistles ]
[ Police sirens ]
We're just gonna bring him in
for questioning, right?
We aren't gonna hurt anybody?
Well, that's up to him.
But just in case things get ugly,
you're stayin' here,
and you're not goin' up there
until l see what we've got.
This is my niece. Come on.
Stay.
And you stay with him.
Camille?
-SlLAS: You all right?
-Never better, Tiger.
Today is a new day.
Yeah.
LESLlE:
Yes, sir, it's right here.
[ Police sirens ]
POLlCEMAN:
Perimeter secure?
POLlCEWOMAN:
l've got the perimeter secure, yes.
POLlCEMAN:
l'm pulling around back.
All right, let's move in, guys.
l've got the exits!
All right, l've got it!
[ Knocking ]
Bellman!
[ Whispers ]
-Hey! Hey!
-What?
Shh!
[ Knocking ]
Bellman!
-SlLAS: All right, can you jump?
-CAMlLLE: Oh, God!
-Tiger, what about all our stuff?
-l got it right here.
l can't jump down there! l can't!
Tiger, l can't.
All right. All right, then.
l'm gonna need you
to do somethin' else, okay?
Okay.
Oh, l've got a key.
[ Door unlocks and chain rattles ]
[ Sighs ]
Police! Freeze!
-SHERlFF STElNER: Oh, Jesus.
-DEPUTY RUDDY: Check the room.
SHERlFF STElNER:
Stone cold.
Send in the coroner.
She's dead.
DEPUTY RUDDY:
Balcony's clear!
[ Flashes click ]
Any idea on those stains?
l think it's formaldehyde.
Sick bastard.
[ Elevator beeps ]
[ Elevator music plays ]
PARAMEDlC:
You never get used to this stuff.
We're immune to it, ma'am.
When you're an officer,
you've been to those dark places.
You've seen the evil
that lurks in the hearts of men--
[ Sneezes ]
[ Screams ]
OFFlCER RlLEY:
No, stop, please! Oh!
[music] l want a girl like that [music]
[music] That makes me want to dream [music]
OFFlCER RlLEY:
Freeze!
[ Shots fired ]
[music] l want to lose my mind [music]
[music] l want to bring it back [music]
[music] Yeah [music]
[music] l want a chic, gas, fast-track,
matter-of-fact... [music]
[music] Matter-of-fact [music]
[music] l want a girl like that [music]
[music] Oh [music]
There's no need to lie,
you know what l mean?
We all make mistakes.
Chief, l swear to God,
she sneezed in the elevator.
The last time l saw her, Riley, she
was dead, D-E-D, and not breathin'.
But you saw her sneezing, huh?
-Hmm?
-Yeah.
Then what did she do,
start flyin' around the room?
Uh, no, actually
she ran down a hallway.
CAMlLLE: Jeez, Tiger, this was
supposed to be our new life,
no more trouble with the authorities,
and here l am, your new wife,
and l'm getting you in trouble.
-There's a hole in your shirt.
-What?
Oh, God. l love this shirt.
This was our shoppin' spree shirt.
You bought it for me.
You know what it is?
l knew it -- it's the rice.
l told them we had to have rice
at the wedding.
l said it isn't a wedding
without rice. lt was a bad sign.
There's another hole right there.
Let me take a look.
Holy shit!
-SlLAS: That's a bullet hole.
-l feel fine.
l don't want to talk about it.
There's nothin' wrong
with just a, you know. . .
a itty-bitty little hole
in my shoulder.
-Two holes.
-There's nothin' wrong with me.
You know what else?
l love my red hair.
l do.
When my hair grows back,
l think l'm gonna color it this way.
That's nice.
[music] One more coffee in a paper cup [music]
[music] One more tread on my soul [music]
[music] One more sunset [music]
[music] One more sweet dream [music]
[music] Rockin' to the rhythm of the road [music]
Hey. . .
-Hey, Robert.
-lris.
You here to stay this time?
Depends.
[ Laughs ]
[ Rattling from inside the truck ]
Uh-oh.
What are you feedin' those horses?
Well. . .
Hi. Hi.
Hi. You got stowaways.
Oh, we're newlyweds.
You know how it is.
l'm not cut out
for this kinda thing --
breaking and entering,
thievin' , mayhem. . .
That's for the young kids.
l'm an old man, Silas.
l didn't sleep a wink last night.
Just get us to the border.
Then you can forget
you even knew us.
Sorry, fellow.
l'm no good for you.
Or anybody.
MS. SAMUELS: Well, l've known
Robert going on 1 5 years now.
He's always had this horse.
l know he takes good care of Maggie,
but look at the blisters here.
You're gonna start peeling
like old paint soon.
She ought to be gone by now.
Maybe she isn't ready to leave yet.
Nobody's ever
ready for that, are they?
You know, a young and pretty
new bride like you
shouldn't be walking around
in an old, dirty, tattered, old skirt.
l know. l sort of
lost all my clothes along the way.
You like rodeo clothes?
COWBOY BOB: Ladies
and gentlemen, boys and girls. . .
these are horses
of a different color.
Here, the ride never stops.
Here, life is forever.
Now, you stay on there, little girl.
lsn't he cute, Silas, helpin' out?
Silas, look.
lt's so silly, Tiger.
You didn't kill anybody.
Why would they say that?
What are we gonna do?
-We're gonna get out of here.
-l mean, after that.
What happens when we
want to go back home?
l'm not goin' back home.
Okay.
COWBOY BOB:
Silas?
Man, can you please
just take us to the Falls?
You're not goin' to the dance?
l don't dance.
You've never danced
with your wife?
She can't wait forever.
[ Hums ]
She's not lookin' so good, Bob.
Well, still alive, still kickin'.
That's a happy horse
that can say that,
even if she can't really say it.
Ooh, looks like she needs a touch-up.
[ Neighing ]
CAMlLLE:
Bob?
Can l ask you a weird favor?
Whoa! Burnt orange!
l'll look so tan!
Okay.
What's that?
Oh, just ignore that part.
You can paint right over it, right?
Camille?
Come on out.
[music] There was a time [music]
[music] When they played
for the love of the game [music]
[music] Everybody stood by
the promises they made [music]
[music] That was somewhere
way back when [music]
CAMlLLE:
See?
You're a fine dancer, Tiger.
Feel like everybody's watchin' me.
Tiger, please.
Everybody's watchin' me, not you.
What?
What's the matter?
Nothin'.
Everything's good.
You know, l think l'm feeling better.
l feel like l'm
comin' through all of this.
l mean, it could have been
some temporary coma
or, like, a weird virus that just
sort of slowed my body down.
Those things happen all the time,
l bet -- we just don't hear about it.
Could be.
[music] We bow our heads and pray [music]
[music] And faith was more
than just a word [music]
[music] You heard some preacher say [music]
[music] That was somewhere
way back when [music]
[music] That's the way the world was then [music]
[music] When l love you now and forever [music]
[music] Up until the very end [music]
[music] l like the way that things are now [music]
[music] Where the Lord is right without [music]
[music] l want the kind of love
our parents had [music]
[music] We can love again [music]
[music] The ways... [music]
[music] The ways of way back when [music]
What?
[ Rain falls ]
-Oh, God. . .
-Camille!
[ A snap ]
Oh. . .
[ Cries ]
Camille?
[ Thunder ]
Camille!
[ Knocks ]
Go away, please!
Please, open up!
Now is not a good time, Silas!
Just let me in!
[ Clanking ]
l'm dead.
lt's true.
l'm dead!
Silas!
Silas, my ring!
Sorry.
lt's okay.
[ Grunts ]
lt is not okay, Silas!
Till death do us part!
Remember?
l'm dead, Tiger!
l think that's
grounds for separation.
[ Sobbing ]
Just leave me alone, please.
Just let me die!
[ Clanking ]
l'm not gonna let you die.
You're still my wife.
POLlCE OFFlCER:
Stop right there, sir! Now, sir!
Get your hands on the hood!
Do it now, sir! Get down! Get down!
Put your hands on the hood!
l've got the cuffs, Jerry.
l got 'em.
What? You don't want mine?
Don't need two cuffs, Jerry!
COWBOY BOB: Yes, we do.
We need two cuffs, Jerry.
Think you better drop it, ma'am.
[music] lt's out there [music]
[music] Somewhere [music]
[music] Something less ordinary [music]
[music] lmagine a little more money [music]
[music] And Freedom [music]
[music] A little less burden to carry [music]
[music] A good life is calling my name [music]
[music] lt's out there [music]
[music] l don't want to complain [music]
[music] 'Cuz my life really ain't that bad [music]
[ Police sirens ]
[music] lt's only human to want
more than what we have [music]
[music] Wouldn't it be cool if we... [music]
[music] ...vacation [music]
[music] Settle my spirit [music]
[music] Trade all my worries [music]
[music] For peace of mind [music]
She's not breathing.
She'll wake up.
How do you know?
l don't.
l just hope she does.
Did you really kill her?
lt was an accident.
She's gotta be some kinda ghost.
l don't believe in ghosts.
l don't believe in anything.
She believes in me.
l don't know why.
No one's ever believed in me before.
[ Birds chirping ]
[ Coughs ]
Where's Bob?
[ Buzzing ]
[ Neighing ]
SlLAS:
Bob?
l was hopin' you'd sleep through this.
Go on back in the truck.
Let me do this.
SlLAS:
What are you doin' , Bob?
Somethin' l should
have done years ago.
-lt's time to go.
-Bob, don't do it!
Don't do it, Bob!
[ Shots fired ]
Get out of here!
Go on! Git!
[ Neighing ]
COWBOY BOB:
Ah. . .
Go on, Maggie.
Go!
Maggie. . .please. . .go.
Bob. . .
Ah, hell!
Unhitch the trailer.
You take the truck.
lf l stay with you,
l'll just slow you down.
COWBOY BOB:
Go on.
l'm stayin'.
Where will you go, Bob?
Wherever she takes me.
Good luck to you two.
[ Neighing ]
Tiger! Look!
[ Camera clicks ]
CAMlLLE:
We're here!
-Jeez!
-Yeah.
Well, l knew
it would be big, but jeez!
Yeah, it's their truck for sure.
Must have just gotten here
a couple minutes ago.
SHERlFF STElNER:
Okay, l'm on my way.
l don't want anybody shooting
until l get there!
Ten-four.
[ Coughs ]
Got you somethin'.
Thank you, Tiger.
SlLAS: You know,
that's a nasty habit to get into.
Well, it's a good time
for a bad habit.
Besides, l think
the risk of lung cancer
decreases when you
don't have lungs any more.
[ Coughs ]
Come on, Camille.
This is your big trip.
We're here.
So, what do you wanna do?
Let's do what you came here to do.
l didn't really forget everything.
You were lying to me?
l was pretending, Tiger.
lf l pretend to forget
what you said at the truck stop,
then maybe we'd both forget.
At least that's what l thought.
Camille, just because you're dead
doesn't always make you right.
Now, come on.
Let's take this stupid boat ride.
Come on, girl.
[ People chattering ]
[ Horn sounds ]
What?
l'm ready now.
l'll get a picture.
All right?
Silas!
l love you.
[ Camera clicks ]
Excuse me.
Can you take a picture of us?
Thank you.
Camille!
[ Boat engine rumbles ]
SHERlFF STElNER: Like lookin'
for a needle in a damn haystack!
Still don't think he'd cross on foot.
He doesn't look that stupid.
From what l can tell,
he's 1 00% stupid.
That's what makes him smart.
What?
[ People chattering ]
Grrr. . .
-RAYMOND: Silas. . . !
-Raymond.
Raymond! Raymond. . . !
Wait!
Raymond, you don't understand!
-What did you do to her?
-l didn't do anything!
What did you. . .?
She's still alive.
You gotta trust me.
Look, l need her, Ray.
l need her. Okay?
l'm a lawman, but l'm not afraid
to take the law in my own hands.
The real law.
The law of love.
Get going, son.
POLlCE: Clear back!
Make way! Make way!
Wait! Get back!
-You let him take you, you idiot?
-Look, l'll shoot him!
-Then shoot him! He's an idiot!
-l will!
POLlCE:
Get back, get back!
[ Screaming ]
Let's go!
[ Police sirens ]
SlLAS:
Move!
[ Police sirens ]
Silas! Freeze!
Freeze!
Get out of the way!
He's headed for the horseshoe!
Box him in!
Move it! Look out!
MAN:
Watch out!
-WOMAN: He's got a gun!
-BYSTANDER: Who's got a gun?
MAN: The guy in the black jacket.
[ Commotion and police sirens ]
SHERlFF STElNER:
Hold it, Silas! Hold it!
Drop it! You're boxed in!
Hold it!
Give it up!
You've got nowhere to go!
Silas! Drop that gun!
Camille!
Fire a warning shot.
[ Gunshot ]
Camille!
Silas! Drop that gun!
[ Gunshot ]
CAMlLLE:
Tiger. . .
Why did you come back, Tiger?
Why?
You should have left without me.
l couldn't.
l love you.
Tiger. . .
l had a great honeymoon.
Me, too.
Wait! You can't just leave!
[ Commotion ]
[ Sprinkling ]
lt's rice.
it's rice.