www.1000fr.com present
Capture:FRM@FadeOut Sync:FRM@Uranus
Another runner.
Did you get a plate?
Are you kidding me?
Total disrespect.
Don't these idiots get it?
If you're going to roll,
you pay the toll.
Well, if we don't catch them,
the camera will.
WOMAN IN CAR:
Stop, you're hurting me.
(engine roars)
What about your change?
Oh, my God.
What is it?
I'm calling the police.
(indistinct police
radio transmission)
Tollbooth witness
couldn't see the driver.
Said the car was charcoal gray.
What about the passenger?
Nothing,
except she was female.
Female,
no hard ID.
Our mystery girl
did leave us this.
Looks like blood.
CAINE:
"He's going to kill me!"
Think it's a prank?
No such luck, Frank.
* Yeah! *
* We don't get fooled again *
* Don't get fooled again *
* No, no! *
??What did Hemotrace say?
Blood's human.
Dispatch says you wanted
the AV equipment.
Let's check the cameras
in these booths.
They may have something.
If I find something,
where you going to be?
We just found a body,
right down this road.
Powdery substance on her leg.
Could be soil.
Doesn't look like
it's from around here.
Who found the body?
Jet skier.
Taking a break.
Horatio, she was
definitely restrained.
Marks are parallel.
Looks like something rigid.
Maybe from handcuffs.
What about those nails, Alexx?
Broken, worn down.
Could be acrylic.
Wherever she was,
she tried to claw her way out.
(screams)
CAINE:
I.D.
Miss Leslie Anderson.
Pretty girl.
Think she's the one
from the tollbooth?
Could be.
(indistinct police radio
transmission)
WOLFE:
Hi.
This the surveillance video?
Yeah, it was downloaded
from the tollbooth.
Okay, here's
where the car comes in.
WOLFE:
The passenger compartment's
no good at this angle.
You get a plate?
It doesn't make any sense.
The numbers are distorted,
but the car is in focus.
They got a PhotoShield;
people use them to beat
overhead cameras
at traffic lights.
But I can't make out anything.
Well, it's transparent;
it uses a thin diffusion lens.
Light at an oblique angle
causes the cover
to reflect and refract.
It makes it
impossibleo read
unless you're
directly behind it.
DUQUESNE:
So somebody really wanted
this car to be anonymous.
This missing girl's
in a lot of trouble, huh?
Yeah.
You got
another angle?
It's hard to see
the driver
because there's sunlight
reflected off the windshield.
There's something
under the wiper blade.
WOLFE:
It's a valet stub.
Those numbers or that logo could
help us find the neighborhood.
You know what?
Let's see if we can take
a better look at the passenger.
All right, so this is where
she hands the bloody bill
to the witness.
Wait a minute.
Check out her arm.
It's ligature marks.
Oh, yeah, look
at the bruising.
Horatio said
that the victim at the jetty
had the same thing.
(elevator bell dings)
Horatio.
I finished the post
from our vic on the rocks,
Leslie Anderson.
She had a broken frenulum.
So she was suffocated.
I also did
a photo comparison
with the girl from the car
and our vic.
Ligature marks are ckssistent.
The bottom line, Alexx:
they were attacked
by the same predator.
Leslie Anderson was dead
at least two days
before she was discovered.
And our missing girl
is still out there.
Thank you, Alexx.
Hey.
Hi.
It's the trace
from Leslie Anderson's pants.
Yep. Silicon dioxide
and aluminum oxide.
It's clay dust.
No, I get that,
but what's the gray stuff?
It's mortar.
Like from
a clay tile?
Mm-hmm.
75 years ago, mortar was used
without additional fasteners.
Now it's wired
or nailed secured.
So this could be like
from an historical building?
Yeah. Well, this
amount of trace,
the vic had to be around
a lot of clay dust.
Sorry to interrupt, you guys.
Uh, valet stub.
I ID'd the company logo.
Yeah.
You got an address?
Yeah, it's a neighborhood
restaurant in the Gables.
You know who eats there.
People who live
in the neighborhood.
(chuckles)
This restaurant puts us
a block away from a building
that's over 100 years old.
According to the bank records,
this place is in foreclosure.
So what, our suspe
is squatting here?
No rent,
no questions asked.
Looks abandoned to me.
Clay tile.
A trace from our victim.
Frank.
No.
Stop it!
(screaming)
Our murder vic was
definitely here.
(footsteps approach)
Freeze! Don't move!
Hands, mister.
I'll shoot you
where you stand.
You e owner?
Tommy Boyer.
Hook him up.
I'll call Horatio.
I don't know Leslie Anderson.
She was suffocated two days ago
d evidence leads us to you.
My-my fiance, Jill Girrard,
we're supposed
to be married in a week.
She went off with some friends,
never came back.
That still doesn't explain
why you were in the building.
I got desperate.
Jill and I are on the TeleAid
account for the Mercedes.
They gave me the address.
I figured she
got cold feet.
Ran off with
some rich guy.
Didn't have the guts to tell me.
I went inside to take a look.
Her car was there.She wasn't.
That's when you
guys found me.
I-I don't know Leslie Anderson.
I certainly didn't
suffocate her.
Do you have
a photograph of Jill?
Yeah, I do.
I'm also going to need
a personaltem,
like a hairbrush.
Please, help me find her,
Lieutenant.
I'll do that.
TRIPP:
That's one solid safe.
You know, my uncle
was a safecracker.
He taught me
when I was 11.
That's pretty cool.
Hope there's not a body inside.
(clicks)
They're not bodies.
I think they're something worse.
They're trophies.
TRIPP:
Necklace, underwear, glasses?
WOLFE:
This is a picture
of Leslie Anderson.
Let's get this
stuff out of here.
And, Frank, put on some gloves.
These are our only link
to the killer.
Did you process
the fiance's Meedes?
Yeah, nothing.
The onlyhing that we have
to go on for the passenger
in the tollbooth is
the five-dollar bill.
Yeah, well,
the blood on the bill
didn't match
Leslie Anderson
or the DNA from
Jill Girrard's hairbrush.
So there's a chance our mystery
girl could be one of these.
Yeah.
I think these pictures were
taken by somebody they trusted.
Yeah, you're right.
They don't look afraid.
It's like he got them to go
with him willingly somehow.
Hey.
These the photos
from the safe?
Yeah, Ryan found them.
We're processing
the blood from DNA.
We're going to see
if one of these girls kicks out.
Oh, my God.
What?
That-That's Anya.
Who's Anya?
(cell phone beeps)
(spe dialing)
BOA VISTA:
Voicemail.
Anya, it's me,
um, I'm...
I'm worried, so call me.
Will you just keep
hitting "redial"?
I'm gonna go
check something out.
Who's Anya?
Are those the samples
for the DNA bill?
Yeah. They're almost
ready for the 310.
I've got one more
sample for you.
You worked in here, Natalia.
You know
the evidence submissions
are processed in order.
So you can wait
for the next run.
Valera, one of those pictures
is of my sister.
That rates a jump.
Please compare this
against these other samples.
I'm sorry. I...
Just do it now, okay?
* *
(printer running)
Miss Boa Vista?
What's going on?
The girl
in the tollbooth car
is my sister.
We have to find her,
Lieutenant.
We will.
SIKES:
Lieutenant Caine,
who are the women
in these photographs?
As you can see,
some of the women behind me
have yet to be identified.
Where did these photographs
come from?
We recovered the photographs
from a locked safe
during the execution
of a search warrant.
Is that person a suspect?
Is there anyone
in custody?
Lieutenant,
who are these girls?
While I'm not at liberty
to discuss the details
of an ongoing investigation,
I can say that any help
that the public gives us
in identifying these women
will be deeply,
and I mean deeply, appreciated.
Thank you.
(reporters clamoring)
Lieutenant, thank you
for not mentioning my sister.
No problem.
How do you think her photograph
ended up in this gallery?
Ever since
she was a little girl,
she always wanted to be a star.
She loved having
her picture taken.
Okay, when was the last time
you talked to her?
A few days.
Okay.
Take a uniform,
go to her apartment,
and go through it
with a fine-tooth comb.
What am I
looking for?
Anything related
to her last 24 hours.
You're gonna have to
get your soundbites
somewhere else.
Actually, I wanted
to ask you a favor
The answer is "no."
Come on, I heard
you were letting
a documentary film guy
follow you around.
No comment.
I got to get
back to work.
Boa Vista's missing sister?
You're not fooling
me this time.
I've already got it in deep
background that it's her sister.
Ex-husband says she has two.
Is it Christine
or Anya?
You're literally
the worst.
You know that, right?
You can't release that.
You could get
the girl killed.
What do you want to bet
in under 20 minutes,
I'll know which girl?
SASHA:
Natalia?
Is everything okay?
She lives here.
I just got back
from a tryout
for a reality show--
South Beach Babes.
I think I really have
a chance this time.
Where's Anya?
Um, that's why I'm here.
Anya's missing.
When was the last time
you saw her?
Um, yeah, I talked
to her two days ago.
She got a callback
for a modeling shoot.
She's so lucky.
The guy promised
her a cover.
Do you know anything
about this guy?
He was, like,
really old, like 35.
But, I mean, he sounded
nice on the machine.
Okay.
Do you mind
if I take it with me?
Yeah, sure, I give out my
cell number for callbacks.
I'm sure she's fine.
She's very careful.
Okay, look, Sasha,
do me a favor, please.
Don't go on any callbacks
until this is over.
Please.
Okay.
But she's fine.
There's nothing.
Whoever these belong
to was very careful.
Horatio seems to think
the guy's a photographer.
That makes sense.
You think that these
are color copies?
No, take a look.
Oh, yeah, that's pretty grainy.
Rules out digital.
Film is black and white.
(camera clicking)
Why would a photographer
prefer a low-resolution image?
Going for a distinct look.
There's not a lot of places that
develop black and white film.
I'll go make some calls.
To photo shops in Miami,
the model shoot capital
of the world?
(chuckles)
I think you're gonna be making
a lot of phone calls.
Have fun.
(camera shutter clicking)
MAN:
That's it, baby.
Give me sexy.
Perfect.
Hold that look.
All right, I want sexy,
not slutty.
Come on. Give me sexy.
DUQUESNE:
Did you get a name for the black
and white specialist?
Well, Homicide
pointed me towards
this photo developing
place downtown.
All the high-end
photographers use it.
It's owned by
this German guy,
and he says that our man's
name is John Stockman.
Calleigh Duquesne,
ueRyan Wolfe, MDPD.
These girls are all of age.
I've checked every one
of them out, personally.
What about the photographers?
Do you check them out, as well?
Look, what is this?
We're looking for John Stockman.
Shoots in black and white;
thinks he's Ansel Adams.
Thank you.
Give me sensual.
(camera clicking)
All these girls,
they have the wrong dreams.
I don't know
that their dreams are bad,
just the people who promise
to make them come true.
John Stockman?
Yeah, what
do you need?
Your DNA.
Excuse me?
I don't understand
what I'm doing here.
Oh, no,
I think you do.
You took all the photos
of these girls.
I take a lot of photos.
Yeah, but your camera's
a single lens reflex.
That's right.
And you use dual-edge
black and white film.
It gives my work detail.
Hmm.
And the fact that you keep these
in a safe with murder trophies
in an abandoned
building--
is that just a coincidence?
You want to pin that on me?
I hope you have proof.
(cell phone ringing)
This is Wolfe.
Yep.
Your DNA matches
the semen we found
in Leslie Anderson's underwear.
You feeling pinned?
That proves I had sex with her.
It's a photographer's perk.
Where'd this
little hookup occur?
In her dressing room,
after the shoot.
* *
It was sex.
Nothing criminal.
Anyone could've stolen my photos
and put them in that safe.
Well, then I'm gonna need
a list of those "anyones."
Erica Sikes reporting.
Sources say there's
a personal connection
at the Miami-Dade Crime Lab
to the current murder case.
MDPD Criminalist
Natalia Boa Vista,
this morning identified her own
sister's picture
from among the photos
of the missing girls.
That's right.
ghtalia.
One of the missing
and perhaps dead...
There's something
you should know about.
(cell phone rings)
What?
Oh, my God.
It's my sister.
Anya?
ANYA (on phone):
Natalia.
Where are you?
I only have a second.
I'm in a house.
I think it's near the water.
I don't know...
An...
They're going to kill her, Ryan.
Listen, no, listen.
If she called, it means
she's still alive, right?
So focus. What'd you get
from the answering
machine?
Um... nothing.
I got nothing.
I have listened to this
a thousand times.
There's no ambient
sound. Listen.
MALE VOICE (on recorder):
Anya, it's me.
Your pics are ready.
These are the ones, baby.
Call me.
You've got the number.
See?
There's no accent.
I mean, this could be
any guy out there.
Not really.
I think I know that voice.
From where?
The model shoot.
Mr. Laporte,
you placed a call
to Anya Boa Vista.
I did?
You did.
(plays tape)
LAPORTE (on tape):
Anya, it's me.
Your pics are ready.
These are the ones, baby.
Call me. You've got the number.
(laughs):
Right.
Yeah, her. I called her to let
her know her proofs were ready.
Go on.
You should really be
talking to Stockman.
All right, he's the one
doing all the models.
You have quite a history, too,
which includes
a rape charge, doesn't it?
I was acquitted.
Yes,
but that doesn't mean
you're innocent.
Does it?
I'm just a guy
who processed her proofs.
But I can help you, Lieutenant.
I know what goes on
between model and photographer.
Describe it  me.
All about fame.
Hey, and these girls,
they all want it so bad.
So you point a camera at them,
you get them to do
whatever you want.
They'll take their shirts off.
They'll hop into bed
with you. Anything.
That's what you did,
Mr. Laporte. Isn't it?
You prove that, let me know.
I guarantee it.
No, no. That's too much
backlight there.
To the right.
Hey. News chick.
Do you realize
that you signed
my sister's death warrant?
I know you're angry, but I'm
just reporting the facts.
You tied her to law enforcement.
That makes her
a primary target.
DUQUESNE:
Nat.
Do you deny that?
This is exactly what she wants.
Don't give it to her, okay?
I'll meet you inside.
You do understand where I'm
coming from, don't you?
I do. I understand
you have a job to do
just like the rest of us.
Thank you.
I also understand
that your need for attention
may have put these girls'
lives in even more danger.
My need for attention?
Mm-hmm.
You didn't just report the news;
you chose a salacious angle.
That's more
attention for you.
I'm a journalist.
I want my attention
on my stories.
If that were true, sweet pea,
you'd be writing
for a newspaper
not planting your face
on the evening news.
Have a nice day.
(elevator bell dings)
Lieutenant Caine.
Mr. Boyer.
I just got home
and found this in the mail.
It's a letter from Jill.
What does it say?
It says that we're through.
The wedding's off,
that I shouldn't even
bother trying to find her.
Man, this doesn't
sound like her.
After your press conference,
I know something's wrong.
Mr. Boyer, I need you to
leave that letter with me.
You think it'll help?
I know it's gonna help.
So Horatio told me
you're processing the paper.
Why aren't you in QD?
'Cause I got what
I needed in there.
Which was what?
This paper's store-bought.
It's, um... it's untraceable.
But this logo's gonna help us.
See that? It's embossed.
So someone modified
the paper themselves?
The paper passes through
and each time, uh...
the sheet gets pressed.
All right.
Well, again, why
are we in here?
Embossing machines
have many uses.
I noticed there was
a little bit of trace
on the outer edge
of the imprint.
A little trace from
whatever was being embossed
before the paper.
"Trivalent chromium sulfate."
That's used
in the pparation of leather.
That's right; the higher
the concentration
of the tannins,
the higher the quality.
So whatever this business is,
it deals in high-quality
leathers.
I'll call Calleigh.
Good afternoon, officers.
Bill Starr.
Bill Starr's Custom Upholstery.
No snappy catchphrase?
Look around.
I don't need one.
Maybe you can explain to us
why a missing girl
would write a "Dear Jo"
on your letterhead.
I don't know. Busy place.
Hand those out like candy.
What?
We have our own theories.
Can you read
that plate for me?
It's blocked like the car
at the tollbooth.
I got Anya's blood.
She cut herself on purpose
so we could ID her.
MAN:
Pay the toll, bitch.
Who owns that car?
I don't know. Uh, I forget.
The guy dropped it off
for reupholstery.
He didn't leave his name,
only an address.
I t the info inside.
Oh, great. You can give
me the address.
You can give him the car.
Miami-Dade Police.
Who is ever behind that door,
I want you to open it slowly
by the count of three
or I'going
to kick it down. One...
Two... three.
Jill?
Yes.
Jill Girrard.
You're okay now.
Let me help you up.
Jill, we know this is
incredibly difficult,
but is there anything
that you can tell us
about what happened?
I answered an ad
to get my portrait taken.
It was supposed to be
an engagement gift
for my fiance.
Your fiance, Tommy.
The guy left a message
on my answering machine.
Okay, did he leave a name?
No, he just told me to meet him
at his place in the Gables.
Hello?
(gasps)
Do you by any chance
have the answering
machine message or...?
I erased it.
Did his voice
sound familiar?
Just a guy.
All I remember
is being put in a car.
He had something over my head.
So you couldn't identify him.
What about when you
were in the car,
did you hear noise?
Could you notice
anything?
There was another girl.
Was it Anya?
I don't know
what her name was.
She couldn't stop crying;
we drove around
for a bit, made a stop
and then suddenly she was gone.
I figured I was next.
Did he hurt you in any way?
Ma'am. We're gonna get you
to the hospital.
Hang in there.
(indistinct radio dispatch)
WOLFE:
Remember: eyes, no hands.
What is it?
Do you see something?
Yeah, this door
locks on both sides.
If you want to keep
someone in a room,
why would you have it
keyed fromhe inside?
Unless you want to be locked
in here with them.
Sorry. I, uh, I didn't
mean to imply...
No, no, um...
we need to know
what we're dealing with.
(clears throat)
Oh, my God.
Natalia, don't touch that.
Oh. Okay,
but that's Anya's.
I got that for her
last Christmas.
Okay, but you can't collect
evidence in this case.
She was here.
And we just missed her.
Calleigh, honey, Horatio
asked me to check in
on your victim Jill Girrard
at the hospital.
Yeah, how's she doing?
Well, I spoke
to the SART nurse,
and she found
several contusions on Jill
that were consistent
with her account of the attack.
What about the
sexual assault exam?
Get this.
There were no
physical findings.
Really?
In fact,
based on the exam,
she's never even had
sexual intercourse.
That doesn't make sense.
Why would somebody lie
about being raped?
Take a look at this.
She swallowed a key.
HORATIO:
Miami-Dade Police
(coughs)
What about this one?
Anya Boa Vista.
I've never seen her.
You weren't being held captive,
were you?
What are you talking about?
An abdominal x-ray shows
that you swallowed a key,
and my bet is that that key
opens the lock on the boat.
He told me I was special.
Please.
Don't.
I've never done it before.
That I was different
than the rest.
Tell me what happened.
He made me watch.
Please! No!
(grunting)
He called me
his girlfriend.
He made me write
that letter to Tommy.
So Tommy wouldn't try
and find you.
I was so scared.
Told me to go to the boat.
Pick up a necklace.
He let you go to the boat alone?
No.
I was never alone.
He was testing me.
When the cops showed up at
the boat, I had to do something.
I couldn't screw it up.
So you protected him.
He said bad girls
always die the slowest.
What's his name?
I...
I can't. I'm sorry.
Why me?
Why did he spare me?
Just be gratefull that he did.
So, uh, the runaway bride,
Jill, went Stockholm on us.
That poor girl, man,
she's so messed up.
She won't be so poor
after she signs a book deal.
You think she's faking?
I think she's getting her wish.
To be famous?
She'll be living off
of this for years.
You know,
she's really traumatized.
That kind of hell
she went through,
it's not easy to deal with.
Yeah, well,
ask Natalia about that.
All I know, is this girl could
be saving Anya's life
and she's not talking.
Well, you know what?
She's not going to tell us,
maybe this car will.
I got something.
Some kind of rock or mineral.
You mean clay?
No, it's coarse.
Looks like granite.
Killers have a comfort zone
for body dumps.
If that's granite...
There's only
one place: jetty.
It's government cut.
Officers, she's going
to be somewhere
underneath these rocks.
The tide's rising.
Let's pick up our pace.
This quadrant's clear.
Moving to the next section.
Eric, we're running
out of time;
this tide is rising.
H, move to your right.
She's two rocks over.
Two rocks ahead
of you right there.
Yeah, right there.
She's right there.
Ma'am, hang on.
Gentlemen, hurry please.
Ma'am, we're going to get you
out of there right now.
Who did this to you?
Gavin. He's got another girl.
It's got to be Anya.
Where are they?
They're at the studio.
(police siren blaring)
(tires screeching)
What you crying for?
This is it. This
is what you want.
This is your dream, baby.
You're making
it all happen.
Anya.
Get on your knees.
I'll make you a star.
Gavin Laporte.
Miami-Dade Police.
Let her go.
Come on. Let's go.
Let's get out of here.
Move it.
Help! Please
I'm here, Anya.
Here I come.
Let's go.
That's far enough, Gavin.
Now,
put the gun
on the ground
or I blow your brains out.
Do it.
OFFICER:
You're under arrest.
Get him up.
All right,
let's go.
Move it.
You okay, Anya?
Come on.
* *
Are you mad at me?
Yes, I am
so, so, so mad ayou.
Oh, my God. Thank you.
t a problem.
It's okay. It's all right.
Come on.
There are more girls out there,
Gavin, and I'm nna find them.
I've been all over
this country, Lieutenant.
A lot of cities along the way.
Take him.
Miss Boa Vista.
How's Anya doing?
Time will tell.
She's lucky to have you.
Horatio...
did you know that
Laporte lawyered up
and that there's another case
in California?
Different suspect, same MO.
I'm not surprised.
All those women.
They could be anywhere.
Where do we start?
We take it nationwide.
welcome to www.1000fr.com
Tonight's episode was based
in part on a real-life story.
>> Napisy pobrane z http://napisy.org <<
>>>>>>>> nowa wizja napisów <<<<<<<<