Stick him, B, stick him!
Come on, B!
Oh my God!
Oh yeah!
Put him to bed, son.
Put him to bed, B.
There you go, son.
Come on, B.
Put him to bed, B.
Put him to bed.
Yeah, there we go, son.
There we go.
That's it.
# Bet your ass, motherfucker #
# You ain't know? #
# Shit changed, pussy #
# We running this shit now #
# We can't run out here #
# We got pushed a lot #
# But you better get
your motherfucking weight up #
# Pussy #
# Y'all leave the street now,
big mouth, you better take a seat now #
# If you speak foul, you'll get
smacked up with the heat now #
# Keep it discreet
on the concrete now #
# Kick all 100 feet,
catching a beatdown #
# Y'all leave the street now, big mouth,
you better take a seat now #
# If you speak foul, you'll get
smacked up with the heat now #
# Keep it discreet
on the concrete now #
# Kick all 100 feet,
catching a beatdown #
# It all started and really began
with this cold-hearted man #
# Who kept guns knowing
he wasn't nice with the hands #
# And running pistols
was his whole plan #
# He was supposed
to be my fan #
# How can I fuck with fam
who fucks a man? #
# Plus I
couldn't understand #
# How some of these niggas
hopped on his bandwagon #
# Braggin' about
bitches they was baggin' #
# And speaking like a deacon
with a dragon #
# And bringing the agony
to me and my peon #
# Every day bitch-ass shit
is what he be on #
# Nailing fat bitches
and Pathfinders and Neons #
# Trying to be primetime
just like Deon #
# Pulling the sock out,
talking about #
# How he got clout
to rub cops out #
# How niggas pull their Glocks out,
and clean the blocks out #
# Reaching in the sock
and pulling some rocks out #
# And yelling he got into jail
on a serious felony #
# Plus some other shit
he was telling me #
# I ignored him,
laid him to the side #
# Told me, "Come on,
let's take a ride" #
# I had to dip and slide
to the left #
# He was wanted
by the angel of death #
# And I'll be damned if he be the cause
of my last breath #
# My man Proctor says, "This dumbass
nigga should start wearing a vest" #
# Only to test my niggas
in the terrace #
# Who came here
to put his ass to rest #
# Yo, I suggest
he take my best advice #
# Before he speaks once,
he better think twice #
# Ain't it nice
in the terra-dome #
# The streets where the big-mouth cat
no longer moves #
# Y'all leave the street now, big mouth,
you better take a seat now #
# If you speak foul, you'll get
smacked up with the heat now #
# Keep it discreet
on the concrete now #
# Kick all 100 feet,
catching a beatdown. #
Man, you were
fucking awesome, man.
That guy was talking
so much shit,
and you put on
a fucking clinic.
But it looks like
he got you a little bit.
- What's wrong with you, man?
- Easy easy.
Man, what did dad
used to say?
Walk it off.
What'd we clear anyway?
Two Gs for the winner.
Two? Man, it's got to be
more than that.
There is, there is.
Don't shit yourself.
I got to give
Ganz's cut first.
Okay, well,
I'll go with you.
Huh-uh, no way, junior.
Plus I gotta
make a stop.
You didn't.
You did, didn't you?
I told you you should have
put that money on me.
I love the ponies
better than you.
Plus after this
I'm straight.
Yeah, right.
I've heard that before.
It's cool, man.
All right?
Don't worry about it.
You have got to go home
and get some sleep, killa.
And then tomorrow morning we'll get
together and we'll do the split.
Thank you.
Huh-uh.
I love you, man.
Go home.
Are you Brandon?
I'm Detective Harris.
I was the one that spoke to you
about your
brother's case.
These are your brother's
belongings.
Not much for a life,
is it?
What did Dad used to say?
Listen, like I told you,
the guys that did this
were just out on parole
and killed a cab driver
the same night
before we
picked them up.
The D.A. told me
this morning
the state's going to seek
the death penalty.
I'm sorry.
Hey...
I gotta get going.
- Thank you.
- You take care.
We need to talk.
A nice place
you got here.
Sit.
Sure, come in.
Now I know you just
lost your brother,
God rest his soul,
but now we got to
talk business.
When your brother
passed on,
he was carrying a large
amount of my money-
$60,000 to be exact.
Now I know you want to do
the right thing here, Brandon,
so out of the kindness
of my heart
I'm gonna give you a week
for you to get me my money.
There's no way
we took in that much.
You guys cleared
20 grand,
but Frankie was into me
for another 40
from betting on the ponies.
That makes 60
you owe me.
Where the hell am I supposed
to get that kind of money?
Oh, I don't know,
rob a bank, deal drugs,
blow niggers on the corner. I don't give
a shit. Just get me my fucking money.
That's fucking bull-
Let me put it
in focus for you,
you little
piece of shit-
either I get
my fucking money
or you're gonna be another
shit stain on the wall.
Picture that
for a moment.
Got it?
You got a week.
# I didn't really
even know #
# To notice you went out
of your way to find a way #
# Inside someone,
feel better about yourself #
# I didn't care
to know your name #
# But you made it a point
to try to dump mine #
# And then the words slip #
# Try my best
to find a way #
# To will this
bullshit past aside #
# Run through #
# So hey #
# Don't you run away
from me #
# So I can see
your face #
# I can lay a fortune
on the floor #
# Seems like you've found
your place #
# On a torture raid #
# Now you're laying a fortune
on the floor #
# You're bleeding #
# Yeah yeah yeah yeah #
# I didn't think
to realize #
# But I know... #
Hold on!
Can I come in?
Suit yourself.
So how have you been?
All right.
I can get around
a lot better now.
Things would be great
if the government would
stop messing with my
disability checks.
16 years in the service-
I got to beg 'em
for money to eat.
Maybe I can help out
a little bit.
Plan on staying a while?
For a little bit, till I can figure
something out.
Well, it's 500 a month.
Jesus.
Uh...
there'll be no blasphemy
in my house.
I thought I taught
you boys that.
Taught us?
The only thing I remember
you teaching us
is how to take a punch.
Did Frankie have
a nice funeral?
Yeah.
I took a picture
of his headstone.
Would have been nice
to see you there.
You can bunk
in the spare bedroom.
- Thanks.
- Yeah.
Hey hey, that's not
how I taught you.
We say grace.
Father of mercy,
full of grace,
we humbly thank you
for this bounty
we are about to receive.
And please
watch over my son
and lead him not astray.
Amen.
You know, if you're
looking for work,
I have a friend of mine
that's doing some construction
that needs some help.
I'll give him a call.
Am I looking for work?
Well, you're not sitting
around here all day.
That's my job.
Now I told you guys
you gotta wear gloves, didn't I
Didn't I tell you that?
Take them to the foreman
and get them some gloves,
all right? Thank you.
- You must be Brandon.
- Yes, sir.
I've heard a lot about you
from your dad.
I am sorry to hear
about your brother.
Thanks.
You ever stack palettes?
No, not really.
Well, it's real
complicated.
You see those?
You're on cleanup.
Those have to be moved
from there over to there
so they can be loaded up
and hauled off-site.
And you are to wear these
at all times, understand?
At all times.
I don't want any fines in case
the OSHA inspector drops by.
If you can hack it,
I'll take you on full-time.
If you can't, I'll fire
your ass just as quick.
Friend or no friend,
that's my name on the sign.
All right?
Understood.
Okay, well, get to it.
- We're burning daylight.
- Thanks.
Hey.
- I'm Todd.
- Brandon.
First day here?
Yeah, the longest one
of my life.
If you think it's bad now,
you should try living in this hellhole.
You new to town, right?
Does it really
show that much?
A little.
Yeah, my dad moved here,
so I'm staying with him for a bit.
Cool.
Been into town yet?
So that stop sign back there
is your town?
Is that all of it?
Don't let it
fool you, man.
There's some crazy shit
goes on around here after dark.
Oh really?
What, like naked cow tipping?
No, man.
Look, you obviously need someone
to show you the sights, man.
- I'll hook you up.
- Appreciate that, man.
So what do you guys do around here
on a Friday night anyway?
Funny you should ask.
So there is
life after dark around here.
Man, totally.
Who's that?
Oh, that's Erin Dean.
She's, like, perfect.
She's also untouchable.
Bro, there's no chick
untouchable.
Seriously, dude.
Do not pass go.
Do not collect $200, man.
I'm telling you,
she's got this brother
who's like a grade-A
psycho hillbilly, all right?
He's roughed up more than
a few guys who've tried to tap that ass.
Bro, I can handle myself.
I'll be back.
All right, man,
it's your funeral.
Hey there.
- Hi.
- I'm Brandon.
- Erin.
- Nice to meet you.
I'm super fucking drunk.
I can't even see straight.
But then she pulls
the whole, like,
"No no no, it's okay. I'm gonna
take care of you. " And I'm like-
Looks like your sister's
got a new friend.
Haven't seen
that dude before.
Fuck that.
You're not from here,
are you?
How can you tell?
Well, I haven't
seen you here before...
We gotta go. We gotta go.
Hey, Erin.
- Dude, what the fuck?
- We should go now.
I told you about it.
We should go.
- Where are you from?
- I'm from all over.
- Really?
- Yeah.
Hey, kids.
Hey, man.
Um, what the fuck
do you think you're doing?
Victor, come on,
stop it.
Come on, just stop.
- Stay out of this.
- No.
Do you not speak?
- I'm not staying out-
- Oh, you're a funny guy, huh?
- I am pretty fucking funny.
- No no.
Erin, go home.
- Go the fuck home.
- Whoa whoa, get your hands off her.
- Get the fuck out of here.
- Get your hands off her.
That's my fucking sister.
Who the fuck are you?
If anybody's going home,
it's your bitch ass, motherfucker.
What the fuck are you doing?
I don't need your fucking help.
Doves don't mate with crows,
motherfucker.
Go back where you came from.
Some skinny kid brought you
home last night around 1:00,
said you were in a fight
and got beat up.
I hope that other guy
looks worse than you.
Other guy? What other guy?
I don't even know who hit me.
I was just talking
to this girl,
and next thing you know,
I'm waking up here.
Whatever you're into, I don't want you
bringing it back to my doorstep.
I already told you
it was a party.
"He who seeks trouble
always finds it"-
Proverbs, chapter one.
Yeah, thanks.
That helps.
Well, you'd be good
to think about it.
Just what I need-
a fucking bible lesson.
I thought you'd be taking a week off
after that beating you took.
Man, hell no.
My old man won't let you
lay around the house.
I want to thank you though
for getting me home last night.
No problem, man.
You looked pretty jacked up.
I was afraid you were dead or something.
How did you know where my
old man's place was anyway?
I checked your wallet.
I was looking for number
or something
and found a piece of paper
with an address on it.
So I just took a chance
and cruised you out there.
Appreciate it.
Yeah, no sweat, man.
Oh, and I sneaked a 20
out of your wallet for gas.
You little bastard.
Just stay busy
today, man,
'cause I heard Garret's
was a bad mood
after losing a wad of cash
at the fights Saturday.
Fights?
What fights?
Underground.
We've got a fight club
scene here.
Are you fucking
kidding me?
Like real fights?
Money fights?
Nah, we just sit around
and trade chickens.
Yeah, real money fights, man.
We're not that hillbilly.
Well, some of us are.
Man, I want in.
Oh yeah?
You like to gamble?
Not really.
I'd rather fight.
What?
Bro, you didn't do so good
the other night, remember?
You want to climb in the ring
with those guys? They'll smear you.
That one dude
that stomped you-
that's Victor, man.
He's the top dog.
Man, that wasn't
a fucking fight.
Come on.
I'm gonna fight his little ass.
You'd better believe that.
Man, if you're crazy enough
to get in the ring,
you'll get your chance.
Just make sure
your insurance is paid up.
Man, whatever.
Just set it up.
All right.
There's some fairgrounds
about five miles from here
on the other side
of the highway.
Meet me there
tomorrow night.
And don't embarrass me
by getting your ass kicked again, okay?
Let's go, man.
I want to get some bets in
before I go.
Look at this.
This is nice.
All right, come on.
The wet T-shirt contest
is on!
All right, it's time
to get wet.
Wet it.
They set up
all sort of fights-
different weight divisions,
everything.
I've seen guys
come in here with 50 bucks
and leave
with five grand.
Look who it is.
I'm going to grab a beer.
You want anything?
Yeah yeah.
Just be back quick, man.
The next fight's in five.
Oh yeah.
What a wet t-shirt.
Oh, wet it up,
wet it up.
Look at you.
Go, girl.
Whoa.
Brandon.
Oh my God,
I'm so sorry.
I was so worried about you.
Are you okay?
How is your head?
Yeah, I'm okay.
I'm so sorry.
I don't even know how to apologize
for something like that.
Don't worry about that.
It's not your fault.
You do owe me though.
- Do I?
- Yes, you do.
And what do I owe you?
A chance to get
to know you better,
maybe a dinner
and a movie.
I need a beer.
That one's for you.
Thank you.
Cheers.
Hello hello.
$50 on Victor.
How are you doing today?
I'm very well.
I'll be better
after Victor wins.
You got it, right?
Am I on the board?
- Yeah.
- Cool.
So I thought I'd come home
for a while,
you know, to get
my head together.
And then you met me.
And then I met you.
That's the part
of the story that I like.
Yeah, me too.
So I gotta get going.
Excuse me, do you have a pen?
What? Where are you going?
They fights haven't even started.
Yeah, I know.
I'm late for my shift
at work.
I was just stopping by
to drop of my brother.
His car's in the shop.
Don't worry.
He's in the ring.
Yeah, that's him.
You don't want
to watch the fight?
Nope.
Yeah, but anyway,
call me.
Yeah, that's for sure.
You can count on that.
Good.
All right,
so I'll see you later.
Do me a favor,
stay away from him.
He's not right
in the head.
And call me.
Questions?
Touch him up, touch him down.
Now back up.
Ready?
Fight.
# My life #
# This rage #
# Made to crawl
through broken glass #
# A prisoner of
a jaded past #
# A helping hand
out of reach #
# Forget what they tell you,
forget what they preach #
# Oh yeah, this rage,
my life... #
That's it.
Yes! Yes!
That's Jason.
He's the guy that bottled you.
Yeah.
Yes! You're the man!
You are the man!
Yeah! Whoo!
Love it!
This looks like
it could be good.
Holy shit.
That's Drake Colby.
Who?
Drake Colby.
He's a fucking legend, bro.
He dropped out of sight
years ago.
Dude, bet it all.
Bet it all on Drake Colby,
seriously.
Go.
All right, guys, they came to watch
you fight, not the referee.
You know the rules.
Any questions?
All right, touch him up,
touch him down.
Step back.
You ready?
Fight!
# Let's end this life #
# With a bloody
knife fight #
# Let's end this life #
# With a bloody
knife fight... #
We're set.
#... I got my blade,
switchblade switchblade #
# I got my blade,
# Let's end this life #
# With a bloody
knife fight #
# Let's end this life #
# With a bloody
knife fight #
# Let's end this life #
# With a bloody
knife fight #
# Let's end this life #
# With a bloody
knife fight... #
That's it.
#... Let's end this life. #
Brandon, bro.
Dude, I've got your cash.
Okay, I'll catch up
with you later.
Uh, yeah, man.
Hey, where's the money?
- For fuck's sake.
- Come on.
Hey hey, keep calm, all right?
Don't do anything stupid.
Prize money.
Come on.
Hey!
Nice.
So I take it
you're a fighter then.
Yeah. Man, I used to
watch you on TV all the time.
You're a goddamned legend.
I don't know about legend.
That was a long time ago.
Oh, not to me, bro.
You're Drake Colby.
Hey hey, keep it down.
Keep it down, all right?
I'm trying to keep
a low profile around here.
All right, listen,
I think I owe you a beer.
- Want a beer?
- Yeah, sure.
Come on, man.
Asshole!
- Let's go.
- Okay.
Here.
How bad is it?
It ain't good.
Either I hit too hard
or these hands are too soft.
Either way I'm not having
these fights I've got booked.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
I really needed
that money.
Maybe we can
help each other out.
Really?
How?
What if you put me in
as a replacement?
We'll split the winnings
down the middle, 50/50.
You're a confident
little bastard, aren't you?
Well, you know, fair enough.
I like your style.
Um, all right.
These guys might be hicks,
but they know how to fight.
Yeah, let me worry
about that.
Okay okay, tough guy.
No problem.
But we're gonna need $5000
to get the ball rolling.
That's the buy-in.
I have a few thousand
stashed.
Okay, well, as I said,
we need $5000.
We're going to need
$3000 more.
I was hoping for
the "knockout of the night"
but I smashed
my hand up.
I had to settle
for the submission.
So you don't have any
to kick in?
I haven't got two pennies
to rub together, seriously.
I don't live here because
I'm an eccentric millionaire.
Yeah, I wanted to ask you
about that.
What are you doing
living out here
in the middle
of fucking nowhere?
Fucking hell, man.
What's with all the questions?
We've just met. What, are you a fucking
policeman or something?
So how are we gonna get
the rest of the cash?
I'll have to work
on that.
All right, you do that.
And when you've got it,
come and see me.
We can talk
some more then.
So where are you gonna
get that $3000?
I don't know.
I know my old man
doesn't have it.
He wouldn't lend it to me
if he did.
What about you?
I just paid my phone bill.
I'm skint.
Man, you're a tightass.
That's only like 100 bucks.
No, bro, I just ran up
a $1000 phone sex bill.
I'm paying my mom back
right now, so I can't.
Oh, you're one of those guys.
I'm glad you find it funny.
Yeah yeah, laugh it up.
Did you have a full
bottle of lotion?
Fuck you, man.
Come on.
Wow.
You're serious?
I think I know where
you can get the money.
Where is that?
Him.
- Garret?
- Yeah.
He was at the fights,
wasn't he?
He likes to gamble.
- Yeah, but I don't know.
- But what, man?
Come on, it's not like
he's gonna turn us in or something.
Let's just-
let's ask him.
I'll ask him.
All right.
You think he'll really
go for that?
You think you can
make him some money?
$3000? No. No way.
Garret,
this could be huge.
Have you ever
seen him fight?
Well...
Yeah, that's what
I thought.
Look, I'm willing to put down
a couple hundred,
but $3000- no.
Listen, if I lose your money,
I'll work for free.
What do I get
for my money?
50% of my cut.
Does your daddy know
about this?
No, and he shouldn't either.
You know what I mean?
All right.
I'll tell you
what I'll to do.
I know a couple
of local guys.
I'll set that fight up
for here,
Friday after work.
If you win,
the money's yours.
If not, you're gonna
be shoveling
a lot of dirt
this summer.
- Deal?
- Sounds like a deal.
Hey, what's up, Drake?
- Hey.
- How's the hand?
Eh, feels like it's full
of broken glass, to be honest.
What are you doing
chopping wood?
That's a good question.
I think it must help me
forget my financial
problems.
Talking of which,
did you get
the rest of the money?
Not exactly.
I have somebody who's
willing to put it up.
So what's the problem?
He wants
to see me fight.
And how are we gonna
do that?
It's already set up
for this Friday.
Sweet.
I'll be there.
Did you get into
another fight?
No.
You gotta go to work
tomorrow.
I don't want you
to get fired.
Eat your dinner
and get some sleep.
I can't.
I gotta make a phone call.
Stop pushing me.
What's her name?
What are you talking about?
A man only misses dinner
for one reason.
Hi, Erin.
It's Brandon.
I told you I'd call.
This is amazing.
Yeah, it is.
Yeah, I sometimes come
over here after work
just to get away.
It helps me forget.
About what?
Life, things, people,
my stepfather.
What about your mother?
She passed away
a couple of years ago.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
She was sick
for a really long time
and in the end it was
almost like a blessing, you know?
Was it cancer?
Yeah.
Yeah, my mom too.
Wow.
So do you have any
brothers or sister?
Uh...
yeah, I had a brother.
What happened?
He was murdered.
Oh my God, Brandon,
I'm really sorry.
This is a romantic
conversation?
Well, it's like my dad
would say, you know,
God gives you
what you can handle.
I don't know.
Maybe there's a lesson
to be learned
in all this.
I just haven't
found it yet.
You have something
on your-
What was that for?
'Cause I think
you're kind of beautiful.
Beautiful?
Yeah,
like a sensitive,
beautiful soul.
Wow, that's a first.
Thank you.
Don't worry.
I won't tell anyone.
That's our
little secret.
Yeah.
I guess it is.
You're beautiful
as well.
# Hearing your words
out of my mouth again #
# Leaves me stuck
with the key to #
# All these reasons
you got in my head again #
# Buried here
inside of me #
# Return #
# All of this to sender #
# The mirror spoke to me
and showed #
# All of this pretending #
# Is catching up to me #
# Lights out, wake up,
stay calm, decide #
# Reach up, stand
or be an eyesore #
# Lights out, wake up,
stay calm, decide #
# Reach up, stand
or be an eyesore. #
Aw fuck.
Dude, I think too late
to run, bro.
Shut up.
I'm gonna enjoy this.
All right,
let's get to it.
You want time
to warm up?
I don't need time to warm up
to drop this punk.
Okay, the first man down
is out.
Ready?
Fight!
I got this today.
What?
The detective that was
handling Frankie's case.
It's Frankie's
death certificate.
Ashes to ashes,
dust to dust.
It's almost as if
God ordained Frankie-
Bullshit.
Fucking bullshit.
Don't you dare.
God?
What does God have
to do with anything?
If He was in charge...
why did He let Frankie
get killed that way?
He put you
in that chair?
And Mom?
Why did He let her
get cancer?
Huh?
Tell me.
Answer me.
You can't, can you?
Can you?
All you can do
is give me
those bullshit
religious sayings...
so you don't have to
feel anything...
really talk to me.
I am talking to you.
You just don't want to hear
what I have to say.
That's not fair.
Fair?
Life's not fair.
Frankie's dead,
and no amount of talking
is gonna bring him back.
So you might as well
get used to it.
You fucking bastard.
You're right.
I am a fucking bastard.
So what are you gonna
do about it?
Are you gonna come over
and hit me?
Come on, you've been
waiting your whole life.
I'm in a chair.
Come on and hit me.
I'm not going anywhere.
Come over here
and hit me.
I'm in this chair.
Now's your chance.
So hit me.
I'm nothing
fucking like you-
nothing.
I'm never gonna be
like you.
I'm not that little boy
anymore.
Can I ask you
something?
Yeah, what's up?
You ever thought
about just leaving,
just packing
your bags
and just go,
just leave?
Like every day
of my life.
So why haven't you?
I don't know.
Come on.
It's-
I'm scared.
- Scared?
- Yeah.
You?
You're like the most confident person
I've ever met.
It's very scary.
Besides,
where would I go?
What would I do?
Anything you wanted to.
Do me a favor,
close your eyes.
Trust me.
They're closed.
Pretend that you can
go anywhere,
do anything.
Where would you go?
What would you do?
I'm right where
I want to be.
You know what's funny?
When I was a kid
I used to have
the map of the world
above my bed.
And when I was
really upset,
I would just point
at various places-
close my eyes
and just point.
And I promised myself
that I would go
visit those places.
And now I'm older
and I'm still here
in this small little town
and I've never visited
those places.
But, you know,
the funny thing is
you actually got out.
You made a decision
and you just went,
you followed a dream.
I really admire that.
You make it sound
romantic.
It is.
Isn't it?
My dad- he's a real
son of a bitch.
He used to make
me and brother fight
in the backyard
every day.
He would come home
and drink a beer
and watch us
beat the shit
out of each other.
And one day
we just decided-
Why fight each other?
Why fight for free?
So we just left.
What else is going on
in that head of yours?
I don't know.
I just can't help
thinking
that I should have
been there for him.
I should have been
there for Frankie.
What could you have done?
I don't know,
just been there.
I wake up
and just think,
"Why the hell
didn't I go with him?"
I should have fucking
went with him.
And then maybe that would
have been you too.
Yeah.
But it haunts me.
I hear him
calling my name
just like
when we were kids.
And I'm not there.
Understand, I loved
my brother Frankie.
We used to watch out
for each other,
especially around
the old man.
Have you forgiven him?
I just-
I'm not afraid of him
anymore.
So what are you gonna do?
Are you gonna stay here?
Would you stay here
for me?
Hey, what's up?
Yeah, I understand.
Saturday?
Okay.
All right, yeah.
Okay, all right.
For sure. Bye.
Drake set it up
for Saturday.
Sweet.
Good.
Now I can get
some sleep.
What?
Garret, man- that guy has been
calling me every night
wanting to know
when it's gonna happen.
Dude, he hit me up
like three times today.
He's freaking crazy.
Stop for a minute.
What?
This boy
Erin's seeing-
do you know anything
about him?
Yeah.
He's-
he's new in town.
He works for Garret.
He's a fighter?
I guess so.
Could you
deal with him?
I already have once.
In the ring, smartass.
Yeah.
Why?
The word's up
somebody's trying
to book him
some big
money fights.
I was thinking of bringing
some of my friends in.
But before I do,
I want to make sure
you can take this guy.
Set it up.
This is it?
What the fuck
were you expecting?
It's a private bout.
Come on.
This should be interesting.
Howdy, fellas.
- How's it going?
- Good.
This your man?
Yeah, this is Brandon.
That's my boy Lonnie
over there.
You'll be fighting him.
$5000 buy-in.
Winner takes all.
- Here's ours.
- I'll hold the money.
- I don't think so.
That ain't
very neighborly.
Sorry.
Alrighty.
But don't be getting any ideas
about skipping without paying,
'cause we wouldn't
like that.
You understand
what I'm saying, boy?
You just have
yours ready, okay?
All right.
Let's do this.
- What do you know about this guy?
- Not too much.
I have seen him
fight before.
He's sloppy,
but he can hit.
You should keep your hands up, okay?
Come on.
Bring your man out.
You boys shake hands.
- Come on, B.
- On me.
Fight!
# Now you're gonna wake #
# Up to the bleeding #
# Get down, yeah #
# Get down, there's a wildfire
in the streets #
# Now you cannot fake #
# What you are feeding #
# Get down, yeah #
# Get down, there's a wildfire
in the streets #
# Now you're gonna wake #
# Up to the bleeding #
# Get down, yeah #
# Get down, there's a wildfire
in the streets #
# Now you cannot fake #
# What you are feeding #
# Get down, yeah #
# Get down, there's a wildfire
in the streets. #
Oh, shit.
I lost my
motherfucking money.
All right, you and Todd
get ready to leave.
I'm going to get
our money.
Your boy's good, but-
Our money?
Your choice.
Take it.
It's a pleasure
doing business with you.
Let's get the fuck
out of here.
So this is what
$10,000 looks like?
This is
fucking awesome.
Well, listen, this is
just the beginning, boys.
Our next fight's
a 10-grand buy-in.
- But I got a question.
- What's that, Todd?
When do I get some?
I want in.
I mean, I discovered him.
This fucking guy. How would you like
to discover this?
I'm serious.
Listen, fighting's all
about getting paid, yeah?
These fights today-
these private fights
with fucking pig farmers-
that's bullshit, man.
You want to fight in real fights-
proper fights
with proper prize money
and betting money.
That's how you make money
in fighting.
- So when do we get some?
- I've already put the word out.
When Brandon wins his next one,
we can book an open fight.
I'm telling you, that's when we're all
gonna get paid.
Hell yeah. That's what
I'm talking about.
- Cheers.
- All right.
Are you crazy?
What the hell are you doing, man?
Where's your punk friend
of my sister's?
Huh?
How would I know?
Dude, I'm gonna ask you
one more time nicely.
I told you-
I don't know.
See, that's not asking
very nice, all right?
- Are you stupid?
- Come on, guys,
I don't have anything to do
with your beef with Brandon.
Shut up.
Shut up!
Tell your friend to stay the fuck away
from my sister.
You understand?
- You understand?
- Yeah.
You make sure
he gets the message.
You got that?
Do you, like,
clean your tools ever?
Can you hand me
a socket wrench?
Is this it?
What is this?
Does this look like
a socket wrench?
I don't know what that is.
Look here-
socket, wrench.
It's a socket wrench.
How about I just sock you
with this-
this giant hammer?
I thought you were sweet
when I met you.
You want to make me
a sandwich instead?
- A sandwich?
- Do you want to make me a sandwich?
Yeah, I'm gonna give you
a sandwich, honey.
Oh, I will give you a sandwich,
you know I will.
Hey.
- Hey, what's up?
- How's it going?
I can book you
another fight,
but it's tomorrow.
- Are you up for it?
- Yeah, man, set it up.
Are you sure?
Are you sure you can fit it in
between your little
palettes there?
- Yeah, book it.
- Yeah, all right then.
I'll pick you up
at noon.
Get your ass
back to work.
Hey, Garret, boss,
I need a word with you.
- What is it?
- I need some time off.
- You're not sick, are you?
- No no, nothing like that.
Drake booked another fight.
It's tomorrow.
Oh, good. Of course.
Of course.
Take the week off-
protecting my investment.
I appreciate that.
Hey, tell Todd
I hope he's feeling better.
- What do you mean?
- You haven't heard?
That Victor kid
kicked the crap out of him.
His mom said he worked
him over really good.
When the fuck
was this?
Yesterday, I guess.
I thought you knew.
No.
Thank you.
Todd honey,
one of your friends
is here to see you.
Hey man, what's up?
Not much, bro.
But I don't think Victor
likes you very much-
just the sense
I'm getting.
Man, don't sweat him.
It was him and Jason.
You shouldn't be thinking
about that stuff right now.
Are you all right?
Do you need anything?
Just don't tell anybody
I still live with my mom,
okay, please?
You got it, bro.
So when's
your next fight?
It's tomorrow.
I'll be there.
Are you gonna be all right
to come?
Yeah, man, don't worry.
Just get ready.
Kick some ass,
all right?
Appreciate it.
You get better, okay?
Eh, my ribs, man.
- Are you gonna be okay?
- I'll be all right.
- Hey, Connor.
- Hey, Price.
I hope this isn't
your fighter.
No. This is Brandon.
Kyle.
- All right.
- Let's get going.
These boys came all the way
down here from Dallas.
Okay, 10 large.
Right.
Let's get it on.
Now I know nothing
about this guy.
Take him out quick.
Ready?
Fight!
That's it.
Hey, you look good, man.
You look really good.
Interested in coming up to Dallas,
doing some fighting?
I can make you
some good money, man.
Hey hey, he's already got
a partner, Price.
I hear ya.
No harm in asking.
- All right.
- Nice fight.
Thank you very much.
I'll be talking to ya.
See you, Price.
Oh, it's so nice
not having to go to work.
I could do this
every day.
You'd get bored.
No, I wouldn't.
You would, honestly.
I do this
nearly every day.
You'd get bored.
A man needs a reason
to get up in the morning.
So is that why
you stopped fighting
and moved out
to this bumfuck town?
I didn't stop fighting.
And I certainly didn't move here.
I had no choice.
What do you mean?
Well, believe it or not,
I'm in the witness
protection program.
Are you serious?
Seriously. Seriously.
I'm glad you think it's funny.
Well, the story goes,
I was being backed by some
wise guys out of Jersey,
doing well, making money.
Then one day they came to me,
they said, "We want you
to throw a fight. "
I said no.
One thing led to another.
It ended up with me
smashing the guy's head in.
When the guy died,
the Feds came to me,
offered me a deal.
They said if I testified,
they'd set me up with
a new life somewhere.
Yeah, this is somewhere all right.
Anyway, I fight once in a while.
It stops me
going out of my mind
and gives me
a bit of spare cash.
So what, the Feds
don't give you any money?
Shit.
Fucking hell, man.
No, the fucking
assholes-
they literally give me
just enough to survive.
That's why
I took your deal.
One minute, sweetheart.
I'll be right back.
Well...
it's good.
We are on.
And the money?
Open book.
Who knows?
Could go
as high as $50,000.
But there is one thing.
Yeah, what's that?
You're fighting Victor.
Do you really
have to do this?
Yeah.
I don't want
any part of it.
Forget about that shit.
Focus on the job at hand.
Come on.
Cool, man?
Of course he's cool.
I don't know how you're not nervous.
I'm freaking out.
Will you
shut the fuck up?
You shouldn't even
be here.
Hey, man, I'm Kent.
I spoke with you on the phone.
- How's it going?
- Good good.
- This is pretty exciting, huh?
- Yeah.
Every high roller
in the county must be here.
- It is quite the event.
- Your boy ready?
He's always ready.
Good good.
You know, I was thinking-
Cut the shit, Kent.
Let's get this thing started.
All right.
Let's do it.
We need to get the bets in.
Bullshit. I'll cover anybody
lays off on Victor.
All right, boys,
let's have a good show.
Fight.
# Feel better
about yourself #
# I didn't care
to know your name #
# But you made it a point
to try to dump mine #
# And then the words slip #
# Try my best
to find a way #
# To will this bullshit
past aside... #
Boy, you got nothing!
# So hey #
# Don't you run away
from me #
# So I can see
your face #
# So I can lay a fortune
on the floor #
# Seems like you've found
your place #
# On a torture raid #
# Now you're laying a fortune
on the floor #
# You're bleeding #
# Yeah yeah yeah yeah #
# I didn't think
to realize #
# But I know if I'm wrong,
ways to figure out #
# What could have been
and what's just wrong #
# And I hate to be
the one #
# To fucking throw it
in your face #
# To put you
in your place #
# To show you
the other way #
# Try my best
to find a way #
# To will this
bullshit past aside #
# Run through #
# So hey, don't you run away
from me. #
Oh!
Did you see that?
- Told ya.
- You got him, B.
What's the matter? Get up!
You got him.
Man, good job.
That's the way, man.
Well done.
Can I come in?
Please.
So you're
a tough guy, huh?
Can I come in?
Are you okay?
I'm sorry.
I wouldn't hurt you.
Are you expecting
somebody?
No.
Can I talk to my sister
for a minute?
It's okay.
I had this whole
speech planned.
You know,
when Mom passed away,
you were all I had, so-
- Victor, I don't-
- No, wait wait.
Just-
what I'm trying
to say is
that I-
I know that I haven't been
the best brother,
but it wasn't
for lack of trying.
You know, Dad split...
and Mom passed away.
And we got stuck
with Rod.
And...
you were
my responsibility,
you know?
I'm not your
responsibility anymore.
I know that.
That's what
I came here to say.
I know you're not
a little girl anymore.
And...
you- you grew up
to be this really
beautiful woman.
And you deserve better.
And I'm gonna have to
learn to let you go.
And it's not
gonna be easy,
but I'm gonna try.
I'm gonna try, okay?
Thank you.
He's not such a bad guy.
I know.
He's not.
I'm gonna go.
Are you okay?
Yeah, it was
my mom's ring.
I didn't know
he had it.
I'm gonna be leaving.
I want you to come
with me.
Of course.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
"Dear Dad,
you always told Frankie and me
that a man is measured
by the strength
of his enemies.
But you're wrong.
A man is measured by the strength
of the love others have for him.
I hope one day you and I
can put away the pain
and actually talk
to each other.
Love,
your son Brandon. "
You're not gonna fucking
believe this shit.
Oh, the prodigal son
returns.
You got a lot of balls
coming in here, kid.
But then again, I take it
you got me something.
Not exactly.
Exactly what then?
A business proposal.
Unless this conversation
starts and ends with me
getting my fucking money,
you ain't walking
out of here.
Just hear me out.
Sit.
What if I told you
I can get your money back,
plus a whole lot more?
I'm listening.
Okay, here's the deal...
Give me a call when you're ready
to make some money.
You don't really think this fucking
mug's gonna lie down, do you?
Why not?
He's as greedy
as his brother Frankie was.
But just in case,
follow him.
And another thing-
call around, see if
anybody heard anything.
If not,
book the fight.
When this is over,
I want to go as far away
as possible.
Yeah? Where would
you want to go?
Anywhere,
as long as it's sunny
and there's water
and there's
really nice beaches.
We can always take a ride
up the West Coast.
Yeah?
That would be
amazing.
Hey.
All right, good.
The day after tomorrow.
All right, kid,
you know what
you gotta do out there.
And just so you don't
do anything stupid,
we've decided to get
a little bit of insurance.
Don't fuck it up.
All bets are closed.
All are closed.
All right,
are you ready?
Are you ready?
On my mark.
Fight!
# Hearing your words
out of my mouth again #
# Leaves me stuck
with the key to #
# All these reasons
you got in my head again #
# Buried here
inside of me #
# Return #
# All of this to sender #
# The mirror spoke to me
and showed #
# All of this pretending #
# Is catching up to me #
# Lights out, wake up- #
# -Or be an eyesore #
# Lights out, wake up,
stay calm, decide #
# Reach up, stand
or be an eyesore. #
Sweetheart,
you know how to pick 'em,
don't you?
That kid just chose
his ego
over your life.
Can you believe that?
I just can't
figure out why...
this fuck hole would choose
to get his goddamn neck slit
to keep a fucking win streak!
Can you tell me?
Can you fucking tell me?
Can anybody fucking tell me?
Give it to Jimmy.
Pay 'em their
fucking winnings.
I had this little
black dog
when I was a kid.
We tried like hell
to train that mutt,
but it was so stupid.
Maybe it was retarded.
They got retarded dogs?
I don't know.
I tried
to teach this little
nigger dog
for hours,
but he just
didn't get it.
Finally,
you know what that
little fucker did?
He bit me.
You know what happened
to that little dog?
My father
shot it
right in
the fucking head.
But you know what I remember
also about that day?
My father
was still not
satisfied.
So I'm not going to
kill you.
I don't think
I'm going to get
the emotional closure
I need out of that.
Instead I'm going to fuck
pointy tits over here
right in the mouth
while you watch.
And then I'm going
to have Carlo
shoot you
in the fucking head.
And then maybe,
just maybe,
I might get
some satisfaction
knowing that you'll go
to the great beyond
wondering if
I'm gonna keep her
or kill her.
That depends on
how good she is.
Fucking step over here now!
Nice doing business
with you boys.
Thank you very much.
- Take care of yourself, kid.
- You too.
Love to do it again
sometime.
See you around.
Cutting it a little close
back there, don't you think?
That's because dipshit got us lost
on the way over.
Hey, come on.
All right, man, don't hang
around here too long.
Take it easy.
You take care.
Hey, if you're ever
in town-
You got it.
Can I drive?
You're lucky
you're not walking.
That's a lot of money
you got there.
Yeah.
Are you really gonna
do this?
Yeah,
I think so.
Are you scared?
Not as long as
I have you.
# This is our time #
# This is our moment #
# After everything #
# That we have been through #
# This is my chance #
# To pull you in closer #
# We'll have it all #
# Yeah #
# Yeah, this is our time #
# This is our time #
# This is our moment #
# After everything #
# That we have been through #
# This is my chance #
# To pull you in closer #
# We'll have it all #
# Yeah #
# Yeah, this is our time. #