Baby...
It's okay. It's okay.
Don't be frightened.
I'll take very good care of you.
I'm going to take very good care of you.
Excuse me?
- Can I help you?|- I want your database.
Look, I don't know what you think|you're gonna find here, we're just "a..."
I wasn't asking.
All right.
- Looks like we've got a problem.|- What?
Michael, hostiles converging|from the south quadrant.
Listen, "please..."
Michael, go!
I need a location on Nikita.
She's just behind you, Michael.|Getting an elevation reading.
Nikita's location.
She's on the ground, Michael.
Sixteen meters south-southeast. You're|going to have to make a ground approach.
right in front of you, Michael.
Michael, do you have her?
Michael?
Michael, report.
Michael, can you hear me?
Michael?
Housekeeping found this.
It's a thermo-block.
We knew that Bright Star had the|technology to block our IR and RF scans.
But not this.
This is why we couldn't see them|until they left the back room.
What's the status on Nikita?
Nikita's implant went dark a few minutes|after we lost visual on her.
Last known location?
Two blocks from where she fell.
She's off the board.
Quinn's isolated another Bright Star|substation in Rouman.
And since they mirror their database|information across their network...
we'll assemble a storm team...
and attempt to acquire|the personnel database we lost.
It is essential we obtain this information|within the next 72 hours.
There will be severe repercussions|if we can't.
Nikita has the disk.
Your mission is now listed|as aborted, Michael.
We consider database information|you acquired on premises unobtainable.
We've had no contact with her|for six hours.
Per procedure,|she'll be listed as killed in action.
I don't think you're being fair, Mother.
I made you dinner and there's a nice,|hot bath waiting for you.
You're alive.
Where am I?
Well, you know,|you wouldn't be if it wasn't for me.
Alive, that is.
It wasn't easy getting that bullet|out of you.
Thank you.
Mother always said|if you're going to be good at anything...
you'd better resolve yourself to practice.
Who are you?
Your doctor.
You smell a lot nicer|than most of my patients.
Do you think you could|take these handcuffs off me?
I like that.
The patient telling the doctor what to do.
I'll make those decisions,|if it's all right with you.
I appreciate everything|you've done for me.
I will take very good care of you.
You're very safe here.
What's your name?
Henry...
Paul Collins.
What's yours?
Nikita.
That is a very pretty name.
Do you want to know a secret?
Besides my mother...
you're the first girl I have ever...
been able to talk to.
No one as smart and pretty like you.
Where's Michael?
He's in his office.
- Was he informed about the briefing?|- Yes, sir.
This briefing will be rescheduled|one half hour from now.
You're aware of the procedure, Michael.
Did you expect|we'd make an exception for Nikita?
No.
Then you know you have a job to do|and you're expected to do it.
If you have to grieve,|do it on your own time.
You owe me 15 days.
For helping your friend.
Yes, I did promise you that.
I'd like to take them now.
All right, Michael.
You do what you've got to do.
But you're on your own.
If I find out you employed...
any Section resources...
put a drain on our manpower...
I will act accordingly.
I understand.
You know what I wished for?
What did you wish for, Henry?
Nothing.
Absolutely nothing.
I finally think I've got everything|I always wanted, right here.
You care about me?
You're very special, Nikita.
Haven't I proven that to you|by saving your life?
But I don't understand...
why you're keeping me down here.
Why the handcuffs?
You don't want me to feel like|a prisoner, do you?
You're not nearly well enough to get out|of bed and start running around.
You'll catch your death.
I'd take your advice, Henry.
Even if you took the handcuffs off, "I..."
If you said that I should stay in bed,|I would stay in bed.
Then it really doesn't matter|that much, does it?
You know, Mother baked this cake herself.
I think she's getting rather jealous|that I brought the rest of it down here.
She thinks I spend too much time|down here.
Does she know about me?|She know I'm down here?
Truth is...
I think she's getting|a little too attached to me.
I suppose it's better than not being loved.
She sounds like she's really very nice,|your mother.
I'd love to meet her.
I'm sure you would.
You see, I knew you were smart.
Henry, I need something to drink.
Some water.
Mother...
One of these days|she's gonna push me too far.
Be a good girl and drink your milk.
Nut case.
Thank you, Henry.
Hi.
Forgive me for being rude.
I forgot to say goodnight.
Mother said you might need this.
Oh, hi.
Can I help you?
Hi.
You feeling better, Nikita?
If you're going to recycle a sim|or check redundancies...
you've got to clear your subnet mask|and make sure your gateways line up.
You're just saying that to get me excited,|aren't you?
Your loins must be a sad|and primitive place, Mr Crawford.
They're just lacking for company,|is all, darling.
And tact, apparently.
Tact is for the boardroom,|not the bedroom.
Or in your case, just bored in the bedroom.
You're too good for me, darling.
Smarter...
faster with the one-liners...
and I'll bet that moat around your thighs...
has kept most every human male|standing at the drawbridge...
trying to figure out why he ever wanted|to cross it in the first place.
I need a DMV trace.
No can do, Michael, you know the drill.
Trust me, pal. Been there, done that.|Forget it.
You know the iceberg|that sunk the "Titanic?" It's an amateur.
What do you need?
No good deed goes unpunished.
She's always trying to pound that into me.
And I always resisted.
Seems mother knows best.
Nikita, you and I are friends now.
And...
we should treat each other...
like friends.
You really do need your milk.
You are so beautiful, Nikita.
So very beautiful.
Won't mother be happy|when she learns of our surprise?
I spliced off Quinn's network bus...
and stuck a null terminal on the line.
She won't even know we were here.
That's good there.
I can enlarge and enhance.
That's good.
Now all we gotta do is run this puppy|through the DMV database.
That means Quinn.
Half an hour.
I'll do my best.
I try a little harder.
Dear God.
It's going to be small,|but that doesn't mean we can't do it right.
I think it really does something|for the room, don't you?
Henry...
come here.
Sit down.
I'm very excited about all this.
Haven't you forgotten something?
Forgotten something?
Well, I've got the decorations, the cake...
and we're both here.
No.
No, I "don't..."
I don't think I left anything out.
You never asked me|how I felt about all of this.
I saved your life, Nikita.
I've taken excellent care of you.|I can't think of any reason why...
Then you don't know anything|about women, do you, Henry?
Even if a girl's going to say yes...
she likes to be asked.
If I ask, you promise you'll say yes?
That's cheating.
Nikita, will you marry me?
Henry, look at me.
Look at me!
Come back here and sit down.
You promised.
Henry, take the handcuffs off.
You know I can't do that.
If you cared about "me..."
Oh, Nikita, please.
You're like a broken record.|"If you care about "me..."
If I unlock those handcuffs,|you're going to try and run for the road.
Henry, I'm sorry.
You're right.
That was before|you asked me to marry you.
It's different now.
What's so different now?
When I'm all tied up like this...
I can't even touch you.
Henry...
I want to know what you feel like.
You sound like a whore, Nikita.
I would never marry a whore!
You utilized Section facilities|and manpower...
to assist in an off-profile operation.
I thought Michael worked here.
You know very well what I mean.
All right.
So I helped the guy out some.
It took ten minutes.
You're not going to climb out of your skirt|about that, are you?
Why did you do it?
The guy's okay.
Doesn't talk much...
but he plays straight. I like that.
Besides...
all he's doing is trying to help someone|he cares about.
I don't really see the harm in that.
And despite the rules...
you believe it all comes down|to how you see it.
I get the point.
So what now?
You gonna cut my head off?
No.
I'm actually quite pleased|with your progress.
It seems the more time you spend with us,|the more like your brother you become.
You're doing quite well, Jason.
Quite well.
Mr Collins?
That's right.
I'm here to read your meter.
- My meter?|- Right.
This is really a bad time.
I'd have to clear a path for you.|Maybe you could come back next week.
I'm sorry.
According to our records,|you're already overdue.
- Lf you could just give me a couple days...|- I wish I could.
Rules.
Beautiful day.
What...
What are you doing down there?
Mrs Collins...
can you help me, please?
Talk about bad timing.
Henry pleaded with him to come back|next week, but he wouldn't have it.
Anyway, it'll be nice|to have another guest, huh?
I'd say you were, what? Autumn.
Earthy. Rosy.
Henry's so excited about all of this.
You've made him happier|than I've seen him in years.
I believe that a boy inevitably|reaches a certain age...
when his mother's attentions|just aren't enough anymore.
It's funny, you know, because you keep...
tending to think of them as babies...
and then one day...
you open your eyes|and you realize that they're all grown up.
And that your hugs and kisses|are not what they're looking for.
Sad, isn't it?
There are people looking for me,|Mrs Collins.
Very dangerous people.
Who won't hesitate to hurt your son.
See, you have to understand about Henry.
His father died just after he was born.
And I've tried to be both|a mother and a father to him.
I expect that you'll do|everything in your power...
to make him happy.
Mrs Collins...
if you keep me here, you and Henry...
will be in jeopardy.
Oh, look at you! You've got butterflies!
I remember I had such a case of|the humpy-jumpies before my wedding.
It's perfectly normal, you know.
You are going to be just fine.
Got it.
I ran satellite surveillance|on the four likelies I told you about.
And lookie here.
That's the same truck you were looking at|on those security tapes.
You have an address?
I got more than an address. Look at this.
Thought maybe I could pick up|some faces for you.
Couldn't get much more than the top|of the head of this little guy over here.
But the gas man...
just as he looks up...
here...
I ran an ident scan on the guy.
His name's Craig Burrell.
We have him listed in our database|as a third-level operative for Bright Star.
He never left the house.
Could be we stumbled|on a Bright Star substation.
Thought you might want to know.
Thank you.
Hey, any time.
As soon as they got wind|that I was helping you out...
old Mata Hari with the shape to die for...
she was all over me|with the compliments.
I think she likes it|when I take my own initiative.
You really think she's still alive?
Yes.
You think or you want to think?
You know you've got enough|to go to Operations on this.
You've got a location,|you've ID'd a Bright Star operative.
If she is in that house|and she's still alive...
he might reconsider.
He won't.
You don't know what you're walking into.
If this is a Bright Star operation...
you might find a very large|welcoming committee.
I'll get her out.
Henry...
You look just like your father.
You look beautiful.
Dearly beloved...
we've gathered here today to witness|the bonding of these two young people...
in holy matrimony.
Do you have the rings?
One at a time, Henry.
Yours first.
Do you, Henry Paul Collins,|take this woman, Nikita...
to be your lawfully wedded wife?
In sickness and in health...
for richer or poorer...
forsaking all others...
until death do you part?
I do.
You can't do this.
Where's the disk?
I don't know what you're talking about.
Where is it?
You should've had backup.
You had no way of knowing|I was going to be alive.
What if this had been|a Bright Star substation?
You wouldn't have made it out of here.
If you weren't alive,|it wouldn't have mattered.
Been here a couple of weeks now, Jason...
and already you're checking|anomalies in the inventory.
What can I tell you?|They don't have cable. Gotta keep busy.
So what do you say, Walter?
I got a couple of Beretta 92F's,|a Glock 9 millimeter...
a MAC-10, all unaccounted for.
They seemed to go missing|around the time Michael showed up.
You know, maybe you should check|your figures one more time.
Four times.
All right, be that way.
I guess you're the kind of guy who just|doesn't like to get a pat on the back.
Don't make sense to me.
What do you mean by that?
You and me, pal.
We seem to be the only two in this place|who want to help that guy.
That really seems to impress the brass.
- Impress them?|- Hell, yeah.
I thought I was gonna get a promotion|on the spot.
I'll put in a good word for you.
Don't.
All right.
Have it your way.
I like you, Walter.
I really do.
You're my kind of people.
Excuse me.
I don't think you should press|those buttons while you're walking.
I'm just finishing the download now.
It's the entire Bright Star database|from Nikita's disk.
It's complete.
Do you have a location|and an ETA on Michael and Nikita?
No, sir, the download was sent|automatically, on a timer.
I had only one voice contact from Michael,|giving me the channel and frequency.
Well, where the hell are they?
There was a message on the file header.
It seemed cryptic to me. Code, maybe.
All it said was:
"It took me four days to find Nikita.
"That leaves eleven."
Does that make sense to you?