ENGLISH SUBS: =DS= 2011
[ enjoy another crappy vamps flick, Peter! ]
Hyung-kyu Kim, Da-in Lee
Ho-young Son, Ye-won Han
There is no such way
to go back to yesterday.
But my only hope for now is
to turn back to the past,
Even though I have to stay
in the hell.
For those who can easily smell the weak,
we were always their food.
Can't you do it better?
One, two.
Three, four.
Hey, hey, do you think
we're gonna be okay?
Sink or swim!
How long should I lick his ass?
Are u gonna take a hidden camera film
of girls for him forever?
Written and Directed by
Hong-ick Kim
- One, two.
- Three. Four.
The gangster!
There, stop!
Ah! Jesus!
Be careful, you're gonna get hurt.
Ah, my bone, my bone!
Ah, sorry, ok, ok, I will hit above.
Ok, ok, it will finish soon.
It's done, go.
I feel like dying on every step.
Hey, did he go? huh?
Look around quickly.
Did he go? answer me!
Move!
Hey!
My first love, Mia Hong.
I met her again after 10 years
at the school
but it seems that she must
have forgotten all about me.
Would you like some?
No, thanks.
Try some.
Hey, hey, are you seriously
thinking of her everyday?
Don't take it wrong I'm taking a film
for the school film festival.
Yeah Right.
She is so wild like a tomboy
I don't think
she is attractive at all.
Are you kidding? You said
you had a bath together
when you were young.
How can you not speak to her a word?
She doesn't even remember that.
And that was not a bath,
it was just playing in the water!
Idiot!
Can I have a chocolate milk,
dried squid, 3 pizza bread and...
no, no, that one please.
Just go and tell her that she had a bath
with you so she should take you!!
What!?
Dan,
What.
Dan, I'm short of 1,300 won.
Why aren't you coming
if you know that well?
What are you doing?
Are you done? You stalker!
Hey, shut up!
Have you finished taking a film?
Mia, what's wrong? Are you okay?
Sorry, I will talk to you later.
Look at this, this is so great.
Wow, you look gorgeous like a model.
Is it okay for the students
to access the hotel?
Huh! Even though you are staying
with my father because of his money,
don't you think this is too much?
Don't you have any common sense?
Common sense?
I've been taking care
of a living corpse for 3 years until now.
Can you even imagine how that is?
What? Then just leave him!
What the hell are you making
my father miserable?
Well, I think I have to finish
what I've already started.
Don't you want to let
your father go in the peace?
What the... are you crazy? huh?
What the hell are you doing?
Devils like you... go to hell!
Hey, lady! Are you alright?
Hey.
You look so drunk.
Do you need some help?
You're lucky today.
Because it's not easy to meet
the gentlemen like us.
Shut her mouth.
We're just helping you.
Dan, are you still in the bed?
Get up!!
Ah!
Are you crazy?
Get up!!
We are late!
Hey, run!
Please, open the gate.
Please, sir.
Dan, Dan, What's wrong?
Ma'am, what's wrong with me?
Have you got bitten by a dog?
What?
It seems that you're infected
with rabies.
What?
High fever, nausea...
and photophobia.
No...It can't be rabies in these days.
In your age, it's more like...
the symptoms when you guys do
'that' too much! Take it easy!
Take it off.
Ah... I like when these are tight.
Ah! Ah!
I couldn't get pizza bread today...
do you think we're gonna be alright?
Hey, what's wrong?
Here we go!
Look, how beautifully these
six coins are going across the desk.
Check the line.
Cheol-seung,
here I brought your snacks...
shush!
See? It's an art give it to me.
Hey, Mia He seems so strange.
Look, look, he keeps looking at me.
Before I saw him taking me
a film with a little camera.
I'm so hot! Don't you think?
Oh, hey Mia, oh my good! Oh, my god!
I think he is having a drug or something!
You know, some strange drugs!!
What's wrong?
Dan.
Pizza bread?
Uh... that was sold out so I bought
something else instead of that...
What? Something else?
Are you insane?
How patheic fuck off.
Yo, what's wrong with her?
It's not your business.
Yo, Mia! Are you having a period?
Eun-seok!
Do you really wanna fight with me?
I'm sorry!
Cheol-seung... I am so sorry...
Funny? huh?
Do you think this is funny?
Huh? Funny?
What the fuck is so funny?
Huh? What the fuck is so funny?
You retarded!!
Stop it! Cheol-seung!
What now?
He already apologized to you!
Who the hell do you think you are!
You know... These kids like this...
Did you mind?
See? He likes this.
He likes when I pat him like this.
Do you think this is also funny?
ok, laugh, laugh, moron!
Cheol-seung!
What the fuck is this...
Do you wanna see
what it's like? you bitch?
You guys know this final test
is so important!
So, prepare for it I will watch
you guyshey! you!! Come here!
Fuck off!! you morons!
Stink!
Are you happy now?
Are you a fucking gay?
Ah... I think I'm having a...
Are you now getting a help from a girl?
Do you even have a penis?
Relax, guys! Well... Sir?
Yes?
Ah, Good afternoon, sir.
Ah Cheol-seung,
how is the senator?
Ah, my dad is so busy nowadays
to take care of things
Ah, I see.
And he mentioned that he wanted
to meet you for the fund raising
So, he will contact you
sometime soon.
Really?
Yes, sir I will talk to you soon.
Oh... Ok.
Relax! Guys?
You son of bitch.
You moron, do you think of me funny?
Guys? Am I your friend?
How do you feel? Good?
Lick it.
I will make this a good film
and make you famous!
Bingo!
Hey, look at me!
Smile! I will make you famous!
Look at this moron crying.
How pathetic...
Uh, what is this?
Hey, check this!
The asshole!
Huh, that was not bad.
Hey, Park! What are you doing?
Are you a psycho!
I don't understand a single word
you are talking about.
Hey, Mia! He took a film of something
very interesting about you.
Are you going out with a sugar daddy?
What the hell did you do at the hotel?
This stalker took everything here.
What the hell are you talking about?
Man, fuck you!
Fuck You?
Ya, Fuck You!
What the fuck!
Give it to me.
Take it if you can.
Look at your face,
where is your confidence?
It's not worth to
speak a word to you.
I see, then we can check
this out right here.
Cheol-seung Park!
Mia!
Dan, are you okay? You rock!
Let's go for lunch!
I'm so sorry.
For what?
Was it funny?
Tell me, was it funny?
If it's that funny,
why don't we watch together?
I don't know what is in there,
but if that is that funny,
Watch with me!
Mia, I've never expected
this would happen.
You didn't know this would happen?
Then what did you expect?
Such a stalker.
What?
If I knew you became this kind of freak,
I wouldn't be so happy
When we had the same class.
Do you have any reason to live?
Do you have anyone
that you can make happy?
If you don't, just kill yourself
I'm so sorry, sorry
They suffer as much as
they wish to die and then
they will die within 3 or 4 days.
Just kill yourself!
There are not many people who have
courage to save other people 's lives.
But today,
one high school student showed us
a beautiful courage
to save the blind lady.
There is a disabled woman standing
on the platform.
And one suspicious looking man
is approaching her
and pushed her into
the rail for no reason.
It was very dangerous situation.
This high school student is the hero who
saved the blind woman out of the rail.
Today, a miracle happened
when the high school student
saved the blind lady out of the rail.
We have to applaud him loudly
for having the courage to save
others in this kind of world.
Nowadays, up to the bottom, everyone
is just only thinking of themselves
When every politician
and businessman is corrupted,
this kind of person is a real hero.
Mia, pick up the phone!
Dan became a star!
He is a hero! Call me back!
Today, a high school student jumped
into the rail and saved a blind woman.
According to the witnesses,
when the train was
approaching to the platform,
a mental patient, Mr Choi pushed the victim
And immediately
one high school student jumped into
the rail and saved the victim
in dangerous situation.
This student had a severe injury however
he just left the scene as soon
as he saved the blind woman.
And in this panic situation he was
so naive to look for his subway pass.
These images of him on the internet
made him so famous to be a real hero.
I really wanted to tell him this...
When I had a really difficult situation
I sometimes wanted to kill myself..
But now I will try to live.
Even though when it's difficult
I will try to be strong.
He is the real hero! You rock!
My hero!! Thank you!
Hero! Thank you so much!!
Dan, it's too late,
what are you doing there?
I'm washing my laundry to help you!
Just finish quickly and go to bed!
You have to get up early tomorrow!
Yes!
Dan!
Don't you know
what you've done wrong?
If you ever try to kill yourself again,
I will kill you.
She is the new trainee teacher
of the school Behave yourselves.
Hello, everyone.
I am Yuri Lee, a student teacher
to teach Korean language for 2 weeks.
Nice to meet you all.
Hello, sir.
Hey, look at me.
I'm going to study very hard for you.
So hot.
You!
What!
Hey, where are you going?
Where are you going?
Who are you?
Haven't you forgotten me already?
What?
Hmm, I look better than this picture.
What are you doing?
Do you remember me?
What the hell are you?
Me? Blood drinking species.
In history,
they call us a vampire you know?
Do you think lwill believe that?
It's up to you
whether you believe or not.
See? You couldn't eat anything.
When you eat something
you want to throw up and
when you go outside in the sun,
you feel like burning.
And when you are around
with girls you are going crazy.
And when you smell the blood,
your heart beats so fast.
It's your choice But you have to
realize this is the real situation.
Poor thing, you must have been starving.
Let's go to eat something.
Come on.
She is too short to have anything.
Why don't you pick the menu?
What?
Okay, today's menu is the type A blood
which is full of mineral.
1 00 dollors!
Sorry, I'm so sorry.
No, it's ok Don't worry about this.
Ah... this is the taste...
Follow me!
You must be not that hungry.
Please donate blood.
Please.
I don't have enough blood
to feed myself!
Hi, please donate blood.
We are short of blood.
I think I have type B blood
but I think my blood is getting hotter,
is this ok to donate?
No problem!
Come on!
Oh, no!
Hey, let him go!
You let him go!
He wanted to donate blood!
He is short of blood!
We are short of blood too!
What the hell are you doing!
Oh, my god!
- Hey!
Hey, wake up!
Just lie down and take some rest.
You shouldn't move now.
Are you crazy to donate your blood?
If people receive your blood
they will become like you.
Why did you come back?
Why not!? I came back
to eat your blood again!
I couldn't leave you like that.
Because anyway you sincerely
worried about me at that time.
Even though you will hate me
forever for making you a vampire.
What's done is done.
Don't hesitate.
You are no longer a human being.
But is this ok?
Isn't the sun, the cross and the
garlics are really fatal to vampires?
That's bullshit. Except for the sun
that we are a little sensitive about.
I am originally a devout Christian.
And garlics are also fine
because Korean loves garlics anyway.
And how long have you been a vampire?
Are you a reporter or something?
Who put me in this kind of situation!
I have to know something to
prepare the life of the vampire.
Okay, okay, relax.
Well, It's been less than
1 50 years I think.
Because that's when there
was western invasion in 1 866.
Wow, you don't look that old.
Good for you.
I know, I take care of
myself all the time.
What...
Why were vampires in
Korea at that time?
How did they come here?
Vampires have existed
since the history begun.
They were completely
hidden from others.
Some vampires escaped from
the West and came to Korea.
And the Christians in Korea had
missions to execute the vampires.
But when the unjust persecution of
the Christian was started by the government,
the vampires took the government
side and massacred the Christians.
At that time I became a vampire.
Then isn't there anyway to extinguish
the vampires?
Are they immortal?
Before my scar quickly disappeared...
Why? Don't you like it?
Don't you want to live forever?
Do you really like this?
Well, that's up to how you think.
It's not that you cannot die.
You don't have die if you don't want to
Be optimistic!
No, thanks.
I just wondered how the life
of the vampire hunter would be.