FULL FRONTAL
Subtitles ripped by ~FilVe~ ©2003
CALVIN: Gus Delario--
the invisible man is Gus.
He's one of those guys...
who you feel like
you know them really well...
but when
you think about it...
you don't really know them
at all. you know what I mean?
And. you know. obviously...
you look at his track record
of all the movies he's done--
He's been very successful.
Almost every actor in town...
wants to work in. you know.
one of Gus's movies.
FRANCESCA: I've done
some mean things in my life.
Yeah. And sometimes.
the--ahem. ahem--
the worst part is
is that sometimes...
it doesn't bother me.
I just say. well.
yeah. this is mean.
I wanted to be mean.
and I was mean.
Period.
LEE: Well. I have to be
somewhat judgmental...
because of what I do.
you know...
so I don't think
that it's such a bad thing...
to be judgmental.
I think that's
how you get through life.
You have to assess things...
and people do it
about you all the time...
and that's life.
and it's too bad.
CARL: I think there is
no amount of money...
I could have been paid--
there is no deal
that I could have made...
that she would not have felt
that I had been too passive...
and that--I think that...
her opinion of me
on that level...
was formed before
the movie was ever sold.
I think it has nothing to do
with the movie. frankly.
ARTHUR: It's frightening.
It's monstrous.
It's evil
to not have feelings.
So I spoke to Carl about it.
and we discussed it...
and we went immediately...
to the most monstrous
character...
we could think of in history--
you know. Hitler himself.
LINDA: Yeah. they're always
trying to set me up...
Lee and Carl. They--
Well. they never have
introduced me to anyone...
but they always talk about
how I should be dating.
But they're
trying to set me up now...
with this producer friend
of theirs--a guy named Gus.
Uh... we'll see.
I don 't think...
a film producer's going to go
for me. but I don 't know.
(Piano music playing)
-Catherine?
-Nicholas.
Yes.
-How are you?
-l'm good. How are you?
Excellent. Thank you.
Thank you for having me.
-Sure.
-Mind if we get started?
So, I play his partner.
An equal partner?
No, l'm his flunky...
if that's what you want to hear.
Is that what you want to write?
Is that what
you want me to write?
No.
No, you can write sidekick.
That's fine.
See, the thing is,
l've done a lot of TV.
He's an established star,
a big star.
I figure it doesn't make me
any less talented.
So, no,
I don't have a problem with it.
Look, if l'm going to make
the leap to the big screen...
I expect to work for it.
Don't that make sense?
Don't you think
most black actors...
expect to have to work
to make that leap?
It doesn't seem to happen
as often with white actors.
-Jesus.
-Don't you find that the case?
A couple of movies...
1 5, 20 million dollar paychecks,
magazine covers.
OK, is this the kind of story
you want to write?
We can go there.
Trust me, l've got plenty
of opinions on the subject.
(Heavy breathing)
Jesus.
(Shower running)
LEE: Carl.
I've reached the point...
where I can't continue
in this marriage.
I'm writing because
I can't take any more...
emotional confrontations
about it.
I'm out of ideas.
and I want to make a change.
When I get home tonight.
we can discuss...
the practical issues
of how to separate.
Please don 't call me.
I'm sorry.
Fifth robbery in two weeks
at a pornographic bookstore.
CARL: Oh.
LEE:
They say it's a woman.
Jesus.
Did you have
bad dreams last night?
LEE: No.
Well, I did.
Well, I had a weird dream.
I dreamt that my job...
was that every day
I would go into work...
and narrate a documentary
about some guy's life...
and go home from work
and have dinner...
and go to bed and go back
to work in the morning.
It's like
I have no effect on anyone.
So. what's on for today?
More bloodshed.
God.
How do you stand it?
(Sighs) Hey, listen, don't
forget to make the brownies...
for Gus tonight, OK?
Right.
Bye.
ARTHUR: Nobody I know...
is in any kind
of long-term relationship...
with anybody they've met
on the internet...
but the short-term stuff
have been pretty exciting.
I don't know what
I'm gonna do when I meet her.
She thinks I'm twenty-two
years old. and I'm not.
I'm not a painter.
although I'd like to paint.
So. it could be anything.
I mean. the imagination
could take you anywhere.
I find that
really. really exciting.
And it's one of those places
where I can lie.
LINDA: I'm happy with
meeting men on the computer...
on the internet.
in the chat rooms.
And. you know.
people disappoint...
and these people
don 't so much. so...
I really connected
with somebody.
So--and he's a painter...
and. you know. gosh...
five years from now. I'd like
to be living there with him.
I've told him
I'm a massage therapist...
and I didn't lie.
Um...
I lied a little about my age--
just a little--
because he's so young.
(Laughs) So. I just knocked
a few years off of that.
CAL VIN: She said.
No. baby. you're bored...
but why are you
taking that out on us?
(Chuckles)
It was that kind of thing.
It just--you know,
everything clicked...
for me.
(Click)
Oh. Sorry.
You transcribe those yourself?
Someone at work.
-Like an intern?
-Mm-hmm.
Male or female?
What do you think?
Male.
(Laughs)
Yeah. So, which is it?
And don't tell me
you're not gonna say.
Male.
-Ah.
-Mm-hmm.
Do you want to know
if he's straight?
Oh, no, I know he's straight.
(Cell phone ringing)
Oh, shit.
Yeah, l'm coming, l'm coming.
(Ring ring)
Wait. Wait. I--
Django, go, go, go, go, go.
(Ring ring)
(Beep beep)
Hey, Frank!
CARL: I'll tell you--
I'll tell you what it's like.
OK. you know.
I work at this magazine.
This magazine is great.
It's very good.
It has very high standards.
I think.
I think they can do
really good work.
But I think the guy
who runs the thing...
is just not very smart.
I mean. you know.
this is between us...
but I just don 't think
he's very smart.
I think his instincts
are all wrong...
and I think
he's. you know. the big butt.
LEE: Yeah. you know.
I've lost my temper in traffic.
I have. I've lost my temper.
I wouldn't call it road rage...
but I have gotten pissed
driving...
because people. you know...
they drive cars
that are ridiculous--
you know. wrong for them.
(Car door opens)
(Car beeping)
I don 't really like my job.
I've thought about
doing something else.
I like the money.
I don't even
like that that much.
I could get a betterjob.
LINDA: Lee is ambitious
and smart and beautiful...
and she always has been
all of those things...
and she's always done
really well. you know?
So. maybe she is
completely in control.
(Razor buzzing)
-Hey.
-Coffee.
-Herr director.
-How are you?
-What's up, man?
Rehearsing something
for ten days sucks.
And I know how tough it's been.
Oh. no. no. no.
Listen. Iisten...
I think I know
where you're going. man.
First of all,
I got to apologize.
I know l've been
all over the map...
and that's my process,
and l've kind of been crazy.
Listen, I really feel bad
about what I said...
to your friend.
I know he's Jewish...
and I went way too far
with that whole oven thing.
But believe me,
I was going over...
some of my anger management
stuff last night...
and I really feel like
I had another breakthrough.
That's great. That's great.
But I just--oh, I felt so bad.
You know what,
Carl and I wrote this for you.
You are our Hitler.
Don't you ever forget that, OK?
That means a lot,
but I know this is...
your and Carl's vision--
I mean, you wrote this.
But, yeah, it's funny,
I was talking to Tom Sizemore...
and he was saying the only way
to learn how to act is to act.
-Right. Yes.
-And I know you're concerned...
because I haven't really
memorized anything...
and l've been
all over the place...
but believe me, on the day--
well, you know, tonight--
yeah, I really think
it's gonna be salty.
You're gonna be OK.
I just want to make sure
you're all right.
-l'm good.
-OK. All right.
-See you later.
-Oh, hey. Um...
I don't take cream,
could you--just, black?
-Sure.
-Thanks, pal.
All right.
* Bad boys. bad boys.
what you gonna do? *
* What you gonna do
when they come for you? *
LINDA:
Well. no. not married.
This guy that I was seeing...
This guy Tom that I was seeing
last year at this time...
said when he broke up with me.
he said he was...
getting back together
with an ex-girlfriend...
but I don 't know
if that's true or not.
I heard he's--
I heard it's not true.
But that's what he said
at the time.
-Hey!
-Hey, how are you?
-l'm OK, how are you?
-Good, good.
It's funny.
Yeah, what are the odds, right?
Well, uh, have a good day.
See you.
LINDA: I like Carl.
Uh, have you ever been
in therapy?
(Chuckles) Who?
No. I don't even get that.
I don't even get that.
It's like...
they're just selling you
back to yourself.
What is that?
Hmm.
I never thought of it that way.
-Mm-hmm.
-Um...
your appetite
is certainly worth noting.
-l'm hungry.
-Mm-hmm.
Oh, don't tell me
you're one of those--
-You don't eat?
-Oh, no, I eat.
I just don't eat airplane food.
Why not? It's first class.
They cook the shit
on the premises.
What's the problem?
I'll wait for the cookies.
Man, how corrupt
was your father?
And milk.
Did he kill people?
He killed their spirits.
Did he threaten
their identities?
Something like that.
So, what about you?
He, um...
No, no, that's all right.
Sorry.
-No.
-OK.
No, he didn't.
He--he adored me, actually.
-Adored?
-Mm-hmm.
Wow.
I don't think
l've ever been adored.
CARL: You can get paid
to have sex by a company--
I mean.
acting in an adult film--
but if some guy pays you
five hundred bucks...
to have sex with him.
that's illegal.
So. you're in porn.
Why are you in porn?
Two reasons.
Either you need the money.
or you're an exhibitionist.
WOMAN: What do you think
is exhibitionism?
CARL: Porn.
What--well. no. OK.
That's a good question.
I think it goes way beyond
just wanting to perform.
You can't pretend that you're
having sex with someone...
when you are actually
having sex with them.
Well, I think
it's easier to think...
that they're
enjoying themselves.
Or maybe they want you
to enjoy yourselves.
Why would you want
to think about it so much?
It's been made to turn you on.
It's nothing deeper than that.
Yes, I do.
Sorry. I thought you said
this didn't bother you.
Carl, I can't have
conversations like this anymore.
(Chuckles) You can't?
I've met someone.
-Oh.
-lt's not appropriate anymore.
-Oh, I understand.
-Sorry.
Don't be--sorry? Hey, you are
showing absolute respect...
by being honest with me and not
being weird or, you know...
protracted about it.
Thank you.
I just--hey, I like to know
where I stand.
Otherwise,
I feel like an asshole.
(Laughs)
Are you all right?
Yep.
Yeah, I was just thinking
of the rest of my day.
Jerry wants to meet with me.
-Really?
-Yes.
He's never liked me,
you know, from day one.
Just--nothing I can do
about that. I just, uh--
I'm sure you'll do just fine.
LEE: You are aware
of the recent layoffs. correct?
MAN: Well. yes.
LEE: We're making some changes.
rearranging our priorities...
getting things straight.
that sort of thing.
(T akes polaroid)
Mmm. Are you a smoker, Brian?
I participate
when it's available.
-Are you a smoker?
-No, but I smoke.
Have you ever been caught
driving under the influence?
Under the influence of what?
DUl--
you're familiar with the term.
Yeah.
-Correct?
-Yeah.
No. I mean,
what does this have to do with--
Do you vote
democrat or republican?
Neither. Either.
I--I vote for the best person.
-And how do you judge that?
-Uh...
-Do you know in an instant?
-Yes.
Right.
Hmm.
(Laughs)
(Woman crying)
(Man taps table)
(Sniffles)
Oh, come on, kitten--
the water works?
You know,
we've talked about this.
Nothing's changed...
since the last time
we had this discussion.
(Sniffles)
No, l'm just--
l'm too committed to my work...
to sustain a serious
relationship right now.
You know, I bring work
home with me. I'm distracted.
I'm taking a swim in Lake Me,
you know?
And, you--hey, you deserve
better, believe you me.
I would only cause you pain.
Remember how I let you
twirl my key chain?
Nice, right?
Hugging, kissing, all nice.
Now, go on, sweetie.
Go on, split. Come on, come on.
I'll call you.
If the phone doesn't ring,
it's probably me.
(Sighing) Oh, man.
(Pager beeping)
Fucking Goebbels--
he thinks it's a toy.
(Chuckling)
Gone to get haircut.
What an asshole.
LINDA: I don't know why.
I just started that.
I don't--I just don't want
them knowing me. you know?
I don't want them knowing me.
I give--I give the name Ann
all the time...
because it seems like Ann is--
One.
And it's less invasive.
It's less--
or more anonymous. you know?
More invisible.
If they know me as Ann...
they don't know who really
is in the room with them.
And for some reason.
that feels good to me.
CAL VIN: Nicholas.
I will begin simply.
l love you.
Have always loved you...
and will always love you.
Ever since the moment
I met you...
the love I feel for you
is overwhelming.
When we are apart,
you are all I think about...
and can't wait until...
we are just even
in the same room again.
Until then.
I've been away a lot.
(Placing note in envelope)
Ahem.
-Hi.
-Hey, Mike?
-Yes?
-Can I ask you a question?
-Yes.
-lt's kind of personal.
-Shoot.
Is that your real hair?
Absolutely.
Hmm. I'm thinking of
getting some more.
Don't do that.
-Why not?
-You'll have doll head.
I don't care. I want more hair.
Low-level, free-floating
anxiety about it, you know?
I have anxiety about it.
I see homeless guys
with a full head of hair...
and I think, What the fuck?
You know, Kirk Douglas,
what the fuck--
Does Lee mind?
Uh, she says no.
Well, that's a lie.
She doesn't say anything,
and I assume that's a no.
We sit in the same room,
we live in the same house...
but, uh...
-And.
-What?
Try changing your buts
to ands. See what happens.
We live in the same house,
and--
Now you got it.
Yes, I would say that.
-How often?
-Um...
Once a week, once a month,
once a year, once--
-This is kind of--
-l'll come back to that.
(Laughs) God.
Do you believe in him?
Well, you know,
not like a bearded guy--
It's a yes or no question,
David.
Yes, then.
Listen, l'm sorry,
I just thought--
I'm going to be straight
with you, David, OK?
OK.
In three years,
you haven't impressed...
a single person at this agency.
You'll be notified officially
through the mail.
-l'll watch for it.
-OK.
Do you have a girlfriend?
-What?
-Are you involved?
Are you--are you--
What--what are you doing?
Put that chair
against the door.
-Ms. Bright?
-Yeah.
Is this a joke?
'Cause I'm a good sport.
This is a test of skill
of sorts.
I like you, David.
I'll tell you that right now.
-OK.
-OK?
Yeah.
On one leg--balanced.
(Laughs)
You--you are a piece of work,
do you know that?
-OK.
-Good!
-All righty.
-OK.
Now. name all the countries
in Africa.
-Oh!
-One minute.
LINDA: There's this guy I met
on the internet.
WOMAN:
Ooh. are we doing this now?
LINDA: Mm-hmm. He wants me
to meet him in Tucson...
for the weekend. He's a kid.
-In Tucson?
-Mmm.
-You have to try these.
-Do they have sugar?
-No. sugar free. Why Tucson?
-Mmm. He lives near there.
WOMAN:
Does he live in the desert?
LINDA: But we're staying
at a Holiday Inn.
-Uhh.
-I'm intrigued.
-ln Tucson?
-These are good.
I know. They're sweetened
with fruit juice.
I could eat
this whole damn tray.
I bought new underwear.
-Have you seen a photo?
-No.
That Holiday lnn part--
that's kind of a little sad.
-Why is that sad?
-Because, Tucson?
-So what? He knows a good one.
-All right.
Seems like you put
a lot of thought into this.
-Planned--we both have.
-Mm-hmm.
-Kind of like a wedding?
-Sort of.
OK, I think that was good,
but I really, really think...
you guys shouldn't make
eye contact.
Hold on, hold on.
That whole thing of you guys
being an extension of me--
Hold on.
Stop giving them directions.
One second.
Just let me work this out, OK?
You know when we do...
that first scene
where l'm exercising...
you guys gotta have
athletic supporters.
You know what. stop. Stop.
Hey. guess who the world
doesn't revolve around?
You. OK? I'm trying--
Maybe you want to come out here
and look at it.
Give me the jacket--
Can I talk to you for a second?
I'm fucking giving my all here.
I know, I know.
I'm giving my all, and
l'm really fucking worried, OK?
Because last week you tell me...
you want me to play it
like Danny Kaye, right?
This morning,
you come in, and you say...
Hey, why don't you play it
like Alan Alda.
What am l, fucking Danny Alda?
OK, I think
you're really distracted.
You've been
on the fucking laptop...
Iike a little crack monkey,
logging onto Expedia...
for this fucking chick
in Tucson?
Let me tell you something, man.
This is art.
I dumped my girlfriend
the day we started rehearsals.
You're not here, man.
You're not present.
I am here. I am here.
You're not, OK?
And l'm starting to question...
whether you and Carl know what
the fuck you're talking about.
Because let me tell you
something...
Peter Ustinov said,
To act is difficult...
but it's more difficult
to write a bad play...
than to give
a bad performance.
You know what? You know what?
What a great fucking idea,
watching me squirm.
What are you talking about?
-Catherine.
-What are you talking about?
-The letter.
-What letter?
Uh, the letter.
-May l?
-Oh, yeah.
You're acting crazy.
Hmm.
Wow. Well.
Pretty extraordinary.
Really?
This is a prank, right?
I mean, that's cool.
You can tell me.
I don't think it's a prank, no.
You didn't write this?
Is it your fantasy
that I wrote it?
Oh, don't. Don't do that.
I don't know what to tell you.
OK, here's the deal.
This right here,
you can't write about.
-I can't?
-No, you cannot. It's not fair.
You know, they really do
have ovens back there.
I am onto you, girl.
Well, I think l'm onto you,
all right?
Look at me.
-Look at me.
-Oh, my.
Come on,
did you write the letter?
It's OK.
See?
Ahem. I'm just not gonna play
this game with you anymore.
I ain't even thinking about you.
Look.
You missed a piece.
(Sighs)
CARL: So. Tracy--
is that your given name?
-Yes.
-Mm-hmm.
And what's your porn name?
I'm--
Do you know about porn names?
-No.
-OK.
Your porn name
is your middle name...
and the name of the first
street you grew up on.
OK.
So. Iike. my porn name
is Andrew Highland.
(Laughs) It's terrible.
It's not very sexy.
So. you're Tracy...
I don't have a middle name.
Oh. well. you can--
Yeah. well. you can also use
the name of your first pet.
We weren't allowed to have pets.
Ivory Coast, Senegal,
Sierra Leone...
LEE: Mm-hmm. Good.
Ghana, Mali.
Have you ever--been tested
lately for the H.I.V. virus?
No. Yes.
Morocco, Mozambique, Angola...
Good. My goodness.
-Cameroon...
-Stay there.
-Congo...
-God, you are good.
Gabon, Angola.
-Go east.
-Kenya, Somalia Republic...
-Jesus.
-Ethiopia.
Time.
You are very impressive.
I don't think
you're allowed to do this.
(Takes polaroid)
Of course I am.
Get down from there.
LEE: Just meet me
in the lobby. please.
You'll have a great time.
I know you'll love Gus.
I can't go to a party like that.
I have nothing to wear.
LEE: Wear the green dress.
You look great in it.
It's too tight.
It doesn't fit me anymore...
and it has a stain that's--
LEE:
You always have an excuse.
It's not an excuse.
Lee, that's a reason.
There's a difference.
Look, are we still
having lunch today?
Because I have
a birthday present for you.
LEE: It's tomorrow.
You know what? I know
when your birthday is, OK?
I'm not here tomorrow.
LEE: Hey. Linda...
Hello?
LEE: You're breaking up.
Call me back.
Hello? Listen, if you can
hear me, call me back.
LEE: Call me back.
(Hangs up)
Fuck.
LINDA:
Yeah. I think about him a lot.
You know? It's hard.
I found him in the basement.
And then I found Lee...
who was outside. I think.
or somewhere else in the house.
I mean. I remember screaming...
and then I remember her
appearing.
Uh. and then. you know.
no one else was home...
so she ran to a neighbor's...
and. uh. I stayed with him.
And then neighbors came. and...
and then my mom was home.
They found my mom. and so...
LEE:
It's pretty surprising...
when you see
somebody you know...
Iike your dad. you know.
in that state. you know?
So. it was surprising...
but I think that. you know.
in retrospect. he...
(Groaning)
He was pretty unhappy...
most of the time.
My friend Gus says that people--
the straight world--
will always be fascinated
by gangster sagas...
because, here are these guys...
they say,
We're not going to live...
by some unspoken rule...
that we don't take you
to the cleaners...
when you're not looking.
We don't have any agreement
not to take advantage of you.
And these people, they're
in the minority, fortunately...
otherwise, there would be chaos.
But we love watching them,
because--because...
it's a walk on the wild side...
without any real risk
of corruption.
It's two-dimensional, you know?
And it's always
going to be compelling.
Uh, you know, sometimes,
we can't look away.
But--and we should.
(Door opens)
-Hey, Carl, how you doing, pal?
-Good to see you.
-You look great.
-Thanks. Uh...
you know, that's amazing
that you called today...
because l--ahem--
I needed to see you.
I have an idea. I have an idea.
I think it's a cover.
You got slobber
all up on your...
Mmm.
What time is it?
Oh, I feel--I feel nauseous.
Are you ready to talk
about this?
Ohh. Nicholas...
Iook, I think
that you're very talented...
and l'll probably write
a very nice piece about you...
but you're really annoying
about this whole letter thing.
No. You're annoying.
Mm-hmm. OK.
CARL: You see. I think that is
worth discussing. I really do.
Well, Carl, l'll discuss
anything with you anytime...
because every time
you've come into my office...
every time
l've asked to see you...
or you've come to see me
with an idea...
about a cover
or a feature story...
or anything you want to do...
it always has validity.
It always has...
it's important to me
to hear your ideas, you know?
Thank you. thank you.
Let me ask you a question.
The reason I called you in
today. actually...
Yeah. Sorry. Ahem.
I have a question for you...
and it's kind of important
to me to hear the answer.
And the question is...
when you go to your
refrigerator in your home...
and you open the door,
and you see a bottle of beer...
do you take
that bottle of beer...
and pour it into a glass
and drink it...
or do you drink it
from the bottle?
Um. I--I--
well. I drink it from a glass.
Ah, you see?
Ohh. That's the problem.
You see, I want this magazine
to drink from the bottle.
In talks? What the fuck, Alex?
Tch. All right, in talks.
I need this.
All right, all right.
NICHOLAS:
I suppose we've come a ways...
since Sambo. Mr. Bojangles.
Step and fetch it. boy.
What?
Man. call me Mr. Tibbs...
we've heard Poitier say.
It's a new day. some say.
Because every now and then.
black men are even in.
Motion picture heroes.
It's the American way. Wesley.
Be cute
and still save the world.
Yes. we will. Will.
Go from Boy in the Hood
to Man of Honor.
Show 'em the money now. Cuba.
Give 'em funnies
like Chris Rock or Tucker.
Or just cool it,
be anybody, like Denzel.
But wait. He ain't even really
getting no loving...
Iike Sidney before him
and whoever after him.
Romancin' and dancin'
with amore's passion...
ain't in the script's equation.
But can even Mr. Washington...
briefly be seen kissing
a Pretty Woman...
underneath a Pelican Moon?
Can even he be a romantic lead?
Check it. From Sambo to Sidney
to Denzel to me.
Brothers ain't getting
nor giving no love now.
I don't want to complain, but
my doctor says l'm suffering...
from underloved syndrome.
Maybe it is a conspiracy.
But do folks still fear...
the black man's sexuality
like that?
A fear that could be wiped out
just by seeing us love...
not by race, but by heart.
And can't a brother
get some love?
Now, that, Catherine...
is a question
for the screen pages...
written by folks
who rarely look like me...
but want to see me
run and jump and shoot...
but don't care to see me kiss
a woman with my skin tone...
and would shoot me if I were
kissing a woman of their hue.
Who are you?
Who are you? Who are we?
We are human, too...
and we love loving, and...
can't a brother get some love?
That's the state of being...
a chocolate leading man
in Hollywood today.
(Click)
I keep bringing it up...
because I don't want you
to think I forgot.
Look, you just pay me back
when you have all of it.
-I have half now, so--
-Keep it. I don't want--
-lt just feels awkward.
-Please.
-Hi.
-Right this way.
-Thank you.
-Thanks.
What would you like
to start with?
Some evian or pellegrino?
-Thank you.
-You're welcome.
You still going on your weekend
with that guy from the internet?
Mm-hmm.
No, I haven't cancelled.
I'm putting myself out there.
I'm going.
Good.
You need money for that.
You want me to meet men,
and l'm meeting men.
You could meet men there.
There'll be plenty.
I can't come tonight.
I can't.
On the internet?
How is that meeting?
It's encountering.
What airline are you flying?
Southwest.
-Southwest?
-Yeah.
That's a good airline.
Southwest, younger man...
new underwear, Tucson,
Holiday lnn.
What is your point?
Have you ever stayed
at a Holiday lnn?
No. Have you?
I think that's what's
really bothering me.
You know what, Lee?
He's paying for it.
So if that's what's
really bothering you--
-What does he do?
-He's an artist.
-An actor.
-A painter.
In Tucson?
Yeah. He says the desert
inspires him.
-Lend me what?
-What is wrong with you?
Seriously. what is wrong
with you right now?
Friday. Fridays are good.
T. G. I. F. Fridays are good. Lee.
You're acting insane.
I'm going to have the squash.
But this is
a boundary issue. man!
What I do off-stage is
my process and my business. OK?
And I don't care
what anybody thinks.
And it's my business
to put on a play.
And now l've got three hours
to find a new Eva Braun.
Oh, OK. You know what?
Fuck her.
And here's why. Number one--
anyone who's offended
by drinking blood...
obviously doesn't drink blood.
Number two--anybody who drinks
as much blood as I do...
knows it has no effect.
Number three--
there is absolutely
no scientific connection...
between drinking
a shot of blood a day...
and being
an extraordinary actor.
And number 4--it is impossible
to prove number 3.
You know, do the words Masai
mean anything to you?
Do you know who that is?
Yeah. Herzog made
a documentary about them.
The herdsmen of fire.
warriors of Africa.
They drank blood.
Jack fucking LaLanne
drank blood in the fifties.
Yeah. granted.
his wife wouldn't kiss him...
but this is bullshit. man.
I don't care what you do
outside of this theater.
I don't give a shit. You could
eat the ass out of a dead wolf.
I don't care.
Just keep it to yourself, OK?
Just keep it to yourself.
I think it's fucking hysterical
that she walked.
And I know comedy.
LINDA: I don't understand.
I don't understand
what's wrong.
I mean. birthdays are fun.
Well, OK, this is mom
when I was four...
at my birthday
introducing me to people.
And this is Lee. She ruined
my body, didn't you, dear?
-There.
-Thanks.
I won't be here tomorrow.
so happy birthday.
Oh. It's smaller than the gift
you gave me last year...
for my fortieth birthday.
You know what. Lee. you make
forty a bigger deal than it is.
You have no idea about forty.
I'll be forty.
What did I give you last year?
I don't even remember.
You know, that--that thing.
That...
-Oh. You didn't like it?
-No.
Well. honestly.
I would have rather had...
just. Iike.
a card or something.
OK. God.
It's just a weird gift
to give your sister...
who's married.
on her fortieth birthday.
You know what Gus gave me
last year for my birthday?
First edition of Bernard Shaw's
The Sanity of Art.
Did you get anything out of it?
-Which?
-The gift I gave you.
Are you kidding?
No. I mean, yes or no.
But for my fortieth birthday?
Well, I have one, so...
I used it once.
OK. All right.
Well, what happened?
Um, I got stuck in the chair.
You used it in a chair?
Well, yeah,
that's what's on the box.
Different ways. I've never...
Not in a chair. I've never...
Well...
gift-giving--
you know, it's an art.
You should have
the person in mind--
OK, l'm sorry. I thought
you'd like it. I like it--
Well. that's--
but you should give people...
what you think
they would want--
you know. something personal.
How much more personal
could that be?
But then. you and that guy--
what was his name?
-Tom.
Yeah. You sat at
the other end of the table...
and just stared
at each other the whole time.
You didn't even
really socialize.
Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
Lee, forgive me, OK?
I happened to be in love--
for a brief period of time.
Once--which happened
to include...
the week of your birthday.
-This is all a year later.
-You don't get it.
Christ!
You know what?
Gift--it's a gift.
A gift is a gift.
Don't question it.
At least not to the giver
and out loud a whole year later.
Chr--
-OK, now I know.
-What?
Well, that it meant something
to you.
What?
Just the whole thing,
that you put thought into it.
You know.
it's for your small change.
FRANCESCA: So he gives me
this injection...
and I become invisible.
And I can do anything. right?
Because. you know.
I'm invisible.
What do I do? I go to
one of my colleagues. Carl...
and I make him
sign a confession...
while I hold a knife
to his neck.
Now. it's just weird.
because I really like Carl.
He's a brilliant,
talented man...
completely misunderstood
by his boss.
Well, you know, l'm not
surprised he was in my dream...
really, because
I think of him a lot.
I think l'm actually--
MAN: Wheel in Nicholas.
We're ready for him.
It's funny, because
he's one of these guys--
You know what?
I want to tell you...
what I think about that,
but I gotta go do this.
OK. I'll be here--listening.
Hey, Pitty.
(Laughs)
Hey, man. What's going on?
OK, exactly the same thing.
We're starting from over here.
It took me a little bit--
I needed to do this
with track...
instead of just the walk-up...
so we're gonna do
a little bit of a push-in.
There's probably
going to be some focus stuff...
so we're gonna shoot a few.
OK.
But just split the extras
as they come through--
don't be precious about it.
Tell them we're coming through.
I will, I will.
R-1 39, take one.
(Man muttering)
And background action--action!
Move! Move!
-Out of the way!
-Goddamn it.
Uh, looks like we're late.
Looks like.
Back to square one.
That's what he thinks.
You think different?
Like the back
of my big ten-inch.
-Oh.
-Come on.
(Sighs)
CARL: One minute
I'm drinking a beer...
and the next minute
I'm unemployed.
How does that happen?
(Laughs)
He said I have confused...
my personality quirks
with standards.
What the fuck?
CARL: You have no idea
what I have lost just now.
This goes way beyond this job.
I could lose everything.
The ripple effect.
It's the ripple effect.
It's like. Oh. yeah.
by the way. you're fired.
Oh. yeah. honey. by the way...
uh. you don 't think
I'm so great.
Guess what? They don 't think
I'm so great at work.
Hey. maybe I'm not so great.
Hey. that's simple.
Well. there. I can write that.
I can write.
I'm not so great.
Maybe I can write it...
a hundred-fucking-thousand
times on a blackboard--
Oh. I can teach.
I used to teach.
I love teaching.
I do love teaching.
R-1 39, take 49, mark!
MAN: OK. here we go!
And background! Action!
BRAD: Move!
-Out of the way!
-Move!
Ohh. Looks like we're late.
Looks like.
Back to square one.
That's what he thinks.
You think different?
(Both panting)
I know different.
Come on.
(Sighs)
-Cut it!
-OK. we got.
Nice one.
Very nice, very nice.
Check the gate. Check the gate.
BRAD: Lunch?
OK.
So, David, David.
You need me for anything?
No, no. Absolutely.
Lunch--go ahead.
-Nice scene, man.
-Yeah, thanks, Brad.
Thanks.
Would you not take a role
if you felt...
the people of the black
community wouldn't like it?
Hmm.
This guy that lives
in my neighborhood--
Iives right across the street
from me.
And he dresses like--
yeah, yeah.
He dresses like a vampire
twenty-four hours a day.
I don't know if he's got a job.
I don't know what he does...
but I know
he dresses like a vampire...
Iike Dracula all the damn time.
-You want to go?
-Mm.
I mean, look,
I see this guy at Pavilion's...
buying romaine lettuce
dressed as Dracula...
so you got to figure...
he's an actor, right?
He's got to be.
Well, you could find out.
Yeah. The point is, the answer
to your question is...
if I needed the money,
abso-fucking-lutely.
Absolutely.
Now, am I proud of that?
No.
But, yeah, l'd take it...
'cause, look,
a brother's got to eat.
-OK. Are they gonna say cut?
-I don't know.
OK, what's going on?
-OK, can somebody--
-Did they call cut?
Well, can somebody
communicate--OK.
Bonnie, Bonnie, this is
itching me so bad today.
Fran, listen, listen.
Hey, after lunch...
next time we do this.
could you give me...
more to work with
on this whole attraction--
What do you mean?
That was good, huh?
We can't hear in there, though.
We can't hear anything.
No, 'cause l'm not feeling
the whole sexual chemistry.
No, no, but remember...
you gotta leave yourself
somewhere to go...
for the second letter
at the airport.
All right. Oh!
All right, all right.
Right?
In the way it's got to build...
you got to give me
something to go on.
-We had it going before.
-Did he call?
-Yeah.
-lt's not working for me.
OK, well, if you're
going to stay for lunch...
Iet's talk about
whatever it is--
No. I gotta run an errand,
so next time--and maybe it's me.
All right.
We'll figure it out.
Don't worry about it.
All right. I think it was good!
Oh. thanks.
No, it's the movie.
This is the only movie.
As far as he's concerned,
it's the only movie.
CALVIN: Hey. can you
hold that door for me?
-Sure.
-Thank you.
Got it?
Excuse me.
CARL: Oh. the film.
Well. the film--
Artie and I wrote this.
We started working together--
really writing together.
about a year ago.
We tossed around
a couple of ideas.
And Artie's a pretty good
playwright in his own right.
And we thought.
you know. maybe this--
sort of my understanding
of Hollywood and everything...
and his ability
to actually write...
would be a good combination...
and so we came up
with this idea...
for what is now
Rendezvous. the movie.
It's almost like a spy film
in the intrigue...
of this romantic encounter...
between this guy
that Calvin plays--
I'm sorry. there's a...
Uh. and this woman.
And anyway.
I think it's a neat story.
And I think it's a great cast.
Um. uh. but. uh...
Yeah. I'm sorry.
I have some--it's weird.
I'm really happy about
the project. I really am.
I got--you know. there's--
I've got issues with some of--
Actually. Calvin. Calvin is.
I think. I don 't know--
You know. other people...
get more excited about him
than I do.
It's not to say I'm not happy
having him on the movie.
I think that's great. and
I'm sure he's very good in it.
I just don't get what
the big thing is with Calvin.
I think--you know. you picture
a role in a certain way...
And sometimes it's--
I'm not always right. either.
I know. you know. certainly
my wife thinks he's great.
(Heavy breathing)
(Shuts door)
FRANCESCA:
I'm starving to death.
-Well, l've got it right here.
-I might actually faint.
OK, tuna. No celery.
No celery and no...
-Onion.
-Right.
Uh. so listen...
you know that thing
that we were talking about?
Um. I can't keep--
OK. I mean--
-Come on, come on.
-OK, OK.
I'm uncomfortable dealing
with this aspect of your life.
I don't want to talk to them.
Well. I don't want
to talk to them. either.
I don't even want to talk
to the guys l'm dating.
Uh-huh.
Well. I'm not dating anyone.
A date is not dating.
Well, you know,
someone buys you dinner...
you owe them a phone call,
in my opinion.
See. dinner--
that's where I fucked up.
It should have been lunch,
because lunch is meaningless.
They all seem pretty nice
to me.
Well, they don't strike you as,
like, networky, freaky...
actress-dating
executive types...
with their water bottles
in, like, a mesh tote bag?
This is really--
this is disgusting.
I can't eat this.
That arugula is so bitter.
It's like
my algebra teacher on bread.
-OK.
-Ugh.
I'm truly, l'm--look at me.
I'm gonna faint.
I might actually faint.
We all know how you get
when your blood sugar's low.
All right. I'll be right back.
OK. Thank you.
-You're welcome.
-I need some wet naps, too.
-OK.
-Tuna fingers.
-Don't want tuna fingers.
-No, we don't.
-You're an angel. Thank you.
-Oh, you're welcome.
Oh. post-its!
LEE: See. I knew
something was wrong. I just--
I didn't know it was that.
I had that one this morning.
(Kisses)
CALVlN: Hey...
I need to talk to you
about something.
-Lee--
-Don't.
(Cell phone ringing)
(Ring)
Why did you even pursue this?
What? Wait a minute.
You came over and spoke to me.
Now, all of this began
because of you.
Are you saying
you weren't attracted to me?
No--
Gus told me
to watch out for you.
I'm forty-one tomorrow,
Calvin--
the age where
I could have a stroke...
in the middle of the night.
If you think l'm not going
to Gus', you're...
OK, I have a meeting.
Go fuck somebody else.
-Hey.
-Hi.
-You're still here?
-Yeah, I was just upstairs.
I was shopping
for my friend Gus.
-Oh.
-Yeah.
-Are you OK?
-Oh, yeah, l'm good.
I've just had really some
sad cases today, so l'm just--
-l'm sorry.
-l'm emotional.
Yeah.
What did you get him?
-Who?
-What did you get Gus?
Oh. They didn't have it.
-What was it?
-Yeah.
-Are you...
-lt was a thing.
He's--he's, uh...
It was--they didn't--you know,
'cause he's forty today...
and I was just gonna get him
some, I don't know, this--
-Are you OK?
-Yeah.
I just have to go.
I'm really late, so--
-Are you sure?
-Yeah.
I'll call you later.
Oh, OK.
Thank you.
Um, you need to find him.
I don't know if he knows
l'm here at the office...
so I have to have a contact
name in order to transfer you.
Um. Harvey's not here
at the office right now.
He sees on the TV a murder...
and as he listens to the murder,
he just goes white.
His whole face
just goes white...
and he bolts
from his apartment.
Now. we follow him.
The murders--they deviate
at this key point...
for reasons nobody can
understand. because--
T ell Trevors l'm not gonna
do it. I'm not gonna do it.
Good, good. Go. Sorry. Go ahead.
Aah.
My brother Bob
should look at this.
Yeah. Good. Good!
-Great.
-Good.
CALVlN: Motherfuckers.
Did you see their faces
looking at us?
Yes.
It was like a labrador
staring at a Picasso.
Right.
Ed, we walked in there
with a china cup.
-They want beer mugs.
-Yeah, right?
I could so see myself
in that part.
Right?
Fuck!
-lt's all right.
-All right, I gotta go.
-See you later.
-See you.
Hey, Ed, keep the faith.
It was good. It was good.
-Mr. Liveright.
-Hey, hey. Bill.
-Come on in.
-Thanks.
-Ann?
-Yeah.
My massage is here.
I'll call you back in an hour.
-How about in back? Good?
-OK, sure.
Um, what do you think
about the lighting?
A little light--too bright?
Whatever you're comfortable
with is fine. Yeah.
I think a little darker.
-Like so.
-Sure.
-Need some help?
-No.
Done it before, huh?
Bill Liveright--great name.
Well, a name with a message
is a good name, right?
I don't know.
It just always eluded me.
Mmm.
Money is just feminine energy.
Huh. It always seems so male.
I don't get it.
Money: Mater. The Latin.
You connect with that,
and you're golden.
You make it sound pretty simple.
-lt is.
-Just connecting with it.
You're catching on, Ann.
Look, don't be
one of the confused people.
If you have purpose,
you can just wade right through.
It's like running past
people who are asleep.
OK...
you can turn over now.
I think I kind of drooled
a little bit.
Just scoot your head down.
so you're not in the hole.
(Exhales)
OK.
You're from L.A.?
No. Miami, actually. You?
-New York.
-Oh.
(Sniffs)
Do you find me attractive?
What?
Yes.
In what sort of way?
In a human sort of way.
-Ann.
-Bill.
It's my birthday, Ann.
-Really?
-Yeah.
Happy birthday.
What's your philosophy
on release?
You know what, Bill, I know
where you're going with this...
and the thing is,
I don't do it, so...
Right. Not even
for a little extra money?
Mm-mmm. It's not
the kind of massage I do.
Right.
I offer a release
of tension and toxins...
and sometimes emotion, but...
Yes, well,
that's what l'm talking about.
-Well, I don't do it, so--
-lt would take thirty seconds.
Oh, yeah.
You can come in thirty seconds?
-Do you have a second-hand?
-Look, I can't do it.
You could stop
after thirty seconds.
Five hundred dollars.
When was the last time...
you made five hundred dollars
for thirty seconds of work?
-You're cruel.
-l'm not cruel, l'm practical.
You need the cash,
I need the release.
This is crazy.
Five hundred dollars, Ann.
You can't make any noise.
-The place is noisy.
-No. You can audibly exhale.
You can't moan or grunt or sigh.
I can't moan or grunt or sigh,
just audible exhale only?
-Yes.
-Ahh!
No. Too loud. And if
you do it--it's too much.
I'll be quiet.
OK, Ann, l'll be quiet.
Are you ready?
Fuck.
Will you just hand me
that plastic bag right there?
Well. why?
No reason.
(Sighs)
Oh.
Oh, my God.
Ahem.
-Here.
-Thank you.
GUS: Shit.
-Hey, Ann?
-What?
I'm sorry.
I thought I had more cash on me.
-That's OK, Bill.
-I saw an ATM in the lobby.
You know what? There's a limit.
There's a limit.
To the machine. You can only
get three hundred dollars out.
Could you move that, please?
That bag.
-You're kidding.
-No, l'm not kidding.
-I feel bad.
-You should.
You should feel
really bad and ashamed.
It's...
-Hold on.
-Forget it.
-Just hold on a second.
-You know what? Forget it.
It's pathetic.
Mater equals money.  I mean.
give me a fucking break.
All the world loves a winner.
You know why
they love the winner?
Because they think
he knows something.
I mean, he had to know
something in order to win.
So, we admire him.
But the winner doesn't
learn anything from winning.
No, the loser--the loser
learns something about himself.
Losing teaches you
about yourself.
So. the loser's the winner.
I don't know. I mean.
it's not in actual terms.
I'm speaking figuratively.
(Elevator doors open)
Sorry. Excuse me.
-Good night, Denny.
-May I see you, please?
The gentleman in 205
left this for you.
Oh. Huh.
Wow. That was nice.
GUS: Ann. thanks
for the happy ending. Bill.
Nice card.
(Opens bottle)
Django?
Django? Hey, hey, hey!
(Clapping) Sweetie-pie?
Dja--
(Hums)
LEE:
I know what they say.
I know what they say
about me--
my colleagues...
and my family.
I don't--fucking movies.
OK, let's fucking go.
Fucking movies!
Fucking overpaid, fucking
unhappy childhood fuckers.
Fucking movie fucking fuckers.
Let's go! Somebody--
Jesus, buddy!
Uh, do you think somebody else
could go?
Maybe one of us could
fucking cross the street?
Fucking movie cop!
Hey. fucking movie cop!
Could I maybe
fucking cross the street?
Francesca Davis. Fuck.
Yes. He's gonna get--what?
Dehydrated? OK.
Yes. Yeah, I understand.
Thank you.
Hello. Yeah, hi.
(Clears throat)
I did that...
and--and I gave him
some water, yeah...
and I was just hoping
that Dr. Green could come by...
and, uh, and give him
a quick look.
Oh, he is?
Oh, I see. Uh...
Yeah?
Well, if--you know,
I just--I just, uh...
want to make sure
he's not gonna die...
you know, or anything.
Um, so if you could,
that would be great.
Right, heh heh. Yeah.
Uh, that's fantastic.
Yes, I will see you then.
Yes. What? The address?
Oh. Oh, my address. Oh, yeah.
I guess you'd need that,
wouldn't you? Heh heh.
(Alarm chirps)
(Cell phone rings)
Hi.
I know.
You know, I can't really talk.
I'm going into a store.
Can I call you back?
OK.
Oh, really?
Oh that'd be--
that's--that's great.
I'm--l'm glad.
You met Gus?
Where? Wow.
Yeah, well, there's a guy...
who could change your life,
you know?
(Sighs)
So, l'm gonna get the dress.
-Oh, good. Great.
-Yeah.
LINDA: Mm-hmm. Sure.
Yeah. I was. um. fat...
overweight. and very short...
and. um. I hadn't
gone through puberty.
So. yeah. I mean. I looked.
you know--I did not look...
Iike I would've liked
to have looked in high school.
Yeah. surely I would've
changed my social status.
I still would. Heh heh. Yeah.
Treat myself.
So, that's five there.
Oh, great. Thank you very much.
-OK.
-Excellent. Thank you.
Hey, you came. I thought
you were coming later.
No.
Hey. How are you, man?
Good to see you.
The house is open, guys,
if you want to...
-Oh. Hi, Dee.
-lt's good to see you.
Good to see you.
Thank you for coming.
Good.
That guy didn't pay.
Did you pay, sir?
MAN: I did. yes.
Would you like--
No, no. I just--I saw you
come the other way...
and most people were coming...
I'm sorry.
Right in here.
Right there on the sofa.
Oh, boy.
What else was in the brownies
besides chocolate?
Um...
-Hash?
-Yeah.
Aw, come on, man.
No. My wife
brought it back from London.
We made the brownies
for my friend's fortieth--
So, what'd you do,
leave it out for him to eat?
No, no. I know.
When I left it, look...
it was right here
on this counter.
I didn't think
he could jump that high.
He's got little legs like a...
All this--he ate all this.
It's so much better than pot,
right?
-Uh--
-Aw, no, no, no.
You don't understand,
you don't understand.
I haven't smoked that in years,
so, you know what l'm saying?
Goddamn.
When I was in my twenties,
this guitar player and l...
would make up all these lyrics
while he played...
and our songs would end up...
with all these fucked-up
rhyme schemes.
Heather. Heather, l'm sorry.
Is he going to be all right?
Oh, he's going to be fine.
He's going to be fine.
So, uh...
you going to throw that out?
(Saxophone playing)
Look, you liked it...
and you've told me
you haven't liked things.
You liked it. Man, listen.
I don't want you telling me...
you're not going to pursue
any more meetings...
because
this is what I want to do.
I'm serious. OK?
Hey. Iisten. Could you. Iike...
It's better now.
It's a lot better now.
Ed and l,
we've been working on it.
We've been
beefing up the scenes.
And that whole thing
you mentioned...
I agree with you--
about me being in it.
I'm not going to do it.
Even if they ask about it.
we're not going to build it in.
I figure. you know.
in the long run...
it's probably a good thing...
me trying to establish myself
as a writer instead of an actor.
Like Pinter. You know. Pinter.
he was an actor.
He started off as an actor.
He still acts. occasionally.
All right, this shit
is cyclical, you know that?
All right. don't.
Don't. don't. don't.
I got it.
OK. Thank you.
(Line ringing)
If you stop telling me
that that letter makes sense...
you can throw up all you want.
How about that?
Tch. Yeah. Aw.
Do you know her?
-Ahem. Who?
-Carl's wife.
Nuh-uh.
That's kind of funny, because
l've heard things, actually.
Yeah. Yeah.
A couple of them.
-Hey, how are you doing?
-Uhh.
Hey, Fran, listen,
I want you to meet--
Frannie. It's Lucy Morgan.
L.A. Magazine.
-l'm sorry. I--
-The Sedona piece.
Oh, my God. Yes. Oh, wow.
Wow. You changed your hair
or something?
Yeah. How do you know Cal?
-Uh. we--
-It was a dinner.
Yeah.
Excuse me.
Hey.
Hi.
Is it--is it upstairs,
or is it in there?
God.
-Oh, this is wrong.
-No.
-l'm overdressed.
-You look...
-I wasn't sure what...
-lt's on the roof.
Where's Carl?
He's not here yet.
I just, um...
-We should go up and...
-OK.
-Wow.
-You OK?
Yeah.
You know,
I wish I didn't have this on.
No. You look great.
Well...
You know, I have to admire you
for your belief...
in this project.
but the reality...
is a whole different thing
altogether.
It's all marketplace shit.
And I don't think that
this is a good role for you...
so don't even push that.
When does this article
come out?
In a couple of months.
Well, you call me...
if you can't get any answers
out of this guy.
Thank you.
Nice to meet you.
Nice seeing you.
Huh?
Meltzin.
Name kind of suits him.
Oh, Nicholas.
No, it looks good.
Where'd you get that dress?
-Seaver.
-Where?
On Third. Do you know it?
-ls it good?
-Yeah.
-lt was on sale. I like it.
-No, it's...
Oh.
God.
All chromium is not bad,
though...
because
I get Fitness magazine...
I need a drink.
No. I'm saying there's
a lot of good chromiums.
-I read it in a magazine.
-Hey.
Hey. I wouldn't go
to the lengths...
of bathing in bottled water,
that's all l'm saying.
I believe what you're saying.
-Franny Davis?
-Yeah.
Sam Osborne.
-l'm sorry.
-The Duchess of Malfi.
-Birchers.
-Yeah.
I was the lighting guy.
Mmm. Oh, my God. Oh, OK. Yeah.
-Sam Osborne.
-Osborne.
-How are you?
-Nice to see you again.
Oh, you, too. Wow. That's funny.
-Yeah.
-That's--
Do you remember when you said...
l feel like a waitress
on vacation?
Oh, God.
It was, like, just the cutest
thing l've ever heard, and...
I don't know why
that just stuck out.
I don't--yeah.
I just--um, well...
-I was going to go...
-OK.
Jesus. You remember that?
Yeah.
Yeah, I do.
-I got a funny memory that way.
-Oh.
Anyway, hey,
l--I don't want to bug you.
I know you got
lots of people to see.
I just wanted to say
how happy I am for you, and...
Oh, thanks. Thank you.
It's--I always thought
you had something special.
This...
You know, it's just amazing
what you've been able to do...
-well, from...
-From nothing. Ha ha ha!
Or, well...yeah.
No. I'm just--l'm--thank you.
Thank you.
Right. Good. Well, hey...
-Cheers. Good to see you.
-Thank you. Cheers.
I couldn't Cheers you.
I don't have a drink...
but, well, shit,
Sam Osborne...
Ha ha!
Birchers lighting guy.
Birchers.
Get me a--
why don't you come with me?
(Laughs)
-Yeah. OK.
-OK.
-Nicholas. Oh, my goodness.
-Oh, God.
-Uhh.
-Let's get you on the sofa.
-Oh, God, did I just--
-Yes, you did.
-Ohh.
-Go slowly.
Ah, Catherine, l'm sorry.
Are you all right?
-Here's some water.
-Oh, thank you so much.
-I feel a little light headed.
-Here, have some water.
-Yeah.
-Drink it.
Yeah?
Are you sure you're all right?
-Mm-hmm.
-Thank goodness.
-I need to ask you something.
-What?
I need you to come back
to New York with me.
-Nicholas, I can't--
-No. It's the letter.
Catherine, it's that letter.
I can't get it out of my head.
Well, but that was--
I've never had anybody
write me a love letter.
-Never.
-But I just--
No, listen.
You come back to New York.
You're here.
You there just makes sense.
You write the article,
and--and we go from there.
Nicholas, these kind of things--
A moment of inspiration...
that's all
anybody ever really wants.
Mmm.
To have an original idea...
to fall in love.
It takes courage...
to surrender these things.
Especially when you have
control issues.
I get that a lot.
(Sighs)
I know what
they're going to talk about...
when they talk about me.
They're going to talk
about the mustache.
People are so fucking petty.
People say,
God, what's up with that?
Like, didn't you know
that Chaplin had it first?
Yeah! I knew, OK?
(Sighs)
It's either the name
of your first pet...
and the first street
that you ever lived on...
or it's your middle name...
and the first street
that you lived on.
Well. which is it?
I think--is it pet?
-Pet.
-lt's pet.
So. if it's pet...
all right.
WOMAN: I'm Daisy Bufane.
Daisy Bufane?
Jo Jo Mountainview.
(Laughter)
I would be Peavey Meander.
-What?
-Peavey Meander.
Meander.
-Thurston Craddock.
-Hmm.
Uh, Baron Von Hugecock.
(Laughter)
What?
That's--that was my street.
I lived on
Van Hugecock Avenue.
(Laughter)
MAN: The little kid
who lives on Van Hugecock.
FRANCESCA:
Oh. God. where is Gus?
-Save us from this misery.
-Uhh.
CARL:
So. it's your middle name...
-Right.
-first.
CARL: And then--and then...
the name of the street
that you grew up on.
HEA THER: OK.
(lnhales)
Lolita...
Honeysuckle.
(Both laugh)
(Line ringing)
(People chattering)
CALVIN:
All right. I'll open it.
Obviously. everybody.
Gus is not here...
so I was thinking...
to pass the time,
why don't we all just kind of...
whoever wants to, stand up
and give our little Gus stories.
Uh, so, let me start off.
I think
my favorite Gus moment...
was when he called me
at 1:20 in the morning...
to ask what
I really thought about him.
WOMAN: What'd you say?
What did I say?
I said, Well, Gus,
whatever I think about you...
l'm going to think the same
thing at 10:00 in the morning.
Then I hung up.
-Whatever.
-Calvin.
Aw...
It's all right. It's all right.
Listen.
Iet's get down to business.
If someone wants to stand up.
please. feel free.
The floor is open.
MAN. TAPPING GLASS:
All right. I got one. Calvin.
Yes.
that's right. that's right.
So. Gus and I--some of you
may not know this--
Gus and I used
to hunt together. all right?
And this one time, we're
waiting up in this deer stand...
and, uh, Gus climbs down...
to relieve himself
in the bushes, OK?
(lnflating)
And. uh--it gets funnier.
It gets funnier.
So. uh...
Wow. Thank you. man.
I can't tell you
how much that means to me.
I really appreciate that,
you know?
Especially coming
from someone like you...
who writes and acts and directs
and plays the sax.
Originally,
I kind of felt like...
it was really coming after me,
you know?
Now I feel like
l'm coming after it.
Perfect.
It's not coming after me.
I'm going to get it.
-Can you grab that sword?
-l'm already on it, man.
It's weird. I was watching
this interview with Al.
-Pacino?
-Yeah.
And he was talking
about the differences...
between stage acting
and film acting...
and he was talking about
how being on stage...
is like being on this high wire,
like, a hundred feet up.
And if you fall,
you're fucked...
but acting in film is like
having the wire on the...
-Ground.
-On the Ground.
Oh, OK, you've heard that.
Yeah, man, working for guys
like you and Carl...
-the writing, just everything--
-Aw, come on, man.
Where is Carl, by the way?
Is he...
He had a party to go to.
Oh, that's right.
Is that that producer guy?
-Gus Delario.
-Oh, OK.
That's not too shabby.
Carl owns a tux, huh?
Mm-hmm.
Huh. Not just one of those
shirts with the design on it?
You know, he says
good luck and break a leg.
Thank you. Thank you.
Did I tell you about tomorrow?
Yeah. Fuck, man.
Good luck, you know?
That should go really good.
Ann? Is that her name?
Yeah. It's a nice name.
I hope so, man.
I've been looking a long time.
Yeah. I hear you.
It's hard. I don't know.
You want to go for a beer
or something?
No, I got to teach a pilates
class, but thank you.
FRANCESCA:
Shouldn't we all say grace?
I think you're right.
Listen, it's been 45 minutes,
and Gus is still not here...
so let's eat.
Everybody dig in.
MAN: Thank you.
FRANCESCA:
Even at a party--bossy. bossy.
CALVIN: You know you love it.
You love it. You know you do.
(Low conversations)
-Oh!
FRANCESCA:
What are you doing? Shit.
* C-C-C-Calvin *
I'll get my ball. (Giggles)
CALVIN: Uh. everybody. this is
Lee Bright. Carl's wife.
Hi!
Our writer.
Gave us a beautiful script.
-Hi.
Hi. Thank you.
Lee, Lucy Morgan. L.A. Magazine.
I've worked with Carl.
Oh, yeah. That's right. Hi.
How are you? Nice to meet you.
Hi. I'm Lee.
Yeah. Hi, hi.
Hey, can you name all
the countries in Africa, Calvin?
What do you want from me?
-l'm not drunk.
-OK. Let's go.
I'm just--
you know, fuck you, man.
-Yeah, let's go.
-He needs to sober up.
All right. Sorry.
Sit down. Sit down.
He needs to fucking sober up.
I mean, come on.
LlNDA:
You know what? Enough. No more.
No more drinks, all right?
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
No more. Do not drink anything.
Carl's on his way, all right?
-Where are you going?
-l'll be right back.
Don't drink
and don't talk to anybody.
No one!
Tch.
(Knocking)
Hey, Soledad. Do me a favor.
-You're beautiful.
-Oh, thank you.
-You working?
-No, l'm not.
You know.
I left something in here today.
Could you just let me in
for a second?
Of course.
Yeah. Thank you.
Thanks. Gus?
Hello?
Oh, my God.
Oh. my God.
(Linda runs out)
LEE: I mean. I'm wearing
a linen suit. for God's sake...
and mascara's
running all over my face...
(Cell phone rings)
And I'm the only fucking car
in the parking lot.
(Cell phone rings)
It's...Iate...
Hey, where did you go?
Why?
He's what?
OK, OK, look, look, look,
we gotta call somebody, OK?
We'll call down, and l'll say
I left something in here...
and I came up and I knocked
and he didn't answer, OK?
What? What?
Lee, I don't know what!
-Just wait.
-Fuck!
Wait for what? Oh, my God!
A few hours ago he was alive,
OK? He was really alive!
-Oh, man!
-Gus?
-Fuck, fuck! Do not touch him!
-He's cold.
-Jesus Christ!
-Oh, my God!
Of course he's cold!
CARL: I don't know
ifyou can calculate...
I don't know
if you can quantify...
the effect that would have
on a ten-year-old girl.
I think Lee is like...
Have you ever seen
a dog get hit by a car...
but walk away?
And... there's this impact...
and you know
something terrible...
has happened to that dog...
but it walks away...
and it doesn't seem to even
realize the implications...
'cause it just goes on.
But you know
that something terrible...
has happened inside this dog.
LEE:
Why do you think he did it?
Oh, God, I don't know.
It's some weird sex thing.
I don't know.
LEE: No. Not this.
Ohh.
CARL: That's. I think.
what happened to Lee.
It's like--it's like--
She's a dog that got hit by
a car. and she walked away...
and she's still walking. but...
LINDA: I don't know.
I guess he was really sad.
CARL: Some very. very
important things...
inside her are damaged.
LEE: Oh.
Jesus.
(Traffic noise)
CARL: So... my wife and I
were having trouble...
and I said I thought
maybe we were in a rut...
and that maybe
we should try something...
to liven things up.
and she said. Like what?
And I said like maybe we should
tape ourselves doing it.
And she was
completely shocked by this...
and she thought
it was beyond disgusting...
and that was that
for. Iike. four months.
And then one night.
out of the blue...
she says. Let's do it.
Ohh... (Laughs)
So, we get it all set up, and
l'm ready and she's ready...
and, uh, and she has gone out
and bought herself...
a little toy to use
in the video.
Really?
Well, it's not a little toy.
It's a--it's a huge...
(Giggling)
Fucking...I mean, it was--
No one has a--you know, OK.
Well, anyway, I took one look
at this thing...
and I knew
I would not be able to--
(Laughs)
I mean, it--I just couldn't--
I couldn't...
I couldn't.
So we haven't.
And, you know...
you can't come back
from something like that.
I don't know whether
she lost respect for me...
or I lost respect for myself,
but something was lost.
HEATHER:
What are you going to do?
CARL: I have no idea.
I mean. I know professionally.
I'm gonna go back to teaching.
I always loved teaching.
-Really?
-Yeah.
CARL: Never learned a thing in
my life. but I love teaching.
The legacy of higher education.
HEATHER: What about your wife?
CARL: Tsk. I...
will hope
that we get over this.
HEATHER: Hmm.
CARL: Aside from loving her.
I just really like her.
A lot.
But...
I guess she thinks...
everyone and everything
is against her.
Somehow I just think...
it keeps her from being happy.
(lnhales)
Is that your wife?
-Hey!
-Hi.
HEATHER: l'm with Dr. Green.
CARL:
This is--Heather, this is Lee.
-Django, he was sick.
-Django ate the brownies.
-Yeah.
-He's OK.
-He's fine now.
-We put him to bed.
CARL: Are you OK?
Um, the...
they found Gus
in his hotel room.
He's--he's dead.
(Crying) He's--
HEATHER: I should go.
CARL: OK, OK. Thank you.
Thank you. Thank you for that.
HEATHER: Yeah.
Hey...OK?
(Sniffles)
OK. OK.
He--he's dead.
Oh.
Oh, sweetie pie. OK.
Um...
(Sobs)
Well...
If you ever left me,
I would die.
I would die. Please don't.
OK.
(Kisses)
(Sighs)
I just want this day to be over.
(Laughs)
Mmm.
(Sobs)
Yeah. Let it out.
OK.
(Door closes)
-Happy birthday.
-Thanks.
CARL: Mmm.
LEE: Hi.
Did you have any
interesting dreams last night?
CARL:
Um...no. Back to normal.
LEE: Oh.
CARL: I had an afro.
LEE: Huh?
LEE: I really don't know
what you should do...
when you're in love
with someone.
I know that you're thinking
about them all the time.
You want to be with them
and see things with them.
I think it's impossible.
It's an ideal to just think...
that you can actually
be kind all the time...
and never be disappointed
in them or by them.
It's hard. I mean. it's like
the dream is short-lived.
CARL: You've got
to keep hoping that...
that there's more.
FRANCESCA:
You know. you always--
It's when
you least expect it...
that something
kind of pops up. Iiterally.
He just was--
appeared. kind of...
Um. so...
And nice that it's somebody...
that I knew
a really long time ago.
And. clearly. you know.
paid attention to me...
before I was. you know. blond.
(Laughs)
So. that makes it nice...
but I think
that it's just fate...
and it's kind of. um...
I don 't know. And today. just
negative ions in the air...
bringing good fortune
and--and. yeah.
Yeah.
Sam Osborne.
CAL VIN: I think.
you know. with Lucy...
she's a good listener.
Iike I said...
but she's also. you know.
she's teaching me stuff.
She comes from a nice family.
Her parents are still together.
She got three-four
brothers and sisters...
and they're
a real close-knit family.
It's just the opposite
of where I had come from.
I don 't know. Honestly.
I don 't know what it is.
I mean. I gotta just kinda go
off my gut right now...
and just see what feels right.
And right now.
when I'm with Lucy...
man. it just feels right.
(Piano playing)
(Sighs)
(Footsteps)
Catherine.
Nicholas.
You're here.
I am.
I wasn't sure.
Neither was l--
until now.
Mmm.
-Mmm.
(lce rattling)
(Announcement on P.A.)
(Soda hissing)
-Did you get that?
-The announcement? No.
-Where you going?
-Oh, Tucson.
Mmm! I'm going to Tucson.
-Oh, yeah?
-Yeah.
-You ever been?
-No.
It's supposed to be beautiful.
That's what I hear.
I've never been, either.
(lce rattling)
-l'll see you on the plane.
-All right.
-Oh, are you Russian?
-No.
No. you're supposed to say.
Am I rushin' where?
(Both laugh)
-That's funny.
-Thanks.
Hi. I'm sorry.
Is this seat taken?
-No, no.
-Great.
Ohh.
Sorry.
I hope this isn't a full flight.
-Yeah, I hope so, too.
-Sorry.
LINDA:
You know. I was ready to go.
I was at the airport.
and I met...
Iike. in the food court.
I met this guy. um...
and then he sat next to me
on the plane...
and we just hit it off.
His name's Arty. and we just...
He just made me laugh.
He's really funny and sweet...
and. um. sort of open.
We just talked the whole time.
the whole flight.
ARTY:.
She laughed in a way...
that made me feel like
she saw me.
I blew off
meeting--meeting Ann...
but we ended up spending
the weekend together.
And she's terrific.
LINDA: It was amazing.
We just had an amazing time.
It was definitely--
It was like out of a movie.
(Rock music playing)
* Do something real *
* Sidewalks chasing.
citizens racing *
* Do something real *
* Bloodhounds closing in
on opposing men *
* Do something real *
* Crows like rats
like cats on vacation *
* Do something real *
* You've been scrapped.
I'm trapped at the station *
* Small claims courts.
community snorts *
* It's fine
when it's so concealed *
* Do something real *
* Extra special happiness *
* Defined
by an endless field *
* Of nothing real *
* Do something real *
* Crap stripe exits.
examiners expect it *
* Do something real *
* Plot of rockets.
holy ghost markets *
* Do something real *
* Small claims courts.
community snorts *
* It's fine
when it's so concealed *
* Extra special happiness *
* Defined
by an endless field *
* Of nothing real *
This is, like,
the apex of the drama.
When we know
who the killer is...
I know.
The audience doesn't know yet.
But I know.
(Snaps fingers)
And this is where you see me
put the pieces together.