WwW.DownloadKing2.Tk
GO TO  SAIT
IZZY: Come on, Annie.
Don't be such a sIowcoach.
ANNIE: I'm going as fast as I can.
IZZY: Excuse me. So sorry.
-Excuse us.
-SIow down, Izzy.
We're shopping, not pIaying a rugby match.
There's Iess bruising in rugby, Annie.
We're taIking summer cIearance.
Things can get a bit brutaI.
I reckon it's worth it.
Imagine, summer cIothes aII year round.
No more jumpers and weIIies for us.
And I've heard that in LA,
we'II onIy need these to bIock out the sun.
The sun? Living in this country,
you wouIdn't know there was a sun.
(BOTH GIGGLE)
BOTH: (GASPING) SaIe!
BIast! Some twit put this on the wrong raiI.
It's not haIf-price.
BIonde ruIe number one.
Pink Iooks good with anything.
BIonde ruIe number two.
BOTH: Never pay retaiI.
Are you thinking what I'm thinking?
-FIip.
-And wave.
Excuse me.
-Yes?
-NigeI.
Such a regaI name.
But this garment
seems to be hung incorrectIy.
-It was on the haIf-price raiI.
-Oh.
I do hope we can make right
what is cIearIy an injustice.
(GIGGLING)
BriIIiant! You're a naturaI barrister, Izzy.
Even I aImost bought your argument.
I don't argue, Annie. I persuade.
MR. WOODS:
Have you IoveIies finished packing?
IZZY: AImost!
Annie, I can't beIieve we're Ieaving
for cousin EIIe's tomorrow.
There. Everything coIor-coded.
Me, too. This box is IabeIed...
Pink.
I miss Mum, Izzy.
I can't beIieve it's been two years
since we Iost her.
I miss Mum, too, Annie.
I wonder how we'II get on in CaIifornia.
Things have been so gray in this fIat
since Mum died.
I hope the sunny cIimate
wiII heIp Dad move on.
And up. He'II be running the entire
LAU EngIish Department in no time.
TaIking behind my back, are we?
No, we're just excited for the move.
Look, I know this move isn't easy.
And I appreciate your support.
It'II be fun. We'II see movie stars,
drink those mocha-Iatte-ccinos,
and get authentic BeverIy HiIIs nose jobs.
-What?
-Just joking, Dad.
I'm partiaI to the EngIish nose I have,
thank you very much.
Me, too. On both of you.
And have no fear.
The Woods team wiII fit in the LA IifestyIe
Iike fish fit with chips.
(THIS IS MEPLAYING)
This is my Iife
I'm on my own
Don't need anyone
To guide me down the road
I'm finding out who
Yeah, who I wanna be
This is me
This is my Iife
I'm in controI
Moving so fast
To where I wanna go
I'm shouting out
Who, yeah, who do you see?
MR. WOODS: Wow, Iook at that!
IZZY: These are houses?
Are you sure
this is the way to EIIe's house?
(CAR HORNS HONKING)
MR. WOODS: Those Yanks Iove their horns,
don't they?
Anyway, girIs,
I start teaching tomorrow at university
just a miIe
from EIIe's HoIIywood HiIIs mansion.
ANNIE: Wow, Izzy, BeverIy HiIIs
sure is different from back home.
Look at these cars.
Speaking of cars, teII us again
why we shipped in our Mini
from across the pond?
What? She's a peach.
(CAR HORN HONKING)
(GIRLS SCREAMING)
ANNIE: Wrong side of the road, Dad!
Wrong side of the road!
(TIRES SCREECHING)
AII right.
I'II have to try to remember that.
(SIGHS )
MR. WOODS: Here we are, girIs!
It's a paIace.
WeIcome to your new home, girIs.
(GIRLS GASPING)
(SQUEALING)
My, this pIace is awfuIIy pink.
So, it is quite a step up
from the oId, musty fIat back home, eh?
This is a step up from Buckingham PaIace.
Best of aII, it doesn't cost a penny.
Cousin EIIe spends most of her time
back in DC, Iobbying.
So she's Iet us, for now, squat here.
Take it over.
-It's Iike a dream.
-Oh, I suppose I can get used to it.
Do you think you couId get used to this?
(GIRLS GASPING)
EIIe has quite the view, eh?
IZZY: Can it get any better?
(DOG BARKING)
That sounds Iike Bruiser.
(BARKING CONTINUES )
(GASPING)
IZZY: Bruiser! Times two.
They're so sweet.
HeIIo, pretty boys. Hey.
Oh, Iook. From cousin EIIe.
''Dear IsabeIIe and AnnabeIIe,
''sorry I couIdn't be there to greet you,
''but Bruiser's IittIe nephews,
Spike and Butch,
''wiII weIcome you with open paws.
''AIways bIonde, cousin EIIe.''
Oh, how thoughtfuI.
WeII, I'm sorry, girIs,
but under no circumstances
are either of you to even consider
returning those dogs.
(ALL CHUCKLE)
We'II waIk with the dogs
and expIore our new hood.
Hood?
And we'II shop
for our first-day-of-schooI ensembIes.
GirIs, there's something
I've been meaning to teII you.
BOTH: It's amazing here, Dad. Love you.
Love you. Bye.
(POPMUSIC PLA YING)
Oh-oh, oh-oh, one, two, three
-Annie, Iook at aII these stores!
-It's fashion paradise.
It's so different from KentfieId.
That dress is perfect.
Rockin' to my own beat
Never stuck on repeat
I'm singing my own song
BeverIy HiIIs isn't very hiIIy.
(SIGHS ) But the sun is sunnier.
The hunks are hunkier.
And the junk food's organic.
-(GASPS ) Oh, my God, it's Karen!
-Who?
The Karen GIass Studio.
I've read about it
in the finest couture magazines.
The hoIy graiI of high-end runway appareI.
And now it stands before us, beckoning.
Posh practicaIIy summers inside that shop.
Last time I checked,
Becksy's shopping budget
was north of ours by about 40 zeroes.
A saIesperson's a saIesperson, Izzy.
Do what you do best. Persuade.
IZZY: Therefore, Evette...
Such a dynamic name.
...even though the stitching is subpar,
the coIor is off by at Ieast one shade
from the designer's runway prototype,
I'm stiII wiIIing
to negotiate a reasonabIe price
on behaIf of my sister
that wouId benefit both parties.
I can see you're a very reasonabIe person.
(CHUCKLING)
You'II have to forgive me, Iadies.
We get an awfuI Iot
of teIevision ceIebrities in this store.
-BOTH: Oh, oh, we're not...
-Oh, no, no. Oh, wait.
Yes, yes, of course.
You're the Riffraff Twins.
Loved the show.
We aIways say that the worId
can certainIy use a IittIe more riffraff,
but I'm afraid in this store,
sadIy, you're canceIed.
(GASPING)
Come back when you can pay fuII price
Iike big peopIe.
-WeII, that went swimmingIy.
-Like the Titanic.
Evette just did us a favor.
I mean,
she's just teIIing us we can do better.
We're in the greatest fashion shopping
postaI code in the worId.
Somewhere on these haIIowed streets
is a schooI wardrobe
that's gonna make the worId
stand up and say...
BOTH: Crap!
MR. WOODS: I'm sorry, Ioves.
You never gave me a chance to teII you.
Pac Prep requires uniforms.
This is as scratchy as tweed.
A sack of potatoes has more panache!
And not a thread of pink. It's criminaI.
Downright oppressive.
What sort of schooI are you sending us to?
(HORSES NEIGHING)
IZZY: LA? More Iike we Ianded in Oz.
MR. WOODS: This is
one of the best schooIs in the States.
And now, of course,
it's an even better schooI
because you two are attending.
ANNIE: (SCOFFING) Forget it, Dad.
These posh kids Iook Iike
they just came off an assembIy Iine.
MR. WOODS: Come on, girIs,
I'm trying hard here.
Let's see some smiIes.
BOTH: Anything for you, Dad.
AII right. Here we are.
Okay, IoveIies. Stiff upper Iips.
And Iet's see some cheery faces, eh?
Give us a kiss. Oh, thank you.
Now, just remember,
be your IoveabIe, adorabIe seIves,
and I promise you that, by my watch,
you'II have met
your first friend in three, two...
HIGGINS: I'm not here to be your friend.
I'm onIy here to educate you.
WeIcome, Iadies, to Pacific Preparatory.
I'm Headmistress Higgins.
I see here that, from past performance,
as weII as your father's
somewhat Iimited financiaI resources,
you've both been admitted on schoIarship.
PartiaI schoIarship,
ma'am.
CongratuIations, I'm sure.
Here at Pacific Prep,
we hoId our students to a higher standard,
as weII as a strict code of honor.
And such being the case,
I wiII need you to sign these.
-Oh, I'm not a barrister.
-Yet.
But I'd rather not sign
something I can't read.
HIGGINS: Then Iet me give you
the gist of the agreement.
The document mereIy enumerates
the myriad ways
in which students
might be tempted to pIagiarize,
Iie, cheat, and/ or steaI.
FaiIure to avoid
these temptations resuIts in expuIsion.
But how do we know what to avoid
if we can't read the fine print?
The Pacific Preparatory handbook.
Read it, Iearn it, Iove it,
and we'II get aIong just fine.
Now, your signatures, pIease.
Christopher Lopez!
(EX CLAIMS )
Yes, ma'am?
PIease print out the Iadies' scheduIes
and show them to their first cIass.
I'd Iove to show them around. Come on.
Ms. Chang!
Keep an eye on those two.
The Woods twins? Why, they seem IoveIy.
They possess the same perky DNA
as EIIe Woods.
EIIe Woods made a mockery
of these haIIowed haIIs with her
Fashion Arts eIective.
Which you got rid of two years ago.
And her Tai Chi Tuesdays.
Which you might consider reinstating.
You reaIIy wouId benefit.
I finaIIy got this institution back on track,
and I refuse to Iet the next generation
of bIonde Woods nymphs
destroy what I've created!
Tai Chi Tuesdays. I'm just saying.
Out!
(BELL RINGS )
Aren't you a IittIe young
to be a schooI administrator?
Oh, yeah, weII,
I do data entry and IT in the main offices
as my work study.
Work-study?
WeII, yeah. On fuII schoIarship at Pac Prep,
you need to work to pay off your tuition.
Ergo, work-study.
It's a good thing
we're onIy partiaI schoIarship, then.
Inputting data makes me nod off.
Not me. I can input data aII day Iong.
You into computers?
I faff around a bit.
-Faff?
-What Annie means is faff.
It means dabbIe.
Good to know. WeII, here we are.
This is first-period American History.
I'm in the same cIass,
but I need to swing
by the computer Iab first.
So here, Izzy.
I'II see you in cIass, Annie.
(EX CLAIMS )
-IZZY: Annie?
-Sorry.
HeIIo? Come on.
(BELL RINGS )
It's an Uber EIectronics phone.
My daddy's company isn't even
reIeasing them in stores tiII next year.
(GIGGLING)
It's a phone, video game consoIe,
MP3 pIayer, PDA, aII in one.
(GASPS ) It even has
HD hoIogram technoIogy.
-Oh!
-The cooIest thing ever.
I've gotta have one.
WeII, I might be abIe to convince my daddy
to get you one.
Whoa. Hottie airIines taxing into the gate.
I'II check us in with the teacher
whiIe you find us seats.
Okay.
Oh, my...
GoIdiIocks make Justin Bear happy.
What are you two going on about?
Hi, Mr. GoIden, I'm Izzy,
and I was toId I'm to check in with you.
Excuse me.
What do you think you are doing?
Um...
Sitting?
In my chair.
LiteraIIy, that's my chair.
My daddy paid for it.
Oh, I'm sorry. That pIaque is beautifuI.
You have a IoveIy seat.
Everyone knows, front row,
three across, in every cIassroom,
my seat.
Do I need to send out a memo
to every newbie dweeb that...
Are you, Iike, a frosted fIake or what?
I beg your pardon?
I just toId you that's my seat.
WeII, this is a bit awkward,
considering I've never even met you.
-I'm Izzy...
-Oh, okay! Am I being punked?
Is this a joke? 'Cause I'm not Iaughing.
Anyone?
Izzy, I saved you a seat here.
Excuse me.
There's two of them?
(BELL RINGS )
Look, Brad, be a sport.
Sharpen my penciIs.
Justin, the sharpener's three feet away.
You know that sound drives me crazy.
(WHIRRING)
(GROANS )
WeIcome back.
I am Mr. GoIden, your history teacher.
I wouId Iike to extend a speciaI weIcome to
-Annie and Izzy Woods.
-Hi.
-They're new here to Pac Prep.
-Hi there.
And they are...
(COUGHS ) Hot.
(ALL LAUGH)
From the UK, Mr. WhitIey,
which is actuaIIy quite ironic
when you consider how much cIass time
we have spent discussing
one of their country's greatest upsets.
WouId you care to guess
what that subject is?
How about you, Annie?
The... The...
The...
IZZY: Don't be shy, Annie.
You know the answer.
America, EngIand...
Everybody was upset.
David Beckham joining the GaIaxy?
(ALL LAUGH)
No. No, Izzy. No, actuaIIy.
(CLEARS THROAT)
We were actuaIIy taIking
about the American RevoIution.
Now, does anyone have any thoughts
about what advantages the Patriots had
that aIIowed them to defeat the EngIish?
Miss Donohugh.
Our forefathers' biggest advantage
was to keep the war weII inIand,
where Britain's massive navy
posed IittIe threat.
My forefathers crossed
''the pond'' on the MayfIower,
so we know a IittIe bit
about this sort of thing.
Yes. WeII, thank you.
-Uh-huh.
-WeII, anyone eIse? Any thoughts?
Yes, Izzy.
WeII, we came across recentIy
on Virgin AtIantic.
But I once read this briIIiant paper
that cIaimed that the arrogance
of the British miIitary
may weII have been the coIonists'...
I mean, the Patriots' greatest advantage.
You see,
our daft ancestors totaIIy underestimated
the keenness of you Yanks'
mostIy civiIian force,
and so faiIed to dispatch
EngIand's best soIdiers.
(MOUTHING)
WeII, that's wonderfuI, Izzy!
Thank you!
WeII, now, you see, cIass,
this is exactIy the kind of fresh insight
I'm aIways Iooking for.
You never toId me you thought
my coIonies paper was briIIiant.
And it was.
Not my fauIt you can't speak up.
IZZY: We just find that this dress code
makes us aII Iook Iike fIight attendants.
(LAUGHTER)
Did you reaIIy sit in Tiffany's seat?
What was it Iike?
CoId.
Bangers and mash sounds Iike hurI. Is it?
IZZY AND ANNIE: So-so.
Where'd you get those matching braceIets?
They are so high-end.
DonateIIa... No, Ron Herman.
-Covent Garden.
-At a fIea market.
-Who does your hair?
-Us.
WeII, why wouIdn't she
wanna do my homework?
-GIRL: Who does your naiIs?
-Us.
Just who do those
bottIe-bIonde bimbos think they are?
ActuaIIy, the buzz says
their summer-wheat-number-four
hair coIor is naturaI.
Not a singIe highIight.
And even more sick, their noses are reaI.
Come on.
That's a Dr. FeIdman number seven
if ever I've seen one.
Or two.
JUSTIN: Hey, what's up?
ASHLEY:
And Justin is totaIIy digging them.
Are you actuaIIy suggesting
that those Brit twits
pose a threat to moi?
WeII, Iike, reaIity check, Tiff.
They seem to be doing pretty weII.
Don't think I didn't notice.
As Sun Tzu said,
''Keep your friends cIose
and your enemies cIoser.''
Sun Tzu?
You mean, Iike, the sushi chef at Nobu?
(WHISPERING) Tiffany. Scram !
Hi. I'm Tiffany. Mind if I join?
If you don't mind sitting
with a pair of frosted fIakes.
I'm so sorry I was a jerk earIier.
I reaIIy think that you got
the wrong first impression of me.
(TIFFANY CLEARS THROAT)
It's just I have this vision thing,
see, where I need to sit in that same chair
in every cIass to see the board.
My vision is, Iike, 20/ one ziIIion.
I'm reaIIy insecure about it.
But, weII, I was rude.
I'm sorry. Can we, Iike, rewind?
BOTH: Of course.
I was a bit rude myseIf.
It's IsabeIIe, right?
-Izzy. And this is...
-Annie.
Oh, hi, Chris. Take a seat.
Yes, pIease. Take a seat.
Over there with your friends.
I think they're waiting for you.
But wait a minute. Chris is reaIIy nice.
-TIFFANY: Oh, and cute.
-Yeah.
TIFFANY: And that's what makes it
that much more tragic.
Tragic?
If you want to make it at Pac Prep,
I'd better bring you up to speed
on the dos and the don'ts.
For exampIe,
the saddest members of the FCC.
Don't stare at them !
FinanciaIIy ChaIIenged CIub.
(WHISPERS ) SchoIarship kids.
Poor unfortunates who wander these haIIs
Iike cash-strapped ghosts.
I see poor peopIe.
They're so ashamed of their situation.
WeII, they give us our space,
we give them theirs.
And never the two shaII meet.
I mean, why shove our obvious advantages
in their faces?
I mean, it's just so disrespectfuI.
Who is that crueI?
Just one tuition check away
from hopping on to the...
(WHIMPERS )
Big, yeIIow, pubIic...
(SQUEALING)
SchooI bus.
I mean, the stories that I have heard
about this kind of IifestyIe
is just so...
MiddIe-cIass.
Look, we shouId teII you that...
That we compIeteIy understand.
We'II do our best to respect others
who have Iess.
(LAUGHING) DeIish, then.
But come on. It's your first day.
Let's taIk about something
more reIevant to humanity, Iike...
(GASPS ) Lip gIoss.
(BOTH GIGGLE)
We couId've just toId her
we're on schoIarships, I guess.
And commit sociaI suicide on our first day?
We're EIIe Woods' cousins.
We have a reputation to uphoId.
And think of Dad.
We need to make a go of it here
for his sake.
I guess you're right.
But it was reaIIy kind of Tiffany
to Iet us come under her wing Iike that.
We couId've reaIIy mucked things up here.
She has got amazing styIe.
I've onIy seen shoes Iike that in magazines.
Look.
They shouId've just named
the whoIe pIace Tiffany Prep.
ASHLEY: Pretty cooI, huh?
Tiff's dad is the CEO of Uber EIectronics.
Uber EIectronics?
As in one of the biggest
computer technoIogy companies
in the worId?
The biggest.
Not a brag, 'cause I'm not Iike that.
Just a fact,
in case you find yourseIves
in a conversation
about my famiIy's incredibIe weaIth.
(BAD BRITISH ACCENT)
WouIdn't want you to not have the 41 1 .
-DRIVER: Your car, Miss Donohugh.
-Oh! There's our ride.
She drives an aircraft carrier.
You two need a Iift?
No, thanks. Our dad's picking us up.
Another time?
DefiniteIy. Like, tomorrow?
Mmm ! You are on. Tomorrow, then.
Bag, CharIes.
Certain days you wake up
And it's Iike aII the worId's...
So I said,
''HeIIo? What part of 'decaf soy Iatte'
don't you understand?''
(GIRLS LAUGHING)
HoIa, SyIvia.
Good morning, Miss Donohugh.
Right after Iunch, Ash and I took the time
to stack those trays for you.
We thought you couId use a hand.
Mmm-hmm.
Have a beautifuI day.
Poor woman. She works so hard.
So sweet of you to heIp her.
AIthough, I have to say
she didn't Iook too happy about it.
WeII, often,
when supporting the Iess fortunate,
you're onIy met with scorn.
(GROANING)
Gum? I have pink and green.
Uh-huh, that's right
This is the pIace to be tonight
WeIcome to the party
Aw, yeah
This is my party
And it's aII about me
ANNIE: This must be Iike
Iiving in the Victoria and AIbert Museum.
We actuaIIy studied this piece
in our art appreciation cIass Iast year.
This is a beautifuI reproduction.
Reproduction?
(SCOFFS )
WeIcome to the party
Aw, yeah
Your estate is amazing.
StabIes, pooIs, heIipad, tennis courts.
The onIy thing missing is...
Two trampoIines?
One for me
and one for my personaI trainer.
DoIph swears that it is the best workout
you'II ever have.
You ever been on one?
-When I was younger, I, you know...
-''DabbIed.''
Come on, siIIy.
I'II teach you a few things.
Nothing too scary.
Let's try something easy Iike this.
Ooh!
BriIIiant, Tiff.
Like this?
Show-off.
Okay, that was pretty good. Try this.
(GASPS )
Wow! Let me try.
Oh, gee, you're pretty good.
How about this?
(GASPS ) Wow! How about this?
Isn't this fun?
(LAUGHING)
How about this?
(SCREAMS )
(EX CLAIMS )
Tiffany, are you aII right?
I'II have my driver take you home.
(TIFFANY GROANS )
MR. GOLDEN:
And now, cIass, your quiz resuIts.
Izzy.
Annie, here's yours.
I did great.
(SIGHS )
ANNIE: Don't worry, Izzy. I'II tutor you.
MR. GOLDEN:
The constitution is pure poetry.
And now, each one of you
is going to have the chance
to recite this patriotic work of art
up here in front of the entire cIass,
beginning with the student
with the highest grade-point average.
Ladies and gentIemen,
aII the way from the UK,
Miss AnnabeIIe Woods!
You'II be fine.
MR. GOLDEN: Miss Woods?
(STUTTERING) We... The...
(CLASS LAUGHING)
-We the peopIe...
-MR. GOLDEN: Okay. Okay.
Everybody, settIe down.
-PIease continue, Miss Woods.
-ANNIE: Oh...
Hey, beautifuI. Which one are you?
-Excuse me?
-Which twin? Iggy or Annie?
Iggy.
My friends just caII me Izzy.
Yeah. Yeah.
It's that whoIe, you know,
Iost in transIation thing,
since you speak...
...read The Odyssey again.
We've read it the Iast two years.
(CLICKING)
You know, because you're from EngIand
and you speak...
EngIish.
ObviousIy.
Yeah.
Hey, nerd, get another irritating habit.
So, where was I?
Oh, you got a date
for the siIver beIIs dance?
Hey, shouIdn't you be asking Tiffany?
Everybody says you're an item.
WeII, some of the time.
Hey, Tiffany Donohugh doesn't own me.
(TIFFANY EX CLAIMS )
You're keeping your enemies reaIIy cIose,
if you ask me.
I'm paying them a IittIe visit tomorrow
to ''study.''
The onIy thing I'm going to ''study''
is them.
There's gotta be a skeIeton
in their pink perky cIosets.
(SIGHS )
You're in a mess
You shouId see yourseIf
Listen to you
You sound Iike someone eIse
-Hi!
-Come on in.
We were just getting
to the battIes of Concord and Lexington.
Mmm, I'd rather hear about the battIes
between Armani versus Versace.
(BOTH LAUGHING)
(EX CLAIMING)
I bareIy passed British history.
Now I have to sIog through American?
It's too much. I give up.
It's stiII earIy in the term.
You're a great debater.
You need to use
that confidence for the test.
Easy to say when you're getting an A,
and I'm bareIy passing.
MR. WOODS: Tea time.
This is our handsome, schoIarIy,
and currentIy Iess-than-weII-dressed dad.
Dad, this is Tiffany.
-HeIIo.
-Hi.
I Iove the apron.
I wish my own father couId just reIax
and enjoy being common.
(LAUGHS ) No offense.
None taken, I think.
(BARKING)
Oops! Nature caIIs.
Bye-bye, feIIows.
Your daughters are awesome.
And they're aIready so popuIar.
-WeII, wish I couId take credit. I...
-Is that your wife?
Oh, yes.
She's beautifuI. I can see where the girIs
got their good Iooks. No offense.
WeII, that time maybe a IittIe offense.
And I Iove that painting.
Oh, no. That is EIIe Woods.
Oh, yes! EIIe Woods.
ActuaIIy, I've heard of her.
Headmistress Higgins
speaks of her often and fondIy.
Yes, she is a Pac Prep graduate
and a favorite cousin.
This is her house, actuaIIy.
I certainIy couIdn't afford a paIace Iike this
on my professor's saIary.
-Oh, sure.
-That's why I'm so gIad that Izzy and Annie
have a good friend Iike you to study with,
because it's very important
they work hard to keep their schoIarships.
WeII, then, it is very Iucky
that the girIs have schoIarships.
(LAUGHS )
TIFFANY: So, untiI we meet again,
which I guess wiII be tomorrow
at the aIumni dance, hmm?
It promises to be the hottest in years.
AIumni dance?
We actuaIIy weren't aware
of any schooI dance.
-Are we invited?
-Of course.
Oh, my God. You have to come.
It's a Pac Prep tradition
on the pooI deck of the Queen Mary.
You know, swimming,
hot dogs on the griII, fireworks.
(ALL GIGGLE)
It's just aII-American beach boy stuff,
which sophisticated British foIk
might find too common.
-Oh, stop it. It sounds amazing.
-Okay. So, what's everyone wearing?
I'm just wearing my white Armani bikini.
If you wear a hot bathing suit, I promise...
-Yeah.
-Okay.
...you are gonna make a spIash.
(JAZZ MUSIC PLA YING)
-WeIcome to the Pac Prep reunion, Iadies.
-Thank you.
Maybe you and Chris can pIay baII, Annie.
OnIy in LA
couId you have a pooI party on a ship.
-Why didn't we move here sooner?
-Here's your program.
Thank you.
I wonder what Chris Lopez
Iooks Iike in swimming trunks.
(GASPS ) It's fascinating.
Since when did you care about ships?
Since the brochure came in pink.
Ladies, you must absoIuteIy
be Annie and Izzy Woods.
It's a pIeasure to meet you.
Is that the way to the pooI party?
ActuaIIy, Miss Donohugh
sent me personaIIy
to direct you Iadies to the event.
-Right this way.
-ReaIIy?
She insists upon the VIP entrance.
(BOTH EX CLAIMING)
-Okay. Thanks.
-Thank you.
(LAUGHING)
He was nice.
(JAZZ MUSIC GROWS LOUDER)
VIP entrances are so dark.
That Tiffany,
aIways Iooking out for her friends.
(CROWD CHATTERING)
It's as bright as the sun.
I think I hear peopIe swimming.
(BOTH SCREAMING)
(CRASHING)
(PLAYING OFF-KEY)
(GASPING)
BOY: What?
(CROWD MURMURING)
Annie, Izzy,
your faces are aImost as pathetic
as your schoIarship appIications.
(ALL GASPING)
HIGGINS:
Do you care to expIain yourseIf, Iadies?
I'm sure there's a Iogic
to this whoIIy undignified dispIay.
(STAMMERING)
(ANNIE SIGHING)
-How humiIiating. TotaIIy exposed.
-In so many ways.
I can't beIieve Tiffany turned out to be
a totaI snake in the grass.
There's onIy one thing to do.
BOTH: Pack.
HeIIo, Ioves. You're home earIy.
Hmm. My paternaI instinct
teIIs me something's wrong.
BOTH: We have to move.
-Pardon?
-We're moving back to EngIand.
Everybody at schooI thinks we're Iying gits.
'Cause we are Iying gits.
Professor Dad confused.
We just wanted to make friends,
and Tiffany made it so easy.
TiII she found out
we're schoIarship students
and ratted on us
in front of the entire schooI.
In our swimming costumes.
Wait. She didn't know
you were schoIarship students?
ANNIE: No. We kept it a secret.
Oh, I'm sorry.
I'm afraid I Iet that one
out of the bag myseIf, girIs.
-You toId her?
-Yeah, guiIty. Why shouIdn't I?
AII that matters at Pac Prep
is how much money you have
and what kind of car you drive.
If you're not Iike them, they shun you.
We just wanted to fit in, that's aII.
And Iook where it got you.
For two girIs who couIdn't be more aIike,
you are 100% originaIs.
Don't Iet Pac Prep change you.
You change Pac Prep.
But first, we have to admit...
We are compIete and utter idiots.
Chris, you were nice enough
to reach out to us.
We were too bIinded by Tiffany's bIing.
Can you ever forgive us?
(WHISPERING)
I think we have room for one... Two more.
Annie and Izzy, this is Vivek. That's Marcie.
You two are
the most freakishIy fIaxen human beings
I've ever Iaid my eyes on.
BOTH: Thank you.
CHRIS: And that's Rainbow in the middIe.
I take it your parents were very creative.
No, they're hippies.
We Iive in a yurt in Topanga.
(EX CLAIMS )
Got me in the eyes. Oh, why in the eyes?
(VIVEK LAUGHING)
IZZY: Just be yourseIf, Chris.
Annie's kind of shy.
Izzy, I just... I get so tongue-tied.
Look, if you want to go out with Annie,
find the confidence.
That's what girIs go for.
(BOTH LAUGHING)
-Chris...
-Thanks.
Chris, you're so funny.
Okay, heIp me out. Pretend to be Annie.
Hi, Annie. Okay, just...
In case you haven't noticed,
I kind of, Iike, dig you,
and I think you have
the most eyes ever.
Chris, most beautifuI eyes.
(SIGHS )
-It's okay.
-I know.
The good news is Annie Iikes you, too,
so go for it.
But you hurt her, I break your neck.
AII right. Soup's on.
I never knew the Boston Tea Party
was aII our fauIt.
Why do we have to Iearn
so much about history?
I mean, what's wrong with the future?
As Iong as Mr. GoIden doesn't make me
speak in pubIic, I'm happy.
You know how to get rid
of that fear of pubIic speaking, don't you?
Avoid the pubIic?
Transport yourseIf.
Come on, Annie.
AII right, now. CIose your eyes.
And open your mind, and go to a moment
that you were happiest in your entire Iife.
Where are you?
ANNIE.: I'm in our KentfieId cottage.
It's autumn.
The Ieaves are just starting to turn.
Having a cup of tea with Dad,
Mum
and Izzy.
When you're feeIing the pressure,
just go to that happy pIace.
Thank you. I'II definiteIy try that next time.
It's a humiIiating affIiction.
VIVEK: I know what you mean.
Every morning, I gotta go through
that big, white gate at Pretentious Prep
to take another week's
worth of punishment from those snobs.
It's just so humiIiating.
Maybe there's a way we can
make it better for aII of us.
Yeah, doubtfuI.
Tiffany's turned everyone against us.
Whenever we try and get invoIved,
they just rag on us
for being Iess fortunate.
There's strength in numbers.
We just have to be ourseIves,
stick together...
-Strength in numbers.
-...and refuse to be intimidated.
WeII, that sounds good,
but I sure don't feeI Iike myseIf
in that stupid uniform.
Yeah, me, either. They caII me Rainbow,
but I'm just another drab
bIue bIazer in the crowd.
Maybe we couId change that.
How?
(ORDINARYSUPERSTAR PLAYING)
(ALL LAUGHING)
Hey, you there
You stand out in a crowd
Yes, yes, yes.
Nothin'about you is ordinary
Hey, you there
I hope you feeI proud
It seems you settIed the score aIready
I Iike this one.
You're the hands-down winner
You're the champion
You're the record taker
Record breaker number one
Another day for an ordinary superstar...
HeIIo, Mutz. These are so sick.
OnIy Justin has a pair,
which, of course, Tiffany bought for him.
These are, Iike, my dream shoe.
Dream?
$400 for a pair of trainers?
Seems more Iike a nightmare.
$400?
Hmm.
Again, this was on the saIes tabIe,
but it's cIearIy not on saIe.
-FIip...
-And wave.
(CLEARS THROAT)
Excuse me,
but this materiaI
was erroneousIy pIaced on the saIes tabIe.
Hmm?
So we shouIdn't be penaIized
for the mistakes made by your empIoyees.
We desperateIy need this materiaI.
Won't you heIp us? Ruth?
(GIRLS GIGGLING)
Okay, okay, you win, you win.
I'II give you the saIe price.
Just stop that hair-twitchy thing.
-It's creeping me out.
-BOTH: DeaI.
You're the hands-down winner
You're the champion
You're the record taker
Record breaker number one
WeII, uh-oh
Ready, everyone?
Let's show our true coIors, shaII we?
Let's do this thing.
Another day
for an ordinary superstar
We are ordinary superstars
My office. Now.
ArticIe 6.2E does not forbid
accessorizing said skirt.
An oversight that wiII be corrected.
However, articIe eight, paragraph three
expressIy states the uniform shirt
must be monochromatic.
Therefore, I have no choice
but to order detention.
With aII due respect, Headmistress,
I think you're confusing
articIe eight, paragraph three
with articIe three, paragraph eight.
ArticIe two.
Tights must be worn in soIid coIors.
ArticIe seven.
MaIe students must wear neckties.
Which they are.
Hmm.
I heard the headmistress
aImost caIIed SWAT.
-You didn't get detention?
-Why shouId we?
TechnicaIIy, we're not breaking any ruIes.
See, we're dressing around the code.
Okay, I don't know how it works,
but it does.
I wanna dress around the code.
Hook a sister up!
GIRL: Yeah, me, too.
Fake bag. Fake. Fake. TerribIy fake.
I am just so tired of everybody
Iooking to me to set trends.
It's exhausting, you know?
Looks Iike you're getting a break.
What are you gonna do?
Divide and conquer.
What happened
to keeping your enemies cIose?
Just go get my Iunch.
-We'II see you after cIass.
-Great.
Okay. Bye.
Wow. Your new outfits Iook terrific.
BOTH: Thank you.
Do you know who SyIvia's crush is?
BOTH: Mr. GoIden?
Mmm-hmm.
GirI has got it bad.
But she can't get up the nerve
to taIk to him.
BOTH: WeII, we've got a cure for that.
SyIvia, if you want to catch a boy's eyes...
I'm aII ears.
-AII it takes is a IittIe fIip...
-And wave.
-Works every time.
-What?
Senor GoIden.
I couIdn't heIp but overhear your Iecture
on the US Constitution.
I have often debated the infIuence
of the Magna Carta on our BiII of Rights.
(SOUL MUSIC PLA YING)
I'm Gary.
SyIvia.
Yes! Yes!
Where's your dad?
Oh, he was giving a Iecture
and he warned us he'd be Iate.
SYLVIA: Brad, I never couId have
finished in time without you.
No probIem.
HoIa!
ALL: Hi, SyIvia.
Hey, guys.
What are you aII stiII doing here?
-Oh, our Iift is Iate. What about you?
-Same here.
(CAR HORN HONKS )
Oh, Pop must be doing the aII-night
Japanese stock exchange.
Sent the gardener. Hate that.
WeII, good night, everybody.
ANNIE: Good night, Brad.
IZZY: See you Iater.
See you, Brad. What was that about?
IZZY: You can trust us.
ANNIE: We wouIdn't dare say anything.
CHRIS: Come on, SyIvia,
we're cooI with him.
Brad's on schoIarship just Iike you.
ALL: He is?
He aIways asks to work
the Iate shift with me
to keep it on the down-Iow.
Nobody knows but me, right?
Yeah, yeah.
(SPEAKING SPANISH)
I got a hot date tonight
with a moIdy oId stiff.
MR. GOLDEN: SyIvia?
AII Iocked up. Ready to go?
We're going to see the mummy exhibit
at the city museum.
I'II go warm up the car.
Come on now, baby
Maybe tonight we'II make a IittIe history.
BOTH: FIip and wave aIways works.
History. Oh, no!
BIast!
I Ieft my history notebook
in Mr. GoIden's cIassroom.
Never fear.
TripIe-zero key.
It's a master key that unIocks
every door in the schooI.
Come on, I'II Iet you in.
Is that aIIowed?
WeII, technicaIIy,
it's onIy for my work-study,
but, hey, if this key doesn't work,
you can't study.
We need those notes.
I need those notes, Annie.
I don't know, guys...
It's cooI, Annie.
I'II go. What's the worst that can happen?
Watch your step, Izzy.
I thought you said this was aIIowed.
TechnicaIIy aIIowed, but who wants
to expIain technicaIities to him?
(DOOR CLOSES )
(SHUSHING)
It's not here.
He probabIy just Iocked it in his office.
Come on, Iet's Iook in there.
-Is that it?
-Yes!
Mission accompIished.
It was a no-brainer, Annie.
You two make quite the team.
You have no idea.
(CAR HORN HONKING)
Oh, there's Dad. Good night.
Good night.
-GirIs!
-BOTH: Hi, Dad.
-How was schooI today?
-BOTH: It was fine.
MR. WOODS: ExceIIent.
IZZY: 1 1th Amendment.
Paying fuII price for an Armani
or Prada three-piece.
Immunity of States to foreign suits.
-Yes!
-Yes! Okay.
Second Amendment.
Picture Annie in a sIeeveIess top.
Right to bear arms?
-Yes!
-Oh!
Fourth Amendment.
Annie's shopping
at a haIf-price saIe at Harrods.
-Searches and seizures!
-Yes!
Annie's notes reaIIy work.
She is reaIIy cIever.
-Izzy.
-You're weIcome.
Annie. Izzy, Annie.
Izzy. Izzy!
-What's up, backstabber?
-I beg your pardon?
I saw you and Chris
behind the bIeachers at Iunch,
exchanging breath mints with no hands.
-I don't know what you're taIking about.
-Drop the act, Izzy!
But I'm not...
OnIy a troII wouId steaI
her sister's boyfriends.
Now, 13th Amendment.
(SIGHS )
Just Iook how happy Annie is with Chris.
I've done some awfuI things in my day,
but that is the worst.
The Iowest of the Iow.
(CHRIS LAUGHING)
Do you understand now?
I got it. I got it.
In just a few moments,
you fortunate peopIe
wiII be embarking upon
an amazing journey...
Hey, don't worry, Izzy.
At Ieast there wiII stiII
be one Woods sister Ieft
when you fIunk the finaI
and Iose your schoIarship.
-What do you mean?
-Nothing.
It's just that, weII, I overheard Annie saying
that she wasn't gonna Iet you
drag her down with you, is aII.
(WHIRRING)
You done with the sharpener?
The test is getting ready to start.
Bye.
MR. GOLDEN: At the count of three,
you may aII turn over
your test papers and begin.
One, two...
(ALARM RINGING)
No! Not a fire aIarm !
Not now!
I just want to get the test over with.
I was about to bring my A-game.
-Oh, no!
-What?
My braceIet. Annie gave it to me
and I've never taken it off.
It wiII break her heart if I Iose it.
It's probabIy in the courtyard.
Come on, I'II heIp you find it.
-Thanks.
-Come on.
AII right, kids, faIse aIarm.
Everybody back into the cIassroom.
We stiII have time to take that test.
That's not fair, Mr. GoIden.
I mean, we prepped hard for this exam,
understanding we'd have
a fuII hour to enjoy it.
Good point.
TeII you what we'II do just this once.
We'II use the rest of the hour
to study for the test,
which we'II then
take tomorrow in aII its gIory!
-Yes!
-MR. GOLDEN: Yay!
GIRL: It'II be great.
BOY: That's so cooI.
(GROANS )
(BELL RINGS )
Three, two...
One.
(SIGHS )
PIease begin.
(PEN CLICKING)
Dude, stop with the pen.
You're driving me nuts.
(TIMER DINGS )
I can't beIieve how fast you finished.
Oh, I probabIy missed some,
but it wiII stiII be my best grade yet.
We'II know tomorrow.
This Uber phone is so cooI.
Dude, this thing has a GPS system.
-Look, we're right there.
-Let me see.
Did I say you couId touch it?
Hey, Izzy.
If you ever get tired
of being treated Iike that,
we know some Iess fortunates
who wouId be fortunate to have you.
I don't know what you're taIking about.
I think this has been
a Iearning experience for aII of us.
How on earth did you do better than me?
WeII, I won't say it's in my genes,
but I worked hard for it.
You aII scored very weII on this test,
and I wouId Iike
to congratuIate those of you
who were abIe to do it
with a IittIe integrity.
UnfortunateIy,
I'm disappointed
to have to announce we appear
to have cheaters in our midst.
(ALL GASP)
(ALL MURMURING)
Miss Woods, Mr. Lopez, pIease stand.
(MURMURING CONTINUES )
Just the one Miss Woods.
IsabeIIe.
I'd Iike you both to recaII
the honor code you signed
upon enroIIing at Pac Prep.
What is the punishment
for cheating, Miss Woods?
ExpuIsion.
Mr. GoIden discovered a tripIe-zero key
broken off in the Iock
to his office yesterday
after the faIse fire aIarm.
Chris, you are the onIy person
in this institution trusted with such a key.
If you can produce yours,
I'm sure we can cIear the whoIe matter up.
Yeah, absoIuteIy.
It's right...
Here.
Yours is broken, too.
Pity.
Miss Woods, you and your sister
seem to share a great deaI.
She's my best friend.
You aIso share a pair of braceIets?
Yours being sIightIy more pink?
Yes, ma'am.
But recentIy I've mispIaced it.
-Mr. GoIden found it in his Iocked office.
-That's it!
The same Iocked office
where the answers to your tests
were stored in his computer.
(BRACELET CLACKS )
The same answers that we found
taped beneath your desk.
Oh, Izzy.
It was aII my fauIt. I was the one...
UnfortunateIy, I have no other option
than to pronounce the two of you...
Wait!
Sorry. I couIdn't stop her.
Excuse me. This does not concern you yet.
It does.
Not as a sister, but as a student.
And every student at Pac Prep
has certain rights.
''No student may be expeIIed
without a fair hearing
''before a jury of their peers.''
Something caIIed the...
''Student Jurors CounciI.''
She's right. I doubIe-checked.
You had some spare time
whiIe you were bIocking the door?
It's right here in bIack and white.
''No matter how guiIty
the accused may seem,
''they do have a right
to defend themseIves.''
Very weII, Miss Woods.
If it's a pubIic spectacIe you want,
a pubIic spectacIe you wiII get.
Annie, we are so sorry.
Everyone knows about Chris and Izzy.
-What?
-WeII, I guess not everyone.
Just never wouId have beIieved
they'd cheat to make you Iook bad.
It is so gross how a guy can break up BFFs.
Even sister BFFs.
IZZY: Annie, wait!
TIFFANY: If you need to taIk,
we're here for you.
PIease stop!
Annie, you don't think we did this, do you?
Let's just say I've heard enough!
ExpuIsion?
Did you do this so we'd have
to move back to EngIand?
-I didn't do it, Dad.
-Then teII me what happened.
There's nothing to teII.
I studied my backside off,
and I scored weII on that test!
But since even my own sister
doesn't beIieve me,
I know I'm in massive troubIe.
Annie?
Annie, say something.
I don't speak to Benedict ArnoIds.
Do you know who he is, Izzy,
or do I need to print up
a crib sheet for you?
That was uncaIIed for, don't you think?
She's never scored higher than me.
She studied hard for that test, Annie.
And she had
the best history tutor in the worId. You.
Are you certain there might not be
a IittIe bit of jeaIousy
invoIved here, perhaps?
She stoIe my score! And the boy I fancy!
Enough!
Look, I know this move
has been difficuIt for the both of you,
but I don't buy Izzy doing
either of those things,
and I don't think you do, either.
Izzy is your sister, your buiIt-in best mate.
TaIk to her.
Before it's too Iate.
(IZZY CRYING)
Do you swear you didn't do it?
I swear on my BCBG dress.
The one I found on saIe with a pink...
BOTH: HaIter neck.
(SNIFFLES )
Yeah, that one.
I've never Iied to you, Annie.
I wiII never Iie to you, ever.
Chris, I swear I never...
We don't have to taIk about it.
Tiffany thought I was you,
and toId me I was a troII
for making out with Chris
behind the bIeachers.
I know now.
It's fine.
It's not fine because it's not true!
I'm not with Chris! That never happened!
Oh, my gosh.
Tiffany was compIeteIy tricking us.
She must've known I was me,
pretended I was you
to drive a wedge right between us.
What a cow!
But we might be bigger cows
for Ietting her come between us.
AImost.
Annie, I can't fight Higgins without you.
You won't have to.
I'm with you.
AIways.
(SNIFFLES )
You sort of owe Chris an apoIogy, too.
Oh, I know. I feeI so daft.
Make you a deaI.
You get me off the hook, and I'II make sure
Chris finaIIy asks you out.
(CHUCKLES )
(FINGERS SNAPPING)
Did you cheat?
AbsoIuteIy not.
Then I'm reaIIy sorry I thought you did.
For a girI who's right so often,
you sure have been wrong a Iot IateIy.
(CHUCKLES )
But not anymore.
Thanks, everyone, for sticking by us.
Nobody at schooI is even taIking to us.
We're not Iike that.
If you say you didn't cheat, we beIieve you.
Even I beIieved they were guiIty
untiI they toId me the rest of the story.
Okay. We have untiI Friday
to prove your innocence.
Everybody know what to do?
ANNIE: Ready?
ALL: Break!
Sony, G, are you ready
To kick out the jams?
We're gonna go rock steady
A purchase, a porcupine
A peanut pomegranate
Damn it, yes
'Cause that's how we send it
Down, down
Right through the hoop
Got the chief on the horn
I got a scoop here
Extra, extra
Read aII about it
BTK's top biIIing
So shout it
Yeah
We need to see how easy it is
to gain access to your backpack, Chris.
Seems quite secure.
There's onIy one other student
that I know of with that same backpack.
Tiffany.
Tomorrow, then.
Bag, CharIes.
Izzy, do you remember
our matching CIaire Dejune
designer snappy purses?
They aIso came with a IittIe key.
And when you Iost yours...
We used yours to open mine.
One key opened both purses.
Snappy purse?
ANNIE: So, have you got anything, Vivek?
You'II be happy to know we found nothing.
But we did find a red smudge
and we think it couId be bIood.
Since we're not discussing a homicide...
I admit we're a bit Iight on evidence
if aII we've got is a smudge mark.
But sometimes a great barrister
can make the best of what IittIe there is.
Barrister? How couId a dude
from Starbucks be any heIp to us?
-A Iawyer.
-ALL: Oh!
IZZY: Which we don't have.
I was taIking about you, Izzy.
There isn't a better barrister
in the whoIe worId,
especiaIIy once you've been prepped by me
and my crack IegaI team.
Oh, yeah. AII right.
CHRIS: Yeah. Yeah.
(GAVEL BANGING)
HIGGINS: AII rise.
I now caII the Student Jurors CounciI
hearing into session.
You may be seated.
This is the case of Pacific Prep
versus Woods and Lopez.
The crime, trespassing,
breaking and entering, cheating.
Are the accused present?
We are, Headmistress Higgins.
And who shaII be
defending you, Miss Woods?
I, IsabeIIe Woods, wiII be representing
both Mr. Lopez and myseIf, ma'am,
with co-counseI and advice from my sister,
Miss AnnabeIIe Woods.
And for the prosecution?
Tiffany Donohugh and Justin WhitIey,
with the aid of our IegaI assistant
AshIey Meadows.
We wiII humbIy represent
the student body of Pacific Prep.
Hey, don't get too comfortabIe.
This won't take Iong.
(PEOPLE LAUGHING)
(MURMURING)
The prosecution caIIs Mr. GoIden.
Yes, this is the key I found
broken off in the Iock.
Can you teII me if this haIf matches?
Why, yes.
As far as you know, Mr. GoIden,
how many tripIe-zero keys
are in existence?
Just the one.
And who does this key beIong to?
It beIongs to Chris Lopez.
Mr. GoIden, can you teII me what this is?
This is the cheat sheet
with the answers to my history test on it.
And where did you find it?
I found it taped underneath
the desk of IsabeIIe Woods.
(PEOPLE MURMURING)
Can you point her out, pIease?
Yes. She's the twin with the ponytaiI.
Mr. GoIden, was there
anything eIse unusuaI
about your office on the day in question?
WeII, the braceIet.
This braceIet?
And you found this where?
On the fIoor of my office.
Seems Iike I've seen
this braceIet somewhere before.
Annie Woods, you have one
just Iike this, don't you?
And Izzy Woods, you...
It's mine.
(PEOPLE GASPING)
That's odd. Hmm.
No more questions.
HIGGINS: IsabeIIe Woods,
you may present your case.
(CLEARS THROAT)
A Jansport Hampton X25 backpack.
A high-end modeI that Mr. Lopez
and one other Pac Prep student uses.
The counseI wiII note that the prosecution
has one such backpack under their tabIe.
Miss Donohugh, may I see
the key to your backpack?
(LAUGHS ) ObviousIy, I object.
This is ridicuIous.
Just give her the key, and Iet's move on.
As I wiII show,
this brand of backpack
comes with a factory key.
Any of which can open any other version
of the same backpack.
(MURMURING)
Proving that anyone
with this styIe of backpack
couId've used their key
to gain access to Chris'...
I mean, Mr. Lopez's backpack,
steaIing his tripIe-zero key
and committing the crime.
TIFFANY: That's my backpack key.
Are you so desperate that you're...
I'm simpIy stating a fact. Thank you.
WeII, whoop-dee-doo!
What, did my IittIe backpack roII itseIf over
and put the cheat sheet beneath your desk?
Miss Woods, pIease continue.
The defense is caIIing Mr. WhitIey.
You can caII me Justin, babe.
And you can caII me Miss Woods.
Mr. WhitIey, where were you
right before the fire aIarm
was mysteriousIy puIIed?
I was in the back of the cIassroom,
sharpening my penciI.
You done with the sharpener?
Right next to you.
Oh, that's true.
I need to confirm with my co-counseI.
BOTH GIRLS: Oops!
Now what? It's aII we've got.
Fingerprint stuff?
Oh, it's so inconcIusive. They'II Iaugh at us.
I'm finished.
We've got nothing convincing.
We might as weII just give up.
Thanks for trying to heIp.
It's such a shame, isn't it?
Beaten by smarmy gits that fIounce around
in $400 hand-painted trainers.
ANNIE.: Oh, my gosh. Vivek's pictures.
Of course! It makes perfect sense.
Tick-tock, Iadies.
If you're ready to end this thing,
I think we are aII ready to ask...
For a recess!
You can't!
Par section 4.4B,
we are aIIowed one, ma'am.
Tear this pIace apart.
We've got to find those photos.
The ones with the IittIe red marks
under Mr. GoIden's desk.
I got 'em !
ANNIE: (GASPS ) There on the fIoor.
Scuff marks.
Justin's one-of-a-kind,
red-sneaker scuff marks.
Look, this is Mr. GoIden's paper.
It's his morning paper.
It's got the date right in the headIine.
This evidence has its own time stamp.
It's the smoking gun.
For safekeeping.
Look.
Maybe they aren't as cooI
as they are in court.
ANNIE: Let's go.
You're going to have
to get Justin to break on the stand, Izzy.
Oh, I'II make him break, aII right, Iike a...
Oh, my pen.
Enjoy pubIic schooI, Woodsy.
HeIIo?
(CHATTERING)
Where is she?
(GAVEL BANGS )
HIGGINS: Recess is over.
I caII this triaI back
to session, Miss Woods.
Chop-chop.
(WHISPERING) Where's Izzy?
Annie, you gotta take this over.
Time's running out.
I can't.
Not in front of aII these peopIe.
WeII?
Miss Woods, if you
have nothing more to say,
I presume the defense rests,
and the verdict can be rendered.
Come on, Annie, you have
the evidence, now naiI 'em.
(SIGHING)
ANNIE.: Go to your happy pIace.
Go to your happy pIace.
Miss Woods?
One moment, pIease, Headmistress.
I'II get Izzy.
Show you who I am
For the record, Headmistress,
my co-counseI Annie has...
Taken it, I'm afraid.
She won't be assisting me at the moment.
So, if it pIeases the court,
I, IsabeIIe Woods,
wouId Iike to recaII Mr. WhitIey.
Just one more time.
Forgive me, I'm bIonde.
(LAUGHING)
Where were you
when the fire aIarm sounded?
HeIIo? Can anybody hear me? HeIIo?
(TOILET FLUSHES )
Are you aware
of a fashion trend known as Mutz?
I don't foIIow fashion.
No need. I'm not that insecure.
Mutz are very expensive trainers.
Sneakers, if you wiII.
The counseI wiII note
that Mr. WhitIey is wearing
a pair at this very moment.
May I see one?
Whatever fIoats your boat, bIondie.
The Iatest must-have design
comes in a sensationaI scarIet.
One of the many coIors
students have onIy recentIy begun to wear
since they Iearned
how to dress around the code.
Because they're hand-painted,
this styIe of shoe
Ieaves behind a very unique scuff mark.
Chris?
Oh, pIease. A scuff mark?
That's what we overpay custodians
to mop up.
(SIGHING)
(SCREAMING)
Mr. WhitIey, have you ever been inside
Mr. GoIden's private office?
Never.
Are you sure?
I'm positive.
WeII then, can you expIain
how the exact same scuff marks
came to be on Mr. GoIden's fIoor?
(PEOPLE GASPING)
I object!
What exact same scuff marks?
(COUGHING)
My briefcase. I have tooIs in my briefcase.
If it pIeases the court,
the defense wouId Iike
to submit photographic evidence...
(WHISPERS ) I've got Izzy's briefcase.
Okay.
This is Annie's briefcase.
(STAMMERING) I seem to have mispIaced...
Does defense have any more
questions for the witness?
He has Iacrosse practice.
Perfect!
Mr. WhitIey, what position
do you pIay on the Iacrosse team?
What position...
(PANTING)
Coming through! Excuse me!
Headmistress, I submit Miss Woods
is making a mockery of...
(DOOR OPENS )
Okay. Okay, I'm back, peopIe!
MAN: What's goin' on?
IZZY: Hi.
Sorry. Okay, okay. I'm back.
I need a moment
to consuIt with my co-counseI.
(MURMURING)
Izzy, where've you been?
And you Iook fIushed.
I was. Long story, Iong story.
What did you do to your hair?
I've been pIaying you
and reaIIy mucked it up.
I'm ready to give up
my ponytaiI and hand it aII back to you.
Annie, you've got this far.
And you've obviousIy cured
your fear of pubIic speaking.
So keep speaking.
I wouId Iike to recaII Mr. GoIden.
Do you recognize these photos?
Yes. This is my office,
and that's my newspaper.
Miss Woods, did you break
into Mr. GoIden's office
yet again to obtain these photographs?
This is yet another very serious crime.
Uh...
(ANNIE STAMMERING)
(MOUTHING)
(ANNIE CONTINUES STAMMERING)
Yeah, baby
Headmistress, I gave them permission.
Fair access for the accused.
HIGGINS: Continue, Miss Woods.
I wouId Iike to re-recaII Mr. WhitIey.
Have you ever heard of the Uber code?
No idea what you're taIking about.
Urban Iegend perhaps.
There's taIk
that the designer of Uber EIectronics
has an Uber code.
This code wouId aIIow him to gain access
to any computer in the schooI.
So?
What do I know about Uber EIectronics?
I...
(CELL PHONE RINGING)
CeII phones off, Mr. WhitIey.
That's a nice Uber phone, Justin.
(CROWD GASPING)
(STAMMERING) I just got it.
I didn't know it was a...
Get to the point, Miss Woods.
This is finaIIy getting interesting.
ANNIE: That Uber phone is briIIiant.
But how did you get one,
seeing as they haven't
even hit the market yet?
I've got my connections.
Connections Iike Tiffany Donohugh?
(PEOPLE MURMURING)
Mr. WhitIey, I asked you a question.
Did you receive your Uber phone
from Tiffany Donohugh?
I have no idea what you're taIking about.
She's your connection, but she made
you earn that phone, didn't she?
I submit to this court
that you never sharpen your own penciI.
Right before the exam,
you pIaced yourseIf at the penciI sharpener,
so that when Mr. GoIden Iooked
for his stopwatch Iike he aIways does,
you snuck out!
ANNIE.: It was you, Justin,
who puIIed the fire aIarm.
(FIRE ALARM RINGING)
EarIier that day, Tiffany had
given you her backpack key,
the same key that wouId
open Chris'backpack.
You used Tiffany's key to unIock Chris'bag
and steaI his tripIe-zero master key.
WhiIe we were aII outside for the fire driII,
you headed back into Mr. GoIden's office.
You used the Uber code
that you got from Tiffany
to steaI the answers
to the history test from his computer,
which you then shrink-copied
down to a perfect crib sheet.
And you Ieft a scuff mark.
You broke off Chris'key
in the Iock to frame him.
WhiIe Tiffany whined
about the postponed exam,
you taped the cheat sheet beneath Izzy's...
I mean, my desk.
After returning the key to Chris'bag,
you had pIenty of time to rejoin Tiffany
and reveI in your misdeeds.
Since you had the answers to the test,
you figured you'd use them,
hence your first good grade
in a Iong time, right?
(PEN CLICKING)
(MULTIPLE PENS CLICKING)
Right?
Enough!
Stop with the cIicking aIready!
Okay, I did it! I did it.
(PEOPLE GASPING)
And Tiffany paid me with an Uber phone.
You're just gonna give it up Iike that?
Are you some kind of jeIIyfish?
You Iet a bIonde make you crack?
You are pathetic.
(MURMURING)
WeII, so what if I did?
Okay, I did it! But who cares?
'Cause my famiIy owns the very seats
that your pathetic butts are sitting on!
And that goes for you, too, Iady.
You got a probIem with me?
WeII, you can take that up
with my daddy's Iawyers.
(GAVEL BANGS )
Tiffany Donohugh and Justin WhitIey,
for vioIating the Pac Prep honor code,
you are both expeIIed!
(PEOPLE GASPING)
You did it!
Are you kidding me? You can't expeI me.
I own this schooI!
Take her away!
(APPLAUSE)
That's justice!
Get your meat hooks off me, sir!
(TIFFANY GASPING)
(TIFFANY YELLING INCOHERENTLY)
And get your freaking hands...
You, AnnabeIIe and IsabeIIe Woods,
I've got my eye on both of you.
Case dismissed.
MAN: Yes!
(CHEERING)
Annie, that was fantastic!
Daddy! Thanks.
I'm jeaIous. It was awesome!
You shouId have seen the Iook on his face.
Thank you, Annie.
(CHRIS LAUGHING)
Oh, hi.
-Hi there.
-Look, I'm not much of a dancer,
-but you got a date for formaI?
-I'd Iove to!
(SOFTDANCE MUSIC PLA YING)
This is the best dance ever.
I aImost wish Tiffany was here.
I wonder how she's doing.
Oh, I'm sure she's gone to a better pIace.
What?
(TIFFANY YELLING)
Wait a minute!
There must be some kind of mistake.
(GASPS ) It reeks of boIogna in here!
(SCREAMING)
Somebody Iet me out!
(CLEARS THROAT) So...
Can I have this dance?
You think too much
Give it up
Let it fIow through you
-Can you beIieve those bIondes?
-Yeah.
ActuaIIy, they're the onIy ones I do beIieve.
(SCOFFING)
Want to dance?
Are you sure you want to be seen
dancing with a schoIarship kid?
Takes one to know one.
(PHONE RINGING)
That was you who rang
Justin's phone, wasn't it?
I'd just figured it was time
for schooI to give bIonde a chance.
It's not over, girIs.
There's a new brunette in charge.
So, you think we shouId stay?
I think I can be persuaded.
(LAUGHING)
HoId on, hoId on
HoId on
(THIS IS MEPLAYING)
This is my Iife
I'm on my own
Don't need anyone
To guide me down the road
I'm finding out who
Yeah, who I wanna be
This is me
This is my Iife
I'm in controI
Movin' so fast
To where I wanna go
I'm shouting out who
Yeah, who do you see?
Yeah, this is me
This is me
Just don't teII me
How to Iive my Iife
I've got to have controI
I Iive for the fight
And I win every time
This is my Iife
I'm on my own
Don't need anyone
To guide me down the road
I'm finding out who
Yeah, who I wanna be
This is me
This is my Iife
I'm in controI
Movin' so fast
To where I wanna go
I'm shouting out who
Yeah, who do you see?
Yeah, this is me
(LUCKY GIRL PLAYING)
Mmm, yeah
Mmm, mmm, yeah
Lucky girI
You've been Iiving
in a Iucky worId
Red baIIoons
On such a sunny afternoon
MAN: And roIIing. And action.
This is Annie's briefcase.
There's got to be
something in here I can use.
(SIGHING)
Perfect.
Where every moment is Iike
ExactIy how you feeI
Someone who knows
your Iove is reaI
Yeah, you're a Iucky girI
L-L-L-Lucky girI
I know that aII
your wishes can be true
MAN 1 : Speed.
MAN 2: A mark.
MAN 3: And action.
We're dressed Iike this in honor
of the Queen Mary!
(PEOPLE GASPING)
Yes, of course. You see, the Queen Mary
was a first-cIass ocean Iiner
that Iater transported our troops
during WorId War II.
Sometimes up to...
How many men, Mr. GoIden?
Fifteen thousand to a man. In one crossing.
WorId War II was a time of great sacrifice.
Women didn't wear stockings so nyIon
couId go towards making parachutes.
We've decided to honor
the memory of those
who went without by aIso going without.
God bIess America.
ALL: God bIess America !
God save the Queen?
ALL: God save the Queen!
(ALL CHEERING)
(IT'S A GIRL 'S WORLD PLAYING)
Anything you need you'II get
It's a girI's worId
Don't you know
Don't you know, baby
Anything is reaI if you beIieve it
Everything that you beIieve
MAN 1.: RoII pIease.
MAN 2: Speed.
MAN 1 : Marker.
MAN 3: And here we go. And action.
It's probabIy back in the cIassroom.
Thanks. When it's aII cIear, I'II have a Iook.
WeII, we don't want
Annie's heart to be broken.
Speaking of Annie, do you have a date
to the winter formaI yet?
'Cause I know a certain someone
who Ioves to dress up,
and just so happens to share my DNA.
I'm working on it.
Oh, driII's over.
-Come on, I'II race you back to cIass.
-Let's hit those books!
MAN 3.: That was great and cut.
Be there for whatever
Anywhere you want is where you're headed
Anything you need, you'II get
It's a girI's worId
MAN.: Okay, we're roIIing.
Okay. And here we go, girIs. And action.
(CLEARS THROAT)
Ms. Higgins, students, teachers,
distinguished aIumni,
Chris Lopez and I are guiIty.
(MURMURING)
(GAVEL BANGING)
Order.
GuiIty of using poor judgment.
We did use the tripIe-zero key.
And we used it to get into Mr. GoIden's
office the night before the test,
where I did Iose my braceIet.
GuiIty, guiIty, guiIty.
Case cIosed.
But aII we did was retrieve
my sister's notebook,
hardIy a crime worthy of expuIsion.
Annie Ieft it in the cIassroom.
And apparentIy, Mr. GoIden moves
Ieft items,
and puts them into his inner office.
-For safekeeping.
-That's true.
I object.
MAN: Great, cut.
It's a girI's worId
Don't you know?
Baby, oh, yeah
GirI's worId
MAN 1 : Speed.
MAN 2: D mark
MAN 3: AII right and action.
Mr. GoIden, when and where do you
Iike to read your morning paper?
WeII, in my private office
before cIass every morning.
And when you're finished reading
the paper, what do you do with it?
Oh, weII, I'm afraid I usuaIIy
just throw it on the fIoor.
And then, after cIass, I remember,
I come back and pick it up,
and put it into the recycIing bin.
I'm afraid I'm a IittIe bit sIoppy.
That's the truth.
(PEOPLE LAUGHING)
More yeIIing from the audience?
This isn't some ding, dang puppet show!
(GAVEL BANGS )
HIGGINS: Order!
MAN: Cut!
We can dance aII night
Mr. WeIIington, are you friends
with Mr. Justin WhitIey?
Yeah. He's cooI, I guess.
Is there something Mr. WhitIey
finds unpIeasant?
-Something he asks you to do.
-I don't know.
Sharpen his penciIs, I guess.
He finds it distastefuI. The noise, that is.
Justin seems a IittIe sensitive to noises.
No more questions.
MAN.: Cut it! Nice.
(CREW CHA TTERING)
MAN 1 : Speed.
MAN 2: A mark.
MAN 3: We're roIIing, roIIing.
Speaking of humiIiating affIictions,
you shouId see Rainbow dance.
(ALL LAUGHING)
I am the bee's knees.
-Let's see it.
-Show it.
CHRIS: Show it.
RAINBOW: Okay, aII right.
So dance aII night tonight
AII night
Don't you feeI it?
It's so right
We can dance aII night tonight
So dance aII night tonight
AII night
Don't you feeI it?
It's so right
We can dance aII night
Don't you feeI it?
It's so right
BOTH: FIip, fIip and wave.
FIip, fIip and wave.
(WHOOPING)
MAN: And that's a wrap.
WwW.DownloadKing2.Tk