THE CHOSEN ONE
Paul, I'm Christine ...
... Listen ...
... I'm sorry I hurt.
I never wanted this to happen.
How I feel if I were away for
the last two years ...
... I love you Paul, but I want
something more in my life.
Bye.
Paul, shit!
Paul, go, go!
By God! Shit!
Curse!
Give me that! Give me that!
What the hell?
No, no, no!
Get out of here,
get out of here!
Qu est wrong with you?
You hate to see you as old.
Look, I s that of Christine
est killing you ...
... But you have to get
over, she's gone, man.
You can not let a bad experience
derail your whole life.
She left me for a
yoga instructor.
ramos partners ...
... Tenamos a life plan ...
... Has thrown down the toilet.
It's my fault.
Look ...
... You know, wait!
Stop, stop that!
T did not you go,
she did, right?
What you have to do is find
someone more, and move on.
S not how to do that.
NISSAN POWER
Buenos das, Paul.
What did you do last night?
Trying to burn my house.
Forgiveness, what did you say?
Congratulations, you just
made a big deal.
Paul, I can talk to you?
As you know, Paul ...
... We are the Nissan dealer
number four in the pas ...
... And number two in the state.
Y t helped to llegramos ah.
Last year you were the best Nissan
dealer in California ...
... But have not made a single
sale in three months.
Now, s you have problems, Paul,
we all have problems.
Hell, the dog Manuel will pas
a truck of garbage on top.
l was here very early
the following day.
I sold a maximum and
a SUV before noon.
I'm still motivated, Bob?
Is that what you are
going on right now?
See, s to ESTs having trouble
in your marriage.
I have no problem ...
... She is gone.
T know, some of the guys have been
talking about a revision ...
... Say that last year was
only a coincidence.
Really?
All I'm saying is that
shit happens.
Some give you the windshield,
others give you the bug.
And today I'm an insect?
Bob, ESTs being totally
wasted here ...
... Because this is simply gold.
Friend, strongly suggest
you know what?
You go home ...
... You shower, shave, you
put some clean clothes ...
... And you work really hard to
get you the head of the ass ...
... Because you're tucked
deep inside ah Paul.
Y est starting to affect
people around you ...
... Like me and do not
need this shit!
Is that the new Nissan
Armada V8?
It is a hybrid, right?
As is.
There are only two in
the entire country.
They have one in Michigan,
and we have the other.
At Nissan of Bill Smith almost shit
when you get it, and they do not.
It's a very nice car.
That baby is going to be the star of
the presentation of cars on Friday.
Hello!
Hello Señoritas at a time
when I'm with you.
I have to talk to
these girls ...
... Will be working for
us in the presentation.
They look spectacular,
this is fabulous ...
... I love those costumes
are very colorful.
May only be turned into a spin
to see how the sarong?
And there is nothing wrong with them, as that,
because they do without the sarong?
This is beautiful, and
only turn to BC for m.
It's beautiful, I like
the colors, not bad.
Hey Paul, do not touch that car!
Paul!
Perdnenme, Señoritas.
Paul, Paul, do not you
step on that car!
Get out of that car!
Open that door!
Damn it, Paul, opened the door!
I tell you, I have had enough already
or enough of this shit.
Get out of that car!
I have to spell it for you?
Damn!, You can get out of this -
Wipers off these, do not
mess with the radio!
And if you look down action,
sir, is 6.9%.
I say this, fired
ESTs, ESTs fired!
Do not turn the fly!
That devils being
wrong with you?
I tell you, never work on a Nissan
volversa in this city!
By God, you've lost your mind?
Damn!
Son of a bitch!
Hello.
We come from the Sierra
Nevada of Santa Marta.
We are very honored to meet you.
Estn you in some sort of
charity or something?
This man is our holy
chamn Arawak.
We have traveled many miles, and
crossed many rivers to meet him.
Look, I'm in the middle of
something, at this time.
Here ...
... This is only here,
only tmenlo.
Tmenlo all ...
... And good luck with that.
Hello.
Paul, thank God ah ESTs.
I tried to call you.
Paul, I knew your brother
Neal as ESTs happening.
Mam, I'm in the middle of
something right now.
Well, we want to see you, Paul.
I can call you later, mom?
But Paul, they never
return my calls.
I call.
Paul -
Come on, come to BC, I want
you to see for yourself.
I love these bums out
of our neighborhood.
Is l, Zadzig, is the
man he calls them.
First pass on my mailbox,
and then has ...
... Homeless people camping
in their front yard.
I'll take charge now, sir Danis.
Get out of here!
How do I sell my home?
It seems that we are the
problem, officer.
Hit the mailbox of this man?
I honestly do not remember.
Liar!
I saw it all, look at your car.
Is this your car sir?
Is the distributor
for that job ...
... Worked.
It always happens with your car over your
neighbor's mailbox on the way home?
Not always, no.
Know these people?
S. ..
... Are my friends.
That's Jim Jones and Curly, s.
Let's go now.
Thanks, I take care of that.
Go home for a drink, Jim,
bring your friends.
I like your hat.
They will not do anything?
Estn on private property, there
is nothing we can do.
Come guys ...
... Do not worry about my
neighbor is a real idiot.
I can offer something ...
... A beer, water, juice?
S not if you have any of those.
Water to be fine, thanks.
S?
Of where they say
they are, again?
In the Sierra Nevada
of Santa Marta.
Where is it, exactly?
In the mountains of tropical
forests in Colombia.
Colombia?
Colombia, South America?
Well ...
... Brings to ac qu?
These are holy men of
the Arawak tribe.
- Ahuahua?
- Arawak.
He is the spiritual leader ...
... The Mama.
l is the mom?
Have been guided to your door by
the spirit of their ancestors.
My door?
At 2254 Avenue Roslin?
What are making?
It is a blessing.
A ritual of purification.
They believe they are the
keepers of the world.
Have lived in the rainforest, under
the shadow of the great spirit ...
... Of the mountain, for
thousands of years.
From the beginning of time ...
... There has been snow on
top of that mountain.
But ...
... Now the snow has melted.
Sorry to hear that.
The Arawak believe that if
the mountain dies ...
... The world suffer
the same fate.
I do not understand that
has to do with me.
They believe that you
are saving it.
Qu?
I am a car salesman ...
... To be honest, I'm not
even that anymore.
He said?
He said his former spirits have
great blessing on them.
Because you, is really
the choice.
Okay, you can stay tonight ...
... And tomorrow I take them
to the bus station ...
... And take it to go wherever
I need to go.
Thanks.
Must be hungry, right?
No s. ..
... I have.
See if I can prepare something.
It's turkey.
How long are going to be as?
Not s.
Hi man!
It was quite a stake
that you got today.
Yes, sorry.
- However much you love me?
- Qu?
I fixed it.
What fixed it?
Your job, you idiot!
Bob wanted to say goodbye and make
arrest, now can not do anything.
All that happened is that the windows
of the room exhibicin broken ...
... WILL BE deducted from your
commissions. That's all.
I need the car keys.
Take the car to the workshop, I
fully arranged for Saturday.
Done.
I told Bob ...
... If Paul goes, we go all.
- Really?
- No.
Of course not.
What are you, moron?
You're really lucky that
Nakamori want your ass.
He told Bob he was very excited to
see your best salesperson working.
Bob saw the phone with Nakamori,
seriously ...
... I think that really is cag.
Knows he can not kick you out.
Do not put me through?
- I have someone here.
- Ah got a girl inside?
Well, you've been hiding me!
Hey, respect ...
... Revenge sex is the memory
of you will not get tired.
It is ace.
Llmame only if you
need any help.
- Be well.
- I meant to her.
Okay, see you after.
As will be well?
I can bring a blanket
or something?
Estn well.
You must be tired.
Let me show you where the
room or est of guests.
I apologize, I'm not used
to having company.
Sorry, not even s your name.
Marisa, Marisa Orcs Daz.
I'm Paul, Paul Zadzig.
You're a acucaca too?
Arawak.
Arhuaca.
No. No, I'm from Bogota.
One working for the government
of Colombia ...
... To help people assimilate
into our society Arawak.
Wow, that's very
admirable of you.
S, well ...
... Instead of assimilating
them, they assimilated me.
Est the bathroom just
across the aisle ...
... Leave a light on for you.
It was very nice.
You know? wait a second.
This should stay.
Thanks.
Well, good night.
Good night.
You have a voice.
Paul, I'm Christine ...
... Listen ...
... I'm sorry I hurt ...
... I never wanted
this to happen.
How I feel if I were away
for the last two years.
I hope you do not mind,
I made some coffee.
Not for nothing, knew she had.
These guys are amazing.
S.
I did something to this plant?
No.
- Empty the tequila?
- No.
Look, I've been good ...
... But this is not well.
These shots were we.
This tequila bottle
cost me 30 dollars.
Now I have to go out
and get another ...
... You should not
have to do that.
Also I need back
my credit cards.
The Arawak do not need money.
Well, I realize that in this
country is quite useful.
Who are these people?
These people are the last of the
pre-Columbian civilization.
They have never known war ...
... Never been conquered ...
... Never felt threatened.
Up a secret path of
1300 steps ...
... To the top of an
inaccessible mountain.
His sense of time is
different from ours.
They speak of the conquerors
like it was yesterday.
They believe they have been secretly watching
the world for thousands of years.
They believe that what
is important ...
... Is not what can be seen, but
what connects all things.
Forgiveness is a little early
so you can understand that.
So you're saying I do not judos?
God did not see you
ah, das good.
Cared about, guys, tell me
why they threw my alcohol?
The head should be clear to receive
the message from the heart.
Well, tell your foot is going to go
in the ass if they do it again.
No, do not translate that.
They are doing?
It is a combination of marine
snails and coca leaves ...
... The relaxed, when they
feel anxious or nervous.
Coca leaves?
Recurdame not pass through customs
at the airport with these guys.
Tell them you do not
have to be nervous.
What say?
He said you do not want to be
the one to save them, sorry.
Marisa, You are an educated
person ...
... You have to explain that
I am not who they believe.
I can not save anyone ...
... I can not even save myself.
But do not get me wrong,
I'm flattered.
The Arawak not have the word
flattery on her tongue.
I wonder if they have the word
delusional in their language.
Do not translate that!
Let's get something to eat.
Kids want to eat? Food, food.
Put the leaves of coca away ...
... And we eat, we go.
How is that came up
here from Colombia?
Walk.
Walked?
Sometimes we cross rivers
by swimming.
What about the office, how is
that crossed the border?
That is why some times we
crossed rivers to swim.
As who are in the country
illegally?
Well, welcome to Los Angeles, half the
people in this town are illegal.
Encajarn perfectly.
Except for hats.
What say?
We are very fortunate to be here
the day of the great harvest.
It's like da harvest every
day, in this place.
Sorry, you will pay for it?
Sorry, l think the pear
page with this seed.
Great, is a very nice seed,
but prefer an bank money.
You have to pay for it.
Sorry, estn me, I will make
it over to the exit.
Well, thanks.
Please Djelid, l think that
bought it honestly.
Okay.
He wants to make a trade
for the apple.
There is a trade,
only can get it.
They like making deals.
Okay ...
... But it will cost
three seeds.
A?
Tell him that I was the number
one in sales last year.
Three seeds.
Two?
Well, two seed ...
... But I say that
s fucking est.
Do not translate that.
Very good, congratulations, you
just get a great deal ...
... And a new block of luxury.
And I get them.
There are fruits, vegetables and
other things for you guys.
There are also cans of tuna, a
can opener, and some water.
Thanks, has been more
than generous.
Well, I feel bad that you have
come this far for nothing ...
... Wanted to be the guy
they want, but I'm not.
Do not judge so harshly ...
... No forgiveness for us,
we love nothing more.
Try to remember that.
He says it's a very good apple.
Hope you have snow on
the mountain soon.
Vamos! Do not do that.
Hello!
Hi Paulie, it is impossible
to have you on hold.
Hi mam, hi Neal.
Narandamundi cool is that you
could come from Colorado?
S.
It was fate.
Vavanasalomi decided to make his trip
to India just when mom calls.
Pens that will be the ideal time
to visit my another family.
Good to see you again, Neal.
How are things at the monastery?
Quiet.
My God! What it happened here?
I bought one of those sparkling logs, I think
that sparkle more than you estimated.
Paul, you can be dead!
I hope not drinking again ESTs.
Mother talked about
this in the way ...
... We were not to confront
Paul about his alcoholism.
Thanks for not mentioning it.
Who has been caring
for your plants?
Wish that more would do this.
What you give?
Ms sun, I think.
Mam, you can give your plants more sun
burning your curtains only as Paul.
I can offer you a t?
Orgnic ...
... If you have it.
What do you think the
new apartment, Mom?
Is small, but nice, I do
not need much space.
You miss home?
Remember that the
shoulder injury -
Remember that the shoulder injury
I have from my school?
It does not hurt.
Wow, that's good news.
For the first time
in twenty years.
Not if decrtelo must, but
call me Christine.
What say?
I wanted to know how I
was in my new home.
Keep an instructor
of yoga with that?
Qu?
She did not mention.
Neal!
Thanks for the soup, mam.
I'm glad you liked it.
Do not you want some, Neal?
Hello mam!
T know I'm vegetarian.
But you always liked
my chicken soup.
I've been a vegan
for eight years.
Bean I forgot how much we enjoy
eating vegetables ...
Isolate with men ...
and strangers for weeks
without end.
Here we go.
Look at your watch mam, as time passed
before the first comment homofbico?
Guys, please.
L I am a Buddhist, you're
a car dealer.
The Buddhist, Buddhist
quin did you?
I spend my days looking
for lighting ...
... Trying to create more
compassion in the world.
Not like t, you spend your das
trying to fool the people.
Okay, first let's make
something clear ...
... I do not engaoa people ...
... And second, I have nothing
against gay people in s. ..
... Only the bitter, who use their
supposed spirituality ...
... Like a hammer to hit people who
believe spiritual inferiors.
I'm over your little ones
and petty jealousy.
Detnganse!
I will not tolerate this more
than they did his father.
How many times did he say?
The family first.
That's why he committed suicide?
They do not want to
talk about it?
Of course not, sorry.
I go.
If you touch the bell again, I'm going
to get very deep in the ass.
Well, how much anger.
Do it!
There are strange people
in the door.
Hey!
Children, lost their autobs?
Spend, spend, spend!
Meet my family.
Know these people?
S, she is Marisa, and they
are the avocados.
- Arawaks.
- Arcuacos, forgiveness.
They are from South America.
l is the mom.
Is mam?
Nice to meet you.
They are shamans, Colombia.
This is incredible!
This is my brother Neal ...
... And that's my mom.
My spiritual name is Narandamundi,
my brother can not pronounce it.
It's a great honor to meet the mother
and brother of the Chosen.
Chosen?
Come guys, we have soup.
Come, come.
- Qu shamans are tribe?
- Arawak.
I do not know.
Estn yanimanis connected to?
Do not know the people
you speak of ...
... But the Arawak estn connected
to all living things.
Well, I studied with the great
chamn yanimani Aranangaragi.
You know him?
Really?
Everyone in South America
Aranangaragi know.
Interesting.
By the way, they realize that
there is meat in the soup?
S.
For all the shamans
I know are vegans.
The supreme being knows that eating
meat blocks their spiritual path.
They can eat whatever they want,
not everyone has to be like t.
Well, they are vegetarian ...
... But believe to be more
Daino for their bodies ...
... Insulting his anfitrin ...
... To eat what was prepared.
That is a lovely custom, most
people should be like you.
Okay, we went back a bit? ...
... I'm an confused about how my brother
is one of the chosen people?
No chosen people, chosen.
I am the chosen, not t,
not Marindemongi, yo.
Really?
And how is that selected
the chosen?
How it works, use a
alcoholmetro test?
Come on, Paul, these people
are a deception.
You are in a very vulnerable state,
and estn taking advantage of it.
Hey Neal Maringimingi tell
you shut your mouth!
Where to estn quedndose
friends ...
... Have family near here?
They stay with me.
How much money you
have taken so far?
See mom?
I tena reason, we estn
removing their money.
We do not want to cause problems with your family.
Bye.
You stay. Sintense!
Paul, you never know what
you do, this is crazy.
- These are my huspedes.
- But we are your family.
Neal, carried home mom.
Give me that thing -
We mam, we are not welcome here.
There is a difference between
chamn and thief.
Marisa?
What is going on?
Estn facing the mountain
in the Sierra Nevada.
Why do that?
Estn praying for her.
Well, I'm back on
planet Earth now?
I have to go to work,
but there ...
... No food in the refrigerator.
What say?
Each morning we are
born again ...
... But what we do today
is what matters most.
If you want to watch TV ...
... This is the remote control.
Only press the red button,
and voila ...
... The TV lights.
Here, right?
See you later ms.
See cumbia funk, do not have to be
a dancer, gets carried away -
Hi I'm Paul Zadzig the number one seller
of cars in Nissan Power ...
... And we're offering great deals
on the new Sentra SER ...
... Target or the new Nissan
GTR, 249 dollars a month ...
... Or you can drive home a
new Nissan maximum SV ...
... I'm talking about zero down
payment, have to come and ...
... Why not save with the new Nissan
Rogue?, Go to the green now ...
... Get a hundred percent electric
Nissan Leaf's right, me ...
... Paul Zadzig, come see
me at Power Nissan.
When times are tough, the tough do business.
Come, come now!
Estn customers waiting in the
room exhibicin, please.
Estn customers waiting
in the room exhibicin.
Hey, hey, hey!
- What are you doing?
- I can not do this.
S you can, all you have to do
is go one step at a time ...
... Until you reach your desk, back
to you, you're a natural, baby.
You got it, you can do this.
Now say it!
I am a native, I can.
As is, I'm proud.
Now I have to close that
deal, ah to be, right?
No, no!
Buenos das, Paul.
Those bastards!
What did you do this weekend?
Attempts suicide.
Hello, friend, t are the third.'s
Steve, Saud, and then t.
And sells two hybrid 4x4.
It's a great morning.
How do you feel man?
- I feel I'm going to vomit.
- That's my boy, that's my boy!
Listen Paulie, Nakamori comes in
the night of the banquet ...
... Want to go out drinking
with us ...
... Remembered as are those asian
crazy about karaoke ...
... Is how to crack for them.
This could be huge for us ...
... The answer is that liver of yours,
can give us our own franchise.
I see you more later, my friend.
- Hello Paul.
- Buenos das Bob.
If it depends on m,
t be out of here.
Nakamori But somehow she thinks that
worth something to the distributor.
I second AFTER of Saud.
And I say, how an incident
ms before ...
... And even your friends SERN
able to protect Japanese.
Yo, I have a client, Bob.
You better watch your back.
Okay, let's go with the ninety
das, no down payment ...
... Removing the tax and license,
that's like 10% less ...
... Are 3200 dollars, more Where to go to get that?
...
... And only remember to tell your friends
Where to get so good deal ...
... Because I am not making
a dime on this, right?
Congratulations, you just made
a big deal for a new luxury -
Can apologize for a second?
What are making here, guys?
What say?
He said this should be the
temple of your choice.
Temple?
You know, when they see,
disclpenme a second.
You can not light
it here inside.
You can tell them they can
not light that in here?
What devils being
happening here?
What you are making?
- Who are these people?
- These are my clients, Bob.
Would serve them right away.
Llvalos out of here!
They are a very environmentally conscious
tribe of South America.
I'm trying to close a deal here.
- They love the hybrids.
- Well, let stand, yscale.
Great, Paul, this is great,
looks smoking suit.
Only get rid of bad spirits.
Fantastic, you can only get them out of here, please?
Help me.
Is that the girl from last
night Is it too good!
Thanks guys, I really appreciate
the barbecue, but ...
... S could only leave
here, you better -
Can you please close the deal
with the Rosses, all ...
... Give them six months
of free satellite radio.
Go it worth the dollars!
They see when you do with it?
That will be strange,
may lose my ereccin.
Close the deal!
- S only can take -
- Thanks Bob.
Thanks for the smoke.
- I ended up with that.
- Well, that's good.
Come on.
Thanks for the smoke, sir.
Thank you, thank you, goodbye.
Thanks for all the smoke.
Nissan mad Monday, folks!
Look, I'm not the best place
emotionally, now ...
... I'm trying to stay
within ah well!
S that money may not mean
much to you, but s to m.
Thanks, but I have an addictive
personality type ...
... And probably will not have
enough to m ah, anyway.
Alright guys, came from far
away to Los Angeles ...
... Djenme think of something.
YATES SPRING SPORTS FISHING
Santa Monica
There is something you like?
Want it?
Hey guys!
Come on, hey guys, come on.
- Listen to how much it cost?
- Five dollars.
Okay, you must match three.
Mira.
ESTs What really doing
with these guys?
You may think to ATRS ...
... When they really wanted to
do something with your life?
To be honest ...
... I do not think I ever
had that moment.
If you see deep in your heart, you
can see who is having the time ...
... Right now.
Marisa, I'm only an
average guy ...
... Rising in the morning ...
... Going to work, comes home and
tries to take over your life.
And he finds it satisfactory?
S, my wife left me ...
... My boss wants to say goodbye, and
two days ago, almost melt my house.
Est seems working pretty well.
This is the Cuban salsa ...
... Is to have the flat stomach,
and abdominal laundry.
But do not be deceived
by all this fun ...
... The buzz is so effective that
tried to burn calories est ...
... A cup over a thousand -
I did not order that
channel, I swear.
It's like a trial period ...
... They'll take it for
a couple of months.
Really.
Porn, not me.
Why not listen to some music?
Is Fairport Convention.
It is one of my favorites.
It's nice.
In fact you only listen
to while dancing.
- One of the rules.
- Is as?
Will offer you a drink, but they
found my last dotacin arrack.
Was on the roof.
It seemed like a good hiding.
They are very good.
No need to talk with you or
what your heart has to say.
Estn saying that
the Arawaks, ot?
- I understood this time, right?
- S.
Dganme qu is going on.
I know what happens,
and I know now!
What happens?
Estn affecting my dreams?
We are making?
- Wait.
- Dganme now!
It is time for the
selected wake up.
I'm not chosen, I am nothing!
I believe in nothing!
It is more important to
have faith to believe.
But I have not much faith.
That's why we pray.
I'm not God, I can not make
snow on your mountain.
Hey, hey!
I hope you do not mind,
guest myself.
What is going on?
The Umpa Lumpa estn
having a party.
What are you doing up so early?
On my way to the airport
to pick up Nakamori ...
... Comes today, no one
else knows. Remember?
Want to go out and have some fun
before his wife comes to town.
And call in sick to both.
Not if I keep this up.
What do you mean you
do not want to go?
We worked six years
for this day ...
... This is not going to let you spoil
it by sleeping with Pocahontas.
- I'm not sleeping with anyone.
- Hey, that's an even worse!
I do not understand ...
... Quin these people?
How can you let come
into our lives ...
... And ruin everything
we've worked?
- Do not try to sell now.
- Well, Christine is
an about, right?
You have to keep working ...
... Is what we are.
Now, tonight we will show
Nakamori some fun ...
... And some women easy.
Morning, you will receive the
prize for best seller ...
... And we are inside.
Mantn sight in the dam ...
... And I pick you up at six, and if
not acostndote ESTs with her ...
... At least hblale good m.
Help a brother out!
There can be only a coincidence, there
must be some kind of explanation.
Afraid?
Fear of what?
In this world there are mysteries
that can not understand.
That's not the same person
I was yesterday.
Do not want to be the same
person I was yesterday.
Hello.
What happens?
I came to pick up some of my stuff,
and mam ah est inside.
How about in here, Mom?
Hi Paul.
I see that you're sitting
in the old seat of pap.
It's too big to fit
in my apartment.
As that Neal says you've
been here for a while.
No, not so long.
Need something?
S, have a coffee latte, maybe a blackberry muffin, y.
..
... If you do not have that, maybe
my third grade books ...
... Or my electric train
from there up.
The security guard says she has
three or four times a week ...
... And not leave until close.
Hey, Mom!
Perhaps you should consider getting
rid of some of this.
Why? is our life.
The s, but we are not usndolo,
maybe someone more able.
No! This is ours, we
need it, is ours.
Possessions degrade us.
They are an impediment ...
... For our transformation to
achieve a high posicinms.
Okay mam, Let 's go from here.
- Do not you guys go, I'm fine.
- Mom, come on!
Everything is fine.
All is not well!
T ESTs not good, I'm not well,
and he definitely is not well.
Wait, do not interpret my life!
Let's stop pretending that everything
is fine, because I do not est.
Only because your father is not
here does not mean that -
Here?
Is not here, you say it like
I was in the room next door.
We can only say?
Only because we can not say it?
Knew not what he was doing.
Why not tell us what
happened that day?
I do not remember.
Why not share it with me?
It was my dad too.
S sentacmodo not with quin
am, but avoid pruning.
You can not say that
about your father.
We do not talk the last couple
of years he was alive.
I was always trying
to come to l.
Wait for that phone call, to come and chat.
Never came.
He was always so easy for you.
Pruning only because hitting a baseball ball, or
going fishing without getting motion sickness.
I hated you for it.
T had everything an death.
Even that had.
Why do not I, why could not
commit suicide in my home?
Why could not at least
give me that?
he called me that day ...
... I was in the middle
of a business, y. ..
... He was upset,
wanted to see me.
I sent him home. "
There was this friend who
had for thirty years ...
... And she offered us a ...
... Society in the piercing
of oil wells at sea.
We were told it was safe, that there
were no way perdiramos ...
... Made a geological reconnaissance,
and everything.
As we put all our money
for jubilacin ...
... Everything habamos saved.
This is how we lost everything.
l I did not want to come to you.
I obligu to go, was too proud
to ask for your money.
I did not know that
more pruning to do.
I was drunk ...
... That's why I
do not remember.
He was stinking drunk.
Were forty cars.
It was this small company to hire
that was had been working ...
... And needed a replacement
fleet, a whole fleet ...
... I mean, that's like two years'
wages for many types ...
... But not me.
And I tena such ah, and I was about
to close the deal, just ah.
Then call pap.
I told him that anger
at a time ...
... And then the type
hesitation ...
... See?
that's the thing, you can not give
even a second of respite ...
... Or you lose.
And I was not going to lose this
guy, not going to lose.
As that Friday night, took
him for a drink ...
... And drank.
We drank!
And closed the deal.
S not how I arrived home.
I could not see.
Saba that something
is wrong, but ...
... I could not see it.
Only me away ...
... And keep walking.
Were forty cars.
Hello.
Hello mam.
- What are you?
- S.
- Okay.
- I have it, I repent.
Bring my stuff is very
sweet of you.
We had to hire a removal.
- Well, we have a problem.
- What, what now?
Only wait.
- Come on, this heavy est.
- Slo expected.
Neal, your dress is falling est!
Well, you chose to wear
skirts this morning.
Care dear, est edge
under your foot.
Mam, we can not take travs you!
You know?
It's all right.
- It is too narrow to pass.
- Is right.
Going straight, straight behind.
I have no eyes behind your
head, your going.
- Stay to the left.
- Cul left, yours or ma?
Okay, your right, your right.
Think we should go all out?
I take it inside ...
... Or should I eat?
As all deliveries at the door,
it's all yours, man.
I can ask you something?
S, of course.
This morning you said that
I was not the same person.
What made you say that?
I see something new.
What we have seen, is one of the
pair of red-tailed hawks ...
... Who have been evicted from their
eaves to 12 stories high ...
... In this luxury apartment building,
on Fifth Avenue ...
... Here in New York City.
The hawks have nested on this
site for seven years ...
That is the bird.
Cras ...
and they have every year.
The nest, however,
was withdrawn.
The Administration argues that the
birds were renters dirty ...
... And that their nest had great danger
to the inhabitants of the building ...
... And for pedestrians.
Since then there has been a growing
din of protesters ...
... Claiming that the nest is
returned to the building.
Was going on when the workers
were destroying the nest ...
... And fortunately I was able
to rescue the nest away.
With the breeding season
about to end ...
... The protesters fear that unless the
nest is returned to the building ...
... The Falcons lost the opportunity
to mate this season.
That's the same bird
in my dream.
Qu?
Because they are watching me?
Want to save this bird?
Is that it?
That's what they want to do?
But how will make it snow
on your mountain?
In the web of life, all
things connected estn.
That is until New York.
It is not anything close.
No algnpjaro around
here who can help?
Ms a bird close to this area.
In truth, there are a lot of
bird in the neighborhood ...
... As good as all ...
... Maybe even better.
It has to be that bird, right?
Well then, djenme think for a minute,
and imagine something.
We are grateful to the elected.
I did not say it will, only
let me think about it!
Tell them to stop with
that, I think!
This is like the second
time I see you smile.
Disclpenme for a second.
Hello?
Paul, I'm Christine,
we need to talk.
Look, I'm in the coffee
Ahmed in Arvin.
Good to see you.
I bring something to drink?
I drink more coffee.
I drink coffee too.
No, wait, are three shots
of tequila, thanks.
Now, because ESTs here?
Paul, s that it has been
difficult for you.
It has been difficult for both.
S? What happens, you do
not like to do yoga?
Well, I deserve that.
Be ...
... Est complete.
Comet error.
Well, I guess everything is to forgive,
take your bags in the car ...
... And move back home.
Paul -
Christine, it was good to see you again,
really, you look very nice ...
... I have to go.
How can you be so cruel?
Forgiveness?
Not understanding that ...
... How I can I be so cruel?
Do yoga with a guy ...
... Strips the toilet four years
of marriage, and I'm cruel?
I do not understand that.
Paul, s who hurt you,
and sorry ...
... But I'm coming to you.
All I want to know is if you
give us another chance.
Should not be so hasty.
As you said the yoga instructor seems
like a very interesting person.
I will make this charge
is the least I can do.
Carol be home by the upcoming
two days, you want to talk.
Hi guys.
Marisa, I do not
see it that way.
Tom me a couple of
drinks, and what?
Be well.
I have to do this
thing at night.
When I return, I want
to talk to you.
Agree?
S fine?
Hey, look quin is! Is Elvis!
I like the suit.
I want to see.
I hope not having awakened.
He tried not to make noise.
No, I have been awake.
To be honest with you, I've
been taking a bit.
Marisa ...
... I have to tell
you something.
Hey Carlo, Let 's go now.
Will not you introduce
me to your friend?
S.
Marisa, this is Christine.
Christine, she is Marisa.
Nice to meet you.
Nightgown that you feel good,
you should keep it.
Well, I'm not going
to need more.
Thanks.
Paul, going to pack your bags.
I see you outside in the car.
It was a pleasure to meet you.
Please say something.
Anything.
Sorry I can not go to New
York at this time.
There are many people
who depend on m.
I can not go as anything
more than this.
Not at this time.
We can talk about it tomorrow.
Estbamos wrong ...
... You are not chosen.
Wow, that looks good on you.
Mam will not be ready at
least half an hour ...
... So thought I'd come and
see if you need help.
Always.
You know how to do this
shit better than me.
What is that supposed to mean?
Deca only that t you better
for that than me.
So ...
... Is your big night.
I think so.
Where to estn your friends?
They left.
Sorry to hear that.
I too.
Necesitars take you tonight?
Fred and Christine recogern
me, thanks.
Christine?
There is a bit fast paced?
What do you think of that?
We are only talking.
- How goes it, doc?
- Est ready.
If your tie is loosened, llmame.
Hey!
I was just getting used to
the costume of a monk.
Thank you, brother.
Hey!
Est Ah, the seller of the year!
I'm not going.
They told me ...
... Before he could have compassion
for someone more ...
Tena ...
give me a little
of myself first.
You know what?
I think I'll try that.
Because while I can not
get another chance.
Friend, our distributor!
Freddie sorry that's your
dream, not the mo.
FLIGHTS ARRIVING
FLIGHTS STARTING
S that pap wanted to have it.
Thanks.
AFTER I see ...
... Naramundi.
Where to go?
A Central Park.
Central Park is great, you know?
In which part?
S not, we will find.
Here 's good man, thanks.
Sorry, I saw on TV, talking
about the Falcons, right?
If you're with the government authorities,
I have the legal right to be here.
I'm not with them.
Is this the nest in the bag?
Almost all envious of rich people do
not care about anything except them.
Where to live that rich
people just jealous?
- In this building.
- Cul?
The nest was just all up.
- All up, right?
- S.
Release the nest!
Is fine, I'm the chosen one.
How est?
Buenos das McDell lords.
Excuse me sir, a fifth
come to see?
I'm with them.
Lord, I'll have to ask
you exit the elevator.
Damn, going to kick my ass!
Lavandera.
Have a great day.
OUTPUT.
Wait, AFTER I call him.
Okay, what do we have?
It is a white guy in a tuxedo,
carrying garbage.
- Where is it?
- It was the elevator.
Look, ah est!
- That's all that -
- well, wait a second.
We have a jumper.
All right, everyone, for ATRS!
Shit!
From either side of this man
is trying to jump ...
... Carrying a bag, and we have definitely
got to do with the situation ...
... And also wearing a tuxedo.
Lord, lord, for here!
Can you hear me, sir?
Ac down, sir.
Esccheme, I need
to sit, just ah.
I need you to hold,
qudese still.
Shit, that's going to
be a disaster, man!
Esccheme, I'm officially Hill, you can call me Tad.
How is your name?
Let's talk about this, not only do
something stupid, not worth it ...
... Only give me five minutes,
I have help coming.
There is a deposit of trash
inside the building!
No, do not go more
far qudese ah ...
... Please sir, only hbleme, many
people worried about you.
If it were black and
would have shot him.
May vacate this bloody
hallway, please?
Are putting back the nest!
A twenty-five floors each,
and the man survived!
No doubt be in the
headlines tomorrow.
IN MEMORY OF MARVIN AND ZIGGY.
Translated By: Mr.LoRd