[Siren wailing, distant]
[horn honking]
[alarm blaring]
[Man on TV]
We are live on the scene
at the Carlson Police Department
with a shocking new development
in the teen murder spree.
A police detective investigating
these heinous crimes
has now gone missing.
Authorities have yet
to comment other than to say
parents need to stay close
to their teens
and keep them well guarded
till further notice.
- Good morning.
- Morning.
- I brought you some coffee.
- Thanks.
[Man #2 on TV]
We can be traced and tracked.
Did you get any sleep
last night?
- No, not much really.
- Uh-huh.
...no matter where you are
at any given point in time.
Even our soldiers
out in the battlefield.
- Even our children on the playground.
- [Sighs]
- Turn it off.
- Can we trust them with it?
[Muffled gasp]
[muffled grunting]
[Man] All right.
So what are you thinking?
[Woman]
I think she should come to the office.
Well, I'm willing to look at it.
I just don't--
- [conversation continues, faint]
- [panting]
[muffled whimpering]
- All right.
[Breathing heavily]
[heavy breathing continues]
[bell dings]
[engine starts]
♪♪ [pop]
[muffled screaming]
[screaming continues]
- [horn honking]
- [brakes screeching]
- Damn it!
- ♪♪ [Continues]
Slow down!
[Volume increases]
Hang on a sec.
[Muffled scream]
[muffled screaming]
Stop!
[Horn blaring]
[screaming continues]
No!
[Screaming]
[Man, muffled yelling]
[muffled whimpering]
Life in the modern world
has a new anxiety these days.
Just as we've become dependent
on our computers,
they're now being stalked
by saboteurs.
[Man] The Federal Bureau
of Investigation can hear
everything you say even when
your cell phone's turned off.
[Man #2]
We can 't control technology
because it is everywhere.
[Man #1] The Unabomber sent
a letter to the New York Times
claiming to be a member
of the Freedom Club.
[Man #3] They crashed
his computer with a virus
and used his own e-mail
to infect everyone
on his friends list.
Security experts fear
an all-out assault
on computer systems
around the globe.
They're scrambling
to come up with anti-virus--
I've had seven
different passwords,
and they got them all so far.
[Man #3]
Victims of computer fraud
are wondering, why is this
all happening to me?
[Man #4]
Now, I know you've heard that story
about the Special Ops soldiers
captured in the Middle East
and tortured because he had
a government-issued cell phone.
[Man #3]
Here's an interesting new statistic.
Three-quarters of all cell phones
now come with global positioning.
[Wallace] The terrorists
were able to track his location
just because he had it on.
Special Ops soldier
infiltrates a terrorist camp,
gets captured all because
his cell phone was tapped?
The legislation has given
the government new powers
to eavesdrop on both domestic
and international--
- We're supposed to feel safe?
- I believe
in domestic terrorism
and I think I'm being watched.
[Man #1] As targets,
we're people who contribute
to the industrial technological system.
At the stroke of midnight,
January 1, 2000,
elevators may stop,
heat may vanish.
[Man #1] Y2K hackers are ready
to attack computers all over the place.
[Man #3]
Stock markets around the world
may suffer some form of collapse.
[Wallace] What is the government
doing with all of this technology?
With all of this information?
Can we trust them with it?
Do we know that
it isn't being hacked and used
by outside forces,
possibly enemies,
people who want to kill us?
[Echoing]
[Man, muffled grunting]
- [chains clinking]
- [gun cocks]
- [gunshot]
- [radio static]
- [rain falling]
- [phone ringing]
[thunderclap]
- [ringing continues]
- [thunderclap continues]
Hey.
Hey, bitch.
So whatcha doing?
- Studying.
- What's that?
Shut up.
Just kidding.
God, you're such
the little Miss Perfect Student, Jessie.
Yeah, whatever.
So, did you get a chance
to ask Michael about me?
No.
Dude, I don't know
what to say to him.
I mean, we've all been friends forever,
and now suddenly you like him.
He wasn't exactly this hot
- in fourth grade, Jessie.
- Obviously.
Wait. What ever happened to that
Anthony dude that you met online?
Oh, my God. He turned out
to be a total perv.
I found out he was, like, 40 or something
when he was claiming to be 18.
- [Chimes] You've received chain mail.
- You should really be careful
of all the online dating stuff,
dude, seriously.
Okay, this guy, Ghetto Pirate,
just sent me a picture
of his you-know-what.
You attract the weirdest men.
Okay. Yeah, it's official.
I need to stop dating boys online.
Agreed. All right. I gotta go.
I'll call you tomorrow.
I love you, and I will see you
tomorrow at school, okay?
Okay. I love you.
- ♪♪ [Rock]
- [bell ringing]
[chattering]
-? It makes the world go better?
- [Phones ringing]
? The different sides of you?
? And in the darkest weather?
That's grade school.
- No, he taught me.
- Johnny boy.
- Hello, Mikey.
- Man, what happened to you last night?
Oh, come on, man. You know how
my pops is with this football thing.
Hey, you hear about Kevin getting
that letter to Nebraska?
Yeah, I heard it about
a million fucking times already.
Damn, man,
what's your problem, man?
Just relax, man, all right?
What's wrong with you, man?
My dad is all over me
about this football scholarship.
Relax. You know
you're good already.
- [Girl squeals]
- Ooh.
What's up, Rach?
Adam dumped Heather last night.
Oh, nobody gives
a shit about that.
- Yeah, what else is new?
- [Phone rings]
They do that every week, right?
Whatever, boys.
Hey, Rachel,
what is your problem?
Why were you telling Mom
what I was doing last night?
Well, after you told Mom
about what happened to me,
I'll tell everybody, Neil.
Oh, but I don't
give a shit, okay?
I was jacking off, all right?
That's what I was doing.
That's really funny.
Yeah, fuck you, you jack off.
You know what?
The point is, Rachel,
come into my fucking room again,
and I'm going to tell Mom
where you keep your box
of condoms, all right?
- Fuck.
- Jergens, Neil.
- What's wrong with him?
- Hi. I don't know.
- Hey, Michael.
- What's up, girl?
So, you ready
for the game, Johnny?
Of course I'm ready.
What's wrong with everyone? Jeez.
He's tripping today.
I'll holler at you guys
after class, all right?
- Okay.
- [Phone rings]
Ew, ew, ew.
It's the 40-year-old
fucking virgin.
I'm seriously changing
my phone number today.
Can't say I told you so.
- Hey, Jessie.
- You should start...
- Wow, Dante.
- Hey.
I will see you in class.
I got this for you.
[Giggles]
Thank you.
I picked it down the street for you.
[Both chuckle]
- It's pretty.
- Can I walk you to class?
- So how was your weekend?
- It was good.
Yeah, just working on my car.
She'll be done in a couple of weeks.
Cool.
So do you think when you're done,
you can take me for a ride?
Yeah, sure.
Yeah, of course,
I'll take you for a ride.
Privacy is something
that was, at one time,
considered sacred,
but that's no longer the case.
For instance, right now,
right here,
I would like some privacy
with this class,
but modern technology
prevents me from doing that.
[Beeps]
- ♪♪ [cell phones ringing]
- Hey.
What the hell?
My phone just, like,
stopped working.
Better.
How did you do that?
19.95 at Sharper Image.
- Blocks cell phones for 50 feet.
- [Students groaning]
Oh, man.
You see, there was a time
when you couldn't call somebody
at any time.
There were no cell phones.
When you went out,
until you went home,
you had privacy.
Your messages were at your home.
[Jessie]
I have a question.
Don't you think it's worth giving up
some of your privacy
so you can communicate
with the world?
That's a good point, Jessica,
but what about the Internet?
What about MyTube, YourSpace?
Doesn't it bother you
that a complete stranger
can communicate with you,
know what you look like,
know what your favorite color is,
know what movies
you like to watch?
All that information is out there,
and for what reason?
- The ladies.
- Yeah, man.
- The ladies. Really?
- [Chatter, laughter]
- The ladies.
- Yes, indeed.
And what do you do
with the ladies
on the Internet?
- Everything.
- Nothing.
You do nothing.
You see,
I think your generation
only sees the good side
of technology.
But I assure you
that where there is a good side,
there is also a bad side,
and both are out there
lurking somewhere.
- [Bell ringing]
- [chattering]
- [thunderclap]
- ♪♪ [rock]
Okay, kiddies,
let's see what we've got here.
Wow, Barclay.
Five hours later,
you're still here, huh?
Well, man, I guess
you just want to die again.
[Screaming]
♪♪ [continues]
Come to me.
What are you doing?
Did you leave your computer?
I'm taking all your experience points.
- All right, that's fine by me.
- [Chimes]
Fucking Dwight, man.
Go away.
I have got to save my comrades.
[Chimes]
Oh, what the hell?
Okay, what is this?
"You've proven yourself
a worthy opponent.
You're the first link
in the chain."
Link?
Okay.
- [Chimes]
- Well, that is fine.
Cool, man.
I'm a link.
[Chimes]
You've received chain mail.
[Typing]
[chimes]
You've received chain mail.
[Chimes]
Yeah, chain master,
I got your text.
- I get it.
- [Door opens]
Neil, my computer froze.
Can I get on yours real quick?
What? What the f--
Yeah, don't bother
knocking at all.
Sorry to bother you,
Mr. Personality.
Will you please get up
and move?
Fuck you.
Get the fuck out of my room.
Neil, I was just writing
an email.
You're sitting here
playing games.
I have a social life.
I have people who
are fucking counting on me.
- Oh.
- And my computer froze.
Can I just write an email
really quick?
I forgot.
I'm sorry, but no, you can't.
Neil, please, get up.
- [Neil] Fuck.
- Just let me deal with this.
- Fine.
- What is this?
[Neil]
That's a stupid chain letter.
I hate those things.
"Every chain has a link.
Every link is a life."
Yeah, please don't touch it
because I'm just going
to delete it.
No, you don't
delete these, Neil.
They threaten
really terrible things.
Like, why take the chance?
Freaks me out if I don't.
Is that kind of
the same thing, Rachel,
as, like, Susie Joe--
she got it,
and she didn't send it off,
and five hours later
she's dead?
- Exactly.
- Right.
And Jessie
and... Johnny
and... Dante.
Can you hang on one second?
You're fucking sending
a chain letter.
- Can you get off my computer?
- No, stop.
- No, you're not sending--
- Neil, just let me finish this.
...you're not sending chain letters
off of my account,
please, so you need
to excuse yourself.
- Neil, fine, I'm just--
- Off my seat, thank you very much.
Let me just finish this.
It'll only take a second.
Neil, just let me do this.
[Growls]
Excuse you. You can leave.
You can get off--
I have a phone call. That's the only
reason I'm leaving right now.
Oh, really? Are you sure Dante
is not working out or something?
Johnny's got his shirt off.
You better go.
If you must know,
it was your doctor, Neil.
He's really sorry, but, um,
surgery's just not an option.
There's nothing they can do
about your midget penis.
Oh. Well, that sucks.
I guess I'll just have
to fuck a midget.
Rachel, you only put four people
on this stupid thing, all right?
Whatever. I'm going to put
your name on it.
Rachel Conners.
There you go, bitch.
A chain letter.
Thanks, dick.
"Break the chain,
lose a life."
Are you fucking kidding me?
Delete.
Stupid.
- ♪♪ [Pop]
- [thunder rumbling]
- [laser zapping]
- [Boy] Get the flag. Go, go, go!
Come on, shoot, shoot!
It's getting tight.
So what are we doing?
What's the essay topic?
Technology and piracy.
Piracy, right?
- Privacy?
- Privacy, privacy.
You jocks can't seem
to get that one right.
So we have a five-page essay
and a presentation,
so I want it to be
something creative.
Do you guys have anything
to contribute,
or is it just me?
- [Cell phone beeps]
- Oh, shit.
Anyway.
- [Phone rings]
- Oh.
[Michael]
It's another fucking chain letter, man.
"Break the chain, lose a life"?
That's pretty extreme,
don't you think?
Neil's dumb ass.
- I'm surprised he isn't in here right now.
- [Dante] Mm-hmm.
I know you got one,
didn't you, Dante?
No, I don't have a phone.
What?
Snigglers ain't got a phone?
I'm just not into
the whole phone movement.
[Michael] How do you even
survive without a phone?
Listen to me,
you need a Sidekick
or an iPhone or get you
a rotary phone if you have to.
I have a phone at home.
They just buzz, and they beep,
and they have little buttons
on them,
and I'm just not into it, man.
Regardless,
you still got one.
Check your computer at home.
You're on the list, Buddy.
Oh, thank you. Shit.
His ass has it, and you got it.
Kevin got it, too,
and your ass
and your ass got it.
All right, this boy
ain't pressing his luck.
I just delete them
as soon as I get them.
Poof, gone.
[Clicks tongue]
Just like that.
Like bam!
Knockdown.
All right, you guys have two minutes,
two minutes to play games
because I'm going
to the bathroom, okay?
When I come back...
And then right, right,
uppercut with the left.
[Sighs]
[gasps]
[door opens]
Oh, sorry.
[Chains clinking]
Oh, shit.
Jesus, man.
- You scared me, dawg.
- Sorry, bro.
- God.
- See you out there.
- What's up, man?
- Hey.
I heard you got a letter, right?
- Yeah, finally.
- Nebraska, huh?
Yeah.
Hittin' it hard.
Find out
where you're going yet?
No, not yet, but my--
my pops is hassling me
about it, so hopefully soon.
Hey, maybe you can play
for the junior college.
They're going to be good this year.
Yeah, well, I'm going
to hit this bench over here.
Do it.
[Cell phone ringing]
What?
Yeah.
All right, okay,
I'll be home in 15, okay?
Yes.
Good-bye.
[Beeps]
Hey, Johnny, did you get
this chain letter text from Mikey?
Yeah, I got that bullshit,
and then I deleted it.
A little intense, huh?
Ooh, you're all going to die.
Lame. Delete.
Bro, I gotta head out.
Later, man.
Have a good workout.
Put more weight on there.
You're looking kind of small.
Fuck you, asshole.
Fuck!
[Muffled scream]
Kevin?
Kevin!
♪♪ [Rock on headphones]
♪♪ [continues]
[thunder rumbles]
[high-pitched ringing]
[panting]
[man roars]
[man growls]
What the fuck!
[Coughs, groans]
The fuck are you doing?
[Screams]
What the fuck?
[Whimpering]
[coughing]
[man growls]
[bones cracking]
[screams]
[cracking]
- [moaning, gasping]
- [chains clinking]
[screams]
[sobbing]
[chains clinking]
[whimpering]
[screaming]
[thunder rumbles]
[Computer]
You've received chain mail.
[Typing]
[chuckles]
Chain letter.
Junk mail.
[Beeps]
[Johnny screaming]
[police radio chatter]
[sighs]
What have we got?
Hey. This is bad.
Looks like we've got injuries
to the mouth,
teeth missing.
Crenshaw, his face is gone.
What about over there?
He must've been over there
getting a drink, and wham.
Makes a lot of sense
the perp would blindside him.
He's a big boy.
Any prints from the fountain?
We've got a bunch of partial
and smears.
We're running them
through NCIC,
but don't hold your breath.
Oh, jeez.
Coroner says the arms appear
to have been snapped off,
hyper-extended.
What could this kid have done
to bring something like this on himself?
He must've been
into something deep.
Nope, nothing so far.
Everybody said he was
a pretty good kid.
The coach did say
something interesting, though.
These chains don't belong here.
No one's seen them before.
That's interesting.
[Camera shutter snaps]
Where's this kid's locker?
I'll take you.
And there was no attendant,
no video camera?
Just a sign-in sheet.
The other kid
with John signed in--
Kevin Daniels.
Kids say they were workout buddies.
We have officers going
to his house now.
You know, the odd thing is
his car's still parked out in front.
Good. Anybody on it?
Yep, done.
Oh, damn.
The kid was juicing.
Look at this.
[Beeps]
Let's bag it.
See who called him
in the last 24 hours.
You got it.
And let me know what's going
on with that Daniels kid.
We need to talk to him
right away.
Okay.
Come on.
[Thunder rumbling]
Jessie!
I hate to bother you.
I'm Detective Crenshaw.
I know this is a painful time.
This is some bullshit.
That's what it is.
You were Johnny's friends,
and I need your help.
I hope you have
some answers, Detective.
Not yet.
Three days, and your people
don't have anything yet?
That's my son in that box.
Maybe you should
figure something out
before another one
of these kids dies.
It's my son's funeral.
Show some fucking respect!
Just a few questions.
[Car engine starts]
Did Johnny have any enemies
that you knew about?
- Anyone wish to do him harm?
- No.
Did anything out of the ordinary
happen over the past few days?
No, not at all.
[Car doors closing]
- Well, if you can think of anything,
- [engines starting]
call me or e-mail me.
♪♪ [Rock]
♪♪ [continues]
426.
What's up? So, you gonna look
at it or ask it out on a date?
[Chuckles]
It's beautiful.
Yeah. I'm glad you like it.
You put this up all by yourself?
No, I had help.
My left and my right fucking hand.
[Laughing]
It's, uh-- It's perfect.
1 to 10. What do you think?
I think it's an 11.
Jessie. What happened, man?
- I'm working on it.
- Working on it?
- Working on it.
- Give me something concrete.
First base, second base?
Bunt.
[Chuckling]
Well, at least you didn't
get hit by a pitch, right?
No, it's early innings.
- I'm taking it slow.
- Mmm.
Well, when this is all done,
you'll be hitting home runs, man.
This is a grand slam.
Oh, easily.
But when this
and this is all done,
you'll be a fucking
hall-of-famer, man.
I'm gonna get those jacks.
All right, man. Yes.
Put this sucker up.
- Hey, beers are up here.
- Oh.
Nothing but muscle.
[Metallic clinking]
Hey. Hey, Jessie.
How's it going?
You're looking particularly
ravishing today.
This? This is just one of
my many little projects.
You want a--
You want a ride?
Why don't you hop in?
Take a little spin.
We'll go park, hump a little bit.
Oh, shit.
Shit.
[Grunts]
- [clangs]
- Ow!
- [Laughing]
- Shit.
- What are you doing?
- You fucking scared me, man.
There's something leaking
out of the engine.
- Are you serious?
- Yeah.
- Well, we can look at it.
- [Screaming]
No!
- Hey.
When it rains, it pours.
What about Kevin Daniels,
the jock who's still missing?
They have the same friends,
and they were in the same history class.
What do we know
about the teacher?
He was a bit strange,
but he cleared.
He had a solid alibi
for both nights.
The first night,
he was with his family.
The night of
the Trafford murder,
he had a huge faculty meeting.
Now, what's up with these
chains and these markings?
What do you think?
Has the lab come up
with anything new yet?
Nothing new since preliminary,
but they promised us
something later today.
I'm Mark S. Allen.
Topping today's stories,
the ongoing investigation
of the brutal killings
of two students,
with one student still missing,
in crimes that have shocked
and outraged Carlson,
a town known nationwide
as the technological
and software communication
industry capital.
Investigators at prestigious
Brickman High School
still not releasing
any information to the public
for fear it'll jeopardize
this ongoing investigation.
It's been one week
since the brutal slayings
and student athlete
Kevin Daniels went missing
in an unexplained
twist of violence.
Today Brickman High School
reopened after a few days off
to let the students deal
with the tragic events.
Police are asking
all students and parents
to please come forward
with any information
that might help this investigation.
More on that in moments.
Now a look at your forecast.
[Chattering]
Can everybody sit down?
We're on a short schedule,
and we only have a few minutes.
You've all had
a couple of days off
to deal with the tragic events
that have touched
this school community.
And I know
that most of your parents
are going to
the community meeting tonight.
I know I'm gonna go because
I want my questions answered.
But as for this class right now,
we have to get back on task.
So,
the midterm final
is due on Monday.
[Bell ringing]
Okay, class is dismissed.
Jessie, stay after class,
if you will.
I'd like to have
a few words with you.
[Chattering]
[whispers]
Lucky you.
You wanted to see me?
Yes. I know that you've
been through a lot lately.
Tragic, terrible news.
So I want you
to take all the time
that you need
with your project.
You're a very good student,
and I can tell
that you're not yourself.
Okay. I don't think
I need that, but thank you.
If you should change your mind,
let me know.
I'm not much of
an e-mail person,
so just call me on the phone.
Jessie, if you need
to talk to me
for any reason at all,
call me.
Okay. Thank you.
Okay? You have
a good weekend.
You, too.
[Man on TV] Patrick Taylor heads up
Internet Security Systems,
a company that protects computers
at the largest commercial banks,
telecommunications companies
and 35 federal agencies.
They call themselves "Anonymous."
They are hackers on steroids,
treating the Web
like a real live video game,
hacking into Web sites
and invading MySpace accounts,
obstructing the lives
of innocent people.
[Thunder rumbling]
[clinking]
[clinking continues]
[muttering]
♪♪ [blues, faint]
Mr. Bradford!
♪♪ [Continues]
Detective Crenshaw!
Carlson Police!
♪♪ [Stops]
- [gasps]
- What are you doing? Who are you?
Crenshaw, Carlson Police.
What do you want?
I'm talking to all the ranchers
in the area.
You mind if I ask you
a few questions?
You ever use a blacksmith
or a metal worker out here?
- Maybe even a long time ago?
- Everybody does.
I'm looking for the person
who might've made this link.
Where'd you get this?
You've seen this before?
I have.
I don't remember where.
My wife would know.
Well, can I talk to her?
She's dead.
I'm sorry.
You better go now.
If you can think of anything,
I'd appreciate a call.
[Thunderclap]
[thunderclap continues]
[clinking]
[Dante's voice, echoing]
I just delete them.
As soon as I get them, poof, gone.
[Echoing continues]
Your ass and your ass got it.
All right. This boy
ain't pressing his luck.
[Clinking continues]
[phone rings]
Remember that creep from
the Internet I told you about?
[Thunder rumbling]
A chain letter.
[Echoing continues]
[click]
[typing]
You gotta pass it on.
[Line ringing]
Come on, Rach.
- [Water running]
- [ringing]
[ringing continues]
♪♪ [humming]
♪♪ [slow tempo,
Woman singing]
[phone clicks]
[line ringing]
[ringing continues]
Rachael, it's me.
I found some stuff on the Internet,
and I just-- I'm really
scared right now.
I just need you to call me back
as soon as you get this, okay?
I just need to know
that you're okay.
Call me back.
[Chimes]
♪♪ [continues]
[thunder rumbling]
- ♪♪ [rock]
- [chattering]
[gunfire]
[phone beeping]
Yeah?
Neil, where's Rachael?
I can't get a hold of her.
I-- You know what?
I don't know.
But I'm gonna take
a crack at it.
Uh, she's probably balling
somebody about now.
Neil, come on. I'm serious right now.
This is an emergency.
- Okay? She might be in danger.
- [Yawns]
I just called the house.
Nobody picked up.
Well, what do you want me
to do about that?
- Where are your parents?
- Look, I don't know.
They went to some benefit thing.
Jessie, can I call you back, please?
I'm knee-deep in some action here.
I need to call you back.
No, no, no, listen.
Neil, wait.
Okay, just meet me at the house
as soon as you can, please?
I'm going there right now,
and I'm too scared to go alone.
So just meet me there, okay?
Please?
Okay, I'll-- I'll, uh--
Yeah, I'll be--
I'll be right there.
[Mutters]
[panting]
♪♪ [continues]
[metallic clanking, faint]
[thunder rumbling]
[thunder continues]
[dog barking, distant]
[clinking continues]
[thunder continues]
Neil?
[Screams]
- No!
- [Yells]
[glass shattering]
- [whimpering] No! No!
- [Shattering continues]
[screams]
[panting]
[crying]
[rattling]
[grunts]
[rattling stops]
[shuddering breaths]
[sniffles]
[breathing]
- [breathy whispering]
- [gasps]
[sniffles]
[crying softly]
[screaming]
- [yells]
- [screams]
- [helicopter overhead]
- [sirens wailing]
[police radio chatter]
[chattering]
[crying]
[Man]
You got it.
[Crenshaw]
Listen, l--
I really don't think
we need a profiler
on this case right now.
Yes, I am--
What's his name?
Wiggins? Fine. Fine.
Jessie, listen,
I'm really sorry
about your friend.
I, uh-- I can't imagine
what you've been going through.
[Jessie crying]
Listen, I just wanna ask you
a few questions
so we can figure out
who's doing this.
- Okay.
- Now,
what made you
rush over here tonight?
We all got these chain letters.
Um...
[sniffles]
- [chimes]
- See?
[Beeps]
Who sent this?
Jessie, what's going on?
Rachael's dead.
What? She's dead?
Jessie, can you forward this
chain letter from your phone?
Mm-hmm.
I want you to send it
to this address.
And then send it to me.
- There's my e-mail.
- Are you sure?
- Don't I have to send it to four people?
- No, no.
- Because-- And the thing is--
- Don't worry about it.
I'll take care of it.
Just send it to me.
- Taylor.
- Excuse me.
I want you to call the lab.
Tell them I'm sending a chain
letter over there right now.
See if they can trace it,
or if it matches anything
we already have in the system.
Right.
Can either of you think
of anything else
that I should know about?
Drugs, uh, boyfriends, enemies?
Um,
yeah.
There was a guy she met online.
He was an older guy.
She wasn't freaking out,
but he was sending her some weird stuff.
- He was texting her all the time.
- Okay. Ever meet this guy?
No.
- All right.
- Okay.
[Crenshaw] Okay, look--
look, that's-- that's enough.
- Oh, man.
- That's enough. Listen, take her inside.
- Take her inside.
- [Jessie crying]
If you get any more chain letters
or any suspicious texts,
I want you to call me right away.
Send them to me.
This is Stephanie.
She'll take care of you.
- Jessie?
- Yeah.
[Chattering]
[vehicle doors closing]
You okay, son?
No. No, I'm not okay.
- [Neil crying]
- [Crenshaw] It's all right.
It's not-- It's not--
It's not all right.
- It's not all right.
- Let's go, son. Let's go.
[Vehicle departing]
[chattering]
I hope you've solved the mystery.
Detective Crenshaw.
I knew it was you because
your name's on the plaques.
I know who you are.
- You do?
- Wiggins. Profiler.
- Frank.
- I heard you transferred over.
How do you like it so far?
Big change from New York, huh?
Yeah, it's-- it's different,
but I'm-- I'm adjusting to it.
I've known about you
for quite a while.
- 1996, I believe it was,
- Mmm.
Was the year that you broke
the Browning Brother cult.
That was pretty impressive.
Can I ask you a question,
Detective?
You can ask.
How'd you do it?
- Just instinct.
- [Chuckles]
Instincts. That's good.
So, what do your instincts
tell you about this case?
These chains are key.
Always chains,
always the same kind.
Most of them are in Evidence,
but l-- I held back a few.
Mmm.
Yeah, a little stamp on the side.
That's what you're talking about?
Whatever it is, it's the key
to cracking this case.
I profile people, not metal.
Well, somehow,
it reminds me
of a radical group
a few years back.
- Hold on, hold on.
- [Snaps fingers]
Keep talking.
What was their name?
- Um...
- Something, uh...
It was about technology,
anti-technology--
Antech.
- That's it.
- Yeah.
- Okay. That's it. Antech.
They were apocalyptic
Luddites, right?
They hated computers,
the Internet...
But that was a group,
and I'm sure
that this is the work
of a single guy.
Do you remember, Detective,
the, uh, Unabomber?
Uh, Ted Kaczynski, right?
Went to Yale,
taught at Berkeley.
He was a smart guy.
He knew technology,
but he hated it.
And if a guy is so anti-tech,
why would he, uh,
send e-mails to people?
I don't know.
Why don't you tell me?
Why? Why would someone
embrace something
that they are so opposed to?
Unless it's strategy.
Fight fire with fire.
[Stammering]
That doesn't make sense.
That doesn't make any sense to me.
Look, I mean, look at all the good
that technology has done.
Breakthroughs in medicine,
instant communication all over the globe.
- Detective, you don't get it, do you?
- Helps save innocent lives.
They don't like technology.
It doesn't matter about
the result or the application.
They don't like technology.
That's it.
Please, do me a favor.
Allow me to take these photos
for a couple of days.
You know, I got one plaque
in my whole life,
and they spelled my name wrong.
Two G's, not one.
Hey, Michael, it's Jess.
I've been doing some research
on the chain letters.
Call me back when you get this.
I'm headed home now.
[Beeping]
How can someone do this?
Someone's tracking us.
[Beeps]
[beeping]
[line ringing]
[ringing continues]
[voices overlapping]
[Man]
Huh? Huh?
[Phone ringing]
[voices overlapping continues]
Hey.
[Muttering]
Hey, buddy. How you doing?
How do you think I'm doing?
- I miss her, too, Neil.
- Yeah.
Yeah.
So, uh--
[stammering]
You wanna tell me what
this meeting is about, guys?
I mean, you're not gonna stop
any of these killings, Jessie.
You send out five chain letters,
and then five pop up everywhere.
I know. I know.
Just listen to me, okay?
There's a person behind this,
and I think I know what he's doing.
- He's tracking us online.
- Tracking us how?
There's a virus that I found
in my phone and in the e-mail, okay?
The virus is a tracker.
We all have it.
That's how he knows whether
or not we pass it on.
That's fucking crazy.
How could he know where we live? How?
It's easy, okay? Everything you have
is connected to a bill you pay, right?
And all the companies who bill you
have your addresses.
It's not that hard.
I never even thought about that.
But why us, huh?
Why us out of everybody?
Because he's a fucking
psychopath, Michael!
Why did Jeffrey Dahmer kill people?
- Why did O.J. slash his wife?
- What are you saying?
- What do you think I'm saying?
- Guys, come on. Stop.
No. This is not
on you guys, all right?
- Who do you think got the first message?
- Who did he send it to then?
Me. He sent me
the message, all right?
I-- He said it was a game.
And I sent it to you guys.
You know how that feels?
You wanna know what that--
Fuck it. All right.
- I'll show you what that fucking feels like.
- What are you doing?
- Neil, what are you doing?
- I'm gonna show you.
I'm gonna fucking show you what it's like
to be in my fucking shoes.
What the fuck are you doing?
What are you doing?
Give me your phone.
- [Beeping]
- I sent you the message.
- You got it.
- [Ringing]
- [chimes]
- [muffled crying]
All right. It's fine.
You fucking shit.
[All yelling]
- Stop!
- You threaten my life?
- This isn't on you!
This is on me, all right?
This is on me!
Everybody's fucking dead,
and you pull a fucking gun out on us?
[Phone chimes]
- Oh, fuck.
- [Michael] What?
- He fucking sent me another chain letter.
- What?
Fucking break the chain,
and you will die, man.
Man, he's watching us.
He is watching us.
Fuck you, Neil.
What are you saying? Where is he?
- He's here. He's watching us.
- We gotta do something now.
Okay, so the way this works
is you die if you delete it, right?
The chain letter said
we had 24 hours.
I don't wanna die.
I'm just gonna send the fucking message
to people that I hate, right?
I mean, if they die,
big fucking deal.
- Too bad for them.
- You're fucking tripping right now.
- Just chill out for a second.
- Hey, I sent the message to you,
didn't l?
Fuck you guys, man.
I'm fucking outta here.
So listen to me. I know how
we can pass these on, okay?
And then once it's over,
we just have to get rid of our phones
and our e-mail addresses, okay?
Whatever.
[Scoffs]
What the fuck
does it matter now, huh?
[Sniffles]
[computer chimes]
You've received chain mail.
Why the fuck do you keep
sending these to me, man?
I'm doing everything you want me to do.
I keep sending them on.
Fucker!
[Chimes]
You've received chain mail.
What the fuck
you want me to do?
I've sent off these goddamn chain letters
to everyone I fucking know.
[Stammering]
[chimes]
You've received chain mail.
Fucking relax, man.
I just gotta take...
I gotta take a deep
fucking breath.
[Exhales forcefully]
I just gotta think
what I'm gonna do.
[Chimes]
You've received chain mail.
Fucking Rachael.
[Mutters]
[chimes]
You've received chain mail.
[Sighs]
All right.
[Stammering]
I gotta fucking--
- You've received chain mail.
- I gotta fucking do something.
He wants to fucking
play games with me.
That's what he fucking
wants to do, huh?
- [Computer continues]
- You wanna fucking play games?
You wanna fucking
play games with me!
- Kill my goddamn sister!
- You've received chain mail.
- Fucking delete this.
- [Beeps]
Delete your fucking message, man.
Why don't you come and get me?
Why don't you fucking
come and get me?
[Grunts]
[cries out]
[grunting]
[screaming]
[screaming continues]
[yelling]
[screaming]
[phone ringing]
[gasping]
[ringing continues]
- Jessie, what's going on?
- Just forward me the chain letter.
Forward it to me,
and then change your number.
Change your e-mail address,
and never use those old accounts again.
Crenshaw has it set up so that
all the e-mails are going
to some police computer
that tracks them.
I don't feel good about this.
If it doesn't work,
everything's gonna fall on you.
Just trust me, okay?
Just send it.
I'll be fine. I'll be okay.
[Sighs]
[thunder rumbling]
[ringing]
Crenshaw.
[Mr. Bradford]
Remember that link you were looking for?
Oh, Mr. Bradford.
I remembered.
Used to be a place
out on Ramsey Road.
Wilson. Dead now.
One of his sons
went off to that war.
Used to supply chains
to the meatpacking plant.
Plant went out of business.
So did they.
[Thinking]
"They brand themselves with bar codes."
Oh, my God.
[Beeping]
- [line ringing]
- Come on. Pick up.
Crenshaw. Oh, shoot.
Crenshaw, I know these are our guys.
They're an old cult
that grew in the 20th century.
They call themselves
Technology Terrorists.
They were vocal until Y2K,
and when nothing happened,
they dropped out of sight.
They brand themselves
with bar codes
to demonstrate how technology
destroys individual identity.
- Oh, shoot.
- [Beeps]
[clinking]
[clinking continues]
[Man yelling, distant]
[yelling continues]
[yelling grows louder]
- Who are you?
- I'm Kevin Daniels.
I'm Kevin Daniels.
Ooh, you're all gonna die.
[Echoing]
Delete.
Hey, man, I wanna go home.
Okay, son.
I'll help you.
- Please! The line!
- Okay.
All right.
Where'd he go?
No. No.
I don't know where he is.
I'll get you down.
I'll help you.
[Yelling]
[screaming]
- [whispers] Hello.
- [Man] Investigation.
[Panting]
This is Crenshaw.
I need to speak to Wiggins now.
Crenshaw,
where have you been?
We've been trying
to reach you all day.
- Our security system 's been hacked.
- What?
The guy claiming to be Wiggins yesterday
turned out to be an imposter.
You're not gonna believe this,
but the actual Wiggins
turned up deceased
less than an hour ago.
We need you back at the station.
Where are you?
It doesn't matter about
the result or the application.
They don't like technology.
[Echoing]
- [Crenshaw's voice] Antech.
- [Female's voice] They're a cult.
- They're a cult.
- [Crenshaw] What's his name?
- Wiggins?
- Fight fire with fire.
- They're a cult.
We all got these chain letters.
[Wiggins' voice]
They don 't like technology.
[Female Detective]
Cult. They're a cult.
Where there is a good side
there is also a bad side.
- They're a cult. They're a cult.
- Both are out there
- ...lurking somewhere.
- They're a cult.
[Grunting]
[yelling]
[thud]
[phone ringing]
[ringing continues]
[thunder rumbling]
[Crenshaw's voice]
Jessie, can you forward
this chain letter
from your phone?
I want you to send it
to this address.
And then send it to me.
Don't worry about it.
I'll take care of it.
[Phone chimes]
We can handle it.
[Phone ringing]
[thud]
[line ringing]
Hey, Jessie, it's Michael.
Look, I need you to call me back
as soon as possible,
'cause I'm seriously worried
about you, all right?
I don't know if this whole
sending the chain letter things
to you was a good idea.
Just call me back as soon
as you get this, all right?
If not, I'll be there
early in the morning.
[Beeps]
[thunder rumbling]
[thunder continues]
[ringing]
[ringing continues]
[gasps]
[panting]
[alarm blaring]
And we are live on the scene
at the Carlson Police Department
with a shocking new development
in the teen murder spree.
A police detective investigating
these heinous crimes
has now gone missing.
[Man] All right.
So what are you thinking?
Maybe she needs more
than a counselor.
Jessie's gonna be fine, sweetheart.
Crenshaw's gonna solve this thing.
He's the best there is.
And in the meantime,
I promise you she's safe.
[Chains clinking]
[muffled panting]
[muffled whimpering]
Just forward me the chain letter.
[Echoing]
Crenshaw has it set up so that
all the e-mails are going
to some police computer that checks them.
[Echoing continues]
[muffled gasping]
[chimes]
[clinking]
[whimpering]
[bell dings]
[engine starts]
[muffled screaming]
[screaming continues]
- [horn honking]
- [brakes screeching]
Damn it! Slow down!
Damn it, Michael.
[Muffled screaming]
[horn blaring]
Jessie! No!
- Oh, God!
- No! Jessie!
No! Jessie!
[Clinking]
[beep]
[ringing]
♪♪ [rock]
♪♪ [continues]
- ♪♪ [ends]
- [laughter]
♪♪ [Woman singing]
♪♪ [continues]
♪♪ [ends]