I just missed your heart.
You're dead.
Right now.
I've killed you.
Use your hands!
Drag that deer back yourself.
What's wrong?
Are you hurt?
You were half asleep.
You must always be ready.
Even when you're sleeping.
Think on your feet.
Adapt...
Or die.
I'll do better next time.
German.
Italian.
Spanish.
How much did you
pull off the deer?
120 with scraps.
200 pounds in total.
I think so.
That explains it.
What?
How you beat me.
You're getting strong.
"The great blue whale is the
largest animal to have ever existed.
"Its heart weighs
1300 pounds,
"and a male has 7 gallons of
"testicles.
"The blue whale's music can
be heard for over 500 miles.
"A blue whale's tongue weighs
over two and a half tons. ' '
What does music feel like?
"Music.
A combination of sounds,
"with a view to beauty of form
and expression of emotion. ' '
I want to hear it
for myself.
We have all we need
right here.
It's not enough.
I'm ready.
Papa, I’m ready.
One, two, three,
four, five, six.
One, two, three, four,
five, six. One, two...
I live in Leipzig.
German city.
Population 0.
million peoples.
Tell me again.
Wilhelm Grimm's house. Stephanstrasse
260. 10559 Berlin, Germany.
We live at number 7
Weissingerplatz.
I go to school at
the Klaus Kohle Gymnasium,
and my best friends are Rudi
Gunther and Clara Schliess.
Wilhelm Grimm's house. Stephanstrasse
260. 10559 Berlin, Germany.
I like literature and sport, in
particular tennis and athletics.
We live at number 7
Weissingerplatz.
I go to school at
the Klaus Kohle Gymnasium,
and my best friends are Rudi
Gunther and Clara Schliess.
I also have a dog
called Trudi.
I’m ready.
I’m ready now.
...26, 27, 28, 29, 30,
31, 32, 33, 34, 35, 36,
37.
Did you see it? Did you
hear it? It’s like thunder.
It was so beautiful.
What is it?
It tells Marissa Wiegler
where we are.
If you think you're ready
and you want to leave here,
all you have to do
is flip that switch.
But once it's done,
there's no going back.
She won't stop
until you're dead.
Or she is. You understand?
I won't be there
to hold your hand.
So be sure.
Be sure it's what
you really want.
It’s here.
There's no rush.
"Laika, a mongrel dog
from the streets of Moscow
"was the first animal
to orbit the Earth.
"She was launched
into outer space
"on the 3rd of
November, 1957.
"Scientists believed
humans would be unable
"to survive conditions
of outer space,
"so flights by animals were
viewed as an experimental precursor
"to human missions.
"Her rocket was not designed
to be retrievable,
"and Laika had always
been intended to die. ' '
But she didn't, did she?
They couldn't bring
the rocket back, remember?
I remember.
But sometimes I wish you
would read it differently.
"When a star collapses,
"the supernova explosion
is 10 billion times
"brighter than
the other stars. ' '
Will you hunt with me?
If you want.
It’s up to you.
Me?
Yes.
I’ll stay.
Yes. Good.
Marissa Wiegler.
Come and find me.
You were lucky
you caught that deer.
There was nothing
out there today.
It smells good.
When will it be ready?
Soon.
We picked up an unencrypted
signal. One of ours.
When?
0632 Eastern Standard.
Triangulated about 60 miles below
the Arctic Circle. Near Kuusamo.
We think it's Erik Heller.
Erik Heller?
You were
his handler, right?
Sure. Name sounds familiar.
Fuck, Erik.
Why now?
How does it look?
Good.
Almost good.
Erik Heller.
Recruited in 1991.
Former FSK operative.
He became integral to our
counterintelligence ops
in Eastern Europe
and Central Asia.
His file ends in '94.
And there was no sign of
life until April 18th, 1996
when his fingerprints were
found on a. 22 caliber Luger
found beside the body
of one Johanna Zadeck.
Johanna Zadeck.
Born 1970. German.
She was spotted and developed by
Heller in 1994. Never recruited.
Why was she being developed?
That's not in the file.
Let's keep on task.
Heller is a rogue asset. I
propose we go in and pull him out.
We've got bigger problems,
Marissa. Let Interpol pick him up.
He's no longer
our responsibility.
Interpol nabs him, then
exposes him to BND, FSB, France.
Do you really want
every intelligence agency
in Europe scratching
at this thread?
Lewis?
I’m sorry,
but we need to keep this
contained, gentlemen.
Keep it small.
I worked with this man.
He knows things I don't
think you wanna know.
I appreciate
your candor.
What do
you need, Lewis?
One man, one day operation.
Tell me again. Then?
Marissa Wiegler.
Postcard.
Then?
What?
The address where we meet.
Wilhelm Grimm's house. Stephanstrasse
260. 10559 Berlin, Germany.
What else?
Adapt or die.
Think on your feet.
Even when I’m sleeping.
Papa...
Remember what I taught you.
You'll be fine.
I’ll see you there.
Entry 1, copy.
I’m on target. 5 right.
Sky Guard.
Flank 1, clear.
Watch your step.
He knows we're coming.
Entry 1, copy.
Downrange, you're clear.
Alpha moving.
Move!
McCullum, do you read me?
Sky Guard, over.
McCullum? I repeat,
McCullum, do you read me?
Go, go, go! Go, Bravo, go!
We got men down! We need
help! We need a medic!
Secure the area!
Erik Heller escaped.
How did that happen?
Unclear. We think he got away
in the snowstorm or...
But he's in the wind,
and I’ve got 2 men down.
"One man, one day operation. '
' There were a lot of variables.
Just find him, Lewis.
Poor visibility,
he knows the land, shit intel.
Find him and bring him to me.
There was a kid. Things
got out of our control.
Wiegler?
Wiegler, are you there?
Where is she now?
Hello, Hanna.
Hello.
My name's Dr. Burton. Would
you like to talk to me?
I was told by my father
to gain the upper hand.
That's very interesting.
What else did
your father tell you?
Where am I?
You're in holding.
I’ve never been
in a room like this.
It must all be
very strange for you.
How long have you
been in the forest?
Hanna?
Are those cameras?
Uh-huh.
They're taking our
picture right now.
To keep a record.
How does that make you feel?
Camera obscura.
It’s Latin for
"dark chamber. ' '
It was first described by the Arabic
scientist Ibn Alhazen in the year 1021.
Plug the CCTV
through to Langley.
Yeah, you should have visual
on the psych evaluation now.
Can I get you something?
What do you like?
Music? Magazines?
Just ask. Anything at all.
I want to speak
to Marissa Wiegler.
Tell her
I’ll be there tonight.
I can handle this.
Just do what you're told.
John, take a look at
this kid's blood sample.
Is that right?
Is it?
Can't be right.
I got a sample of her hair.
Must be contaminated.
Run it again.
My name
is Marissa Wiegler.
You wanted to
speak with me?
You can wait outside.
Where am I?
You're in
a safe place, sweetie.
Where did you
meet my father?
Erik.
You mean Erik?
Yes.
I met him by a news kiosk in
Alexanderplatz, East Berlin.
I met him at a news kiosk.
Alexanderplatz.
Say it was raining.
In the rain.
He had just
arrived from Prague.
Just arrived from Prague.
He had just
arrived from Prague.
Do you know
where your father is?
Did he tell you
where he was going?
We're all worried
about him.
It’s okay.
Agent, keep your distance.
You want me
to give her something?
I think that
might be necessary.
Abort.
Open up.
I repeat, Agent, abort.
Oh, my!
Wiegler!
Target is in sector 3.
Shut it down! Shut it down!
Lord, help me.
You think she got out?
She can't get out!
Who's on the perimeter?
Detail every unit available.
Mama!
She will never be yours.
Hey.
Hello?
Don't you speak English?
It’s not your fault
if you can't.
MIA couldn't speak English
until she was 8
because she was, like, a refugee
or something from Sri Lanka.
And now she's a pop star.
In America, too.
So don't worry if you
can't speak English yet.
Who's she?
I found her. She can't speak
English. She's from Sri Lanka.
I’m from Germany.
Oh.
I live in Leipzig. Population
0.7 million peoples.
We live at number
7 Weissingerplatz.
I like literature and sport, in
particular tennis and athletics.
I go to school at
the Klaus Kohle Gymnasium,
and my best friends are Rudi
Gunther and Clara Schliess.
They sound fun.
I also have
a dog called Trudi.
We had a dog
called Vincent.
But he went mad and died.
Sophie!
See you.
Sophie! Come on!
I’m Sophie, and that's
my brother, Miles.
I’m Hanna.
Do you need
a lift somewhere?
No. I prefer to walk.
Suit yourself.
Sophie, come on.
We're all waiting for you.
Tactical says she's in the
desert southeast of Essaouira.
Focus all operations
on Heller.
Are you saying the girl
is not of interest to us?
Yes, of course,
she's of interest, Lewis,
but not an immediate
threat to the security
of the United
States of America.
Erik Heller is the immediate
threat. Focus on Heller.
Where is your family?
Are you Arab?
I’m Moroccan.
Morocco.
Capital city: Rabat. Places of
interest: Marrakech, Essaouira.
Religion: Islam.
Language: Arabic.
It’s the German girl!
Is "Kraut" an ethnic slur?
Like "queer" or "lesbo"?
I think I'd quite
like to be a lesbian.
But not one
of those fat ones.
One who's, like,
a supermodel.
But we'd only hold hands, and I
think I'd probably marry a man.
What?
No kiss?
She's a bit old
for you, isn't she?
She has male and
female genialitas.
And you love her
just the way she is.
I like to give people
what they want.
I’ll save it
for when I need it.
What do you want, Marissa?
Erik Heller is still alive.
Of course.
And the girl.
Ah.
Why are you here?
Be concise.
I need you.
You need me? Little old
me? I’m very flattered.
I need your
talents, darling.
I need you to do things
my agency will not let me do.
The devil is in
the details, isn't he?
It’s the girl or Erik?
She's in Morocco.
It’s all in the envelope.
Let me worry about Erik.
Shall I kill her?
Just find her.
Marissa.
Did she turn out
as you hoped?
Better.
She was married to this footballer
and gave him lots of advice
about how to spend his money
and do his tax.
'Cause even though
she's beautiful,
she's actually
brilliant with money.
Get off! Like,
for their anniversary,
he said,
"Here's 15 grand
"toward a Hermes Kelly bag
or a boob job. ' '
Now, she said she knew
the boob implants
would have to be replaced
every 10 years,
but that the Hermes Kelly bag
never depreciates in value.
That's enough with the boob
jobs. That's just common sense.
That's why
everybody loves her.
Mum is against
plastic surgery.
I am.
Mum doesn't even
wear makeup.
I don't.
I think it's dishonest.
This is my face.
Take it or leave it.
If you study history of
art or anthropology...
Rachel got her
first at Cambridge.
...you learn that red
lipstick mimics arousal
and suggests the geography
of the labia minora.
Puke!
Whereas, I have a lot of
natural red pigment in my lips
so I really don't need it.
Vomitorium!
Soph...
It’s embarrassing!
Just grow up, all right?
Grow up?
Yeah.
Oh, because yesterday
Mum was saying
I shouldn't act
beyond my years.
It does leave her with
mixed messages, darling.
Because we're trying to communicate
to her how to enjoy childhood.
I just want her to stop saying
"vomitorium. " All right?
Oy, it's not funny.
So, Hanna... Hanna?
I’m quite impressed about you
traveling around on your own.
My father encourages me
to be independent.
You see,
that's wonderful.
I was backpacking at your
age. Where is he? Your father?
I spent a heavenly summer just
island hopping around Greece...
Bed hopping around Greece.
What? No, it's valuable.
Our experience makes us who
we are. Isn't that right, kids?
So, Hanna, is your mum
and dad still together?
My mother is dead.
Nice one, Dad.
I’m sorry to hear that. I lost my
mum when I was very young. So...
It’s all right.
It happened a long time ago.
Hanna,
what did your mum die of?
Three bullets.
Oh, my God,
that's appalling.
"A combination of sounds,
"with a view
to beauty of form
"and expression of emotion. ' '
"Abnormal. ' '
What happens
if it rains?
Well, you're gonna get wet, aren't you?
Because someone
broke the sunroof
and seeing as me
and your mother are...
"Your mother and I.' '
Seeing as me and your mother,
your mother and I,
are responsible adults,
it leaves you two.
My fungal nail
infection's back.
Is there gonna be a swimming
pool where we're going?
Yeah, there'll be a swimming pool. Yes!
Yes, there will be. Have
you packed up the bags?
I don't
understand why VIP means
after the illegal
immigrants and the goats.
Brilliant.
Absolutely brilliant.
Let's play "shut up"
for 20 seconds, everyone.
Yeah!
Go, go, go!
Shh.
I’ve contacted Interpol.
On whose authority?
Walt. We can't keep this
to ourselves anymore.
Were you not listening?
He killed 2 policemen.
He's reframed the situation.
It is out of our control.
Then we must
regain control, Mr. Lewis.
I am the first
and the last person
Erik Heller will see.
Are we clear?
Are we clear, Mr. Lewis?
Yes, ma'am.
Oh, my God!
What are you doing here?
The sunroof. Was it you?
Would it be
very bad if it was?
You mean, you were in
the van the whole time?
My dad would have a heart
attack if he found out.
Will you have to tell him?
Hanna! You are so mental.
Of course, I’m not
going to tell him.
I think it's brilliant.
Have you got
anywhere to stay?
No.
Yes, you do.
You're staying with me.
I am?
Yeah, obviously.
I’m sneaking you in
on one condition.
What?
These boys.
Spanish.
Gorgeous.
No, don't look.
They're not all preeny
about it like footballers.
Haven't got their
eyebrows waxed or anything.
Good.
Anyway, I’m meeting them
tonight, and you have to come.
All right.
God, you're not
hard to convince. Ho.
Ho?
Got anything to wear?
You can't wear those. You
look like some mad German.
Are you scared?
Of what?
Are we going to kiss now?
Would you like to?
Kissing requires a total
of 34 facial muscles
and 112 postural muscles.
The most important muscle involved
is the orbicularis oris muscle
because it is used
to pucker the lips.
Hanna, you mentalist!
Please, tell your friend
I just wanted a kiss.
Hanna!
Should I let him go?
As opposed to what?
Yes, you should let him go!
I’m going to go now.
Okay.
It was nice.
Sophie? Is that you?
Oh, my God, they're at it like
rabbits. That's so embarrassing.
At what?
I can't believe you.
Hello, Mama.
I know you're disappointed
in me. I know it.
I’m so sorry, Mama.
But...
But maybe I have found
a way to make it better.
I’m in a program now,
a program to make
babies stronger.
It’s an American program.
Very scientific...
Hanna.
Hanna?
Yes?
Where do you
really come from?
Leipzig.
I live in Leipzig.
If we're going to be friends, you're
going to have to be honest with me.
Them's the rules.
Are we friends?
Yes. I like you.
I'd like to have a friend.
I mean, you're a freak and
everything, but I like you.
I like you, too.
I really do,
but there are things
I can't tell you.
Do you understand?
Yes.
Actually, no, I don't.
There are people
that want to harm me.
Bad peoples.
I see.
And they won't stop.
Right.
So for your own safety...
Can we still be friends?
I don't know.
I mean, I don't really
know who you are, do I?
That's just it.
Neither do I.
What is it?
It’s something about me.
I know what DNA means,
but I don't understand
the rest of it.
Are you sick?
I don't feel sick.
What's wrong with you?
Nothing's wrong with me.
What are you going to do?
I’m going to Berlin.
I have to meet my father at
the house of Wilhelm Grimm.
As in "Grimm's Fairytales"?
That's right.
If you say so.
Did I say
the wrong thing again?
Keep this.
To remember me.
It’s a friendship bracelet.
Thank you.
Where's Hanna?
Wow, you look rough.
Do you want some tea?
Had some. Who's Hanna?
The girl we ate dinner
with in Morocco.
She's here, or was. She
came out with me last night.
How did she get here?
Is she with her father?
No, she came on her own.
What?
Why don't you let other people
have their own style of parenting?
He's promoting independence.
She's like an orphan.
Call me conservative.
You're inherently
conservative, darling.
No, I’m not.
I said we'd give her
a lift to Lille.
We are going to Lille,
aren't we?
I found breakfast.
That's gross.
Your mum was so stoned,
she'd have eaten anything.
We've got him.
Picking up now.
Do you read me?
Bring him to Wiegler.
She will ID and interview.
Is that what she said?
Orders confirmed
with her 2 minutes ago.
Marissa.
Damn her!
I feel so grounded
in the countryside.
The city stifles me,
emotionally,
creatively, spiritually.
Places like this
bring us closer to God.
God?
Well, not in any
monotheistic sense.
Buddha, Krishna,
the god within.
Whatever you believe in.
What do you
believe in, Hanna?
Nothing.
Everything all right?
I think so.
I’m not sure if it's true
that the baby can hear me,
but at night, I sing.
I hope she hears me.
Was it like this
for you, Mama?
I think I know
what she looks like.
I can see her
when I close my eyes.
I can hear her inside me,
moving.
Is that silly?
I think it's a girl.
I hope so.
Erik helped me
make these tapes.
What?
He says
he will get them to you.
For Christ's sakes, Lewis!
Hello, Marissa.
I heard you were dead.
Did your little girl
tell you that?
Even though
he knows all about me...
What are
you listening to?
Self-help.
Are you in need of help?
It’s good to hear you.
I didn't imagine we'd have
the chance to talk.
You don't have her, do you?
You're not that good.
Oh, Erik,
you're such a flirt.
Tech's on the way up.
You were a good agent, Erik.
Was sad to see you go dumb.
What did I miss?
I couldn't do it anymore,
the things we did.
I’m sorry? With Johanna?
With all of them.
With Hanna.
So why come back now?
Tech guys.
I asked you
a question, Erik.
Erik, are you still there?
Move. Get up.
Shit!
Shit, shit, shit!
Hanna, I think we're lost.
I’m gonna have
to pull over.
No. Don't.
Can't see the map.
Have we stopped?
I need to pee.
I don't want you going
too far right now, love.
I think you should stay
where you are, Sophie.
Hanna, what's going on?
Are we in Lille?
No, we're not.
I don't know where we are.
Whatever you do,
don't follow me.
Promise not to follow me.
I promise.
Thank you for
being my friend.
Hanna!
Titch!
Hanna?
Definitely odd.
Disconnected.
You know,
I like to think I have
a rapport with kids.
You know,
I get on with them.
You know, sir, it's days like
these that I really hate my job.
Yeah, I’m sure you do.
This is very,
very difficult.
But sometimes children
are bad people, too.
Stop crying.
I’m not telling you anything.
Do you know this boy?
No.
He knows you.
Your friend is in
a lot of danger.
I don't know anything.
She said
she lived in Leipzig.
She went to the
Klaus Kohle Gymnasium.
Her friends
were Rudi and Gunther.
She likes tennis, and
she has a dog named Trudi.
She lied to you.
Absolutely.
She seemed lost, like
she needed taking care of.
I’ve got something
to show you.
A bit of mothering.
This is Hanna's mother.
Biological mother.
Fifteen years ago,
she was shot to death
by Hanna's father
on a camping trip.
Don't you wanna see
what's inside?
Say please.
Please.
You like her, don't you?
It’s okay.
I won't tell anyone.
She's very pretty.
Where is she?
You tell me.
She in lots of trouble?
The worst kind, sweetheart. Some
very bad men are looking for her,
and I need to find her.
I want to protect her.
Do you want Hanna
to get hurt?
No.
She's going to Berlin,
to Wilhelm Grimm's house,
to meet her dad.
Hanna! Hanna, Hanna, Hanna.
Come. Come.
This way.
Been waiting
for you a long time.
What has Erik
told you about me?
Wilhelm Grimm's house.
Stephanstrasse 260.
10559 Berlin, Germany.
That's it?
He didn't tell you
about my magic?
What day is it?
It’s today, my dear.
Come.
Sit.
You're hungry.
Waffles.
May I have one?
An egg? Of course.
You can eat whatever
you want, my dear. My shoe.
I almost forgot.
Present.
For me?
You will need
a fresh photograph,
but everything's
in order, yes.
Why do I need a piece of
paper to tell me my name?
Not you. Not you, my dear,
but everyone else.
We need paper and computers
so we don't have to ask people
their names or look them in the face.
You have a good face.
You look just
like your father.
And you walk like him, too.
I don't walk like that.
Yes, you do.
You do, my dear.
Did you know my mother, too?
But of course.
She was a singer.
A wonderful singer.
Do you sing?
Papa...
Erik didn't teach me.
Oh, you poor child.
He has truly limited you
from all the wonderful things
the world has to offer.
No magic.
No music.
I’ll teach you.
Is that him?
Upstairs with you, my dear.
Quickly.
The park is closed,
boys and girls.
Where is Erik?
He doesn't know much.
Or he's a very good liar.
He knew Johanna.
Yes, of course.
Bits and pieces
about the program.
What does he know
about the girl?
He thinks Erik's the father.
Everybody thinks
Erik's her father.
That's precious.
Yes?
This is Marissa Wiegler.
Walt, I didn't...
Lewis is dead.
You didn't think it would
be important to tell us?
Why didn't you call it in?
"One man, one day operation. "
We trusted you with
a promising agent...
Yes, yes, yes,
we all loved Lewis.
And on top of that, you
left a crime scene, Agent.
He was shooting
through the door, Walt.
As of this minute,
you are to stand down.
No, I’m not standing down.
No, I am inches...
Your career is on the line.
Well, yes. That is fine.
No.
Listen.
Walt.
Heizinger block.
Hi, boss.
So off to
Grandmother's house we go.
Hanna!
Sit down.
Are you my father?
Sit down, Hanna.
Please, sit.
Are you?
Hanna.
Of course I’m your father.
I raised you.
But Marissa said...
Hanna!
Don't lie to me.
I am your father.
I’ve been with you
your whole life.
Treated you like you're
my own flesh and blood.
But I’m not your
flesh and blood.
I’m abnormal.
No!
Where was I born?
Tell me the truth.
You were born
in a research facility
in rural Poland. Galinka.
What was the research?
They took fertilized embryos
and made small changes
to them to improve them.
To reduce the capacity
for fear, for pity,
to increase muscle strength,
heighten senses.
Anything to make
a better soldier,
the perfect soldier.
I recruited your mother
at an abortion clinic.
I recruited 20 women
the same way.
There were other children?
Yes.
When you were two,
Marissa Wiegler,
she closed the whole program.
And all of this research,
it was disposed of.
Do you understand?
I love you, Hanna.
You have to know that.
Because I’m a freak?
No.
Because you are my child.
We're not finished here.
Stop this!
Let me go!
Hanna!
Hanna, please!
I tried to prepare you
for what your life would be.
You didn't
prepare me for this.
Run.
Is that
all you've got?
Huh?
Run, little piggy!
Why now, Erik?
Kids grow up.
Mr. Grimm!
Mr. Grimm! Mr. Grimm?
Hanna!
I’m here now, Hanna.
Ah.
Don't worry, sweetheart.
Don't!
Don't move any closer!
Hanna, I can help you.
Please.
I don't want to
hurt anyone anymore.
I just wanna talk.
It’s over now, Marissa.
Let me go.
Hanna!
Don't walk away
from me, young lady!
I just missed your heart.
Music.
A combination of sounds,
with a view to beauty of form
and expression of emotion.