[ Man ]
Last time, onHercules.
You have made my life complete.
I couldn't have asked
for a greater gift.
I've no regrets.
- I love you, Mother.
-[ Alcmene ] No regrets.
What do you want?
Why are you here now?
It's time for you to take
your rightful place.
By my side. Ruling
the gods of Olympus.
We think it could be
the right thing for you,
Hercules.
To go to Olympus.
Yeah.
Maybe Zeus was right. People
would be better off with you,
- you know, up there.
- What's your answer?
I'm ready to go.
You sure you don't want me
to stick around?
I can't ask you to do that.
Besides... I've got enough
memories in that house
to keep me company.
I admire your strength, Jason.
Alcmene wouldn't
want me to spend the rest
of my life mourning.
It'll take time, but
I'll be all right.
Do you know
where you're headed?
Well, I've been thinking about
my mother the past few days.
After all that's happened,
I feel like I owe her a visit.
How long has it been?
[ Scoffs ]
Too long.
You know, I was such
a troublemaker when I was a kid.
Then, as soon as I thought
I was old enough, I just--
[ Makes Whizzing Sound ]
She got married again
a couple of years back.
To a poet.
I haven't even met him.
[ Chuckles ]
Prodigal son.
I'm sure she misses you.
She'll understand.
Take care of yourself, Jason.
[ Softly ]
You too.
Iolaus?
I know I don't have
to say this.
But it wasn't easy
for Hercules to leave you.
[ Booming Thunder ]
[ Wind Whistling ]
Still having doubts,
aren't you?
Of course I am.
That's because you have
a mortal heart.
[ Chuckles ]
It's never easy to let go
of a life you've built.
The people you care about.
You have a new life
to build now.
This is your destiny,
Hercules.
Come! Join me on Olympus,
as a god.
Welcome home, son.
[ Man Narrating ]
This is the story
of a time long ago,
a time of myth and legend,
when the ancient gods
were petty and cruel,
and they plagued mankind
with suffering.
Only one man dared
to challenge their power--
Hercules.
Hercules possessed a strength
the world had never seen,
a strength surpassed
only by the power of his heart.
He journeyed the earth,
battling the minions
of his wicked stepmother, Hera,
the all-powerful
queen of the gods.
But wherever
there was evil,
wherever an innocent
would suffer,
there would be... Hercules.
- [ Screeching ]
- [ Roaring ]
Hail!
[ Hercules ]
It's, uh, been a while. I like
what you've done with the place.
[ Zeus ]
Oh, it's not much,
but it's home.
All of history
is recorded here:
The past, the present,
woven into a tapestry of time.
Look.
Later--
[ Echoing ]
Iolaus.
[ Chuckles ]
That was the day we met.
You're a god now.
You can look back on
any part of your life.
What's the matter?
I think I'd rather
keep the past inside.
It means more
to me that way.
Well, then--
try the present.
It's Mother.
You see, you don't
have to say good-bye
to those you love.
[ Hercules ]
She looks happy.
[ Zeus ]
If anyone deserves to be
in the Elysian Fields,
it's Alcmene.
Not a day has gone by...
that I haven't
looked in on her.
You mean, you've watched
her entire life?
She's always been...
extraordinary.
[ Hera ]
Oh, is she now? Well--
That's what
you do all day, huh?
Sit around and
spy on people?
Knowledge is power, Hercules.
What good is power,
if you don't use it
to change things
for the better?
Where are you going?
People need my help.
But you've just got here!
Look, no offense.
But I came up here to try
and make the world
a better place.
I may be a god now, but that
doesn't change who I am.
Believe me, Hercules,
I don't want you to change
who you are.
I, um--
I'm just proud
to have you as my son.
We'll finish the tour
when I get back.
Mm.
Excuse me. Uh,
does Erytheia live here?
- Who wants to know?
-[ Woman ] Iolaus?
[ Gasping ]
Hello, Mother.
[ Chuckling ]
This is such a surprise!
So.
- You're Iolaus.
- And you must be Pandion.
I'm glad we could
meet each other finally.
I-I'm sorry I wasn't
at your wedding.
Hercules and I, we were
in Mycenae,
dealing with a... big, um,
fire-breathing--
Don't worry.
We didn't expect you there.
What Pandion means is...
we knew you were busy.
Yeah.
So, uh-- So anyway, uh...
I'm sorry.
And, uh...
[ Chuckles ]
I know it's been
a long time, but...
well, I've missed you.
Come inside. I was
just preparing lunch.
[ Chuckles ]
- [ Screaming ] Help me!
- Daddy! Daddy!
Hold on, Thalonius!
I've sent for help!
[ Screaming ]
[ Girl ]
Mommy, help him! Daddy!
- Maybe I can help.
-Help me!
[ Softly ]
I hope this works.
[ Woman ]
What? [ Gasps ]
The gods be praised!
[ Gasps, Laughs ]
Daddy!
[ Laughing, Chattering ]
Have some.
Thank you.
I'd forgotten how good
a home-cooked meal could be.
[ Scoffs ]
Uh, tell us more
about Hercules.
Nah. I've-- I've talked
too much already.
Besides, I've already told you
all the juicy parts.
- I'd, uh, like to hear
more about you two.
- Would you?
Well, where should we start?
I mean, you missed so much.
- Pandion.
-It's true, isn't it? Your son
drops by out of the blue...
after who knows how long,
and expects you to welcome
him home with open arms.
- Don't do this.
- I don't expect anything
from either of you.
And I know I
haven't been here as much
as I... should have, but...
[ Chuckles ]
I-I just--
I wanted to-- Um--
You don't even know
why you came, do you?
I think you're feeling lost
without your friend.
You stopped in for
a shoulder to cry on.
Listen, pal, you don't know
anything about me.
- And whose fault is that?
- This is not your problem.
[ Inhales ]
It's between us.
It became my problem...
every night that I saw you
cry yourself to sleep,
because you thought
he'd abandoned you!
Is that true?
Sweetheart, you have to
tell him how you feel.
Welcome home.
[ Hera ]
They look so insignificant
from up here, don't they?
The only one who looks
insignificant to me,
Hera, is you.
I didn't come here...
to fight with you, Hercules.
I came to make an offer.
You might even call it
an offer of peace.
[ Scoffs ]
Peace.
Despite our differences,
we've always had...
our contempt
for Zeus in common.
You and I have
nothing in common.
[ Chuckles ]
Believe it or not,
I once loved your father,
and your father loved me--
[ Scoffs ]
until something else
caught his eye.
As strong as our bond was,
it couldn't compete with
his fascination for mankind.
[ Scoffs ]
Oh, please, Hera!
You have never loved
anyone but yourself.
You couldn't stand to lose
your power with Zeus. You made
sure the world felt your pain.
I wanted Zeus to understand
what he had done to me.
The world was incidental.
Not to me!
You're a god now.
I don't want to fight with you
anymore, Hercules.
It's Zeus I despise!
And I am not alone.
Why don't you just say
what you have to say?
Do you really believe
he brought you to Olympus...
justto help mankind?
Zeus!
[ Echoing ]
I know why you're here.
Hera got to you, didn't she?
Tell me she's wrong.
Tell me that you haven't
kept something from me.
It's not as simple as that.
Hera would stop at nothing
to get me out of Olympus.
Isthatwhy
you brought me here?
You don't understand
what's at stake!
Just tell me the truth
for once!
Did you lie to me, so that
I'd come up here and protect
you against the other gods?
Answer me!
Yes, Hercules.
I did.
I trusted you.
Everything you said
has been a lie.
That's not true.
I meant it
when I said I was proud
to have you as my son.
Well, I can't say I'm proud
tobeyour son.
Why didn't you just
ask for my help?
I knew how you felt about me.
Didn't want to take a chance...
that you'd refuse me.
[ Scoffs ]
- Well, now you'll never know.
- Now, don't you walk away
from me!
You've had my protection
since you were a boy.
- Youoweme the same.
- I... owe you?
You have permitted
the greatest sorrows
of my life.
Where was
your protection then?
I owe you nothing!
I never thought
I'd see the time...
when you'd take Hera's side.
I'm not on anybody's side.
As far as I'm concerned,
you two deserve each other.
If you leave now,
don't come back!
Take care of yourself, Dad.
It's what you're best at.
Oh! Why-- [ Chuckles ]
You startled me.
I didn't mean
to frighten you,
Alcmene.
I'm sorry.
Have we met?
[ Inhales ]
Now, we have all the time
in the world to become...
the closest of friends.
[ Thunder Rumbling ]
Here. Let me help.
I can manage.
Mother!
[ Sighs ]
Mother.
I know I've hurt you.
If you keep it inside,
it's just gonna
make things worse.
I always wanted you
to go out in the world,
and make a life, Iolaus,
and I'm glad you did.
[ Panting ]
I just thought I'd be
a bigger part of it.
I'm so sorry.
When your father left me,
I was so hurt.
I couldn't understand how
he'd choose a life of war
over a life with me.
- It was his loss.
- That's what I told myself.
Until you left too.
And then I had
to wonder if...
maybe I'd done something
to drive you both away.
No. No!
You did everything right.
It's me. I'm the one that
made all the mistakes.
Getting into trouble.
Stealing. [ Sighs ]
I couldn't come back,
because I was ashamed I'd
put you through all that.
That was years ago.
You were a child.
[ Chuckles ]
I know.
I guess...
I wanted to be
the kind of man...
you could be proud of.
I love you, son.
But the truth is,
I don't know you well enough
to be proud of you.
[ Hercules ] Mother,
I'm trying to work things out
with Zeus, like you wanted.
[ Sighs ] But maybe
it wasn't meant to be.
I know if you were here,
you'd...
say I have to accept him
for who he is, but--
Gods. You can't live
with them, you can't--
Even though he'll
never change, I can't
turn my back on him.
For better or worse,
he, uh--
He is my father.
I wish you were here
to talk to me.
I miss you.
Oh, Hercules!
You sound so grave!
[ Laughing Hysterically ]
- Oh, "grave." Get it?
- For once, Apollo, I hope
you're here to pick a fight.
I'm in the mood.
[ Gasps ]
What will the children say?
You know, the funny thing
about kids, they love
to play with matches.
But they're afraid of fire!
Lemme show you.
[ Man ]
So, class, that's
what is meant...
by the old adage, "What
goes up, must come down."
- Yes, Aristotle?
- What about him?
- Hi, kiddies!
-[ Child ] He's floating!
[ Children Laughing,
Chattering ]
- I love playtime.
- [ Horse Whinnying ]
[ Apollo ]
Hey, over here,
Herc!
-You ready for me, old man?
- [ Girl Screams ]
You done playing
your little game?
NowI'm ready
to pick that fight.
Your son has
abandoned you, Zeus.
And you have no allies
left to speak of.
You will never,ever
take my throne.
I thought I was going to
have to take your power...
with the help
of the other gods.
But... not anymore.
You, dear husband, are
going to give it to me.
I would destroy Olympus first.
You know?
I couldn't understand
why you waited so long...
to bring Hercules
to Olympus...
until now.
You didn't want to take him
away from his mother.
She wasn't just
a casual encounter, was she?
You chose her.
[ Chuckles ]
Your jealousy has
made you delusional.
And your love
for a mortal woman...
will be your undoing!
[ Screaming ]
What in the name
of all the gods
have you done?
[ Screaming Continues ]
I've taken her spirit
from the Elysian Fields.
And she'll remain like this
forever, unless you surrender
your godhood to me.
And what makes you think
I won't cover the world
with your ashes?
If anything happens to me...
you'll never find her.
And you'll have to
live out your eternity...
knowing that you couldn't save
the only woman you ever loved.
You have no choice.
[ Screaming ]
[ People Screaming ]
You have always been
so captivated...
by your pathetic mortals.
Let's see how you like
living as one of them.
- You're a mortal now.
- [ Laughing ]
Hey, kids!
How about a barbecue?
[ Apollo Laughing, Whooping ]
[ Screaming, Yelling ]
Whoo-hoo!
[ Laughing ]
[ Man ]
Come on! Come on!
Duck!
Go! Get them
out of here.
- Hercules!
- Iolaus! Make sure
everybody's out.
[ Apollo ]
Giddyap, horsie!
[ Laughs Maliciously ]
Wait! Wait! Come back!
Apollo!
Whoa!
Hey! Come on.
Would you stop?
Whoa!
- [ Laughing ]
- Whoa!
You promised me you'd
leave these people alone.
This is a special situation.
I took you once before.
I've improved since then.
- Why are you doing this?
- [ Chuckling ]
While you were saving
all these worthless peasants,
Mom was giving
dear old Dad a--
what would you call it?
- A demotion?
- What has she done with Zeus?
He's one of your puny,
flesh-and-blood mortals now.
A dried-up old husk
whose time has nearly gone.
You could have stopped it,
too-- if you'd been there!
Instead of here.
And how many of these people
would be dead if I had?
[ Laughing Hysterically ]
Well, that was kind of
the point of it all!
Who cares?
Other than you?
And my guess is
you're next on Hera's list
to be... neutralized.
[ Chattering ]
I'll be right with you.
Oh!
Who is this?
I'm going to have one
of whatever he's having.
Something a little stronger.
[ Chuckling ]
Hi, fellas.
- Is this the local health club?
- [ Giggling ]
Ooh. Look at that
little raven.
What are you lookin' at,
old man?
Not much.
Oh, sweetie!
[ Laughs ]
This is your lucky day.
Have I got
something for you.
[ Chortling ]
What do you think
you're doing?
Aww.
[ Kissing ]
[ Laughing ]
No, don't go,
sweetie.
This won't take
very long.
You're okay!
What's your name?
Zeus!
Zeus?
[ Laughing ]
Oh, that is rich!
[ Groans ]
Oh!
Aw, you're--
You're a knockout.
Oh, he infuriates me!
Wouldn't you know
he would end up
with a bimbo? Ares!
He's supposed to be suffering,
driving himself crazy...
because once he was somebody.
You know, maybe it might
just come to him how
miserable he is without you.
If I thought he wasn't
going to suffer, I would
have killed him outright.
Now, I want you
to go and do it.
- Go down there and kill him.
- [ Chuckling ]
I'll be back!
dddd [ Drunken Singing ]
Come on in here, stranger!
Have a drink! This guy
thinks he's Zeus!
-[ Patrons Laughing ]
- That's no stranger.
That's my son.
Yeah.
Aww.
Hercules.
[ Man Laughs ]
Hercules?
[ Woman, Laughing ]
Stop it!
You're killing us, man.
Zeus and Hercules! What
is it, the circus in town?
All right, all right.
Let's go.
Don't be a wet blanket.
These are very...
good people.
I-I can see that they are.
Come on.
Yeah, well-- Come on,
let's have a drink together.
Just-- Just you and me.
Father and son, eh?
Just a little drink.
Phew!
Hmm?
You're not safe here.
Oh, I'm safe.
You know, that business
with Hera isfinished.
I'm as safe as a babe
in his mother's arms.
[ Groans ]
[ Woman ] Thisbe, I'll
help you fix the wagon.
Hey! Friend.
What happened here?
Apollo went nuts!
Tried to burn
the whole place down.
If it hadn't been for
Hercules and Iolaus, we
never would have survived.
Iolaus?
Oh, yeah.
The school was on fire.
He went in and brought me
and the kids out. We would
have died for sure...
if he hadn't been there.
Risked his life,
he did.
Pandion!
This is no good.
[ Exhales ]
I guess I owe you
an apology.
No. No, I'm the one
that should apologize.
To you, and to my mother.
I had my mind
made up about you...
before you ever
came home.
I never considered you do
what you do for a good reason.
Well, a wonderful reason.
And I'm sorry.
You love my mother.
Well, so do I!
[ Chuckles ]
You're concerned
about her feelings,
and this is a good thing...
because so am I.
We can be friends,
can't we?
Okay. Come on.
[ Groaning ]
I really don't want
to have to carry you
out of here.
Le-Let me go. Now don't
be in such a hurry
to break up my party.
- Yeah.
-Yo, Zeus. Any more of your
family stops by...
- we'll treat 'em right.
- Yeah, like, uh, Hades
or... Ares?
- So predictable.
- Mom sends her best.
I should have known
you'd be here to make this
tougher than it has to be.
You'd kill your own father.
That's low, even for you.
Hey! Like father, like son.
Zeus stuck it to old Kronos
like Kronos stuck
his old man, what can I say?
- It's a family trait.
- Hmm.
Well, that is new.
What do you say
we, uh, settle this
the old-fashioned way?
- Mano a mano.
- One on one.
Face to face.
Eye to eye.
My boys!
[ Whooping ]
Now, come on, lads.
Now, come on. Get--
Get stuck in there, eh?
[ Laughing ]
- [ Choking ] Zeus!
-Make your old Dad
proud of you.
Sock it to him, Herc.
[ Laughs ]
Zeus!
Zeus. Zeus!
[ Groans ]
Ooh!
[ Groaning ]
Say, what--
What's that?
That would be pain.
Something you've never
felt before.
This is not a good thing.
Well, you're hurt.
How hurt?
Bad. You're dying.
[ Laughs ]
Dying!
No, that's impossible.
I'm a g--
Uh-oh.
That's right.
Mortal.
What did I do?
Did I--
- Did I drink too much?
- Building fell on you.
Yeah, well, it--
It feels like it.
Hey!
Now, you're a god.
You can heal me.
I thought of it.
So, why don't you
do something?
Thought I'd let you
get a real taste of what
it's like to be human...
before I brought it up.
[ Laughing, Wheezing ]
Oh, you're devious.
Yeah.
And look who's talking.
I'm glad you came.
Me too.
Sorry it was so overdue.
I-I just never thought--
Never thought
I'd miss you?
Never thought it would
matter to me? You should
have known better.
You should know...
I'm very proud of you.
When you were in trouble,
and couldn't find your way,
I had faith in you.
And you proved me right.
Don't be a stranger.
You're always welcome.
Come back soon.
I will.
I promise.
You're inmyyard
now, buddy!
I'm not your buddy.
[ Apollo Screaming,
Echoing ]
[ Screaming ]
[ Laughing ]
[ Hera Laughing ]
Hercules!
- Look out!
- [ Grunts, Screams ]
[ Laughing ]
You fall, and that's all.
This is the Abyss of Tartarus.
Old Kronos is down there.
Captive till the end of time.
[ Grunts, Sighs ]
I'll watch my step.
[ Chuckling ]
Get ready
for company, Kronos!
- [ Yells, Screams ]
- [ Laughing ]
- No!
- [ Grunts ]
- [ Cries Out ]
- [ Growls ]
- [ Groans ]
I'm going to
miss you, Hercules.
[ Laughing ]
[ Knuckles Cracking ]
- [ Screams ]
- [ Chuckles ]
[ Screaming ]
Ah, Hercules!
I won't missyou.
You sure you want
to return?
The only way I can
truly help mankind...
is to be among people,
not above them.
As a complete god,
you could do
so much more for them.
And for yourself.
No. You once said that
I was born as the Fates
meant me to be.
Half god and half mortal.
That's why I'm going back.
Stubborn.
Always so stubborn.
I take after my mother.
I don't want any
special treatment from you.
I'll deal with the other gods
and everyone else on my own.
Well, if that's what you want,
that's what you'll get.
You're saying good-bye?
Is that what this is?
This is me,
getting on with my life.
If you want to be a part
of it, it's up to you.
[ Footsteps ]
- [ Grunts ] Yah! Oh.
- Whoa!
I, uh--
I missed you too.
Hercules! Uh--
It's good to see ya!
Good to see you.
[ Sighs ]
Well, uh, I'm back.
Back? You mean, like,
"back" back?
Like, really back?
No more Olympus?
No more, "Hercules, the god"?
No, just, uh, half god.
[ Chuckles ]
[ Laughs ]
That's terrific!
So, what happened?
I realized how much
my family means to me.
And... you're it.
Oh, ah--
Iolaus, wait!
Is something wrong?
No! No.
I'm just glad you're back.
Ah.
So, uh,
how was Olympus?
Olympus.
Uh, not very friendly.
[ Chuckling ]
And, uh, Hera?
You could say she's...
history.