In 1973 the Chilean army overthrew
President Allende
and General Pinochet
took control of the country.
After 15 years of dictatorship,
Pinochet faced
increasing international pressure
to legitimize his regime.
In July, 1988,
a referendum was held.
The people would vote YES or NO
to another 8-year term
for Pinochet.
For 27 days, the two sides
would fight it out daily on TV:
15 minutes for the YES camp
and 15 for the NO.
First of all, I'd like to say
that what you're about to see
fits with the current social context.
We believe the country is ready
for communication like this.
Absolutely.
Remember, the citizens
have increased demands about the truth,
and what they want.
Let's be honest:
Today, Chile is thinking of its future.
Let's watch.
The new soft drink has arrived!
It's young, liberated, and Free!
The time has come
The time is right for Free
It's what you were waiting for
It was made for you
And now, Free!
Refresh yourself now!
And feel Free!
Free like you
Now, you. Now, Free!
It's OK, but...
Why the fuck is there miming in my film?
When did we talk about miming?
There is no doubt that...
that it is very well done,
You can see the effort.
Carlos,
This is very, very, very original.
It might work in the US,
but we have to trust our product.
We have a product
different to the competition.
It invites you to be young,
and be brave.
If you're brave, you're Free.
I think.
This is everything our youth needs.
Music, a rebellion,
an idyll.
But with order and respect.
Excuse me. There's a Mr. Urrutia...
No, we're in a meeting.
He's here.
Here?
Please go and see. Go on.
OK.
Take a look at the 30-second version.
There's no miming in it.
Thanks.
José Tomás Urrutia?
Yes.
The communist?
What do you want?
You've become very fucking important.
No wonder you won't take my calls now.
I work.
What's going on?
How's Vero doing?
Well, I suppose.
What can I do for you?
I'm working on the campaign
for the referendum.
I know.
For the NO campaign, of course.
Everyone knows.
What does everyone know?
That you're with the NOs,
and you want me to do the campaign.
Who?
Me.
You?
Yes. Me.
No.
Besides...
Why are you bothering with it?
This election is rigged from the outset.
Listen,
international pressure
has forced Pinochet to agree
to an opposing campaign.
This is our chance
to overthrow the dictatorship.
So, Pinochet set up a referendum
in order to lose it.
No, be serious,
I'm being serious, man.
Pinochet could win this vote
without cheating, if he wants.
Really?
That's what's so terrible.
Legally?
People either vote for him
or not at all.
No, let's take a cab.
We'll take a bus.
A political campaign
takes up a lot of time.
A lot of people... A good team.
Of course, but the campaign
is in the hands
of experts in political communication
who know their job and do it well.
Let me tell you that at first,
I wasn't too sure,
but they've surprised me.
Good people, responsible, capable.
What I need, man...
is an external opinion.
An opinion!
Just an opinion from me?
I wouldn't even give you that.
Calm down, man.
No!
I didn't know
you were pals with that communist.
Urrutia's no communist.
Yes he is.
No.
He was my classmate. I know him.
No, he's not a communist.
What is he, then?
He's the other...
Christian Democrat?
No.
Socialist?
No!
It doesn't matter,
they're all forms of communism.
No, I know Urrutia from...
He's a family friend.
Are you going to tell me
how microwave works?
It's laser technology.
Invisible heat,
and you say "a" microwave.
A microwave.
Yes.
You were offered the NO campaign?
Are we going to talk about that
or about a microwave?
You tell me, dickwad.
Yes.
Yes,
but I said no,
I didn't have the time,
I had my hands full, and I couldn't.
I'm only going to give them my opinion.
Even if it hurts you.
Thank you.
You're such a showoff, asshole.
Loads of people are offering me work.
Freelance.
With your family background,
I never should have hired you.
You'd have passed up a goldmine.
And what about you?
Forget my loyalty to Pinochet.
Please be coherent.
You didn't share that goldmine
with the communists.
Enough with the communists, old lady.
An old lady? No, an old man.
Who's on board with the campaign?
I don't know.
Did they call anyone from abroad?
No, just me I think.
You?
Yes.
But you've been away for ages.
What do you know about it? Nothing.
Do they have money?
No.
The communists don't have money.
It's not them.
Oh no? So who is it then?
Everyone but the communists.
Not the communists.
Nicaragua, Cuba and the Soviet Union
didn't put any money in.
No.
The Americans did.
No, they're on our side.
And yet they did it.
The CIA financed the coups
and are supporting us.
How much are they paying you?
The Americans are with the NO.
...for public spaces,
we've designed some posters.
This doesn't mean
that these are the definitive ones:
"If I govern, you govern"
"YES, for a winning country"
"We are millions."
Lucho Guzman.
Explain to us your theory
about reactionary people.
No, Minister.
What I meant to say
is that the concept of dictatorship
packs a strong punch.
And that on top of that,
now they're going to say it on TV.
15 minutes of screen time.
15 minutes of TV
split into different opinions
lost in the middle of the night.
That's what the opposition has.
The YES camp will have those 15 minutes
and all of the remaining time, too.
They didn't have that platform before.
Platform? How many parties are there?
Seventeen.
It'll be chaos.
They'll fight like cat and dog.
The general is respected everywhere.
Even the biggest hypocrites
know he's modernized this country.
Do you know what I've heard
my fellow Argentineans say?
"We want a Pinochet."
Everyone wants a Pinochet.
Show him.
You control the radio,
the newspapers, television. But...
we have to get him out of uniform,
and compose
an elegant, very Chilean anthem,
for the people to sing
with pride, to the general in a suit.
That spells trouble.
How about in black tie?
I prefer him in a suit.
I think we should take advantage
of his blue eyes, his smile.
We'd need to test it, Minister,
to be sure.
I'd make him wear a pearl.
It's very elegant.
I'll have to talk to him.
Pinochet out of uniform
is a government without soldiers,
in other words, progress.
This country's progress
has been stunning.
It's not like Latin America.
You don't realize the...
your influence in the world.
But these "gauchos" keep protesting.
The country is full of ingrates.
They forgot everything.
So scare them.
Excuse me?
You've lost me.
Shouldn't we show
a nicer face?
If you want to scare people,
scare them with their past.
Their past of poverty,
endless queues for bread.
The opposition
misses socialism,
but the only thing people care about
is handouts.
They know
socialism makes them unhappy.
Here, you have a system
in which anyone can get rich.
Careful, not everyone.
But anyone.
You can't lose when everyone
is dreaming about being that anyone.
Move, dammit!
Move, you idiot!
Free the political prisoners!
Free them all!
Why just some of them?
Veronica!
Fucking cops!
Stop it!
Why are you hitting her?
You're hitting a woman!
Out!
How can you hit a woman?
Let her go, motherfucker!
Let her go, asshole!
Let go of me!
How much longer?
How much longer, for fuck's sake?
That's right.
Turn the news on.
OK.
There.
Free the nation
from frayed populist paths
and economical stagnation
and lead it to modernization
and progress for all Chileans.
Augusto Pinochet Ugarte.
from a very young age
showed his love for serving his country,
influenced by the stories
of the nation's forefathers
which set ablaze his courage,
and made him enter the military.
From dawn to dusk,
he worked tirelessly...
Give me that.
...Devoting all of his time,
his attention and his energy.
He sacrificed himself.
He endured everything
to accomplish his mission
to save Chile.
Iorana, President
Hear the voices of your people
Thank you for coming
Ariki Nui
Carmen!
For being here, Ariki Nui
Ariki Nui
Iorana, President
We will always be here
Thank you for giving us
A home to live in
Ariki Nui, Ariki Nui
Mahu Ariki Nui
My main concern
is...
not losing what we've won.
That's what matters.
This is for Simon, OK?
OK.
Is he asleep?
I don't know.
Nice.
How have you been?
Fine.
And Simon?
He feels lonely.
And the maid?
Fine.
Is she a good cook?
Yes.
He's not alone.
He knows I'm here.
Did they hit you much?
No.
That kid understands everything.
No, he doesn't get any of it.
Neither do I, to tell you the truth.
The maid can't do everything.
You're going to work for the NO?
To do what?
To win.
You'll legitimize Pinochet's sham.
You'll say yes, he's my president.
this is my constitution.
Mercenary.
The boy has to get up at 7am.
Why don't you stay tonight?
We'll have breakfast together.
OK.
Are they paying you well?
I can't complain.
Oh, well.
Let me give him a kiss, please.
Go ahead.
I love you, sweetheart.
We're going to get rid of Pinochet.
WAR PRISONERS MEETING POINT
34,690 TORTURED
200,000 EXILED
2,110 POLITICAL EXECUTIONS
1,248 DISAPPEARED DETAINEES
FOR FREE ELECTIONS
VOTE NO
Right.
René, we're listening.
Is that all?
I think so, isn't it?
Sorry. There's nothing else?
Something else?
Something else...
Something a little lighter.
A little nicer.
Comrade,
do you think
that what's going on in Chile is nice?
No. Let's see...
It moves me as it moves all of you.
However,
I think that
it's not very appealing.
Well. Let's try.
Let's try, from both sides,
to give more constructive opinions.
Me too?
Everyone.
Let's give our opinions, and move on.
I'd like to know if anyone thinks
we can win with this campaign.
I think the main objective...
Excuse me?
We must open the eyes
of those who don't want to vote.
That's the main objective.
Dictatorship has destroyed this country
and will continue to destroy it,
with its economic success
and 40% of the population
living below the poverty line.
We all agree
we want to win the referendum,
but some only want to win,
without really reforming Chile.
We want another kind of victory.
But the advertiser
asked a different question.
Our comrade asked
if you think that we're going to win.
The answer is no.
We don't think that we're going to win.
The referendum was lost from the moment
the fascist right called for it.
Then why pitch this campaign?
To raise awareness
and fill the spaces
the dictatorship had to open,
and which we won.
Let us fill them.
Exactly.
Let them allow us to win,
maybe, but let them accept us.
If we already lost, we should give up.
This referendum is a fraud, we know it.
Dad, what are you doing?
I'm working.
This isn't work, you're playing.
Hand me the rocket.
It's over there.
I'm going to put it together!
Really?
It's already put together.
Then I'm going to drive it.
Stop it, please.
I want to play with my train.
Go to bed.
Abstentions: 35.1%, 146...
"YES" votes: 19%.
Abstainers: 76,2%.
That's it.
Thank you.
What do you think of this?
A feeling of false hope,
deeply internalized,
preventing the voters from feeling free
at the moment of voting,
because they're completely repressed.
As a result,
with so many unanswerable questions,
the results are quite unsure.
As for the fear,
it is significantly increasing
the number of undecided voters.
These two are the undecided groups, no?
Those who don't know if they'll vote?
Yes.
It's impossible.
You can't make
a campaign with such extremes.
Their interests are too different.
It's impossible.
How impossible, would you say?
We need a miracle.
I think you've said the key word.
In other words, God,
and His celestial army,
angels and archangels.
Faith.
That's what's going to change Chile.
This country needs
a divine act.
How are you?
Fine.
I don't want to lose any clients.
Or get beat up.
Nobody will know.
I'm not here.
José Tomás, Alberto Arancibia.
Inside this rat lurks my mentor,
my best friend.
He came but "he's not here."
OK?
Don't worry, I understand.
Can I get you a drink?
Would you like that?
We have a group of undecided voters
who, in reality, would vote NO.
But the indecision
involves whether to vote or not.
What?
They're the old ladies,
around 60 or 65 years old,
middle class, or lower middle class.
They are scared of what NO represents,
a return to socialism, to recession,
to queues and all that.
And there's the young people who think
that this election is fixed,
and it's useless.
We have to find a solution.
No, a product.
We need a product
that is sufficiently appealing
to old ladies and to young people.
Ms. Carmen?
Do you have a second?
We'd like to ask you something.
While we were chatting, René told us
that you're voting YES.
Is that true?
She's voting YES.
Her silence shows
that she's voting YES.
Could you tell us why?
I'm doing fine.
My son is in college.
My daughter has work.
And what about
the dead, the tortured,
and the disappeared?
What do you think about that?
It's not that I don't care about it, but
that's all in the past.
Democracy is the future.
My General says we can have an opinion
thanks to this vote.
Democracy is the problem.
The old man's taken hold
of the term "democracy."
We haven't worked that much,
we spent our time walking and eating.
That's work, too, José Tomás.
Isn't it, Alberto?
No!
We haven't talked
about what defines us as an opposition:
human rights,
exile, injustice,
arbitrary arrests, torture,
disappearances.
All the pain we've lived through.
We didn't even mention it.
We have to.
It's got nothing to do with it.
We must talk about it.
It's too dark.
That's fear.
We can't bombard folks with fear.
They're scared. Terrorized.
We have to find a product
that appeals to people.
Democracy isn't a product.
Fine, let's call it a concept.
We have to offer
something pleasing,
but which has meaning, something...
happy.
Let's list everything that's happy.
Happiness, joy, fulfillment.
Yes, but what is...?
Springtime, parties.
The calm after the storm.
To me, democracy's fun.
It's appealing.
It's something...
attractive to experience.
A fun product.
Then happiness itself.
Of course.
What's happier than happiness?
Nothing.
Happiness in itself is happy.
What's happier than that?
Come on, we need to be serious here.
If you think I'm going to stand there
in front of all the whole coalition,
and say our campaign
will be based on jokes,
and happiness,
you're nuts.
It's totally naïve
and disrespectful.
We have to consider their pain,
their neglect.
Where is that?
How am I going to tell them
that our concept is happiness?
Why not?
How's it going?
They're there.
Pass me the...
Now?
Thank you.
You're welcome.
They're here.
I'm on it.
Hey, Diego.
This is what we have.
I like these ones best.
And Guzman?
Is he watching you?
Is he watching me?
How?
No, he won't know how.
Great. Is he here or not?
No.
Fine.
Look, here he is.
Fernando.
How are you?
It's good to see you.
René Saavedra, Fernando Costa.
We know each other.
Really?
Through work.
I've rescued him before.
He's going to work with us
as a director.
You know very well
that I don't do that.
You've done it a thousand times.
I don't know, call up a rocker,
a folk singer,
someone to write an anthem.
No. I want a jingle.
No art,
no folk, no pop, no rock,
a jingle.
Do you really think
they'll let us go out on air?
Yes.
They'll throw us in jail!
We don't know.
We don't?
The key thing is all being here.
Thanks. Many wouldn't have dared.
Listen,
if you draw a line with this vote,
what's left?
No more!
No more Pinochet and dictatorship!
Well?
It could work!
It's perfect, man.
No more torture, no more deaths.
No more censorship.
No more abuse.
No more debt, no more interest,
no more unpaid bills.
How's things with you?
We need more people, more time.
More content.
We have to fill 15 minutes
every day for a month.
They fill each day.
3 weeks to go and we got nothing.
15 minutes is too much!
We better get to work.
That one... It's finished.
See you at the production office.
Yeah, he's coming.
How are you, Lucho?
We're about to begin.
Is everything OK?
Yeah. How are you?
Fine.
Great.
Weren't you going to give it up?
It's just advice.
Don't bullshit me, man.
You have an easy life with your son,
your own house,
a sports car,
plenty to eat.
No one has bothered you
since you got here.
Let's be partners.
I'll cut you in on the agency.
You're a rat, boss.
Why?
You threaten me and you offer me...
Hello. How are you?
How are you?
How about those dishes!
They're great!
We're ready for you.
We'll be right over.
Whenever you say!
A partnership?
Yes.
A good percentage.
I'm going to do this anyway.
That camp.
Hello.
How are you?
Nice of you to come.
Hello. You look nice.
Thank you.
I'm handling everything, it's all fine.
Excellent, thank you.
This is suicide, don't be an idiot.
Fire me.
First positions!
Get out.
Fire me!
Get out!
Leave.
Go ahead, fire me.
Think about my offer. It's good.
Fine. We're done here. It's perfect.
What is it?
Important accounts
from the state broadcaster.
I'll talk with the bitch. Where is she?
Over there.
It's great, isn't it?
It's perfect.
Everything OK?
Is it working?
Yes.
Is it?
Chicken.
Mind the radiation.
Don't get too close.
I'll stay away.
Yes.
I don't think this thing's very safe.
You OK with the skirt?
Yes, I feel comfortable.
Good.
Great. Everything suits you.
It's really good. It's beautiful.
What dish did you choose?
What?
We'll start with dessert.
We're getting ready to shoot.
First of all,
I'd like to say
that what you're about to see
fits with the current social context.
After all, today,
Chile is thinking of its future.
Let's go.
They say what they like
I have freedom of thought
Because I feel it's time
To find freedom
We're tired of the abuse
It's time to change
We're done with poverty
I'm going to say NO
Chile
Happiness is coming
Is that all you have?
Because...
This is all we have as,
let's say, a draft.
This is the campaign.
It's like an ad for Coca-Cola.
It's more than that!
With all due respect,
we're doing something much more serious.
I was also exiled.
He's Manuel Saavedra's son,
I don't know if you know him.
Everyone knows Manuel Saavedra.
We're using advertising language
that is universal, familiar, attractive,
optimistic,
but with a political concept behind it.
Ricardo.
Look, José Tomás,
I understand perfectly well that
there's advertising semiology.
This is a campaign.
We must be pragmatic.
We are, by getting involved in
a referendum held for the dictatorship.
We're taking big risks,
we have no idea what's going to happen.
I understand.
But I also understand
that there are ethical limits.
What's your name?
René Saavedra.
René.
I knew your father very well.
René, maybe in your editing room,
making ads for big corporations,
you've lost a little perspective.
We have physically suffered
the violence of this dictatorship.
My brother has disappeared,
my best friends' throats cut.
This is a campaign of silence.
We understand, and for good reason,
your pain,
and the pain of all of those involved.
But you're missing a key point.
I'm not an idiot, José Tomás.
I get what this is about.
This is legitimization.
This is a campaign to silence
what has really happened.
I'm shocked, Fernando.
I'm sorry, comrade and friend of mine,
you're involved in this shit.
I see here what you really are.
Those images are what you are.
I see your point, but understand...
I understand perfectly well!
But I will not be party to something
for which history will never forgive us!
So you can go fuck yourself, asshole.
Go get fucked, yourself.
Excuse me.
Listen.
Yes.
Where are the parties in this?
They're here, in this idea.
I see all the parties,
but you explain it better.
The rainbow represents
all the political parties?
Is that the idea?
Yes, they're all there.
It's all in the rainbow.
All the party colors
and political tendencies are there.
For example: the red,
which is very powerful,
represents the radicals, communism.
Socialism!
Sorry, socialism.
There's blue, that's very...
The most hopeful one,
for the Christian Democrats.
The green is totally...
Social Democrat.
Orange for the Humanists,
and all those who feel included in that.
The PPD can also feel included.
All the colors are there.
And they all, democratically,
bring their differences to the NOs.
I'll go on foot.
Comrade?
Are you ashamed to be with us?
Goodbye, brave one!
Don't be an asshole!
You misunderstand our politicians.
Some are worth the bother.
Please!
They all want out while they can.
We already got what we wanted.
Now it's time to work!
Excuse me, René,
I don't mean to be a pain,
but what is this shit?
Are you selling chickens?
It's something else, Veronica.
Then, this is it.
NO, orange, NO, singing bird,
NON, petit arbre.
NO, mental age of 5.
No, it's not that.
Shit!
This.
NO, rainbow.
Almost. That one, yes.
Almost.
OK.
Something like...
Yes.
Looks good on you.
But we're going to win.
With that?
Yes. With that.
Sure.
Where were you, man?
I was at the station.
They want the title to be:
"Hair Salon Love."
No, that's really bad.
Really bad.
Too menopausal.
Can I have that?
Thank you.
You've got a lot of nerve.
This is going to make us famous.
A rainbow?
Yes, a rainbow.
But it's for faggots, isn't it?
No, I think it has to do
with the flag of the Mapuche people.
Gay Mapuches?
No, Mapuche Indians.
Do you know why you're paranoid?
Because you've got
homosexual communists
there in your office.
No Mr. Minister, in my office.
there are no homosexuals nor commies.
Don't worry about it.
No-one will see that propaganda.
You think?
Of course. Everyone will be sleeping.
I'm sleeping at that time.
Me too.
See? Everyone's sleeping.
Who's behind the NO campaign?
I don't know any of those people.
Who are they?
People too much at ease for me.
Be careful what you say, Guzman.
If I open that door
you have to close your eyes.
Give me that.
Stay here.
MARXIST TRAITOR
Don't go out!
Carmen!
What are you doing?
What are you doing here?
Go to bed.
Go! This is a nice neighborhood.
Go to bed, Ma'am!
Go to bed, you old bitch!
Brats.
Let's go inside, Carmen.
Did you see them? Do you know them?
I saw them up close.
What happened?
We were all threatened last night.
Not me, as no-one knows I'm here.
Why are you surprised?
They know where we live and work,
they know everything.
Calm down, we'll be fine.
The eyes of the world are watching us.
I've been being followed for ages.
It's normal that they follow us.
It means we're doing well.
We're getting to them.
We have to go to the theater.
The actors are waiting.
Let's go.
Let's go again! From the top!
Come on.
From the top.
This is a positive message, isn't it?
With happiness and...
Smiling... As much as you can.
We'll try.
Like "We Are The World". Up there.
No. Nothing like that!
No.
That was never...
No. Let's go.
It isn't a ring shining on your finger
It isn't the prince of the gypsies
It isn't the sword of a musketeer
It isn't a mystery for the sorcerer
I don't like it, no
I don't want it, no
I don't want it, no, no
I hate seeing him every day
I don't like his cold smile
I don't like his literature
I'm depressed by his mini-culture
I don't like it, no
I don't want it, no
I don't want it, no, no
His words and deeds bring nothing
He's no leader to follow
His words fail to move me
He simply cannot move me
I don't like it, no
I don't want it, no
I don't want it, no, no
The editing room is in back.
Action!
Don't think that he's indispensable
Don't think that he's eternal
Don't fluster me with nonsense
I don't like him in any way
I don't like it, no
I don't want it, no
Let's do the shot now.
Ready, Matías?
We got it.
Silence! Sound?
Rolling!
Camera?
Speed!
Action!
Isn't he too tall?
No, he's perfect.
I don't like it, no
What happened?
Fernando?
Get me some homemade bread...
It's weird.
There's nothing else right now.
No, but how...
Fernando, please.
Fernando, this looks good.
I don't care,
no one eats baguettes here.
It's fine. It's not a problem. It works.
It needs identity.
Is this a picnic to you?
What did we talk about?
People have to see themselves in it.
Please, it's lovely. It's fine.
It's great.
It looks nice.
Fernando, it's great.
Help me. Stop being a drag.
Hello, Pato, how are you?
Thank you for coming.
Hello, Patricio. How are you?
How are you, Pato?
Hello. René Saavedra.
How are you?
We'll mike you up.
Silence, we're going to roll.
Three...
Two...
One... Action!
We democrats are transparent.
We understand that government,
or "public affairs"
to the Romans,
interests us all
and should take place in public view.
I am trained in democracy.
Chilean democracy
made great efforts
to move our country forward,
to stimulate its growth,
for social justice...
René.
What's up, man? Don't be childish.
You think they're ruining your campaign,
and we're losing votes?
What's up with you?
Nothing.
I think there is.
It doesn't belong to you.
They have the right to speak.
We've kept our mouths shut
for too long now.
Important people are involved.
It's a drag.
Action!
I'm the mother
of Alfredo Rojas Castañeda, disappeared
on March 4, 1975.
I'm the sister of Nicomedes Segundo.
I'm the wife of Enrique...
Newton Morales Saavedra...
...detained...
I'm the mother of Manuel...
Miguel Angel...
...disappeared...
I'm the sister of Ruperto Torres,
disappeared 13 October 1973.
You can decide
to never let this happen again.
No more disappearances.
It's good.
It's good, but a little ugly.
It doesn't fit with what we're doing.
We're using it, no matter what.
Why?
Because it's good.
Because it has content,
and we have 15 minutes to fill.
No matter what? Why that tone?
What tone?
Who makes the decisions here?
You're not the boss, you know.
I'm not arguing this bullshit.
What bullshit, motherfucker?
We're working. Take it easy!
This isn't personal!
My joy is different than yours.
Oh, really? What's mine then?
I don't know.
What happened here in the last 15 years
was never shown on TV
Doing that now is my joy.
Yes, but if it goes wrong,
it's going to look pathetic.
It works.
I got goosebumps.
It's visceral. I love it.
I'd put it in.
It's in then.
And what if we mention it's been
15 years since we've had a show
that is dissident?
Yes, of course. There's...
the greeting, right?
The slogan is "Happiness is coming."
"Chile, happiness is coming."
"Hello. Chile, happiness is coming."
No, actually...
"Chile, happiness is coming"
and "hello" after.
Weird, right?
Yes, but I think it works.
And then, "It's been 15 years since..."
Exactly.
We could try it once.
If not, we start over.
You're shooting it.
Perfect, thank you.
We'll do it then.
OK.
Rolling.
Mark.
Patricio Bañados, take one.
And...
Action.
Chile, happiness is coming.
Hello.
For the first time in 15 years,
those who don't share
the official point of view
are talking to you
through their own TV show.
I am returning to my profession
that I was removed from.
15 minutes in 15 years isn't much.
Let's talk about that coming happiness.
Happiness is coming
Chile
They say what they like
I have freedom of thought
I feel that it's time
To find freedom
We're tired of the abuse
It's time to change
We're done with poverty
I'm going to say NO
A rainbow is born
After the storm
I want to see flourish
A thousand ways of thinking
Without dictatorship
Happiness will come
I think about the future
I'm going to say NO
We're going to say NO
With the power of my voice
I sing it without fear
We're going to say NO