"A sexually repressed society
will resort to violence." Wilhelm Reich
What are you doing here?
You were supposed to stay inside.
I didn't know you had another job.
I called these guys. One during
the day and another one at night.
Let's go.
Lie down as flat as you can.
And if we got to stop, pull that old tarp
and cover yourself and don't move.
I'm going to drop in the place of a friend.
It's at night, but at least you
have something to eat.
Why are you doing all of this?
Because you're in trouble.
You know you don't owe me anything.
Don't talk like that.
That's no help.
Angela, this is Bill.
I told you about him.
I'm going to go to Roberto's to find a
place for him to stay for a couple of days.
I should be back in an hour.
Go have a seat.
I'll bring you something to eat.
I don't have any money.
That's OK.
Most people who come here
don't have any money.
Luis said he's trying to get you
out of here in the next truck.
That's his idea.
Well, if I understood correctly,
you are in some kind of trouble.
Yeah ...
You don't look like someone
who gets into trouble.
That's 'cause, in a way, I probably
still look like a banker.
I jumped bail.
You don't like it?
I'm not very hungry.
Angela, can I pay tomorrow?
- No problem.
Bye. - Adios.
That was Luis who called.
His friend, Roberto, has been arrested.
He asked if you could find a place
to stay for tonight,
and he can meet you here tomorrow.
Sure ...
Thanks for the food.
Sure.
Do you have a place to go?
Ola.
- How are you?
Very good. How are you?
Oh, thank you.
You're welcome.
What did she give you?
A quarter.
Why?
I give her some food every night,
and she insists on giving me a quarter.
Out of dignity.
She will not accept free food.
Even if she can't feed her kids,
and she has three jobs.
Three jobs?
- Yeah ...
she sells flowers in the evening,
as you can see.
She cleans offices at night and
during the day she works in a sweatshop ...
with her oldest daughter.
-A "sweatshop"?
Yeah... you know ...
the kind where they work twelve hours a day
with half an hour break ...
for less than minimum wage.
Her husband left her.
She's all alone.
See? Not much dignity there.
Not much luck either.
- Do you believe in luck?
I believe more in bad luck.
You?
Yeah... I believe everything in life
happens from bad luck...
and will.
Will? You mean like the will of God?
No ... No.
I mean your own will.
I stopped believing in God a long time ago.
Really?
Yeah. Too many people
who died in His name.
It's here.
Welcome to my living scrapbook.
It's safe.
We're on the roof,
so it's a little hot.
That door goes out.
And when one person needs privacy,
the other one can go outside.
Listen... I don't have
to stay here.
Of course you don't.
Don't worry.
I'm used to having people here.
The other good thing about being on the roof,
is that from up there you can see the world.
Come out. I'll show you.
What's that?
That is ...
The "L" of "Life."
See?
I also have the "H".
There's no "H" in "Life".
So, it must be the "H" of "Hell".
I take it, you don't
believe in Hell either?
Oh, yeah. I believe in Hell.
I believe in Hell on Earth.
I see it every day.
It was the old sign from the hotel.
I dragged it in at the beginning.
It still worked. It was my only source
of light. I got used to it.
From up here you can hear
all the life of the city...
and you can see all layers of society.
on that side only poor people.
Dealers, prostitutes ...
below us is a transient hotel ...
for those who don't have anything anymore
but still need to find a way to survive
over here we have middle class people ...
in their condo apartments.
I recommend watching the couple in this apartment,
who have sex every night at their window.
And over here,
we have the financial district.
with its luxurious hotels and some of
the most powerful banks in the world.
I used to work over there.
So, what went wrong for the banker?
Ambition... need for power...
Really?
That's it? - Pretty much.
I made a big hole in the bank.
And? What happened?
And from that point everything collapsed.
Lawsuits, bankruptcy.
Mine. Not the bank's of course.
I lost my house; my family rejected me;
my wife divorced me.
Everybody deserted me.
That's funny.
Where I come from, the son is in trouble,
everybody comes to help.
It's from Peru.
A friend of mine brought it back.
Go ahead.
It will help you dream at night.
I don't dream anymore. - You do.
You just don't want to remember them.
Maybe.
They always think I should
leave this place, but...
I've been here for years
without any problems.
I guess you're not really interested
in possessions, are you?
If possessions were important in life,
rich people would be happy.
You can sleep in the bed with me,
if you want.
Don't worry, you don't have to have
sex with me.
If you prefer, I have a sleeping bag.
I could set it up for you over there.
That would be fine...
thank you.
OK... enjoy.
Since it's very hot
and there're no walls, ...
if nudity bothers you,
you can go outside while I undress.
Or you can stay.
It doesn't bother me.
Really?
- Really.
Well, I'll just turn towards the wall.
OK. Good night.
Try to remember your dreams.
Oh my ...
Hi.
How are you?
Hey ...
How come you didn't run away?
I guess I needed a chance to be alone.
Away from it all...
solitude for a lonely man.
Beer and burrito for a lonely man?
Sounds great.
You were right, it's...
very, very interesting to
watch people from up here.
Did you notice how frantic they all are?
They all run around honking at each other.
as if the few minutes they gain
would change anything in their life.
I guess that's kind of the way
I've been living - always running.
Running for more.
You American people live in the future.
The future? - What did you do
with the first money you earned?...
first big chunk you got?
Bought a house, new car.
Invested the rest in stock.
To make more money later.
And what would you have done
with more money?
Bought a bigger house,
more stock, probably.
See?
You continue to kill yourself
for later, for the future.
Rather than enjoying what you had at the time,
you risked everything for the future.
I guess you could look at it that way.
Since we're born
without that ...
if God put us here it was because
He had a purpose for us...
a destiny that we were
supposed to figure out.
Can you see how crazy it is to think
that we have a purpose in life?
Well, you don't think
your life has a purpose?
No. I don't.
We are here by chance, by accident.
Your father met your mother, fucked her,
and you were born.
And you can think of two million good reasons
for you father to have met another girl,
and then you wouldn't even be here.
But, who am I to talk?
We need some music here.
I should go meet Luis.
Luis says the next truck doesn't leave
for two or three days.
Cops are still looking for you.
You know Luis was my driver?
Yeah ...
Luis is a great guy. Do you know
anything about him?
Luis was a farmer ... in Honduras.
He and his wife had a couple of
fields of coffee.
They were able to live from it, you know.
Not well, but they lived,
until small growers weren't needed
any more.
And, little by little,
they were not able to survive.
So he had to sell the farm,
but his wife didn't want him to.
They moved to Tegucigalpa to find jobs,
and then his wife got sick.
He could not afford any doctors
or medicine, so
she died.
That is when he came here.
Can you see the irony?
Immigrant driver gets his banker boss
out of trouble.
Look, I don't need him to get me
out of trouble, OK.
I'm done.
You didn't get it, did you?
You exist. That is
what matters.
That you live.
- It's not so bad being at the end.
It's actually quite peaceful,
almost liberating.
Can you stop thinking of yourself as different
or more special than anybody else?
For me, I'm close to suffering all day long,
and then it's not peaceful.
Well, you're right about
one thing, Professor ...
there's nothing more to lose.
So, what do you suggest?
Stop thinking and start to feel
what is around you.
The city, music, me ...
Have you even really looked at me,
since we met?
I just mean as a human being,
one human being to another human being.
What if for once you let things happen
without trying to control them?
Close your eyes and try to feel.
What are you doing?
You agreed you had nothing to lose.
Don't think anymore.
Just enjoy.
Who are you?
I'm just a little part of your
here-and-now. No more than that.
You're right. It's my turn.
I come from Nicaragua, where the people
are extremely poor.
My mother was from Algeria.
- From where?
Algeria ... My father
was the one from Nicaragua.
I was raised by my grandmother,
after my parents were killed.
They were killed?
They died when I was very young.
So I was raised by my grandmother, ...
and my grandmother was a teacher.
Actually she couldn't find a job as a teacher,
so to feed us she became a janitor.
She wound up cleaning this huge library
at night, at the central university.
That's really where I got
most of my education.
I was too young to stay alone,
so she used to bring me with her.
For a young girl, it was this
huge, magical place ...
with thousands of books.
She taught me how to choose my books,
and read while waiting for her.
after she died, I took over her job,
cleaning as fast as I could, and spending
the rest of the time reading.
Let's go inside.
Are you here illegally?
Yeah. I want to keep it that way.
I really don't want to become
a part of this country.
What did you do when you first got here?
It was fun, actually.
The only address I had was a
hippie community in San Francisco
I always thought they would be
the only Americans I could deal with.
This is the only thing I kept from there.
- What happened?
- It was great.
From the beginning they
welcomed me, they helped me.
They taught me to speak American.
Some of those pictures are from there.
Still uncomfortable with me?
Seems like you enjoyed it outside.
I did.
Don't tell me you'll sleep
on the floor again?
Don't worry. I know I'm not the type
that bankers like.
I don't have blond hair
or an American body.
I'm not even pure Latina.
I'm just a mutt.
Why are you doing all this?
Does nudity bother you?
Better?
You know, when I was a teenager we used
to say: "Life's a bitch, and then you die."
I guess I'm beginning to understand
what it means.
Well, we say the same thing, but ...
at the end we added:
"So fuck the bitch."
Look, I agree, for most people
life is not very beautiful.
I just try to make every moment
as good as possible.
See? I'm exactly the opposite of what
men like you are interested in.
How do you know what kind
of women I like?
Why?
Do you have a hard-on?
No ...
Show me.
Huevones! That's what you are.
You people are such Puritans.
- Huevones ...
It means "big balls, no guts."
It's only you and me here.
Nobody to judge you.
Show me!
Bravo!
Come here.
Don't think now.
Just enjoy.
What do you feel right now?
I don't know ...
Arousal.
Me too.
Strong desire for you to kiss my breasts.
Touch me ... here.
Come inside me.
Fuck me.
Take me; take me like ...
Come on. Harder, harder!
Do you like it? - Yeah ...
Did you enjoy watching yourself?
I think I have a hard time looking
at myself, right now.
You should love this guy who came so hard.
Maybe it's the banker you should
have dropped long ago.
So sex is the solution for you?
You know, research shows that ...
a lack of sexual pleasure
leads to frustration ...
bitterness, anger, violence ...
All that, huh?
When's the last time you had sex?
I don't know ...
months ago.
And when you were married,
how often did you have sex?
Once a week, ...
maybe.
Do you masturbate?
You Americans are such a bunch of
frustrated hypocrites. I can't believe it.
You can show body-parts and heads
being blown away on TV ...
movies, video games ...
like it's no value whatsoever, but ...
you can't talk openly about masturbation.
I don't get it.
Doesn't everybody have sex?
Doesn't every boy or man masturbate ...
have erections.
Why should it be hidden?
- Yeah, you're probably right.
I mean, of course I masturbated
every now and then when I was a kid.
I guess I just stopped it after college.
It seemed childish.
Pleasure is childish.
You people.
Do you regret it? - What?
Both ... that you stopped masturbating
and having sex with me.
Having sex with you? No.
Masturbating ... I don't know.
Why do you ask?
To see that even in your
desperate situation ...
having a good time now is better
than waiting.
Now, now, now ...
Drink now, live now, fuck now ...
I'm going to start calling you "Now."
Hello, "Now." How are you today?
It will be a pleasure.
And I will call you "Later."
Life is now, Mister Later.
I know, it's hard to masturbate
in this country
where the President is preaching
abstinence to kids.
He's trying to transform this
entire generation with his
insane idea of abstinence, while he's off
doing bombs on women and children.
Why are you still in this country ...
if this is what you think of us?
I was waiting for you.
I feel like I'm more useful
here than there.
Useful, you mean, like ...
giving food to poor people?
That and my work at the clinic,
and here ...
Once a week I tend to people
at the hotel with medical needs.
Plus ...
Can you hear it? The wind!
Can you hear it?
Come on. It's coming from
the east... Come on.
Come on; help me.
Come sit with me.
Take off your clothes,
soldier boy.
Let the wind touch you.
It comes from the East. You'll see.
It's warm and dry.
I love to feel it.
You're not afraid of ashamed
of anything, are you.
But I just have one life to live.
I mean, I can be afraid, but shame
is for those who believe in ...
heaven or a judgment day, ...
you know, who kind of live in the future.
Come on, ... come on!
Eh, come on. What are you doing?
Remember Mr. Later.
You are living on Now's time.
Wait a sec. Those are the
only ones I have.
Time to get rid of the past.
I just killed the old you.
Be Happy!
A poor guy will find them
and use them.
I hope your illness is not contagious.
Now lay down; let the wind
touch your body.
So you think teenagers and kids
should have sex?
Sure ... sure, if they feel like it.
When they should at least know it's
available to them, a nice girl for them.
It's good to learn about
life, and themselves.
They shouldn't be ashamed about it,
thinking that it's bad.
It's called "natural sexuality."
It's a natural need, like any other.
What are you doing?
- I'm feeling the heat.
Listen, your wife is coming
to Eddie's to see you.
My wife?
She got in touch with Luis,
who's bringing her there.
He told me he'll make sure it's OK,
it'll be safe.
Can you tell her you couldn't find me?
Why don't I just tell her
you don't want to see her?
Thank you, Professor Now,
for reminding me of the way.
I never thought I would see
a banker wearing one of my T-shirts.
Yeah, well, banker's shirt was thrown
to the wind yesterday.
Hi. -Hi.
You know, the police came to
my parent's house ...
to see if I knew where you were.
I can't believe you jumped bail.
You're a fugitive now ...
a wanted man.
Do you realize that ...
I invested my best years ...
into our marriage.
"Invested."
You're starting to sound like me.
And what do you expect in return?
What did I expect?
A normal life. With my family.
"A normal life" ...
What is that?
- What?
What do you mean?
A normal life is a family
living together ...
taking care of their children ...
going on vacation with family and friends.
I'm glad you're so sure of that.
- And what's wrong with that?
- Something must have been.
Well ...
Yes ...
You.
You ruined it.
I'm sorry.
So, what are you going to do now?
I'm leaving the country
in a day or so.
Why?
Why don't you just go to jail?
It's only eight years.
They'll let you out early ...
and you will have paid your debt
to society, and ... - What debt?
What is it that I owe society?
You mean the debt for doing what I was
raised to do, what I was trained to do?
The debt for what I got paid to do?
Or do you mean my debt to the bank ...
that spent years pressuring me
into do its dirty work
You mean that debt?
- What are you talking about?
What dirty work are you talking about?
You've changed, Bill.
Yeah ...
Let's hope so.
And where will you go?
Nicaragua.
Nicaragua?
And then what?
You'll be a fugitive for the
rest of your life.
You won't ever be able to come back.
What exactly do I have to come back to?
Good luck, Bill.
Wait ...
Can you pay for the water?
I don't have any money.
These are yours. I don't
need them anymore.
Enjoy Nicaragua.
Sorry, guess I should knock first?
How did it go?
Why?
But why?
Just to hear you say that.
No, I was on my way back, and ...
passed this crazy store ...
and I just wanted to give it to you.
So I stole it.
- You stole it?
Yeah ...
I was scared to death.
I couldn't stop running.
But it was kind of exciting.
- It was kind of stupid.
I mean, if they caught you
and called the cops ...
Nah, it felt good anyway,
after my dive into the past.
You can talk about it, if you want.
No, there's not much to talk about.
We really didn't have very much
to say to each other.
I felt ...
alone ... sitting with her today.
Well, you're always alone.
I've felt alone most of my life.
This solitude of being missed ...
don't belong to any group ...
couldn't find my place ...
For Latino men I was always "La Negrita."
Little Black one.
Just good to play with.
Here is ... a little souvenir ...
from that time.
So ...
was "la Negrita" ever loved?
Well ... there is true love,
and then there is everything else.
Then how do you recognize true love,
Professor Now?
You don't, I guess.
But any feeling is worth it.
So just enjoy it for what it is ...
and don't be afraid to walk away
when the feeling goes.
But how do you ...
truly enjoy something when you know
it's going to end soon?
What do you mean?
Like now, with you ...
I can't stop thinking that in a day or two
I'll be gone, and ...
won't ever see you again.
Same answer, sooner or later ...
you have to trust it.
Just enjoy it. It's worth it.
You'll deal with that time when it comes.
What's here now will always be yours.
What would you desire most?
Right this minute? And don't stop yourself.
Everything is OK.
I'd like to watch you masturbate.
Unless, you know, you ...
Thank you.
My pleasure.
Do you like it. - Very much.
I'm always hungry after an orgasm.
You know, for centuries ...
women have been seducing men through food,
doing all sorts of crazy stuff.
Well, like what?
Well ...
for example, women used to make bread
and sit on the dough ... naked
and infuse the dough with their juices.
Really?
Where do you come from?
You really want to know?
Yeah.
That's my grandmother's village.
that's her writing.
She's wishing me a good life.
She wrote it for me before she died.
That's my mother.
She was a singer.
She danced, too.
That is my mother ...
her only recording.
I have very few memories of my parents.
It's hard to grow up without parents.
What happened to them?
- They were killed ...
by the contras in the beginning
of the civil war.
They were part of the
first literacy campaign ...
teaching peasants to read and write
This is the only thing I have left
from my father.
I thought you said he was a teacher.
He was ...
but he was a "Sandinista"
He used to go help the peasants harvesting
sugar cane in the fields ...
every week-end.
So what about these "Sandinistas?"
Well ...
In short we had a dictator
for two decades ...
financed and supported by the U.S.
The Sandinistas fought them for years,
and little by little the people joined them
and created a popular revolution,
deposing the dictator
And what happened?
And it became a new country.
with free health care, free schools ...
literacy campaign in the country ...
But ...
Unfortunately, the Sandinistas are
what your country calls socialists
The Sandinistas didn't want their money
and resources to go to U.S. corporations,
they wanted it to go to their people.
So, your actor President, Reagan
ordered the CIA to put together an army,
called the contras
to overthrow our government.
and this created a civil war,
that raged on ...
Your CIA got entangled in its mess
and realized that it would need
more money to continue, but
it was a secret war, that the
American Congress did not want to finance.
So, the CIA decided to sell weapons to Iran
which was forbidden by your
Congress and by international law.
And when your CIA needed more money,
they decided to sell drugs.
Cocaine, to be precise,
in your country to finance the Contras
You read way too many novels.
And you don't read enough.
It's all documented.
Reagan authorized the CIA ...
to finance an army to
overthrow a government
with money from weapons and drug trade.
Carter first, and then Reagan
after him, in full force.
You see, that is what I am trying
to explain to you,
People here do not know what is going on
in their own country.
You are educated by Walt Disney,
and Fox News, and ...
Star Wars.
You live in a bubble.
Your country has been responsible for the
removal or assassination of
dozens of leaders around the world.
You want names?
Patrice Lumumba, Prime Minister of Congo.
Salvador Allende, President of Chile.
Mossadeq, Prime Minister of Iran.
All democratically elected, all dead
because of the CIA organized coup.
Your country has initiated massacres
in Indonesia, Guatemala, Iran ...
- OK.
OK ...
Sorry.
I get worked up.
That is why my parents died.
It's hard for me to talk only about it.
You don't believe me, do you?
That is what was left from my parent's car.
After the Contras killed them,
they came to my grandmother's house,
and tossed it at her feet.
She knew immediately what it meant.
You know ...
what's confusing is that ...
for the last thirty years I've been living
in a world where we were the heroes ...
and what you're describing
is completely different.
It's like two totally different worlds.
Did you really believe in this system
in which you were a banker?
Yeah, of course.
I mean, why wouldn't I?
Your system remains only because it has
exploited and plundered dozens of countries ...
and oppressed and starved millions of people
around the world for decades
You know, I worked in foreign markets.
I was an international trader,
and traders are supposed to influence
foreign markets.
With the international banking system
it's very easy
to cripple the economy of another country.
That's what I did for ten years,
and I was rewarded for it.
You know what international bankers
call themselves?
"Masters of the Universe"
You're kidding, right?
- No, it's true.
We spent our time bidding on the economy
of countries
Buy Brazil, bid half a million on Pakistan,
sell Argentina
Oh, man ...
How did you put a hole in the bank,
"Master of the Universe"?
Well ...
It was during the time when
Argentina was falling apart ...
unable to repay its debt and
heading for election ...
and we were supporting candidates ...
- Who's "We"?
Well, the government,
the US government, of course.
Of course.
And?
And ...
The bank suddenly decided to buy
Argentine debt in massive numbers
and they felt for sure that our candidate
would be elected no matter what.
And since I'd had so much success
doing the same thing with Brazilian debt,
they called me in and put me in charge
of the operation.
And?
And ...
They put enormous pressure on me to ...
buy an incredible amount of Argentine paper
At that time I was thinking
it was the best thing to do.
I knew that if I was successful
we would make so much money
that I would be king of the bank.
How could you make so much money
if the country could not repay its debt?
Well ...
You buy the debt from the original lender
at ten cents on the dollar
and then, afterwards, you sue the
government to repay to loan at face value.
I see ...
Well, what happened?
At the time I was so caught up
in the gamble,
and I was "Master of the Universe",
that I continued to buy
without authorization,
signing the papers myself,
even after the bank had
stopped the project.
So, how come you didn't make so much money?
Well ...
the wrong guy was elected.
Depends for who.
Maybe.
He decided not to repay the debt.
Never happened before..
Wasn't it the best thing he could do
for his country?
I think I understand why you have come
to hate this country so much.
My parents' death was a real turning point for me.
I made me open my eyes and wonder why.
Why all these violence, why
all these deaths, all these misery.
I'm going to go get some fresh air.
- You're OK?
Yeah ...
You don't sleep much, do you?
- Not any more.
I'm late.
I was too sure..
How are you feeling?
Right now?
Feeling like I want to watch you shower.
Go on.
And according to Professor Now, I don't
have to hide the fact that that excites me.
Of course not.
It's a pleasure for you to get excited.
It's a pleasure for me
to see you get excited.
You can masturbate, if you want.
- I think I'd prefer to be inside you.
Wait ... wait for me, wait.
Oh ... thank you.
Thank you.
That was great ... great.
Oh God, I have to go. I have to go.
It is crazy at the clinic.
I hope they pay you
You're funny! You think I am paid?
What? You're not?
With what?
Why do you think these people are paying?
What about the doctors?
Same. Everybody who works there
is a volunteer.
Are they real doctors?
O Madre!
Everybody who works there has a diploma.
Yeah? What about you?
Yeah, me too.
I have my nurse's degree.
I know.
I know it's hard for you people to
understand wanting to go to work every day.
Even Saturday, without pay.
You're right. It's another world.
I have to go.
See?
Just a minute.
What are you doing here?
Well, I'm very sick, doctor.
I think my appendix is inflamed.
Very stupid for you to come here.
Who told you where I was?
- Luis.
Look. I don't want to bother you. I just want to
stay here for a while and watch you ...
and learn. If I'm bothering you,
I can leave
You'd do better to watch them.
You'll learn faster.
I think you might be a little on the
wrong track, Mr. Later.
Is there any such thing as the right track, Professor Now?
Good ... good answer.
So, did you learn anything today?
- Well, I prefer the private session.
Oh, my God!
You scared me!
I didn't know you were back!
- I just wanted to see you.
I'll come back later,
if you're going to be here.
It's just like friends, Diego.
This is my student, "Later".
Later?
- Later. Hi, Diego.
I never knew you were teaching, too.
Yeah, she's a wonderful teacher.
- A-ha ...
Teaching what?
Life rescue.
- Really?
Interesting.
It's hot here.
Ah ... I'm going to go ...
Oh, no, no, no, please stay.
I ... just came bye to say "hi."
I'm in between two planes.
I can't believe it. You're leaving again?
Well ...
Diego is a reporter.
Always going around the world.
Just got back from Pakistan.
Where the fuck are you going now?
Congo.
Don't go.
Come dance with me. - No, it's OK. I'm just
gonna go outside and get some fresh air.
Hey!
I don't want you to be upset.
I'm not.
Diego is a love of mine ...
and I miss him.
It's OK.
You don't owe me anything.
It's me that owes you.
Enjoy your time with him.
I can go, if you want.
Of course not.
He has to go.
I just want to spend a little time
with him, and then I'm going to take him
to the airport with Luis' car.
OK.
I'll be here.
What?
Nothing. Never mind.
Come with me.
- What? Where?
To the bedroom.
I spoke with Diego.
I want you to be a part
of this too. - Well thank you both,
very much, but I'm afraid ...
I can't do that.
I'm still this dumb American who freaks out when
he hears his lover having sex with someone else.
I'm sorry.
I just missed him a lot.
Come on now.
I can't .. I can't do that.
It would just be for a minute.
He has to go anyway.
Do it for me ... if nothing else.
Oh God, I thought you were
never going to come back
Sorry man, I had to bribe him.
I ... I'm not really ...
We don't want to hear it.
Just let Now be in charge.
Who is "Now"?
A friend of his.
What the ... ?
Listen, my friend. Enjoy.
OK? I prefer women ...
but I've been known to experiment.
Salud.
And ...
when there's a beautiful woman on top ...
Does this excite you, Darling?
Too many in bed?
what a question ...
But it's more than that.
That sounds nice to me.
Come with us.
That would be nice.
Not bad for a student.
And he clearly likes it.
I'm sorry ...
I can't.
Hi.
It finally cooled off.
I thought for tonight I'd do something special.
I stopped at an Italian tratoria.
The menu is Italian antipasti and Lambrusco.
You were reading ... ?
No, not really.
I picked it up
when I saw you coming.
It looks better.
Come on.
How was your time alone?
OK, I guess.
I was ... thinking, of course.
What were you thinking about?
I'm leaving tomorrow ...
this morning.
You could stay longer, if you want to.
I think Professor Now is right.
I have a whole new life to start.
Besides, we know that only foolish students
fall in love with their professors.
Well ...
you know ...
you leaving this morning will be
as hard for me as it is for you.
Don't forget, that for me, too,
love is the most important feeling.
It's the only one which redeems mankind.
Do you love him?
- Who?
Yeah ...
But you have to understand.
I'm not like you.
Saying that I love him does not mean
that I don't love you ...
or that I love you any less.
So you believe in ...
free love?
Yeah, of course I do.
Free love is the only true love.
It's the love you keep on testing
with others, and the love which endures.
That is the only form of love
which liberates the ones who live it ...
rather than limiting their freedom.
You're a dreamer.
But I'm not the only one.
What can I do for you?
Remember last night?
Don't worry.
I spent the last twenty years
taking care of my desires. - No ...
It's my turn.
Please.
Kiss me.
Isn't it beautiful?
You know the most precious gift
you gave me?
Anal sex?
No ...
You gave me strength.
I mean, here I am ...
a fugitive ...
seeing my country for the last time.
Going to ...
leave the only person I have in my life ...
going to a place where I don't speak
the language, no money, no connections.
I think I'll be freakin' out.
You're not?
Can I wear this? It smells like you.
Sure, if you think it can help.
I know it will.
I hope it smells like you for a long time.
If you make it to Nicaragua, ...
call that number.
He's a dear friend of mine.
You'll like him.
Another lover.
And this will help, too.
No, thanks. I'm not taking your money
I understand. But you're going to be back
in a harsh reality soon,
and everything has a price.
I know, I know ...
but it's my problem,
and I will deal with it.
I think I should go on alone now.
And you go.
There are other people
in desperate need of help.
The truck will stop three blocks down.
The driver will be with Luis.
He'll see you.
Thank you for ...
I wrote the restaurant address
in the inside.
Write me every time you cross the border.
I will.
It's a long read, but you'll have the time
to read it and re-read it.
Remember, to exist is the only thing that matters ...
to exist here and now ...
and nothing else.