MRS. RODRIGUEZ: After 20 years
of payment, Mr. Fender,
this can't be!
Considering
the circumstances,
I think the death benefit
is more than generous.
But we only missed a couple
of payments toward the end!
You know, a lawyer could probably
get you a bigger settlement.
But in the long run,
he's gonna cost you.
After the policyholder's
Paramed came back clean,
he signed up
for a Preferred Best Rate.
Essentially, this means we
lowered his monthly premiums,
because he didn't drink,
and he didn't smoke.
Now, if I can just draw
your attention
to the highlighted
section right here.
But Hector, he quit the
smoking years ago.
Perhaps you would turn and
look at the screen behind you.
FRANK:
As you can see,
the policyholder was not
exactly honest with you.
You spied
on my husband?
You bastard!
I'm afraid that I'm gonna
have to take this check back.
But you can't!
You just gave it to me!
[SIGHS]
FRANK: No,
maybe not.
Maybe if I told them
that you had
already accepted it.
[WEEPS]
[MUSIC]
[BEEP]
[CLICKING OF KEYBOARD]
[MUGISON "LITTLE TRIP TO HEAVEN"]
♪ Little trip to heaven ♪
♪ On the wings
Of your love ♪
♪ Banana moon
ls shining in the sky ♪
♪ Feel like I'm in Heaven
When you're with me ♪
♪ Know that I'm in Heaven
When you smile ♪
♪ Though we're stuck here
On the ground ♪
♪ I've got something
That I found ♪
♪ And it's you ♪
♪ You're my North Star ♪
♪ When I'm lost
And feeling blue ♪
♪ The sun is breaking
Through the clouds ♪
♪ Don't you know,
Know it's true ♪
♪ Honey, all the other stars
Seem dim around you ♪
♪ I'm thanking my lucky stars
That I've found you ♪
♪ When I see
Your smiling face ♪
♪ I know nothing's
Gonna take your place ♪
♪ And it's you ♪
[MUGISON "MURR MURR"]
♪ I'd shout
like that old fly ♪
JOSIE:
What are you drinking, sugar?
LONG-HAIRED MAN:
Give me a Bud.
You gonna need
a room?
No.
Just passing through.
Well, ain't that
a coring shame.
You want
another shot, honey?
On the house.
Not tonight, hon.
'Night.
[GAGS AND SPITS]
[MUSIC]
[ENGINE STARTS]
Shit!
LONG-HAIRED MAN:
Thanks, man.
[MOTOR SPEEDS UP]
[TIRES SCREECH]
Whoa! Uh--
Do I know you?
It's pretty slick out there.
You really should slow down.
[TIRES SCREECH]
What the--?
It's stuck.
The belt's stuck!
Slow down and stop the car!
Let me out!
Hey!
LONG-HAIRED MAN:
Ahhh!!!
[AMBULANCE AND POLICE SIRENS]
[HONKING]
[RAIN POURING]
[GROANS]
[GROANS AND HEAVES]
[LABOURED BREATHING]
No. No!
LONG-HAIRED MAN:
Oh. Oh.
[SCREAMS OF AGONY]
[SCREAM]
[EXCITED VOICES]
[KNOCKS]
Thanks.
All right, then.
Now,
I've originally guessed
that about half of you
climbed aboard this bus
after the accident.
You all know that this
Huntsville community bus
is owned by the city.
And you're thinking
that the city
might pay
out big bucks.
A nice juicy settlement if you
were to file a medical claim.
Well, I'm here
to tell you
that you're breaking
the law.
In the past, you could get
away with this for sure.
But what
you might not know,
is that behind that mirror
is a video camera.
You all
have been videotaped.
Now, I'm gonna sit
right here,
I'm gonna close
my eyes,
and I'm gonna
count to ten.
I strongly advise those of you who would
like to remain free citizens to leave
before I get
to the count of nine.
One,
two,
three,
four,
five,
six
seven,
eight,
nine,
ten.
Did you give them
the video speech?
The city ought to install
those things.
It'd make our jobs
a hell of a lot easier.
I've got a doozy
for you,
up in North Hastings.
Our contact down at
the Police Department,
he heard that a guy named Kelvin
Anderson died in the car accident.
There's a woman
named Isold,
his sole beneficiary,
Kelvin's sister.
Kelvin busted out of prison a few
years back, nobody's seen him since.
Until now.
Who the hell
insured a con man
with a million dollar
death benefit?
One of our bureaus
down south.
He did it before
he went to prison.
You want it, then?
North Hastings?
It's a couple hours.
Come on, the drive
will do you good.
Can't this wait
till Monday?
Actually, Weaver called ahead, and the
local yokels are kinda expecting you.
He's a big scam
artist, Abe.
Weaver wants you
to get on it right away.
A weekend
in Hastings.
You're the man, Abe.
Yeah, I'm the man with
no wife and no kids.
Geez, Frank.
It's a lot of
money, Abe.
Make sure this
guy is really dead.
And if he is dead,
dig up some dirt
on him.
About time
you got here.
[MUSIC]
Hello, fella!
Hi.
Name's William.
My son, Russle.
Hey.
Abe Holt.
Nice to
meet you.
How was
the drive?
Long.
WILLIAM: The car is registered
to one Kelvin Anderson.
RUSSLE: Which came
as quite a surprise.
ABE:
How's that?
At first, we thought
it was Fred's Malibu.
Fred?
Fred McBride.
He's married to Isold.
ABE: They, uh, drive
the same car.
WILLIAM: We ran the plates,
checked the VIN number,
it all checks out.
We also found Kelvin's driver's
license in the glove box.
Oh, yeah?
RUSSLE: Yeah. Poor sap.
Burned to a crisp.
WILLIAM: He must
have been drunk.
Let's hope so,
for his sake.
Great, we can nail him
for drunk driving.
That'll teach him
a lesson.
What's on
the other side?
WILLIAM:
His sister, Isold.
RUSSLE: I reckon he came
to hide out with her.
You fellas
know Kelvin?
No, they're not
from around here.
Oh.
What do you think?
You gonna have to pay
out on this one?
Yeah.
Looks like that.
How much
you reckon to lose?
A lot.
The death benefit's
worth a million dollars.
Death benefit.
Damn!
A million bucks?
Who gets
all that money?
Isold's the sole
beneficiary of this.
Shit! Fred's gonna
be drunk for a decade.
Yeah, it's like
you hit the jackpot.
It came at
a pretty high price.
She lost
her brother.
Some might say that.
Yeah.
Let's get the hell
out of here.
When are you gonna break
the news to the sister?
You're in a hell
of a rush.
How about we ID the body before
we start upsetting people?
[MUSIC]
[ENGINE STOPS]
[DOOR CREAKS OPEN]
[SHOUT]
Oh, geez!
No! Sorry!
Can I talk to you?
Oh, geez.
Hello.
Sorry, I didn't mean
to scare you.
Well, you sure did.
Uh,
there's been
an accident.
An accident? No, no, it's
just that time of the month.
No, I mean by the tunnel,
there was a car wreck.
Was anybody hurt?
Were you expecting
anybody last night?
No. Why?
Oh, I, uh, I was just
trying to establish a time
and if you
were expecting--
No, I mean, why would I
be expecting somebody?
Are you a cop?
I'm Abe Holt,
nice to meet you.
Who was in the car?
We haven't IDed
the body yet.
My husband's asleep inside, do
you want me to wake him up?
No, no,
that's OK.
You sure?
Yeah, I'm sure,
I, uh,
are you
gonna be okay?
Yeah.
Okay.
It was nice
to meet you.
Jesus!
You scared me,
little fellow.
Where you going?
Me? I'm going
to town.
Can I come, too?
You? You want
a ride to town?
FEMALE VOICE:
Thor! Breakfast!
Your mom's calling.
How long does it take
to get to Heaven?
Do cats get to go?
You gotta go.
Here, go.
Jesus!
What's the verdict?
Death.
He was frozen
by fire.
For all I know, this could've
been the devil's grandmother.
What about
dental records?
You serious?
Are there
any broken bones?
He crashed into a tunnel.
He broke--
I mean, before.
Before what?
Like when
he was younger.
I'm not
his family doctor.
Can't you take
some X-rays?
With what?
Oh!
[CLICK]
ABE: What do you two know
about this, uh, Fred?
Fred?
Why?
They moved here
a while ago.
Why you so interested
in Fred?
You heard
what the doctor said.
The body
could be anybody.
Body?
Okay, you're saying
it's not Kelvin.
Well, who do
you think it is?
Are you saying
it's Fred?
How?
It's Kelvin's car. We found
his driver's license.
Yeah. Exactly.
Wait...then how the hell did Fred
end up dead in Kelvin's car?
Kelvin.
Kelvin?
Well, that means
Isold must be in on it?
Somebody's got
to collect the money.
So where's Kelvin,
then?
That's downright crazy.
Is it?
A broken arm can
bring in about $20,000.
A leg, well,
it all depends
on where it's broken.
Above or below
the knee.
Nyah!
[SCREAMING]
ABE:
The big money...
well, that all comes
if you up and die.
[MUSIC]
Can I help you?
Oh, hi.
WILLIAM:
Hello, Isold.
This is Abe Holt,
he's--
I'm an investigator.
Uh-huh, we met.
I see you brought the whole
force with you this time.
What did
I do now?
Hey, Isold.
WILLIAM: There was an
accident in the tunnel.
Is Fred around?
[THOR WHIMPERS]
Isold.
Everything all right?
Yeah, we had
a minor tragedy.
Our cat's missing.
Well, is he around?
Who?
Fred.
Hey, Dad!
Come here!
Yeah.
Hold it.
Don't shoot.
I'm unarmed.
FRED: This a raid?
What's going on?
RUSSLE:
Hey, Fred.
Hey, man.
What the hell
was that?
Got a new car?
Taking it out
for a spin.
ISOLD: Fred, the police here
wanted to ask you a question.
FRED: Well, all right.
Shoot.
What happened?
Oh, yeah, I, uh, just got
silly drunk last night.
We better get going.
Don't you have
a Malibu?
Why, you want one?
Yeah.
Can I see it?
Yeah. Sure.
Come on.
She's a little love, but,
uh, here's your Malibu.
What's going on?
What really happened
to you last night?
Oh, nothing.
Just got drunk,
fell on my face.
ISOLD:
Honey, what are you doing?
Let's get you
cleaned up.
[PAUL ROSENKRANS "AIN'T NO SUNSHINE"]
♪ Ain't no sunshine
when she's gone ♪
♪ It's not warm
when she's away ♪
MALE ANNOUNCER: What would
happen to your loved ones
if you died?
♪ Ain't no sunshine
when she's gone ♪
♪ She's always
gone too long ♪
Would they be protected?
♪ Every time
she goes away ♪
MALE ANNOUNCER:
Why gamble on tomorrow?
Quality Life.
Your future
is in our hands.
Here you go. It's all
in the up and up.
Fred and Isold
are legally married.
WILLIAM:
Like I told you.
RUSSLE: What do
you want it for?
It's for my files.
Why'd you make Isold
think you were a cop?
When I tell people that I'm
an insurance investigator
they slam the door in my
face and call their lawyer.
Investigator? Aren't you
guys called loss adjusters?
We're concerned with the
bottom line just like...
any other business.
Why don't you put that
in your commercials, then?
People with dead relatives
being cheated out of their--
what do you call it--
death benefits?
Well, Fred looked pretty
much alive to me.
ABE:
Yeah.
Hey, Josie.
Hey, Rusty.
Can I get
a receipt, please?
Sure.
Loss adjuster.
[WIND HOWLING]
Check under the bed.
He's all gone.
No monster.
The night light.
Can you tell me
a story?
What kind
of story?
A ghost story.
No, you'll be up
all night.
Then I can help you
carry Fred to bed.
You're such a brat.
What'd you say
about me?
THOR:
Nothing.
Uh-huh.
Night, dude.
Ah.
I want you to tell me a story.
Me?
All right.
Let's see, hmm,
once upon a time there
was a man and a woman,
and they were old
and poor.
I want a story
about rich people.
Okay.
Once upon a time,
there was a filthy
rich millionaire,
and his
cheap-looking bimbo.
[GENERAL LAUGHTER]
All right,
all right.
Once upon a time, there
was a king and a queen,
and they lived
in a big castle.
Did they have
a horse?
Mm-hmm.
They had
a little horse named...
BOTH:
Lightning.
[HOWLING OF WIND]
JOSIE:
On the house.
Oh, no,
I don't, uh--
So...how long
you stayin'?
I'm leaving tomorrow.
In the morning?
Yeah, can't stay
long this time.
This time.
Honey, once you leave Hastings,
you ain't never comin' back.
So...
how's the big
case going?
Oh...it's, uh...
it's, it's going
all right.
[AL HIRT AND ANN-MARGRET
"IT'S COLD OUTSIDE"]
You're friends
with Isold, right?
Sure.
And Kelvin, you're
friends with him, too?
[ANN-MARGRET FROM JUKEBOX]
♪ I really can't stay ♪
[AL HIRT FROM JUKEBOX]
♪ But baby, it's cold outside ♪
♪ I've got to go away ♪
♪ Yeah, but baby,
it's cold outside ♪
♪ This evening has been ♪
♪ Been hoping
That you'd drop in ♪
♪ So very nice ♪
♪ I'll hold your hands ♪
♪ They're just
Like ice ♪
♪ My mother
Will start to worry ♪
♪ Beautiful,
What's your hurry ♪
♪ My father will be pacing
The floor ♪
♪ Listen to
That fireplace roaring ♪
♪ So, really,
I should scurry ♪
What about Fred?
Who?
Fred, you know Fred.
Oh, Fred.
He treats her okay.
That's not what
I'm sayin'
JOSIE: How'd a guy like
that end up with Isold.
Up here we gotta take
what we can get.
[JOSIE SINGS ALONG]
♪ What's in this drink ♪
♪ No cabs to be had
Out there ♪
♪ I wish I knew how ♪
ABE: The night of the accident,
anything strange happen?
Nothing happens
around here.
♪ I'll take your hat,
Your hair looks swell ♪
♪ I ought to say no,
No, no, sir ♪
♪ Mind if I move in
A little closer ♪
I don't, uh--
Come on.
You can dance.
No, but--
Everyone can dance.
[SLOW MUSIC]
♪ Hey, I simply must go ♪
♪ Yeah, but it's cold
Out there ♪
FRED:
Ah! Shit.
Come on!
She giving you
problems?
Oh, hey.
You're back, huh?
Say, you were at the bar the
other night, weren't you?
[STRAINING] Oh, yeah. Oh, yeah.
You see anything?
You sure do ask
a lot of questions.
You're still here?
Yeah, still tying up
some loose ends.
Ever find out
who was in the car?
As a matter of fact, we
think it might be Kelvin.
Kelvin?
Yeah.
Your brother.
What was he doing
in Hastings?
You're sure
it was Kelvin?
You were expecting him?
Expecting him?
First place the cops
would look, huh?
Had to be kinda
stupid to hang out
at his sister's farm,
don't you think?
Like driving around
in your old Malibu
with your driver's license
in the glove box...
and you're an escaped con.
[ENGINE DOESN'T START]
Where's Thor?
[ENGINE STARTS]
I don't know.
Excuse me,
I gotta find him.
Thor!
Thor!!
ISOLD:
Thor!
Thor!!
Hurry up, sweetie!
Come on!
I think
you better leave.
All right, then.
What's that?
What's what?
What's MVC stand for?
Oh, this old thing.
It's, uh,
Mid Valley Central.
Yeah, go Bulldogs.
All right, then.
[MUSIC]
Where you going
with the boy?
[SIGHS]
I can't believe
this is happening again.
Uh-huh.
Come on.
ISOLD:
FRANK:
Those cops called.
Man, were they pissed.
ABE: Tell Weaver I'm gonna
need a couple of extra days.
He wants you back, Abe.
Today.
Tell--tell--tell him
my car broke down.
Your car?
Yeah, that--they--they said
it'd be done by tomorrow.
You gotta do something
about that stutter, man.
It gives you away
every time.
Look, if you want to milk your per
diem, that's your business,
but you can't go around joyriding
on the company's time.
I think
I'm on to something.
I can feel it.
All right. I'll go
to bat for you.
Come back
with something big
or this adventure
is out of your own pocket.
FRED: Now look, let me explain.
I don't want to hear it
right now.
Isold, sorry,
all right?
For what? Making us hide
out like fucking rats?
I feel like I'm stuck
in a mud flat.
Ah, fuck.
Look, it-- it was an
accident, all right?
Why Kelvin, then?
I just took advantage
of the situation.
I've heard that before.
We can finally get out
of this backward-ass town!
Go ahead,
keep running.
You're goddamn right I'll keep
running, 'cause it's shit here!
It's shit, Isold!
Squattin' here...
trying to squeeze every last
drop outta this frozen land?
It's like we're...
waiting for the weeds to grow
over our own goddamn graves!
If you hate it so much, then why
the fuck don't you stay away!
And take Thor
with me?
Huh?
Look at you.
Mother-fucking-Teresa
all of a sudden.
I'm sorry.
Let us not forget
how you got these.
[SCHOOL BELL RINGS]
[CHATTERING]
FEMALE VOICE: Quiet in the
corridors and no running!
May I help you,
young man?
Are you looking
for a student of ours?
A former student.
Uh-uh-uh.
BOY:
Sorry, Ma'am.
Who, might I ask,
are you looking for?
Freddy McBride.
McBride?
Do you mean
Frederick McBride?
Yeah!
You remember him?
I'm sorry, who did you
say you were again?
We don't tend to discuss the
private records of our students
with perfect strangers,
I'm sure you understand.
Well, don't worry,
I'm--I'm--I'm family.
Family?
Yeah, yeah,
I'm--I'm--I'm--
I'm his brother-in-law.
Oh, really?
Frederick McBride.
What was
your name again?
My name?
Yeah.
Oh.
Kelvin.
Kelvin Anderson.
Kelvin Anderson?
Yeah. Fred's married
to my sister, Isold.
So, Frederick McBride
is married to your sister?
Yeah.
Anderson.
Well.
Kelvin Anderson.
Welcome back
to Mid Valley Central.
FEMALE VOICE:
You from up North?
ABE: Yeah.
How could you tell?
We don't get too many
outsiders round these parts.
You a cop?
Martha, tell me, how long
you been workin' here?
Since I was about 15.
You must know lots of
folks around here.
I reckon I've served the
entire town once or twice.
Do you know
the McBrides?
Sylvia McBride?
Yeah. Sylvia.
You know her?
Why you lookin'
for Sylvia, officer?
No, no,
I'm not a cop.
See, I'm--I'm--I'm with the
State Assessment's office.
It seems we owe her
some money.
We overcharged her on some
property taxes years back
but it's tough, I haven't
been able to locate her.
That's 'cause she don't
live here no more.
You wouldn't happen to know
whereabouts she went, would you?
No.
Maybe you can tell me
where she used to live.
I'm sure I could track
her down that way.
How much money
did you say it was?
Oh, it's a lot.
It's--it's--it's a lot.
She used to live
on Route 12.
About 15 miles
past the junction.
You got
a street address?
Honey, there ain't
no street signs out there.
[MUGISON "MURR MURR"]
♪ I try to do it quietly ♪
♪ Not a whisper,
More like a shock ♪
♪ I try to
Disorganize neatly ♪
♪ What to keep
And... what to block ♪
[CRACKLING OF FIRE]
Are you
a McBride?
No. You?
No.
I don't reckon you belong
around here neither.
Do you know where I can
find the McBrides?
Follow me.
[SONG CONTINUES]
Don't let
the fire get you.
I'm just killing
some weeds.
♪ I wait for the moment
To call ♪
♪ Or will I hesitate ♪ ♪
I'm trying to get something
to grow around here.
I guess
it's a waste of time.
[WHISTLES TO DOG]
[DOG BARKS]
ABE:
Daniel McBride.
Sometimes, it's just time
to pick up and move.
[PIANO MUSIC]
Oh, Jesus.
Frederick McBride.
ISOLD:
All right, all right.
You poison
my food?
With what?
Methane gas?
Goddamn it, Kelvin!
Why don't you just
light him up a doobie?
It's Fred.
My name is Fred.
ABE: [OVER PHONE]
Hello?
Frank, I got a favor
I need from you.
I need you to look
into something for me.
Okay.
I want you to find out
if Kelvin had any kids.
What for? I told you Isold is
the only name on the claim form.
Just do it,
I need this.
Okay, I'll stop
by the records.
Frank...
Find out
who the mother is.
The mother?
I need to know.
Isold!
You done?
THOR:
Sorry.
FRED: We did it! High five.
[FRED LAUGHS HAPPILY]
Hang on here.
ABE: And how is
Frederick McBride today?
Surviving.
Is Isold home?
Yeah, she's inside.
I need to talk
to her.
Back again.
Yeah.
I'm afraid I need you
to identify Kelvin's body.
I was...just...
fixing Thor a snack.
Come on in.
Is this you
and Kelvin?
That's us.
He took
real good care of me.
FRED: Come on,
buddy, get inside.
You hungry?
FRED:
Let's get you a sandwich.
Let's sit down.
ISOLD: Everyone else
said he was crazy.
He got into fights
all the time.
One day he tied a firecracker
to the back of a cat
and set it loose
in our classroom.
[CHUCKLES]
The teacher
sent him home.
Said he was
sick in the head.
When did you
see him last?
[SCRAPING]
Yeah, when was that?
William and Russle...
they're meeting us
at the morgue.
We better get going if we
want to beat the storm.
Sure, just
let me get Thor.
FRED:
It's not a good idea
to take the boy on the road
in this kind of weather.
What do you say,
little man?
You wanna stay here with me and
finish building the snowman?
Yeah, Daddy.
No, no,
he'll be fine.
I'll put him to bed
with a good story.
I'm gonna wait outside.
That's a nice one.
Yeah.
What the hell
am I supposed to do now?
Just identify the body,
and Kelvin's history.
Don't bring Thor
into this mess.
Sweet-talk him,
would you?
Do what you do best.
You still know
how to--
flirt with a man,
don't you?
What are you now?
My fucking pimp?
[THOR GIGGLES]
[CHUCKLES]
Hey, Thor!
Ahhh!
[BOTH CHUCKLE HAPPILY]
Swim like a fish!
Where's William and Russle?
Uh...they'll be along.
It's here.
[ISOLD GASPS]
That could be anybody.
It could...couldn't it?
He didn't die
on impact.
Do you know what it's
like to burn to death?
First the fat oozes
out of you.
It starts poppin' and bubblin'
like a hot dog on a barbecue.
Then your eyes--
they crack...like glass.
Your skin burns off
layer by layer until...
the fire hits bone.
And that's
not the worst of it.
It's the smell.
Your hair singes...
but you can't reach
for your head
'cause your hands
are gone.
Imagine what it's like
to smell yourself die.
What's going on
in here?
Nothing.
I--I--I was just--
bringing her by
to ID the body.
That's our job,
son.
Well, who is he,
then?
It's him.
I guess things are gonna be
different now, aren't they?
Why?
What do you mean?
The money.
What money?
The million dollars, Kelvin's
life insurance policy.
As you probably know, you're
the sole beneficiary to that.
Who's that?
Ta, ta, ta...
FRED:
Thor!
Let's go, buddy.
Come on!
Come on.
Let's go.
Let's go, Isold,
I gotcha.
FRED: Come on. Get in the back.
[PHONE RINGS]
[RINGS]
Come on!
Answer the goddamn phone!
I'm sure they're okay.
The line's probably down.
[PHONE RINGS]
[PHONE RINGING]
[SLOW MUSIC]
ISOLD: You never notice your
mistakes when you're making them.
Then it all catches up to you
when a kid comes along.
ABE: I wouldn't know about that.
You don't have kids?
No. I haven't had
that kind of luck.
Luck.
Yeah, I guess
you could call it that.
Thor asked me
the other day,
"Why is God in Heaven and
the Devil in the ground?
Heaven's so far away."
What'd you say?
I told him it's easier to
lie down than it is to fly.
Don't be embarrassed.
I'm not.
I'm ashamed
of how I got him.
[MUSIC]
[PANTING]
ISOLD:
Kelvin!
[KNOCKING]
[ANGRILY] Damn it,
where are you?!
Thor!
MALE ANNOUNCER: What would
happen to your loved ones
if you died?
Would they be protected?
[PHONE RINGING]
[PHONE RINGS]
[MOANS]
[RINGING]
Hello?
Kelvin, is that you?
Where's Thor?
Thor's fine.
Jesus Christ, Kelvin, what
the fuck are you doing?
Calm down, Isold.
Don't tell me
to calm down!
You went too far.
It was an accident, okay?
You killed somebody.
And you're a millionaire,
motherfucker!
You're sole beneficiary.
Just go and get the money
and Thor and I will be
waiting for you, okay?
Will you let me talk to him?
It's for you.
THOR:
Hi.
It's me, sweetie.
I'm eating
a milkshake.
For breakfast?
You're a naughty boy.
See?
Everything's fine.
Now, listen, they have
14 days to pay you
once you file the death
certificate, so I suggest--
I can't believe
you went this far!
Listen, listen,
go and play your part.
Don't say that,
this is murder!
Just dumb luck.
What the fuck
are you talking about?!
Who's body is
down at the morgue?!
Just some drifter I
ran into at Josie's.
Just one last con,
Isold.
Just one last con.
[MUSIC]
This is gonna
kill us, Kelvin.
[CAR HONKS HORN]
[TIRES SCREECHING]
[SCREAMS WITH PAIN]
Nyah!
[SCREAM]
[LOUD DRIPPING]
I'm here to see Abe Holt.
Please.
Come in.
Right. Isold.
All right, then, you're here
to collect the death benefit.
Yeah.
I'm afraid I have
some bad news.
There was a no-fault
clause in the policy.
What?
What's going on here?
May I draw your attention
to the highlighted section.
As you can see,
it clearly states
that the death
must be a no-fault death.
"No-fault"?
An accident, like
if the policy holder
was run over by a car.
What, like crashing into
a tunnel isn't enough?
That depends.
Depends?
That was--that was--
that was--
before--before we got
the blood tests back.
It seems that, um...
the policy holder...
was driving under the
influence of alcohol.
A DUI.
He was drunk?
Well, blood tests
don't lie.
I know...
it's difficult.
Fifteen hundred dollars?
That's the bluebook
on the Malibu.
I'm afraid that's the best
I can do for you.
I need that money.
I'm sorry... Isold.
We're just--just--just
trying to run a business here.
You know?
Yeah, I wonder what my
lawyer's gonna say about this.
Would you like
to use my phone?
To call your lawyer?
Thor.
He's--
Kelvin's son.
I know that.
I need you to sign this document
in order to take the check.
FRANK: Blood test on
a charcoaled corpse.
That was brilliant.
The house always
wins, right, Abe?
Isold!
Wait!
What's all this crap about blood tests!
The body was fried!
I just saved you there.
Insurance fraud
is one thing.
Accessory to murder,
that's another.
I haven't reported that Kelvin's
alive, but there is no money.
He's got Thor!
He took Thor?
I need that money!
ABE: Get me Mike Connor over
at Central Savings and Loan.
Mike...it's Abe Holt,
over at Quality Life.
I need you to put a hold on a
check for me 'till tomorrow.
Check number QLI 3245.
MIKE:
Okay, I got it.
[BEEP]
Just a minute,
please.
Is there a problem?
I'm sorry, there has been a
hold placed on this check.
You'll just have
to come back tomorrow.
TELLER:
14, 20, 40, 60, 80...
fifteen hundred dollars.
And I need to open
up a safety deposit box.
Come on.
Let's get out of here, yeah?
OK honey,
let's get your clothes on.
What the fuck?
What is this?
It's the bluebook
on the Malibu.
Where the fuck
is the rest of it?
Central Savings and Loan.
Go and get it yourself.
Oh.
Come on.
We're gonna go home,
sweetie, okay? Yeah.
Where are you
taking my son?
Your son? You mean
Kelvin's son, don't you?
I'm Kelvin's sister,
I'm next of kin.
What are you
talking about?
You're dead, remember?
Thor belongs
to me now.
Wait, wait!
[SHOUTS]
Wait, wait, wait!
Is that why you went
through it all?
Changing my ID,
marriage...
No, that was to get
the cops off your back.
Anyway, it was
your stupid idea.
Your forged
the marriage papers.
Do you think
I'm stupid?
Do you?
No!
I hope
you're not bluffing.
Wait, wait, wait!
Please don't take Thor
away from me!
Come on,
little man.
Say goodbye!
THOR:
No, Daddy!
Okay, get inside.
ISOLD:
Wait!
ABE:
Let the boy go.
KELVIN:
Fuck!
You went too far.
Taking a boy
from his mother.
His mother?
No, that bitch ran away
years ago, man.
Didn't she?
Isold's not his mother.
She's my fucking sister,
all right?
She's just looking
after him.
I know that. But she's
still the mother.
Let your son go.
Let him go, Kelvin.
Get out of the car,
kid, come on.
Go on.
ABE: Nice and easy,
nice and easy.
I want you to get out of
the car so we can talk.
Nice and easy.
Don't shoot.
Stop the car.
ABE:
Stop the car now.
You shoot me, we both
go down, all right?
But you let me go...
I'll split the money with you.
A million dollars.
There is no money. I switched
the insurance policies.
What do you mean?
I insured
Frederick McBride.
You can't insure
a dead man.
You brought him
back to life.
William and Russle will ID your
body as Frederick McBride.
For them,
Kelvin's dead.
So if I shoot, Isold collects a
million dollars over a dead husband.
Or give yourself up, and
as far as I'm concerned,
that poor sap is Fred McBride--
I got you, you and Isold
are millionaires?
The House has to pay out
every once in a while,
otherwise people
will stop gambling.
Well, it looks like
I'm pretty fucked!
Stop! Stop!
Stop the car!
FRANK:
it's tragic.
One of our own involved
in your husband's death.
I don't get it.
Well,
as usual, we did
a background search.
He came up
absolutely clean.
Not even
a parking ticket.
It seems Frederick
McBride was a saint.
You can't imagine.
One million dollars.
This will settle things
as we agreed.
[MUSIC]
THOR:
Where's Daddy?
Shhh.
Go to sleep, buddy.
I can't.
Want me to sing
to you?
Okay.
[SINGING] ♪ Little trip to Heaven
On the wings of your love ♪
♪ Banana moon
Is shining in the sky ♪
♪ I feel like I'm in Heaven
When you're with me ♪
♪ I know that I'm in Heaven
When you smile ♪
[MUSIC FROM TV COMMERCIAL]
[MUGISON "LITTLE TRIP TO HEAVEN"]
♪ And I don't have to take
No trip to outerspace ♪
♪ All I have to do
Is look at your face ♪
♪ Before I know it,
I'm in orbit around you ♪
♪ I'm thanking my lucky stars
That I found you ♪
♪ When I see
Your constellation ♪
♪ You're my inspiration ♪
♪ It's you ♪
♪ You're my north star ♪
♪ When I'm lost
And feeling blue ♪
♪ The sun's breaking
Through the clouds ♪
♪ Don't you know,
Know it's true ♪
♪ Honey, all the other stars
Seem dim around you ♪
♪ I'm thanking my lucky stars
That I found you ♪
♪ When I see
Your smiling face ♪
♪ Nothing's gonna take
Your place, it's you ♪
♪ And it's you,
And it's you ♪
♪ And you ♪
♪ And it's you ♪ ♪
[GUITAR MUSIC]
[MUGISON "MURR MURR"]
♪ I try to do it quietly ♪
♪ Not a whisper,
More like a shock ♪
♪ I try
To disorganize neatly ♪
♪ What to keep and ♪
♪ What to block ♪
♪ I'd shout like
That old fly ♪
♪ In that window
And wait ♪
♪ I wait for the moment
To come ♪
♪ Or will I hesitate ♪
♪ There ain't no logic,
There ain't no plain ♪
♪ No roads you can travel
Free from pain ♪
♪ I'm only a shoulder,
I'm only a kiss ♪
♪ Good for comfort
And cool for ♪
♪ The diss ♪
♪ The lord is my mom,
She's my saint ♪
♪ I'm her troubled boy
Unto the grave ♪
♪ I pretend she's blessing,
Blessing me ♪
♪ Hoping that she
Saves me from ♪
♪ This misery ♪♪