As a child, you spent hours on this swing.
Why the long face?
- Can I ask you a question?
- Sure.
Did you have another love before grandpa?
He was the only man in my life.
I married because I had no choice,
but I learned to love him.
Back then they said:
"A woman without a trade has two options:
Marriage or prostitution."
That's about the same.
What if you could start anew?
- Would Pepe be the man of your life?
- No.
If I could start anew
I'd get fucked as much as I could.
Everyone should share your ideas.
A man who gets laid is a super macho.
If it's a woman, she's a slut.
- Sexual equality.
- Forget what they say!
If they made love more and spoke less...
- It would be better.
- It's not that simple.
What isn't?
Pay no mind, grandma.
- It's hard to explain.
- You know what you should do?
Look.
Jot down your doubts, ideas,
problems on a sheet of paper,
but interrogatively
so you can see them from
outside and understand them.
I did that at you age, and it helped a lot.
And I still do, but so as not to forget.
Dinner is ready.
Come on.
When you made love with grandpa,
how was it?
You're very curious.
Come, I've made shellfish
meatballs for you.
Enough for you to take to Barcelona.
I lost my virginity on
the 17th of July, 1993,
at 2:46 in the morning.
It was during a vacation period,
when I was 15.
You never forget a moment like that.
- Are you okay?
- Yes.
I remember I felt nothing,
just deep shame for not having bled, and
that strange feeling of
having pissed in bed.
I left with the excuse of the toilet,
with the feeling my experience with Edouard
couldn't be like that.
A feeling that
made me go back to him.
I was lacking something.
But, what are you doing here?
- Again.
- Once again?
No, hundreds of times.
Hundreds of times.
That strange release of energy aroused
in me a desire to communicate
through my body,
a curiosity to experience
sensations through a kiss,
a caress or the contact of my skin.
14 years after my
first experience with Edouard
I live in Barcelona and still have
the same urge to experiment
through my body.
DIARY OF A NYMPHOMANIAC
- My diary, it was here.
- You're writing a diary?
- I follow your advice.
- I didn't tell you to.
Just to jot down your problems
for a better perspective.
Diaries are for lonely people.
That's not true.
They have something to tell.
Because their life is different.
And they always hope that
someone will discover it,
read it to get to know the
true personality of the author.
Right, because they feel lonely.
It's the third blackout this week.
- The dark still scares you.
- This lighter doesn't work.
Don't speak badly of me in your diary.
Of course not.
Could you write something for me?
That you're not alone, that I'm with you.
It's about time.
I'm unbearable in the dark.
Unbearable.
You smell of fields,
of wet, recently cut grass.
Why don't you stay over?
No, I can't.
Tomorrow I have a meeting and
must prepare my presentation.
Alex, why don't you ever stay
to sleep with me? Please?
You don't want me to sleep.
No.
Don't you ever get tired?
Val, I can't keep up with your pace.
Besides, I told you
I have a meeting tomorrow.
Come on.
Hassan.
Valerie.
Nice to hear you.
You disappeared into thin air
but I found you?
I'll be in Barcelona this week.
I want to see you?
- How about Thursday?
- Okay, I'll call you. A kiss.
- Who was that?
- Hassan.
- He's coming?
- I'll see him Thursday.
Back to my desk, things are getting rough.
What is?
They're restructuring.
I've heard that ever since I'm here.
Yeah, well...
I've been asked what
I feel when I make love.
It's like a mix of energy with the
other person that makes me fly
and merge with the cosmos.
The energy of my orgasm is a
small part of me that goes
and ends up mixing with the universe.
A sidereal trip that takes me to infinity.
In my country they say Allah
told the south wind that he'd
create the Arabian horse from it.
"So be it", said the wind.
He held a puff and tied it
to the horse's mane
so it wouldn't forget where it came from,
but it turned out to be so fast
and cunning that no one could
ride it, and it was Ishmael,
the first faithful, who was able
to tame one of them
and called it Kuhaylan, the Black Antelope.
You're more difficult to tame
than that first horse.
I don't know how to name you.
Are you calling me wild?
Yes.
I think I've never fucked you in a bed.
We can do that now, if you want.
Although... I've just had
a better idea.
Here, look.
Where are they?
You've hidden them again?
No.
Not now, Hassan, please.
I don't feel like it right now,
not today, no.
Here they are!
No, please.
No.
Not today.
Yes, yes, today.
Look, look, come on.
Good morning.
Be careful, Val, you're late again.
Want one?
I don't want to even see them,
I need coffee.
I bought a dress for Marcos' wedding.
When I tried it on I realized
I couldn't zip it up.
So I cried like a baby and
then I called you.
You knew about Hassan.
I forgot, but I never find
you when I need you anyway.
I'm thinking of publishing
an ad to find a boyfriend.
An ad?
What do you mean?
You have to stop being obsessed.
How can you find him not going out?
I don't want just one-night stands.
You must try before falling in love.
I need to fall in love, Val,
find a man who loves me and
perhaps buy me flowers now and then.
I rather he fucks well.
I'll buy the flowers.
I can't stand not having anyone
to talk to at home,
to wake up alone and find
half a lemon in the icebox.
Love fills iceboxes and mine's
been empty for a long time.
I was worried. You didn't call
yesterday to say good night.
I got home late.
I had dinner with some friends.
- Did you like the meatballs?
- Yes, delicious.
I'm hanging up.
I must finish your sweater?
- I love you, I love you.?
- Me too. Till tomorrow, grandma.
Tame me.
- What?
- Tame me.
You deserve some flowers.
I want to fuck all night long.
I can't. I can't. I can't, Val.
- I have to go.
- What's the matter?
No, Val. Val, Val, Val, Val.
I have to tell you something.
- You have a girlfriend.
- You knew?
I imagined but, don't worry,
I'm not jealous.
Besides, I never asked you if you
were alone. It's not my problem.
I didn't think you'd take it like that.
You wanted me to cry?
Val,
we must stop seeing each other.
I want to fly.
Val, Val, Val.
Haven't you understood?
Can't you think of anything else?
You got a problem.
You can't spend all day
thinking about fucking.
I do, but you're an S.O.B..
Don't ever call me again, okay?
Never!
Fuck!
Alex, another man who has left me.
The loneliness, the silence.
I need some air.
What? Are you new here?
This is my turf, baby! Beat it!
Go work somewhere else.
Some days I'd spend hours in
the shower, feeling the water,
forgetting everything.
But I can't get Alex off of my mind.
I liked him a lot.
Like him, many others just want to fuck me,
and I like that,
but it hurts
because, above all, I'm a woman.
Darling, I was calling to say good night,
but I guess your out having a good time?
You are so right!
Enjoy it while you're young?
Bye. A kiss.
It's not fair, Val, they're pigs.
You give them part of
your life, and they fire you.
Want a hand?
Forget it, I was fed up anyway.
Weren't you on a diet?
How can I be being so depressed?
You get it, I don't work here.
Yes?
So, Valerie can't attend to you,
she no longer works here. Bye.
Yes?
Speaking.
I got furious when I found
out they called you.
Thanks for coming, but there's no need.
I got a few days vacation at work.
I'd have come anyway.
Don't look like that, Val.
I've no intention of dying so soon.
It was just a slight problem.
My heart is holding out.
Doctors always exaggerate.
- What is wrong with you?
- Nothing.
Val, I know you well.
Is it over a man?
One?
Over all of them.
Do you know what nymphomania is?
I think that's my problem.
I can't control it.
I need sex.
I see a man and I need him.
But no one understands that.
People stare at me.
It happens with strangers
that don't attract me.
I'm scared.
Scared of not being like other women.
Scared of being hurt someday.
Of not being able to live with
one man, not having a family.
Nymphomania, a man's invention
to make women
feel guilty if they break the rules.
Everyone is the way they are.
Never give up anything you really long for
because you'll regret it.
Believe me.
To me,
I think that you
don't dare to live your life.
Want a piece of advice?
Enjoy life
as much as you can.
And go get my sweater, I want to finish it.
You should rest, grandma.
I've rested enough.
Go on and get my knitting.
Go on.
CALL VAL
I've lost the only person
who understood me.
I feel absolutely alone.
I'd like to have the company
of a man to comfort me,
but I haven't the strength
to go looking for him.
I'm exhausted.
Darling, I was calling to say good night,
but I guess your out having a good time?
You are so right!
Enjoy it while you're young?
Bye. A kiss.
Darling, I was calling to say good night,
but I guess your out having a good time?
You are so right!
Enjoy it while you're young?
Bye. A kiss.
Darling, I was calling to say good night,
but I guess your out having a good time?
You are so right!
Enjoy it while you're young?
Bye. A kiss.
I called you a lot.
You could at least answer.
What happened?
I know that my sex life
is harming me, and that
I can't go on like this.
Although I'm sunk, I'm looking for work.
Okay, you're the person I need.
You speak English, you
have knowledge of marketing.
We sell a lot to France,
and you'd take care of our communications,
go with me to fairs,
and have a ham for Christmas.
- A ham?
- I give them to my employees.
You can't say we foreigners
don't integrate.
Interested?
I have another interview today.
- I'll let you know this week.
- Okay.
I see you're very observant.
You see, we're moving.
Why did you quit your last job?
They cut down on personnel,
including me, Mr...
Rijas, Jaime Rijas.
What?
Rijas and Associates, general manager.
You're a graduate in
business administration
and applied foreign languages.
A really impressive curriculum.
- May I ask you something?
- Sure.
- Are you married?
- No.
Engaged?
I think that is irrelevant.
Yes, you're right, but in this job
one must travel the world over.
There's no commitment on my part.
Would you like to ask me anything else
on the salary, or whatever?
What perfume do you use?
Well now, you really have
a very, very good sense of smell.
It's a special lavender perfume.
Yes?
Valerie?
Yes, speaking.
It's Jaime Rijas?
How are you?
Oh, hello.
I've made a decision, but have a problem
and would like to talk to you in person.
What sort of problem?
I think I can speak openly to you.
Would you mind talking
about this over a drink?
Can't we do that in your office?
I'd prefer a quieter place?
My secretary
interrupts constantly.
I'm 39 and have always been
a businessman with clear ideas,
but nothing like this had
ever happened to me before.
And I thought it was important
to talk about it with someone
without prejudice, and you're that person.
Why? You hardly know each other.
Precisely because we don't
know each other at all,
your opinion will be more objective.
That all depends.
I met a woman at work and,
due to my status as director general,
I don't know what to do.
I've always controlled my
impulses but his thing,
- it's getting out of hand.
- She works in your company?
Not yet.
Does she know?
She's smart and I think she has realized
there's something more,
but she's made no comment and
I'm afraid she may not
feel the same for me.
Sorry. Did I step on you?
- The table's small.
- That's okay.
You're beautiful, Valerie.
I'd like to buy you a rose, but
I have no money.
Or do I?
I forgot to tell you something.
The job was yours until this evening.
But from now on I don't think
I couldn't order you around.
- Good night.
Any relatives?
Two grown boys, but he's
been separated for years.
Isn't he too old for you?
He's the smartest man I've ever met.
He's intelligent, polite, cultured,
caring. He's got it all.
I had never felt like this before.
When I see him my heart leaps
and his hands drive me crazy.
Val, you, in love?
As a child I'd let my balloons go.
I liked to watch them rise.
It made me feel free.
I don't know if I'm in love,
but I like him a lot.
He's different from all the other men.
Maybe you too were born for matrimony.
Not so fast.
I feel a normal woman
for the first time in my life,
a feeling that fascinates me,
to be like all other women I meet.
I see Jaime nearly every day.
I realize I've discovered something
as important as sex.
The love of a man.
I have fallen madly in love
for the first time in my life.
He takes me to the best places,
and always picks me up.
In his Jaguar?
I'd like that, really.
A boyfriend with a Jaguar.
And how is he in bed?
I don't know yet.
You're in love!
Jaime, you need to use a condom.
Really? I want to feel you.
- Is it necessary?
- Yes.
Okay, no problem.
I'll go get one.
And while you're at it, take
the cat out. We should be alone.
Caress me.
Sorry I was so fast,
but I've had a tiring day.
Don't worry. It's okay.
Could you leave the light on?
You should fear nothing now, you have me.
And tomorrow will be a very,
very special day.
You'll see.
Today we finally made love.
I hardly felt anything,
like the first time with Edouard.
But I love him and he loves me.
That's the most important to me.
- It's marvellous.
- Yes.
The office. Don't look,
it's all a mess right now.
I'm living a marvellous dream with Jaime
from which I don't want to wake.
A room with a view,
wooden floors. Nice?
The corresponding full bathroom,
and here is our bedroom.
Look, and the bathroom...
This closes completely.
Black out, really.
It's the perfect size.
3 bedrooms.
Yes, our room, the office downstairs,
and another for...
Guests.
Yes, and...
the other day you said you
wanted children soon,
but don't take that as pressure, please.
The windows are 6 stories tall.
I've always dreamed of a view of the sea,
but it's too expensive, darling.
Don't you worry, okay?
That's up to me, and period.
And how is he in bed?
Truthfully, nothing out of this world.
He comes too fast.
He says he works too much.
You always said sex is most important.
Maybe because I wasn't in love.
Val, I think it's a bit soon
to go live together.
You haven't been going out long.
You said I should change my life,
and I'm doing just that.
Being with him, I feel,
for the first time, no need for
anyone else. Besides, I'm nearly 29.
Maybe I should think about having kids.
- So that's it.
- One of many reasons.
A man who doesn't like animals worries me.
He's allergic to cat fur.
Okay, pay no mind to me.
I'm going through bad times.
- Will you take him?
- Yes.
- Can you zip me up?
- Sure.
- What are you looking at?
- The icebox.
- What's wrong with it?
- I love it.
Do you love me as well?
With that dress on, you look
beautiful.
To you?
Are you okay?
Of course I am, but I feel
a bit uncomfortable.
You're paying it all. You spent
a fortune on furniture.
What good is money if you can't spend it?
When you find a job,
we'll talk about this again.
See anything?
It's beautiful.
Thanks, Jaime, but you can't pay
it all and give me these gifts.
It's to say I love you.
Sorry, did I step on you?
The table's small.
What a son of a bitch!
What?
There's no need.
You fuck well. I can tell
you've been with many men.
I don't want to think about that now.
You're mine only.
Mine only.
Don't talk.
What are you doing?
Embrace me.
Aren't you afraid?
Not any longer.
Yes?
- Valerie?
- Yes, speaking.
- Hi, it's Harry.
- Hi, Harry.
Could I see you this morning?
Sure, I'll be there in
half an hour. See you.
I hired a girl, but she was a disaster.
She didn't last a week.
If you're willing,
you could start right now.
Right now?
Yes, I need someone urgently.
We present the collection in
3 weeks. We're up to here.
We haven't spoken about money yet.
A ham for Christmas.
Right, Maite?
- A client is waiting.
- I'll be right there. Thanks.
Don't worry about money.
We'll reach an agreement.
Coffee?
Hello.
I have very good news.
Where were you?
- I've started to work.
- What?
I called your cell phone but it was off.
- Harry wants me to start right...
- Harry?
- They're...
- Who the fuck is Harry?
The boss, an Italian.
I've been hired by a fashion firm.
An Italian?
He hired you just like that?
Not knowing how you work?
How weird.
Isn't that weird?
You're still young and have a lot to learn.
What's wrong?
I thought you'd be happy about my job.
And I am. I am happy,
but I didn't expect it,
and that's why I reacted that way.
But I am happy.
Forgive me.
Really, forgive me.
That night, that marvellous dream
I thought I was living
began to turn into a nightmare.
I just give an account that I did not know
the person of which I had fallen in love.
When the catalogues?
They should be printed tomorrow.
You do it, Valerie.
Where is he?
I'm losing my patience!
- What's going on?
- I'll bust your chops!
What are you doing here?
So, you're the one who
wants to fuck my wife?
Why is she here so late?
You think I don't know what's going on?
You think I don't know?
Jaime,
go home. I'll be there soon.
Right away, darling. Wait for me.
I'll wait outside.
Get up. Come on, get up.
How are you?
Did you sleep well?
Darling, you know what I've thought?
That we could both use a trip.
Forgive me, my love.
Forgive me.
Truthfully, I am very stressed.
I can't forget my problems.
We'll go on vacation, and we'll be fine.
Don't touch me! It would
be best for us to separate.
Separate?
My darling, we can't separate.
I can't live without you.
If you leave me, I won't bear it.
My darling, my little love,
please.
You have to understand me.
Give me a chance, I'm in bad shape.
Jaime, you're not well.
You're a compulsive liar,
your moods are unpredictable.
You're aggressive, you come
to work and show me up.
You're not acting in a normal way.
- You need to see a doctor.
- I'll do as you wish.
Whatever you want, but don't leave me.
Please, you can't leave me.
I need you.
- When did you get here?
- Today.
You're unrecognizable.
You know what I'm thinking about?
Kuhaylan. Remember?
The first Arabian horse.
I think than man learned to tame it.
Honestly, you're unrecognizable,
Valerie. You need to be alone.
Look at me.
You know you can always count on me.
People don't change, but I had
hopes of doing so with Jaime.
Sonia was right. I'm blind
and, what's worse, I still love him.
I can't go on. All I want to do
is lose consciousness,
disappear from this world.
Oh, Val, Val! Why don't
you take a vacation?
It would do you well.
I appreciate it. You're right,
I can't work like this.
I can't concentrate.
And don't forget to take the ham.
Hit him with it and make it
look like an accident.
Were you not gay,
you and I would be together.
Oh, Madonna!
Yes, yes, that's it.
Do it. Don't stop.
Darling, look, I have a
Christmas present for you.
- What's your name?
- Vane.
Vane, this is Val.
Val, this is Vane.
We make up a perfect team.
Come here, my love.
Come here, love, come here.
Please, come here.
We could have a great time.
- What's your name?
- Vane.
Come, come on, my love,
come, come, come here.
Come, my darling.
What tits, huh?
What tits!
The biggest thing you've got, bitch.
You've got a piercing, huh?
That's enough.
Get off, off, off!
Where's my money?
I have no cash, you know?
- Where are my 100 euros?
- I don't know.
I have no idea.
Jaime, we're expecting a baby.
What?
We're expecting a baby.
That's impossible.
Why is it impossible?
I don't doubt you're expecting,
I doubt it's mine.
How can you say that?
You know why I doubt it?
Because I'm sterile for many years now.
You laid someone else and
want to dump it on me.
You're a monster.
And you are a hysterical piece of shit.
I've always wanted to tell
you this. You're a whore!
You lie all the time, like all whores!
I don't know how I stood you so long.
And that's it, the conversation is over.
Don't cry, you pig.
Don't cry, pig.
A baby is what I most wanted in this world.
You did right, Val. You're
still young for having kids.
I don't know what to do now.
I quit my job, spent my savings and,
thanks to him, I'm in deep debt.
I paid the rent for months.
Well, don't worry.
What, what is going on here?
Can't you see?
She is leaving.
What, you're clearing off?
My love,
- I beg you, baby.
- Leave her alone.
If you walk out that door,
I swear I'll kill you. Understand?
I'll kill you, you hear?
I am going to destroy you, bitch!
- You hear?
- I'll call the cops.
This is fuckin' shit!
Let's go, Val, we're out of here.
I beg you.
I beg you, please.
I swear I'll change, my love.
Forgive me, my love.
You can't go, my love.
You won't get away from me, you hear?
Whore!
No one leaves me, you know?
No one leaves me, you bitch!
You're coming to my place
until you get over that
son of a bitch bastard.
Val?
Hello.
Val.
Val, you can't go on like this.
Val, you have to react.
You look terrible.
How long have you been here?
Oh, my baby...
I'll help you clean all this up.
Look, I've brought food.
Come on.
Breaking off with Jaime
nearly cost me my life.
Seeing the depths of the pit, I want out
and to see the light again.
After several months without an orgasm
my body was beginning to rouse.
It was like waking from
a long, eternal lethargy.
I'm starving.
I know what I will do to
quench my appetite again.
- Hi.
- I think I made a mistake.
- No, it's here. Come in.
Come in.
- You're Val, right?
- Yes.
You called for the interview.
- I'm Cindy. One of the girls.
- It's a pleasure.
You'll be attended to right away.
- Cristina.
- Val, Valerie.
Valerie? A nice name. Let me
have a look, please. Thanks.
Have a seat, Val.
- Where have you worked?
- In this?
Yes, of course.
This is my first time.
Interesting. What can you do?
Everything, as long as it's with a condom.
That's fine.
Go with Cindy.
Use more make-up.
Clients don't pay for
what they have at home.
- I think I found a job.
- Tell me about it.
For what company?
In a brothel.
Come on, Val, that's not funny.
I start tomorrow.
- Are you serious?
- Yes.
Look,
we spend most of the time waiting.
Want to see the man of my life?
His name is Migue.
He lives with my mother near Rio.
I sent him there because
his father is a bastard.
I take all this for him, but I can't go on.
I must whisper.
These walls have ears.
Come on, girls, let's dance.
Are you going to behave?
Cindy.
I'm Mar.
I'm Stephanie.
- What's your name, child?
- Laura.
I'm Val.
Val, I want you.
- What do I have to do?
- That's up to you,
but he's always high.
He cannot have full sex.
A good hand job will make him happy.
A two-hour hand job?
You know, you play a little, massages...
This is no school, Val.
The client isn't going to gobble you up.
You look beautiful.
Hi.
You're new, aren't you?
Come on, get in the water with me.
Come here.
- You have a special smell.
- Really?
You like it?
- Let's go to bed.
- No. Let's stay here.
Fucking doesn't turn me on.
Okay, relax, we'll see what can be done.
Well, I'm from Seville.
I work for a machine company
that sells throughout Europe.
Fuck!
Stop, girl, or I'll go crazy.
Why the fuck did you stop?
Because you told me to.
You pay no attention to me.
Keep going, shit!
No one's ever done this to me before.
- Did you go to the April fair?
- No.
You know what's happened
to me all of a sudden?
- I've fallen in love with you.
- But we just met.
That's right, love at first sight.
Why don't we get into bed?
Okay, but just because I love you.
What a nice ass you've got!
I'm sorry if I hurt you.
Slap me again.
At that moment I felt a strange feeling.
The same as at 15, with Eduard.
I needed to know more,
to learn from this world I just entered.
What are you doing?
The first time is tough, I know.
We have all cried the first time.
But you get used to it,
it becomes an exercise.
- Are you okay?
- Of course I am.
- Where's my money?
- Here you are.
- How did it go?
- Fine, but a bit of a pain.
You expected a cultured, interesting man
with a pleasant conversation?
I remind you you're a whore.
You look tired.
Not at all, I'm delighted.
What do clients like?
A bit of everything.
Some want to tie you up,
others stick things in you.
You just gave me an idea.
That handsome is he!
His name is Giovanni.
He's Italian.
The other one's a pig.
They come to Barcelona often.
They're good clients.
I'll be right out.
Come on, you look divine.
It was a pleasure to meet you.
I hope you enjoyed it.
What an intense life.
I would like mine to be that way too.
What's your name?
Valerie.
I have a strange feeling
that here, somehow, time stands still.
You're just learning to be who you are.
What about you?
You are the future of my past.
And me, perhaps, the memory of your future.
It's not a difficult job, just different.
How can you say that?
I like to do it free, you know that.
And I get paid, what else could I want?
- Have you ever been spanked?
- What?
Try it. You'd be surprised.
We have too many preconceptions.
And those flowers?
A present from Pedro, a client.
- They're pretty.
- Yes.
Still thinking of Jaime?
Not at all.
I have an Italian client I like a lot.
Be careful, Val.
I've seen that look before.
- Keep it.
- No.
Don't be silly.
Yes, Cristina?
Okay, I'm on my way.
It's Giovanni.
Giovanni is different from
all other clients I've met.
I shivers when he touches me.
He makes me go to the cosmos, see stars.
I think I'm in love with him.
Thank you.
I live in Calabria because
mama lives there.
I spend most of the year travelling.
- What?
- Your left eyebrow.
- What's wrong with it?
- I like it.
That uncombed hair.
You know?
I communicate better with
my body than with words.
With a caress I describe things
that make me feel alive.
I'm scared, Giovanni, I like you too much.
Your smell is irresistible.
- What smell?
- The Mediterranean,
freshness, life.
I like you too much too.
- Give me your phone number.
- I can't.
- My boss would kill me.
- Your boss should pay you more.
Will you call me again this week?
Do you want to know the answer?
Look,
this proves that I will call you again.
Save it for me, and take good care of it.
I have to go.
Your time's up.
Although I'd like to sleep with you...
What did you say?
Nothing, forget it.
What about the money?
I'm a disaster.
What if I pay you another hour?
This one is on me.
Val, be very careful.
Don't fall in love with him.
It's sheer logic.
It's impossible for a man
who goes with whores
to be loyal.
Believe me.
Valerie, you're beautiful.
Your new job suits you.
Although I'm jealous of the other men.
When does your plane leave?
- In 3 hours.
- Why, why don't you stay?
I have to go to Madrid.
We could order a Coca-Cola
and go to the bathroom.
I thought you dropped that.
I'm thirsty again.
I guess you'll give me a good discount.
A Coca-Cola and an opener, please.
Don't you like it?
Of course I like this suite but
I don't want to be your fiance, Pedro.
Val, listen to me.
I'll do whatever you want
for you to love me.
And I won't say a word while we're fucking.
What I want is for you to marry me.
Look,
this is for you.
Fuckin' look at it.
- You don't like it?
- No.
I was given a similar one once.
I can't accept it.
Don't give me anything.
And no flowers, I hate flowers.
Pedro, you're pressing me.
Go see some other girls.
What are you saying?
I don't want others, I want you!
You're hurting me.
I won't marry you.
You're drunk.
- I had better go.
- Go, go?
You know what this room costs me?
Do you know what this room costs me?
I pay you, and you'll do as I say.
You understand me?
Here's your fuckin' money.
Pick it up.
Pick it the fuck up!
Stay there on all fours.
Stay there on all fours. Yeah.
- You're hurting me?
- Do you like it?
Now you'll ask me to spank you,
like you've always done.
You like that?
Bitch, you're a real bitch.
You're hurting me.
Please, Pedro.
What are you complaining about?
What?
You chose to be a whore.
You'll do as I say,
in one way or another.
Tell me you like this.
No, please!
You like this?
I love you, Val.
And you, what a view?
That night I understood, what grandma said,
prostitution and marriage
aren't that different.
You become the property of someone else.
And when they're like Jaime or Pedro,
your life has no value any longer.
I thought he would kill me.
There are many Pedros in this.
Go, you're still in time.
After, it's difficult to drop it.
You could go to Rio and give
my son an enormous kiss.
Now go home. You look tired.
I don't want to be alone.
Hi,
you've got a client, and
there aren't that many Pedros.
I'm sorry, I can't go.
I haven't slept for nights.
- And I have a date.
- I'll go.
You're going nowhere.
Who's the date with?
You're committed to me.
I'd go if I were you.
It's the Italian, your friend.
- Giovanni?
- Yes, and his friend.
Mae and you will go right now.
Cheers!
- Hi.
- Hi, darling.
Come on, princess.
I've finally convinced Giovanni,
the 'macaroni', that
you'd be mine tonight.
Come here, beautiful.
Come here.
You've said nothing since you're here.
What a pain of a whore!
I couldn't stop thinking about Giovanni.
I couldn't believe he didn't pick me.
I felt disgust while Alejandro fucked me.
Cindy was right saying
I should quit prostitution.
I could still do that.
But Cindy was trapped.
She owed Cris a lot of money,
and she was infatuated with her.
She couldn't stand not having her son.
What happened?
Cindy.
She foll out the window.
A suicide, we think.
She got a call. Seems like
her husband took the boy,
but we know nothing more.
Cindy would never leave her son.
We buried her the next day,
just the girls from the brothel.
I was devastated.
I can't stop thinking about Cindy.
We're all sorry about Cindy,
but life goes on, and the job
that feeds you as well.
I'm not going.
Yes you are, darling.
Hello?
Hello.
- Hi.
- I see they didn't tell you.
- That's okay.
- What's your name?
- Valerie.
I'm Inigo. Delighted.
Could you pick me up and put me on the bed?
I could do that but
it takes me a great effort.
Have no fear.
I feel absolutely nothing.
No, you don't need to undress me.
The only place I feel anything is my neck.
And my hands a bit.
- You smell nice.
- What do I smell of?
- Chocolate.
- Chocolate?
Could you do me a favour?
Move your fingers.
Come on, Valerie,
Move the fingers of your hand.
For you it's easy.
I am incapable of moving a single finger.
You don't know how many times, suddenly,
I imagine me hands and my
fingers start to move, and
I get up off the chair and I start to run.
I can tough the flowers,
feel the velvet,
and caress a woman as beautiful as you.
We should love ourselves more, Valerie.
Go, you're still in time.
After, it's difficult to drop it.
Never give up anything you really long for
because you'll regret it.
Believe me.
I know where you live.
I'll go get you.
Where are you going? Where, huh?
I don't care what you say, I'm gone.
I do care about what is said.
Clear out! Give me the bag!
You whore!
Go on, get out of my sight!
You're unbearable!
We always realize things
when it's too late.
Since the accident,
whenever I see anyone, I give them advice.
What advice?
To take advantage of their
life every day, but truly.
Live.
You need to be alone.
Enjoy life as much as you can.
And I can touch grass, feel velvet.
I slowly started to caress my body.
I had finally discovered
what road to follow.
That of being myself.
Although it was pouring rain,
I decided to go out.
I wanted to share that moment with
who'd always been by my side.
What are you doing here?
I know I'm unpresentable.
Congratulations!
- Are you okay?
- Better than ever.
I wanted to thank you.
For what?
For being my friend, for your advice.
I always follow your advice.
I've decided to leave the brothel.
I'm so happy.
I'll spend some time with Hassan.
Won't you open your present?
It's beautiful!
It has no zipper.
Now I don't have that problem.
He helps me.
This is Marcos.
We met through an ad.
- Hi, Marcos.
- Hi.
- I'm glad for you.
- Come in and change.
- No, I have to go.
- What will you do now?
Live.
I'm a promiscuous woman, yes,
because I want to use
sex as a means to find
what everyone is looking for.
Recognition,
pleasure, self-esteem and, in short,
love and affection.
What's pathological about that?
If you want to give me a name, go on,
I don't mind.
But you must know I'm really a mermaid,
a dryad, simply a nymph.
- Hi.
What?
Get home?
I want to fuck with you.
I have no money.
No matter. It's free.
It's impossible for a man
who goes with whores
to be loyal.
Valerie...
Live.
Sazu489...
Facebook.com/sazu489