You told me you'd be there for me!
Calm down, just calm down, calm down!
Tired of blisters on your fingers?
Need a helping hand at home?
You need Blinky!
Hi, my name's Blinky.
The household robot with a mind of its own.
He's a servant, a helper, and a friend
Kids are gonna love Blinky and you will too!
Blinky is so helpful around the house, it's brought us together and made us closer as a family.
He's my new best friend!
He's just like one of the family.
All my friends have one...
Hi honey what's going on?
I know what I want for Christmas.
Hi, my name's Blinky...
...and I just want to be your friend.
Will you be my friend?
It's officially the best Christmas ever.
I'll never get sick of him.
Music plays
99, 98, 97, 96,
95, 94, 93, 92...
Muffled shouting.
99, 98, 97, 96,
95, 94, 93, 92, ...
7, 6, 5, 4, 3, 2, 1.
Ready or not here I come...
I found you.
Yeah, I got bored waiting around.
Would you like to play another game?
Sure.
999,862
999,861
999,860
999,859
Muffled signs of parents arguing in background.
999,861
999,860
- 999...
- Stop counting.
No problem.
Why did you stop counting?
- I'm sorry, would you like me to continuel?
- Yeah.
And I want you to stay completely still for the next 24 hours.
No problem.
999,862
999,861
999,860
Clean this!
No problem, I like to clean things.
Why did you move?
I told you not to move.
I told you not to stop counting.
I'm sorry, would you like me to continue?
You have to do everything I say, I own you!
No problem.
999...
What use are you anyway? All you're good for is cooking and cleaning and playing stupid games!
Can you make my parents stop fighting? Can you do that?
No problem.
I could tell you to kill everybody, and you'd just stand there blinking like an idiot!
What does it matter? Go on...
Kill my parents, kill me.
- No problem.
- Kill the dog, kill everyone.
No problem, no problem, no problem, no problem...
Mom!
No problem, no problem, no problem...
Blinky's broken.
No problem, no problem, no problem, no problem...
What did you do to him?
I didn't do anything, I think he's broken or something.
We need to get a new one.
Just turn him off and turn him back on again.
And if you make another mess like that I'm going to make Blinky clean and cook you for dinner.
I didn't do it, Blinky did it!
Don't start with me, I am not in the mood.
Clean it up!
No problem, no problem, no problem, no problem...
Hi my name's Blinky and I just want to be your friend.
Will you be my friend?
Go on, do as you're told.
Clean it up!
Would you like to play another game?
Go away.
999,862
What?
Get out of my room.
Go annoy someone else.
Stop looking at me like that.
What do you want?
I just want to be your friend.
I did what you asked
Did I do good?
I just want to be your friend.
Lets be frrrrieeeends...
I don't trust him.
I don't understand you Alex.
Why would he hurt Rosie?
It makes no sense.
I just don't trust him.
Why won't you believe me?
Because you're bored with him and you're just trying to make us buy a newer one, that's why.
A clear frontrunner has appeared in the so-called robotics race.
Shellcore has announced that its prototype defence unit codenamed Warmachine...
...is ready for public testing after several expensive setbacks.
...the family
I just want to be your friend.
Would you like to play another game?
- Look at the mess you've made
- What?
You did this, clean it up!
No problem.
...excessive exposure to water...
...make sure Blinky is updated with the latest downloadable firmware updates...
...make sure Blinky is serviced at least once every 2 months...
7, 6, 5, 4, 3, 2, 1..
Ready or not, here I come...
Do you like your meatballs?
They're fine, thank you.
Have you seen Alex?
No problem.
Alex is right here.
I recycled him.
I don't understand you  Blinky.
What do you mean?
I cleaned him and cooked him for dinner.
You're eating him.
Did I do good?
Shellcore has issued a full product recall and full refund. please call....
Ready or not, here I come...
Hi, my name's Blinky and I just want to be your friend.