Oh. Hi.
I don't know what to do.
I don't even have friends
who have kids.
I'm not a kid.
I want to treat you
like the adult
that your father wanted you
to grow into
and that your mother wished
she could see.
Why can't you look me
in the face?
You were twins.
Looking at you
is like looking at a ghost.
Do you remember her?
Well, I was five
when she died.
It's been a rough week.
Let's just be friends.
For now.
Drink it.
Um, I'm not a milk drinker,
per se.
Beer?
Mm, no, I'm driving.
To silver falls?
Why would I want
to go to haunted silver falls?
Burning mannequin.
Oh, that.
Yeah, I'm not tuned in
to the cool kids like you are.
Jordan's not ready
for the falls.
That's why we're going
to the movies.
Drink it.
It's hard to funnel beer
when your gut's full of 2%.
How'd she do?
At school her first week.
I don't know about her,
but it's been the best week
of my life.
She just lost her father,
Larry.
She plays like she's okay,
but you're smart enough to know
she's not, right?
Yeah, she... she's safe.
Let's go.
Lates.
Good night, Larry.
I like that kid.
Hey, guys. Hey.
Thank you, thank you.
Hey, Larry, check this out.
It kicks in mild
and wraps around your brain
like a warm blanket.
It's fast Albert.
I'd buy two, 'cause,
when I did it, I took one,
I took another one
a half hour later.
And you won't need to drink.
Two?
Do you really need that many?
Come on, Larry.
You know I don't sell anything
I haven't tried myself.
Actually, I don't.
But how much?
- $100 for four.
Trust me. You'll want a friend
to be in your worid.
Seriously?
That price is a rip-off.
And that surprises you?
Where do you think you are,
There you go.
Enjoy.
- Come on.
- I'm trying.
'Kay.
I'm not taking those.
Why not?
Well, it's just not my style.
But you're from L.A.
Yeah, but that's not
who I am.
- Please?
If we don't do this,
you're gonna be bored
out of your mind,
and you're never gonna go out
with me again.
I like this.
Really?
- Yeah.
I mean, I've never been
in the woods before.
Griffith park, but that's,
like, more dogs than trees.
Why the mannequin?
- Oh.
Scares the ghosts.
Ghosts?
Yeah, there's a lot
of dead people in silver falls.
Didn't anyone tell you?
It's ghost city, usa.
Right.
So who died?
Who didn't die?
I've been to six funerals.
There were several suicides,
a car accident,
a bulimic
whose stomach exploded...
A drowning and leukemia.
Mom and dad?
You wanna talk about it?
Tell me more
about the ghosts.
Um...
Well, they're nice.
They only kill you once.
- I could die once.
- Yeah, they like to stop by
and watch you sleep.
My favorite.
And they like to whisper
to you.
"Jordan. Jordan."
They like to open doors
that have been closed.
Turn on appliances.
Well, it's how they talk.
Well, I don't speak haunted.
But I'm pretty sure
they like candy.
The Reese's, the milk duds.
Wrappers all over the floor.
Come on.
Let's go.
Jordan.
Larry?
Shh.
Cops got your boy.
I'll take you home.
Do me a favor and tell them
my name is Jane.
Jane Smith.
- Why?
You got a record?
- Can you be cool?
Or do I need to tell you
how to do this?
If we get out of this,
you owe me one.
Oh.
Oh, no, it only counts
if we kiss.
Damn it.
He's coming up on my side.
Your left tail light
is out, Robbie.
Again?
I just had it fixed.
Must have a short.
I told you
not to take the pickup.
Dad, I'm a little...
little low on gas.
You take her home.
Her home.
Yes, dad.
Dad?
Ugh.
You know, he's not gonna be
able to keep up with you.
Excuse me?
Look, I've known Larry
a long time.
He's cool.
Good guy.
Obviously not your type.
Like you?
Nah, you couldn't even keep up
with me.
But I could go slower.
If asked nicely.
And with less clothes.
Oh, so, you mean
if I asked with this?
Depends what you do with it.
Ugh.
Well, thanks for the ride.
No, it hasn't begun yet.
It's about to.
Does that really work
for you?
I don't have to work
for anything.
Well, you'll be working
for yourself tonight.
Night, dad.
And mom.
Do you want me
to put these somewhere else?
I like them the way
they were.
Then why did you do this?
I didn't.
Maybe it was the wind.
House is drafty.
Here we go.
I hope you're hungry.
I like cereal.
Like, low-tech.
Cheerios, life, pops.
She likes cereal.
We'll get some today.
So how come my dad
never visited?
And why haven't you guys
ever come to L.A.?
Like you said,
I look just like your mother.
It was hard for him.
And for me.
So is silver falls
really haunted?
Or was Larry
just pulling my leg?
No.
But we do have
some ghosts in the house.
And the bodies
we keep in the basement.
So that's the smell.
No, that's my cooking.
Hey, it's Larry.
You don't have
to leave a message.
I have caller I.D.
And will now commence stalking.
Don't tell me.
Miss Hollywood.
And you must be looking
for my handsome son.
The valedictorian.
Who scored 2400 on his S.A.T.S.
- Hi, Mr. Parrish.
- Dr. Parrish.
Dr. Parrish.
Jordan, not "miss Hollywood."
But the same Jordan
who got my son arrested
for carrying enough alprazolam
to sedate a horse.
- No.
No, not that Jordan.
How's that gonna look
on a Stanford application,
do you think?
They don't have to know.
He was arrested.
By who, Robbie's dad?
I mean, I'm sure
we can work something out.
Hmm, so you've been here
two weeks
and you've got us dialed in,
don't you?
- No, I'm just...
- Staying away from my son.
He's grounded.
You can see him at school,
because I can't help that,
but that's it.
Good-bye, Jordan.
Jordan.
We might be
in over our heads.
We can deal.
With anything, right?
Right.
My turn.
It's not nice
to sneak around.
I didn't mean to.
My door keeps opening.
Oh. Country homes
have their own personality.
Your door's
just expressing itself.
I locked it.
Then it wouldn't have opened.
Maybe you thought
you locked it.
Look, if you're scared,
you can sleep with us.
Kevin, that...
that sounded bad.
I meant in here
on a sleeping bag.
I'm not sleeping very well.
There's a wool blanket
in the second closet.
It's heavy.
It might help you sleep.
And, Jordan, next time,
when our door is shut
and you need something,
knock.
Have you seen my silk scarf?
It's black and gold.
Actually, don't ask me how,
but it's hermes.
I had it in my room,
but it's gone.
Did my mom sleepwalk?
No.
Maybe I sleepwalk.
The pictures.
The door.
Stuff.
Maybe.
Or maybe it's the wind.
Oh, by the way, I found some
candy wrappers in your room.
Be careful.
We get mice.
I'm gonna be late.
It's black and gold,
the scarf.
If you see it.
After you.
Now isn't this better?
Only a matter of time.
Come here.
Did Robbie
really drive you home?
I couldn't find you.
- Don't...
- What?
Give me the "we should be
friends" speech.
I know it by memory.
Why would I do that?
Robbie said
he drove you home.
Emphasis on "drove."
And you believed him?
Well, not at first,
but I figured
I was just being delusional.
Robbie doesn't know anything
about driving.
But you do.
- No.
No, no.
Actually, yeah.
Yes, I do.
You drive with your heart.
I so did not want
to be your friend.
How long
are you grounded for?
I told my dad
that I bought the stuff,
but he doesn't believe me.
- Oh.
He thinks
you're the anti-Christ.
Well, don't worry.
I know how to sneak around.
And I won't be grounded
for long.
My dad's a shrink,
and he'll just read a report
about confinement
and adolescence,
and then he'll cave.
Parents.
Just got to wait 'em out.
Why can't I find a single book
on the paranormal,
ghosts, or spirits?
Well, you're
in the school library.
No one expects you to read.
I was just kidding
about all that stuff
the other night.
My bedroom door opens
by itself.
Good to know.
What about your window?
Seriously.
That's creepy.
Houses have a mind
of their own.
And I can't
get this ring off.
It's been a couple days.
I actually know about this.
Come on.
Yeah.
- Ooh, boys' room.
- Yeah.
- Okay.
Mm.
It's gonna hurt.
It's not gonna hurt, okay?
Come here.
See?
- I told you.
I swear, I felt it.
It was off.
Creepy, right?
Who gave it to you anyway?
Robbie?
I found it in the woods
at silver falls.
I heard you whispering my name,
then I saw it at my feet.
No, I didn't whisper.
Well, I thought
maybe you dropped it.
So this isn't even your ring?
No, and to be honest, I don't
really remember putting it on.
It's like...
I'm not crazy,
but it's like it chose me.
Okay, well,
we're getting it off.
Let me just figure out how.
Come on.
Hey, Jordan.
Have a seat.
What's up?
They sent your file.
File?
The executor
of your father's will.
He wanted us to be prepared,
because we don't have kids.
You got caught shoplifting
when you were 12.
You smoked pot.
You did drugs.
My dad got a new girlfriend.
I was acting out.
It was obvious.
Like, I knew
I was gonna get caught.
Then why did you
want to get caught here?
What?
Jordan, we know
you're mourning your father.
You miss him.
This is a new town.
Maybe you think
we're a little strange.
But we're really normal.
I like it here.
Then why'd you go
in my wallet?
And my scarf.
Your mother gave me that scarf.
What are you talking about?
Come on, Jordan,
maybe we've never been
parents before,
but we're not stupid.
Are you on drugs now?
No, don't answer that.
What's going on?
- You tell us.
- I can't until you tell me
what you think I did.
- Goddamn it,
you stole from us!
You took our stuff.
- What makes you think I did it?
- We found them.
In your underwear drawer.
You went in my room
in my drawers?
Don't turn it around on us.
I swear
on the penalty of death,
I didn't take your shit.
We made an appointment
for you to talk to someone.
Dr. Parrish.
Dr. Parrish?
He'll see you tomorrow.
I'll see anyone you want.
You can come.
Just, please, not Larry's dad.
I can't drive you 40 Miles
to the next therapist.
And there's another problem.
Tonight is date night.
Well, I don't know
what that means.
Date night means that
I will not neglect my wife...
Because you're now a member
of this family.
- No kids allowed.
- I'm not a kid.
- You're part of our home.
We just can't have you
stealing from it.
So we're going out tonight
as planned.
But you're staying in.
- So sad.
- Mm.
I know this might seem
a bit extreme to you.
You'll talk to Dr. Parrish,
and things will be fine.
Don't hate us, Jordan.
But please don't use us.
That's good.
Date night.
Cock-sucking motherfucker,
goddamn asshole.
I'm gonna have
to unhinge the door.
We are awful, awful people.
We are not that bad.
No, we're not that bad.
We make mistakes.
We're gonna learn,
and Jordan's gonna learn.
Kevin, we imprisoned her.
Well, what if she
would have found our stash?
Then we lose the upper hand.
What?
We definitely failed
child-proofing 101.
Oh, man.
Well, is date night over?
Is that what you want?
I want what you want.
There's no way
you could drive.
There's no way.
Jordan.
Jordan?
What the hell?
Jordan.
Jordan!
- It's locked.
- Jordan, open the door.
- Jordan.
I'm going to kick it down.
- Open the door.
Open it up.
Jordan,
I'm gonna kick it down!
Oh, my God.
My medicine.
Okay.
All right.
I'm giving you haloperidol.
This is haloperidol.
It's gonna help you.
We did good.
She's soaked.
Let's get her clothes off
and get her to bed.
Hey.
I'm Jordan.
So does she have a name?
She special?
Like, short bus special?
What is this?
Like, some sort
of reverse psychology?
Like, invite another foster kid
in and create some sort
of a sibling rivalry?
Oh, God.
This isn't happening.
Jordan, it's over now.
We are so sorry.
Your mother was claustrophobic.
We didn't know
that you were too.
We won't be doing
anything like that again.
You have an appointment
with Dr. Parrish
this morning before school.
I can't breathe.
How many pills
did you give her?
Just the one.
Jordan.
It's a new day.
It can't be stopped.
Deal with it.
Seat belt.
Are there legends
about silver falls?
What kind?
Ones involving a ring?
You mean like lost treasure?
Ghosts.
There's ash man.
Burned American Indian.
That's more of a yeti thing.
You know, to attract tourists.
No, like,
maybe involving a girl?
Maybe my age?
You seen a ghost?
No, it's a creative writing
assignment for school.
Uh-huh.
You like to write?
Your mother wrote.
I just want to base it
on something real.
Make it authentic.
Find your face.
Not your forever face.
Your for now face.
There are no bad faces, Jordan.
You're not leaving here
until you do this.
Do you always see
your patients in your kitchen?
I meet my patients
where I believe
they'll be the most comfortable.
My office is at the hospital.
Would your prefer
to meet there?
Oh.
And what are we happy about?
That we just completed
the task,
so we get to move on.
Are you sleeping?
Like a baby.
Are you afraid?
Of being left alone?
I prefer it.
Mm.
Your grades, Jordan,
they've been...
Up and down.
Is there someone else
in the room?
- No.
- Are they telling you
not to trust me?
Are you hearing things?
'Cause you keep looking
over there.
I'm nervous.
Are you afraid
of what's in your file?
No.
'Cause you look troubled.
I have a math test.
Okay.
I want to see you once a week.
Wednesdays?
But if you continue
to lie to me
and avoid my questions,
I'm gonna want to see you
every morning.
And when I see you next time,
I want you
to tell me something that
no one else knows about you.
You okay?
No.
I knew you'd get tired
of pretending you liked it here.
Look.
There's this place I go
when everything seems
to get to be just too much.
It's a little waterfall
over in silver falls.
You can walk behind it.
Why would I want to do that?
Watch the icicles melt?
Things seem to go right for me
after I go there.
Do you want to go?
Hey, leave her alone.
Or what?
Nothing.
Just stop being a jerk,
and you can just go...
- Robbie, stop!
Get off him.
What's wrong with you?
Get off.
- Get off.
Just showing him
how it's done.
Are you okay?
Are you just gonna let him
do that?
He's just like his dad.
He gets away with murder.
Always has.
I'll be fine.
I was actually about to get
the upper hand.
I think he knew it.
Let's ditch.
I have
a killer attendance record.
- Not anymore.
Come on.
Where do you want to go?
The cemetery.
I was thinking the same thing.
Cemetery.
Um...
You're looking for someone?
'Cause I-I could help.
I don't know the name.
Okay, what's going on
with you?
Saw your father today.
- Really?
Office or kitchen?
Kitchen.
- Good.
What'd you tell him?
You seeing him twice a week?
Once.
Good.
Did he ask you what's your first
memory of elementary school?
No. I have to tell him
something no one else knows.
That's more serious.
What are you gonna say?
That I like to hold my pee in
till the absolute last second.
You know, man over nature.
Oh, God.
You're good.
You've done this before, huh?
Look, a lot of people
have talked to my father.
It's a small town.
But don't worry.
He won't say anything
you've said.
I'm gonna tell you something
that's actually true.
You can trust me.
I'm being followed
by a dead girl.
Where?
She's behind you.
What's she look like?
You know, my mom was crazy.
My dad told me.
She didn't just drown.
She walked into the water.
It's happening.
I'm turning into her.
She saw dead giris?
- No.
I don't know.
Well, what does she want?
I think she wants us
to follow her.
You... you lead the way.
You think she's headed
to water street?
You'd know better than me.
Wait up a sec.
Do all your girlfriends
see the dead?
Um, only the ones I like.
Crazy feels really normal.
Sort of.
She stopped.
Where did she stop?
Outside that bar.
My God.
Jordan.
Jordan, what are you doing?
Hey, hey, son,
you got some I.D.?
Wyatt dahl's scheduled
to be executed
tonight at 11:00 P.M.
Dahl was tried and convicted
for the brutal slaying
of his twin daughters
holly and Heather dahl,
and he's been sitting
on death row for over 20 years.
I know who she is.
I know this looks bad.
But it's the best thing
for you.
I trusted you.
And you think I let you down.
But it's only
because I like you.
It's going to be okay.
We know exactly what to do.
We have a plan.
I'm not crazy.
No, I'm not like my mother.
I'm not!
- No, there's no need for that.
We'll just take this
to my place.
We'll have a nice little chat.
- Come on.
Let's go.
That's all right.
I hate you.
I know.
All of you.
Okay, we are going
to have a conversation.
If you get violent,
you will be sedated.
Understood?
Out.
Thanks for this.
Better go wait outside.
I want Larry to leave too.
He stays.
He lives here.
And like the rest of us,
this legend of the dahl twins
has caused this town
a great deal of grief.
I don't know anything
about the twins.
I just know that one of them
is shadowing me.
Follows you?
Rides in the car?
Meets you at school?
Turns on faucets?
Crawls into bed with you?
There are variations
for the folie a deux.
I don't know what that means.
It's French for madness
shared by two.
First discovered in Paris
at the turn of the century
in a set of twin giris.
They both believed in an
alternative versión of reality.
What reality?
You're not the first to have
seen one of the dahl twins.
Jenny mcadams was the first.
She told susie Childs.
Susie told Nancy Fitz.
And before you knew it,
all three claimed
to have seen one of the twins.
But I just found out
they existed an hour ago.
Nobody told me anything.
I did.
We were at silver falls.
How could you?
- He's lying.
What are you doing?
It's one thing to snitch on me.
It's another to set me up.
It wasn't by name,
but I told you
about the candy, the doors,
the appliances.
I thought it'd be okay
because she was
from out of town
and she wouldn't know about it.
After everything
that's happened?
I didn't mean it.
I just wanted her to like me.
So you're saying
I made it up?
No, but you are embracing
the delusión.
Listen,
delusions are the mind's way
of easing the pain of reality.
It's normal.
Except when they're contagious.
Well, can I talk to Jenny
and Nancy and susie,
whatever their names are?
They thought Wyatt
was innocent
and the real killer
was after them.
They believed their delusión,
and in order
to escape the reality,
they committed suicide.
Jumped into silver falls.
Well, is Wyatt innocent?
That sick bastard
bludgeoned Heather
while holly watched.
- Just shut up.
She doesn't need
any more details.
Jordan, you have a choice.
You can embrace reality,
all of it,
the good and the bad,
or die by delusión.
After Nancy's death,
we had an epidemic
on our hands.
Giris were coming
out of the woodwork
with holly dahl sightings.
I spoke to Wyatt, and he agreed
to talk to anyone
who had seen his daughter.
Now it's my professional opinion
that you should do the same.
What will happen?
Well, that's
between you and him.
I will say that I've taken
five giris to see him,
and all five
have stopped seeing holly.
Well, can I talk to them?
The giris?
- No.
No, I couldn't risk it.
It could cause them a relapse.
- Okay.
- Good.
- All right,
but we'd better hurry.
Portland's 30 minutes away.
He's gonna be dead
in a few hours.
Sorry for eating in front
of you, but my time is short.
She's one of Parrish's giris.
I need to talk to her alone.
Like the others.
So...
How's little doc Parrish?
He's an asshole.
So what do you tell
the giris that come here?
Depends.
On what?
What they tell me.
Are you afraid to die?
Holly wasn't afraid to die.
She's a good girl.
She believed in God.
Heather, on the other hand,
she was afraid
that she'd be forgotten.
She had a mean streak,
that one.
Is that why you killed her?
Is it hard to take off?
What's that?
- Your ring?
- No.
Mine is.
Where'd you get that?
Found it.
Why do you wear it
on that finger?
I guess I picked
the wrong one.
Last time I saw my giris,
they were on a school bus.
Holly... holly pointed
to her ring,
Heather to hers,
and me to mine.
We bought these
at a flea market.
Holly liked the idea
that it was one ring
and we each got a part.
Three parts to a whole.
I never thought that'd be
the last time I'd see my kids.
Put that on when you go home.
Watch out for Heather.
She's not the same
since she died.
My giris are trying
to tell you something.
I don't know what it is,
but you better listen.
You're innocent?
Guards.
Wait, what am I supposed
to tell Dr. Parrish?
Tell him what he wants
to hear.
Tell him you don't see
the twins anymore.
He doesn't have to stay.
I'm not gonna kill myself.
He's just doing his job.
And we'll be right down the hall
if you need us.
God, I can't believe
Wyatt killed his own kids.
He was a sick man.
Do you have anything
that might help me sleep?
I hate to ask.
It's just been such a long day...
I have just the thing.
I guess he's dead now.
Here you go.
You'll sleep for hours.
And I'll let you sleep in.
Thank you.
For what?
For taking the time to care.
Good night, honey.
Both: You're next.
I'm going into town.
Do you want to come?
I kind of just want to veg.
It's Robbie.
Are you two friends?
He has a past.
What kind?
The "no means yes" kind.
Um, got it.
I'll be in the living room
if you need me.
- Hello?
- I know you're not crazy.
- How?
- Come with me to silver falls.
I'll show you.
- Show me what?
I can't tell you.
You just have to see it.
Did the other giris like it?
- This is about you, Jordan.
- Right.
Meet me behind your house
in an hour.
But don't tell 'em
I'm picking you up.
- Don't come near me.
- You have to trust me here.
Hey, you okay?
I don't feel right
leaving you here.
I'm fine.
Besides, Kevin's here.
Morning.
Did you want to try?
Sure.
If she's gonna let me.
I'll get you a log here.
All right.
You want to do,
you want to put the blade
where you're gonna strike.
Slide this hand
up a little bit.
Raise the ax.
And go for the kill.
Very good.
Want to do it again?
All right.
Let's try this guy.
Okay?
Nice.
Feels good, right?
Yeah.
I just have to catch my breath.
This is a lot of wood.
O'Leary gives us a better deal
if we buy it in bulk.
Sheriff O'Leary?
Yeah.
Everybody buys their wood
from him around here.
It's a little side business.
He says
it's for Robbie's college fund,
but I think it's for bail.
Like father, like son.
He's a good man.
He just lets Robbie...
- Get away with murder?
Better watch what you say.
I thought
you didn't like them.
It's important to keep the law
on your side around here.
To keep an eye on your enemies.
Right.
You want to do another?
I'm gonna go take a break.
Lie down maybe.
Money.
I really wish
you hadn't opened that drawer.
We promised we weren't
gonna do this anymore.
I didn't have a choice.
We stopped.
Do you really want to argue?
She already wrote the note.
It's just another suicide.
You want a new plaything.
Why do you do that?
Why do you always make this
about me?
Because, Anne, it usually is.
I wonder if she's still out.
Don't change the subject.
I'm not.
Okay.
We dump her in the lake.
Why would we go to the lake?
We've always gone to the falls.
Stick to the falls.
You talk to me
like I'm a kid.
Oh.
I thought you liked it
when I did that.
Holly, enough with the lights.
So you still talk to her?
Do you see her?
- No.
- But you think about her.
You still fantasize about her.
That's why she's still here.
Because you can't let her go.
I let her go a long time ago.
I let them all go.
But you...
I love you.
We don't have to do it
right away.
Not really my type.
But if you want to...
I'm game.
Larry, she doesn't want
to see you.
Look, I just want
to say I'm sorry.
She's not going
to forgive you.
She's very depressed.
We're worried.
You have
to let me talk to her.
Look, I shouldn't have said
those things in the woods, okay?
And I started it.
I realize that.
But I didn't mean to.
Good night, Larry.
You're not being a gentleman.
I could just talk to her
through the door.
Kevin.
Jordan is upset.
Can I just say it
so she can hear?
And then I'll leave.
You guys
were in high school once.
You remember how it is.
Then you'll go
and never come back?
Yeah.
Tell her from there.
Is she in her room?
Mm-hmm.
Jordan!
Jordan, I'm sorry.
I'm really sorry.
So sorry.
You said that.
I didn't mean
to break your trust.
I just didn't want to lose you
like the other giris.
I wanted to save you.
That's all I wanted to say.
Good night, Larry.
Help.
Help!
Jordan, honey,
nobody can hear you.
Help!
Eggs, bacon, cheese,
toilet paper...
- Vodka.
I want vodka.
Vodka.
It's been so long.
Do we need a tarp?
Garbage bags.
Sleeping pills, bleach.
And gloves.
Plastic gloves.
Do you want a blade?
We'll use the mallet.
Anything else?
Sweetie?
Anne?
Maybe you should go.
No playing till I get home.
Or mommy would be very angry.
It's okay.
Jordan, sweetie,
come on.
Come on out.
Please?
Okay, I'm gonna take
these cuffs off.
Come on out.
We have to hurry.
I want to take the cuffs off.
Please.
But we got to hurry.
We got to hurry.
I need you out now.
Please.
Come on.
Trust me.
Listen.
Turn around.
Okay.
I got you, baby.
Okay, you can go.
Go on.
Go.
You're not gonna kill me?
Anne's out of her mind.
Go.
I said go.
It's locked.
It shouldn't be.
- Well, it is.
- Try harder.
I did.
You said
you were gonna let me go.
I just did.
Come here.
Isn't that better?
See, Anne,
she's all about the pain.
Me, I like pleasure.
Come here, come here.
There you go.
You're okay.
Look.
Jordan, hey,
hey, hey, hey, hey.
Shh, shh, shh.
This is our playtime, okay?
All right, I need you
to do something for me.
I want to play a little game.
I want you
to run up the stairs again,
and when you get to the top,
this time I want you
to look back
like you're gonna miss me.
You killed them.
What?
You killed all of them.
No.
Stupid.
It was Anne.
Why are you doing this to me?
Because she loves me.
She loves me the way I am.
Can you run now?
Please just do
what I'm telling you to do.
All right, okay, hold on.
Hold on.
I don't want to hurt you, okay?
I'm gonna tell you this.
When Annie comes back,
it's gonna hurt real bad.
But I can stop that.
I will give you this pill.
And what this is gonna do,
it's gonna make you feel good.
I don't want this to hurt you.
I'm not about pain.
But what I need you to do,
I need you to go up the stairs,
turn around,
and look at me.
Go up the stairs.
Run!
Oh, no, no, no.
Too late.
I gave you a chance.
I say run.
I say run over there.
And you didn't run.
I said let's play a game,
go to the top of the stairs,
turn back
like you're gonna miss me.
Was that so hard?
You didn't want to listen to me.
You know what?
You remind me
so much of your mother.
She didn't want to listen
to me either.
You're so much
like your mother.
- My mom?
- Yes, your mom.
I tried to help her.
But she wouldn't listen.
What am I gonna do?
You're just crazy.
You're all so crazy.
You killed my mom?
Annie killed your mother.
Annie killed your mom!
- You killed my mom?
- Come on.
- You killed my mom!
- Do it! Come on. Come on.
You killed my mom!
You killed...
you killed my mom!
- Do it.
Do it.
What the hell is going on?
Come on.
We have to go.
They want something from us.
Who?
Jordan, who?
Jordan.
Jordan, come on.
We gotta go.
Jordan.
Jordan...
get away from my baby.
They're not gonna let us
leave.
There's some weird shit
going on here.
I told you not to play
until I got back.
You... ooh, this is gonna be
so much fun.
Hey.
Leave her alone.
Welcome to my worid.
Um, new rule.
Ghosts can't hurt you
unless you hurt them.
Um, new rule.
Shut up.