.
Subtitles downloaded from Podnapisi.NET
[girl narrating]
Once upon a time
in a deep, dark forest
lived the Great Witch
of the Woods.
She was a fearsome,
powerful creature
who ate nothing but
the wayward children
foolish enough to wander
into her forest.
To lure them close enough
so that she could eat them,
she constructed
a beautiful house
made out of gingerbread
and candy.
To the Great Witch
of the Woods,
we bring you
a soul to protect.
The terror of
the Great Witch of the Woods
could only be defeated
by descendants of a long
bloodline of witch slayers.
And one day, two slayers
would finally emerge
worthy of the challenge.
They would be twins.
Bring me more children.
I'm still hungry.
[school bell ringing]
Break it up.
[groaning]
Why?
This is your third fight
this semester.
Do you want to get
kicked out of school?
Mom said Dad's furious.
Adam's not our dad.
Not if you keep this up.
[sighs]
Come on. Let's go.
[engine starts]
Are you sure
I can't change your mind?
I can't let him go alone.
He needs me.
Lebkuchen-Haus Academy.
This is one of most prestigious
private schools in the country.
Presidents,
vice presidents, CEOs...
Your father had to
pull a lot of strings
to get you in this school.
You mean Adam had
to pull a lot of strings.
If it was so important to him,
he should've been here.
I'm serious, Jonah.
This is a real
opportunity for you.
Don't blow it.
You take care of yourself.
You, too, Allyson.
Ella, you keep an eye
on your brother, okay?
You know I will.
If he gives you
any trouble--
I will.
All right.
Call anytime.
[engine starts]
Here we are.
Splendid.
So you must be
Jonah and Ella.
I'm Mr. Sebastian,
the headmaster here at
Lebkuchen-Haus Academy.
It is very nice
to meet you both.
Thank you.
Can I help
you with your bags?
That's fine.
I've got it.
How about the grand tour?
Your father spoke
very highly of you two.
I look forward
to challenging you
here in many ways.
Our academic program here
was ranked the highest
in the nation.
Our graduates have gone on to
Harvard, Princeton, and Yale.
In fact, 25% of last year's
graduating class
went on to
an Ivy League school.
Our baseball team
was first in the nation
three years in a row.
We're very proud of that.
I don't play.
You don't play baseball?
Well, that's okay.
I'm sure we'll find something
that interests you here.
It was lucky to have a spot
open up when it did.
While the majority of our
students come from high-income
families like yourself,
we also pride ourselves
with our outreach program,
offering a complete scholarship
to those worthwhile
individuals who need it.
In fact, most of our recipients
are actually orphans.
Jonah?
I was right.
You have found something
to pique your interests.
[laughs]
Let me show you
to your dormitory.
You must be
the roommate of the month.
Sorry?
Seems like they're always
sending the new kids in here.
Apparently I don't
play well with others.
Charles.
Jonah.
Nice to meet you.
So what brings you to Salem?
Fighting.
Relax, dude.
I'm not gonna hit you.
What about you?
Scholarship.
Our "world-famous
outreach program"
benefitting
the best and brightest
of the less fortunate.
They should call it
"drippings for the poor."
Well, I don't think
it gets any easier
just 'cause you're rich.
You know who says stuff
like that?
Who?
Rich people.
[chuckles]
That would be my adoptive
mom and dad, not me.
In that case,
welcome to freedom.
Just remember one thing.
What's that?
Watch yourself.
Around here, you either
eat or you get eaten.
I think I can
take care of myself.
We'll see.
Here we have our newest member
to the Lebkuchen-Haus family.
What's your name?
Ella.
Ella! Apparently Ella comes
to us all the way from 90210.
That's Beverly Hills
to you luddites.
She has a brother named Jonah.
Her dad is the vice president
of a bank,
and her favorite food is pizza.
Actually, it's sushi.
Good luck finding that here.
Kristen.
Welcome.
How did you know all that?
I'm senior editor
of the school paper.
If I didn't know
how to use Google,
I'd be pretty sucky at it.
Let me give you the tour.
Bed, desk, closet.
Right side's mine.
Bathroom's down the hall,
but if you have to go
number two,
I recommend using
the one on the second floor
because this one
gets backed up.
I'll keep it in mind.
Thanks.
What you working on?
Just a kick-ass story
that's gonna blow the lid
off this school.
Sounds juicy.
It's not ready yet.
Oh, sorry.
What's that one?
Stuff.
Really?
That's my favorite book.
Look, I'm under a deadline,
so just make yourself at home
and we'll hang later. Cool?
Oh, yeah, sure.
What Golding is trying to say
is that it is human nature
to reject the morality
and responsibilities
of civilization.
We take part in the system
because we need to survive.
But remove us
from that situation,
remove the need to follow
a certain code or set of ethics,
and we will regress
to our basic human nature.
Savages.
Am I not
interesting you, Jonah?
I was listening.
Then would you be so kind as
to repeat what I just said?
Why, Ms. Thoman?
They're all paying attention.
I'm sure they heard.
Humor me.
The book says
we're all savages,
and we only participate
'cause we have to.
An appropriate statement,
indeed.
God, can you at least pretend
you're paying attention?
[school bell ringing]
Hey!
Hey! You got
a problem, dude?
You want to take
your hands off me, man?
Yeah? You telling me
what to do?
Why don't you just
mind your own business?
Why don't you go
mind your own?
Leave my sister alone, okay?
Oh, look at this guy
right here!
What, are you jealous?
Here we have
a textbook example
of two male members
of the species
engaged in a competition
to establish dominance
over the most eligible
female of the pack.
She's probably in heat.
You keep away from her.
Who?
I saw you looking at her.
Maybe she just wanted to see
what a real man looks like.
Oh, yeah? Yeah,
that's really funny,
isn't it?
Is that why
you're on the ground?
Who is that?
Landon?
Only the school's top jock.
Your brother must have done
something to piss him off.
We don't fight
amongst ourselves.
Oh, yeah?
Apologize.
Sorry.
Make me believe it.
All right, get the hell
out of here. Move!
[school bell ringing]
Your brother
better be careful.
Landon and Megan,
they practically
run this school.
Same crap,
different school.
It's the law of nature,
didn't you know?
One day. That's got
to be a new record.
He was nothing
I couldn't handle.
I thought we both agreed
it was going to be
different this time.
What was I supposed to do,
just walk away?
I just want you to be
careful. Dad said--
Yeah, I wouldn't want
to disappoint the parents,
would I?
He's the only real father
you've ever had.
You've gotta realize he
just wants the best for you.
By shipping me off and
making me someone else problem?
He's trying
to help you, Jonah.
I'm trying to help you.
Yeah, well,
no one asked you to.
I just want you
to be careful.
You know, for once I'd
actually like to be someplace
where I actually fit in.
Look at him.
He's a total jerk,
but everyone respects him,
everyone likes him.
Maybe I'd like to know
what that feels like for once.
Who cares
what anyone thinks...
as long as
we stick together.
That's easy for you to say.
No matter what school
we end up in,
you always end up
getting good grades,
making friends.
It's not that easy for me.
Jonah...
Screw this place.
Hey. I'm Megan.
Ella.
That's your brother, right?
Yeah.
He's little young,
but cute.
Look, we don't want
to cause any trouble.
Yeah. Sorry about
what happened.
My boyfriend can be
a little possessive.
Truce?
Yeah.
[scoffs]
This is so Downton Abbey.
Does Grandma know
you took it?
It's my parents'.
Hear that? Sounds like
someone's got some
mommy-daddy issues.
Stop it!
Guys, we're hurting
her feelings.
Why don't you and Raggedy Andy
go find another school?
Just give it back.
Now beat it.
What is this?
I'll see you after school.
All of you.
Everyone,
mind your own business.
Wait!
Are you hurt?
In my time, they would've
put a frog in your lunchbox
and called it a day.
It's fine.
I can handle it.
I'm Ms. Keegan.
I'm the guidance counselor here
at Lebkuchen-Haus.
Ella.
I know it can be hard
adjusting to a new school,
so please, if you need anything
or you just want to chat,
you can call me anytime.
If you don't mind,
I'd like to be excused
to my room now.
Take all the time you need.
And don't worry.
I'll see to it the girls
get punished appropriately.
Thank you.
You know, we don't get
many twins here.
It's interesting.
[voice whispers]
Gretel...
That's some good reflexes
you got there, bro.
Coach could use
a guy like you.
I'm not interested.
Oh, really? You know,
we're first in the state.
Yeah. Three years in a row.
I'm not the team type.
You know this mysterious
loner thing you got going?
That shit
doesn't work here, man.
Why are you
even talking to me?
I like to win.
And I think our chances would be
better with you on the team.
Look, about before,
I'm sorry about that.
Okay?
No hard feelings?
At least come check it out.
Tomorrow morning
before school.
This is where you practice?
Think of it as a warm-up.
Hmm?
Not interested.
Oh, really?
Your loss, bud.
[knocking]
Come in.
Hey.
Hi.
Is Jonah around?
I haven't seen him.
I'm Ella, his sister.
Ella.
I read in the paper.
You like pizza, right?
Actually, it's sushi.
I heard about what happened
in the courtyard.
Word travels fast, huh?
Well, I heard
Megan and her friends
have to peel potatoes
all night.
I'm Charles.
I'm Jonah's roommate.
Are you leaving?
Things are getting
too crazy around here.
It's not safe.
What are you talking about?
All the dropouts.
How do you think
you and your brother
were able to get in?
I don't understand.
The last one, Barry,
they said they found him
wandering the courtyard
in the middle of the night.
He didn't even remember
his own name.
He just... snapped.
Like something
sucked his soul out
and left him like a shell.
Like a zombie.
Really?
Something funny's
going on.
I'm not gonna wait around
to be next.
Where did you get that?
Oh. It's my roommate's.
You know this book?
Look, if you know
what's good for you,
you'll get you and
your brother as far away
from here as possible.
You hear me?
[door closes]
Hello?
[thud]
Is anybody here?
Hello?
Who's there?
You made it.
This isn't a warm-up, is it?
Uh, no, it's not.
Don't worry.
We don't bite.
What is this place?
This is The Circle.
The Circle? What's that?
Did you know this school
was originally founded
by witches?
Are you serious?
Each year,
the most promising students
are selected
to join The Circle
in order to fulfill
their potential.
Potential?
Greatness.
So it's like some kind
of secret society?
This school has had three
presidents attend here,
two governors,
four senators.
Our brothers and sisters
of The Circle
have gone on to
take their place among
the highest top echelons
of business, science,
medicine.
Because they realized
their potential.
What do you mean?
Like they used magic?
Isn't that cheating?
How'd you do that?
We can all do that.
That's what
The Circle's about.
Once your power's awakened,
you can do anything you want.
Anything?
Look, there are
no tricks here.
No optical illusions
or anything.
Everything you see
is real.
You can do this, too, Jonah.
It's okay.
We all stood
where you are now,
and we said
the same thing.
You can make anybody do that?
Not anybody.
You have to be special.
It's passed down.
My mother's side of the family
was originally from Europe.
I have her blood inside me.
This is crazy.
I'm an orphan.
I barely know my parents.
How do I know if I'm descended
from anything like this?
There's a mark on
the back of your head,
just above the hairline.
It's a circle.
How'd you know that?
Well, I have one, too.
A birthmark?
Think of it
as a birth rite.
Whether you realize it
or not,
you were meant
to come to this school
since the day you were born.
What about fate?
Who do you think
controls fate?
Look, you have
this power, too, Jonah.
Let us help you awaken it.
But remember,
what happens here,
what you see,
what you experience...
You don't tell a living soul.
That is the price.
We must always
work in secret.
So you haven't seen her
since last night.
She said she was gonna be
working on her paper all night.
Well, I realize
your concerns,
but you have to remember
this is a high school.
Kids have fun,
they take off,
do stupid things.
She didn't seem
like the type.
You'd be surprised
what I found going on here.
I've heard there's been
a lot of dropouts.
Is that true?
Lebkuchen-Haus is
one of the top schools
in the country.
Its academic program
is disciplined, strict,
second to none.
From time to time we get
students who simply can't
handle the pressure.
And they just all happen to be
part of the outreach program?
Well, actually,
the outreach program
was my idea.
I was tired of seeing
nothing but privileged
trust-fund babies
with their private tutors
and sense of entitlement.
I thought it'd be good
to bring in some new blood.
But unfortunately
the students in
the outreach program
were less likely to have
the kind of support system
that some of
the more affluent
students can afford.
They become overwhelmed.
We do what we can to help,
but it's inevitable
that some are simply eaten up
by the system, as it were.
Eaten up by the system?
But, Ella, your grades,
your test scores,
you're too smart
to be worrying about
the other students.
Let me worry about them.
It's my job, not yours.
In the meantime, I wouldn't be
surprised if Kristen was back
in the room right now.
Probably sleeping off
whatever it was she did
last night.
Probably.
Remember,
I'm always here for you.
Charles, I really need
to talk to you.
Let's see.
Circles.
I see them everywhere.
I'm gonna follow them
and see where they lead.
They're taking students out
in the middle of the night.
I don't know why
or what happens exactly,
but they're never the same.
Something's happening.
Whoever that is, I think
he's the one behind it.
What the heck
is going on here?
[cell phone ringing]
Don't feel like
talking, huh?
Ella.
What were you doing
in the woods?
What are you
talking about?
I followed Mr. Sebastian there.
I saw you.
Wait. You're stalking
the headmaster?
Something strange is
going on at this school,
and my roommate thinks
he's behind it.
What do you mean,
something strange?
I don't know.
You tell me,
since you were there
with your new friends.
Is that what
this is about?
It's funny what a difference
a day makes.
Landon apologized
for what he did.
What about
me and his girlfriend?
She--
She embarrassed me
in front of the whole
entire school.
I'm sure she's sorry.
Oh, so you're speaking
for her now, huh?
What's your problem?
My problem is that you're making
friends with the wrong people.
Or maybe
you're just jealous.
You can't be serious.
Jealous that
I've made friends
and you haven't?
You know,
for once you're not
the center of attention,
or the good little girl
who has to rescue
her poor brother.
Look...
I'm just watching out for you.
I mean, if there was
something going on,
I just want you
to be careful.
No one asked you to come.
I was trying to help.
Doesn't appear
that I need it now, do I?
[scoffs]
If there was something
going on,
if you did know something,
you would tell me, wouldn't you?
Of course.
Why wouldn't I?
Okay, then.
See you around.
What were you
working on, Kristen?
What is going on here?
[Greta reading]
"In the Old World,
witches and warlocks
lived together in harmony,
using their abilities for good
to help their non-magical
brothers and sisters.
However, when the New World
was discovered,
one of them, a young
and ambitious witch,
saw the opportunity to use her
powers to rule the new land.
She called herself the
Great Witch of the Woods.
Unwilling to sit back
and watch as centuries
of goodwill were undone,
a group of witches
broke off from the rest,
dedicating their lives
and craft to hunt down
those of their kind
who would use
their powers for evil.
They became witch slayers.
Most of the Great Witch's
original followers
known as The Circle
were executed during
the Salem Witch Trials.
However, she soon found
new followers.
And now over 400 years old,
the only way for the Great
Witch of the Woods to survive
is feed on the souls
of the young.
The Circle's job
is to bring her food."
Oh, my.
Wow.
"The Circle." Now,
that's something I haven't
heard about in a long time.
So you have heard about it.
Of course. I was a student here
once myself, you know.
Walk this campus long enough,
and you'll hear all kinds
of stories.
So is it true?
This school was founded
in 1829 by Benjamin Corey,
one of the descendants of
Giles and Martha Corey,
who were both executed
in Salem in 1692
as part of
the Salem Witch Trials.
There are some students
who believe that Benjamin
started a secret society
called The Circle.
A secret society which advanced
his ancestors' teachings
among the privileged few.
What do you think?
The school has never
officially acknowledged
the existence
of secret societies.
But you
as a former student...
Are you familiar
with the stories
of the Brothers Grimm?
Fairy tale?
Are they?
Is it possible
that their stories,
from "Hansel and Gretel"
to "Rumplestiltskin"
were actually written
with an entirely different
purpose in mind?
Such as?
There are some people
who think that the brothers
were involved in these
ancient rituals,
and that their stories
were actually warnings
passed down from
generation to generation.
To warn people
about the Circle.
Do you know what the words
"Lebkuchen-Haus" mean?
No.
Gingerbread house.
Where the Great Witch
would lure her prey.
Look, they're just stories.
But--
Do me a favor.
Don't get involved.
Stay out of it.
But if The Circle is real,
and the Great Witch
of the Woods is real,
then witch slayers
might be real.
No good can come from this.
But Kristen might
have found something
that cost her her life.
It's ancient history.
And if it isn't?
There might be witch slayers
at this school right now.
Look, if I promise
you to look into it,
will you agree
to leave it alone?
Yeah. Thank you.
You're welcome, Ella.
Uh--
Everything
all right, Ella?
Yeah. I'm just gonna
get going. Excuse me.
My parents were witch slayers?
Lebkuchen-Haus.
[line ringing]
Come on, pick up, pick up.
Hey, Jonah, it's Ella.
Please call me back
as soon as you get this.
Okay, bye.
All right,
let's get him.
Come on, Jonah, open up
if you're in there.
Jonah.
[door closes]
[footsteps]
This is what we do.
We help souls cross
into a better place.
What do you mean, cross?
The world's a dark
and nasty place.
It is our responsibility
to help those souls less
fortunate than ourselves
to find the light,
to find paradise.
Once you've helped,
the Great Witch
will reward you and
awaken your powers.
The other day you said after
your powers are awakened,
you can do anything.
You can,
and you will.
What's going on?
Just watch.
Charles.
Jonah, what's going on?
Silence.
Megan?
It's her turn
to be awakened.
Don't let them do this.
Don't worry.
This is a good thing.
Please!
To the Great Witch
of the Woods,
we bring you
a soul to protect.
Come on, Jonah,
do something.
What'd you do to him?
Don't worry.
His body's still here,
but his soul's
in a better place.
What happens now?
She has awakened.
[bell tolling]
We need to talk.
Witch slayers?
Yes, and their ancestors
before them,
all going back
to the original Grimms,
Hansel and Gretel.
The fairy tale.
It's true.
Do you know what
"Lebkuchen-Haus" means?
Gingerbread.
Just like the book.
[scoffs]
I'm going back to bed.
In fact, they were twins.
The only twins before us.
I mean, that's gotta
mean something.
It means two separate eggs
fertilized by two separate
sperm. That's it.
Don't you get it?
Our parents--
Our real parents
went to this school.
You want us to follow
in their footsteps
as witch slayers?
Look, this is their journal.
The last entry
from Greta said,
"I know she's close.
I can feel it.
Tonight we're gonna
stop her."
Stop who?
The Great Witch
of the Woods.
Okay, what happened?
Don't you get it?
They came here to stop her,
and now she's back.
You really believe that?
Well, maybe
that's why we're here,
to finish
what our parents started.
If that's really true,
I say let someone else
handle it.
There's no one else
on the list.
If there were other
witch slayers in this school,
they've kept
their identities a secret.
Of course they have.
[chuckles]
And I suppose that this
is some kind of magical
witch-slaying weapon?
I don't know.
Well, you're wrong.
The witches aren't here
to hurt people.
They're here to help.
Oh, is that
what they told you?
They're here to help souls
cross to the other side,
to a better place.
They've been freed.
Like Charles?
Yeah.
I was there.
I saw what happened last night.
He's in
a better place now.
They're feeding souls to
the Great Witch of the Woods.
Do you know
how crazy that sounds?
Do you know how crazy
any of this sounds?
They told me I was special,
that I have a gift.
You probably have it, too.
We are special.
We have powers.
Come to the next meeting
with me. Let me show you.
Join? We're supposed
to be stopping them.
Maybe you're wrong.
Maybe our birth parents
wanted us to come here
to make the most
of our abilities.
For the first time
in my life, I fit in.
I'm popular.
I'm not about
to jeopardize that.
Look, something bad has
happened to your roommate,
and maybe one of us
is next.
I've heard enough.
"Originating from old
Germanic tradition,
the blade is formed
from a special metal
created through
the process of alchemy.
It is known to be effective in
the hunting of magical beings,
including witches."
What you have to remember
is that it was a sailor's
responsibility
to stay aboard the Patna
until everyone was rescued.
To abandon their post
was viewed as a crime.
So not only was Jim a coward,
he was a criminal
for abandoning the people
who counted on him the most.
Can anyone tell me how it was
that Jim found redemption?
Ella?
Yes, ma'am?
Well, since you're paying
such close attention,
perhaps you could tell the class
how Jim finds redemption
in the story?
Well, I, uh--
No, ma'am.
[school bell rings]
Read chapters 19 through 23
for next time.
What's going on, Ella?
I'm sorry. I just haven't
been able to sleep lately.
Well, I read your transcripts
from your last school.
Absolutely outstanding.
The last couple of days,
you have seemed distracted.
I know.
I'm just not focusing.
Well, you're
a brilliant student,
and I'd hate to see
someone like you lose focus.
It won't happen again.
I promise.
I hope not.
Don't worry about her.
Good job.
Thanks.
Excellent.
Thank you.
Pretty good.
Awesome, as always.
Hey, I don't mean
to intrude.
Are you okay?
You look exhausted.
Yeah. I was just wondering
if you've heard anything
on Kristen.
As a matter of fact,
her mother just called me
this morning.
She did?
Apparently Kristen
was stressed out
about some story
she was writing,
and she needed
some time off.
So why didn't she call?
You look so tired.
Why go don't you go back
to your room and get some rest?
I'd be happy to write
a permission slip
if you need
to skip a class.
That's fine. Thank you.
Anytime.
[heart beating]
No way!
Mind if I come in?
I'm actually doing
some homework.
Thanks.
[door closes]
You seem troubled.
What's wrong?
Nothing. Just getting
some homework done.
You've been practicing.
Maybe a little.
What was it? Tell me.
Just this.
I made it move.
Like... this?
That's incredible.
First thing I ever moved
was my cell phone.
It took me three hours
before I could get it
to move an inch.
I wanted to start small.
Don't worry.
Once you're awakened,
you'll be able to do
so much more.
Sure nothing's
bothering you?
No. Everything's been great.
Good. Glad to hear.
What was it like...
to be awakened?
It's like you've been
sleeping your whole life,
and suddenly instead
of just dreaming,
everything is bright
and vivid,
and you have control
over all of it.
And how'd you find out
that you were, uh, special?
When I was a freshman,
there was a girl on
the lacrosse team with me.
She saw how fast I was.
I was a top scorer,
and I'd only been on
the team a couple of weeks.
So one night, she invited me
to a Circle meeting.
But when you're like us,
part of you always knows.
Just like I'm sure
part of you always felt
that something was missing,
that something wasn't...
Quite right?
So you did feel it.
Yeah.
And now?
It feels, uh, different.
Better?
Like I belong.
That's because you do.
[bell tolling]
Hey, where's Jonah?
Reiko was asked
to keep him company.
Oh, yeah?
This is a secret meeting.
The Great Witch wishes to speak.
We are here, Great One.
Speak to us.
My children, foreseen
a great disturbance, I have.
The witch slayers have once
again returned to these woods.
The twins are scions
of the Grimms,
the brother and sister
of prophecy are they.
Jonah's no witch slayer.
I recruited him myself.
And yet, flow through
his veins their blood does.
Blinded are you
by his potential.
The question is,
which path will the heir choose?
Look, we offer him greatness.
He'd be an idiot
to deny the us.
And you are convinced of this?
Yeah.
Then your responsibility
he shall be.
If they do not join us...
...they must be sacrificed.
Hey, buddy. Heard you had
a good time last night.
Huh? Hey, don't be shy, man.
What happened?
Hmm? Yeah,
I knew it, buddy.
What about you?
What'd you do last night?
Nothing.
Just studying.
Wasn't sure you guys
you actually did that.
Well, we do have to graduate,
you know.
So, um, listen.
We've been talking,
and we think it's your turn.
My turn?
Yeah, you know,
to be awakened.
[hums fanfare]
Really?
Yeah.
Unless you don't think
you're ready.
No-- I mean, of course, yeah.
Yeah? See you tonight then?
Sure.
Good. Pssshh!
Well, well.
I don't want any trouble.
We need to talk.
Later. I'm late for class.
I think we'll talk now.
Inside!
Nice room.
It was so depressing
when Kristen lived here.
All work and no play.
Did you actually
read her writing?
Total buzz kill.
What did you do to her?
I didn't say you could talk.
Now, a little birdie told me
you think
you're a witch slayer.
You killed her, didn't you?
Do you really think
you're strong enough
to take us on all alone?
Who says I'm alone?
Maybe this school is full of
witch slayers just waiting.
We've been watching.
You're the only one.
You're not going
to get away with this.
Yes, we are.
You think just because
your parents were witch slayers
you're so strong?
So powerful? Huh?
I'm gonna give you
a shot to prove it.
Go ahead. Slay me.
Is that the best you can do?
Let me tell you
what's gonna  happen.
First thing,
I'm gonna kill you.
Right here.
Then I'm gonna bring your body
to your brother
and make sure he sees what I did
before we kill him, too.
Then we're gonna burn you both.
Just like they did
to your parents.
They were weak...
just like you.
[groans]
Now, that's the best
I can do.
Ella. Ella, wait.
I know what you're up to.
Stay back.
I don't think you do.
I think it's time
we had a little chat.
We've waited a long time
for your arrival.
Once there were dozens.
Now I'm the only one left.
If The Circle I knew
I was a witch slayer,
they would've
killed me years ago.
How long has the Great Witch
been out there?
Since before
the school was built.
Since before our ancestors
landed in Plymouth.
And she can
really be stopped?
Not alone.
According to the book,
only twin descendants
of the family Grimm
possesses the ability.
Well, that's not gonna happen.
Why is that?
My brother's one of them.
Don't worry.
He can fraternize with them.
He can attend their rituals,
but in his heart,
he will never
truly be one of them.
So they may try to hurt him.
Yeah, which is why
I need to train you,
so we can protect him.
So what, is there like
books or videos or maybe--
We don't have time for books.
En garde.
Ah, you truly are
your mother's daughter.
How about a warning next time?
I did.
That was a crappy warning.
What, do you think
they're gonna warn you?
They're never gonna warn you!
I was just saying maybe
you can be a little nicer
about it, that's all.
Okay. Pretty please
with sugar on top.
En garde.
Okay.
Let's work on
your reflexes.
So, Mr. Sebastian
is a witch slayer.
Looks like it.
I never liked him.
You know what to do.
Yes, ma'am.
The important thing is
you must be ready
when the time comes.
How'd my parents die?
After graduation,
your mom was pregnant,
so they moved away,
and that's when they had
you and your brother.
But word had gotten out that
the Witch was growing stronger.
After years of lying dormant,
she was building an army,
getting ready to strike.
So they came back.
So yes, they came back,
but they were betrayed.
An old classmate of theirs,
she lured them into the woods,
she said she wanted
to be a slayer,
that she needed to know
how to fight witches.
Who was it?
Her name was Cassandra Keegan.
Ms. Keegan,
the guidance counselor?
The powers of evil
does not play by the rules.
If you truly want
to be safe-- truly--
you can trust no one.
And my brother?
He said he could never
be one of them.
I never said
you could trust him.
Run! Run!
Going somewhere?
This is for Megan.
[stab]
Bring forth the sacrifice.
Ella.
Jonah! Jonah, please.
Silence!
Hey, what's going on?
She needs our help
to cross over, Jonah.
Don't you want to help her?
Yeah, but--
Hey, Jonah.
What's the problem, man?
I thought you wanted
to be awakened.
Her soul is going
to a better place.
A happier place.
You need to do this.
Do it, Jonah.
Do it.
To the Great Witch
of the Woods,
we bring you a soul
to protect!
[thunderclap]
Kill her, Jonah!
I don't want to fight you.
You're one of us.
Now kill her!
Mr. Sebastian
has taught you well,
but it was not enough
to save him,
and it will not
be enough to save you.
Jonah, we're supposed
to be on the same side.
Don't listen to her!
The Circle
doesn't help anyone.
You're not helping anyone
cross over.
You're sacrificing them
to the Witch of the Woods.
You're lying!
Now finish her!
Jonah... please.
No. I can't do it.
Very well. Kill them both.
Are you ready?
You have no idea
what you've given up.
I think I'll
take that chance.
I can't hit a girl.
But I can.
I knew it was a mistake
bringing you into this.
You heard what she said.
The Circle
isn't about doing good.
You had so much potential,
and you threw it away.
Landon, we can use our potential
to do some real good.
Oh, I plan on it.
Pity.
Leave my brother alone.
Oh, you're in
way over your head.
No. You are.
That's impossible!
No one can do that.
A witch slayer can.
Jonah, you okay?
Yeah. She's getting away.
Come on.
I'm really sorry that
I didn't listen to you.
I don't know about you,
but I think it's time she pays
for what she did to the school.
And our parents.
Boo! The Great Witch
has been expecting you.
There she is.
I'm everywhere.
Don't you get it?
She's the Great Witch.
It's been her all along.
Clever boy.
A shame things didn't
work out between us.
You would've made
a formidable ally.
For centuries I've lived here,
preying on the weak.
Finally I decided
why not expand my resources?
So you had Benjamin Corey
build the school.
And now my disciples
are everywhere.
One day the pitiful people
of this world
will wake up and realize
who's calling the shots.
All I ask in return is
a little nourishment.
Hmm... I can't decide
which of you to eat first.
I've always been partial
to boys, but Ella looks
particularly delicious.
Your parents were tasty, too.
I can't wait to sink
my teeth into you.
I've got something
to sink into you.
[screaming]
Our parents.
Hey, how'd we get here?
Hey, who are you guys?
Think they'll ever remember?
I hope not.
All packed?
Almost done.
You sure about this?
Well, like
the Great Witch said,
this school
gives a lot of rise
to some powerful witches.
Someone's gotta slay 'em.
There's a lot of pages
left to fill.
I wonder what Adam and Allyson
would say about this.
I know, but Mom and Dad
would've wanted it.
Ah.
Oh.
What's this?
I don't know.
Looks like someone
left you a note.
It's from Mr. Sebastian.
Says, "Ella, hopefully
everything has gone well..."
[Mr. Sebastian]
"...and according to plan.
Inside this envelope,
you will find something
your parents left behind,
something I'm sure
they would've wanted
you and Jonah to have.
Hopefully we will meet again
in another life.
Fondly, Mr. Sebastian."
What is it?
It's our original
birth certificate.
No way!
Yeah.
Look! Our real names.
You know what?
What are you doing?
Signing our real names.
Well, Gretel?
Yes, Hansel?
Let's slay some witches.
I'm comin' for you now
Like a hurricane,
I'm comin' after you
You
I'm comin' for you now
Like an avalanche,
I'm comin' after you
You
I feel her touch
rising inside of me
It's feeling like her
Her, her
Can you hear the melody
ringing in the ears like her
Her
Run away
Run, run, run away
I'm comin' for you,
comin' for you
Run, run, run away
I'm comin' for you,
comin' for you
You can't hide
I'm comin' for you
You
I'm comin' you now
Like a predator,
I'm comin' after you
You
I feel her touch
rising inside of me
It's feeling like her
Her
Can you hear the melody
ringing in the ears like her
Run away, run, run, run away
I'm comin' for you,
comin' for you
Run, run, run away
I'm comin' for you,
comin' for you
You can't hide
I'm comin' for you
You
I'm comin' ya
I'm comin' for you
Can you hear the sound
Hey
Now it won't be long
Hold your breath
I'm coming after you
Run away
Run, run, run away
I'm comin' for you,
comin' for you
Run, run, run away
I'm comin' for you,
comin' for you
You can't hide
I'm comin' for you
Run, run, run away
I'm comin' for you,
comin' for you
You can't hide
I'm comin' for you
You
Closed-captions by CAPTION FILES
www.captionfiles.com