Mr. Merdle, having got him away
from that little dancer once,
I now find him
in her clutches again.
I need you to find him a post,
an occupation.
I believe I need to hold a dinner.
I find you perfect, my love.
I wouldn't change
a single thing about you.
I am happy
but marriage is so... different.
I never thought about
what it would really be like.
This is most irregular.
Upon my soul! you mustn't just barge
in saying you want to know, you know!
But I do want to know.
How's a man to get anything done
is this benighted country?
In the old days...
We do not refer to the old days. Amy,
I demand that you conduct yourself
in a manner satisfactory
to myself and Mrs. General.
£1,000, you know what I have.
The man knows nothing!
He is not to be seen here again,
Flintwinch, or heard of again.
CHURCH BELLS RING
GONDOLIER YELLS IN DISTANCE
Amy?
Yes?
Has it ever struck you that
Papa and Mrs. General
are becoming very fond
of each other's company?
What do you mean, Fanny?
I mean that Mrs. General
has designs upon Papa
and he is not averse
to being designed upon!
How should you like Mrs. General
for a Mama, Amy?
I...
I don't think I should
like it very much.
I shouldn't like it at all.
I couldn't bear it!
I wouldn't bear it.
I'd marry Sparkler first.
Oh, Fanny. You said
you'd never marry Mr. Sparkler!
Circumstances alter cases.
Consider! you may be wrong
about Father and Mrs. General.
I may be...
but I am not.
'Dear Mr. Clennam,
we are still in Venice
'and my dear father and Fanny have
adapted themselves to our new fortune
'with wonderful ease.
'I, however,
have not been able to do so.
'Mrs. General is always with us
and takes great pains to teach me,
'but I find my mind wandering to
my old cares.
'Then I remember
that there are no such cares left
'and I feel strangely lost.
'I have found great solace in Mrs.
Gowan's company,
'during these recent times,
'and I visit her almost every day
in her confinement.'
DISTRESSED PANTING
PET SCREAMS
The cloth, please.
SCREAMING CONTINUES
PET SCREAMS
We have no idea what women
go through at these times, Gowan.
So I understand, yes.
Yes, I know that you feel as I do.
We wish we could bear the pain
for them but we can't.
Absolutely, absolutely...
Fatherhood! What a potent mixture
of joy and anxiety it is.
Oh, Pet...
You'll discover that for yourself and
it'll be the making of you as a man.
(Pompous buffoon!)
Sorry?
BABY CRIES
A little boy! And both well!
'Mrs. Gowan has had a little boy to
be called Henry, after his father.
'He is a beautiful child,
as you would expect.
'Mrs. Gowan likes me to be near her
'and help her look after little
Henry, which gives me great pleasure.
'So your Little Dorrit
is a great deal happier now
'and content to still be in Italy
for the time being.'
Amy!
I have a bone to pick with you.
Oh? Could it wait till this evening,
Fanny? I was just going out.
- Where, may I ask?
- To meet Mrs. Gowan.
That is just what I wanted
to mention to you.
Now, you may not realise it, dear,
but you're letting us all down again.
You've turned yourself into
a nursemaid for that Gowan family
and it's reflecting upon us.
You'll have everybody thinking
you're a common servant!
- Would it be so bad if they did?
- Yes, it would.
I am determined Mrs. Merdle shouldn't
have anything to sneer about.
But Mrs. Gowan likes to have me
near her.
I'm not saying
you should never go to them,
just don't let them take advantage
of you. We're ladies of leisure now.
I don't think I shall ever learn
to be a lady of leisure, Fanny.
Now that is not the spirit, is it?!
Of course it is hard.
It's downright boring sometimes
but one just has to work at it.
Do you not think
I sometimes long to dance
and do my high kicks
in the grand people's faces?
Do you really, Fanny?
Do I ever?!
One, two, three, kick!
Five, six, seven, kick!
Right in their silly
astonished faces!
But it wouldn't do, so I don't do it.
So, you see,
we all have to make sacrifices.
Even Sparkler's making sacrifices.
I'm teaching him not to say
I'm a damn fine girl
with no biggod nonsense about me.
- And he's getting a job.
- What? Here, in Italy?
No, in England.
Mr. Merdle's going to get him one.
Mr. Merdle, he can do anything.
'The first Lord of the Treasury.'
The Lord Chancellor.
The Bishop of Southwark.
Mr. Eustace Barnacle
of the Circumlocution Office.
Mr. Septimus Barnacle
Mr. Tite Barnacle, Principle
of the Circumlocution Office.
Lord Decimus Barnacle, First Lord
Mr. Ferdinand Barnacle...
A lot of Barnacles tonight.
They all come out for Merdle.
I understand this evening is about
a little bit of jobbery.
Mrs. Merdle's son by her previous
marriage, name of Sparkler.
- Do you know the boy?
- Nice young fellow.
Absolutely nothing between the ears
at all. A total blank.
They're fixing him up with something
at the Circumlocution Office.
Well,
I suppose he'll do no harm there.
No good either. Oh, come on...
MEN LAUGH, CUTLERY CLATTERS
And so we pass, gentlemen,
through the various changes of life,
from Eton pears
to Parliamentary pairs!
Excellent, sir,
never heard you on such good form!
We are all sorry
not to have the pleasure
of Mrs. Merdle's company
this evening.
She is in Italy, sir.
Ah, Mrs. Merdle's son has been
spoken of... Mr. Sprinkler?
Mr. Sparkler, sir.
Sparkler, of course. He was mentioned
in the context of a possible opening?
If you please, sir.
Is he here this evening?
In Italy, with Mrs. Merdle.
Ah, well...
it's not indispensable that he
should actually be on the spot.
The magic name of Merdle
will suffice.
Quite so.
I think we may consider it settled.
Thank you, sir.
STRINGED INSTRUMENTS PLAY
MUSIC STOPS
Bravo!
Yes! Dear Edmund is to be one of the
Lords of the Circumlocution Office.
I expect you may have seen
the notice in the Times.
What a pity it will take him
away from us all!
Congratulations, old fellow!
Feet under the table now, eh?
Well done!
Well, point of fact, didn't actually
do anything. Thing just happened.
It's a total mystery to me.
It will keep him in town a deal
and he prefers the country,
don't you, Edmund?
Well, I am fond of ratting
with a couple of good terriers.
Not much ratting in Venice.
Lot of rats though. Odd that.
- Edmund.
- Yes?
- Be quiet.
- Right.
Still, though the Circumlocution
may not be ideally suited
to Edmund's talents, it is a position
and not a disagreeable one.
Quite, and without wishing to
disparage Mr. Sparkler's abilities,
I think we must see the appointment
as a compliment to Mr. Merdle -
the man of the age!
Thank you, Mr. Dorrit,
that may well be so.
POLITE CHATTER
- How we do fret about our children.
- How indeed.
I wish you joy, my dear old fellow!
There will be nothing to do
and you will do it charmingly!
There'll be a handsome salary to
draw and you'll draw it charmingly!
Eh? I'm delighted to see my dear
old donkey so admirably stabled!
Well, you know, I...
I dare say you wouldn't say no to
such a stable yourself, Mr. Gowan.
Indeed, no, but my relations seem
to have sadly overlooked my talents.
Leaving you to sponge off
the in-laws you affect to despise.
I say!
You know, Fanny, draw it mild!
I'm not sure Miss Dorrit knows how
to draw it mild but I am rebuked.
I don't suppose
you'll change your ways, though.
No, Miss Dorrit,
I don't suppose I will.
I suppose I should congratulate you,
Mr. Sparkler.
I've spent a good deal of time
at the Circumlocution Office
and I never heard one word of sense
in all that time.
They seemed to me
the very epitome of how not to do it!
Well, you know,
I've not got in there yet.
It's not as if I'm up
to the mark yet.
You'll have to forgive me but all
I've seen anyone do at that place
is push pieces of paper around
and give each other jobs for life
and let the country go to
rack and ruin in the mean time.
Barnacles, yes, a well-named family!
Steady, Mr. Meagles.
I must insist, sir, that you
do not speak disrespectfully
of a very distinguished family.
and your good friend, Mr. Clennam,
will say the same.
He spent day after day at that place,
trying to get some sense out of them
about your tangled affairs
and precious little good it did him,
or you, sir!
'Private gentlemen.
Well put. You're very good, sir.'
'We should have made each others
acquaintance before, should we not?'
Aitchoo!
KEYS JANGLE
DOOR LOCKS
Poor Pa, he does suffer so.
I felt sorry for
Mr. and Mrs. Meagles too.
The Meagleses are all very well.
They're happy, they know their place
and they don't care tuppence
for what the world thinks of them.
We, on the other hand,
labour under peculiar disadvantages.
Don't tell me you don't know
what I'm talking about.
I'm sure I shall,
after a few more words.
We're not quite the thing, are we?
Some of us look the thing.
Pa is very gentlemanly
but he's terrified of people
knowing what he once was.
And Uncle, though a dear creature,
is altogether unpresentable.
Edward is frightfully expensive
and dissipated.
He isn't even any good at it -
the, um... dissipation, I mean.
And then there's you and me.
And we don't have a mother
but we do have a Mrs. General,
who goes about like a cat in gloves
and she will catch a mouse
and the mouse she'll catch is Papa.
- Fanny!
I refuse to be step-mothered
by Mrs. General.
The sooner I become Mrs. Sparkler
the better.
He has a good position now
and I don't think a clever husband
should suit me.
I shouldn't be able
to defer to him enough.
But, Fanny, if you loved someone,
that feeling would change.
I know it would!
Oh! You know that, do you?
Oh, bless me!
How much some people know
about some subjects!
Well, they say everybody has
a subject and we've hit upon yours!
Don't tease me, Fanny.
It's only in fun, little one.
Fanny...
you do deserve someone you love.
Well, maybe I do,
but there he is.
And as Mrs. Sparkler, I shall be able
to torment his mother -
that piece of insolence -
for the rest of her life.
That little dancer
she gave her old bangle to,
she will dance through her life.
Mow there is a face I'd like
to land a good high kick on!
Fanny, you wouldn't marry Mr. Sparkler
just to annoy Mrs. Merdle!
Now don't look so anxious.
We have talked it over comfortably
and now it's time for bed.
Oh, you are the best
and dearest little mouse, Amy.
Good night.
I refuse to know you, sir.
I refuse to know you.
Father?
- Not in bed yet?
- No, no, I, er...
Let me help you to bed, Father.
Help me?
I am perfectly capable.
I know, Father.
But I should like to help you...
as I used to.
You should say Papa, you know.
I know. I keep forgetting.
Miss Amy Dorrit,
what are we to do with you?
I don't know, Papa.
I'm a disgrace, aren't I?
I fear you are.
But you're a good girl, Amy,
for all that.
You're a good girl.
Ah, Mr. Blandois!
Very prompt. Very punctual.
Always, for you,
my dear little Flintwinch.
Let's go in here and have
a few glasses and talk it over.
They don't know me here.
Well, let's put that right,
shall we?
DOG BARKS
Have you seen this, Mr. Clennam?
I know that man!
Blan-DOYS.
Blandois, a Frenchman.
Last seen at Clennam & Co.
Surely they don't suspect
my mother of foul play, do they?
They wouldn't issue a handbill
like this if they didn't.
My God.
On your way!
How did it seem to you, Mr. Clennam,
when you saw this man
at your mother's house?
She said she had business with him.
Any idea what this business was?
My mother has never in her life
taken me into her confidence.
Try her again, Mr. Clennam.
She's in trouble now.
She'll have to swallow her pride
and accept help.
Well, we'll see.
Signor! Signor!
Signor! This is him! The bad man!
You know him? You know Blandois?
No, no, no, no. No Blandois!
He is call Rigaud
and he is a killer!
Good day, Constable.
Flintwinch, what's going on here?
What did the Constable want to know?
No need to worry, Arthur.
We're right as rain here, we are.
Here he is.
How are you, Mother?
I am exactly as I was the last time
you called here, Arthur.
I'm relieved to hear it, after
your visit from that Frenchman.
You were right to suspect him.
He's not as he presented himself.
- And now he has disappeared?
- Yes.
That is not your concern. You severed
all connections with the firm.
I am still your son, Mother.
I am concerned about you.
There is no need to be.
Monsieur Blandois,
if that is indeed his real name,
came to Clennam and Company
with a business proposition
which, after consideration,
we declined.
is what I told the constable.
I have been told that this man
is a notorious criminal.
I'm glad I have nothing
to do with him.
Mother, this is a serious matter.
The authorities believe this man has
been murdered.
Do they indeed?
And I am suspected, am I?
Then let them produce the body
confined to this chair,
could have committed the crime.
Now, if you'll excuse me,
I'm rather tired.
Yes, of course.
Mother... I worry about you,
trapped up here in this room.
I've hardly seen you
since I got back from China.
I'd like to call on you more often,
make sure that you're well.
That won't be necessary.
I may be paralysed...
but I'm not a weakling,
like your father was.
Goodbye, Arthur.
Shut the doors.
CHURCH BELLS RING
- Oh!
- Oh, indeed!
I suppose you know what this means,
little sister?
Well, you mean you...?
She's as beautiful as she's doted on
and there's no nonsense about her.
It's all arranged.
- No need to explain, Edmund.
- No, my love.
In short, we're engaged.
We just tell Papa and there's
nothing more to say about it.
My dear Fanny,
I should like to say a word to Amy.
Must you?
I think I must, my love!
Well, go on then.
My dear Amy,
if ever there was a girl -
next to your highly-endowed
and beautiful sister -
who had no nonsense about her,
not one atom of...
Edmund!
I know it's a habit of mine,
for which I apologise,
but she really hasn't got
the least little bit...
What I wished to declare is that,
though I may not be up to the mark
on some subjects,
on the subject of Amy
I am up to the mark.
And, when we are at home in London,
a knife and, er...
fork and an apartment
will always be at Amy's disposal.
There...
So...
Ah. Yes.
There, there.
It'll be all right. I promise.
My dear Fanny, I am delighted.
On the arm of Mr. Sparkler,
you will move in circles
at the very pinnacle of society.
Your noble ambition
finds harmonious echoes in my heart.
You are a child brimful of duty
and good principle.
Thank you, Papa.
Mark and learn, Amy.
Mark and learn.
'Dear Mr. Clennam,
'I received some news last night,
which allows me to hope
'that I may soon be leaving Italy
and returning to London.
'My sister Fanny and Edmund Sparkler
are to be married.
'Mr. Sparkler has secured a position
at the Circumlocution Office and,
'as soon as they are married,
'he and Fanny will travel to England
to start their new life.
'It is my dearest wish
to travel with them
'but I think I must wait
so that I may travel with my father.'
In nominee Patris et Filii
et Spiritus Sancti. Amen.
Amy,
now that your sister is married,
she and her husband
will travel to London
to take up residence
in the Merdle household.
I myself intend to travel with them.
I've some affairs to settle in
London - investments and so forth.
Indeed, I hope to consult
with Mr. Merdle about them.
So we shall all go back together?
No. Edward is going to do some
exploring, I believe,
and you and your uncle Frederick
will stay here.
You will, of course, be under the
excellent supervision of Mrs. General.
Couldn't I travel with you and look
after you on the journey to London?
Whatever makes you think
I need looking after?
HE CHUCKLES
No, no, no.
Much better that you stay here.
It is to be hoped, Amy, that one
day you too will find a husband
but Mrs. General and I agree
that you have some way to go yet
before that may be possible.
To be frank, my dear,
you're not yet quite presentable...
in society.
Mrs. General has a little more...
a little more forming to do,
in your case.
Isn't that so, Mrs. General?
I fear it is, Mr. Dorrit.
I've been approached
by a factory in St. Petersburg.
I hope you've said yes!
We ought to make our capital work for
us. I want to put it into Merdle.
I should be grateful if you could
give me the benefit of your advice
as to the prudent investment
of my capital.
- Why the devil are you here?!
- I brought you cigars.
Damn your cigars! I don't smoke!