DAMN, FROGGY.
YOU FUCKING
RETARDED OR WHAT?
HE GRABBED IT.
- "HE GRABBED IT."
- YOU SHOT HIM IN THE FUCKING FACE.
- SO?
LOOK AT
HIS HAND.
YEAH, YOU SHOT
HIS HAND TOO.
GRABBED IT
THOUGH.
THIS IS GONNA MAKE WAVES
FOR US, FROGGY.
YOU KNOW
WHO HE WORKS FOR?
ALWAYS ON EVERYBODY ELSE.
ALL RIGHT.
WE GOTTA BOUNCE.
JEEZ, IT'S ALL BLOODY.
OH. HEY. I WANT YOU TO
STASH THAT SHIT, GO HOME.
DON'T TALK TO ANYONE ELSE.
OKAY, FROGGY?
YOU JUST GONNA
LEAVE HIM HERE?
UNLESS YOU HAVE A MAGIC BAG
TO STUFF HIM IN, YEAH.
IT'S JUST ANOTHER
DEAD HUSTLER, HOMEY.
AND WHAT ABOUT WHITEY?
WHEN IT COMES
TO HER BUSINESS,
MY MAMA DON'T LIKE
NO PUBLICITY.
AND WHAT YOU DID
WAS A BIG NO-NO, ESE.
WHO HAS HER MONEY, PUTO?
IS IT LOYALTY?
QUE CUTE.
BROTHERHOOD
AND ALL THAT.
THAT LOYALTY'S A BITCH.
TELL ME WHO
YOUR SIDEKICK IS
AND NO MORE PAIN,
CARNALITO.
OH PLEASE
PLEASE PLEASE.
ISAIAH, ISAIAH,
ISAIAH.
HUH?
SAY IT AGAIN.
DONATO.
WHAT?
ISAIAH DONATO.
OKAY, SHH.
WHAT AM I GONNA DO
WITH YOU, MR. FROGGY?
YOU CAN'T KEEP A SECRET.
AND MAMA DON'T LIKE
NO RATAS.
FUCKING RODENTS...
THEY MULTIPLY.
WE CAN'T HAVE THAT.
NO!
YOU GONNA KILL 'EM
TONIGHT, LUPE.
- YOU THINK?
- FO' SHO'.
YOU GOTTA RELAX THOUGH,
FOR REAL.
RELAXING AIN'T GONNA
GET THIS PLACE PAID.
HAVE SOME FUN
FOR YOURSELF, LUPE.
I SWEAR, YOU WORK
TOO MOTHERFUCKING MUCH.
CHILL.
WATCH AND DREAM.
WELL, I'M DOING JUST FINE.
JUST DON'T GET
YOUR FINE ASS
KNOCKED UP BY YOUR
ASPIRING HUSTLER.
WHAT THE FUCK, MAN?
WHY YOU GOTTA BE
LIKE THAT, HUH?
FUCK.
I JUST WANT
WHAT'S BEST FOR YOU.
¿BESITOS?
C'MERE.
BY THE WAY,
THAT'S MY SHIT.
WHATEVER.
CALL ME LATERS, OKAY?
OKAY, WHATEVER.
- HEY, LUPE.
- KILL ANYONE LATELY?
YOU HURT MY SISTER,
I'LL HURT YOU BACK.
I'M NOT GONNA HURT
ALICIA, LUPE.
EVER.
I'M JUST SAYING.
YOU'VE BEEN WARNED.
HAVE FUN AT YOUR GIG
TONIGHT...
MOTHER HEN.
THAT FATE CREEPS,
ISAIAH-
EITHER THE GRAVEYARD
OR THE PEN.
- BABE.
HEY.
DON'T WORRY
ABOUT HER, OKAY?
SHE'S JUST TRYING
TO BE MY MOM.
ISAIAH.
I'M RIGHT HERE, BABY.
I JUST CAN'T
SHAKE IT, BABE.
YOU CAN'T SHAKE WHAT?
ISAIAH,
WHAT'S THE MATTER?
WITH THE RIGHT
AMOUNT OF MONEY,
WE CAN DO ANYTHING.
THAT'S MONEY.
AH, BROTHERHOOD.
COMPA.
BEEN A GRIP.
OYE, I JUST WANTED
TO THANK YOU
FOR KEEPING ME
IN YOUR PRAYERS...
AT LEAST.
YEAH.
YEAH, I JUST
CAME BY TO, UH-
TO GIVE MY RESPECTS
TO YOUR MOM.
ORALE.
OH, ADAN.
- AY, MIJITO.
- HI, MADRINA.
HI.
- I HAVE SOMETHING FOR YOU.
AY, QUE BONITO.
WHEN DO YOU HAVE TIME?
WELL, I'M BACK,
SO ANY TIME.
OH, VEN, MIJITO. VEN.
I'LL GET YOU A DRINK.
NO, ACTUALLY- NO, I HAVE SOME
PEOPLE TO-  -  iESTRELLA!
WHAT THE FUCK?!
WHAT?
- WHAT'S THAT?
- WHAT THE FUCK?!
- DON'T STOP.
PLEASE, CONTINUE.
WHAT THE FUCK
ARE YOU DOING HERE?
I JUST CAME TO KICK BACK...
PARTY WITH YOU.
QUERIA PARTY.
THIS AIN'T THE TIME
OR PLACE, BRO.
GET THE FUCK
OUTTA HERE!
I ALWAYS SEE YOU TWO.
SEEN YOU WALKING HAND IN HAND
DOWN BY THE OLD BRIDGE.
AND I OFTEN WONDER WHAT
THAT WOULD BE LIKE, ESE.
TO HAVE ME A FIRME
LITTLE HONEY BABY...
JUST LIKE THAT.
YOU BEEN DANCING WITH THE
DEVIL AGAIN, HAVEN'T YOU?
RENDER UNTO DONA
THAT WHICH BELONGS TO DONA
AND UNTO GOD
THAT WHICH BELONGS TO GOD.
- WHITEY, NOT HERE.
- DO NOT CALL ME THAT.
ONLY MI PLEBE CALL ME THAT.
ANDA, BRO.
I'M ASKING YOU, CARNAL.
- I GOTTA LIVE, TOO, BRO.
- SHH SHH.
- I GOTTA EAT.
- SHH SHH SHH.
YOU KNOW,
WHEN I WAS LOCKED UP,
MY JEFITA,
SHE WAS THE ONLY PERSON WHO
TOOK THE TIME TO COME AND VISIT.
SHE HAD MY BACK WHEN
NO ONE ELSE GAVE A RAT'S ASS.
AND THESE LITTLE THINGS,
THEY'RE TATTOOED ON MI CORAZON.
THAT'S WHY I TAKE IT
VERY PERSONAL
WHEN A LITTLE PUNETA
SUCH AS YOURSELF
DECIDES TO BURN MI JEFITA.
NOW YOU GOTTA DEAL
WITH THE FUCKING DEVIL.
YOU KNOW,
SOMETIMES IN LIFE...
WE SEE THINGS AND WE-
WE WONDER,
"AM I REALLY SEEING
WHAT I'M SEEING?
IS IT AN ILLUSION?
A VISION?
OR AM I JUST MAKING IT UP
IN MY MIND?"
LOOK AT ME WHEN
I'M TALKING TO YOU, CHAVALO.
IT'S TIME.
THIS IS WHAT
I WANNA SEE.
IS THIS HOW IT IS?
YOU WANNA GET LOCO?
WELL, LET'S ALL GET LOCO.
TOMA.
YOU FIRST.
OOPS.
ITOMALO!
ELECTRIFIED, TERRIFIED,
LOOK IN MY EYES.
- MORTIFIED CRIES
SATURATE THE NIGHT SKY.
SHRIEK AFTER SHRIEK
SYMBOLIZE MY DEMISE.
TRUDGING THE STREETS,
MY FACE A DISGUISE.
UNDER THE BRIDGE
IS WHERE I RESIDE,
SHOOTING THE FIX
JUST TO SURVIVE.
AWAITING TO EXIT
THIS WORLD I DESPISE.
SEARCHING FOR TRUTH
BENEATH THE SURFACE LIES.
HELLACIOUS FIXATIONS.
DARKNESS, DAMNATION.
IN LIFE I DESCEND
AND IN DEATH I ARISE!
MY MIND HAS BEEN RUNNING
WITH A- A MILLION
THOUGHTS TODAY.
BUT I AM BLESSED.
THE BOND BETWEEN
LIFELONG FRIENDS
IS NOTHING
LESS THAN BEAUTIFUL.
- RESPETO.
- SALUD.
MIJITA, WHAT-
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
YOU SENT HIM?
YOU NEED TO LEAVE.
I LOVED HIM.
OKAY?
I LOVED HIM
- AND YOU TOOK HIM FROM ME!
FUCKING BITCH!
DON'T FUCKING TOUCH ME!
YOU TOOK HIM FROM ME,
YOU SICK WICKED BITCH!
YOU DARE...
YOU TOOK THE ONLY PERSON
THAT EVER CARED ABOUT ME.
- GET HER OUT OF MY SIGHT.
- FUCKING MURDERER!
YOU BETTER FUCKING KEEP
YOUR DOG ON A LEASH,
- YOU FUCKING-
LET ME TELL YOU SOMETHING,
MIJITA, HUH?
I REMEMBER YOU!
DO WHAT YOU'RE
GONNA DO, BITCH!
DO WHAT YOU'RE GOING TO DO.
I'M RIGHT FUCKING HERE, CABRONA!
DO WHAT YOU'RE
GONNA DO, PENDEJA!
DO WHAT YOU'RE GONNA DO! I'M
RIGHT FUCKING HERE,  CABRONA.
ALICIA.
I THOUGHT YOU WERE STAYING
AT ISAIAH'S TONIGHT.
WHAT'S THE MATTER?
HEY, YOU WANNA
TALK TO ME?
NO, I'M GOOD.
- WHAT HAPPENED?
NOTHING.
OKAY? I'M ALL RIGHT. I GOT IT.
IT'S HIM, ISN'T IT?
THIS IS BULLSHIT, ALICIA.
WHEN ARE YOU GONNA GET YOUR
SITUATION UNDER CONTROL?
DON'T DO THAT.
YOU DON'T KNOW ME!
I CAN'T EVEN TALK TO YOU
'CAUSE ALL YOU DO IS JUDGE!
YOU SAY, "TALK TO ME"?
YOU DON'T EVEN
FUCKING LISTEN.
ALL YOU GIVE A FUCK ABOUT
IS YOU, THAT'S IT.
WHO'S ALWAYS BEEN HERE
FOR YOU?
I'VE BEEN DOING THIS SHIT
ALONE FOR FIVE FUCKING YEARS!
AND ALL I WANT IS FOR YOU TO GET
YOUR HEAD OUT OF YOUR ASS AND SNAP.
YOU DON'T KNOW ME.
YOU JUST DON'T KNOW ME.
AND YOU PROBABLY
NEVER WILL.
DON'T FUCKING WALK AWAY FROM
ME. I'M TALKING TO YOU HERE.
DON'T TOUCH ME.
- LEAVE ME ALONE.
- ALICIA!
MOVE, LUPE!
RIGHT, IF YOU LEAVE NOW...
DON'T EVEN THINK
ABOUT COMING BACK.
¿OISTE?
HOW'S THE FOOD?
- REALLY GOOD, MAMA.
- OH.
GRACIAS
POR LA COMIDA.
ANYTHING FOR YOU,
MIJITO.
HOW DID
EVERYTHING GO?
MUY SUAVE.
¿DE VERAS? MUY SUAVE.
ANYTHING YOU, UM,
WANNA TELL ME?
NO.
EVERYTHING
WENT SMOOTH.
ARE YOU LYING TO ME?
- NO, MAMA.
- - MM.
DID YOU PICK UP MY MONEY?
THINGS DIDN'T
GO SO SMOOTH, DID THEY?
WHAT DID YOU DO?
¿HIJO?
EL TERMINO.
IDESGRACIADO!
YOU LEFT ME WITH A
FUCKING MESS TO DEAL WITH.
HUH?
UNA HEDIONDA, JODIDA, FEA...
SHE CAME IN HERE AND SHE
ALMOST CRACKED MY HEAD OPEN, UH?
NOW SHE'S A WITNESS!
YOU'D BETTER
PICK UP YOUR MARRANADAS.
BEFORE I DO.
YOU BETTER FIND HER.
SOMEBODY HAS TO CARE FOR THAT
FUCKING LITTLE PUTA.
YOU GOT TO GET
THE FUCK OUTTA HERE.
LIKE NOW!
SERIOUSLY, ALICIA.
HEY, DO WHAT
YOU GOTTA DO.
I DON'T WANNA GO.
I COULD GO WITH YOU.
OH, BULLSHIT, ALICIA.
I AM GOING WITH YOU.
NO.
NO, I'LL GO ON MY OWN.
JUST-
JUST DON'T TELL
MY SISTER, OKAY?
SHE DON'T NEED TO KNOW.
PROMISE ME, DRE.
PROMISE ME YOU'RE NOT
GONNA TELL HER.
SHE'LL TRIP.
I PROMISE...
ON THE REAL.
YOU KNOW ME.
- OKAY?
- YEAH.
OKAY.
YOU'RE MY GIRL, LEECE.
¿TU SABES?
NO.
WHO IS IT?
- GOD DAMN IT.
WHAT?
WHAT HAPPENED?
WHERE'S MY BROTHER?
WELL, LOOK WHAT
THE WIND BLEW IN.
LUPE.
WHAT'S UP, CHICA?
- WHAT'S UP?
- HEY, WORD ON THE STREET...
YOU FUCKING
KILLED IT LAST NIGHT.
THANKS, DRE.
I APPRECIATE THAT.
YOU WANT SOMETHING
TO DRINK?
ONLY IF IT BURNS.
ESPERATE.
SHE WAS MY FIRST.
IT WAS LIKE SHE WAS BURIED
IN THAT TREE FOR YEARS.
YOU MET ADAN?
HE'S GENTE FROM WAY BACK.
JUST NOW GETTING BACK
TO HIS ROOTS.
YEAH, WE MET.
HERE'S TO THE FIRE.
SALUD.
YOU OKAY?
YEAH, I'M GOOD.
SO HAVE YOU TALKED
TO ALICIA?
YEAH.
EARLIER.
WILL YOU TELL HER
TO CALL ME?
SHE'S BEEN DODGING.
LUPE, I'M NOT GETTING
IN THAT MIX.
HER BUSINESS
IS HER BUSINESS.
ALICIA'S MY BUSINESS.
JUST TELL HER
TO CALL ME.
OKAY.
ALL RIGHT.
LATERS.
HEY.
HEY, I DON'T HAVE
ANY MORE APPOINTMENTS
SCHEDULED FOR THE REST
OF THE DAY.
I WAS THINKING ABOUT
TAKING A DRIVE.
YOU WANNA COME?
A DRIVE?
YEAH.
I DON'T BITE.
MMM...
YEAH.
OKAY.
I'LL GET MY KEYS.
DO YOU MIND?
NO.
DO YOUR THING, CHICA.
SO IT'S JUST
THE TWO OF YOU, HUH?
YEAH, FOR THE PAST
FEW YEARS.
MY GRUMPSENT ME TO GO LIVE
WITH MY TIA IN CALIFAS.
HE SAYS I WASN'T
READY TO STAY.
YEAH? WELL, THIS TOWN HAS A SICKNESS.
IT CAN FUCKING
SUCK YOU UP.
SO WHERE ARE YOU
TAKING ME?
SOMEPLACE SPECIAL.
- YOU READY?
- YEAH.
- WE'RE GOING IN THERE?
- COME ON.
LET'S GO.
OH MY GOD.
MY GRUMPO CALLS IT
A THINKING PLACE.
WHO DID THIS?
A FRIEND.
WHY?
WELL, WHY DOES ANYONE
DO ANYTHING?
BUT NOBODY KNOWS
IT'S HERE.
NO.
THEY'D JUST WRECK IT.
THEY'D CHARGE ADMISSION
AND SELL T-SHIRTS.
THIS PLACE NEEDS
TO BREATHE.
HMM.
GRUMPO, TAKE IT EASY,
HOMBRE.
YOU'RE GONNA WORK
YOURSELF TO DEATH.
WELL, THANK YOU, MIJO.
APPRECIATE THE HELP.
I WANT YOU
TO MEET SOMEBODY.
- LUPE.
- HI, LUPE.
NICE TO MEET YOU.
I'M ADAN'S GRANDPA.
- WHAT A BEAUTIFUL
WOMAN, HOMBRE.
- SO YOUR GRUMPO SURVIVES
- OFF THIS LAND?
YEAH. MORE OR LESS.
HE TRADES AND SELLS CHILI
TO THE TOURISTS.
MAN. THIS WORLD
IS SO DIFFERENT.
DO YOU THINK YOUR SISTER
WILL BE ALL RIGHT?
YEAH.
WHAT DO YOU THINK, LUPE?
THEY SAY THERE'S
A REMEDIO FOR EVERYTHING,
EXCEPT FOR DEATH.
ALL RIGHT, HEADS UP.
HOT STUFF COMING THROUGH.
ALL RIGHT.
SIENTENSE.
WHEW.
YOU WANT TO SAY
THE PRAYER?
NO, I'M GOOD.
ANDALE.  I'M
HUNGRIER THAN A HOSTAGE.
GO AHEAD.
OH, DIVINE CREATOR,
LET US GIVE THANKS
FOR THIS FANTASTIC FEAST.
LET THE FRUIT OF YOUR EARTH
NOURISH THE WEAK,
Y POR FAVOR...
AYUDA A ADAN Y SU GRUMPO.
EN EL NOMBRE DEL PADRE,
EL HIJO Y EL ESPIRITU SANTO,
AMEN.
ALICIA?
HMM. I THOUGHT
YOU WERE YOUR SISTER.
- WHO LET YOU IN?
- THE DOOR WAS OPEN.
IS SHE HERE?
I CAME
TO BLAZE HER OUT.
GET THE FUCK
OUT OF MY HOUSE.
THAT IS NO WAY TO TREAT
YOUR COMPANY, YOUNG LADY.
WHAT DO YOU WANT?
YOU GONNA BLAZE IT UP?
THATTAGIRL.
I WANT TO HELP.
I REALLY DO.
PEOPLE MAKE MISTAKES.
I MADE MY SHARE.
NOW I'M NOT ONE
TO HOLD A GRUDGE,
SO LET ME TELL YOU WHAT.
YOU TELL ME WHERE I
CAN FIND YOUR SISTER...
AND I PROMISE
THIS WILL BE
- THE LAST TIME
WE EVER SHARE COMPANY.
SHE'S GONE.
NO TIME FOR GAMES, BABY.
I FUCKING HATE THAT.
THE THING ABOUT
THE PINIS,
- IT KIND OF KILLS
YOUR TASTE FOR GAMES.
I MEAN, WHAT CAN COMPARE WITH
CHEATING DEATH ON THE DAILY?
IT'S ADRENALINE
OVERLOAD SHIT.
IF YOU LIVE YOUR LIFE WITH A KNIFE
AT YOUR THROAT DAY IN, DAY OUT...
YOU GET USED TO IT.
MAYBE EVEN GROW
FOND OF IT.
LIKE A BEAUTY MARK.
WHERE IS SHE?
WE GOT INTO A FIGHT.
SHE LEFT. DON'T YOU
FUCKING DARE HURT HER.
- SPARKITY SPARK IT.
COOL DUDE- ISAIAH.
JUST TRIED TO STEP UP TOO
FAST IN THE GAME, YOU KNOW?
MIRA.  FILLED WITH ALL THE NAMES
OF THE KIDS WE WENT TO HIGH SCHOOL WITH?
THIS FUCKER'S
GETTING THICK, MAN.
I CAN'T BELIEVE
THAT FOOL PASSED, ESE.
THAT VATO WAS CRAZY, MAN.
- CRAZY, YOU KNOW?
- HE WAS COOL THOUGH.
YEAH WELL...
- YOU KNOW, OLD SCHOOL G.I.
- JUST HOPE
THE ANGELS GUIDE HIM.
LUPE.
- LATERS, BABE.
- LATERS.
LUPE.
¿QUE ESTA PASANDO?
IS DRE HERE?
DON'T I GET A HUG
OR WHAT?
- IS SHE HERE?
- HUH-UH.
SHE AIN'T
AT THE TAT SHOP.
WELL, SHE WENT WITH
HER GRANDMA TO SALTA.
WHAT'S UP?
WHAT DO YOU NEED?
CAN I TALK TO YOU
FOR A MINUTE?
LUPE!
TALK TO ME.
I'M RIGHT FUCKING HERE.
WHAT'S THE MATTER?
WHAT, YOU CAN'T SAY WHAT YOU'VE
GOTTA SAY IN FRONT OF JESSE BONEZ?
FUCK THAT PUSSY.
THIS IS MY FUCKING SHOP.
WE KICK BACK.
WE SMOKE CHRON.
WE DO WHAT WE GOTTA DO.
NO, I'M GOOD.
FUCK. HOLD ON.
LUPE.
LUPE. HEY.
ARE YOU GONNA FUCKING
HELP ME OR NOT?
WHAT'S UP?
- WHAT?
- YOU ALWAYS SAID, "COME TO ME," IF I EVER NEEDED ANYTHING,
ANYTHING AT ALL.
WELL, I'M COMING TO YOU.
- RIGHT NOW.
- WHAT DO YOU NEED SOMETHING LIKE THAT FOR?
FUCKING TELL ME
WHAT'S GOING ON.
I'VE NEVER PUT YOU ON A SPOT
LIKE THIS BEFORE, NEVER BEFORE.
YOU COME OVER HERE
TO MY SHOP,
YOU ASK ME FOR A FUCKING CUETE  AND YOU
CAN'T EVEN TELL ME WHAT THE FUCK IT'S FOR?
YOU PROBABLY SHOULDN'T
HAVE IT THEN, RIGHT?
YOU KNOW WHAT?
IF YOU'RE NOT GONNA HELP ME,
- I SEE HOW IT IS. - YOU
GONNA TELL ME- HEY, LUPE.
- WHAT?
- DON'T FUCKING BE LIKE THAT.
SEE THAT? THAT'S ONE IN THE CHAMBER.
IT MEANS
YOU GOT FIRE, CHICA.
REMEMBER YOU CAN'T
UN-RING A BELL.
I JUST NEED IT
JUST FOR IN CASE.
ARE YOU SURE?
YEAH.
CUIDADO.
IS YOUR GRUMPO  STILL
WORKING HIMSELF TO THE BONE?
YOU KNOW HIM.
HE'S GONNA WORK
HIMSELF TO DEATH.
MM.
MAS ATRAS.
THEY USED
TO CALL HIM THE...
MERO LEON DEL TRABAJO.
YOU KNOW, I REMEMBER WHEN
THEY USED TO CALL HIM THAT.
OH, WE'RE ALL LINKED HERE,
ONE WAY OR ANOTHER.
EITHER BY BLOOD
OR BY... SUFFERING.
TIMES ARE
DIFFERENT NOW.
PEOPLE TODAY, THEY JUST
DON'T HAVE ANY RESPECT.
HERE, THEY LEARN HOW
TO KEEP SECRETS.
TELL ME ABOUT GUADALUPE.
OH, COME ON.
YOU DIDN'T THINK YOU
COULD KEEP THAT ONE FROM ME,
DID YOU,
ADANCITO?
WHAT DO YOU WANNA KNOW?
I JUST WANNA
SPEAK TO HER.
AW, WE'RE JUST GETTING
TO KNOW EACH OTHER.
THAT'S ALL.
ADANCITO...
DON'T LIE
TO YOUR MADRINA.
I WANT YOU
TO BRING HER TO ME.
¿ME OISTE, ADAN?
YOU'RE ALL DONE.
SYMBOL OF CONTRITION.
DO I OWE YOU ANYTHING?
NO.
WE'RE ALL GOOD.
IS ISAIAH HERE?
I'M LOOKING FOR MY SISTER.
ISAIAH'S DEAD.
AND MY SISTER?
SHE'S NOT HERE.
I NEED TO FIND HER.
SO GO FIND HER.
I KNOW SHE'S HERE.
- SHE'S NOT FUCKING HERE.
- YOU DON'T UNDERSTAND.
I NEED TO TALK TO HER. THERE
IS SOMEONE LOOKING FOR HER.
NO.
YOU DON'T UNDERSTAND.
WHAT'D SHE SAY?
DON'T WORRY.
I SENT HER AWAY.
YOU NEED TO EAT.
IT'S ALL THE FOOD
HE ENJOYED THE MOST.
MY GRANDMA TOLD ME,
"MIJITO,
JESUS LOVES YOU
AND EVERYBODY ELSE THINKS
YOU'RE AN ASSHOLE."
WHAT'S UP, CHICA?
WHAT'S UP, LUPE?
WHERE'S MY SISTER, DRE?
I'M NOT FUCKING
PLAYING WITH YOU.
- WHERE IS SHE?
- YOU WANT A DRINK?
NO, I DON'T WANT A FUCKING DRINK!
I WANT TO KNOW WHERE ALICIA IS.
- SLOW YOUR ROLL, LUPE.
- WHERE THE FUCK IS MY FUCKING-
- BACK OFF ME!
- HEY HEY HEY HEY!
- DON'T PUT YOUR HANDS ON ME, BITCH!
- HEY! SHUT UP, DRE!
LUPE, YOU NEED
TO GO HOME.
- NO WONDER SHE'S FUCKING DODGING YOU!
- I SAID SHUT UP!
I'M SICK OF PLAYING THIS
BARRIO HIDE-AND-SEEK BULLSHIT!
- ISAIAH'S DEAD!
- I KNOW!
ALL RIGHT? I KNOW.
IF ALICIA TURNS UP,
I SWEAR
I'LL CALL YOU, CHICA.
I PROMISE.
FUCK YOU ALL!
I'M HER SISTER.
I'M HER MOTHER!
I'M FUCKING THE ONLY THING
SHE'S FUCKING GOT!
FUCK!
WHY ARE YOU FUCKING
TAKING HER SIDE?
- WHY ARE YOU RUNNING YOUR FUCKING MOUTH?
- SHE CAME AT ME!
YOU NEED TO FUCKING ACT RIGHT. YOU'RE
ACTING LIKE A LITTLE FUCKING KID RIGHT NOW.
- iANDALE!
- HANG ON, BABE.
BONEZ.
GONNA BE LATE.
HURRY UP, BONEZ.
HEY, HOMEY.
LET'S GO.
WHAT'S UP, CHICA?
YEAH, WE'RE LEAVING
RIGHT NOW.
YEAH, I CAN STOP AT THE LIQUOR
STORE. WHAT DO YOU WANT ME TO GET?
I'LL CALL YOU BACK.
YOU SMOKE BUD?
WHAT ARE YOU
DOING HERE?
I BROUGHT SOME HIERBA.
JUST CAME BY
TO BLAZE YOU OUT.
- GET OFF ME!
- WHERE IS SHE?!
WHERE IS SHE?
FUCKING CALM DOWN!
FUCKING WHERE IS SHE?
FUCK.
BITCH.
AH HA HA!
GET THE FUCK OFF ME.
SHE'S WITH BRUJO.
YEAH.
WHEW.
TALACHE, ECHEME DOS
TEQUILAS, CHICHARRON Y...
TRAIGA DOS CERVEZAS
MEXICANAS.
SI.
I'M SORRY FOR THE LOSS
OF YOUR SON.
IN REMEMBRANCE.
A TU HIJO.
MAY GOD HAVE MERCY
ON HIS SOUL.
YOU KNOW DAMN WELL I DON'T
WANT NO DRINK FROM YOU.
HMM. JUST ONE?
TO TAKE AWAY
THE PAIN.
DON'T BE SUCH
A TIGHT PUSSY.
A LITTLE BIRD
TOLD ME THAT YOU'RE
HIDING THIS GIRL.
THIS DESGRACIADA
CHIQUITITA.
YOU GOT GALL TO CALL ME OUT
AFTER YOU POISONED MY SON.
YOU'RE QUICK TO ACCUSE.
AND YOU DON'T EVEN HAVE
THE BACKBONE
TO LOOK ME IN THE EYE.
I NEVER MEANT ANY HARM
FOR YOUR ISAIAH.
IT WAS THE SICKNESS
THAT TOOK HIM.
I ONLY CAME HERE
TO GIVE YOU A MESSAGE.
WE WILL DO THIS
THE SANGWAY.
AND THE NIGHT BIRDS
AND THE CROWS...
WILL COME FOR YOU.
I WILL MEET YOU
EN LAS TINIEBLAS.
YA LLEGA MI YEGUA NEGRA
TO TAKE BACK MY DIGNITY.
INO ME CHINGES!
IBRUJO!
YOU. YOU.
TOMA, JODIDO.
- YOU HAVE TO GO.
- WHAT THE FUCK, RYAN?
COME ON.
GET UP.
GET DRESSED
AND HEAD OUT.
YOU'RE NOT SAFE HERE.
SHE HASN'T SLEPT
IN DAYS.
GET YOUR ASS UP
AND KICK DUST, DEMI.
NOW!
ALL RIGHT.
I'LL BE OUT BACK.
HEY.
WE HAVE TO GO.
WHAT?
WHY?
WHAT'S GOING ON?
COME ON.
GET DRESSED.
Hello?
ADAN.
HEY, IT'S ARTE.
Yeah?
DRE IS DEAD.
What?
- What are you talking about?
- HEY.
HEY, LISTEN TO ME, BRO.
I NEED YOU TO DO ME
A FAVOR, ALL RIGHT?
All right.
What do you want me to do?
- I NEED YOU TO FIND LUPE.
- Where is she?
SANGRE DE CIELO PUEBLO.
CUT HER OFF AT THE OLD BRIDGE.
YOU CAN GET HER IF YOU LEAVE NOW.
YOU GOTTA
LEAVE NOW THOUGH.
- Okay. I'll go now.
- ALL RIGHT. LET ME KNOW.
HE'S COMING.
KNOW WHERE
YOU'RE GOING?
YEAH, I THINK SO.
ALL RIGHT, I'LL SEE YOU SOON.
WHERE ARE YOU GOING, LUPE?
- OWN IT, LUPE.
- MOVE!
WHAT THE HELL
ARE YOU DOING, HUH?
MOVE YOUR
FUCKING TRUCK, ADAN.
YOU KNOW, THERE'S PEOPLE
OUT LOOKING FOR YOU?
THIS IS NOT
YOUR PROBLEM, ADAN.
GET IN YOUR TRUCK
AND MOVE.
WHAT'S IN
YOUR HAND, HUH?
I'M NOT LETTING HIM
GET TO ALICIA.
HE'S NEVER GETTING
TO ALICIA.
JESUS CHRIST, LUPE.
A FUCKING GUN?
HUH?
WHAT ARE YOU, LOCA?
PUT THE GUN DOWN.
COME ON, BABY.
PUT IT DOWN. PUT IT DOWN. PUT IT DOWN.
SHE'S LOST.
I CAN FEEL HER.
AND SHE NEEDS ME.
I KNOW. WE'RE GONNA
FIND HER TOGETHER.
I'M HERE.
ALL RIGHT?
I GOT YOU.
- SHE NEEDS ME.
- ALL RIGHT? SHH.
PACIENCIA, BABY.
IAH, PUTA MADRE!
ALICIA!
GET UP!
COME ON!
- FUCK!
- ALICIA!
FUCK!
OH FUCK.
NICE NIGHT, HUH?
I'M LOOKING FOR SOMEONE.
HER NAME'S ALICIA.
LOOK, HER SISTER'S
WORRIED.
RIGHT, SHE HASN'T TALKED
TO HER IN A WHILE.
IS SHE HERE?
WHO'S ASKING?
MY NAME IS ADAN.
I'M A FRIEND OF HERS.
HARD TO TELL THESE DAYS.
IS ALICIA HERE?
THEY'RE GONE.
WHERE'D SHE GO?
WITH WHO?
MY SISTER.
HE'S COMING.
WHO'S "HE"?
THE GHOST.
I NEED TO TALK
TO MY SISTER.
I NEED TO SEE HER.
CAN YOU TAKE ME?
NO.
BUT YOU CAN TAKE THAT.
WHERE AM I GOING?
TO THE TOP.
OW, FUCK.
HEY, COMPA.
NICE DAY
FOR A PICNIC, NO?
WHO'S THAT YOU GOT
WITH YOU? IS THAT LUPE?
HI, LUPE.
HOW YOU BEEN, CHICA?
HEY, COMPA, MAYBE YOU
CAN HELP ME.
YOU TWO LOVEBIRDS DIDN'T
HAPPEN TO SEE
A COUPLE OF BLEEDING MARIMACHAS  ROAMING
AROUND THESE HILLS TODAY, HAVE YOU?
COME ON, BROTHER.
WHY DON'T YOU
LET IT GO, WHITEY?
THAT COULD
NEVER HAPPEN, HUH?
L- I WISH I COULD.
I REALLY DO.
BUT WE'RE IN DEEP-
REAL DEEP.
GET OFF, ESE.
YOU KNOW I CAN'T LET
YOU DO THIS, RIGHT?
WHAT, "LET" ME?
OH, PAPACITO.
WHAT THE FUCK MAKES YOU THINK
I'M ASKING PERMISSION, BRO?
WHY DON'T YOU GO HIDING
BEHIND YOUR CUETE, HUH?
WHAT, THIS OLD THING?
QUE TRISTE.
HUH?
ALL RIGHT, ALL RIGHT.
JUST LIKE OLD TIMES,
HUH, BRO?
OKAY, BIG BOY.
AHH.
RED ROVER, RED ROVER.
YOU LEARNED SOME SHIT, HUH?
OH, COME ON- OH!
OH, YOU MOTHERFUCKER.
I'LL FUCKING KILL YOU.
WHY DON'T YOU GO
TO SLEEP, BABY BRO?
GO TO SLEEP, BABY BRO.
GO TO SLEEP.
AND NO FUCKING TAPPING OUT.
YOU FUCKING BITCH!
YOU FUCKER!
I'M GONNA FUCKING
KILL YOU!
I'M GONNA FUCK YOU UP!
FUCKING BITCH.
LUPE!
NOTHING LASTS FOREVER, BABY.
YOU REMIND ME OF MY MAMA-
- BATSHIT CRAZY.
OH, BUT YOU GOT A FIRE.
I LIKE THAT.
WHAT MAMA DON'T KNOW
WON'T HURT HER.
... GIVE A FUCK ABOUT IS YOU!
- I'M HER MOTHER.
- I'M ALL SHE'S FUCKING GOT!
CARE FOR A FRAJO?
MY FATHER BELIEVED
IN KARMA.
YOU BELIEVE
IN KARMA?
WELL, HE DIDN'T
EXACTLY CALL IT KARMA.
HE CALLED IT
SOMETHING ELSE.
MORE OR LESS
THE SAME THING.
YOU REAP WHAT YOU SOW.
WHAT GOES AROUND,
COMES AROUND.
YOU UNDERSTAND?
I DON'T BELIEVE
IN KARMA, PER SE.
BUT I DO BELIEVE
IN JUSTICE.
MORE OR LESS THE SAME THING,
IF YOU THINK ABOUT IT.
IT'S JUST THAT ONE
IS LEVIED BY GOD,
THE UNIVERSE,
WHAT-NOT,
IN GOD'S TIMING.
AND THE OTHER
IS DELIVERED BY MAN.
OR IN THIS CASE
A WOMAN
AND A SNAKE.
POSITIVELY MYTHICAL.
SUENOS DULCES, FANTASMA.
SWEET DREAMS.
OYE...
YOUR MAMA WILL
COME HERE SOON
TO TUCK YOU IN.
A VOLAR, BRUJO.
IBRUJO!
I COME TO MAKE
MY PEACE.
WHERE'S MI HIJO?
IBRUJO!
- ANSWER ME!
SERIO.
THERE'S A REMEDIO
FOR EVERYTHING,
EXCEPT FOR DEATH.
YOU!
IPUTA!
THE SCENT
NEVER LEAVES YOU.
I CAN STILL
SMELL MOM SOMETIMES-
HER CINNAMON GUM
AND HER PERFUME.
YEAH.
SOMETHING ABOUT
THE SMELL THAT JUST
DIGS ITSELF DEEP.
AMO LIKE FUCK,
MY BABY SISTER.
LET'S GO.
IT'S TIME.