Mom?
Dinner!
Do you--?
Dinnertime!
Mom?)
Ma?
She's dead!
Somebody help me!
Mom!
Late. I'm sorry.
- Davis forgot his homework?
- Oh, that'll be the day.
- Mollie?
- Yes, we're halfway to school...
...and she says, "Mom, I'm supposed
to take food for the homeless."
I have to tum around, go to the shore,
then find her.
- Is this the rack we're working on?
- Yep.
This is gorgeous.
Oh, this would be beautiful
with my dress.
- Oh, for the anniversary party?
- I looked it up. Number 20 is china.
How about 21?
Is it beautiful scan/es?
Why wait a year?
Happy anniversary.
Madeleine.
Hello.
This is Billie Clark.
Pardon?
- Hi, Dad.
- Hey, Moll.
- Rick?
- Honey?
Oh, thank God. It's gonna take me
at least five hours to drive there.
I didn't have time to cook--
It's okay.
You sure you don't want us to come?
- Mollie's got--
- Ballet on Tuesday.
Soccer on Thursday,
game on Saturday.
- She's just gonna--
- I cannot miss them.
Mollie, we'll figure it out.
When was the last time
I even saw my mother?
- Doesn't matter.
- Three years ago.
It doesn't matter.
It's okay.
- I love you.
- Love you.
I'm gonna miss you.
Be good, all right?
Bye.
- Aunt Will.
- My girl.
My dear girl.
How is she?
Well, she's just sleeping now.
She sleeps most of the time.
It was a massive coronary.
That's the word the doctor used:
massive.
Are you going to stay at the house?
Is Baby there?
Yeah.
She found your mother.
She thought she had passed
already.
So now she's in her room
and she won't come out.
Billie?
Mom.
How you feeling?
Did the children come?
No. They...
Oh, that's too bad.
I haven't seen them for so long.
I'm sorry.
Have you seen Baby?
No. Mom, just-- You should rest.
You should rest now, okay?
I can't.
Not until I know
that you're gonna take care of Baby.
Mom...
...we never even got along.
Yes, you did.
Before she got sick.
You just don't remember.
I remember everything.
She's your little sister.
Please.
Honey, it is so late.
- You go home now.
- But what about the--?
I'll take care
of all the funeral arrangements.
- You go home to Rick and the kids.
- Thank you.
Thank you.
It's not like I had that much
to do with her, you know?
I mean, how many times
did I even see her since I left?
I used to think...
...when she dies, you know
I won't feel anything.
But I feel...
She was my mother, you know?
And you know what she did...
...right before she died?
She asked.
I mean, for a minute, I thought...
...maybe this time will be different.
She's happy to see me...
...and she's holding my hand and...
Maybe she'll just...
...tell me that she loves me.
And then that moment was passed.
I mean, it's not like I'm surprised.
She's been asking me the same thing
since I was 18, so...
And what did you say?
What was I supposed to say?
Yeah.
Baby is family.
And there's no one else.
Is there?
Hey, Moll.
Slow and quiet, okay?
How is she?
Sorry that she couldn't go
to the funeral.
Should I go up?
I think it's better
if we leave her for now.
Did you tell the kids?
They don't like it.
I don't like it.
Baby.
You remember Rick?
Hello, Baby.
We're all so sorry
about your mother.
And Davis.
And Mollie, all grown up.
Well...
...I'll see you all up at the ranch
as usual.
With Baby.
- You'll come too.
- You remember the ranch, Baby?
You used to love it
when you were little.
Yeah.
Look, Baby,
let me give you a hand with your-
It's okay.
Give me a hug, Baby.
Davis, give me a hand
with the luggage.
- Mollie, you want the ken?
- Yeah.
Here you go, honey.
All right. Come on, Baby.
What I really wanna show you
is the view.
Wait till you see it.
Isn't it amazing?
We have swans and ducks.
You're tired.
I'll show you your room.
So this room used to be Rick's office.
He totally redid it for you.
Here it is.
I tried to make it look like your room
at Mom's.
- I could help you unpack.
- No.
Okay.
Oh, your pills.
Three? And you know
when to take them and--?
Sony. Of course you do.
We don't smoke in the house,
but on the porch is fine.
Well, I'll call you for dinner.
That's fine.
Thank you. Thanks.
Okay.
Here we go. Just help yourself.
That's wonderful, honey.
Baby, would you like to have a--?
Two roads diverged in a wood, and I--
I took the one less traveled
Well, maybe we should all say grace.
My family did. Look at me.
It's not a prayer. It's a poem.
Two roads diverged in a wood, and I--
I took the one less traveled by
And that has made
All the difference
It's about Mom. I know you don't
wanna talk about Mom, but I do.
No.
Ever wonder what her life would have
been like if she took the other road?
They had money. She could've put me
in an asylum, but she didn't.
And I think that was a mistake.
Because she could have made
something of her life.
She was very talented.
Did you know that she fixed everything
in the house after Dad left us?
- No.
- She did. She fixed the toilet.
She fixed the doorbell
and the door in the kitchen.
She couldn't fix the TV though.
She had to have someone else
come in and fix the TV.
-Okay.-
I found her.
I think she had a stroke.
Her eyes were wide open.
She was looking up.
I thought maybe she was looking
at the slats...
...but there were no slats out
that night.
There were no stars...
...that night.
Honey...
...you want some salad?
Mom?
Honey?
What happened?
Did you have a bad dream?
Come here.
Yeah.
Safe and sound.
Mom?
Does Aunt Baby have to stay here?
- Hurry up and eat your breakfast.
- I don't want wheat squares.
They're ugly. I want rice squares.
Wheat squares are the same
as rice squares.
- One's wheat, one's rice.
- I need lunch money.
- I can make you lunch.
- Olive loaf.
What's wrong with my olive loaf?
You love my olive loaf. He's joking.
Good morning. Look who's up.
- Hey.
- You didn't have to get up early.
- We're late.
- You want some breakfast?
- Mom, lunch money.
I'll get you some orange juice.
- What's wrong?
- Is everyone leaving?
You don't wanna be alone?
It's okay. Don't worry.
I-- I'll be here with you.
I'm gonna take a few days off work.
- Mom, I need lunch money.
- Just wait a second.
All right, Mollie. Come on. Let's go.
Davis, here.
- Five bucks? It's a school lunch.
- Deal with it.
- Bye. sweetie
- Okay.
Just give me a second, okay?
Davis.
I have to pick Mollie up,
so come home after school.
- No, honey, he's got debate team.
- I quit.
- What did you say?
- I said, I quit.
- You did what? Davis-
- Listen. Listen, it's gonna be okay.
Because today,
Davis has to take care of his aunt.
We're late.
We will talk about it later.
They're gone.
It's always really chaotic.
All right, breakfast.
I n make you anything you want
Eggs?
- Do you want some cereal?
- I'm not hungry.
Okay.
- Should I tum on the TV for you?
- No.
- Music--
- I think--
I think I'll just go smoke a cigarette
on the porch.
Okay.
Do you want some company?
No.
Madeleine.
Hey, it's Billie.
I'm gonna need a few more days.
Yeah.
Yeah, it's hit me harder
than I thought.
I am not incompetent.
I know what I'm doing
every minute and--
Hey, you sure
you don't wanna watch TV?
Would you turn it off, please?
It makes me hear voices...
...in my head.
Sony.
Mom, I'm home.
Honey, where have you been?
- I told you not to be late.
- I had a test.
Oh, 100. That's good, my good boy.
You keep an eye on her.
I have homework, so...
Baby.
Can you come in here?
Would you mind helping me out?
I know you're such a good cook.
- I can cook.
- Good.
Yeah.
Come on.
You know what you should do? Make
a list for me. That's what Mom did.
Oh, we don't need a list.
Hey, you know what?
How about a pie?
Mollie loves peach pie.
I can make an apple pie.
That's right. You used to make it when
we were little. That was my favorite.
Great.
Apples are in the fridge.
Here you go.
Mollie's actually a lot like I am.
Well, like I was.
She can't sit still
and she does lots of activities.
Oh, yeah, and she's really athletic,
which Rick loves...
...because, you know,
he was this big high-school jock.
But she doesn't do very well
in school...
...which is also like me, right?
Actually,
completely different from Davis.
He's the brain, like you.
But he spends lots of time
in his room...
...and he doesn't
have many friends and-
Like me?
Well...
...with his computer.
You know,
and the video games and...
Kids.
- Good morning.
- Hey.
Hey, Billie.
How you feeling?
Good. I'm good.
It's no problem
if you wanna take more time.
I'm fine. These are supposed
to be in the back, right?
Okay. Billie, what's up?
It wasn't just about my mother.
My sister moved in.
- I didn't know you had a sister.
- Yeah.
Because I don't tell anyone,
because she's...
- She has--
- Issues?
Schizophrenia.
That shut them up.
Billie, honey, I'm so sorry.
Thanks.
So does she like--?
- Pull her hair out? Talk in tongues?
- I see them on the street. I didn't--
No. No, she doesn't do any of that.
In fact,
she doesn't do much of anything.
She just...
...sits...
...and sits.
- Did you suggest a walk or--?
- Yes, she's afraid of dogs.
A drive? She gets carsick.
Movies? She hears voices.
Clothes.
Bring her here?
- Yes.
- Yeah.
She's not Cinderella, April.
She's mentally ill.
Does she wear clothes?
Honey?
- It's midnight.
- Okay. Just wait.
This inheritance, it's good. it's--
- It's good. It's not great, but it's good.
- Okay.
Your mother's house, it was rough.
She was mortgaged to her eyeballs.
The market's soft.
Even if we get half of what it's worth,
we can do a hell of a lot. Here, look.
We pay the loan first.
That's number one.
You have no idea
what a load off my back that'll be.
We can start looking at the mortgage,
credit cards, the rest of it.
I don't want you to think
we can catch up all the way.
But at least we can get some...
Some breathing room.
And that's like-- That's...
Honey, that's...
That's good.
That's really good.
I know.
Yeah.
What are you doing?
We have a bedroom.
- No, that's too far.
- No way.
- I told you I don't wanna go.
- Come on. It'll be fine.
You took your pills, right?
Okay, then.
We're all set.
Don't worry, all right?
We have beautiful things.
- And it's all on me, anything you like
- I don't want anything.
Come on.
Are we in a rush?
Sony.
Hey. Madeleine, April,
this is my sister, Baby. Elizabeth.
Hello, Elizabeth.
- Hi.
- Hi, nice to meet you.
- Welcome.
- Hi.
Did Billie tell you?
We have some stunning new pieces.
If you'd like, I could show you around
maybe by a few things on.
Okay.
- Great. Here. Come with me.
- Yeah. This way.
We'll find some things for you to ﬂy.
Anything you see-
- What about this one?
- I like blue.
Okay. Well, we can try it, you know,
and if it works, it works.
- Anything you don't like, let us know.
- We have tops in blue.
You said you like blue,
so maybe we can try those on too.
Oh, you look great.
- Let's take a look in the mirror.
- Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Oh, you look so good.
- Right, Billie?
- Yeah.
We should go with jeans,
something a little simpler.
- I think it's
- Oh, yeah. The cream-
- We were saying it's a little dressy
- A little too much.
Maybe we should try that cream top
with the jeans.
It's hanging right there.
It's a very simple, easy look.
I think you'll like it.
She didn't really--
I really didn't expect that.
- Yeah, she carries it off.
- She likes clothes.
Listen. Listen to them.
You know what they want.
Shouldn't be here.
- What did she say?
- I was just-
- Miss?
- April, please help her.
- Just go back in.
- Got it.
Go back. Baby, Baby, it's okay.
It's okay.
Now she can't come in.
You know what they want.
You have to be very quiet.
You have to be quiet.
Just don't- Don't- They can hear me.
They can hear me. Just-
Just be quiet.
If they could just be quiet.
We pushed- We pushed her.
I'm so sorry.
Baby?
Oh, my-- Just please--
That's it. Because I'm just crazy.
Just tiptoe- Just-
Baby?
- Turn the knob, okay?
- Tiptoe. Tiptoe.
- I know you can hear me.
- They think you-
You crept away. You climbed out.
You just snuck out!
- What's happening?
- Problem with the door.
No, I'm not in here.
--Something. I'll just need to--
We have rooms up front.
Why don't we go there?
We can take care of that.
Listen to me, okay?
I have to run.
I have to run as fast as I can.
They can't catch you, can't yell at you.
They can't tell you what to do.
Okay? Come out here.
I'm almost there. I'm almost there.
I'm almost there. I'm gone.
- Baby.
- I'm gone.
I'm home. I'm home!
Baby. Don't do this to me.
- Don't do this to me.
- I'm home.
Baby.
Baby, we can get in the car.
We could be home in 10 minutes,
okay?
And you can just-
You can get right in bed, all right?
Or you can...
You can take your pills or...
I mean, is that what you do
when this happens?
When you start hearing voices?
I don't know what you--
Do you want me to apologize?
I'm sorry.
It's not your fault.
It's my fault, okay?
I should never have brought you here.
I know that.
So let's just get in the car, okay?
Please, Baby.
Okay. All right, everyone.
I have something to say.
I dedicate this meal,
this wonderful meal--
- Pizza?
- To Grandma Kathleen.
- By her act of generosity, she--
- I'm not moving.
Oh, no, no. No, honey, of course not.
We're not moving into the house.
- She gave it to us to sell.
- It's for everyone, so we don't worry.
- Are we worried?
- Yes.
- No.
No, Davis.
Look, we just needed a little help
and that's what Grandma did for us.
And there's an account
for you too, Baby. Of course.
- You can have it.
- No.
No, Baby, look, it's yours to do
with whatever, as you please.
Do you understand?
You always wanted a motorcycle.
Now, wouldn't she look great
with a Harley, Mollie?
I'd like a computer.
Great. That's great.
Okay. A computer. Look.
Here, talk to the expert. Davis.
It's gotta be fast.
You think,
'I don't mind waiting a few seconds'...
...but when you have to sit there...
- Hey.
- Hi, Mom.
- What you doing?
- Trying to find a computer.
Any luck?
You want HD, of course,
and as much memory as you can get.
Cool.
Oh, but if you only get
a 13-inch screen...
...is that gonna be big enough?
Thanks, Mom.
But I think we're doing okay here.
Okay.
Hey, girls.
- Hi.
- Hey.
All right.
You just click "enter"
and the computer's yours.
Yeah. It is expensive, but it's like
my dad says when he bids a job.
- Want it good or you want it cheap?
- You can use mine if you want to.
What do I--? How--?
Right there.
There it is.
Davis and crazy girl sitting in a tree
K-I-S-S--
Say that again, I'm gonna hurl: you
Do you understand me?
- What's going on?
- Do you?
- Do you under--?
- Hey. Hey. What is happening?
- What is going on?
- Why don't you ask her?
Honey.
What was that about?
- Yeah, nice.
- Twenty years. I cannot believe it.
It's like yesterday.
- I know.
- I know. Amazing.
I know the name of a great caterer,
if you'd like.
- We're gonna do potluck.
- Yeah. It's probably a lot--
Cheaper.
- No, Douglas, not quite.
- It's great.
- That's a great idea. Plus, it's not so--
- Formal.
- Exactly.
- Yeah. Yeah, and cheaper.
- Funny. More wine?
- Please.
- Oh, honey.
- Another bottle of wine.
Honey, it's late.
No, come on.
The kids are gonna be fine.
Yeah.
No, we really-
We have to get home.
We have an early start. Sony.
- Oh, no. I understand
- Okay.
Thanks.
Outside. We could fit
a hundred people there.
I'm not saying I'm gonna invite 100
of my closest friends, but I think it's--
Honey, is something wrong?
I told Mollie that she shouldn't
invite her friends over...
...and we should do the same.
- Honey-
- You weren't here.
- I had to break up a fight.
- A fight? What fight?
Mollie used the word "crazy"
about Baby and then Davis just--
I mean, they're fine. They're fine.
That is what people will think when
they meet her and I don't want that.
Do you really believe
you can keep her a secret?
- Honey, this is an opportunity-
- Not the sales pitch.
--To have this great party
and, "Hey, here's my sister."
Who might start talking to voices.
- Don't let that spoil the good time.
- She can go upstairs.
- And sit at the computer with Davis?
- He's been good for her.
Great.
My crazy sister with my--
-With your what?
- Nothing.
- What were you gonna say?
- This isn't about Davis.
- They're two peas in a pod, right?
- No.
- Yeah, smart, alone. No friends.
- He's sensitive. He's not a joiner.
- He's in his room all the time.
- He's not into sports.
- Don't even start.
- That's what kills you.
You don't worry about him, huh?
You don't worry?
You want a party, fine.
We'll have a party.
And we'll trot my little sister out
for everyone to see, okay?
And you're damn right I worry.
They had a fight. Did you hear it?
Hard to miss.
Did you hear what they said?
They think I'm like you.
Your mom said something.
- What?
- You know, I studied like you.
And I stayed in my room too. it's--
They say I'm the smartest one
in the family...
...but you'd never know
because of what happened to me.
What did happen to you?
Your mom and I had a fight,
like we always did after I got sick.
But I spoiled her last year in school,
which I didn't mean to, but I--
- I started hearing voices.
- Yeah.
I read about...
Schizophrenia.
It's okay. You can say it.
Anyway, it was
your mom's prom night.
And she was there with her date
and she was taking her pictures.
And she looked beautiful and...
I thought that she needed something
in her hair because I'm very visual.
I-- You know, I see something
and once I think it, I have to do it.
So I went
and I gal: this really special pin...
...and I tried to,
but she didn't want it.
She...
And she started yelling
and screaming...
...and calling me names,
and the voices were--
- Yeah, right.
- It was all--
So I jumped out the window.
They took me to the hospital.
And the doctors diagnosed me
with schizophrenia.
And that was- We knew now.
At least we knew.
And Mom started crying.
She said she started crying.
I don't remember. That's the thing.
You don't remember.
You remember things,
but you don't.
So my mom took me home
and she took care of me...
...all these years.
She really did.
But they're wrong about you,
you know?
You don't-- You're not like me.
- No?
- No.
I'm an expert on these things.
I could tell. I could see the signs.
No, I think you just haven't found
the right group of people...
...or the right person
to connect with.
You know?
Someone to listen.
That's all you need.
Are Mom and Dad gonna dance?
I don't wanna see them dance.
Have you ever seen them dance?
Or any of those people?
Are they all gonna dance?
Is it gonna be like a dance party?
- I'm sorry. Did you say something?
- Davis.
-Hey.
What did you do?
What did I do? What did I do? I made
the house better, that's what I did.
Davis, you wanna help me with this?
This chair?
Sure.
It's feng shui.
- I'm gonna put this chair over here.
- Okay.
Right-- Right there.
Yeah. See that?
See the way the light hits the arms
of the chair?
I'm like an artist here.
My teacher in ninth grade
Mr.- Mr...
It's okay. I already forgot my teachers
from last year.
He always said I should
go to art school.
But...
Mom always said I made the
house beautiful, so that's what I do.
That's what I did here, right? Right?
Your mom's gonna love it.
She's gonna love it, right?
- I bought it.
- Do you think it's enough?
- It's plenty. And I can always go back-
- You sure? Okay.
What do you think? It's feng shui.
I made the house better.
Your house is now
in perfect harmony.
Really?
No kidding.
Well, that would be a change.
You have to put it back.
We have a party tonight.
- Which is coming up, so get ready.
- It's for the party.
- I think it looks good.
- Oh, do you, Mr. Interior Decorator?
- It's not his fault.
- Look, it's nobody's fault.
I want my house back...
...the way it was.
- Mom, you-
- No.
You want your house back?
I'll put it back,
if that's what you want.
Thank you.
It's always what you want.
What?
- What did you say?
- I said, it's always what you want.
You wanna go to the stupid store.
It was a bad idea, but we go
because that's what you want.
Excuse me for thinking
you might enjoy it.
You've never liked anything
that I ever did for you.
- You never did anything for me
- I took you in.
- I cook your meals.
- Let's not do this now.
I don't go to work
so you won't be alone.
- You're afraid of what I'll do.
- And look what happened.
- You want me to leave?
- Of course not.
It was always easier if I wasn't there.
You used to chase me away.
I never chased you away.
I've forgotten almost everything. I can't
forget you standing with your friends...
...stomping your foot, telling me
to get out like I was some kind of dog.
Making a fool out of me.
Isn't that what you want now?
- Come on. Isn't that what you want?
- No, that's enough. Stop it!
That's enough.
Both of you.
Look, we just want everyone
to get ready for the party, okay?
We can talk about this later, calmly.
Come on, honey.
You wanna know what I want?
I want my life back.
Hi.
How are you?
Hello.
- Hi, Baby.
- Hey.
It's so good to see you again.
The place looks great, doesn't it?
The lights and the water?
I know. It's beautiful, right?
- Yes.
- I don't want the cheesy one.
No, I know.
- Hey.
My mom was wrong.
I think what you did was...
...beautiful.
She just likes things
the way she does them.
And forget what she said.
She's all bent about the party.
Plus...
-...I don't want you to leave.
- Someone tum the music off, please.
Please, everyone. I'd like to--
I would like to say a few words.
Someone is supposed
to make the toast...
...but, hey, it's my party,
so I thought I'd start.
- It was 20 years ago today--
- Everybody get comfortable.
Hey, I'm gonna keep this short.
As I was saying
before I was rudely interrupted...
...that it was 20 years ago today...
I became the luckiest man
in the world...
...when Billie Davis fumed to me
and said yes.
She doesn't understand you
like I do.
I think it's because she's jealous.
I mean, you've got this artistic soul
and she's...
Well, she sells dresses.
And then I turn around...
...and that little baby
is telling me how uncool I am...
...and my son's in high school.
How did the hell did that happen?
To the girl I married
20 years ago today...
...and to the wonderful children
she created. Mollie.
Mollie, come here, honey.
Look at my little princess.
And Davis. Where's Davis?
- Where's my genius?
- Genius.
Davis?
- Where's your brother?
- I don't know.
Well, anyway, hopefully he's not
in the kitchen with the champagne.
No, in all seriousness...
I like being alone.
I can't tell anyone that...
...except you.
Cheers.
What are you doing?
What are you doing to my son?
Look at me. Look at me!
What were you doing to my son?
What did you do?
What have you done?
What?
- Did you see what's happening?
- I don't know.
- Billie.
- No.
Wait, Billie.
I don't care if she's sick.
- Those are my kids.
- Be quiet. Be quiet.
Those are my kids
and she can't slay here anymore.
- What do you want me to do?
- Get her out.
You're the one
who wanted to have the party.
who said it would all be fine.
- You're blaming me?
-'She's family. You're all she's got.'
- That's what you said.
- No. I didn't--
You did. That's what you said.
I sure as hell didn't think
this would happen.
I gotta go check on Davis.
Davis?
Why doesn't my door have a lock?
Oh, honey.
Is it my fault, Mom?
No.
It wasn't your fault.
She thought I wanted to kiss her.
You've been such a good friend to her
and she's very pretty.
What?
It's confusing.
For God's sake.
She's my aunt, Mom.
She's mentally ill.
How desperate do you think I am?
No, that's not what I meant.
I just wanted to be her friend. Nobody
would have anything to do with her.
- That's not true.
- It is.
And it's not her fault. It's mine.
- It wasn't your fault.
- And it was yours.
Does it matter if she moves
furniture around? It's just furniture.
She can't help what she does, Mom,
but you can.
Okay.
We'll talk about this in the morning.
Wait.
You have to tell me
what you did with her.
- What do you mean?
- I went to see how she was.
She's not there, Mom.
Baby?
Baby.
See?
I know how it is
to see someone in that condition.
But Elizabeth is not dying.
She's suffering from catatonia,
which means that her mind...
...has, in effect,
shut down temporarily.
So we're gonna go ahead
and transfer her to the state hospital...
...just until she recovers...
...and we can get
to the bottom of this.
But from what you've told me...
...I would say
that all these changes in her life...
...were simply too much for her.
Have there been difficulties
at home?
She stays in her room, doesn't
socialize and says strange things.
You fight?
Have you ever thought
of residential care?
I'm sorry. I wish we could afford it.
It's just so beautiful.
Yeah, but there's just--
There's just no way.
There's a couple more places
on the list.
Okay.
Well, it's not cheap,
but I think that it--
Well, it's competitive.
What do you think?
If you decide to go with us,
we'd put your sister on the waiting list.
- There's a waiting list?
- Three years.
Well, you haven't been looking
very long, have you?
No, this week.
The psychiatric facilities in this area,
in the state...
...in this whole country, for that matter
are oversubscribed.
There is a last resort.
Board and care.
It's not gonna be on your list.
It's basically a room,
two meals a day...
and some supervision. Some.
Baby?
I'm sorry. I...
It's hard for me to talk
with the drugs.
Oh, I hope Davis doesn't hate me.
I have to say I'm sorry. That's okay.
I'll just-- I'll apologize. I'll--
I'll see him, right?
I'll tell him...
Well...
...that's too bad.
That's too bad.
Will you tell him something for me?
Will you tell him
that all those years...
...I lived with Mom...
...I didn't know
that I was missing anything.
I didn't know. I didn't know anything
until you took me in.
And then I saw everything
that you had.
A house, a job, children.
A man.
And I started to think:
"Why can't I have that?
Why do I have to be alone?
Why do I have to have nobody
and nothing...
...when you have everything?"
Then there he was, Davis.
He was so sweet, he was so kind.
And I just thought,
"Why can't I have him?
Just for one moment.
Just for one kiss. Just one."
It was so, so sweet.
That's not--
That's not fair. I shou--
I shouldn't ask you,
but you're my sister.
You're all I got,
so I want you to tell me.
What, Baby? Tell you what?
Am I so different?
Am I so frightening?
Am I so ugly
that no one's ever gonna want me?
I want you to tell me. Is this all I get?
Is this it for me?
- I'm sorry.
- It's okay.
I'm sorry for crying.
I know. It's okay.
- I don't usually cry, you know?
- I know.
They're releasing Baby
at the end of the week...
...and I'm gonna bring her home.
She knows what she did was wrong
and she's so sorry.
And I don't want her to come here
and mess up our lives again...
...but I just can't send her away.
- We had an agreement, didn't we?
- Yes, but--
- You should stick to it.
- She's taking her meds.
- You forget what she did?
- No.
- I can't.
- What do you want me to do?
Drive downtown,
drop her on a street comer?
- I'm sorry, but she cannot come back.
- It's my house too.
If you bring her back here, Billie...
...I'll leave.
And I'll take the kids with me.
Mom?
Why aren't you at work?
Is school out?
You and Dad had a fight?
He doesn't want Baby to come back.
It's my fault.
I thought it was my fault.
I don't want her to come back either.
I don't want Mollie to call her a freak,
you and Dad to fight.
Sol have this idea.
You wanna hear it?
Yeah.
You take Baby to the ranch.
Aunt Will said
she could come with us, right?
I looked it up.
Maybe she'd shirt remembering
the good times...
...with you and everybody.
It might help her somehow.
I don't exactly know how.
I don't know anything.
Isn't that better
than watching her come back...
...and drop into that chair
and just smoke all day?
- Hey.
I'm--
I'm not gonna bring Baby home.
I thought that would get
your attention.
I'm taking her to the ranch.
Davis can look after Mollie...
...and I'm gonna cook some dinners
and put them in the fridge for you.
Billie.
Call me.
Tell me how it's going, okay?
Okay.
Baby...
...I have something to tell you.
We're not going home.
I'm taking you to Aunt Will's.
- Where?
- The ranch.
You remember the ranch?
I don't wanna--
Look, I won't go near Davis.
I won't bother Mollie.
I could stay up in my room.
Billie?
Welcome to the ranch.
It's been so long.
Baby.
This is Billie and this is you.
And your mom and your dad.
Look how young Kathleen is.
Honey, that's just frogs.
They make such a racket.
They make so much noise.
Hey, look.
Remember this?
You must have been, what...?
About 3.
And look, you could already write
your own name.
Always so smart.
I'm getting kind of tired.
Baby, are you all right?
Yeah, I'll be all right.
And this is what I wanted
to show you.
Remember?
You used to love it here.
All these horses are boarders.
That's how Aunt Will makes her living.
- Hey.
Good boy.
Yeah.
You want to pet him?
Good.
You were such a great rider.
When we were young,
you could ride circles around me.
I was so jealous.
Me?
You wanna go for a ride?
We'll ride together. I'll sheer.
You just hold on.
All right. You can do it.
Put your left foot in the stirrup.
Here, grab the horn.
I won't let you fall. I promise.
Great.
And you put your foot back
in the stirrup.
All right.
Are you ready?
Okay, here we go.
You remember how it feels?
Well...
I don't know. Maybe.
Do you like it?
Yeah.
- Good.
- Yeah, I do.
So I found this at a garage sale...
...and the lady wanted $10 for it
with this broken tail.
There. See?
All better.
- Hello.
- It's me.
Why haven't you called me?
I haven't because I've been--
I don't know. I've been waiting
for something to happen.
Well, what happened?
Baby's better.
You won't recognize her.
Well, that's great, honey.
I think you should come up.
It's really beautiful here.
Aunt Will would love to see the kids
and so would I.
And Baby's getting better.
Yeah, you said that.
Look, I think it's better
if we just wait it out where we are.
I miss you.
Yeah. Look, hey, I gotta run.
- Okay
- Bye.
Nice. Good job.
Oh, my God. I can't believe it.
I missed you so much.
Oh, I'm so happy you're here.
Oh, it's gonna be great.
Wait till you see the horses.
You're gonna love it.
- Hi.
You're amazing.
Hello, Baby.
How you doing?
I'm doing well.
I'm doing really well.
I think it's this place.
I feel like it saved my life.
It's given me my life back.
I'm starting to remember things too.
Did you know your mom
was named after Aunt Will...
...and their real name
is Wilhelmina?
When I was 8 and Billie was 11
we stole two horses and rode off...
...because we didn't wanna
come back home.
It's good.
It's really good.
I think it's this place, you know?
I didn't come here alter I gal: sick
so it's not infected.
Does that sound scaly?
I'm sorry.
I don't wanna scare anyone.
- Anyway...
- Anyway--
Anyway, who wants to go for a ride?
Mollie, you wanna go for a ride?
Can I?
Oh, good. Then I can take you.
I'm gelling really, really so good
at this stuff.
And this one is my favorite.
His name is Chester.
Go to sleep.
- Good night, honey.
- Good night.
- Good night, Davis.
Can I kiss you too?
You're a genius, you know that?
Does it make you uncomfortable
to see her?
- She's so different.
- I know.
- Better.
- Much.
I'm glad.
Me too.
And there is nothing wrong
with you.
- Hey.
Even/body's in bed.
I'll be up in a minute.
I wanna sit here and think for a bit.
This is the best place to think.
And I can think now. I don't have
all those voices in my head.
I have ideas. Ideas.
- Okay, just-
- No, don't. I'm good, Billie.
- I'm so good and you know why?
- The ranch.
Yeah, you know what I'm thinking?
I should slay.
- I should stay here. I wanna stay here.
- Stay here?
It's not a bad idea.
Aunt Will's getting old.
I could help her like I helped Mom.
And no one would have to worry
about me.
I could help with those horses.
Something about those horses.
I'm telling you, this place is magic.
I know. I'm hiking too much,
but I'm excited.
I can remember things...
...but I don't remember
the last time I felt this good.
It's okay for me to feel good, right?
Yeah. Yeah. Of course.
- Just come up to bed soon, all right?
- Okay, Mom.
No, I Will. I Will.
I'm just gonna sit here for a little bit.
I just feel...
...normal.
Okay.
Good night.
Stay there.
Billie, look.
Billie, look at what I'm doing
Isn't it nice?
I know. I know. You don't like it
because you don't like anything I do.
But it doesn't matter anymore
because this is my house.
Oh, Billie. I have something very
very awful to tell you.
Aunt Will...
Aunt Will is dead.
She died in my arms. You weren't
there, like you weren't there for Mom.
Because you were too busy,
in bed with him.
How was he?
She died in my arms, Billie.
In my arms. With her last breath,
she gave me the house.
- Did you stop taking your pills?
- No. No. I didn't forget.
I didn't forget the pills
because they're for your house.
- Not my house.
- Hey, put down the scissors.
You're jealous because my house
is better than your house.
Look. Look at what I can do.
- I can do something I could never do.
- No. No.
Call 911!
Because I have talent and you don't.
- Baby!
- You have no talent.
- Stop!
The faces.
Oh, the faces.
I'm an artist.
- I'm an artist.
- Okay.
Don't you understand? You can't
understand. You couldn't understand.
None of you could understand
except for Davis.
- Davis, you--
- Baby. No.
You-- You get it.
You're sweet, beautiful, smart.
Don't let them take that away.
- Stay right where you are, Davis.
- You wanna help me, Davis?
You can help me with the house
if you want.
I have plenty of it left
and I have so many plans!
- Get to your rooms!
- No. No.
Baby, stop it right now! Stop it!
- You did this to me.
- No.
- You did. You did this to me.
- Stop it. Just shop it.
You did this to me, Billie.
- You did this. You weren't there.
- No.
- Why? Why did you hurt me like that?
- Did I hurt you?
- It's okay.
- Did I chase you away like a dog?
- It's okay. No. Look at me.
- Like a stinking dog?
- No, no.
Get away, mutt.
- You stinking mutt
- Stop.
- Thank God.
Yeah. Run, Billie. Run.
- Stop it! Calm down.
- There's no ambulance.
What did you tell them?
I told them
she was destroying my house.
- No, they're not gonna understand
- Stop it!
- Shut up.
- What's going on?
I hear them.
Oh, I hear them.
They're killing my horses.
Oh, God. They're killing my horses.
- Baby!
- No.
- Stay where you are.
- Don't you dare touch my horses.
- Baby, slop.
Don't hurt her! She's ill!
- Don't you touch them, please.
- On the ground.
- She's crazy.
- No, wait.
- Please don't hurt her.
- Stay back.
- Baby. Don't hurt her. Stop.
- Look at me. Stay back.
- Wait.
- Billie.
- Calm down.
- You're hurting her. Baby!
- Oh, Billie.
They're asleep.
Aunt Will, honey, it's late.
Go to bed, all right?
Look.
Imagine that.
I'm so sorry.
I didn't know what to say to them.
I know. It's okay.
Here.
- All right.
- I got you.
- Thank you.
- There you go.
Well...
How did your mother do it?
All those years?
Good night.
Well, that worked out, didn't it?
You tried.
I tried and I failed.
- Over and over again.
- No, Billie--
I did. I hurt her.
The truth is,
I don't know how to help her.
And I want to.
I want her to be happy
and on that horse...
Oh, she was...
She was my sister again.
Now she's--
She's just that crazy woman.
And I miss her.
Today at ballet,
someone sprained their ankle.
We thought she sprained her ankle.
But she actually broke it.
She has to get surgery now.
She went to the hospital.
She was the best dancer
in the class.
And she was the lead in the show.
Honey, you sleeping?
No.
Are you?
No, I'm just thinking.
I know she can't stay here.
She needs--
Professional help.
Yeah.
I think that's what we should do.
But...
...can we afford it?
We'll work it out.
You would do that for her?
Yeah, for her.
And for us.
Baby, I have something to tell you.
And I want you to listen.
Are you listening?
Baby?
Elizabeth.
You can't stay here.
That's the decision.
But it isn't a punishment.
It's a reward.
I don't want any reward.
Remember at the ranch...
...you said if you could just stay there,
that you would feel normal again?
- I don't remember.
- Yes, you do.
You were so excited.
You wanted it more than anything,
didn't you?
Well, we'd like to take you to a place
that could give you that.
- What kind of a place?
- It's a beautiful place.
It's like a college campus.
- A nuthouse
- No.
It's a place that can give you a life.
That's what you want, isn't it?
But I wanna stay here.
But what would you do
if you stayed here?
You would sit in that chair.
So what? What does it matter?
- It doesn't matter.
- It matters to me.
It's my job...
...to help you get what you need.
It was Mom's job for all those years.
And it's my job now.
And I'm telling you...
...that you can't stay here.
You have to go to a place...
...that will make you have a life.
Okay?
I'm afraid.
Me too.
May I?
Goodbye, Baby.
I'll come visit you.
I'll call you, okay?
I have something
I wanna show you.
- I'll stay here.
- Okay.