[upbeat mariachi music]
- ♪ SINGING IN SPANISH ♪
♪ CONTINUED SINGING ♪
♪ SINGING IN SPANISH ♪
♪ SINGING CONTINUES ♪
♪
- NO IFS, ANDS, OR BUTS, OKAY?
I'M GOING TO.
SPEAKING SPANISH
- QUESTION IN SPANISH
- ANSWERS IN SPANISH
- SPEAKING SPANISH
[engine rumbling]
[atmospheric percussive music]
♪
[radio fuzzing in and out]
- ONLY THE FEMALE
OF THE SPECIES HAS THE GOODS.
- WHAT'S ANY OF THIS HAVE TO DO
WITH GETTING HIGH?
I MEAN, WE WERE TALKING ABOUT...
[angry chanting and yelling]
- STOP THE KILLING!
- ANIMALS ARE PEOPLE TOO!
- I HOPE YOU CHOKE ON THE BONES!
- TOFU LICKER!
- MR. AND MS. GRAVES.
- WHAT'S WITH THE TREE HUGGERS?
- HOW ARE YOU, SIR?
- AGAINST EATING MEAT.
- MUST NOT BE FROM AROUND HERE.
[phone ringing]
- WE'RE HERE.
- VERY WELL.
- YOU'LL HAVE TO EXCUSE ME.
- BARBIE'S A SLUT.
OH, I'M MADLY
IN LOVE WITH HER.
I CAN'T HELP IT.
SHE GIVES ME BLOW JOBS
IN THE PARKING LOT
BEFORE SCHOOL.
- SHE'S NOT SUPPOSED
TO BE BACK HERE, SHIT LIPS.
- UM, EXCUSE ME?
- DON'T BE COCK BLOCKIN', DUDE.
- THIS ONE'S CRIME SPREE-CRAZY,
BIRTHDAY BOY.
TRUST ME.
IT'S GONNA END IN TEARS.
- OH, I KNOW.
THAT'S NOT THE BEST PART.
SOMETIMES SHE LETS
MY FRIENDS WATCH.
- A LIVE SEX ACT.
IT'S A ONCE-IN-A-LIFETIME
OPPORTUNITY.
- SENATOR.
NICE TO SEE YOU.
- THANKS FOR ALL YOUR SUPPORT.
- IT'S YOUR LIFE, LITTLE DUDE.
- IF YOU WANT TO DO SOMETHING
AND YOU DON'T,
YOU'RE A PUSSY.
[upbeat mariachi music]
♪
[man singing in Spanish]
[radio fuzzing in and out]
- GONZALES CALLED
THE RECENT UPTICK IN ABDUCTIONS
OF YOUNG GIRLS IN SAN ANTONIO
A FLUKE AND DISMISSED IT.
- WHY NOT?
GIVE ME ONE GOOD REASON.
YOU KNOW YOU WANT TO.
YOU'RE JUST A CHICKEN.
[clucking]
PUSSY.
- YOU KNOW WHAT THIS IS ABOUT?
IT'S 'CAUSE I WOULDN'T GO
FOR A THREESOME
WITH HER AND SOME DUDE
SHE MET ONLINE.
- THERE'S HOPE.
- WHAT?
LIFE IS SHIT, AND THEN YOU DIE.
I DON'T WANT TO READ
ABOUT SHIT IN SOME BOOK.
I WANT TO DO SHIT.
- OH, I'M SURE YOU'LL
MAKE US ALL VERY PROUD.
- OH, EAT ME, BITCH.
IT'S A FREE COUNTRY.
I CAN DO WHATEVER
THE HELL I WANT.
- MIKEY, DO SOMETHING.
SLAP HIM AROUND.
WHATEVER IT TAKES.
- HEY, UM, KENNY.
THERE'S NO SUCH THING
AS A FREE LUNCH.
- AND DON'T YOU
FUCKING FORGET IT, KENNY BOY.
- [chuckles]
- I KNOW YOU.
I'VE SEEN YOU BEFORE.
- YEAH.
REAL FANCY DINNER
AT THE WHITE HOUSE.
- [scoffs]
YOU SAID YOU WAS IN A HURRY.
- YOU'RE NOT TOO BIG
FOR MAMA TO SPANK YOUR BUTT,
MR. SMARTY PANTS.
- [blows raspberry]
- AH, AH, AH.
- WELL, HEY.
YOU KNOW YOU WANT TO.
- RIGHT.
- STAY OUT OF TROUBLE.
- [clucking]
- SHE'S ON HER GAME.
SO WHAT'S THE DEAL?
- I DON'T KNOW.
JUST GOIN' WITH IT.
- YEAH?
- WHATEVER HAPPENS HAPPENS.
- THAT'S GOOD
OR BAD.
[doorbell chiming]
- [laughs]
- ANYBODY GOT ANY ECSTASY?
- I DON'T KNOW.
- SISSY, THAT YOUR BOYFRIEND?
- SHH!
- WHY'S YOUR SISTER ALWAYS HAVE
TO GO OUT WITH NERDS?
- WHY IS THAT EVERY TIME
WE GO OUT,
YOU GET ME IN TROUBLE?
- 'CAUSE YOU'RE A NERD.
BESIDES, YOU ONLY LIVE ONCE.
- YEAH, AND YOU ONLY
DIE ONCE TOO.
- AH, SHIT.
- I LOVE YOU TOO.
- DUDE.
- OH, SHIT.
NOT AGAIN.
LET'S GO!
- OH, LET ME CALL YOU
RIGHT BACK.
GUYS, WHAT THE HELL IS GOING ON?
- GO! GO!
- TRY ME!
BRING IT ON, BITCHES!
- YEAH?
HERE WE GO!
- FUCK YOU, BITCH!
[metal squealing]
- BITCH, I'LL KILL YOU!
I'LL SHOOT YOU IN THE DAMN HEAD!
FUCK!
- ♪ BABY, COME ON
[tires squealing]
- THAT'S WHAT THEY GET
FOR GRABBING MY ASS.
- BARBIE, WHAT DID YOU DO?
- FUCK YOU!
- OUTRAGEOUSLY COOL.
WAY FUCKING COOL.
- WATCH THE ROAD!
[horn blaring]
- WHAT FUCKING RULE
DID I BREAK NOW?
[tires squealing]
- I WANT THIS BITCH.
THIS BITCH IS MINE.
- IT'S GONNA BE FUCKING EPIC!
- LET'S FUCKING GET THIS BITCH!
- WHOO!
- PUNCH IT!
- MY FATHER IS GONNA BEAT
THE SHIT OUT OF ME
WITH HIS BARE HANDS.
- DON'T WORRY ABOUT THAT SHIT.
LET'S GO.
- FUCK IT, MAN.
FUCK IT! FUCK IT!
I DON'T CARE.
[honking horn]
- OOH, THEY'RE CHASING US.
[laughs]
- [laughing]
YES!
[horn honking]
- DUDE, STEP ON IT!
- GO, GO, GO, GO!
LOOK NOW!
- KENNY, CAN YOU CHILL
THE FUCK OUT?
- [snarls]
- WHAT ARE THEY DOING?
- THEY'RE GONNA HIT US.
- SHIT.
- GO FASTER.
- COME ON, DRIVE!
- SHIT, SHIT, SHIT.
- [bellows]
- GET UP ON IT!
DAMN!
- I'M GOING AS FAST AS I CAN.
- DUDE, I FUCKIN' HATE YOUR CAR.
GO FASTER.
- [bellows]
[bells clanging]
[tires squealing]
- IN YOUR DREAMS, BITCHES!
- STOP.
- GOT ME SOME TITTIES, BABY!
- WHOO!
- I'M LOVIN' IT!
I'M LOVIN' IT!
- TITTIES!
- YEAH, BITCH!
YOU'RE DEAD.
WHOO!
- [clapping]
- NO, NO.
NO!
- DUDE!
- OH, SH--
[dog yelps]
- WHAT'D IT HIT?
- THINK IT WAS A DOG.
[pounding on car]
[engine rumbling]
[aggressive rock music]
♪
- HEY, HEY, HEY.
THEY'RE FOLLOWING US.
- OH, SHIT.
- THIS IS NOT GOOD.
THIS IS NOT GOOD.
THIS IS BAD.
- OKAY, KENNY, LITTLE DUDE.
TURN OFF THE LIGHTS
AND MAKE A RIGHT.
GO.
- I DON'T WANT TO DIE.
- NOW, NOW!
- IT WOULD REALLY SUCK
TO BE DEAD RIGHT NOW.
[tires squealing]
THINK WE LOST THEM?
- OH, HEY, GUYS.
SORRY ABOUT THE DOG.
THERE WAS THIS GIRL,
AND IT WAS AN ACCIDENT,
AND ANYWAY, UM, HOW MUCH
DO YOU THINK WOULD BUY A NEW DOG
AND, LIKE, A NEW BUMPER?
WHOA, WHOA!
TIME OUT, GUYS.
KING'S "X," OKAY?
NOBODY HAS TO GET HURT HERE.
LOOK, I'M GONNA CALL 911,
ALL RIGHT?
EVERYTHING'S GONNA BE FINE.
OW!
DUDE!
[grunts]
[moans]
WHAT THE FUCK ARE YOU DOING,
DUDE?
GET THE FUCK AWAY--OW!
[crunching]
OW!
[screaming]
[grunts]
DUDE!
I WASN'T EVEN DRIVING!
IT WAS HIM!
[screams]
- [grunting]
[crunching]
I CAN'T FEEL MY LEG--
[grunts]
I THINK I'M PARALYZED.
[sobbing]
- KENNY, SLOW DOWN, LITTLE DUDE.
- DON'T CALL ME "LITTLE DUDE."
- [laughs]
WE LOST THEM.
- LET'S JUST KEEP DRIVING TILL
WE REACH CIVILIZATION, OKAY?
[chain saw revving]
- PROBLEM, BOYS?
- HE'S AWFULLY BIG.
[chain saw revving]
- [laughing]
FUCKIN' TOURIST!
SEE THE LOOK IN HIS EYES?
[laughs]
- I HATE PAIN.
I THINK ABOUT IT ALL THE TIME.
I THINK ABOUT ALL THE WAYS
THAT I DON'T WANT TO DIE.
- ♪ THEY WERE LAUGHING
♪ SINGIN', DANCIN'
- SOMETIMES I THINK ABOUT
WHAT IT WOULD BE LIKE
IF A TERRORIST CUT MY HEAD OFF
WITH ELECTRIC SCISSORS.
- MIKEY, STOP.
- WHAT?
I'M JUST SAYING--
OKAY.
- IT'S ALL RIGHT.
- OKAY.
- COME ON.
- I HAVE NO IDEA WHERE WE'RE AT.
- DOESN'T THIS THING
HAVE A G.P.S. OR SOMETHING?
- SEE, THERE'S THE FREEWAY.
WE KNOW WHERE WE ARE.
IT'S GONNA BE ALL RIGHT,
BABY BRO.
ALL RIGHT?
TRUST ME.
IT'S OVER.
- OKAY.
OKAY.
- THANK YOU.
WE'RE GOING HOME.
- BUT THERE ARE SOME BAD GUYS
THAT ARE FOR REAL.
I HEARD ABOUT THESE GUYS
THAT BREAK ALL YOUR BONES...
- MIKEY, STOP.
- AND THAT'S HOW THEY KILL YOU.
- I SAY WE BURN A DOOBIE.
THAT WAS INTENSE.
[engine rumbles]
OH, SHIT.
[metal clanging and scraping]
- SHIT.
FUCK.
- OH, MIKEY, ARE YOU OKAY?
WHAT ARE THEY DOING?
- OH, FUCK.
WE'RE FUCKED.
- OH, MY GOD.
TURN ON THE CAR.
- OH, FUCK!
- IT WON'T START.
IT WON'T START!
[all yelling and screaming]
[engine rumbling]
- ARE YOU OKAY?
[engine revving]
- [whispers inaudibly]
GUARANTEED.
- BULLSHIT.
[engine revving]
- COME ON, WE GOT TO GO!
- IT'S FINE.
I COULD USE A GOOD SNACK.
- SHE LOOKS LIKE A TASTY PIECE.
- NOT A TASTE, NOT A SCRATCH.
- THE FUCK ARE YOU?
I'M RIGHT, AND YOU KNOW IT.
- YOU KNOW, WE DIDN'T HIT
THEIR FUCKING DOG.
THIS IS BULLSHIT.
- KENNY, NO.
COME ON.
LEAVE HER DUMB ASS.
- FUCK YOU, BITCH.
THEY'RE NOT GONNA DO ANYTHING.
LOOK.
- WHAT THE FUCK, MAN?
- SHIT.
- KENNY!
- WAIT, WAIT, WAIT.
THIS WAY.
LET'S GO.
- [sniffing]
[spits]
- [panting]
- [sniffing]
[both panting]
- FUCK IT.
I'M NOT RUNNING.
THEY'RE GONNA CATCH US.
YOU BETTER START THINKING
ABOUT WHAT YOU'RE GONNA DO.
- I'M NOT WAITING AROUND
TO GET MY BUTT KICKED.
- PAY THEM.
YOUR PARENTS HAVE MONEY.
PAY THEM WHATEVER THEY WANT.
WHAT DO YOU CARE?
- ARE YOU SERIOUS?
- YEAH.
- THIS IS STUPID.
COME ON.
- WHATEVER.
- LET'S GO.
- I'M FUCKIN' STAYIN' HERE.
- COME ON.
- DON'T BE SUCH A PUSSY.
- YOU KNOW WHAT?
YOU'RE RIGHT.
I'M CHICKEN.
WHATEVER.
- KENNY...
PUSSY.
[slow footsteps]
- HI.
- [sniffs]
[cracks neck]
- LOOK, I'M SORRY
ABOUT YOUR FUCKING DOG.
IT WAS THAT OTHER CAR, OKAY?
[gagging]
[screams]
- I'M HISTORY.
- FUCK, I GOT TO CHANGE
MY FUCKING SERVICE.
- SAN ANTONIO 911.
WHAT'S YOUR--
HELLO, YES?
YES, SOME GUYS ARE CHASING US.
- MA'AM?
- THEY RAMMED OUR CAR
OFF THE ROAD.
I THINK THEY'RE TRYING
TO KILL US.
- WHAT'S YOUR LOCATION?
- NO, NO.
I HAVE NO IDEA WHERE WE ARE.
- MA'AM.
- [screaming]
LET GO OF ME, YOU FUCKER!
LET GO!
[screams]
LET GO OF ME!
[screaming]
- [grunts]
- KENNY, GET UP!
PLEASE, GET UP!
THOSE PEOPLE
AREN'T MY FRIENDS...
- GET OFF OF HER!
- IF THAT'S WHAT YOU THINK.
- [grunts]
- FUCKING PRICK.
- LIKE HOW THAT FEELS?
HUH?
JUST A LITTLE PUSSY.
- [sobs]
- OOH.
OUCH.
WHERE IS THE JUNK?
- THE FUCK SHOULD I KNOW?
- [panting]
CAN YOU HEAR ME?
[screams]
- PLEASE!
- HEY, YOU WANT A COOKIE?
HUH?
MMM!
WAIT, WAIT, WAIT,
WAIT, WAIT, WAIT!
I CAN'T KEEP UP.
LOOK, HEY, I'VE GOT COOKIES!
COME ON, I'M GONNA--
[gagging]
[crunching]
- WAIT, WAIT, WAIT!
I'M 17.
IT'S MY BIRTHDAY.
CUT ME A LITTLE SLACK.
DUDE, MY PARENTS ARE LOADED.
THEY LOVE MY SORRY ASS.
- TELL ME ABOUT YOUR FRIENDS.
- WHAT?
[grunts]
[gasps]
[cell phone ringing]
[coughing]
- IT WAS NICE KNOWING YOU.
YEAH.
NO.
- STOP!
NO, NO, NO, NO!
PLEASE!
- NO.
NO, NO, NO, NO, NO.
YOU'VE GONE TOO FAR.
NO.
NO, YOU'VE GONE TOO FAR.
YEAH.
- [panting]
- WHAT IF THEY CATCH US?
WHAT DO WE DO?
- SAN ANTONIO 911.
- WHAT CAN WE DO?
- SHUT--
- I'M SCARED, SISSY.
I'M REALLY SCARED.
- YES!
YES, HELLO.
YES, PLEASE, YOU NEED TO HURRY.
- WHAT'S YOUR LOCATION, MA'AM?
- I DON'T KNOW.
THERE'S NO--
THERE'S STREET SIGNS ANYWHERE.
[crunching]
- MA'AM?
MA'AM, ARE YOU OKAY?
- [grunts]
- [yells]
- MA'AM?
- [grunting]
NO!
- PLEASE RESPOND.
PLEASE RESPOND.
PLEASE RESPOND
IF YOU CAN HEAR ME.
[smacking]
- [shrieks]
[panting]
MIKEY?
COME ON, WE GOT TO GO.
LET'S GO.
[sobbing]
- DON'T LET THEM CATCH YOU.
- PLEASE.
I'M NOT GONNA LEAVE YOU HERE.
- I CAN'T SEE.
- [whimpering]
WAIT, MIKEY.
I LOVE YOU.
[bawling]
[cell phone rings]
[shrieks]
- HELL AM I?
HELL ARE YOU?
IT'S OKAY.
- I'LL GET YOU.
ALL OF YOU!
- NO, NO, NO, NO.
IT'S COOL.
LOOK, HERE.
THIS IS FOR YOU.
- NO!
- YOU CAN HAVE
ANYTHING YOU WANT!
- [panting]
[cell phone ringing]
[gunshot]
[gunshots]
- SO WHERE'S THE JUNK?
- [panting]
LEAVE ME THE FUCK ALONE!
[gasps]
[cat yowling]
[cat hisses]
[gunshot]
- BITCH!
[clears throat]
[spits]
[sniffing]
NO AMOUNT OF CAT SHIT'S
GONNA SAVE YOUR ASS.
YOU KNOW WHY?
[cat yowling]
YOU KNOW WHAT YOU SMELL LIKE?
YOU SMELL LIKE
A FUCKIN' TWINKIE.
[rustling]
- [panting]
[door squealing]
- TWINKIE, TWINKIE, TWINKIE.
THINKIN' ABOUT YOU, TWINKIE.
[clattering]
I'LL SNIFF YOU OUT.
[sniffing]
[banging]
[yells]
BITCH!
YOU THINK YOU'RE GONNA
GET OUT OF HERE?
NEVER GONNA HAPPEN.
- [shrieks]
WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?
YOU'RE TOTALLY HOT.
YOU'RE NOT GONNA HURT ME, RIGHT?
JUST LET ME GO.
WHAT'S YOUR DEAL?
thwack!
[siren chirping]
- [panting]
[engine turns over]
[siren blips]
STOP!
[tires squealing]
WAIT!
WAIT.
[sobbing]
[majestic classical music]
♪
- LITTLE GIRL.
- [screams]
[thumping hip-hop music]
♪
- WHAT YOU LOOKIN' FOR,
MAMACITA?
- I NEED HELP, PLEASE.
[all muttering]
NO, WAIT!
WAIT!
[yelps]
[bells clanging]
[train horn blaring]
[panting]
[clattering]
[train horn blaring]
[door rattling]
[yelps]
[panting]
[shrieks]
[gate clattering]
[panting and screaming]
- I'M DONE
PLAYING HIDE-AND-GO-SEEK.
[grunts]
[laughing]
RELAX.
I'M NOT GONNA HURT YOU.
- [screams]
- [straining and grunting]
[laughs]
YOU REALLY ATE YOUR SPINACH
THIS MORNING.
YOU MUST REALLY LIKE
YOUR VEGGIES.
[laughs]
WHOA!
[yelling]
[lock clicks]
[panting]
[bellows]
[cracks neck]
[phone beeps]
FANNIN BUILDING.
FOURTH FLOOR.
[radio fuzzing in and out]
- REPORTS OF A YOUNG WOMAN
THROWN FROM A MOVING VEHICLE,
SAN ANTONIO POLICE DETAINED
THEN RELEASED CHILEAN DIPLOMAT--
- PRELIMINARY REPORTS INDICATE
AN ATTEMPT HAD BEEN MADE
TO SURGICALLY REMOVE
THE VICTIM'S VITAL ORGANS
PRIOR TO HER BEING THROWN
FROM THE VEHICLE.
DIOS, WHO HAS
DIPLOMATIC IMMUNITY,
WAS IN SAN ANTONIO
FOR THE PAN-AMERICAN
TRADE CONFERENCE.
[bright music]
♪
- [whimpering]
[lightly tapping and scratching]
[thumping]
[yelps]
- AIN'T NO WAY OUT OF THERE.
- [panting]
- A LITTLE BIRDIE TOLD ME
YOU'RE A TRICKY GIRL.
IS THAT RIGHT?
ARE YOU A TRICKY GIRL?
[clattering]
HEY!
OH, TRICKY, TRICKY,
TRICKY, TRICKY!
- [panting]
- YOU LIKE LITTLE BABIES?
HUH?
LITTLE TINY BABIES?
- [yelps]
- TRICKY, TRICKY, TRICKY,
TRICKY, TRICKY, TRICKY!
- [panting]
[rustling and clattering]
[panting]
[flame ignites]
- [chuckles]
- I'M NOT PROUD.
I'LL CALL DIBS ON THAT SHIT.
- HEY.
WHO I.D.'D THE JUNK?
- YOU KNOW, OLLIE, ONE DAY
YOU'RE GONNA BECOME A MONSTER.
- AND WHAT ARE YOU,
A FUCKING RABBIT?
- THERE'S NO TELLING
WHAT'S IN THAT SHIT.
- EXCUSE ME.
IS ANYONE LISTENING?
I KNOW PLENTY OF CUTE GIRLS
IF YOU WANT TO MEET CUTE GIRLS.
- WHO MADE YOU BOSSBOY?
- THIS IS HOW IT'S GOING DOWN.
THAT SHIT IS TOXIC.
YOU KNOW THAT, RIGHT?
ENOUGH OF THAT SHIT,
AND YOU TURN
INTO A FUCKING AMPHEAD.
- IT'S MY TIME TO GO FIRST.
- HEY, AMPHEAD'S COOL.
- AMPHEAD'S A MESS.
- [snarls]
- IF YOU CAN'T WAIT
FOR THE GOOD SHIT,
SHE'S ALL FUCKING YOURS.
- WELL, THE KID'S UP!
KID'S UP.
THE KID'S UP!
- NOT COOL.
NOT COOL.
- [panting]
- [yelping]
GET OFF OF ME, FUCKER!
- COME GET SOME, DUDE!
[torch hissing]
[wood creaking]
- I WOULD HAVE GIVEN
ALL OF YOU BLOW JOBS,
BUT FORGET IT!
- [chuckles]
- LET'S SEE WHAT YOU GOT.
- [yelps]
[grunts]
WHAT?
ARE YOU GAY?
[shrieks]
[screaming]
GET OFF OF ME, FUCKER!
- [growling]
- [screaming]
[torch hissing]
[snarling and smacking]
- FUCKING JUNKIES.
THIS IS DISGUSTING.
ENOUGH.
STOP.
- [yips]
[pounding]
[snarling and smacking]
- ENOUGH!
[gunshot]
- I HAVE DYNAMITE.
I'M COMING OUT.
- BLOCK HER EXIT.
BLOCK HER EXIT.
- [panting]
- HEY.
- GET BACK.
- THERE'S BEEN A MISTAKE.
I APOLOGIZE.
I KNOW THIS LOOKS BAD.
I'M JUST TRYING TO HELP YOU.
- GET BACK.
- YOU HAVE A SHORT FUSE.
YOU'LL LIKE BENNY.
ALL RIGHT, LITTLE GIRL.
MOVE OUT OF HER WAY, JUNKIES.
GO ON.
GO.
[chuckles]
ANDALE!
- [whimpers]
[gate clattering]
- YUM, YUM, YUM!
- YOU'RE MINE, KID!
[all laughing and whooping]
- TRICKY, TRICKY, TRICKY,
TRICKY, TRICKY!
[elevator rumbling
and squealing]
- [sobbing]
- STAY PUT.
YEAH.
- COME ON!
[snarling and panting]
[gate clattering]
- [yelling]
- [screams]
[whimpering]
NO!
[panting]
[shrieks]
- NOT YET.
- [whimpering]
[engine rumbling]
[aggressive rock music]
HELP!
HELP ME!
- ISN'T THAT THAT GIRL?
- HELP!
HELP!
- THAT'S HER.
I LOOKED RIGHT AT HER.
YOU SAW HER.
- DO NOT FUCK
WITH THOSE PEOPLE, PERIOD.
YOU KNOW DAMN WELL.
- THEY KILLED MY BROTHER!
- DAMN IT, MAN.
SHE CALLED 911.
YOU KNOW WHAT
THEY'RE GONNA DO TO HER.
- WHAT THE HELL
ARE YOU LOOKIN' AT?
- LISTEN HERE.
I GOT A WIFE, AN EX-WIFE,
AND TWO FUCKIN' KIDS.
WE'RE GONNA TAKE THIS SHOW
ON THE ROAD.
- PLEASE HELP ME!
PLEASE!
I SAW YOU!
PLEASE HELP ME.
- MESSAGE RECEIVED?
- I GET IT.
[police radio chatter]
- PLEASE!
- I DON'T LIKE IT.
- I DON'T GIVE A SHIT.
- I SAW YOU!
[whimpering]
- LET'S GO.
- THAT'S THE WAY IT IS.
[engine rumbling]
- COME ON, LITTLE BUDDY.
AH, MAXIE, YOU'RE SO GOOD.
[engine rumbling]
- STOP, STOP, STOP, STOP.
- WHAT?
- [whimpering]
- AH, AH, AH.
- YEAH, IT'S GONNA GET
COLD OUTSIDE.
- YOU LIKE SEX, RIGHT?
WITH YOUR BOYFRIEND?
- HOW MUCH FOR THE DOG?
- OH, HE'S NOT FOR SALE.
- WHAT KIND OF DOG IS THAT?
- HE'S MY BABY.
- GO TO HELL.
- YOU'RE VEGAN.
- WHY DON'T WE TALK ABOUT YOU?
- WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
- WHAT'S YOUR NAME?
- COME HERE.
- WHAT THE HELL ARE YOU DOING?
- I WANT TO PET HIM.
- GET AWAY FROM HIM!
- GET OFF!
FUCKIN' WORTHLESS OLD JOKE.
- WHAT THE FUCK
ARE YOU DOING WITH MY DOG?
GIVE ME BACK MY DOG!
- HEY!
DICKHEAD!
- DICKHEAD!
- WHAT THE HELL ARE YOU DOING?
- FUCKING KILL YOU!
- GIVE ME BACK MY DOG!
- IT'S COMING.
IT'S FUCKING COMING.
- BUT NOT YET.
RIGHT, LITTLE BUDDY?
- WHAT THE HELL ARE YOU DOING?
- I'M NOT YOUR FUCKING BUDDY.
DON'T CALL ME LITTLE BUDDY.
- [laughs]
- HEY!
GIVE ME BACK MY DOG!
MAX!
[dog snarling]
- OW!
GOD DAMN IT!
AH!
[dog yipping]
WHAT?
- AN AMBER ALERT
IS IN EFFECT
FOR 17-YEAR-OLD
ANGELICA MORALES.
MORALES WAS ABDUCTED
FROM THE PARKING LOT
OF A SOUTH SIDE
CONVENIENCE STORE
LATE THIS AFTERNOON.
WITNESSES REPORTED SEEING
A SUSPICIOUS-LOOKING
LATE MODEL BROWN VAN
AT THE SITE.
[muffled metal music]
♪
- ♪ THE HIGH HAWK KNOWS
WHERE THE RABBIT GOES ♪
♪ AND THE BUZZARD
MARKS THE KILL ♪
♪ BUT FEW THERE BE
WITH EYES TO SEE ♪
♪ THE TALL MEN RIDING STILL
♪ WE HARK IN VAIN
ON THE SPEEDING TRAIN ♪
♪ FOR AN ECHO
OF HOOFBEAT THUNDER ♪
♪ AND THE YELLOW WHEAT
IS A WINDING SHEET ♪
♪ FOR CATTLE TRAILS
PLOWED UNDER ♪
- EVERYONE OUT OF THE CAR.
WHAT'S UP, DOC?
- OH, NOW HE THINKS
HE'S A COMEDIAN.
- COME ON.
LET'S GO!
- WHERE ARE WE?
- LET'S GO. LET'S GO.
LET'S GO. LET'S GO.
- WHERE ARE WE?
- LET'S GO.
- DON'T TOUCH ME!
- COME ON!
GOD, YOU ARE SOMETHING ELSE.
- THE FUCK YOU THINK
YOU'RE GOIN', FATSO?
- WHAT ARE YOU GONNA DO, HUH?
- WHY, YOU SHIT BIRDS
ARE GONNA STAY RIGHT THERE.
[zapping]
- [spits]
- FUCK YOU, MAN.
HOLD YOUR HORSES, BUTTERNUT.
[clears throat]
- [whimpering]
- COME ON.
AH, AH, AH, AH, AH.
COME OVER HERE.
COME HERE.
WHY DON'T YOU STAY AWHILE?
STAY.
- YO, THIS IS BULLSHIT.
WE SCORED THE JUNK.
- OH, I AM MOVED
TO FUCKIN' TEARS.
[cackles]
- NEWBOY.
WHY DON'T YOU COME HERE
FOR A SECOND?
- IT'S COMING!
IT'S FUCKING COMIN'!
IT'S COMIN' NOW!
[zapping]
- I LOVE YOU TOO.
LET'S GO, PRINCESS!
- OH, AND THE REST
OF YOU SHIT EATERS,
YOU CAN KISS MY RUBY RED!
[both yelling]
- NOT COOL!
NOT FUCKING COOL.
- [jabbering]
- OKAY, HERE WE GO.
LET'S GO DOWN.
ONE, TWO, ONE, TWO, ONE, TWO.
WELCOME HOME, BABY GIRL.
- [screams]
- [spits]
YOU DO NOT WANT
TO FUCK WITH ME RIGHT NOW!
LET'S GO!
ONE, TWO, ONE, TWO.
WALK!
LET'S GO!
- [sobbing]
[zapping]
[women babbling and wailing]
- SORRY.
WASN'T MY FAULT, I SWEAR!
- DOC, IS EVERYTHING SET UP?
- IT'S ALL SET UP.
- BOSSIE, PLEASE.
FUCKIN' BASTARD!
COME BACK!
DON'T LEAVE ME HERE!
- I WANT TO GET TO WORK ON THIS
RIGHT AWAY, OKAY?
- [moaning]
- I ATE YOUR MOTHER
ON YOUR BIRTHDAY, SHIT BIRD.
- [snarling and yelling]
[zapping]
- GOD DAMN IT!
DAMN IT!
[zapping]
- [screaming]
NO!
[zapping]
- YOU MAKE IT HAPPEN.
YOU!
[zapping]
[laughter]
- [wailing]
- WHAT'S THE MATTER?
[shouting indistinctly]
[zapping]
- [moans]
- [gasps]
- MOVE IT, YOU LITTLE SHIT BIRD!
[zapping]
- AH!
DAMN IT!
- GET OVER THERE.
GET OVER THERE.
SHIT.
WELL, AIN'T YOU THE ONE,
LITTLE BITCH?
HOLD REAL STILL.
WE DON'T WANT NOTHING BAD
TO HAPPEN.
OPEN UP.
RELAX.
- [screaming]
- UP WE GO.
THERE.
AIN'T THAT NICE?
- [whimpering]
- [cackles]
YOU MIGHT WANT TO THINK TWICE
ABOUT ALL THAT WIGGLING AROUND.
- [whimpering]
NOW THIS COULD BE
A LITTLE COLD TO THE TOUCH.
- [whimpering]
- RELAX.
TAKE A DEEP BREATH.
HOLD IT.
[squishing]
- [whimpering]
[shrieking]
- THERE.
NOW, IT'S NOT ALL THAT BAD,
IS IT?
- AMPHEAD'S OUT OF CONTROL.
- NEVER STAND BEHIND ME
WHILE I'M WORKING, SHITBIRD.
- [screaming]
- [cackles]
[whimpering and shrieking]
- LEAVE HER ALONE, ASSHOLES!
[indistinct yelling]
- YOU FUCKING ASSHOLE!
- [moaning deeply]
[chains clattering]
[snarling]
- [laughing]
- [snarling]
- OH, HO, SHE'S THE ONE.
SHE'S THE ONE.
ASSHOLE.
- [snarling]
- [yelps]
- [roaring]
[chains rattling]
[bellowing]
- WHAT THE FUCK IS THIS?
- WHAT ARE YOU?
DUMB?
ILLITERATE?
GETTING TOO OLD?
NEED YOUR READING GLASSES?
- WHO ARE YOU PEOPLE?
- FUCK DO YOU THINK
YOU'RE TALKING TO?
- [bellowing]
- DON'T BRING JUNK DOWN HERE.
- I'M JUST FUCKING WITH YOU.
- [roars]
- WHAT YOU LOOKIN' AT, DARLIN'?
HUH?
AIN'T NO PLACE TO GO.
THIS IS IT.
- WHO ARE YOU PEOPLE?
WHY ARE YOU DOING THIS?
- SHUT UP.
- [roars]
- TRUST ME.
YOU DON'T WANT TO KNOW.
- THE GENERAL PUBLIC
DOES NOT WANT TO HEAR THAT SHIT.
- [roaring]
- YOU THINK YOU WANT TO KNOW?
- I PROPOSE A BURGUNDY.
- YOU DO NOT WANT THAT SHIT
INSIDE YOUR HEAD.
THAT IS SOME DISGUSTING SHIT.
- MODEST BUT EXQUISITE.
- SO I SUGGEST
YOU TAKE MY ADVICE
AND YOU SHUT YOUR DAMN YAP.
- OR WHAT?
YOU GONNA KILL ME?
- [scoffs]
- YOU'RE GONNA EAT ME?
[laughter]
- I FURTHER SUGGEST
YOU USE
YOUR GODDAMN IMAGINATION!
- [snarls]
THAT'S NOT THE BOY NEXT DOOR.
YOU THINK YOU'VE SEEN SOME SHIT?
- [bellows]
- [laughs]
YOU AIN'T EVEN BEEN
TO KINDERGARTEN.
- I DON'T REALLY GIVE A FUCK!
[laughter]
- [roars]
- THE HELL'S MY BLOOD WORK?
- IT'LL BE HERE
WHEN IT GETS HERE.
- WHAT KILLED THE CAT?
WHAT KILLED THE CAT?
- WHAT IS THAT?
WHAT DO YOU WANT?
- [roars]
- IT IS A BUSINESS.
THAT'S WHAT WE'RE HERE FOR.
WE'RE ABOUT PROVIDING QUALITY
AND A VALUE
FOR OUR CLIENTS.
OF COURSE, THERE'S THE SOCIAL
AND ECONOMIC GOOD.
I CAN REFER YOU
TO THE LITERATURE IF YOU'D LIKE.
- SHUT YOUR FUCKING PIEHOLE,
YOU ASS-WIPE COCK JUNKIE!
- WHAT BUSINESS?
WHAT LITERATURE?
YOU'RE BUTCHERS!
- [bellows]
- BUTCHERS.
BUTCHERS?
WELL, MAYBE IN THE LITERAL SENSE
OF THE WORD.
YOU HAVE A POINT.
- KISS MY PEKINGESE ASS!
AND BRING ON THE MARCHING BAND!
WHOO-HOO!
- [bellowing]
- [laughing]
- MUST WE BEHAVE LIKE YAHOOS?
PLEASE.
THIS IS RIDICULOUS.
IT'S ABSOLUTELY ABSURD.
YOU WANT TO KNOW WHAT THIS IS?
THESE GUYS ARE FIENDS.
THEY'RE ADDICTS.
THEY'RE JUNKIES.
NO WAY TO LIVE!
- YEAH.
- IT'S NO WAY TO LIVE.
- YOU KNOW WHAT?
I'M TIRED OF YOUR PUNK ASS.
- LITTLE BUDDY!
- OH, HO!
- THAT'S WHAT THEY CALL YOU,
RIGHT?
- [chuckling]
- INTERESTING.
- YOU'RE AFRAID OF HIM,
AREN'T YOU?
[soft laughter]
ALL YOUR FUCKING FRIENDS
KNOW IT.
- [snarls]
[laughter]
- EVEN I KNOW IT.
I'LL DO IT!
- THAT AIN'T COOL.
YOU FUCKED UP!
- GO AHEAD.
DO IT.
YOU'D BE DOING HIM A FAVOR.
- [bellows]
- WHAT'S THE MATTER,
LITTLE BUDDY?
TOO MUCH WOMAN FOR YOU?
- YOU GOT TO REDEEM YOURSELF!
- YOU BETTER FUCKING KILL ME.
- ANYTHING FOR YOU, SWEETIE.
[yelling]
- YOU LITTLE BITCH!
I AIN'T DEAD YET, BITCH!
- [screams]
- [yells]
[zapping]
- AH!
- BACK UP, SHITBIRDS!
THE DOCTOR IS IN THE HOUSE.
THIS IS HOW IT'S DONE.
YOU CAN TRUST ME, DARLING.
I'M A DOCTOR.
- [panting]
- [making kissing sounds]
DARLING?
DARLING, NOW, COME ON.
YOU KNOW WE WAS ONLY JOKING.
COME ON.
[chuckling]
STOP IT.
BACK UP, SHORT BUS.
[muffled speech]
- WHY IS THIS FUNNY?
THIS ISN'T FUNNY.
IT'S BUFFOONERY.
- BLOW IT OUT YOUR ASS.
- GOD DAMN IT!
I'LL TELL YOU WHAT!
YOU GET
YOUR LITTLE COOKIE BACK
BEFORE I FIND A WAY!
- [panting]
SHIT!
- TRICKY, TRICKY,
TRICKY, TRICKY!
[hatch clangs]
- [panting]
[grunting]
[screams]
- [laughing]
- [shrieks]
- COME ON!
[whimpering]
- [snarls]
- [screams]
[whimpering]
- [snarling and jabbering]
- [panting]
[grunting]
FUCK.
[yelps]
- OUT OF THAT HOLE, CATFISH.
YOU KNOW I SMELLED YOU
DOWN THERE.
[gunshot]
- [coughing]
[whimpering]
- I'M HERE TO HELP YOU.
CARL WAYNE SKRABARCEK.
ROBSTOWN, TEXAS.
I'M LOOKIN' FOR MY LITTLE GIRL.
TEENAGED WHITE FEMALE.
GOES BY THE NAME OF RACHEL.
IF YOU SEE ANYBODY THAT MATCHES
THAT DESCRIPTION,
I'D APPRECIATE A HEADS-UP.
- OKAY.
- I SHOULD INFORM YOU
THAT I AM LICENSED
BY THE STATE OF TEXAS
TO CARRY A CONCEALED WEAPON.
- WE NEED TO CALL FOR HELP.
DO YOU HAVE A CELL PHONE?
- [laughs]
WOULDN'T MATTER.
I AIN'T GOIN' NOWHERE.
[laughs]
'CEPT DOWN THAT SKINNY HOLE.
[gunshots]
- WAIT, WAIT, WAIT!
YOU'RE GONNA LOST.
IT'S LIKE A MAZE IN THERE.
[door creaks]
[gunshots]
- [whimpering]
- EVERY MAN FOR HIMSELF!
- WAIT!
THEY HAVE GUNS!
PLEASE COME BACK!
- FUN IS FUN,
BUT I DON'T WANT ANY SLIP-UPS.
- [breathing jaggedly]
- [groans]
- [yelps]
[grunts]
[panting]
[schmaltzy lobby music]
♪
[floorboard creaks]
[muffled chatter]
- [muffled]
FUCK YOU, MAN.
[muffled laughter]
- [mutters softly]
- [muffled screaming]
- GET HER UP.
GET HER UP.
COME ON.
- [shrieking]
- GOD DAMN IT.
OH, YOU'LL BRUISE
THE GODDAMN MEAT, YOU STUPID--
[zapping]
YEAH! YEAH! YEAH!
- DOC!
YOU GOT TO FUCKING STOP, DOC!
DOC!
DO NOT FUCK WITH ME, DOC!
- YOU PICK THAT MEAT UP!
- GET OFF ME.
GET THE FUCK BACK!
- YOU'RE GONNA PAY,
YOU LITTLE FUCK!
- YEAH! YEAH!
IT'S MY TURN, OLD MAN!
COME ON!
COME HERE!
- AH, SHIT!
- IT'S OKAY.
IT'S ALL RIGHT.
IT'S JUST ALL JUST
A BIG MISUNDERSTANDING.
- ARE YOU RACHEL?
- YEAH.
- I MET SOME WEIRD MAN
WHO'S LOOKING FOR YOU.
MAYBE HE CAN HELP US.
- AH, FUCKING CARL WAYNE.
IT HAS TO BE.
THE ONLY REASON
HE WANTS ME BACK
IS SO HIM AND MY MOM
CAN MOLEST ME.
- DO YOU KNOW HOW
TO GET OUT OF HERE?
- OH, NO, NO, NO.
IT'S OKAY.
ALL WE HAVE TO DO
IS FIND MY BOYFRIEND.
I JUST HAVE TO EXPLAIN TO HIM
THAT IT WASN'T MY FAULT.
I MEAN, I'M PRACTICALLY
LIKE THEIR DAUGHTER-IN-LAW.
IT'S BECAUSE HE THINKS
I HAD MY MISCARRIAGE ON PURPOSE.
BUT REALLY, HE'S VERY SWEET.
- OH, THIS IS IMPOSSIBLE.
[loud thumping]
- LOOK, JUST LET ME
JUST FIND HIM, OKAY?
- SHH!
YOU DO ANYTHING STUPID,
OPEN YOUR MOUTH,
I'LL RIP YOUR FUCKING TITS OFF.
SHH!
SHH! SHH!
OKAY?
LET'S GO.
- [clucking tongue]
NAPPING ON THE JOB, ARE WE?
[spits]
GOVERNMENT PIECE OF SHIT.
[crunching]
[muffled chatter]
- SHIT!
NO, NO!
[laughter]
[yips softly]
- [moaning]
- [yelps]
- FORGIVE THE DISTURBANCE,
CHAIRMAN.
IT WON'T HAPPEN AGAIN.
- THE FUCK DOES HE THINK HE IS?
"NOT A TASTE"?
FUCK THAT.
I WANT WHAT I WANT.
I WANT IT NOW,
AND I WANT A SHITLOAD OF IT!
- [breathing jaggedly]
- GUESS WHAT, LITTLE BUDDY.
crack!
[door thumps]
[urinating]
[sighs]
[door bangs shut]
- [breathing jaggedly]
[shrieks]
[sobs]
[whimpering]
[squeals]
- ME?
I'M FOR LIGHTING
THE FUCKING FUSE.
HEY, WE HAVE SOMETHING
IN COMMON.
WHY THE FUCK NOT?
'CAUSE THAT'S WHEN
IT'S ALL GONNA GET REAL.
AND YOU DON'T WANT TO MISS THAT.
RIGHT?
- [gasps]
- I GET THE MUNCHIES SOMETIMES.
IT HAPPENS.
- WHAT ARE YOU UP TO,
LITTLE BUDDY?
- FUCK ARE YOU?
- FUCK AM I?
THE FUCK ARE YOU?
[grunting and thumping]
I SAID NO!
[porcelain shattering]
- [muffled muttering]
- [gasping]
[panting]
- [muttering]
- JUNK ON THE RUN.
JUNK ON THE RUN!
JUNK!
[thumping]
[record player crackling]
[melodramatic classical music]
- [whimpering]
- YOU BETTER RUN, BITCH!
HERE I COME.
I'M ON YOUR ASS!
- [whimpering]
♪
- [laughing]
- [panting]
♪
- JUNK ON THE RUN!
- [panting and yelping]
[chain saw roaring]
[screams]
- NO!
[chain saw revving]
- [grunts]
♪
[shrieking]
[grunts]
[sobbing]
[coughs]
[music stops]
[moans]
- GO TO SLEEP, LITTLE BITCH.
- HER EYES BUGGED OUT HER HEAD.
I CRANKED THAT BITCH.
- FUN'S OVER.
WE GOT A BUSINESS TO RUN.
- NOW, YOU DIDN'T THINK
WE DIDN'T HAVE ANY SECURITY,
DID YOU, DARLIN'?
WE WAS JUST FUNNIN' YOU.
- STUMBLED UPON A MASS GRAVE
IN AN ABANDONED ROCK QUARRY
WEST OF SAN ANTONIO
EARLY THURSDAY MORNING.
SO FAR, NO FEWER THAN 300
BADLY BURNED
AND MUTILATED BODIES
HAVE BEEN RECOVERED.
PRECINCT FOUR
SHERIFF JESUS MALDONADO, JUNIOR,
SAID THE KILLINGS
APPEAR TO BE THE WORK
OF A MEXICAN DRUG CARTEL.
ACCORDING TO MALDONADO,
THE CARTELS HAVE MERGED
WITH TEXAS PRISON GANGS
AND CONTROL LARGE SWATHES
OF SOUTH TEXAS...
[glass shatters]
ALONG THE MEXICAN BORDER.
- THERE'S A GUY ON THE ROOF.
LOOK!
- OH, MY GOD.
- THINK HE'S GONNA JUMP?
- WHAT'S HE DOING?
- I'M CALLING THE COPS.
- [bellowing]
[monitor beeping]
- NO, WAIT, WAIT!
[screaming]
WAIT, WAIT WAIT!
- WAKE UP, WAKE UP, WAKE UP!
- HE'S WAKIN' UP.
- [snarls]
- WAKE HIM UP.
- TOLD YOU IT WASN'T OVER.
WHAT DID YOU THINK,
THAT WE WERE REALLY
GONNA LET YOU GO?
- [bellows]
- SHUT UP!
SHUT THE HELL UP.
YOU JUNKIES MAKE ME SICK.
- CAN YOU HEAR ME?
GET ME OUT OF HERE RIGHT NOW!
- [bellows]
- I APOLOGIZE.
I AM TERRIBLY SORRY.
- STOP TALKING TO HER.
- IT'S NOT SUPPOSED
TO BE LIKE THIS.
- [roars]
- NOT LIKE THIS.
IT'S IMPOSSIBLE.
I GIVE UP.
[pounding]
THEY'RE ANIMALS.
- THE FUCK YOU THINK YOU ARE?
YOU AIN'T SHIT,
YOU JUNKIE FUDGE PACKER.
HE THINKS HE'S CHARMING.
ABOUT FUCKING TIME TOO.
- [bellows]
- PLEASE, YOU HAVE TO DO
SOMETHING.
- OH, HE'S GONNA DO SOMETHING.
- WHAT?
THEY WON'T LISTEN TO ME.
- RIGHT.
- I'VE TOLD 'EM
TILL I'M BLUE IN THE FACE...
- GOD HELP ME.
- YOU ARE WHAT YOU EAT.
- YOU'RE DAMN RIGHT YOU ARE.
- [snarling]
- PEOPLE ARE LOOKING FOR ME.
- AIN'T NOBODY LOOKING FOR YOU,
BITCH!
- [roars]
- WHAT ARE YOU GONNA DO?
SIT DOWN.
- FUCK YOU.
YOU'RE NOT SHIT.
- IF YOU WANT TO KNOW THE TRUTH,
THAT'S THE PROBLEM.
YOU'VE SEEN WHAT THEY'LL PUT
IN THEIR MOUTHS.
THESE PEOPLE ARE MONSTERS.
LOOK AT 'EM.
THEY'RE SAVAGES.
- THE FUCK UP, DIPSHIT.
- [bellows]
[chains rattling]
- IS THIS ANY WAY FOR
CIVILIZED HUMAN BEINGS TO ACT?
- GIVE IT UP, FOOL.
- CIVILIZATION'S FOR PUSSIES!
- [yelps]
- [roars]
- CARL WAYNE, YOU AND MOM CAN DO
WHATEVER Y'ALL WANT TO ME!
JUST PLEASE DON'T LEAVE ME HERE!
- DON'T EVEN THINK ABOUT--
- [bellows]
- WHAT'S WRONG WITH YOU?
WHAT'S THIS ABOUT?
- WHAT'S THIS ABOUT?
IT'S ABOUT YOU DIE, BITCH.
- [roars]
- NO, NO.
- [screams]
[zapping]
[screaming]
- [roars]
[zapping]
- [screaming]
- GET HIM AWAY!
[yelling, screaming,
and bellowing]
- YOU WANT IT?
YOU GOT IT!
- [screaming]
- [bellowing]
- [screams]
- LET'S GET THIS SHOW
ON THE ROAD!
- [bellows]
- LET'S GET THIS SHOW
ON THE ROAD!
- [snarling]
- GET OFF OF ME!
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
NO!
- TIME TO GO HOME, DARLIN'.
COME ON.
- WHAT'S GOING ON?
- LIFE ON PLANET EARTH.
- THIS IS WHEN IT GETS GOOD.
- SURELY YOU KNOW
YOUR CONDITION.
- [roars]
- MY CONDITION?
- IT'S A GIRL, DARLIN'.
- YUM, YUM, YUM!
- OH, MY GOD.
NO!
- WE WILL RELIEVE YOU
OF YOUR BURDEN.
- [whimpering]
- NO!
PLEASE, YOU CAN'T!
- YES, WE CAN.
- NO!
[screaming]
- NOTHIN' PERSONAL.
- NO!
[door clattering]
- CUT HER LOOSE.
- [growls]
LET 'EM BOTH LOOSE.
[laughter]
- WHAT THE FUCK IS THIS?
- NOW THE PARTY STARTS!
[gunshot]
[laughter]
- [muffled moaning]
- NOW,
ON THE OFF CHANCE
THAT YOU'RE NOT ALL
100% IGNORANT,
YOU MAY HAVE NOTICED
I AM TRAINED
IN THE USE OF FIREARMS.
NOW, CUT THAT LITTLE GAL LOOSE
AND STEP AWAY FROM HER.
DO IT!
- [muffled muttering]
- THAT'S MORE LIKE IT.
NOW, WHICH ONE OF YOU BOYS
MESSED UP MY LITTLE GIRL?
- MAY BE A LITTLE LATE FOR THAT,
CARL WAYNE.
THEY'VE ALREADY LOPPED
THE TOP PART OF MY HEAD OFF.
- OH.
WHAT THE HELL?
- PLEASE, LET'S GO!
- WHY WOULD YOU GO
AND DO SOMETHING LIKE THAT?
- WOULD SOMEONE PLEASE
EXECUTE THIS PUTZ?
- THAT'D BE FAR ENOUGH.
- YOU ASKED A GOOD QUESTION.
- COME ON!
- YOU WANT AN ANSWER?
- WHAT ARE YOU?
HARD OF HEARIN'?
- IT WAS HIM.
- SHOOT HIM!
SHOOT HIM!
- WHAT ARE YOU GONNA DO?
SHOW IT OR SHOOT IT?
- [roars]
- [yelps]
[chains rattling]
[bellows]
- [hollers]
- WHERE'S SHE RUNNING TO?
DON'T RUN TOO FAR!
- [roars]
- SORRY, COWBOY.
THIS JUST ISN'T YOUR RODEO.
- [bellows]
- UH, NO!
DAMN IT!
DON'T MAKE ME DO IT!
[chain links shattering]
ALL RIGHT!
- NO!
- [roars]
- [laughs]
- YOU MAKE ME DO THIS!
[crunching]
YOU MADE ME DO THIS!
AH, TO HELL WITH IT.
[crunching]
- [roars]
- YOU'VE GOT TOO MUCH
TO LIVE FOR!
WE LOVE YOU!
- THIS IS THE POLICE.
- DON'T DO IT, MAN!
- ARE YOU LISTENING TO ME?
SIR, I NEED YOU TO STEP BACK
FROM THE BUILDING RIGHT NOW.
THAT IS AN ORDER.
- [panting]
- [laughing]
- COME BACK, YOU LITTLE--
- IT'S GOT WORMS.
YOU EAT IT.
- FUCKIN' HAMBURGER, MAN!
- MURDERER!
- [panting]
- AN EYE FOR AN EYE!
[crowd chanting]
JUMP! JUMP! JUMP! JUMP!
- STEP AWAY FROM--
- [yelling]
[glass shatters]
[grunts]
[crowd gasps]
- WHAT THE HELL?
- [laughing]
[crowd yelling]
- HE'S GOT A GUN!
[gunfire]
- HOLY SHIT!
[crowd screaming]
OH, SHIT!
- [laughs]
[gunfire]
- [screams]
- [yelling]
[gunfire]
- [laughing]
TRICKY, TRICKY,
TRICKY, TRICKY!
- [yells]
- DROP YOUR WEAPON NOW!
[gunshot]
DROP YOUR WEAPON!
[gunshots]
- THIS LITTLE FAGGOT
SHOULD HAVE STAYED HOME!
[gunfire]
- DROP IT!
OH!
- [laughs]
[crowd yelling and screaming]
[gunfire]
- [roaring]
- [screams]
[metal clangs]
[gunfire and screaming]
[zapping and screaming]
- [laughing]
- [screams]
- I'M HURT.
PLEASE HELP ME.
PLEASE.
- ABSOLUTELY, GOOD SIR.
[gunfire]
[gunshot]
[gunfire and screaming]
- OW!
- [laughing]
- NO!
[yelping]
[shrieking]
- [snarls]
[roars]
- [screams]
- [bellows]
[tires screech]
- COME ON!
[gunshots]
COME ON!
HURRY! HURRY! COME ON!
LET'S GO, GO, GO!
- [snarling]
- GO, GO, GO!
GO!
[tires squeal]
- [bellowing]
- [whimpering]
- MY OLD LADY, MAN,
IS GONNA KICK MY ASS, DUDE.
NOBODY MESSES WITH HER CAR.
- YOUR OLD LADY, MAN?
SHE'S TOUGH.
- WELL, NO SHIT, DUDE.
EVEN OUR KIDS ARE SCARED OF HER.
YOU OKAY?
YOU GOT ANY KIDS?
- NOT YET.
- SOME DAY WHEN YOU HAVE KIDS,
YOU CAN TELL 'EM
TWO CRAZY MEXICAN DUDES
SAVED YOUR ASS, RIGHT?
- THANK YOU.
- [bellowing]
- WHAT ARE THEY DOING?
[gunfire]
- [yells]
[rocket roaring]
[clattering]
- [snarling]
- RIGHT, RIGHT, RIGHT, RIGHT,
RIGHT, RIGHT!
- [screaming]
[explosion]
[sirens wailing]
- [whimpering]
- THIS IS SOME SHIT, MAN!
- CAN'T BELIEVE YOU MISSED,
PINCHE.
HE WAS RIGHT IN FRONT OF YOU.
- IT WAS A WARNING SHOT, ESE.
JUST SAY I'M A LOVER,
NOT A FIGHTER.
I DIDN'T WANT TO KILL THE DUDE.
[helicopter blades whirring]
[sirens wailing]
[snarling rock music]
♪
- ♪ THE HIGH HAWK KNOWS
WHERE THE RABBIT GOES ♪
♪ AND THE BUZZARD
MARKS THE KILL ♪
♪ BUT FEW THERE BE
WITH EYES TO SEE ♪
♪ THE TALL MEN RIDING STILL
♪ WE HARK IN VAIN
ON THE SPEEDING TRAIN ♪
♪ FOR AN ECHO
OF HOOFBEAT THUNDER ♪
♪ AND THE YELLOW WHEAT
IS A WINDING SHEET ♪
♪ FOR CATTLE TRAILS
PLOWED UNDER ♪
♪ HOOF DUST FLIES
AT THE LOW MOON'S RISE ♪
♪ AND THE BULLBAT'S
LONESOME WHIR ♪
♪ IS AN ECHOED NOTE
FROM THE LONGHORN THROAT ♪
♪ A STEER,
AS IT WERE ♪
♪ INCH BY INCH,
TIME DRAWS THE CINCH ♪
♪ TILL THE SADDLES CREAK
NO MORE ♪
♪ AND THEY THE LORDS
OF THE CATTLE HORDES ♪
♪ SHALL TALLY
A FINAL SCORE ♪
♪ OH, THE TALL MEN RIDING
♪ UNDER THE PHANTOM MOON
♪ HOOFBEATS
LIKE HAMMERS OF DOOM ♪
♪ OH, THE TALL MEN RIDING
♪ UNDER THE PHANTOM MOON
♪ HOOFBEATS
LIKE HAMMERS OF DOOM ♪
♪
♪ THIS IS THE SONG
THAT THE NIGHT BIRDS SING ♪
♪ AS THE PHANTOM HERDS
TRAIL BY ♪
♪ HORN BY HORN
WHERE THE LONG PLAINS THROW ♪
♪ THE FLAT MILES TO THE SKY
♪ AND THIS IS THE SONG
THAT THE NIGHT BIRDS WAIL ♪
♪ WHERE THE TEXAS PLAINS
LIE WIDE ♪
♪ OVER THE DUST
OF A GHOSTLY TRAIL ♪
♪ WHERE THE PHANTOM
TALL MEN RIDE ♪
♪ OH, THE TALL MEN RIDING
♪ UNDER THE PHANTOM MOON
♪ HOOFBEATS LIKE HAMMERS
♪ HOOFBEATS
LIKE HAMMERS OF DOOM ♪
♪
♪ UNDER THE PHANTOM MOON