I think ... know ... what they do is fantastic
the two have been through this,
and know the shit that must withstand
when they see the same person every day.
For us it is absolutely the best arrangement,
because we're both very busy,
I work by day, by night she
I can see the Knicks without interruption ...
I get up at noon,
I take a coffee in peace without having to talk to anyone
or comment as I like the rings.
What we are saying is that actually
not have to do ever.
Exactly
Therefore we do not have to endure the attacks of other
-Hmm!
Absence makes everything more fun
And it makes sex hotter
Oh, beware the details! -Is true
I did not tell what we did?
Contále! - Is pretty good ...
Is your face ... like, baby?
Oh. is a little sore
So are "friends with benefits"
but with papers, right?
No, no! listen to me!
We are both in our second marriage
and we are trying to be a little more realistic
this time, about what we need ...
... Or we do not need
I am fully aware
since my last blowjob and I'm fine with it
Enough!
is supposed to have a nice lunch!
I have no idea what it means
traducirmelo could you?
No. .. I think about many things
and I think eventually
you will gain a great blowjob
When we met I really felt
we were perfectly compatible
but then began to haunt both
I think ... what ...
we started to distance ourselves, right?
this fucking ... this fucking!
of course we are very much in love!
Very! - Somehow it again more sensitive.
Oh ... I'm obsessed with the whole relationship,
what I mean is that my sister and I
were educated in a home very, very Catholic
and ... taught us that ...
that marriage is ... is ... sacred!
and to be respectful of it
and ... do not know ...
talk about oral sex at lunch ...
not being respectful.
I heard that if you wake up at least
once a week, look at your partner and you think:
"I made a serious error"
then something is really wrong
with your marriage
Marsha feels that way every morning
then? that is normal too?
Listen ... this conversation is very,
very annoying for me.
No. .. Yes it is.
Marriage is something very special
Oh, yes it is.
is a sacrament, it is!
should be married by that ...
want to spend their life together!
not because she sucks good ...
I think you missed the point
she does not "blow jobs" at all!
Enough!
The problem with your argument is that
We are not married by ...
by ... something special ... a sacrament .... or ...
because they are deeply in love
So I got married!
After 18 years together
going to reveal something else?
you said 18?-Wau, it sounds amazing!
I know. I just said ... OK
when you suggested it, we were in love, ok?-Yes!
well ... when I imagined my life
"Mapeandola" in front of my
I thought "maybe" ... only "maybe"
could have had a musical career
Ha, that music career!? Ha ha! dale!
I do not know "what musical career," that's my point
That's my point, you got a music career
If you had not become pregnant,
we had not married!
Look, I do not understand what you say
think you repent of having married me.
I do not regret anything! I am saying:
let's pretend instead of this wonderful thing
"So lovely" we have
we had other things to do
If we had not married, then, who knows?
could have had more time to meet,
maybe start a career ...
Yes, and then you never would have married me,
I see, yes, I understand what you say
Hey! been married 18 years!,
have an amazing son,
is in a great school ... I mean ...
no ... if everything ended today
probably would call a success, right?
Look, I did not want to ruin the lunch
but honestly ...
are unhappy.
Maybe it should have done is to be honest.
Could have made things worse
because I wanted to say:
"Hey, you two hate each other, divorciense!"
And so it should not go to those unhappy lunches
anymore.
Do not know why we do more often
was hilarious, once a week is little
Ah! I know!, you can believe what he said
about her marriage in front of us???
If you ever feel so
comes to beware that shit please
Seriously!. I liked your comment about the blowjob
Just in case you suck if you really want the
would not be happy, but would
Good to know, because as you know
my birthday is coming ...
Yeah ... mmm ... look what I've done ....
I forget ... you can tie
I thought of a nice pair of socks ...
Sox? 'If
You know, I jack off with those stockings ...
I think relationships should be easy
My first marriage was pure drama
was a nightmare.
And it was a relief to find someone so ...
So ... "free-of-drama"
Look, all these relationships
have so many unnecessary complications
as my first wife, who was ...
Mad-A Challenge
It's nice to find someone
with a balanced personality,
a rational human being, haha!
These relations are always
in which are one above the other
and we promised not let us
... Not drown in a glass of water ...
No ... it may be fanciful
But the thing is that maybe
this period of honeymoon ...
Last forever.
There you have.
Hey!, Dara?
Hi, I can help?
ehhhh ... if, wait
Love is for you, is Dara.
Do it go
I went
you want me to say?
you are? you went to work?
No, no. Tell him I'm sleeping. - Ok
Love, please do not give money
I will not give money, I promise
... Yes, give ...
I promise! I have no need to spend!
Dara I married at a time of ...
confusion.
I do not know, I looked dark and mysterious
Then I grew up and not
and then I realized that
was not dark or mysterious
only alcoholic.
Hey! Shakespeare!
Hey! this Katie?
I wanted to ask something ...
is, but this napping
Look, just in case
I have no money to give you, as you know
And Katie ...
I know you said he could not give a penny more
makes you think I look for silver
a knight can not go to say hello?
Look ... the unexpected visit of the ex-husband
a Sunday afternoon ... usually ...
is not the best idea
regardless I'm always glad to see you
then ... I can do for you?
Nothing, he was in the area
Actually, I have an audition for a play
Dara is a type not so bad ...
is just an actor.
Ok, I'm not being totally honest
there is a hearing
I'm in a financial downturn
so if you got a few dollars I'd appreciate it much
as live as "light"?
where are you going to stop these days?
A girl
this week
let me stay at home
You know what I can do for you?
I have a crap that was going to give
The you can sell on E-Bay
you can them out, 50 or 100 dollars
still works ...
Ok ... I'm taking
Chau Buzz
Always a pleasure
Buzz is that he tried to do the right thing
giving me the vacuum cleaner to sell
I do not know computers,
I do not have much luck
selling it on a website
but I will try to sell on the street
There the coast is clear
To be clear, do not you see him
that guy.
Oh, I was very young
his face was tortured artist.
How much did you give?
Why do you assume that you say something?
Because I know ...
The?
mmm .... you saw the old vacuum cleaner?
That? Why?
Can sell it on E-Bay!
You may be given some money for that
My God, you're so easy to convince!
It seemed hopeless!
Why are you so soft with my ex-husband?
Look, I feel bad for the guy, okay?
He had a chance with you and shit
I have it now
so I'm someone who feels empathy for the cause
When I married you inherited your family, yes?
Then I dealt with the Irish crazy
Your sassy sister, her husband lunatic
and I'm just trying to do
things right for them all, mmm?
Also, I think you would do the same in my situation, right?
In fact it is very good.
I do not look inviting your ex-wife psycho-
to tea
Think is true,
what they were talking at lunch
we are a successful couple
because we never see?
Yes, absolutely
I think it's important to keep
a safe distance, otherwise
you will fully satiate me
But, what if ...?
If we were to see each other again?
If you are pregnant, or something?
Are you pregnant?
No! No!
Are you sure?
Yes, I am
No, because I remember that night
a month ago, we drank too much ...
I'm not pregnant
was all hypothetical
If we need to spend more time together
desmoronaríamos us?
No, we desmoronaríamos ...
but I'm a little confused ...
We both agree on the children.
Yes!, I do not want children
It was purely hypothetical
All right.
It's all
I wanted to be sure we can take
Absolutely, yes. I say, yes
We can handle anything
that life throws us.
Do me a favor
As you spell Vasectomy?
Hello? 'Hi, I'm looking to Buzzy O'Rourke
Ok ... ahh ... is working, who is?
I'm his sister, Linda
Ah ... If your sister ... ok ....
mmm ... Hello
In fact his half-sister
we have the same piece of shit father
Listen, I can upload? very cold
and I'm not properly dressed.
Sure ... just went to work, but ...
Yes, I went.
Hi, My God! Hello, you must be Katie!
And you must be Linda!
My God, you're beautiful!
Thanks, thanks.
You're welcome.
Oh, sorry I wanted you to know that a lot
I missed the wedding
I really wish I could be
Come in, come
Oh, Wau!, Look here!
It's giant twine must be filled!
You have something to drink? a beer or something?
Yeah, sure, Thanks!
Recently I get off the plane
and travel is so stressful ... and all that ...
All that traffic in New York
It Heineken-Oh yeah, you have to be cool ...
That's one reason I wanted to go poque LA
Thank you.
You know, traffic is horrible
Yes, completely
Buzzy you warn him you were coming?
Because I do not say anything
Really?, I say, I called back about a month ago
and told him I thought to come
Ah.
What time back to work?
In a couple of hours, close to 19.
Ok!, I will take a shower, freshen up
There is a good place where I can accommodate?
if ... if ...
There is an extra room
Perfect, I leave you free
is that you have to go to work
and thank you very much for letting stay here
and I want you to know, do not worry ...
... Until I find my own place
Beautiful, totally gorgeous
He never spoke of having a sister,
or I who said they
I think the invite to the wedding but did not come
when he arrived and said he hoped to stay
I was a little surprised.
Hey! guess who I ring the bell this morning?
Your sister!
my brother ...?
Shit! Do not tell me really came
Yep! I left the department
my jewelry will be safe?
do not know if I can guarantee
Well, then better home andd
Look, I have another client
finished, go home and take care
You knew that was coming?
I called a couple of months and said
I was thinking about leaving Los Angeles
save for a plane ticket
but I never really going to show up
Well, it appeared!
and "the impression" that will stay with us
shit!
Heart, look, I will take care of this
I will accommodate in a hotel or ...
no, no, okay, it's your sister, I'm your woman
do the right thing
Cornered, thanks
See you at night
See
I know Linda is a pretty burned mine
our father died when he was 16
and ran away from home after that,
went to Los Angeles, then ...
16, a fugitive in Los Angeles ...
Not exactly a recipe for success.
Guess who?
ehhh .... I'm in town!
I wanted to call and say hello
and know how are you? ... how are you?
I need to see, I'm here in N.Y.
I thought we could be
I'm here! really!
Where were your honeymoon?
He was good?
Dale ... I just want to see
You still there?
Listen do not be an asshole
Let's meet for a drink, yes?
Yeah, ok ... hey!
Thank you.
You're kidding?
My God!
I can not believe it! 'Hello!
We are in N.Y. - Yes!
Here I am
Wau, I was rushing to get home
to greet you, where are you going?
Yes!, Right now I'll find me with a friend
we drink
but I'm glad that we are crossed!
I'm shocked
Look at you, you grew a lot
When was the last time you saw?
It was still a teenager
Actually it was Dad's funeral
Yeah, right.
Neither cried
You keep talking to your mother?, Or ...
No, I do not
and I have no plans to contact her
I can not blame you, either
That's the Katie bag?
Oh, yes, oh you know ...
I did not come prepared for this climate
on the other hand, is nuts-Si, if
I hope you do not mind, you think?
No, no, this also
You should know that
I forgot to mention that perhaps you were coming ...
Ah! ... So this morning was so rare
I mean, a little weird
Look, I have to go fast
I have to meet my friend
but I see you later, we find,
we can chat some more.
I'll be home all night
Excellent! 'See you then!
Welcome to N.Y. and see you tonight, ok?
Yes, totally, we later
Not to tell Buzzy if asked, but
I felt very close to him as a child
He was at home all the time,
and I'm glad I could come
and see for a while,
and re-meet him, I think ...
Linda ... I can say about it?
I can not say I really know her well
I was already in college
when she was a baby
and really I have no memories of her.
What surprised, really!
Because with my band ... we'll be
all weekend.
How many are in the band?
I and three kids
My wife owns the studio ...
and she goes out on weekends.
I can schedule you at this time
How old are you?
Well ... How old are you you? - 23
Really? 'If
Okay ... - If I was born in '87
'87? - JA-
And where were you in '87?
Actually .... it is a long history
I think I have the Oedipus complex
My God, you're giving me a heart attack
Excuse me ....
What? - What are you doing?
Do nothing
Why not ask her out
I mean, I'm sitting here, but again
why not ask her out?
Yes ... but .... no!
I can see you! through the glass, I can hear you!
P.T., you saw it?
Dress like trying to cogérsela or what?
Not out of this!
Marsha, we were checking the lines
and you're making a fuss about nothing
I do not understand ... 'I do not lie
I'm not lying!
We were just talking about it!
Ah! you're the composer and musician ...
and the owner of the studio!
Look, this should be my job, ok?
You're here for me
You do not know anything, you do not know anything!
You have this job because I gave it to you
No? ... Okay?
Because I have to sit down and look at you
trying to fuck a minita
while I'm here in the fourth
if you do, do it in private!
You're turning into a disgusting old
I am a musician, I have ideas, I have dreams
I can do something creative, but ...
not ...
By the way, thanks for making me wait 2 hours
I could not get a taxi
and I come from Queens
Ok! but I say ... 2 hours!
So you do in N.Y.?
I came for you
You came for me?
I think you came 10 months later
Yes, I see. Why not tell me you were gonna marry?
I told someone I had known
and that was serious, I told you
That is very different from saying "I do"
When you left L.A. I did not think
the next I saw you'd see that married
I would have to go
What is this? you hate me yet?
That's the point?
No, do not hate you
I do not want to have this conversation, Linda
He took the job after I told
I would not marry him
I guess I was not prepared
But ... now I think it was a mistake
It broke my heart once
Why do not you follow on with your life?
Because even I love you 'No, no
I do not want to hear that
Why, if it is true
Because I'm married reverendamente, ok?
That's not my fault!
could you not marry me
does not mean you could run away and marry another
No! no! is not it, that's not what happened!
that's not what happened
I want to ask something
What are you doing here?
I do not know
I do
Recontra still be crazy, right?
You say?
I can not
Really?
Yes
Yes, really
He is about to go home
and go to bed with his new wife
wanted me to see that maybe
I can go to bed with someone too,
if to
men respond to that.
I got to a guy jealous
and they will do almost anything you want, yes?
Cute!, Sooo cute.
You're kidding!
Hello dear!
Hello baby!
Hey!
It was a good night?
A very good night!
We covered 94
Wau Wau!
Let's stay here and take a glass of wine, shall we?
How was your night?
You met your sister?
Yes and no is to do with the subject
Yes, it's my sister
but I do not recognize ...
and best of all, this here
by a bed of shit
Glad to hear you say this
because I think it is a "little problem"
say, a little, a little bard
Just a little bit
Yes, I know
Is he here?
No, no, actually came
You have friends here?
I have no idea, but
appeared in N.Y. in the middle of winter
without a coat ...
let him take one of your closet ...
Okay ... good ...
If ... you know which grabbed?
No. .. I know ...
wrong?
No!
Enough then 'Welcome to N.Y.
Why come to N.Y. in the middle of winter
without a coat?
I do not understand.
totally, you're super generous
Thanks ...
No, no! of course.
You're the boss
I drink to that
And now I go for a swim
a bath?
Yes, and I'm taking this with me
Want some company ...?
No, this also
Ah, is there!
that sh ...!
what the hell goes here!
For!
Okay! is my friend!
Parala! Shut the fuck up!
Shut up!
Andate the whore of a mother
What the fuck is wrong with you! 're playing the father here?
What the heck is it, my God?
Get out of my house Andate to shit "friend"
Andáte to shit
Take this all
It's your problem!
Andate to shit!
Wait for me!
Do not know how Katie will react
obviously this upset
because Linda took shelter
and also lied to Katie
saying that I gave him shelter
Steal the warm, bring a chabón,
All within 12 hours of being here
this is not good ...
You should be grateful
not heard it again last night
Why? what happened?
I got up at 5 am
to find an unknown type
zarpados fully in the kitchen counter
That?
Yes, I know, is crazy
... Very funny.
Due to security
clean up the kitchen
Thank you.
But the point is not the kind of thing
you want to see by your sister
What did you do?
The kicks take the
and are taken
But she was re-in fart
and made shit
Not like no one woke up
I was screaming in the hall
Wau ... well, I can not make much fuss, I think
this is what kids do today
go to a bowling alley, know any kid
take them home and ...
Garchan ... the kitchen counter
So that's what they do today.
Absolutely, I read in a magazine
Are not really being of any help
That's my sister
and do not need that image in my mind-pad
No, I'm not angry
Why should she not feel at home?
Been here ... 12 hours ...
Never eat breakfast on the counter ...
then, all right
Now, seriously
maybe I become puritanical,
but I think bringing a strange,
the first night in a strange house
is a little ... promiscuous? I must say ...
Even as you could not sleep
in the midst of this madness last night
It was a bizarre appearance
you almost tear your head with a baseball bat
I guess you were protecting me!
I did not know who was!, Listen to noises
I figured that someone had entered the house
waiting
Speaking of Rome
Ah! There she is
Hello
Buzzy? ... Hey, so ...
these ... very angry about last night ....?
Yes!, If
I'm a little more than angry
Excuse me!, Look, I was half drunk
and we were closer to home than his
and I thought it would be more comfortable, or something ...
Then I can ...
I can go back? or ...?
Waiting
Want to know if its okay to stay with us
If-If welcome back!
Are you sure? - Aha
Hey! good news,
You're welcome back
I'm going to work in a while
but when I get home
We need to have a looong talk on
"Rules", if you stay with us
for a little while
Ok.
secure a long talk ...
When I go crazy, I only see red
I do not think I react
I inherited from my father, was very impulsive
and often exciting because things happen so
others, only shitty situations
Good day
No, I did not
was supposed to do with you
Why?
We can try to start again, shall we?
I know! but I made a mistake!
I was wrong
I did not think about your upcoming move to N.Y.
and you'd get married in 10 months
I thought maybe we would have another chance
I was wrong
Is that what you are playing?
I made a mistake and was wrong
Ok ... well
if you're 100 percent sure
that are ready to go
and say goodbye forever
then I'm leaving tomorrow
I go back to L.A.
and leave you in peace
but if so, call me, ok?
Hey! Buzzy are you?
No, no, it's me
Hey!
Yes, yes, shameful return, right?
It happens to all
Also, you have fun?
It was the best night, you know?
Oh, Buzzy told me you took one of my coats
Oh ... shit ... shit!
I should leave it somewhere
the "left somewhere"?
Do you remember where?
somewhere we can call?
No, not where it was
But maybe ... you can replace it?
was very expensive?
It was ... yes
Hey ... ok, fine
We are happy you are here
There are a couple of things you can do
that would be helpful
and the first would
not use as many towels when you shower
a lot because I hate washing
and the other thing is ...
if you can avoid bringing home strange guys
would be great
Buzzy told you?
Yes ... yes, yes, of course
Oh! ok
Well, first of all
so forgive me for towels
I thought they were there to be used
and then ...
You never had a night of pop?
Yes, yes ... of course it is.
I do not want strangers in my apartment
late at night, if that's okay
understood
I have to hit me a shower
and ... I'm not too dry
Sorry, there are some water here?
Perfect
They saw that, right?
was as hostile ...!
I opened the door in my face!
just trying to be nice
... And she did not like
Ok ...
It's official ... I do not like it
I know I was a guacha
I have this hangover from hell,
I get home
and the first thing I get is what the towels
Who the hell cares about towels?
They broke my heart last night!
To be clear,
I had uncontrolled nights before I got married
Hi, I need to talk
Hey! 'Hello
Hey, my love, by chance this Buzzy at home?
No, Max is training
Ok, I just wanted checkearlo
I do not believe a word these days Max
Heart, listen,
Buzzy I mention something about Max
cheating on ...
No! happening?
I would say if he knew?
Yeah, right! could not hide a secret
to me.
do not know, Katie is half naive
men know
they do not share that shit
Marsha! you are my sister!
I'm his wife!
Want a drink?
If water, please
When I graduated from college
I was married to Max, we met at school
and had a son shortly after
It is he who goes to school
For me, I am involved in the life of John
I mean, when a mother is
is very involved with the kids
Max and I think also
now I feel all the passion
to my son has to focus on other things
I am a little worried about you and Buzzy
Oh, Marsha not start, please!
how well you know her?
I say that this wedding rush
way too fast for my taste
I'm fine, thanks
Trust me, one never really knows
I mean, I'm with Max always
and still do not know
Why insist on doing this, Marsha?
It turns me off, but my husband
and I love it
Heart, I tell you something:
Why do not you said
that his sister would come and stay with pc?
Is not it strange?
No, is a hanging
called 3 months ago
saying that came
and did not call to confirm!
Do you remember what Dad said?
Better to ask forgiveness, ask for permission
I feel that these projecting
your relationship in mine
No! no! -Something happened to Max?
Today I am hypersensitive to dishonesty
I can smell the 1 km
Why be afraid to tell
her sister was coming to stay?
I do not know ... maybe, thought you were going to say no
or maybe he knew it was a pain in the ass
I do not know, the point is he knew and did not tell you
you have to start dwelling on these
little lies, that's what they do men lie
Yeah, I know, and maybe you're right
Maybe I said because it did not want you to know
the very slutty and it's busted
his sister
Last night, brought home a guy at 3 am
and it was trincando on my kitchen counter
and also I banque ... more or less
Until today when I try to talk
and became the canchera
As if asking something unreasonable
to ask strangers not to bring home
Look, the guests are always a problem
but, when a family member, as a
English whore old mother
or a sister trolita of Los Angeles
then it is a bad, bad idea
and that said Buzzy?
I did not tell even
not to say, not as telling
when your sister going to my fucking house?
I thought you said you could tell all
Yes, I can!, But this is different
is his sister, and was always sympathetic
with Dara and you ...
I?
Why is understanding me?
no ... you know ... the 'He' what '?
He thinks you do not like
Well ... not
At least it is smart to recognize
Why, did you?
I did nothing ... look at you to you yourself
're a desirable woman
're beautiful, successful
these wealthy
not, was in a hurry
to put a ring on your finger
A ring that paid you
I think Marsha believes that
I'm not good enough for her sister
We come from different worlds
No ... she never opened me
and it's funny, it grabs with Max
because it was he who introduced us.
she hates me!
I do not hate you!
although it may be that this no longer
"Madly in love"
I have to get away from this marriage
I told you not want to hear this bullshit
Ok? I do not want to go home
and having Katie wondering
about pc, and forced me to lie
Tell her the truth!
Seriously!, Finish with this
and it is for you!
Yo! I have to see me
When you said "18 years is a success"
It's true!
John is in school
does not need us closer together
Do me a favor, okay?
I upload this shit to me, yeah?
I was trying to soften
what was becoming
in a very uncomfortable conversation
Yes! but what you said was true!
Forget I said it!
I can not forget!
I ended
I'll ask Marsha divorce
No, you do not
No need to bother your wife
I do, somehow, responsible
for planting the seed in your head sick
that you are going to divorce!
This the girl in the study
I swear by God that is beautiful
I do not want to hear this boludez
I cogermela everywhere
Back to work, you're a fucking skeleton
The more I give to this
Hello
had hoped that you would know
Listen, sorry about last night
No, nothing happened with that guy
was trying to make you jealous
wanted to come running after me
and tell me I do not go
but you did not
No, I will not leave you alone
because I'm in love with you
and I want to be with you
No you can see me for one night
one night
I do not care ... where you want
We can go to a hotel, no matter
See you then
If, if, if ...
Hello
Hi, Dara
Who?
Dara Flynn, who are you?
I'm Linda's sister Buzzy
Who are you?
Sorry, I'm the ex-husband of Katie
I have this vacuum that had to restore
let me go?
Oh, apparently I have no permission
let men of the department
so, better bass and give it to me
Barbaro, thanks
Ok, give me 5 minutes
My nature is my nature
I see a beautiful woman
react, respond
I ask out ...
pass
it's almost like ... hello, good afternoon
Concerned?
felt in the stomach
it's almost like being hurt
lies with them
I need tenderness
she has the style Blanche Dubois
someone who relies on the kindness of strangers
figuratively speaking
I was excited and a little nervous
to meet Miles
and there was beer in the fridge
and thought it was okay to go for a couple of free drinks
Katie never understood the temperament of an artist
was never emotionally in tune
to really understand where it came from I
Yes, they are so organized
like to have everything in order and so
There is no room for spontaneity
Yes! Yes! I want to take me in your life
wild ride
The road of excess leads to the gates of wisdom
but do not drink ... and pass the gates of wisdom
For me as an artist, I feel ...
is true? is more honest?
I think it's important, you know?
what kind of artist are you?
I'm an actor, stage actor
Ever heard talk of Mizner?
No, it's a writer?
No, no ... Mizner was ...
as decribir at Mizner
It was a God, of the buildings
Give me a second, do a little exercise
Sacudite all, try to relax
Focus
Look into my eyes, ok?
Inspire
and allowed him to leave, exit
at any time
How to talk?
As talking, perfect
Wau, this is intense!
Wau, this is intense
He was flirting with her?
is hard to say
as an artist, what I felt was a kind of connection
was a spontaneous reaction
and her eyes seemed to be appropriate
for the moment
Oh, oh, there it is
Hey! I found Katie's ex-husband, Dara
Dara? where you found it?
Here. He came to leave the vacuum
But ... do not leave it up
Katie because I said I can not let
strangers in the department
Then you talk to Kate
And I was a little brash with me
Do me a favor, do not talk nonsense Katie
is being very generous leaving you be
Yes! there would be no problem between us
if you had not told you what happened last night
Of course he had to tell!
It is my wife, and this is your department!
Yes! but I came with all his judgments
and do not need your blame
Seriously, you can blame her?
with all your performance in the kitchen ...
Well! that's what I need not tell you!
Well good ...
which is supposed to mean?
Do not you remember how it all was when we were kids?
You brought a new girl every night
and dad harangued and complimented?
Yes, I was in college
and it was acceptable behavior,
you're an adult, staying in this department
Listen, I'm not angry!
and I'm not judging
She is going to break the balls
if this behavior continues
Look, I'm happy you're here
miss you, and it's great to see you
but please do me a favor
and just ... calm down a bit while you stay
Ok ... ok
I'll calm down a little
Oh ... I have to tell
I lost the shelter of Katie
Lost you grabbed your coat?
Yes, but I said it would pay
Trust me, you could not afford that coat
I got it ...
I appreciate that you said you find it
Told our story ...?
We met ... Max was training at the gym
listen to me ... my sister
this very good
said the other day who was horny
that you want this ...?
Why is your sister telling you walked
how hot was it?
No, he told Marsha, Marsha told me my
Where's the catch?
if she is so good, why is single?
Obviously I thought there was something wrong with you
you were mentally unstable or something
but luckily did not have anything bad
Bought on the first date!
We started dating
and soon it got serious,
I became infatuated, I proposed to her one night
they were returning from dinner
You say?
If
I said that if
and here we are
here we
She was pregnant
it was a big surprise
and I remember him at the show
we went in a tiny pub
and wrote that song
for me,
yes! did!
and proposed to me right there
opposite worldwide.
I remember being totally scared
with the "project" of parenting, and ... not ...
it all happened very fast
but still sweet
those were good times
If ...
She was upset ...
said, "we can go???"
Actually I said stronger
Forgive me, I can not by meeting and
If they insist on talking in this way at dinner
I mean, it's fine in the locker room,
there is acceptable
but it bothers me
Please Marsha! calm down!
You look like an old woman!
People talk about sex and whore at dinner
ok?, leave aside
No, I will not drop it
because I find it offensive,
on the other hand, you called me an "old"?
No, I said "looked like" an old
Please explain to me rather as "look" an old
So what say you ...
Is that everything and everyone bother you at all times
Everything?-Yes! I like walking on eggshells
terrified of what I can tell you you will fall ill
That's not true!
Katie, you feel like that with me?
No, not at all
See! Buzzy and clearly not
but speak in front of me like a gentleman
Knight? ... That'll never happen!
I think the only person you're terrified
You know Marsha? - What?
You lost the taste for life
The taste
The taste!, Yeah! The fun, joy, happiness
all gone!
Chota and complaining
So your personality became
I'm sick!
Nothing you say fun
Do not even remember the last time you laughed
When was the last time you laughed?
Seriously, when was it?
Want to know? - Yes!
Ok, when I saw you trying pathetically
get up to that girl in the study
I turned hilarious
You should have seen! being "charming"
I re-shit of laughter
Hey! why not leave it there, eh?
Buzzy! contales of those freaks you train at your gym
is very funny
Ok ... let me see ...
This this Chabon, Aaron, Wall Street
that embodies his maid ...
that's funny!
I want a divorce
Yes! ... No ... you know what? ...
Buzzy, you're right
were 18, and we consider it a success
I involucres ...
I say that? I do not remember having said
Is over, right here
Well, that sounds like music to my ears
If? well then!
but I stay with the department
Okay! I go to sleep to study
Great, "perfect"
Max, Max! e-e-e-wait! wait!
what happened?, go get it!
Ask anything!
I have ... to deal with my sister ... then ...
Great ...
Sorry ... I'm fine
pc is what awaits
Yes! I think 18 is a super-successful
My first marriage lasted 6 years
yours, how much? 4 years?
Get to 18???
I think they did a job from hell
Just out of curiosity
future as we see us?
I want more than 18,
I want forever
is that what you imagine, but ...-Yeah, me too!
When I said ... "I do"
Yes! I totally agree
but, 18, say, if we were to 18
'd both be very happy
Why am I back here?
mmm ... I think
to learn that he married
was ...
motivating factor, probably
It made me really want to see what
and go after it
And one for me ...
Ok
Health-Health
than another?
a more
Miss you
I want to put a song for you
I think you'll like
we
good!
you remember?
Dale, you want to dance
I know you want!
Come on!
Seguis love with my
So what?
it does not matter
Of course it matters
I brought you something
That?
You have to wait and see
not go anywhere, ok?
Ok I'm here-
Men are so predictable ...
if you use your sexuality in the right way
then you can get them to do
almost everything you want to do
Hey guys, did not think they would be still here
We're going to have a few drinks, if you want to come ...
What, now?
Yes!
Come with us!
If?
Yes! ... Uh ... 'Give,' Ok!
I can drink ... actually, you know?
I invite you!, who do you think?
My God! I can not believe what just happened!
Divorce! ... At dinner? ... How?
I will take another glass of wine, shall we?
Si-Si ... thought they were really happy
Really? 'If,' why you thought they were happy
Never saw them laughing
never say anything cornered
No, no! in the beginning,
years before knew
when they were still with Johnny
were like ... never saw a couple so in love
The way he looked
buy her flowers every day!
That when he was 18 years ago?
Why did you say your marriage was a success?
Look, I was trying to soften
"Other" uncomfortable dinner
God! known to have problems
but I thought they were any problems as
I had no idea
and you? you noticed?
No. .. no ...
not really
Not really ..??
Sometimes ...-What?
Sometimes in the gym, Max spoke she pests
I thought they were boludeces,
most bad-mouth their wives
You talk plagues me in the gym?
No, not pests of you
where this is going? I will not badmouth you
for at least 2 months ... or so
Cheers-health
You're a "prince" ...
she told me something ...
look ... I did not know
I was going to ask for a divorce at dinner!
We promised to tell all
and now, tell me to the worst
I know everything, have no fear
I agree ... in the future I'll tell you what you know
Because I was blind at the restaurant
was a holy shit ...
Understood ... understood loud and clear
Ok?
I think that relationships work
you have to be completely honest
count everything, even the smallest detail
I agree to some extent
there are certain "things"
that, frankly, is better
silent-If?
Like what?
Well, I do not want to hear about
my deepest, darkest thoughts
I can sometimes get to have
Yes, I want ... I'm telling you all
Bue ... say ... that was me!
sexual fantasy that you got a "temporary"
for example, 2 to 1, with two types of the pizzeria
I do not want to hear-I have no such fantasies
two types in the pizzeria, if you?
No! I have not the fantasy
the girl in the Starbucks not so bad ...
as I said! better beware those things!
Wow ... you look amazing
Why did not you say "yes" when I asked you
Ask me now
Ask me again, now
You know? were the only thing I really wanted
could we be so happy together
We can still be happy together
How could we? if I am already married
Divorciate!, Who gives a fuck?!
if you still love me
I can not
Why not?! if you were not even
married a couple of weeks?
people get divorced every day!
Fuck it, you do not understand
We're having a baby
why I married such a hurry
I'll have a baby ...
What? ...-In a few weeks
I will be father
I am angry with Linda
because he said he wanted to be with me now!
but it is too late.
I asked, I gave my heart
and she did not accept
I wanted to spend time with Linda
and I'm happy as things happened,
could not live with myself
know ... we're talking ...
Yes! three wet towels lying on the floor
Touch them 'Look, I used that towel
No! you always colgás towels
Do you mean? that she purposely shot the towels
on the bathroom floor, yes, yes, 'Why would I?
Because I asked him to cool him not to,
and clearly does not like being told what to do
I think you are putting a little paranoid
but, look, I'll wash the towels
My love is not for towels
but we could put a date to go?
And .. what is it supposed to say?
Ask about plans to stay!
and then to stay sugerile least
not so long
Thursday you fair?
Until Thursday I feel great, thanks
Now, I'm going to shower
I'm going to wash ...
My sister is swollen balls sometimes
Buzzy's sister is
completely on another level
It tests the patience of the saints
This kind of boludeces are those types
not bancan
Who cares if you lost a coat
or someone uses many towels
At chabones do not care "so much" stuff
except except encamarte
with an ex-girlfriend of another
that's probably the only thing that matters
Hello
Pass
as an actor, you know,
Live as if the extreme forces
come to a by themselves
Linda is a pure force
sheer force
You know what I need?
that accurate?
I need a drink
Sorry, but I have drinks at home
I have no alcohol at home
What is true
is that if you and I are here
and all the things you see
is all I need to have
I need no more
to "focus"
You know that is incredibly sexy
when you talk and
I wish we can do this but
we're like ... "family"
No, no! relatives are not
No! but you're the sister of my ex-wife
and this relationship ... Oh, oh -
I mainly hot ... your brother!
this, this is not a relationship
Now, take me to the bedroom,
or want to talk about it ... mmm?
We up-Ok!
No. .. no, no, do not go ..
is so sad!
which part?
Oh ... the whole fucking thing is sad!
You said 15???
I was ... with a silver in Hamburg but cost
If ... is your wife going to live up?
She will live up
I down here in the studio
You know ...?
15 is muchism time
I'll do something really nice for you
Come on!
Hagomoslo right here ...
Oh ... that good!
Are you okay?
If
you keep on crying
Not
want to talk about it?
Indeed, no
I can ask?
It was just a boy who knew ...
You have to tell me about it
Why?
To you that you care?
Yes, Linda cried the first time we had sex
but, and it is true, it usually happen the first time
whatever it is,
seems to have a strong impact on women
Baby, it seems she's not coming tonight
then why not ...
we do something?
If, 'I think it would be good for us
What is love, but I do not encourage this evening
Oh, I can put you in tune?
I can do it quickly!
Ha ha! sounds great
Maybe you can do when she leaves
after Thursday
Touche
I do not think that not having sex is a punishment
see it more as an incentive
to kick the crap out of my house to his sister
Guess what? Max was with the mine
last night in the study-what?
Yes - my God! These kidding
No, no, I hear 'Oh my God!
Yes! I can not be sure, but it was pretty obvious
My God! is very serious! - I know!
I can not stay in the department
if these droppings will be sent
I can stay with you?
Just for a little while
Yes, but Buzzy's sister is still with us
We have no free rooms, you can get you on the couch
The sofa?
You remember what I did for you
when you divorced?
When you came home and
contained you every night until you sleep?
You remember?, Yeah!
Makes this trolita on the couch
When would be good to start dating
I wait a few months
I know, but you were young and you could afford it
Would have to shave? Brazilian style?
I want to do is what I did in years
and want to do now ... tonight!
It might be good
I mean, in a way ...
There are possibilities waiting
that could be fun, exciting ...
and ... who knows,
I'm more mature now and I have more experience
That shit happens here!
Do not tell me two ... PC!
that this is happening!
Not what you think - not what you think?
who is this then?
Come with me, we need to talk
What the hell is it? -What?
What happens here? - We were walking
Walking??
There are 8 million people in this city
and you have to go with him??
Listen, I appreciate that you try
be my brother
I'm trying to do shit!
but these like crazy, we talked about yesterday!
I know, I know, but it happened, ok? things happen
I'm driving the ...
No, you're not driving a shit
What you do is lie
with my wife's ex
No, no, I'm sleeping with him
I slept "yesterday" with him, there is a difference
Obviously I can not talk to you, Hey asshole!
Entendelo, that ends today
Not going to see more
No, you do not understand you, I love it!
love her?! not even know her!
Fuck me that you talk
Your sister and I are cut from the same yardstick
from here, from the guts, Katie and you from here
head, think
streamlining all the time
I do not expect you to understand
You're aware that this asshole
in love with you?
That's what I just said 'No, not this!
No! not these! Listen
're a really sweet guy, but ...
Date around and andate to your house
You mind if I take my coat, please?
these fucking me?
Devolvele the damn coat
Chau! Come on, we need to talk
It is clear that you put me
in a wild storm of shit, yeah?
So this is what you have to do
you have to go and tell Katie
because I'm not going to
Why would anyone have to tell you something???
I must say, I do not want to tell
you put us in this situation
so you have to explain it to you
that's what we do
we tell all, honesty is called
Really? this idea sounds terrible!
You have to promise me when you return,
Now I have to go to the gym, you have to tell you!
if I tell you I will take!
You should have thought of before
Hey!, There you are
Linda, this is my sister Marsha
Marsha, this is Buzzy's sister, Linda
Nice to meet you
Nice to meet you at last
Listen to Katie, I would ...
I would like to talk to you
if that's okay
there is something I have to say
I have to tell you ... ...
eh ... sorry, we're in the middle
of a family crisis, right now
My husband left me 18 years ago
Oh no, sorry!
Yes, we need to talk about where they go to sleep
because I have to spend the couch
I can not stay in my house
the-course is still there!
Yes, because I want to say
is that today I'm going!
Are you going? -Yes! 'That's great!
Thanks Linda!
No, thank you, you were so generous
I do not want to take advantage of your hospitality
No, no, not really - I'm sure no ...
Well ... I'll pack my things
you can change the sheets?
I'm sure that must be changed
Si-Thanks
Thanks Linda!
Hi, I'm Max
yes, I do not have session, I wanted to talk
Thanks
That shit thought, pulling the pump
in the middle of dinner
was not the place for that pedorrada
I thought not, so I went
but the sync was amazing
when I returned to study,
Vanessa, that girl I told you about
was still working
The thing with Max is that it is a poor reflection
of my ability as a coach
not gain muscle mass, not weight lost
all it does is come to the gym
to pelotudear
All the time I say, do not need a trainer
need a psychiatrist
I do not want to hear these stories
okay? so here's the deal
I think I can not train more
This is putting me in an uncomfortable position
I went because I was excited
I thought I wanted to hear the news
This guy ... 18 years married, you know,
yesterday sucked me right
I wanted to tell, share the good news
and I get that I want to train more
No, I think he understood it all wrong
Hello! I am, I am glad you have not attended
Just wanted to call ...
I wish to say this last night
I just wanted to get out of there
but I wanted to tell you now
if he had known the situation ...
never have been,
never have come to N.Y.
I want you to know ... I'm very happy for you
I think you'll be a great dad
and I just wanted to call and say goodbye,
bye
I do not know, I think I have to go
I think I have to go back to L.A.
Marsha is a little time with us aquedar
What happened to the other plan?
that you were going to sleep upstairs and Max in the studio?
Esra well, but last night someone brought Max home
and I could hear them, and I can not ... you can believe it?
I dunno, I do not care ... uh ...
by the way, where is my sister?
Linda was gone!
We were in the kitchen, came and said he was going
that you mean by that is "going"?
He told where he was or where she was staying?
No! -Not
seemed happy
He said ... something else?
About what?
Today when I went to work
came out of coffee and I found it
and Dara ...
My ... were together?
I do not know, I think the quote that was last night
had to be with him
What!? This is another type of relationship?
and as you know this? My God!
He took the whoring to new level
But it is a cobarte, came and said he had to go
packed up and went to hell
because they wanted to tell me that caught my ex-husband
I'm sure ... he was afraid to tell you something
is a young lass, is vulnerable
vulnerable? ... vulnerable! ... then
vulnerable means you have to take
any of N.Y. life and shit!
I liked when I saw
her look was suspicious
You say that my sister is suspect
Fully suspicious!
He stole my coat, my bloody towels used
caught on the kitchen counter
and now what my ex-husband garchó
this is a holy shit, Buzzy, a shit
Look! I'm mad as like you!
I have no my sister is encame with Dara
what you feel is not questioned here, ok?
Now, your reaction is a bit disproportionate
where not going to stop tonight
And I was like the pelotuda knew nothing ...
... And if I had left the cafe and I found them?
You did this to me?, I hid all this?
From this you spoke, units are not known well
before marriage, so I was against it!
My God, Marsha, shut up!
Do not tell my sister to shut up!
My sister is a good person
Your sister is ... the devil!
You're being a little irrational ... ok?
why were not on speaking in the morning
and not have to deal with comments "extras"
I'm going to work, and tomorrow
you and I are going to have a conversation
because I think that maybe, want different things
in this connection
and I think those different things are important
Really? let's get to it?
I told the truth!
my fault what my sister?
Why the hell did you do that?
Why do not you tell about this?
My God ... seriously?
No chance that Max let him in to Hell
Christ!
Dress this girl?
First, he steals my coat
then used all the towels, 2 times
and then take my ex-husband
I say, my ex-husband!
I feel that if I had a bunny
I would be boiling in my kitchen!
Hello! how are you?
thanks for re shit against marriage
I'm super happy that you came to visit me!
do you want!?!-just wanted to talk to someone
Ah! and why did not you call your new friend Dara
and incidentally, spend the night
Sorry, I said I was not thinking straight
I would say you were not thinking at all
Why do not you tell Katie,
as you said you would?
I could not!
I was afraid, and was his dark sister
getting pick, and I thought it best to leave
Ok, now put me up the ass problems
so that, thanks muchísmas
I'm sorry! I'm a mess! I know!
I have no one else, you're my brother
I need your help
Yes! and I was trying to help
and all you did was shit more
Not to do! I have no money
and I just wanna go home!
I do not feel well ... want to go home
Where are you?
I'm in a hotel, I'm in
Cosmopolitan, close to home
Why do not we meet for breakfast?
There is a little bar in the corner, at 9 o'clock and ...
We see that, yes?
Ok, you'll be alright?
If
Well, see you in the morning
Ok, thanks
Hey Buzzy! you awake?
No, I'm asleep!
Hey! you know what I'll do tomorrow?
You know what? I could care less
because I'm sleeping ...
I'm taking one day at the beauty spa
I'll join hands, I will shave ...
I'm going to dye the roots, it will be great!
Guess what? I suck an egg!
and you know I'm going to do next?
You know Marsha? I think I said I was sleeping
I'm going to a bar and I'll take 200 daisies
and I will raise a type, an asshole
a nice asshole
I'll suck it suck it
and then I'm going to get in the kitchen
Yeah ... sounds wonderful, do me a favor?
make sure you use lining
Will not you have to marry again!
Ah! and guess what I do after that?
You know what? ... Hell I care what you do three!
I thought you might like!
're always counting
about your sexual exploits with my sister
I thought you were going to enjoy what I tell you, right?
Marsha ... Good night!
Good night!
it's 2 am and it is obvious
I will not be able to sleep
with Marsha trepanandome ears all night ...
I can not stay in bed thinking
how to fix things with Katie or
go to the restaurant to try to fix them
I can talk a minute?
I am very busy now, Buzzy
You can not give me a minute?
Look ... I understand I should have gone home
as soon as I saw them and tell you
I should not expect me to tell her,
I'm sorry, I fucked up, ok?
I'm scared, Buzzy, very scared
Of what?
I think maybe we rush into this relationship
You're crazy! we are a great couple
we have the perfect arrangement
and these ruined! 'You do not want a "fix"
I want a marriage
and joked all the time
about how things are so random
among us, no dramas,
we never
I think ... maybe we are being naive
that perhaps we are avoiding something
you see what we are avoiding?
We have a great, great
We are avoiding the real life!
I mean, true intimacy
I'm not talking only about sex
I think I was lying to myself
crao I need much more than this
What more do you need? I love you
I love you!, More need than that!?
So why can not you be honest with
I am honest with you! Ok?
sometimes little things do not tell
I forget to tell you things
those things add up
and I have fear that after 18 years
we are so full of hatred and resentment
Max and Marsha,
and now I look, and not who you are
It seems that your sister was talking,
you know me! Look at me, know me!
I do not know, I'm seeing strange attitudes this week
-If foreign attitudes
I was protecting my sister
can you understand that? she's my sister
If, if, instead of protecting me
your wife
and understand, I understand, you worry about your sister
Yes-but it was surprising to me
because you never hear mention
until this week, until he came to our door
and ... I feel I do not recognize you
and the person I married
I have to go back to work, this is crazy
You took everything out of proportion
I can not believe this happening so fast
Two days ago we were happy ...
and now ... she is cuetionando
if you know me or not
no ... I was speechless ...
Good day! -Good day
want some coffee? -Thanks - for nothing
as you sleep? -Not so good
I had a rare night
Buzzy came out, early morning
Yes, trains several clients, before going to the gym
I tell you something really funny?
Last night it was bothering
and said he would go to a bar
to get up a guy and there cogermelo
wanted to "give back" your stupid
"Sexual comments"
He hated it! ... It was so fun!
Marsha know what?, You stay will not work
What, where did all this?
You do not like Buzzy, and you do not like you the
and just get rid of his sister
and that problem, and not want any more dramas
in my house, I'm trying to do
my marriage work
That is, these from the side of it?
Yes, I am, because he is my husband
and we are trying to overcome things
and I have to give priority
Well, absolutely not!
You stayed with me when you needed a place
Now I need a place, then I am!
I stay
Ok!, I'm going to bed
Ok ... you know, I'm getting divorced!
I have also problems
I just get u $ s 2000 in cash to give
must return to L.A. and not even
what kind of life is there, then ...
better have money in your pocket when you return
Well, here there are 2000 dollars
do me a favor, do not tell Katie gave you the
I do not need both
Yes, you need to cover the plane ticket
and if you decide to return to N.Y
you go to buy a nice coat before he came, shall we?
I remember as a kid
came back home and your life was a mess
as you did to change, become a good guy
with a normal life
When I was in my 20,
also was a total disaster
I realized that if I kept acting like
would end only
And now I see, I see your behavior
and the same will happen to you
Because you hurt yourself;
and hurt people who care about you,
as I
We re last night shit things
a little bit, yeah!
but in a weird way
was a blessing
If? as?
forced me to reevaluate some things ...
I need to make some changes in my life
Yes, maybe I feel a little guilty
I am his older brother and I never had relationship with her
not saw in years
and I made no effort
to keep in touch
But now, I can do
is to try harder, and try
keep in touch periodically
and maybe go to L.A. to see
You still here ... where is Katie?
Go back to sleep
Obviously this very angry about something ...
Ah! entonses you go?
You know, I was your suitcase ready from day one
Coward!
Men are cowards ...
Max is a coward
Katie's first husband, Dara
was definitely a coward
and Buzzy ... could also be a coward
I think things can get more complicated
and it devastated quedría
What are you doing?
Oh, you're awake
I'm packing a suitcase
Why? what happens?
I think lingerie is
I stole my sister or everything?
Buzzy, para, you're doing?
I need to leave town
and I would love to come with me ...
the car is parked at the gate
I can not go anywhere, I have to work!
My first thought, after saying "I do"
I wish that my parents were alive
to see, were in my first marriage
did not,
Buzzy and I think they would have liked, much
My first thought, after we said:
"I do", well, she was pregnant
when we got married 4 months pregnant
I could not wait to get my dress
Neither do I
Yes, but not for the same reason
My heart broke! boom, boom, boom!
After saying "I do" was totally happy
I have an amazing girl, the beautiful
Linda is so different!
the opposite, completely
responsible ...
responsible and loving ...
My real first thought ...
was "just wanted a suck of dick more"
My life before meeting Katie
was always chaotic
My childhood, school, my twenties
until my first marriage
and ... after meeting Katie
a feeling of peace finally came into my life
I think the first thought I had
after saying "I do"
was probably ... a feeling of ...
tranquility or serenity?
Katie is a rock
and do you really need in my life
I think I finally feel
at peace
Then! ... Where are we going?
I have no idea, but I think
we need to go as far
of our relatives as we can
and then what?
and then talk
know and maybe work a little better
sounds good ... let's go
Subtitles by: said.sy@gmail.com