# I'm forkin' on it #
# For I've lived all
my blue days that I need #
# Oh, baby,
I've learned how to care #
# And never really loved
oh, my, my #
# And I'm the world's
most happy creature #
# Tell me what
could worry me #
# I'm crazy 'bout my baby #
# And my baby's
crazy 'bout me, yeah #
# Oh, Mr. Cupid
was my teacher #
# On one reason we agree #
# I'm crazy 'bout my baby
and my baby's crazy 'bout me, yeah #
# Whoa, possum,
get that book out #
# Get that book out #
# Hold it steady,
steady in your hand #
# Understand
an a-1 combination #
# Perfect he and she #
# I'm crazy 'bout my baby
and my baby's so crazy 'bout me #
# Whoa, possum
get that book out #
# Hold it steady
in your hand #
# Look out you
can't understand #
# It's an a-1 combination
a perfect he and she #
# Oh, I'm crazy
'bout my baby #
# And my baby's
crazy 'bout me, yeah #
I got, I got to clean
right there.
Right where
you're standing.
I was lookin'
all over for you.
Vera said you
were getting out today.
Well, you look good,
other than your hair.
'Course, I should talk, huh?
Tell you what. There's
a cafe across the street.
Why don't, you go over there
and get us a table by a window?
Go on. I'll meet
you over there.
Go on.
I'll meet ya.
Thank you. Now boarding through
door five. Service to Seattle.
Can I have five-dollars'
worth of those lotto tickets, please?
Thank you.
Bus number seven is now
ready for boarding with service...
to Spokane, Washington.
Yeah, see ya again.
Thank you, sir.
Come outta there!
That was a dirty
little con you pulled.
- You tried to ditch me back there.
- You can't strong-arm me.
Come outta there!
It's a holiday.
- Millie's birthday.
- How old is she?
Three.
Looks like she's put on some weight.
How much she weigh now?
175 pounds.
I'm not goin' back.
Listen, you can
weep and wallow,
but I wouldn't be doin' you
no favors if I kept you with me.
# I was talkin'
to a lady #
# Just a few days ago #
# And these are
the words she said #
# Oh, Lord #
Hey, I'll go
and check this out.
Hey, baby, what's up?
# Tell him I'm waiting
for my child #
- Thank you.
# To come home #
- You play fair or hardball, Mr. Normandy?
That depends on you.
you're a middleweight criminal,
and I'm hopin' for your sake,
you're retirin'. - I'm seriously considering it.
This early release is a
six-month conditional period, Jack.
if I think it's more
than you can handle,
I'll send you back to serve out
your time, one year. - Ten months, sir.
Says here, you
got a son, Nick.
- What about him?
- Where's he at?
He's livin' with my sister, Vera,
on her farm. He loves it over there.
He's a, you know, hick "4-her",
cows and peas
and all that.
Maybe that's best for now.
- Lookin' for a job?
- I sent over 152 letters asking for one.
- Didn't get no reply.
- Special skills?
No, I can't do nothin'.
Well, here's an opening
for a window washer.
- They hire ex-cons?
- They might.
Can I bum one
of your cigarettes?
Yeah, get one but don't
make no habit out of it.
Keep your piss clean.
Maybe you'll make it on the outside.
You won't get
no trouble from me.
I plan to come through
just like a giant.
- Be strong, brother.
- Yes, sir.
Because you're his aunt.
He's a part of you.
You still got my shoes over there?
Yeah. well, bring 'em
when you come collect the kid.
Yeah. I'm over at Rainey's,
913 spruce.
Shit.
- That my jacket?
- That's my jacket, man.
- No, come on. I need this.
- I had this jacket for five years, man.
It don't even fit
you no more.
- That's your old man, right there.
- I feel like a human being.
Yeah. How about my end?
Where's my end, Rainey?
Your end?
You're sittin' on it, Jack.
No, I... yeah,
I got somethin' for ya.
Just a second.
Let's see.
That's $200, not much.
Yeah, I can get ya another
$200 tomorrow, man, but...
it's the best I can do.
Two-hundred.
- For a six large haul.
- That was five years ago, Jack.
That's taking into account all kinds
of costs over a five-year period.
I was real sad to see you take the fall, Jack.
I'm grateful you didn't give me up.
Hardly worth it for
four stinkin' c-notes.
Yeah.
So where you at, Jack?
You up for some action,
or you walkin' spanish?
I haven't even passed my last
prison meal yet, Rainey.
Yeah, sometimes
I think about givin' it up.
But it's like they say,
it's in the blood, ya know?
The way I figure, man,
you're either the doer
or the do-ee.
Hey.
I cased out a jewelry store
up on Pill Hill, man.
Very sweet. Security guard
is deaf and blind.
Keep it to yourself.
I ain't interested.
Younger generation takin' over?
I ain't lookin'
for a new partner.
You remember me, kid?
Geez.
Don't remember me.
I boosted flowers from the hospital
grounds when you were born, man.
I been there from the beginning, man.
Kind of makes us like brothers.
He's just hanging out. Fact, Vera
and Larry's comin' to collect him tonight.
Larry's a dick.
I ain't goin' back.
I'm sendin' for ya
when I get myself settled.
You can't expect to walk out of
the joint and live a normal life.
- Bullshit.
- What do you mean, bullshit?
You never get settled, Jack.
What's the matter
with Vera's anyway?
You got fresh air,
that pig of a friend.
Come on.
Be a stand-up, kid. God.
Vera did a lousy job raisin' you.
Here. Present
from your old man.
Jack London.
Maybe Vera got lost.
Is that the only
razor you got?
I got one face,
I got one razor.
So, what are we doin' today?
Here.
Take the bus
back to Mount Vernon.
Good to see ya, kid.
Hey.
Where's that ferry goin'?
You got a room?
- Sixty-five a week.
Is it just you? - Yeah.
If there's another person,
that's an extra ten.
Rent's due every friday.
don't be late.
I get very upset.
I break out in a rash.
That's okay.
I'll still like ya.
Now you're gonna follow
my three rules to a tee.
Don't tail me, shadow me..
or any way, shape
or form jam me.
And don't ask me
to hold your stinkin' hand.
'Cause I don't need
the aggravation.
- Don't let Rainey in here
or hang out with him. - That's five.
Hey.
Help me with this.
Grab on to that.
Pull it. Pull it!
All right, we're gonna shoot
to see who gets what.
- What you got,
odds or even? - Odds.
One, two, three.
The mattress.
Get outta the way!
Thanks.
I saw a cow give birth
last week.
I'm sleepin'.
See ya in the mornin'.
what are we doin' today?
I'm goin' to work.
you're goin' to school.
What school?
I don't know. Find one.
Yes?
I need to sign up for school.
- Did you just move here?
- Yeah.
You have your transcripts
from your old school?
Your immunization
records?
You got some stuff to do
before you can register.
Well, certain places don't
work out for certain people.
Since this last time
in the joint, I been thinkin'.
- About what?
- Climbin' up to the roof of the world.
- Where's that?
- Alaska.
Ever since I was a kid,
I dreamed about Alaska.
I never knew that.
- This time I aim
to make it up there. - When?
Well, if I get through
parole, springtime.
I wish we had binoculars.
What'll you do
up there, Jack?
I'll buy some entrepreneurial
type enterprise...
steak 'n' bake.
You know,
catch a meal, bring a reel.
Perpetratin' cons isn't
the only business there is.
Didn't work out for me here,
but up there's gonna be different.
Man can get a fair shake without
everybody breathing down his neck.
Well...
I never really thought
about Alaska.
That's because
it's my dream.
It's not yours.
What kind of job are
you workin' downtown, Jack?
Buildin' supervisor.
I'd like to do that.
You're gonna get yourself
an education.
'Course... without one,
a man of my own technology,
I made whole bunches
of money.
Several fortunes spent.
Well, I'll be makin'
big money real soon.
Real big money.
You got a quarter on ya?
I think so.
"Farwest."
An old pen pal.
7-7-0-0.
I wonder what
she looks like.
Yeah,
is Charlotte there?
Rowe?
Charlotte Rowe?
She works there, right?
A friend.
Can you tell me where
she hangs out then?
All right.
Yeah, thank you.
Hit the ball, Charlotte.
Shut up, Flo, shut up.
Next.
Rack 'em up?
I'm in the middle
of a shift.
Come on.
It's your break.
I'm not in the middle
of a shift.
You're in the middle
of something.
I'm a little... rusty at this.
This whole scene.
"Bam, a piss-cold pittake,
a white fang."
Vernon, I want
a diet coke to go.
You don't know
how many times I've...
dreamed of sittin'
here like this.
About a million times.
Man, what a line.
Watch out for this one.
- I'm not tryin' to hustle you.
- But you're hittin' 'em all.
Next thing you'll be sayin' is,
"Don't I know you from somewhere?"
Yep. Can I... can I see...
For cryin' all night!
Let me guess, a unicorn?
What are you, are you
some kind of psychic?
They say...
the eyes are
the windows of the soul...
and I'm into windows.
- Where ya goin'?
- I told ya. Back to work.
- Well, when can I see you again?
- You tell me, Mr. Psychic.
You mind payin' the tab here?
Well...
see ya.
Meter's on!
Unit 105, you want that
fare on first avenue, or what?
Unit 105. oh, don't.
Don't what, 105?
You start touchin' on me
and you think the sky's the limit.
105, I'm not touchin' you and
you're walkin' on my transmission.
you want that fare
on first avenue or what, 105?
Do you think
I'm an easy night?
You're right.
I'm pushin' this.
- You do?
- What, think you're an easy night?
You wanna come
up for a beer?
I can't.
You're right in the
middle of a shift.
Oh, God.
Who's that?
Nick?
This is Charlotte.
Come on.
- Is that your...
- Yeah.
- You didn't tell me
you had a kid. - I forgot.
My kid's been with relatives.
Hey, there's an all night...
A & W down the block.
Here. It's open all night.
You want me to bring
you back a root beer?
Just take your time.
I might. And I might
just come right back.
And I might take you
to a goddamn home.
This doesn't
really feel right.
Don't worry 'bout him.
He's used to it.
Come on. let's get
a couple of beers, relax.
What kind of a father are ya?
Oh, I'm probably the worst kind,
but I make up for it in other ways.
God, you are a big talker.
- Where ya goin'?
- This doesn't feel right.
So can I see ya tomorrow?
I'll get a baby-sitter.
I'll catch ya next time.
Gimme back my money.
Man, I was trippin'
so fierce yesterday, man,
I thought my heart was just
gonna go boom, right outta my ears.
Yeah, I had
a heart attack once.
I was running away
from my uncle.
- Name's Rollie, man.
- Nick.
Later on.
Stop it, Roy. I'm gonna roast you.
Not you, Creamo. Come here.
You're getting me
all jacked up, Roy!
She likes me,
don't you, Creamo?
She likes anybody.
Stop it, Roy!
- She's got sheepdog in her.
- How do you know?
Oh, the shape of her paw,
her coat.
- Could be a herder.
-It's starting, Molly!
Who's there?
My crib's upstairs.
You sleep in a crib?
So what was it you wanted?
Do you subscribe
to the post?
Celeste had her abortion!
- You need help up there?
- Yeah.
Hey, you gonna go
to school, man?
I don't see the point
in perpetrating that.
Yeah, I dropped out
in sixth grade.
My parents made me
go back, though. It sucks.
- What does your father do?
- He just got a job in construction.
What'd he do before that?
He was in the penitentiary.
What for?
He robbed some banks,
I think.
A bank robber?
Hey, Jack. how ya
doin', man?  Long time.
Listen, I... come on around!
I wanted to talk to you about that
jewelry store, man, get some advice.
- Yeah, well, my advice is get
yourself a new partner. - Come on, Jack.
Let me give ya a lift, ride shotgun.
I got wheels, man.
Come on around!
Asshole.
Get out!
Get outta this house!
- I'm leaving!
- Good!
Go to hell!
Homeboy, you got
an extra crib?
Nick!
Jack, you in there?
Jack?
- Hey, come on, get up.
- What?
Out the window!
I ain't goin' out no window.
Jack, open up!
Jack, Cecil Normandy!
Just don't open it.
I got the landlady here.
She's got the key.
Oh, God. This is a shame.
- Thank you, ma'am. I can
handle it from here. - Makes me sick.
I... I can explain this,
Normandy.
Wha... what, do you think
I'm a pervert?
Datin' 16-year-olds is one thing,
but she's 12 if she's a day.
- I'm 15. - Fifteen will
get him 20. Stay put.
Normandy, I... I wasn't
in the rack with her.
- I never even seen her before.
- What'd you do, black out?
See, it's my kid.
I thought
you had a son.
- Turn around, Jack.
- Normandy, please.
- Get 'em up.
- Man, don't bust me.
What do you expect, man?
You missed your appointment yesterday.
You don't show up
at work today.
And I come to your place,
and you drunk with a minor...
in the middle of the day.
Dad, this is Molly.
This is my parole officer.
Somebody tell me what
the hell's goin' on here.
She lives downstairs and she
needed a place to sleep last night.
I'm bailin'.
Creamo, come on.
Hey!
I thought your son
was stayin' at your sister's.
Well, we're workin'
on a relationship kind of thing.
- I figured, why "pronasticate"?
- Procrastinate.
So why'd you miss
the appointment?
He was helping me
register for school.
That's... that's right.
My kid's gotta get
an education.
What high school
did you put him in?
"Garfield".
That's right.
You're not gonna arrest
him, sir, are ya?
We're just starting out.
He's a real good guy.
I need to know
you can handle this.
I can handle this.
- You sure you can handle this?
- Yes, sir.
Get outta the way.
Jack, you better mind
how you go.
Yes, sir.
See ya in my office in a week.
And you take care,
little brother.
We got outta that jam, huh?
I wouldn't have been in it in the
first place if it wasn't for you.
If I wasn't drinking,
I could have handled it myself just fine.
P.O.'s got his thumb on me.
I gotta walk a line. You understand that?
Shit.
My life would be
a hell of a lot easier without you.
Are you gonna dump me?
- You really goin'
to school? - Yeah, sure.
How come I never see no love
notes from your teacher then?
I leave 'em in my locker.
Molly! Molly!
Take Roy!
I have to work!
Kids. Jesus!
What can you do?
You just gotta know what
you're doin', I guess.
- You been hangin' out
with her? - No.
You pissin' on my leg and tellin'
me it's rainin', farm boy?
- You're not ready for these streets.
- You fucking little selfish tramp!
- I'm selfish. - Yeah, selfish.
- You're just jealous...
because you're old and
you're used up, and you're ugly.
You stick with school.
Here, hold that.
You don't have to take math
or science or any of that crap.
Now, cooking. There.
Now that's a skill.
you could...
be a banquet captain
or some such thing.
or a writer... Jack London.
- He graduated high school,
I think. - You didn't.
Never mind about me. You want to wind
up in the joint and a hand like me?
How about being the first in the
family to make it past ninth grade?
I tell you one thing.
You got good timing.
Could have died of old age in the joint
before Normandy sorted that one out.
So I'm not goin' to a home?
You're here, ain't ya?
Are you anywhere else?
No, you're here.
Yep. It's not easy
being green, is it?
Hey, man.
I got you right here.
Well, my brother says
he'd pick us up tonight.
Hey, baby.
You lookin' for a date?
I know what
you're lookin' for.
Look at Perry.
- How ya doin'?
- All right.
- What do you want,
the works? - Yeah.
Let me see your dick.
I got that baby-sitter.
# Call me up on your telephone #
# And talk to me
for a long, long time #
# Hey, Juanita,
I'm comin' over #
# Yeah, pretty baby #
- Beer is in the refrigerator.
- Where is your refrigerator?
- It's over here.
# Hit the town
and fell in love #
- Where's the bed?
- It's right here.
I just want you to know
I used to be a virgin.
So...
are you involved
with anybody?
Now's a fine time to ask.
Well, I'm just curious.
Well, sort of, yeah.
There is a guy.
Beautiful woman like you,
I wouldn't mind bein' in his shoes.
Oh, yeah, you might.
He's in prison.
Yeah.
- You know this guy before
he went up? - Not exactly.
You see, there's this...
there's this magazine.
- "American Heart"?
- Yeah.
Magazine that puts you in touch
with your inside main squeeze?
P.O. box 553,
Walla Walla state penitentiary.
You, you son-of-a-bitch!
- Wait a minute.
- You pig-dog con man!
All that stuff about seeing into
my soul and that psychic shit.
- Charlotte.
- God, I'm so stupid!
- Charlotte, come on, ease up. - You screwed
me just to check me out, didn't you?
A little test drive, huh?
Char...
hey, you didn't visit me.
You never gave me
your home address.
I was afraid you wouldn't
wanna go out with me.
All right.
Hey, okay, I'm sorry.
I should have been
up-front with you. Let's start over.
- No.
- Hey, I think you like me.
No.
You expressed yourself
real nice in those letters.
Yeah, well,
they were good.
You made me feel
like a human being.
Hey, Nick!
Nick!
Come on down!
I got somethin' for ya!
I'm getting a rash,
Mr. Kelson, a big rash.
Well, that's okay.
I won't think any less of ya.
You owe me a month.
- I can give you half that.
- No. That's not good enough.
I want the whole amount.
I'm not gonna be stuck with your kind.
Come on.
- What is it?
- Never mind. Get on.
All right, get over there.
All right.
What's the matter?
I thought you wanted 'em.
Yeah, I did.
It's kind of expensive
when we're late on the rent.
Don't you have any faith in
your old man? I'll take care of it.
I don't know what's
the matter with you, kid.
That's just it.
You're not a kid.
You're like some loan officer
gloom pussin' around.
Hey, tomorrow's sunday.
What do you wanna do?
When are you gonna teach
me how to play the ukulele?
It's a guitar.
You can learn that anytime.
How'd you like to do somethin'
with a lady friend of mine and me?
She the one
you brought home?
Yeah.
You'll like her.
Here, take a look.
We'll have a beautiful day.
- Am I the only one in here who
can't breathe? - All right, Nick.
We're gettin' "fixicated" in here.
Open that window.
Here.
Is there any ketchup?
You're starin' at her like a goddamn
yard bull. That's one fine lady.
- What do you got to say?
- She goin' to Alaska with you?
Nobody's goin' with me. Start actin'
like a stand-up kid. Don't aggravate me.
Here.
Thanks, lady.
- Charlotte.
- That's me, lady Charlotte.
Well...
best damn hot dog
I ever had.
- Excuse me for eatin' with food in my
mouth. - Pulley Fuss, it's a funny name.
Yeah, french.
Pulley Fusey.
- How much this cost?
- Thirty.
Thirty bucks?
- Here's to you.
- Here's to me.
You like your dogs?
Hey, I'm talkin' to you.
Yeah. Cool.
I like it.
- It don't matter.
- What do you mean, it don't matter?
Get the fuck outta here!
Fuck you, then!
- Now tuck and kick. yeah.
- Yeah, you got it.
All right, do it again.
Check out brother's
dope threads.
- What's happenin'?
- Like we just got out.
- You got a cigarette?
- Man, he's down to the curb.
- Why you dissin' me for, Molly?
- Get back, faggot.
I got somethin' for you.
Dancin' around in a two-piece for frat boys.
Pays good. You dance,
I deals. Easy money.
- One, two, three.
- Leave her alone.
- What'd you say, punk?
- I said, leave her alone.
Now what are you doin'
with my skateboard?
Man! Hey, Stony man,
leave the kid alone, Stony.
Fuck you!
- You punk!  Come on!
- I don't wanna hurt you, Freddie.
You don't have
to hurt me, Stony.
Leave him alone!
You can suck the corn outta
my shit, too, you fuckin' punk!
Get the fuck outta here!
Punk!
Freddie, I could have handled
it if my back wasn't turned.
You gotta watch your back
around here, all right?
Llisten, I been in over
600 fights down here.
My specialty's the hook.
Guess which hand I hook with, huh?
Left's a lot bigger, right?
I hook 'em in the jaw.
- You okay?
- Yeah.
Well, you know, I would
have helped you but...
some two guys jumped me and pinned
my arms, man, and one had a knife.
I should have stomped on 'em.
Rollie, I'm fine.
My dad hit me with a 9:00
curfew, so I... I gotta go.
Listen...
later on, man.
Hey. Howdy.
Did you have fun today?
What are you makin'?
Tomato soup.
Want some?
Has a bona fide
penitentiary aroma.
Did you rob a lot
of banks, Jack?
Why, you think
I'd be good at it?
I was a smart thief.
What did you steal?
What, are you
writin' a book?
All right.
I was in for the quick score.
Jewelry stores.
In and out.
In one minute, I'd be gone.
You can steal
a lot in a minute.
You can steal a lot
in 30 seconds.
When did you start?
You don't start out
robbing a jewelry store.
You work your way up.
From where?
I stole my first car
when I was 12.
I was just about your age.
I stole this beautiful,
brand-new maroon Chevrolet.
Rode that baby
all the way to coos bay.
Two inches off
the ground with girls.
Gave it a while,
I got pretty good at it.
If I ever catch you with your
fingers where they don't belong...
- Yeah? - I'll string you
up by your short hairs.
What are you worried
about me for?
Yeah, you got that right.
I got enough to worry about.
Things could be
different for you.
- What's the matter?
What happened? - Nothing.
- Well, come here.
Let me see. - I said nothing.
- Let me see.
- Ouch!
Nothing?
Come here.
There you go.
That's it. All right.
Okay, okay, okay. Turn around.
All right, put your hands up.
That's it.
Now chin down.
There you go.
Now look mean.
Mean.
Mother of Jesus.
You don't have to worry.
I can take on two guys.
Yeah?  You punch one guy,
the other guy falls, huh?
Somethin' like that.
You're slight in the butt.
You better not go to prison.
Hey, Nick!  Nick!
Come here for a second.
Hop in. I wanna talk
to you for a second.
How ya doin'?
Where you at these days?
What are you doin' for pocket money?
- I just got a paper route.
- Is that right?
Your old man
is a righteous dude.
Taught me everything I know.
I could see it, man.
You got the bloodlines of a pro.
Now I'm lookin'
for a back pair of eyes.
Pay's good. No risk.
I think you're the one.
Why me?
'Cause I see somethin' in you.
I got a feel for this.
I know your old man
just got outta the joint.
But believe me, he had a lot of fun
doin' this. He was good at it too.
Think about it.
- What's in the T, Mary?
- Get your hands out of his pants, Derrick.
- Well, is he a he or a she?
- I'm a he.
- How old are you, nine?
- Shit, I'm 15.
You don't look but nine.
I better not catch you
downtown. You're too cute.
Show us somethin'
you do on the farm, boy.
Cop!
# Down in the street
makin' all that noise #
# Don't want no whores on eighth avenue #
- Come on, it's your shot.
# 'Cause tonight
I'm gonna be with you #
I'm gonna take that ride #
- Did you win?
# Cross the river to the Jersey side #
Feels like it.
# And take my baby
to the carnival #
# And I'll take you
on all the rides #
# Down the shore
everything's all right #
# You with your baby
on a saturday night #
# Don't you know
all my dreams come true #
# When I'm walkin'
down the street #
# With you... #
You goin' home
to that old jailbird?
His girlfriend's
probably still there, I bet.
You can stay with me if you
promise not to rip my mom off.
- I owe you a favor.
- You don't owe me a favor.
Nobody better
rip Diane off.
My dad, he remarried
a long time ago.
I've never seen him since.
He lives in Tacoma.
I know he's got new kids.
He has one my age.
I wonder if she's like me.
Close your eyes. You can't kiss
me if you're mad doggin' me.
- But I wanna see you.
- Why?
'Cause I think you're
pretty to look at.
Okay!
Oh, Molly!
Who the hell am I,
the old woman in the shoe?
Oh, shit.
Somebody stole
my fucking dress!
This time, Molly,
I am really gonna kill you.
- You don't believe me?
-I do.
I thought you weren't hanging
out with her. She's not our type.
- Do you like her?
- Yeah, I like her.
Okay, so you like her.
Is she your first?
- What do you mean?
- Your first time out.
You mean my first time out?
Probably. I would say
most probably.
Now I know what it's
like your first time.
They can break your heart. But you gotta
remember, you're a good-looking kid.
You got my looks.
You gotta learn to keep your heart.
See? Let them lose theirs;
you keep yours.
That's the trick
of bein' a heartbreaker.
Did you break
my mom's heart?
Maybe I did.
Why are you telling
me all of this?
Because that's the way a father
and son should be together.
I'm just tryin' to do for you
what nobody ever did for me.
Don't put all your beans in one pot, Nick.
There'll be hundreds of dames.
She's not a dame.
That ain't her
first time around.
What do you know about her?
Hey, I'm just tryin'
to keep you straight!
You keep me straight;
I keep you straight.
- Give it here.
- Okay, you have to read it.
Smells like me.
- Return to sender. - Yes.
-Okay. - I got that in the mail.
"Dear sweet Jack."
"It's four in the morning.
the rain is pouring down.
"I wanna kiss your big mouth...
your sweet mouth... your sweet mouth.
"and lie down with you under
a big, big, big tree...
"on wet the mossy ground.
on wet the mossy ground.
Oh, God. and the droopy violets
brush against our nakedness."
brush against...
- I can't read anymore of this.
- Oh, why not?
My shorts are too tight.
And my kid's around.
What do you think of him?
I can't tell if it's an
actor if he's a sad kid.
Yeah, I know
what it's like to be 14 and sad.
He never really
had a mother.
# Grab your coat
and get your hat #
# Take your worries
to your doorstep #
# Just direct your feet #
# To the sunny side
of the street #
# Don't you hear
the pitter-pat #
# And that happy
tune is yourself #
I sang that song to you a long time
ago when you visited me in Walla Walla.
You and me are
goin' north, Nick.
But...
- You said... - Yeah, I know.
I changed my mind.
Hey, when it's 50 below in the
Klondike, a man needs a partner.
Hey, I finally got
a rise out of this kid.
Here, drink up if you
got hair on your ass.
Gulp!
To Alaska.
Hey, don't I rate a beer?
Oh, I guess.
Here you go.
All right, come on.
- Okay. - When are we
goin' to Alaska, Jack?
Well, not tomorrow.
Remember that
picture of mom?
Yeah.
She was a model, right?
Sort of.
Did you ever know your mom?
Yeah, for about three hours,
and I've never seen her since.
How about your dad?
What is this,
more for your book?
My dad was an asshole.
Weird, I wish I'd got
to know him anyway.
When I was born,
what did you like about me?
You know what
I liked about you?
Nothin'.
How you had a nice laugh
when I stole your nose.
We didn't see too
much of each other.
You know what
I liked about you?
You sang me songs.
All right, real easy.
I'm gonna go in, get me two beads.
Duck as low as you can on the floor.
I'll distract them. Just...
"Lusty Lady"
We run from 11:00
until 3:00 a.m.
Yeah, well we...
Yeah, go on.
We start with ruby at 11:00,
end up with raven at 12:30.
# Darlin' don't say a word
'cause I already heard #
# What your body's
sayin' to mine #
# I'm tired of fast moves
I got a slow groove #
# On my mind #
# I want a man
with a slow hand #
# I want a lover with
an easy touch # - Mom!
# I want somebody who will
spend some time # - Get out!
# Not come and go
in a heated rush #
# I want somebody
who will understand #
# When it comes to love
I want a slow hand #
- Did you get my dress
back, Molly? - Mom!
Can we leave Roy here,
and can I have some money, mom?
Do I look like
I have my purse on me?
You better get
my dress back.
Son-of-a-fuckin'-bitch!
It ain't my fault.
- Was it that guy who isn't a guy,
Terry what's-his-name? - I'm not a snitch.
You gonna run around all day
with your cutie pie,
or are you gonna take care
of Roy like you're supposed to?
Hi.
Bubble Gum, what're ya doin'?
They're minors.
This is totally
against house rules.
Fuck the rules. What about all this
nurturing attitude we're supposed to have?
I'm nurturing here. You're not staying
with me tonight unless you get my dress back.
I am very upset
with you, Molly.
Nicole, can you get the kids
something to drink? Please.
And I think there's
a popsicle left for Roy.
You've got about
another minute on your break.
You're gonna get me fired.
Well I ain't sittin' Roy either.
I'm tired of this shit.
I need money, mom.
I got five more hours
left on stage, Molly.
How much money
do you need?
Nothin'. I'll get it.
I'd shoot the guys
who killed those animals.
I'd look filthy
in one of them fur coats,
- Driving a fast car like a "testaroni" or
somethin'. - Homeboy's gettin' the words.
Aren't those wicked? Aren't those
the prettiest shoes you ever saw?
I once showed up in a dress
downtown just for the fuck of it.
- And nobody recognized me.
I looked good too. - Oh, yeah.
I want those shoes.
I want 'em bad.
- You want the butt ugly ones?
- I know what's comin' next.
Shut up, Freddie!
You wouldn't get those
for a working girl like me.
- Would you, homeboy?
- Come on, let's go.
What, you really like this cleaning
business, Jack? See a future in it?
Tell you what.
There's no end to dirt.
Come on, listen to reason,
would you, Jack?
Here's the reason. I been
walking sideways my whole life.
What are you doin'?
Remember the
good times, Jack?
- What are you gonna do for real
money, Jack? - This is real money, Rainey.
Everything I ever taught you
is bullshit. I'm sorry for it.
Are you shittin' me, Jack?
You got somethin' planned.
I know it.
If I have to work neck deep in shit for
the rest of my life, it's better than jail.
It's over, finished.
I want you out of
my life, get it?
Stay away from me.
Keep away from us.
Keep my name outta your mouth.
If that's the way
you want it, Jack.
- What you got there, Nick?
- Nothin'.
Give me those.
They're mine.
What the hell?
You a fruiter?
No, they're not mine.
They're for somebody else.
- Where'd you get the money for these?
You steal 'em? - My aching ass.
Yeah, you did too.
For her, right?
You could put me back
in the joint for this.
I'll get rid of 'em.
No, I'll get rid of 'em.
Fuck!
What are you messing
with that weed for?
Look at me when
I'm talking to you!
- Marijuana has medicinal purposes.
- Oh yeah?  How do you know?
I read it in a book.
That's the biggest bunch
of bullshit I ever heard.
What else are you doin'?
Let me see your arms.
Get off my back. I stole them
'cause I'm saving my money for Alaska.
Oh, I see.
That's real smart.
You land in Juvie,
I'll go north myself,
back to plan A.
Where'd you get this?
I didn't steal it.
I earned it.
It's for our tickets.
First thing's first.
We almost have enough to pay off
the landlady to keep her off my back.
Another week,
we'll make it.
Why won't she take half?
So she could give us
the bum's rush.
Nut we ain't gonna
let that happen.
- You wanna go for a bike ride?
- Sure.
It's a good thing
you're such a shrimp.
I don't know when
I'm ever gonna grow.
When I was your age,
I was small.
- You were? - Yeah, then
I grew to how I am now.
Fishermen up there, they're
dying for a 'New York steak'.
Cruise around in one of these tubs
selling steaks and gas at inflated prices.
Make a fortune. How's that
for a dream? Not bad, huh?
Not bad.
How much money
do we have now?
About $200. If we save
our pennies we'll make it.
Are you gonna come with
me when I leave town?
Will you come with me
to this party?
If you come with me
when I leave town.
- Whereabouts
you goin'? - "G-nome."
- Where is that?
- G-nome, Alaska.
I hear there's mass
money in Anchorage.
You wouldn't be
selling yourself.
I'd find a straight job,
working construction.
There's places up there
no man has ever set foot.
Just wolves and bears.
I don't know, maybe.
All right now,
put your arms like this.
- Like this?
- No.
All right.
All right, ready?
One, two, three.
And down, down, down.
We got beat!
You see anybody
walkin' out with my bike?
Our policy is to keep the doors
open during business hours.
Mr. Kelson,
I want the full amount.
Can you cut me a little
rhythm on that?
I can't feed Lisa
on rhythm.
I just got beat.
Just a temporary setback.
It'll slide back my way.
Mr. Kelson?
I want you out of here.
I'll get you the money.
You all right?
Telephone.
Hey, Nick?
I'm in kind of
a situation here.
Bring my pants.
I'm on the corner of...
Whistler and Madison.
Jack?  Jack!
Evicted.
Well, that's it.
Flat broke.
Three days, we'll be
hugging the pavement.
- It'll be okay.
- It's all fucked!
You can't give up, Jack.
We'll get there.
Yeah, after 8,000
more fuckin' windows.
What are you talking about?
My job, boy.
Washin' windows.
Washing windows?
You said you had a job in construction.
You're a building supervisor.
So, I lied.
Ain't the first time.
All you've been doing is lying to me since the
day you left me back there in the bus station.
Put your mouth in park, thief,
and get in your room.
I don't have a room.
Well, then get out!
You're crampin' my style.
Where are you goin'?
Hey! I'm talkin' to you!
You're a fuck-up, and
you're gonna fuck me up too!
Don't bother with that.
It only looks like your mother.
She was no model. I'll tell
you what she was a whore.
A five-dollar street whore!
My parents are breathing
holy hellfire down my neck.
Sure as shit they're gonna call
a cop or somethin' if they find you.
What you gonna do?
I don't know.
I can't go back there, Rollie.
That's cold your old
man threw you out.
You're a genius, Nick.
You don't deserve this.
Wake up before
my dad finds you.
Brothers forever, man.
Aren't you gonna go out
there and look for him?
He's 14. he's got
lessons to learn.
Yeah, he's 14. Remember what it was
like to be 14 and out on the street?
Yeah. he'll be scared, it'll be cold,
he'll be hungry, he'll come back.
You didn't. You had to get
drug back by the authorities.
- Just leave it alone.
- Is that what you want?
He'll come back when he's ready
to appreciate how good he's got it.
Come back to where?
He can't go back
to battery street.
You could stay at my place.
Nick can too.
- How's it going?
- All right.
You have a place
to stay tonight?
It's terrible. I know how it feels
not to have a roof over your head.
Look, I have an extra bed.
You can stay there.
I'd like to help out if I can.
My name's Steve.
What's yours?
Harold.
You're a nice-looking
kid, Harold.
Did that make you
uncomfortable?
Or did you like it?
Hey!
I'm sorry. I thought
you were somebody else.
- You seen Nick?
- Nick? Who's Nick?
- My kid. Remember?
- Oh, yeah, Molly's cutie pie.
He's on the streets,
too, now, huh?
Kids. What are you gonna do?
- Wanna get a drink?
- No, I'm lookin' for Nick.
Talk to Freddie. Everybody
down here knows Freddie.
If you see Molly,
tell her to come home.
# Do you wanna touch
do you wanna touch, yeah #
# Do you wanna
touch me there, where #
# Do you wanna touch
do you wanna touch, yeah #
I could've had Barbie do it,
but I wanted you.
And you're better-lookin' than Cathy.
I'll give you 20 more dollars than her.
Come with me.
Get out of here. Get out of this place.
I need to do this.
I need the money.
I don't wanna go down there to G-nome
or whatever. I'm happy with my life here.
# My, my, my
Whiskey & Rye #
# Don't it make
you feel so fine #
# Uh, uh, uh
gonna turn you on #
# Can't you see we're
wastin' time, yeah #
# Do you wanna touch
do you wanna touch, yeah #
# do you wanna touch me there,
where do you wanna touch #
There you go. Half a yard each,
since you decided to bring a friend.
- Fifty bucks?
- Beats the minimum wage.
That's okay. I didn't do
anything, right? I just stood there.
That's what a lookoutmdoes, man.
There's more where that came from.
Next time, come inside;
I'll cut you in.
- I can't get caught.
- Me neither, man.
Hey! It's a bird's nest
on the ground, man.
Hey!
Wait a minute, Nick!
- Where you been?
- Been living.
- What've you been doin'?
- That's none of your business.
- Hey, I'm responsible for you!
- Bullshit!
Hey!  I'm stayin' at Charlotte's!
I want you to stay there too.
Hey, Jack! Don't do me
any favors, remember?
- We have to pick ourselves back up.
- I'm going to Alaska.
Where in the crap
have you been?
- Where have you been?
- I told you, living!
- Where?
- And when I die, I die!
You wanna live out in
the street, big tough guy?
- Have you gone and seen me sleeping
on the streets? - Have you been hustlin'?
- And eating on the streets?
- Have you been peddlin' your ass?
You wa... wait
right there! Hey!
That's right!
Just keep running!
Just run away.
What are you lookin' at?
- What the hell are you doing?
- Family problem, sir.
This isn't a crisis center.
It's a bank.
It won't happen again.
I said I'm sorry.
We could lose customers
with this kind of nonsense.
- I said, I'm fucking sorry.
- What did you say to me?
- I said, blow it out your ass.
- You're fired.
I do a good job here.
Hey, you can't take my job away.
Charlotte?
I was afraid somethin' like this was
gonna happen. His mother was a mess.
He was comin' along, learnin' stuff.
He had a hell of a potential.
Tthat kid could've been anything.
What happened to him?
- He isn't dead.
- No, not yet.
Why do you think
he's out there?
He started hanging out with that
chippie downstairs and those street punks.
Next, he's coming home with a pair
of high heels. The rest is history.
You don't think filling up
that boy's head with dreams,
and then kicking him out on his
ass had anything to do with it?
Hey, when he came to me,
he didn't have any dreams!
He had nothin'.
He had a picture of a pig.
Don't pin that rap on me.
I'm out there bustin' my hump...
while this little wiseass punk
is out there thievin'.
Gettin' mouthy. I take him in,
and he gets mouthy.
You miss him.
It's all falling apart on me.
I wasn't afraid in prison,
and now I'm, I'm really scared.
I don't know
if I can help the kid.
I don't know if I have
anything good to give him.
He needs so much.
This is no good. I gotta turn this
around, get some money quick.
How are you gonna do that?
I got my ways.
Are we going back
to jailhouse correspondence?
I gotta split.
You should find somebody
better than me.
You're all right by me.
I want to be with you.
Shut the door.
It's a nice house.
Hey, what can we do with this?
Is it worth anything?
Beats me.
Take it.
God!
Stale.
- Your hair's getting kind of
long, you know that? - Yeah.
You'll have to get
a little cut here.
Did you just hear something?
- No.
- Hey, check this out.
Hey, goldfish don't
have teeth, do they?
Yeah they do, look.
What are you doing
in my room?
Freeze.
Close the door, boy.
- Rollie, put it away.
- I'm gonna get my dad!
Put it down, Rollie! Jesus!
- Look what you did, you big dummy!
- You're supposed to keep watch!
- You were! You're such a bonehead!
What the hell
is going on in here?
Rollie.
Oh, my God!
Nick!
It's me!
Freddie told me you'd be here.
What's wrong?
Jack, I wanna come home.
Hey, what's all the tears?
What are you cryin' for?
Rollie's dead,
and it's my fault.
What happened?
Me and him, we broke
into this house.
There was a gun,
and this man came in.
We were fighting, and the
gun went off and Rollie got shot.
He's dead.
All right.
- Listen. people like us, we make
a lot of mistakes. - I wish I was dead.
You can't roll over and die
every time somethin' goes south.
You gotta...
pick yourself up, get on with life.
There's nothin' you can do
to bring that boy back.
Now listen to me.
We're goin' north, okay?
You keep me straight;
I keep you straight.
We'll feel clean up there.
we won't have to keep runnin'.
See, I never told you, but I
used to be a runner, just like you.
Now listen, was there anybody who saw you in
that house? Anybody that might rat on you?
- Rainey.
- Rainey?
Didn't I tell you to
stay away from Rainey?
All right.
Never mind that now.
Here.
Now, I want you to get the
tickets, and leave one for me.
Then get on that ferry and
wait for me. I'll meet you there.
- I think it leaves around 7:00 or 8:00.
- Where are you going?
- I got business to
take care of. - Don't leave.
- I'm not going anywhere. I just gotta
go somewhere. - Please don't go.
- Please.
- I'll meet you on the ferry.
Now, can you stay out of
trouble from now 'til then?
Okay.
From here on in,
you're all I got.
Unfortunately
I'm all you got.
What's up, Jack? You scared me, man.
I thought you were the cops.
Where are you goin'?
What're you packin' for?
You fucker!
I kept your ass out of jail!
There are a million
punks on the street.
Why'd you pick on Nick?
What are you...
Gonna do, Jack, kill me?
I told you, you son-of-a-bitch.
Come here!
Get the fuck out of here!
You mother fucker!
I'm takin' my end, Rainey.
Look out!
Get out of my way!
Give me my money!
Stop 'im!
What do you know, kid,
we made it.
I've been lookin' all over
for you. Give me a hand.
I don't feel so good.
What's the matter?
I never was much of a sailor.
- Should I get a doctor?
- No, no. stay here. Don't leave.
Stick by your dumb old dad.
People are gonna tell you
you're no good. Don't listen.
Whatever's happened, I wanna see
you make it up there, little man.
Things could be different for you.
You won't have to keep runnin'.
I did the best I could.
I'm not gonna
let you off the hook.
# Now ring the bell backwards
and bury the ax #
# Fall down on your knees
in the dirt #
# I'm tied to the mast
between water and wind #
# Believe me
you'll never get hurt #
# My ring's in the pawn shop
the rain's in the hull #
# Down at the five
points I stand #
# I'll lose everything but
I won't let go of your hand #
# Now Peter denied
and Judas betrayed #
# I played with the roll
of your drum #
# And the wind will tell
the turn from the wheel #
# And the watchman's
making his rounds #
# Will you leave me hanging
by the skin of my teeth #
# I've only got
one leg to stand #
# You can send me to hell,
but I'll never let go of your hand #
# Swing from the rope
on a cross and a dream #
# Some would watch
you explode #
# From temple to union
to where they have been #
# Walkin' back
home in the mud #
# I must make my best
of the only way home #
# Mourning is only in stones #
# I'm lost on the midway
I'm reckless in your eyes #
# Just give me
a couple more throws #
# I'll dare you to dine
with a cross late at night #
# Dare me to jump and I will #
# I'll fall from your grace
but I'll never let go of your hand #
# I'll never let go
of your hand #