Solo's the perfect soldier.
He's proficient at all types
of combat.
He has no family, no friends...
not even a Social Security number.
Mf he's wounded beyond repair...
we throw him away.
No guilt, no worries...
no medical benefits.
No one will cry when Solo is gone.
We'll simply build another one.
Solo, you're up.
One's hot.
Head's up, Solo.
You got company.
Four's up.
Where the hell is he?
Blue Water, you clear?
We got a problem here.
Son of a bitch!
Blow it.
Solo isn't clear.
Go! Move out! Move out!
Move, move, move!
Move out!
Let's go! Come on!
Go, go, go! Come on! Go!
Where's Solo?
Forget Solo! He's history!
Jesus! What the hell was that?
Get him in! Pull him in!
We've been hit!
Ooh, yeah.
That's a nice bug.
Yes, Bill, the anthropods
are well designed for their tasks.
So, how's the damage?
Is it bad?
No, not really.
Yeah, I get it.
Let's take a look at this.
See what we got.
Come here, baby.
Whew! That's some nasty stuff.
Wow. Man, you're leaking
everywhere.
Guess things didn't go too well
out there, did they?
No, Bill. The mission's objectives
were not achieved.
It's more than that, isn't it?
It's about killing again.
Let's see here.
Oh, shit.
Your power management chip's damaged.
You're gonna have to switch over
to reserve power until I can replace it.
- Ready?
- Ready.
All right. You're on
your backup generator, kid.
So none of that funny superhero stuff
till I replace the chip, all right?
- Okay.
- Cool.
You better download your video
and mission data into the mainframe.
Meet me in the ward room
for the debriefing.
I'm serious. Clyde is pissed.
I'll see you up there.
There. You see it?
He's disarming the charges.
I thought you understood
the directive, Solo.
Yes. Elimination.
That's right. The directive was to
destroy that airstrip...
and eliminate any aggressors
we designate.
- Are we talking the same language here?
- Oh, yes.
Delete, ice, kill, fuck 'em up.
Destroy 'em. Wipe 'em out.
- Terminate.
- Use your own goddamn voice!
Chill.
I'm chilling, Bill.
Your turn, Mr. Wizard.
- Why didn't you follow the directive?
- The directive was overridden.
You disobeyed a direct order
and you blew this goddamn mission!
Which command set
overrode the directive?
Command set 346.
What's that command set 346?
Prevent harm to unit team members
and noncombatants.
They were working for the G's.
That makes them combatants.
They were unarmed and nonaggressive,
therefore the directive was overridden.
You hear that?
Do you hear that?
We're out there fighting for our lives
and it's deciding which team it's on.
That's enough.
Solo, you're dismissed.
I'll talk to you in a minute.
Bill, there's something cooking in that
boy's head, and we didn't put it there.
General, we needed him
to think for himself.
The amazing fact here is that killing
innocent people makes Solo feel bad.
Feel bad?
He isn't supposed to feel anything.
He's a goddamn weapon!
When's he gonna start
acting like one?
He's not just a weapon,
he can make decisions.
- That's bullshit!
- At ease, Colonel.
Look, Bill...
we have two billion dollars
tied up in this program.
When are you gonna build us one
that'll work?
General, you wanted my evaluation.
Well, here it is.
This tin can of his is an insult.
It's a slap in the face
to every American soldier...
who ever put his life on the line
for God and country.
You may not like it...
but my recommendation is that
we cut our losses and move on.
General, it's a glitch.
I can fix him. I just need some time.
All right, Bill, fix him.
But not here in the field. Shut him
down. Take him back to Palmdale.
- Reprogram him there.
- General...
That's it.
Clyde, we are so close.
It's all over. Wake up
and smell the hydraulic fluid.
At least let me tell Solo myself.
Tell him? What for?
Because it's the right thing to do.
All hands, stand down.
Return fo Your position.
Priority outgoing transmission
on Milnet.
Yes, sir.
Well, Captain,
time to get out of Dodge.
Right away, sir.
Helmsman, bearing
two-eight two-niner. Northwest.
Solo, you're not supposed
to be in here.
Notify security.
What's the matter?
Couldn't sleep?
That's a joke, brother.
Yes, joke...
brother.
Hey, wait a minute, man!
What's going on up there?
Attention. All hands to stations.
All hands report to stations.
This is a Class-A alert.
Sir, someone's opened the helo hatch.
- Well, shut it.
- I can't.
The computer won't let me in.
It's Solo.
Solo, this is Bill.
Do you copy?
What's with the
unscheduled flight, buddy?
I saw a very troubling message
on Milnet.
The one requesting
project reprogramming.
He accessed your Milnet transmission.
Blue One, this is Red Six Actual. Return
to base now. That's a direct order.
I am sorry, General Haynes,
but I am unable to comply.
Go find him. Bring him back here before
somebody else gets their hands on him.
- My pleasure.
- In one piece, Colonel.
I don't want a scratch on that
shiny head of his. Do you read me?
Loud and clear, General.
This is Blue Six. We are clear
and initiafing our pursuit.
Roger, Blue Six.
You're cleared for pursuit.
If we cancel the reprogramming request,
will you come back?
No, Bill.
If I return to the ship, logic suggests
my long-term memory would be deleted.
Such deletions would terminate self.
That is unacceptable.
There he is... 3:00!
Get on him now!
This is Blue Six. We're losing him, Red
Six. I'm gonna have to bring him down.
What are you talking about?
He's got nowhere to go.
You can't just blow him out of the sky.
He wasn't designed to sustain that.
Then you'll have to patch him up,
won't you?
That's what you're here for,
isn't it?
Use your own judgment, Blue Six.
You heard the general, Mr. Thompson.
Let's smoke him.
I need a lock!
What the hell is he doing?
He's headed straight for the mountain.
He's bluffing.
He'll never make it.
Droids don't bluff!
Red Six, Blue One is down.
Be advised.
It was a real humdinger.
Roger, Blue Six.
Go down and pick up the pieces.
We gotta put Humpty Dumpty
back together again.
Blue Six Actual to Red Six.
This is Red Six.
Is Blue One damaged?
That's a negative, Red Six.
Hook him up and bring him home ASAP.
I would love to, Red Six,
but he is gone.
What do you mean, gone?
Your boy has slipped his leash.
We've lost him.
Goddamn it!
Don't you people have anything to do?
Let's go.
Solo, I know you can hear me.
Hey, buddy.
I know what you're going through.
And it's just like a bad acid frip,
and it's only gonna get worse.
Remember, I pulled
your power management chip.
So even if you find
an external power source...
your backup generator's onlY good
for a couple of charges.
So please, just broadcast
your position and I'll come get you.
All right, buddy.
It's time to pick a face.
You don't mind if
I watch the game, do you?
All right, let's see what we got.
"Collins. Special Forces.
Delta team." No.
"'David Lee."
Oh, kind of short.
We cut him.
What if mY name wasn't in lights?
What if my face wasn't on TV
every other second?
What if I was just
a basketball player?
Like Mike.
Can you imagine it?
I can.
You got good taste.
Egg, man.
The egg is in your hand.
You got the egg, man, in your hand.
All right, hold it lightly.
What is that sound?
It's laughter.
It means I thought
something was funny.
- Like a joke.
- Define "joke."
A joke is something
that makes people laugh.
The eggs are a joke?
A joke is...
- It's very difficult to define.
- Apparently.
What, are you a wise guy?
Try it again.
Come on.
That's perfect. Perfect.
- That's not part of the demonstration.
- It is now.
I'll show you where he is.
Miguel, if you are lying...
He's in there, Papa.
I swear.
Is he dead?
He's cold.
The snake bit him.
He's an American soldier.
Just leave him there.
He saved my life.
We must bury him.
My son is right.
We should give him a proper burial.
Good morning.
I hope I'm not interrupting anything.
But, please, tell me...
why aren't you working?
What is this, a funeral?
What the hell?
Why didn't you tell me?
Peasant.
- He's already dead.
- Oh, yeah?
- Then this won't hurt.
- No!
Let's get out of here.
Get out of my way.
This is no man.
Of course it's a man.
What else could it be?
It is the Yacayo.
Yes, the forest spirit
who walks as a man.
The eater of human flesh.
Then why would he save
the boy from the snake?
To eat him later.
You've been eating
too many mushrooms, Abuelita.
The snake bit him.
He did not die.
Yacayo cannot die.
- We should ask him what he wants.
- Good idea. Go ahead.
No, not me!
Justos is the leader.
Yes, you go.
Who are you?
What were you doing in the temple?
Recharging.
Recharging?
It's the Yacayo.
- What is he?
- He is some thing, a machine.
A robot that looks like a man.
- What's he doing now?
- He's been working all night.
Where did he come from?
Perhaps he will leave
once he repairs himself.
Or perhaps he will stay.
Let's hope so.
Are you crazy? He can't stay here.
The rebels will kill us if they find out
we've got an American soldier here.
Maybe he will fight on our side.
What do you know about fighting?
You are farmers.
But he's a soldier.
He could help us.
I will ask him myself.
Justos, be careful.
The television...
what is its power source?
Are there more like you
back in America?
No. There's another weapon being built,
but he's not yet operational.
Will he be just like you?
My builders are not happy with me.
I assume he will be
programmed differently.
These rebels...
like the ones in the church...
they killed one of ours two days ago.
Why don't you defend yourselves?
We don't know how.
Will you help us?
You will provide me with electricity.
I will show you
how to defend yourselves.
This will be mutually beneficial.
You, you and you, there.
Go.
Here, here...
there, there.
You, you and you, gather the palms.
You, dig.
There.
Are you damaged?
- What you did was not logical.
- What?
Why did you risk your life?
Francisco's my brother.
He's family.
Look at this.
This is a Mauser.
Very clean.
It hurts. Don't touch it.
- What's wrong?
- I think my ankle's broken.
I'm sorry.
Sorry. Let me take a look at it.
Psych.
I'm gonna get you.
You monkey. You better run.
I'm gonna catch you.
Watch it when I catch you.
- But he was hurt.
- What?
He was hurt, then he got up and ran.
No, he wasn't hurt.
He was bluffing.
Bluffing?
Miguel's not hurt?
No, he's not.
Miguel lied.
He bluffed.
A bluff is not a lie?
You have much to learn
about humans, my friend.
Report to pod one
for arrival of Zulu feam.
What the hell is going on?
When you hunt a fox...
bring your own dogs.
- How are you?
- Check out the suit, Colonel.
- Bayne.
- Long time, Colonel.
- Did you bring it?
- Yeah, I brought it.
- What the hell we huntin', battleships?
- I'll tell you later.
All right, listen up, gentlemen.
Dr. Stewart.
Solo was designed to be
the perfect fighting machine.
He can use any weapon ever made.
He's about 15 times stronger,
ten times faster than any man.
His polymer structure makes
him virtually immune to small arms fire.
He's equipped with infrared,
motion sensors and night vision.
Aside from that, you guys
got a real pushover on your hands.
Excuse me, Dr. Stewart.
Isn't it also true...
that Solo's got a hole in his side
about the size of a grapefruit?
- That's correct.
- And he's also losing power, I believe.
Has to stop and recharge his batteries
from time to time?
So while on a good day...
he might be invulnerable to small arms
fire or conventional weaponry...
Mr. Solo's not exactly having
a good day today, is he?
No, he's not.
If you gentlemen would check
your monitors...
I'll show you what I'm talking about.
There's his soft spot.
Our window of opportunity.
I thought you might be hungry.
What's below here?
This structure's not solid.
Oh, the tunnels.
Putayo was built on top
of the city of our ancestors.
Tunnels run underneath
the entire village.
Show me.
Where do these tunnels terminate?
Here. The chamber of warriors.
We don't use these chambers anymore.
We have no warriors.
You're lucky you had no need
for warriors.
These symbols are similar
to the hieroglyphics of ancient Egypt.
Your people have a long history.
You must have some brain
in that head of yours.
My brain is not in my head.
My brain is here.
This is what makes me me.
If your brain is in your chest,
then where's your heart?
I have no heart.
Hearts are for living creatures.
But you are alive.
I exist.
- What is it?
- They're coming. Ring the bell.
Is it time?
It's time. Go.
No!
Go back!
Get out!
Move back!
Up there!
This way!
What's up?
We're picking up
erratic heat signatures from NEOS.
It looks like a battle.
We got him.
Move out!
Let's go!
Go, go, go, go, go!
- Where are you going?
- With you.
He's not a member of my team.
Lorenzo's our best tracker.
He's on the team.
Lorenzo, get aboard.
I want Solo back
in one piece, Colonel.
Absolutely.
Lorenzo!
You got point! Move out!
It's Solo.
Looks like he found some friends.
Noncombatants, my ass.
There's a village up this path.
We're going this way.
- Solo went this way, sir.
- So?
What about the mission?
Directive 1138
just got itself overridden.
By whose authority?
Mine. You got a problem
with that, Sergeant?
Access denied.
You're out of your mind if you think
this is going to solve anything.
We're just keeping our options open.
What do you mean, your options?
What about Solo?
Unfortunately, Solo's proven himself
to be unreliable.
So I'm resigning. All right?
I've resigned.
- If you think that's appropriate.
- Excuse me, General.
We're receiving a scrambled video signal
coming in from Blue Team leader.
Bring it up.
- Thank you, Captain.
- Sir.
Red Six. This is Blue Team leader.
We saw fhe smoke.
I sent Blue Two to recon.
When we arrived...
He'd gone mad, sir.
- Who, Blue Six?
- Solo, sir.
- This is bullshit. He's full of shit.
- Solo did that?
- This doesn't make any sense.
- He's gone tofally renegade.
Blue Six, you have the authority
to capture and bring Solo back...
using any means necessary.
- I repeat, any means.
- Copy that, sir.
I know how he thinks.
Send me in there.
It was your goddamn design
that got us here in the first place!
With all due respect, Bill might be
of some use in locating Solo.
- You sure?
- Absolutely.
All right, you can go,
but remember, Madden's in charge.
I don't want any bullshit.
You bring him back if you can.
If you can't, I want him
to disappear without a trace.
I want this thing over with now.
Go get your gear.
Thank you, sir.
- Are we out?
- We're clear.
What about this...
What guy? Let's go.
We gathered every appliance
we could get.
You can repair yourself again.
My sister's radio.
AM and FM.
You can stay here with us, Solo.
This can be home.
- The party's started.
- They're waiting for us!
You saved them.
They think you're a hero.
It's not over, is it?
No. They'll be back.
You do not bleed, Solo,
but these people do.
They are not warriors.
They are peasants.
Who will protect them once you leave?
We could leave the village.
This is our home.
We can't just leave.
It is better to leave than die.
Maybe we could reason with them.
Reason with them?
They killed our people!
- We have to give them their robot.
- He's one of us.
- He was never one of us.
- We wanted his help.
We just didn't know the cost.
Lazaro is right. Unfil the robof
leaves, we will not rest.
Solo has fo go.
It's fhe only way.
You can't just leave.
They're right.
I must be moving on.
But they're just cowards, Solo.
No.
They are farmers.
Good-bye, Agela.
Good-bye, Miguel.
For luck.
"Welcome to the jungle"...
said the spider to the fly.
Listen up, Solo.
This is Coloneh Frank Madden
broadcasting to you...
live from the Hearf of Darkness.
Our special guest this morning
is none ofher than Mr. Wizard himself...
Dr. Bill Stewarf.
I'll tell you what, Pinocchio.
You betfer hone in on this signal
and get your butt over here ASAP...
or Geppetfo here is going to be
a pile of dead meat.
I messed up, man.
Solo, how do you like your ribs?
Regular or extra crispy?
Should've stayed in college.
Go in my pocket.
No, this one.
It's your power management chip.
You ignored directive 712.
What?
Save your own ass first, Bill.
You made a joke.
You're the only one who can stop him.
Listen up, amigos.
If's Colonel Frank Madden.
I'm the guy fhat blew up
your airstrip.
It would be in your best interest
fo follow this radio signal...
so we can finally meet
face-fo-face.
How does that grab you, muchachos?
Amazing
Grace
How sweef
The sound
You've got some balls, gringo.
Yeah?
You look good in red.
Oh, shit.
What do you want?
I want the American.
- American?
- Mm-hmm.
I want him too.
I had a feeling
I was going to like you.
Let's go. Keep it moving.
Move it!
- Everybody down on the floor!
- Get down on the floor!
Stay down there.
What are you doing here?
I didn't think you'd come back.
They said they would kill one of us
every hour until you come.
- Who?
- Americans.
They're with the rebels.
It's me they want.
If I leave, they will follow.
What if you're wrong?
Put that away
before you damage yourself.
Solo, they got my family.
We need you.
Shut up.
What's she saying?
It's an Indian blessing.
Keep this old hag quiet.
You sure he's going to show up?
If I know Solo, he's already here.
All right.
Who wants to go first?
- Take me!
- Shut him up!
So beautiful.
What a shame.
He's in there!
Come on! Let's go! Come on!
Into the tunnel.
Get in. Come on.
- Blow it.
- I have men in there!
Not anymore.
First rule when you're dealing
with the devil...
Don't.
Check it out.
- He's got to be dead.
- He's not dead till I say he is. Go.
Oh, shit.
I got a friend up here
for you to meet!
Solo, stay away!
You can run, but you can't hide!
I'll trade you his head for yours!
Don't listen to him, Solo!
Get out of here!
Nap time, Solo!
Think about it, Solo.
How will you feel if you kill me?
Good question. Let's find out.
Solo, why did you risk your life?
You said it was illogical.
Go.
Oh, my God.
Clyde, you son of a bitch.
You're gravely injured, Colonel.
Do you think you will live?
Oh, Jesus Christ.
Does it make any difference?
None.
The first targef has been eliminafed.
First rule in dealing with the devil.
Repeat, General.
Never mind.
Take out target number two.
Miguel, he's after me. Run.
- What about you?
- Miguel, run!
Go!
It is illogical to run.
Termination of a malfunctioning unit
is necessary...
for the advancement of the program.
We are the only two of our kind...
and your design is flawed.
I am the model
for the next generation.
Time for recall.
You fought well for a flawed unit.
Are you ready?
Leave him alone!
Little humans.
You could've escaped.
Instead you used
your last remaining power...
to save that boy.
You are malprogrammed.
Psych!
Miguel, run!
Run!
You had ceased to function.
No, I bluffed.
Bluffed?
It is illogical
to destroy the temple.
We will both be deleted.
Delete this.
This is Recon 1. I've left the village
and I'm over fhe temple.
You want me fo go in?
That's a negative.
Return to base.
They're both gone.
Two billion dollars...
down the crapper.
Papa!