Look out, Pluto!
I'm gonna finish him off!
Take that, and that!
And catch one of these!
Mickey? Hello?
I'm so excited about tonight. Aren't you?
- Minnie! Are you trying to get me killed?
- Maybe.
Oh, Mickey Mouse!
You forgot, didn't you?
- Oh, no. No, no. I... Forgot what?
- Our anniversary.
Oh, yeah. Anniversary.
- Of what?
- Our very first date.
Well, from now on,
you can date your stupid video game.
Minnie!
I fooled ya.
I've got everything planned.
You see, I was saving it for a surprise.
Ta-da!
You and me out in the sun.
Fresh air, blue skies, waterfalls.
For 18 glorious...
Days in Hawaii! Oh, Mickey!
You're so sweet! Aloha!
What am I gonna do, Pluto?
You need moola to hula. Oh!
"Want Ads"?
Ooh, ooh. Listen to this: "Earn
$999.99 for a mindless day's work. "
Oh, boy! I'm back in business.
Well, this is it. 1313 Lobotomy Lane.
Talk about your ironclad contract.
Dr. Frankenollie at your service.
You're here for the job, hmm?
- Yeah. I mean, no. No.
- Oh, don't be shy.
It's not just a job. It's an adventure.
- I hate adventure!
- Perfect! You're hired.
Let me introduce your coworker.
- I made him myself.
- Hey!
Ooh, I like it when they squeal.
Hey. Wait a minute.
What's goin' on?
Ahh. Perfect. Julius! Julius, baby.
Daddy's found you a brand-new brain.
- Wait! You're not really gonna...
- Put your brain in his body?
That's right!
Oh, I don't feel like myself. I...
Oh, my gosh! I'm not myself.
That crazy gizmo really worked.
Oh, Doc. Doc! Doc, look.
Look. I changed my mind.
I don't want the money.
I want my old body back.
Wait. Stop!
Uh... You, monster.
Me, Mickey. Mickey Mouse.
You know, uh, Mickey Mouse.
Just look in my wallet. You'll see.
That's old. Ha.
There's me, next to my girlfriend
Minnie.
Oh, Minnie.
Yeah. And she likes
my body and my mind.
In the same place, that is.
Minnie. Minnie. Minnie.
Stop! Thief!
Where are you going with my body?
We gotta switch back our brains!
Minnie.
Cute suit. Not on my paycheck.
Oh, my.
What would Mickey think?
Mickey!
Why, speak of the devil.
Not till we're on the boat.
Minnie, it's a monster!
Come on, Mickey! Let's get outta here!
- That was close. I think we lost him.
- Minnie!
- Help!
- Stop!
Help!
- Minnie, stop. It's me, Mickey.
- Mickey?
Hang on!
- You'll be safe here.
- Go get him, Mickey! Rip his ears off!
Hey! Let her go.
Hey, Julius. Let her go.
That was close!
- Happy Anniversary, Minnie.
- You're so romantic.