[WOMAN GASPS]
WOMAN: Wait! Come back!
[ROCK MUSIC PLAYS]
No, don't do this!
Aah! Stop!
Aah! Aah!
[SCREAMING]
[SCREAMING STOPS]
MAN: What's up, Austin!
[AUDIENCE CHEERS]
That's my sister right there.
WOMAN: Hayley, you rock!
We have a little song
about obsession.
Aah!
# the voice said to go
# move me
# impossibly tall
# to walk and I've over it
WOMAN: It was always
me and my brother.
We used to hide
under my bunk bed.
I'd come up with a line.
Jack would pluck a melody
out of the air.
But then the songs
started to work.
# let me in, let me in
# the look in your eye
that is punishing me #
So we packed up the truck
and moved to I.A.
Whoo! Oh, my god!
The music was like
our secret place.
And jack and I
were two halves of the key.
And we walk towards the fire.
Ready to erupt.
Nothing could hurt us.
Because jack and I
had each other.
And then I met carter.
- Hi.
He's a journalist,
not a musician.
But he loved my lyrics,
my words.
Things happened really fast.
Pregnant with twins.
Beautiful.
I was 19.
Carter's daughter Lila
was our flower girl.
She lives with her mom
half the time.
Jack was our best man.
Do you cherish her?
- Of course.
- Cherish her.
Of course.
Jack!
- I love you.
- I love you too.
Bye.
Okay.
WOMAN: Bye!
[CROWD CHEERING]
[CANS RATTLING]
WOMAN: Carter and I were
baby bjorning it.
Jack was busy
doing what rock stars do.
[JACK SINGING SOFTLY]
# we are the flesh,
we are the blood #
# baby, you and me
We got Willie nelson
coming to our show.
Gonna get high with Willie.
Give it to me.
Jack. Jack.
Jack. Go fucking call
an ambulance!
MAN: He's od-Ing.
Baby, wake up.
WOMAN: I don't know
if it was the hand of fate
Or if I'd abandoned him.
The guilt pulled me
away from my husband
And my kids.
It took months before I even
started to write again.
But then the lyrics
just poured out of me
Like a volcano.
And then all the songs
Ended up being about jack.
I like your new hair. Blond.
Kind of like
a rock-Angel thing going on.
Yeah. Yeah. [COUGHS]
So how do you replace someone
As special as
your brother on guitar?
Well...
uh...
Enzo is... Is great.
Annie heard him playing
in a bar.
At the audition,
it turned out
He knew all of our songs
really well.
Enzo sort of looked like
my brother.
- Rock and roll.
- You got it, baby.
You'll hear him.
He's coming on...
[HORN HONKS]
- I'm so sorry, guys.
The limo's here.
We can meet at a place...
yeah.
Nobody can replace my brother.
That's... That's not
what this is about.
This album is just my way
of honoring him.
Well, I look forward
to hearing it.
Thank you.
CHILD: Hiya!
Oh! Oh!
This is my ball! Ha ha.
How'd it go?
Well, I think we have ourselves
another spin cover.
- Fingers crossed, right?
- Mm-Hmm.
- All right, thanks again.
- Thank you. Bye.
- Oh. Put that in the car?
- Yeah. Hurry up.
I'll just be a sec.
Say goodbye to your mother.
Wow! Good hug.
I'm going to miss you guys.
I love you.
You guys
go with Mrs. R. Now, okay?
I'm going to go say goodbye
to daddy.
Mmm.
You okay?
- Yeah. Just...
- Yeah?
Never perform without jack.
Well, it's Austin.
It's your home turf.
Say your byes. Let's do this.
- Bye.
[LIMO STARTS]
WOMAN: Johnny!
MAN: Hayley!
Open.
- Ahh.
- Highly inflamed.
- Yep.
You need to moderate
your drinking...
Let's just administer the shot,
okay, doc?
Just a little numbing spray.
Okay. So this is going
to go down your nose.
There we go.
Say "ahh."
- Ahh.
- A little prick.
# the voice said to go
# move me
# impossibly tall to walk,
and I'm over it #
# so I fashioned a key
# I twisted it and I'm inside
# let me in, let me in
# you know, I won't stop
until I can see #
# let me in, let me in
# the look in your eye
that is punishing me #
# I won't stop
# no, I won't stop
# let me in, let me in
# the look in your eye
that is punishing me #
Thank you, Austin.
Y'all are awesome.
So our new album came out today.
And we're going to play
a new song off of that.
This is for jack.
[AUDIENCE CHEERS]
# where did you go
# why did you go, my mystery
# you left me alone
# you left me to drown
in misery #
# so where are you now
# why would you want
to leave me #
# to go sleep in the clouds
and dream #
# still shining down on me
# in pieces underneath
# 'cause half of me is gone
# half of me is gone
# baby, please wake up
# baby, please wake for me now
# ooh
[INAUDIBLE]
[MUSIC ENDS]
[LIGHT APPLAUSE]
Thank you so much, Austin.
Give me a second. Yeah?
Uh, did you hear the applause
on "half of me"?
Yeah.
No. There wasn't any.
Sometimes the new ones
take time to grow on you.
You know that.
Okay? Smile. It's your party.
Hayley, can you sign this
for me, please?
- Sure.
- Thanks.
Big fan.
Can you kiss that too
with the black?
I'm sorry?
Just put on the black lipstick
and kiss it.
Uh, that's not really my color.
Just put the lipstick on, okay?
Hey! She said
it's not her color.
Hey!
MAN: Come here!
Hayley!
Hayley, come back here!
ENZO: I better walk you
to your room just in case.
HAYLEY: Okay.
Do you...
Do you want to come and hang out
for a little bit
Or is... Is that awkward?
Come on, girlfriend.
Who's going to worry about me?
Okay.
ENZO:
You shouldn't look at that.
Yeah, well, I try not to, but...
this guy has written, like,
half a fucking novel
About how I don't have
any talent left.
The new songs are
too sentimental,
And they don't have any edge.
Hayley, don't read the blogs.
I mean, even the douche bag
from spin hated it.
Like, of everything I've done,
You would think that this time
They would have
a little more compassion.
You can't take this personally.
Well, I wrote, like,
half a dozen songs
About the death of my brother.
It's pretty personal.
Hayley...
you already got one going
over there.
Yeah, I do.
Look, maybe you just
need someone
To bounce some stuff off of.
Like you and jack did.
Come on, sit down.
I am going to give you
a neck rub.
My little goody bag.
- For you.
- Thank you.
Just relax.
I don't know
if it's the xanax or the vodka,
But I'm feeling kind of trancy.
Unh. Feel that?
Ahh.
That is a massive knot.
Girlfriend, you are stressed.
Mind if I go deep down
into the tissue?
Go as hard as you can.
[MACHINE VIBRATING]
[ENZO CHUCKLES]
[HAYLEY SIGHS]
[GROANS]
I'll do anything you want,
Hayley.
I just want you to feel good.
It feels really good.
[MOANING]
[MOANS LOUDER]
[BUZZING]
BOY: Mommy, I hate rabies.
Rabies? Okay.
You're looking better, Benjy.
I like your scarf, Lila.
Very cool.
I want to go back to my friends.
Okay.
[BENJY MUMBLES]
- Bye.
- Talk to you then.
What are you working on?
Trying to finish that
Texas debutante murder story
For vanity fair.
There's so many grisly details
about the bucket,
Knots of hair, and...
Sorry. Being a dick.
Just distracted
with everything going on.
But I'm here.
Wow. You look relaxed,
Like you went to the spa
or something.
I miss you.
Yeah, I miss you too.
Carter, some of the bloggers
have not been very positive
About the new album.
Those bozos are just jealous,
I'm just saying.
You know, and you don't
even need to do another album
For a while.
You know, after I get
this book deal...
Make a few bucks...
You could take some time off.
[KNOCKING AT DOOR]
WOMAN: Are you up?
Just a second.
Okay. I got to go brace myself
for whatever's next. Bye.
CARTER: Bye.
- Hey.
Where you Skype sexting carter
by any chance?
Ew! That's for my children.
Thank you. You're disgusting.
Okay.
Ah, are you hungry?
I brought you food.
Wow. Glamorous.
Has the label cut
our expense account already?
[GROANS]
WOMAN: What?
Are you serious?
Are sales really that bad?
It's early. Can't really...
what is this?
No, Annie, it's not...
It's not early.
It's not like
we're some new band.
I mean, if anything we should
come out strong and fade.
You just stay positive
and I worry about the numbers.
This is so sticky here.
What are they cleaning
this thing with? Ugh.
What did you...
What did the other bands
that you managed do
In this situation?
Um, well,
I have a comeback list.
Stop calling me, please.
Okay. Here we go.
Yes, number one...
You hold a big charity event.
I'm already talking
to whale people.
That one's done.
Number two...
Date a hot celebrity.
Obviously not an option.
Obviously always an option.
Number three...
You just get out and...
This one has a tendency
to backfire. Delete.
You know what? You just have
to write a great song.
With more edge.
[INAUDIBLE]
[ELECTRIC GUITAR PLAYING]
Get your jacket.
And bring your guitar.
HAYLEY: Come on!
There's a guy.
Back up, motherfucker!
Enzo, it's a deer.
Deer don't attack people.
Well, there's been
a few cases reported.
Heh. Come on.
Annie told me
to write a new hit song.
Like I can just
push a button or something.
You bring your little book?
Let me hear some lyrics.
Come on.
Okay. I have something.
But it's really rough, okay?
As long as it's really rough.
- It's really rough.
- Okay, good.
So I just have that.
And I thought
it would kind of go...
# if I let you in
# let you see inside
No, that sucks.
- No, it's good.
- Uh-Uh.
Try something like...
[HUMMING]
Okay.
# if I let you in
# let you see inside
# I don't know
if I can hang on #
# to what I used to be
# I let it die
# crawling around me
# it's all yours
No. Stop, Enzo.
I'm trying to be good.
You are good.
Uh-Uh. This is crazy.
We have to go. Come on.
What's crazy? That you and I
make great music together
And have even better sex?
We didn't have actual sex
last night.
[SIGHS] You know we did.
It's okay. We used protection.
Enzo, I was really wasted.
I... I have a husband.
I have kids.
And you're into guys.
Whoever said I was gay?
What is gay anyway?
I really don't want
to hurt anybody.
Maybe this could just be
What happens on tour
stays on tour.
I'm really good
at keeping secrets.
[GASPS]
Don't worry.
I won't do anything
Unless you want me to.
You didn't do anything
like this last night.
Yeah?
First time's always free.
[HAYLEY VOCALIZING]
[MOUTHS WORDS]
[LIGHT APPLAUSE]
Thank you so much, Austin.
WOMAN: There we go.
Oh, that guy
in a coat and tie...
He dropped that off for you.
Ugh. Fuckin' creepy fan.
Ew...
ANNIE:
...these reviews are brutal.
Apparently her brother
had more than half the talent.
Even pitchfork doesn't like us.
I almost fell asleep
during the song.
You guys are assholes.
But some of that shit
the critics said was spot on.
Enzo and I have been working
on a new song.
And it's going to blow
your fuckin' brains out
As long as
you write bass line for it.
Yeah!
- Fuck pitchfork!
- Yeah!
Get me a drink right now!
- Yes, ma'am!
- Thank you.
Uh-Uh. Take that.
It's much stronger.
When can we hear the song?
Well, you just keep
the party favors coming,
Giselle, you'll have a new song
by morning.
- Uh-Huh.
- Egh!
Aah! Dirty! I love it. Yeah.
Cheers!
[BOTH SINGING SOFTLY]
Yeah?
Focus! Okay.
# this is what
[SINGING SOFTLY]
I think that's good.
- All right.
- Okay.
Wow. Hayley and jack, huh?
When did you get that?
Uh... i was 19.
A lot of fans got 'em
after your second album.
Didn't you see the photos
on your web site?
No, I must've missed those.
Did you miss this?
Uh, can you stop for a minute?
Those guys are, like,
our only neighbors.
Evie, Paul.
Hi. Beautiful night, huh?
They're friendly.
Yeah. Well, my kids kind of
torture their dogs. So...
it's just
this next driveway here.
Thank you.
Hmm. No one's home.
DRIVER: You going to be okay?
Yeah. Yeah. I'm sure
they'll be home soon.
I think carter emailed me
something actually.
I'll take this one.
I'll get these.
Thank you. Want me to wait?
Uh, no. It's fine.
Have a good night.
- You too.
- Bye.
[POP]
Guys?
Cody?
Benjy?
Mrs. R.?
Carter?
[TOY MUSIC PLAYS]
Cody, Benjy?
Aah!
Hey.
What's wrong, mommy?
Nothing.
I just missed you guys.
Uh, where's Mrs. R.?
Where's daddy?
Ciao.
Hi.
Oh, forgive me. I'm Camila.
I'm your nanny for the day.
Your husband said
he emailed you.
Uh, yeah. Maybe.
I think so. Um...
I brought the boys a gift.
I hope you don't mind.
[PASSES GAS]
Uh, Benjy.
Sorry.
BENJY: I accidentally farted.
That's very cool. Thank you.
Your nanny Mrs. R.
Had some family issues.
And so the agency sent me.
Your husband
had a late interview.
I'm sorry for the confusion.
No. It's... It's fine.
I guess I just didn't read
the whole email.
But, um, sorry.
The door was unlocked.
So I just got
a little freaked out.
You have nothing to worry about.
I am practically a ninja.
- Hiya!
- Ya!
Careful guys.
I think you guys
are gonna be happy,
Because I've got presents
for you.
Yay!
HAYLEY: Where are they?
BOYS: Yeah!
Where are our presents?
Help.
You know what? I think maybe
I left them in the limo.
[PHONE RINGS]
Oh. I bet that is
the limo driver right now
Calling about your presents.
- Hello?
- Hey, it's Enzo.
I found the puppets in my bag.
Yeah. We were just
looking for them.
ENZO: Must've put 'em
in there by mistake.
Um, when's a good time
to get them?
ENZO: How about now?
Hey.
Uh, how... How...
Your little side gate was open.
- Right.
- It's okay. I locked it.
Oh. Here they are.
Awesome. Thank you so much
for driving all the way over.
I missed you a little.
Uh, I've got to go
get back to my tribe.
- Hi!
Guys, look at your presents.
- What does this do?
- Well, let me show you.
- Careful, careful.
- Hold on. I'll show you.
It'll talk right here.
BOY: Cool.
But you have to record it first.
But how do we turn it on?
Well, let me see
the instructions.
Hmm. Can't really read 'em
out here.
- Come in.
- Okay.
So what you do. Excuse me.
[HIGH PITCHED VOICE]
you push this button here
On my lovely husband's behind.
And you push it and you talk.
Say something.
I'm going to eat you up.
[RECORDING]
You've been bad.
Okay, guys. You're being weird.
Come on.
Time to go to bed.
I'm sorry.
Extreme kiddy fatigue.
- Night everybody.
- Night, stinky!
Oh, you're the stinky ones!
I'll work on the song tomorrow.
Aah! Fuck, Benjy!
Enzo, really?
Benjy, no biting.
You know, he plays guitar
with that hand, kiddo.
- Sorry, Enzo.
- It's okay.
It's just how I make a living,
you know?
Go brush your teeth, okay?
Go brush your teeth.
I'll be in in a sec.
Uh, are you available tomorrow?
For as long as you'd like.
Cool.
May I?
What a gentleman.
Never leave again.
Except to get dog food.
Dog food?
We don't even have a dog,
Bengal.
But daddy said we will
very soon.
Did he say that?
Yes.
Well, we'll just have
to talk about that another time.
Goodnight, baby.
- Goodnight.
- Muah.
Love you.
Sleep well. One more kiss. Muah.
Sleep tight, okay?
[HEAVY BREATHING]
[EXHALES]
[CARTER GROANS]
You're not getting off
that easy.
What's that supposed to mean?
I missed you.
[CARTER GROANS]
You good?
Yeah. Or do you want...
No, I'm okay. I'm okay.
Sorry.
It has been a while.
But next time I promise.
Scout's honor, it's all you.
Okay.
All right. I'm going. Okay.
I'm glad you're back though.
ANNIE: Good morning.
I hope this video boosts
the sales a little.
So am I going straight
to the choreographer's loft
Or what?
I think maybe sit down
for one second.
Okay.
They cut the shit
out of the budget.
Slashed it in half.
Where's... Let me use your phone.
- I'm calling Nigel right now.
- I would not recommend...
No, I want him
to tell me himself.
Actually the label
doesn't want a video
For "half of me" anymore.
They killed the shoot, Hayle.
And the money is from me
for the new song.
Annie.
No. No. That's crazy.
No. You know
what is crazy though?
Driving all day
and all night just to listen
To some scrawny 16 year old girl
and her weirdo brother
Play you three songs
In their parents' McAllen,
Texas, garage. That's crazy.
But it's called faith, Hayle.
And I have believed in you
since the second
I signed up for this insanity.
We'll find a young kid director.
Make something artsy.
I pull every single favor
that I have in this town
And we make this video.
I fuckin' love you.
Yeah? Yes. You are a liar.
But I love you too.
Shit. I'm good at what I do.
- Okay.
So you go to
this choreography session
And you dance
that little skinny butt off.
Because the label
has already paid for that.
And we make our video
that much better. Yeah?
Thank you.
[MUFFLED SINGING]
# no, I won't stop
Whoo!
Yeah!
Wow. Very good.
Hi everyone.
What's... What's happening?
Carter sent me a text.
Oh, yeah. The puppets broke.
And Camila here said that Enzo
could fix 'em.
I brought the new song anyway.
I wanted to show it to you.
I mixed it last night.
Oh, and I brought
my puppet tool kit.
Well, thank you.
That's very cool.
And he taught me something.
Let's give her a little show.
- Oh, yeah.
- All right. Okay, ready?
- This one.
- Okay. All right.
# let me in, let me in
That's awesome. That's great.
- Thank you.
- That's awesome.
- I'm so proud of you.
- Thank you.
I can't even get you to play
guitar hero.
Enzo's persuasive.
Miss Sinclair,
this came for you.
Um...
coat and tie fan guy?
How did he get my address?
CARTER: Is that a snake's head?
Egh. Somebody take that
somewhere else, please.
Yikes.
Who is this fan anyway?
He is, uh, I don't know.
Some psycho in a suit.
He chased me in Austin.
Yeah. It was weird.
He was just, like,
running after us.
We had to hide.
We? Who's we?
I'm not the most macho guy.
So...
we hid instead.
No. No, it was not funny
at the time.
Ooh, ripe.
That reminds me.
I brought tomatoes
from my garden.
Heirloom tomatoes.
Seriously, it's kind of creepy.
Now he's stalking me in I.A.
It's scary.
All the way from Texas
to mess with these guns?
I don't think so.
[BOYS SCREAM]
Yeah, no. I don't think so.
He's welcome to come, huh?
Right? Okay.
Dinner's almost ready.
BOY: I hate tomatoes.
ENZO: Well,
every time you eat one,
You give yourself 10 minutes
of extra super powers.
- Really?
- Whoo-Hoo.
Why don't you ease up on
the potato juice a little bit?
You know, just a touch?
Given everything
that's happened,
I think Hayley's earned
the right to unwind a little.
Don't you?
Yeah. Yeah, no.
I think we all have.
Cheers to that.
BOY: Cool! Cheers, big ears.
Can I see it?
This?
Who's hair is this?
Well, it belongs to
my soul mate.
Look, mommy.
It's the same color as yours.
Well, lots of people
have that color hair.
It's the same as yours too.
Give it back to Enzo.
- Eh.
- Thank you, sir.
BOY: Thank you, sir. [CHUCKLES]
This is good.
- Oh!
- Boom!
Threat neutralized.
Yeah!
Uh, I'm going to go to bed.
Yeah, I should probably go too.
Well,
It has been a lovely evening.
No. No. You're not riding
through the canyon tonight.
Babe, why don't we make him
a bed out there in the studio?
Oh, and I wanted you
to hear the song too.
It's just a demo.
Both of you.
I think I'm going to wait until
she's ready for me to hear it.
I don't really want
to start world war iii.
Oh, I hear you on that one.
Uh, let's just call him a cab.
Come on, babe, you have people
Stay in your studio
all the time.
Yeah, he's not even drunk.
And you're the judge?
You've been going at it
Like it's mardi gras all night.
- Whatever you say, dad.
- Whoa.
Come on, Enzo.
Play me that song.
[SIGHS] Can't live with 'em,
can't kill 'em, right?
Right.
[DOOR SHUTS]
Not cool, Enzo. You can't
just show up like that.
You told me you wouldn't do
anything unless I wanted you to.
Hayley, your husband texted me.
What was I supposed to do?
I didn't want him to get
all suspicious.
- I'm calling you a cab.
- Just...
Listen.
[MUSIC STARTS]
# if I let you in
# let you deep inside
# I don't know if I can hold
# to what I used to be
# I let it die
# coil around me,
it's all yours #
There's a camera over there.
How did you do that?
I've never sounded
like that before.
Tripled your vocals.
Mixed them at slightly
different frequencies.
[HAYLEY GASPS]
Don't bite me.
[MOANS]
Hey.
You were out there for a while.
How'd it go?
Yeah. We just had to talk about
the track for a bit.
It's just a demo
but it sounds wicked.
Well, that's awesome.
Can't wait to hear it.
All right, so this guy
tied up his victims
With the exact same clove knot
as the debutant killer.
Right?
I'm gonna send you the link.
Fascinating.
Awesome.
I can't wait to see it.
You want to come
take a shower with me?
I took one after my run.
So...
Okay. Well, I'll be back soon.
Okay.
Whoa!
[KIDS LAUGHING]
Hayley, check this out.
I'm restringing this piano
with real cow guts.
I'll layer it into the track.
Enzo. Enzo!
You need to back off.
You have to cut me some slack.
This is... It's too much. Okay?
Um, where's your garden?
Your heirloom tomatoes?
I always say that.
I mean the sunset junction
market.
Pretty much live
out of that place.
Uh...
oh, look at this bolex.
It's about the only thing
my father gave me.
[CAMERA WHIRRS, STOPS]
I want to show you something.
Something that I made.
Annie liked it.
I'm a very affordable director.
Especially for you.
Irish gin.
Try this.
My friends in Portland
home brewed it.
Why am I not surprised
that you make films, Enzo?
[DARK MUSIC PLAYS]
I made this a long time ago.
Kind of my early
childhood memories.
My father thought
I was too effeminate.
I'm sorry.
ENZO: Only my mother
really understood me.
That's my sister.
My real sister.
Daddy's favorite.
HAYLEY: She's beautiful.
Very cool style.
So do I get the job?
Yes. It's stunning.
I mean, you inspired me.
Even way before I met you,
I used to listen to your songs
over and over
And play along with them.
Wow, your sister's
a really good actress.
Her fear seems very real.
Yeah.
HAYLEY: Wow. Enzo, it's so...
disturbing.
So universal.
Pain, pleasure.
Light, darkness.
In order to create...
you have to embrace
the dark side.
ENZO: Stay right there.
You'll do whatever I say.
[CAMERA WHIRRS]
Shh.
Yes.
You can struggle.
But you can't escape.
Okay. Get up.
Reload.
Thank you.
That's great.
This is a macro lens.
It'll get you in closer.
Get on the ground.
Hey!
This is awkward, huh?
Yeah.
You know if he wasn't gay,
I might just have to kill him.
Anyway,
the lime tree's gonna fall.
So I'm gonna brace it.
ENZO: Sean, could you put
a little lip gloss
On my finger, please?
Thanks.
And we're rolling.
[CAMERA WHIRRS]
Part your lips.
Do not push her too hard.
We're shooting
the wide stuff now anyway.
Annie, I know exactly
how hard to push.
Tighten the dress up.
Even more.
Annie, can I get a drink.
I'm on it.
- Like, a real drink?
- Definitely on it.
Suck it.
There you go.
Okay. That's good. Thank you.
All right.
Ah. Camila, why don't you
take 'em in the house?
Oh. Come on.
Are my kids wearing leashes?
Uh... i think so. Yeah.
They're not gonna get lost
in the crowd.
And we're back.
[CAMERA WHIRRS]
# if I let you in
# let you deep inside
# I don't know
if I can hang on #
# to what I used to be
# I let it die
# coil around me,
it's all yours #
# this is what you came for,
but you took so much more #
# much more than I can give
# this is what you came for
# now it takes so much more
# much more for me to live
# close enough to fall and die
# close enough to thrill me
# close enough
to crawl deep inside #
# keep me close enough to kill
MAN: # close enough to kill
[LABORED BREATHING]
You guys, the label is gonna
flip over this new video.
Oh, my god!
Enzo, come here!
ANNIE: Enzo,
I'm going to Nigel right away.
Ahh! Uh. I'm so happy.
Happy manager! Happy manager!
The partridge family is here.
You guys want to give 'em
some space.
- Sure.
- Let's do it.
Come on. Enzo, that means
you too. Come on.
[DOOR CLOSES]
Let's give them
some family time. Okay?
[DOOR OPENS]
Get your ski on.
Bye!
Can we see the video?
Ah, not a chance, kid.
Well, maybe Lila and I
can see it.
I'm 11, you know.
Yeah. Well, yeah.
I mean, as soon as I get a copy,
You guys can see it.
Who wants to go to the ridge
and hunt for coyotes?
[IMITATING COYOTES]
Let's go!
BOY: We're doing a race.
Look what I found!
LILA: Oh. Look coyote vomit!
Well, good.
I was getting hungry.
Slightly better
than your mother's cooking.
Oh, gross! Come on.
Let's keep exploring. Let's go.
So why don't you try
something natural, like,
You know, melatonin?
Yeah, like,
I tried the melatonin.
But the xanax is the only thing
That actually calms me down
enough to fall asleep.
So I thought maybe
I could just get
A couple more months of that.
Any recent illnesses,
Severe cold, sore throat?
Nope.
When was your last period?
Uh... well,
it was before the tour. So...
DOCTOR: Today's the 27th.
When did the tour
actually begin?
Six weeks ago.
Okay. Well, Hayley,
You are pregnant again.
Congratulations.
This is good, right?
Yeah. Uh...
it's just that
my husband has had a vasectomy.
Well, they don't always work.
Studies say 1 in 2,000.
Really?
No more xanax. No booze.
No cigarettes.
[KIDS YELLING]
CODY: Mommy, Benjy hitted me.
But Cody started it.
[YELLING CONTINUES]
HAYLEY: Hey, Benjy, no.
Hi, you're home early.
Um...
You know, I shouldn't have
looked at this. But...
are you pregnant?
Looks like it.
The stick was blue.
See, I thought
you didn't want another kid.
Yeah, you thought that.
But you never asked me.
Just like you never consulted me
about the vasectomy.
I told you
I was thinking about it.
You were all for it.
Yeah, but then you just did it.
But you know it's, like,
A 1 in 2,000 chance.
It's a borderline miracle.
Maybe it's meant to be.
Maybe we should just embrace
our destiny.
When are you due?
I have no idea. I'm going
to call the doctor tomorrow.
To be honest, I was just...
I was so in shock
I didn't even pay attention.
But it could be good, right?
Have another little monster
running around.
Morning. Delivery.
Thank you.
Why am I the last to know?
Come on, carter.
It's from Annie.
You know we have to strategize
a little bit.
CARTER: Okay.
[PHONE RINGING]
ENZO: Uh-Huh.
Finally you answer.
What the fuck is going on?
You sent me a baby gift?
How did you know?
And how did this happen?
I mean, you said
you used protection.
ENZO: Those things
rip sometimes, Annie.
You were pretty wild.
All it takes
is a tiny, little hole.
Nothing's foolproof.
It's like 1 in 2,000?
Where did you get that number?
ENZO: Hey, for dinner tonight
I picked up
these organic baby artichokes.
The twins'll love 'em
'cause you peel...
You're fucking kidding me,
right?
You don't understand.
You're no longer welcome
in my house.
ENZO: Don't stay that, Hayley.
You have to leave him.
Oh, Jesus, Enzo.
I can't talk to you anymore.
Do not call me again.
Do you understand?
ENZO: Yes. I understand.
Hey, so I was just about
to call you.
The label flipped out
over the new song.
Annie, I screwed up.
I fucked up really badly.
ANNIE: Why? What's wrong?
How long will it take you
to get here?
I'm turning
the car around right now.
I was just about to come over.
Okay.
I mean, I was just...
I was torn up.
You know,
the critics were in my head.
And I thought that I couldn't do
any good work without jack.
So you fucked Enzo
to get your mojo back.
I totally get it. It's okay.
Yeah, I mean...
I got inspired again.
Because you're riding the beast.
You've opened up Pandora's box
And you're facing
joy and horror head on.
Sweetie, every single artist...
They have affairs because
it fuels their creativity.
Look at woody Allen
and Bruce Springsteen.
And... Picasso.
For god sakes, Picasso...
Every time
he had a new mistress,
He started
a new freaking art movement.
I'm pregnant.
[SPITS DRINK]
Oh, shit.
It's okay.
It's not like you mowed down
a deaf kid while texting.
This is fixable. Um...
you know you don't have
to go through with it.
I could talk to Enzo.
I can be very discrete.
Discrete?
Annie, he's obsessed.
I have to get him
out of my life.
He sent a bassinet to the house
The day after
I found out I was pregnant.
I didn't even tell him.
I mean, how does he know?
You think he bugged
my cell phone or something?
Can you do that?
I'm sure... I'm sure
they have an app for that.
He has no boundaries.
We didn't even do
a background check on him.
Yeah, because we thought
he was amazing.
He is amazing.
I mean, he's a genius.
- And what genius isn't twisted?
- Uh-Huh.
I mean,
my brother was a fucking nutbag.
Maybe I'm being too paranoid.
[SIGHS] I really thought that
He was going to be the one
to take us to the next level.
I thought that too.
I mean, you know,
I've always wanted
To headline
Madison square garden.
And... And score films
And make a fucking opera
on the moon.
You know, I wanted to make
really dangerous music.
And I felt that with Enzo.
You know, I was fierce,
Teetering
on the edge of something.
Here. Oh, you're pregnant.
Right.
Okay. Okay.
This is what we're going to do.
[SIGHS]
You're going to walk this edge
for a little while longer.
We lay down enough tracks
to put together an album.
And then if you still want me
to, I cut the chord.
Just like that?
Pretty much.
I'll call the lawyer tonight
And I'll make sure
that you're protected.
And I'll spin off
the dark prince.
I'll get him his own deal.
And he will be
so busy with that,
He won't have time
to munch your box
Let alone ruin your life.
Yeah?
I will meet with him tomorrow,
give him some Annie rules,
Turn him into a well-Behaved,
willing mistress, okay?
- Okay.
- I'll be here for you.
- Okay. Thank you.
- Okay.
- All right.
- Thanks.
I'm so sorry about Enzo.
It's okay.
- Uh...
- Yeah.
I told carter that you sent
the bassinet.
Okay. Shit.
What?
When I rolled up earlier
And he was digging
in the garden,
He thanked me,
then he mumbled something
About being the last to know.
And that's all that happened?
That's all he said.
But then I said,
I had no idea
what he was talking about.
But it's fine.
I... I can fix that.
- Okay.
- Bye, thank you.
- Bye.
Uh, Camila, will you help me
move this into the guest room?
Yes.
You can leave that right there.
Uh, Annie, didn't know they were
going to deliver it so quickly.
That's why
she was caught off guard
When you asked her about it.
Well,
that's one way to explain it.
- What do you mean?
- Exactly what I said.
But, hey, we're all
just standing on a big rock
Hurling through space.
Did you put the whiskey in?
A whole shot.
Just like you showed me.
Okay. I need it.
I thought you couldn't have
any more babies.
You know what, bud?
I think it would be better
If your mom explained that
to you.
Well, it's complicated, buddy.
But, um,
Sometimes the doctors think that
you can't have any more babies.
You know,
sometimes they make mistakes.
And this time they were wrong.
Um... yeah, no. Okay.
You guys have a bit more food
and you can have a cookie.
What?
Um...
Annie, she...
She drove off the side of
Mulholland on her way home.
They suspect foul play.
And she said
that she didn't make it.
Well, I'm going to go
to the hospital.
You know, I said she's dead.
And her sister's coming down
from Berkeley tomorrow.
You and Enzo can go over then.
Are you leaving?
Uh...
sorry.
Can I help you?
Um, no.
I think it's best if you leave,
And I'll call you tomorrow.
Yes, miss.
Hey, guys. Uh...
you guys go brush your teeth.
And I'm going to meet you in
the bathroom in a minute, okay?
[WIND CHIMES]
[DOOR SLAMS]
Carter?
You've been bad.
[GASPS]
Stop.
I need to tell you something.
You know,
I interview real interesting
characters all the time.
Sexy women in bars, hotel rooms,
trying to impress me.
And I could've fucked
anyone of 'em.
Do you know how many times
I've cheated on you?
Huh?
Not once.
And now you're having
another man's baby!
And you brought him
into our home!
He played with our fucking kids!
Okay. Listen. Listen. Please.
Please, listen.
I just...
I just... When the album failed,
I was just... I was...
I was torn up, you know.
And I'm, like...
I'm so sorry. I'm so sorry.
Would you be sorry
if you hadn't gotten caught?
I wanted to trust you.
But right under my nose.
What a fuck... What a fool!
The big crime writer carter.
And I'm sure you guys were
laughing the entire time.
No! No, not at all.
[COUGHS]
Listen,
I fucked up really badly.
But please just help me fix it.
Help me be better.
I'll do anything.
Anything? No,
you've already done anything.
Okay? So just move.
- Please?
- Move!
Move!
Move so I can finish this!
Why are you doing this now?
Are you burying something?
What did you do to him?
Say his name?
Did you hurt him?
You care more about him
than your own fucking family?
- Huh?
- No! That's not what I mean.
You'd better get the fuck
away from me!
Go! Get out of here! Go!
Hello?
Evie, Carl,
it's your neighbor Hayley.
I need your help.
Hello?
I'm sorry about what my kids
did to your dog.
Can I please use your phone?
[DOOR BUZZES]
Evie? Carl?
Well, well, well.
This is a surprise.
I wasn't expecting anyone.
Why are you here?
I rented this place so I could
help out with the baby.
[DOG WHINES]
Where did Evie and Carl go?
Oh, they wanted
to travel abroad.
I found the house on craigslist.
I could not believe it
when I saw the address.
Our little fuck shack.
Enzo, I have a husband,
and I have children.
Not for much longer.
The husband part that is.
What did you do?
I chopped off the lime tree
roots on this side of the fence.
Made the tree lean over.
Whoo. Carter got all
worked up about it.
Watch this.
[IMITATES STRAINING]
Ahh.
Dug his own grave.
Goochie goo.
Oh, Hayley,
don't feel too bad for him.
I might've saved your life.
I just heard him yelling at you.
Yeah, you're right.
He's an asshole when he's drunk.
Could've just divorced him.
Then I wouldn't have to go
through with all this.
But love makes you crazy.
Right?
Oh, check this out.
A 1960s tube stereo.
Mint condition.
That's amazing.
It's about the music.
You've always wanted
to headline the garden.
Haven't you? Huh?
[CODY AND BENJY TALKING]
Oh, the place is a mess.
I was going to hang some drapes.
Here, don't...
[KIDS CONTINUE TALKING]
Cool, huh?
These baby monitors
have extraordinary range.
Twins are fine.
Yeah, they sound happy.
I cannot wait
to meet our little prodigy.
So you can hear everything
we're saying over there?
Including your little
conversation with Annie
About how I have no boundaries.
And you wanted to be rid of me.
No.
I just got freaked out, okay?
I got freaked out.
Then we went outside
And we talked about it more.
And I realized
that I want to be with you.
I want to create with you.
I have to.
Music is just a starting point,
The genesis.
That is cause for a drink.
You sent that gift?
Oh, yeah. I kind of
liked that fan boy's style.
So I carried it on
after we got home.
This is for you.
Enzo, a martini?
Bad daddy.
Baby!
It's okay.
- I'm so sorry.
- It's okay.
How about some oj?
Well, I think I should probably
get back to the kids.
Don't worry.
I've got it all covered.
Oh, listen.
I remixed "half of me."
[MUSIC PLAYS]
It's a duet now.
I'm channeling jack.
# baby, no, no, no
# I'm right here
# you are the seed
# in ecstasy
# you are the need
# to feed inside you
What's wrong? Are you okay?
I... I just drank that juice
way too fast.
I have a little
morning sickness.
Where's the bathroom?
Uh, use the one
in the master suite.
No, no. Don't go in there.
Left turn. Left turn.
Just know that everything
I've done, I've done for us.
I guess Evie and Carl
didn't have
Enough frequent flyer miles
to make it to Europe.
Whoops.
I'll be out in a minute.
Hayley?
Hayley, let me in.
# we are the blood
# we are the bone
# we are complete
Open the bloody door!
Carter?
CARTER: I can't move my legs.
Camila, help us, please.
Help me get him out of here.
I need to check on the children.
What the fuck? Camila!
CAMILA: A whole shot,
just like you showed me.
Oh, god. She's with Enzo.
Go. We have to go. Come on.
# where did you go,
my mystery #
Come on.
ENZO: Mother?
Go. Go. Go. Go.
Mother?
Okay. Come on.
Let's go. Come on.
I'm tired.
Buckle up.
Aah!
Mommy?
Mother?
Run inside and hide for mommy.
Okay? Up the stairs.
Off you go.
Aah! Ugh!
Get away from him!
The baby!
I'm not having
your fucking baby!
No!
Ugh!
You wanted us
just as much as I did!
Aah!
No!
My mother could've raised
all the kids!
Yes. And we could be free
to create like we should be.
Ugh.
Jack.
Aah!
You fucking killed him!
I had to!
I loved jack!
But jack didn't love me back!
Shh. Not like you did.
Not like you did!
Aah!
My hand!
Carter!
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
[DISTANT POLICE SIRENS]
[POLICE RADIO CHATTER]
Hey. I just came from the house.
And your parents have
everything under control.
The boys are fine.
They miss you.
How are you feeling?
Well...
because of the fight,
I'm not pregnant anymore. So...
I brought your mail.
Wow. You picked
a real psychopath.
They've tied a total of six
murders to him and his mother.
They still haven't found
Camila, right?
No. But they will.
And until they do,
I'll have security
at the house 24/7.
So... So you're in here
one more night, right?
But when you get out...
I guess I should just keep
staying at the hotel.
I think that would be best.
Okay.
I know that I have
a lot of growing up to do.
I really...
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry. You should rest.
I'll go.
[BAG ZIPS]
It's okay.
It's okay. You take
all the time you need, baby.