www.titlovi.com
Ow!
Damn it!
Rachel, I don't think...
It's not like,
you know... You're...
Car's ready.
Are you ready to go?
Ready to go, pal?
Come on. Let's go.
Come on, Bernie.
Let's go.
Come on, Bern.
Car's leaving.
Come on.
Come on, Bernie.
I'll just get him later.
Okay.
Yeah.
This is the last box here.
All right.
Let me know if I leave
anything behind.
Sure.
Oh!
Fuck!
Jesus!
Hey.
Thanks so much for
letting me crash here.
Yeah, of course,
come on in.
Just got to the point
where I guess she...
She lost faith in me.
She lost faith in...
In our relationship. She lost
faith in any possibility
that we might be able
to resolve this somehow.
And she lost faith.
Wow.
What was Mom's
take on all this?
Mom, you know...
You know, she was drunk,
she was angry at me.
She blamed me for everything,
basically.
Yeah.
And called me a pussy,
in her own way.
Yeah, I can't say
I'm surprised.
Is that my shirt?
This? What, the V-neck?
No, the shirt underneath.
The white shirt.
What, with the...
I think Rachel got me this.
The button-down?
I've been looking for that shirt
for, like, two years.
Honey? I cleared out the...
The right hand side of the basement,
the far right hand side by the boiler,
for all of Alex's stuff.
So, okay.
Thank you.
Mmm-hmm.
Thanks. I really appreciate it.
Yeah.
So what about the tour? Are you
still going to go out by yourself?
I have to.
You can't cancel?
I can't cancel it, no.
I need the money, you know.
I need to start chipping away
at this debt.
Unless... Unless you and Clay want to
lend me $4,000.
And you know, I think, you know,
maybe just being on the road...
You know, just alone with
my thoughts for two weeks.
Maybe that's a good thing.
You know, it'll give me...
Give me an opportunity
to reflect on things.
Maybe give me a little bit
of perspective.
You know,
in the whole situation.
And you know, maybe
that's a good thing.
So what do you think?
You want to come with me?
All right.
No, I...
I have Pete's number.
Petey! Pistol Pete!
When did people
stop calling you that?
Oh, okay. I didn't...
Wesley! What's
shaking, brother?
Listen, I know this might seem
out of the blue,
but, um, do you remember that
movie I made a few years ago,
called Woodpecker?
This is the movie that was about
these two birdwatchers
looking for this elusive woodpecker
which is on the brink of extinction.
It starts tomorrow.
It lasts two weeks.
There's 12 screenings
in two weeks.
And I was going to
do it with Rachel but...
...unfortunately, she couldn't
make it because, um...
She's actually working
on a job in... In Miami.
I forgot the name of the city.
I think it's in Western Poland.
And so unfortunately, she's not going to be able
to come with me on the tour,
so I'm just calling to see if maybe you want to,
kind of, just take an impulsive,
crazy adventure with me
through the south.
Totally, man,
I understand. I mean...
The little ones
need their father.
I thought I did invite you
to my birthday party.
Okay, is it still...
Did you switch to Gmail
or are you still Yahoo!?
Say hi to Leslie.
Lisa!
Say hi to Lisa.
Okay, bye.
Fuck!
Alex?
Yeah?
Doing okay in there?
Uh, hold on a second.
Hey.
Uh...
What's up?
Oh, I don't know.
Are you okay? I...
Yeah.
...heard some racket
and some yelling in there.
Oh yeah, that was me.
I was making some phone calls.
Calling my buddies.
Yeah.
I'm sorry if I was making too...
Was it too loud?
Well, no, no. I just, uh...
I was just...
I'm just worried
about you.
Going through
a rough time, right?
I, uh... I don't want
to intrude, okay,
but I did read somewhere
that we form
neurological associations
between swear words
and stress anxiety.
And we make those stress
words very powerful.
One way to maybe
help that out
is to replace the swear word
with a normal, ordinary word.
And maybe the swear words
can kind of lose their power.
Um, and...
And then maybe
later on down the road,
you're going to have to replace
that word with another word,
and then maybe that word
with another word,
but it might be a good way to, you know,
help with your stress management, you know.
Right? Yup.
Clay, that is the dumbest, retarded thing,
I've ever heard in my life.
Yeah. There you go.
Yeah.
You're a good person,
you know that?
You're a very good person and
I appreciate you trying to help.
I appreciate
your act of kindness.
I wish there was more
kindness in this world.
Do you guys, maybe,
want to come down to Atlanta?
Tomorrow? Join me for the first
few days of the tour?
No.
Behind me,
that's a Pileated.
So we're going to stay
right here, Wes.
That's not the bird
I'm looking for.
As you know,
how this works...
We are very pleased to have the
filmmaker with us this evening,
and Alex Karpovsky is selected
as one of 25 new faces
in independent film
by Filmmakers Magazine.
Not only is he a filmmaker,
but he's also an actor.
And in this past year,
he played the voices
of several Russian gangsters
in  Grand Theft Auto IV.
His newest film...
In the early 1940s,
this beautiful creature,
the most colorful,
the largest woodpecker
to ever fly in the American skies,
was declared extinct.
Because of our deforestation,
our negligence,
we lost another glorious creature
on this planet.
Um... Or so we thought.
A few years ago, hikers,
kayakers started spotting what they thought
was the elusive, and long forgotten
Ivory-billed Woodpecker.
And as word grew
and people started
to flock down there to the
swamps of Eastern Arkansas,
hoping to grab definitive
evidence, proof of this bird,
it became sort of
a national story.
But proof was elusive,
no one could get that photo.
And if they could
get that photo,
then maybe its habitat
could be preserved.
Legislation could be passed,
and it could be a protected area,
and these two or three woodpeckers,
or however might still be out there,
could be allowed to flourish.
So, this notion
of a second chance,
in every sense of that phrase,
was very interesting to me,
in a driving source of enthusiasm,
throughout...
Throughout this process
of working on the film.
And something that on a personal level,
especially recently,
is something that I can relate to,
you know, in many...
Well, in one specific aspect
of my life, anyway, I wish...
I wish I also was given
a second chance.
And I think maybe some of
the people in this room,
maybe could relate
to that notion. So...
That's all the time
we have tonight.
Thank you so much for coming out
to check out the film,
especially on
Valentine's Day.
I really appreciate it, and maybe
I'll see you down the road.
Good night.
All right.
Thank you.
Thank you very much.
All right, happy Valentine's Day.
Thank you, you too.
All right. Thank you very much.
Happy Valentine's Day.
Hey, guys.
Ahem! Guys?
Guys!
Fallen tree is right there.
This is the spot.
The Ivory-billed was counted
out of existence.
If it can make a comeback,
anything can make a comeback.
I mean,
that's just a...
It's actually just
one of the few
pleasures of life
that we have,
while we're here,
is making a comeback,
when you're called
down and out,
when you're
called extinct.
Well, we're a...
You can see
something over there.
Henry, what's up, man?
Alex, what's
going on, baby?
What you up to,
you son of a bitch?
Not much, I'm just doing
a tech check
before one of our
Woodpecker  screenings.
Well, listen, I've been
thinking about your offer
and if your offer
still stands,
I'm gonna come down and join
you on the tour if it's possible.
Yeah, yeah, I just think
it will be really inspiring.
That's great.
As long as I'm not imposing.
No, no, no.
That's great news.
Cool, awesome.
I'm really excited about it.
Yeah, I'm so glad
you reconsidered.
I've been sitting in my shitty apartment,
drawing shitty illustrations,
thinking about Shel Silverstein,
feeling slightly suicidal.
I just got to get
the fuck out of here.
But in all honesty, there was this
media blitz, uh...
They were all, sort of, blasting us with this
incredible, strange story
about a strange woodpecker.
It's a beautiful story.
It's a story about Americana,
about second chances.
I wanted to kind of dive into this very new,
rich, unfamiliar place.
Because it's so
free of associations
and so full of wonder, and that's a huge
part of the magnetism as well.
This is a great, like, charismatic,
megafauna kind of story,
and you seem like
a very charismatic megafauna.
So I hope we see more of you
and more of your work,
and I don't really
have a question,
I just wanted
to say that.
Thank you very much,
that's very sweet. I appreciate it.
Charismatic megafauna was actually
a working title for the film.
I've had a wonderful time talking to
you in this beautiful theater.
I'll see you down the road.
Good night.
It's Tricia.
T-R-I-C-I-A.
- T-R-I...
- C-I-A.
C-I-A. Like that.
Are you guys bird watchers?
- Pardon me?
- Are you bird watchers?
I'm more of a hunter.
Thank you for coming
and watching the film.
- Okay, see you.
- Thank you very much.
Hey, how's it going?
Good, good, how are you?
Those were really sweet things that
you said in there.
Thank you.
I really appreciate it.
You were great. It was such a good movie.
Thank you so much.
And you were so funny.
And you're really talented.
Oh, fuck!
There's a maple tree
on one side of my lawn
that has, like, a really
high vibration,
but then there's a cypress tree
on the other side,
and it has the most
mellow vibration
and I can't
figure out why.
I'm thinking because it's older,
you know?
Left here?
Yes.
This was so great.
It was really fun, yeah.
Yeah, I loved it.
Good night.
Yeah, it was a fun night.
Hmm.
Yeah.
So, it was great
seeing you. Mmm!
All right.
Mmm-hmm.
Cool.
Yeah.
So...
All right, Riv. Well,
I'm sorry you got to go.
Yeah, it's just...
It's work.
PF's and stuff.
Well, maybe I'll see you
down the road.
Yeah, yeah.
I would like that.
Yeah, that'll be fun, right?
Yeah.
Take care.
Okay. I love your work.
Bye-bye.
See you later.
That means good night.
Good night.
Put that hat on.
Rachel. The one...
Yeah, put that one on.
I'm just studying.
...I'm gonna be a nurse.
Do you like nurses?
Is this my nurse fantasy
or is this your nurse fantasy?
All right, Ma, okay.
Henry. Henry!
Alex!
How's it going?
Great.
Good to see you.
Good to see you too.
They lost my bag.
They did?
Did you...
This isn't even my flight.
Everybody who was on my flight has
come and gone.
Yeah, they said they're going
to call me when it's ready, so...
What a bummer!
I'm sorry to hear that.
Oh, it's all right.
It's just stuff.
It's just stuff. Good seeing you.
You look great.
Good to see you too, yeah. I've
never seen you with long hair before.
Oh, yeah? What do you think?
You like it?
All right. Well, how much
are you taking off?
It's just cutting,
it's tough cutting.
Fucking bullshit.
Give me those
fucking scissors.
It's looking good.
Uh-huh, yeah.
I think so. This is what
I'm talking about.
Some Thomas Dolby shit.
Rachel asked me to
move something from, uh...
This old TV, it doesn't even
really work that well.
She asked me to move it from the
living room to the dining room.
And I think, I just... You know
how you're supposed to bend your...
...bend your knees. Did you
actually bend over and do that?
I always do that.
I always bend my knees,
but this one time
I spaced out and...
How is she?
Rachel?
Yeah.
She's doing well. Yeah.
Yeah?
You guys have been
together for four years?
Four and a half years now.
Four and a half years.
Yeah.
That's incredible.
That's amazing. I mean, that's great.
You guys are great together.
So I'm really happy for you.
I mean... Yeah.
Yeah.
I wish I could do that.
So how many people
did you call
before you called me
to come on this trip?
I know I wasn't
the first person.
You're not the
first person I called.
I didn't think so.
I'll admit that.
I'm gonna have to get some work done
in between your screening.
I'm not going to make
all the screenings.
Yeah, yeah, of course, of course.
You don't... I mean...
I only expect you
to make one.
And you only have to go
to the first one.
Well, you know... No, I'm
looking forward to seeing it.
I'm just going to have to stay at
the motel certain nights
and get some work done.
Of course, of course.
I have to, so...
You got to work
on your illustrations or...
Uh-huh.
Yeah.
So how's all that going?
What's the latest?
It's going well, yeah.
I got a children's book deal.
Oh, you did get a deal?
Yeah, yeah.
That's great, because
last time we spoke,
you said you were maybe
about to or something,
but you got it... Hey, I found out
about a month ago
and I didn't
want to jinx it.
But you know,
now it's pretty official,
so I'm starting
to tell people.
There's a book I started
about eight months ago,
called  Henry
and the Haunted Piano.
And I sent you a PDF for that
a while back.
Never heard from you
about it and so... Right.
I don't know if I got it.
Did I get it?
Yeah, you got it.
You were busy.
And it's a big commitment to read
a children's book, so...
You weren't the first person
I sent the PDF to, either.
Fair enough.
Henry and the Haunted Piano.
Little boy named Henry,
walking home from
school one day,
He hears this music,
piano playing coming from the cemetery,
goes to the cemetery.
Discovers a piano haunted
by a ghost there, all right?
Gets terrified, runs away,
and continues
to hear the music
because he lives very close to
the cemetery, right.
And later that night,
he can hear the piano playing
while he's doing
his homework,
while he's taking a bath,
while he's trying to sleep.
He gets pissed off when he's trying
to sleep because he can't sleep.
He goes back
to the cemetery,
confronts the ghost
for a final confrontation.
That's where it gets
a little bit dark.
And the publishers are a
little concerned about that.
They think the ending is...
The ending is too dark, so...
Well, why? What happens
in the ending?
Henry dies.
The ghost kill him?
Well, that's interpretive.
The children can
interpret that.
But they think it's a little too dark.
Well, I...
I don't want to take sides,
but I can see where they're coming from.
Right! No, so I'm trying
to find a way to change it.
If I get published by this company,
it's pretty good.
It'll be good for my,
you know, burgeoning...
Well, non-existent career,
but it could lead to things.
So, I wanted to make sure
they're happy and...
Seems like you're very ready to
compromise your artistic vision
to get published by
a medium-sized publisher
rather than preserving
your integrity and your vision
and going to a slightly smaller,
fringe, edgy, publisher.
Absolutely, I'll do whatever it takes
to get this thing published.
So, rape me,
here's the lubrication.
Rape me, here's
the lubrication.
You're allowing
them to rape you.
You're easing the process.
Oh!
In this case,
I want to get raped.
I want to make a living,
having sodomy.
Can you get some more nach...
Uh, the chips?
You want me
to get them?
No, no, I'm looking
for the guy.
Front desk. This is Alan.
Hey, Alan, this is Alex
calling from room 106.
Um, I have a little
bit of a back pain
and it's making it really difficult for
me to sleep at night.
I'm doing a lot of...
Kind of tossing and turning.
And I was wondering if it'd be possible
to maybe get a late checkout.
Oh!
Tomorrow morning.
You're out of luck,
I'm sorry.
It's not in our policy
to allow late checkouts.
It's the hotel's policy to not allow
late checkouts.
How was the call?
It was good. Sorry I was
on the phone so long.
Oh, that's okay.
How are you?
You all right?
Yeah, yeah. Good.
How's your back?
I feel like for the past little while it
was getting better and better and then...
These little...
Just sharp little...
I was in the bathroom a little while ago
and just felt this, like,
jolt of pain go up my spine.
I know this guy
who's a reflexologist
and he... He fixes backs,
by, uh...
You know, reflexologists?
The... The foot?
Yeah, he massages
pressure points in the feet
and he actually fixes
back pain that way.
So you might have to think about
looking up a reflexologist tomorrow
and checking that out,
because it could help.
I doubt there...
I doubt there are reflex...
You shouldn't dismiss it. I think there's
Africans, when they get circumcised,
African women, who wanna have their
clitoris reattached, they...
Plastic surgeons would take the tip of their toe,
they'll sever the tip of their toe
and reattach it
to their vagina.
If there's a connection between the
tip of the toe and the vagina,
there's probably a connection between
pressure points in the foot and, like...
The energy that resides
at the base of the back.
The kundalini, which is... Sounds
like yours is out of whack and...
So, I think it's worth
checking into, Alex.
Like, I'm really sensual
in the sack.
I like to kiss, I like to cuddle,
I'm affectionate.
Mmm-hmm.
Kissing's big.
And kissing's not easy
when you're having sex.
Yeah, I hear girls love it when you
kiss them during sex. Mmm-hmm.
Rachel! Do you guys kiss
when you...
Sure. Sure. Yeah, yeah.
Girls must love the beard when
you go down on them, right?
'Cause then... Have they ever told you that?
'Cause of the bristles.
Um... 'Cause I had a goatee once,
right after college...
Remember when I had a goatee,
right after college? Yeah, yeah.
You looked... And I went down
on a girl and she said,
"I love the fact that you have these
sort of sharp, bristly things..."
Oh, they like that? The girls hate...
This one girl did.
My... The girls that I get with hate
it when I have a really short one,
when it's this really
short and bristly.
They like it when
it's soft, 'cause it's...
When it's long and soft.
Right, right.
Yeah, it's like a cat's tongue, you know?
Yeah.
I've only been with a few girls that have
actually had a cat go down on them.
I've heard that cats
have dicks that hook back
and so, when they latch on,
it's harder for the female to escape.
Have you heard this? I don't know
if it's just like a horned dick.
No. Like with a curve at the end,
like hooks them in.
And you think
that's brilliant
'cause basically all animal sex is rape,
I think. Right?
Oh, right! 'Cause they don't really
ask for permission.
But that... Why haven't we all
developed the hook dick?
It seems obvious.
That's interesting. Right.
Now this is
an interesting... Ohh!
This is an interesting connection.
This is your neck.
And that can be
both physical,
in terms of a crick in the neck,
whiplash, whatever.
Or... I know, sweetie...
It can be, um...
Tied to a... Someone who's being
a pain in the neck.
Quite often your mother, although certainly,
potentially a female person.
I know, sweetie.
Basically, your neck just said,
"Hey, they're all pains in the neck."
No gender specificity here.
It's all a pain in the neck.
Yeah, yeah, you got a point there,
buddy. You got a point there.
I heard that in Africa,
you know there's...
In some cultures there's a strange
tradition of circumcising
women's genitalia.
Yeah, yeah.
And sometimes they have these
Doctors Without Borders or whatever,
and they actually try to
correct the surgery later on.
Yes, yes. I don't know if you've
heard about this.
They actually... What they do sometimes
is that they take a part of their toe
and put it where the clitoris
used to be. Yes, yes.
So is there, anatomically, a part of
the foot that has a sexual center?
Because it is the end of a digit,
for all practical purposes,
my guess would be...
Chances are good.
So, 50-50
would be my thought.
Ohh!
Would it be possible to, like,
sell some DVDs here or somewhere too?
Put up a little table
or something?
Let's go in here,
we'll talk about it now.
I'm gonna stay out here.
Can we eat? Can I eat this?
No! You have to just
stand here and look at it.
Oh, I can eat this.
Don't eat. Don't eat.
We haven't had dinner yet.
It's so pretty... Well, what do you need...
Are we gonna go in there?
Just... Just...
Let's go this way.
Did you hear that? It's coming from
over there, behind me.
That's a Pileated. So we're
going to stay right here, Wes.
That's not the bird
I'm looking for.
Okay. That's good.
Hey, Rachel,
how are you?
I'm just calling to, uh...
To call and... And...
Yeah, if you feel like giving me a call,
I'd love to...
To, you know, to see... Just to check
in with you and see how you're doing.
So give me a call when you get a chance,
if you feel like it.
Okay, I hope
you're well, bye.
Frittata!
We have the gate band concert on Saturday
to try to make some more money
to help buy this place back from
the bank so we can really own it.
We're working
our way there, um...
As you can probably
see on the slides,
we, you know,
have the building fund going on.
We really want to pay off the bank this year,
so fork it over.
And keep coming to the movies and all that.
We have, uh...
I Love You Phillip Morris continues
through Thursday, starting Friday.
- Who wrote that?
- What's that?
- The movie? I wrote it.
That's clever.
Thank you.
It's one of the funniest movies
I've seen in a long time.
Oh, that's nice, thank you.
Thank you.
Thank you, we tried to have
some fun with the... Thank you.
Hey, how's it going?
Hi. Good, how're you?
All right, nice to see you again.
Great to see you.
So, what made you
come out here?
I... You know, it's just better
the second time.
Oh, thank you
very much. Yeah.
Congratulations! You just...
Well, thank you very much.
You keep getting better with age.
I bought my DVD already.
Just... I don't know. Can I
talk to you for one second?
Yeah. Yeah, yeah.
'Cause I just... I wanna...
One second.
- Yeah.
- Hey.
Hi.
How are you?
I'm doing well. It's good.
Oh, sorry!
What's going on?
What're you doing here?
I just... I wanted
to surprise you.
Well, it's a surprise,
it's a surprise. Surprise.
What's going? Why'd you come here?
Because I just...
I thought that we should
be together, right?
I mean, I thought
you would like it.
I just wanted to make you happy.
You thought I'd like it?
You thought I'd like it for you to follow me
to the next town that I'm in?
Yeah.
How did you get here?
I took the bus.
You took the bus all the
way out here? Yeah.
Okay.
River, that night
was just that night.
I'm sorry I have to be
so direct with you.
But we... That's it. Okay?
That's it.
That's... That's it.
Okay?
Wait, I don't know what you're saying.
I'm sorry.
I don't mean to be a dick.
I don't understand.
I don't know how to be any
more clear about this.
Look, I think it's really cute and romantic
and fun that you came here.
But there's no chance we're hooking up
again tonight. Okay?
Okay, that was a mistake,
I regret...
I don't mean to be rude,
but I regret it.
I had... I had
a break in something...
What? A break? ...and I got something
out of my system.
I just... I can't... I have to go
sell some DVDs.
I can't really spend time
with this, right now.
Wait. I don't... I don't know
what you're saying,
I don't understand.
Hey, hey, go home.
Go home.
What do you mean?
How can I be any more clear
to you? Go home.
It's fucking over, okay?
It wasn't any...
There's nothing even to end.
What do you mean,
"It's over"?
What do you mean? Keep your voice down.
Keep your voice down.
Don't fucking touch me.
I wanna touch you.
Shh!
Just relax. Okay, look,
I'll be back in one minute.
Okay? I'll be back
in one minute.
So, she followed
you out here?
I think she researched the next stop
on the tour and she just showed up.
Did you fuck her?
No, no! We talked very briefly for like,
10 minutes
after one of the screenings we
had a few days ago and like...
She thought there's
a brief connection.
We talked about birds for like
10 minutes and the movie
and she thought there's this connection
and now we're like soul mates.
She never would've followed
someone out to another city
because of a conversation
about birds. Okay, I don't...
She thought we're meant for each other,
she thought it was destiny
and she thought it'd be this really grand
romantic gesture for her to just surprise me.
She's really cute.
Yeah.
We should take
her for a drink.
We should go have
a drink with her.
You know, if she's upset,
you know, she...
It's the least
you could do.
I don't want anything
to do with this girl.
She's clingy, she's needy,
she's unstable, trust me.
I mean, she came all the way out here
and she's feeling a little bit out of it.
So we should, you know...
One drink. She's really cute, man.
What I love about this place is that it's haunted,
there's an actual ghost here.
Don't you think there's something
going on here? Kismet?
That's like my favorite word.
That's a Turkish word.
Kismet?
Mmm-hmm.
It's like fate, it's destiny.
How do ghosts fit in that?
Well, you know, two spirits,
two lost spirits, having spirits
at a place that's
haunted by things.
You know,
everybody's got a ghost.
A skeleton
in the closet, right?
But the third and the most important S...
You're so wise.
The most important S...
Thank you, so are you.
...is to celebrate your life.
But celebrate with an "S".
Not a "C", right?
Sounds crazy!
it's not just important that you
spell things differently
and that you see
things differently,
and that you live
things differently...
You live your
life differently.
That's so brilliant!
Isn't it? So brilliant!
You're so brilliant.
I am going to go celebrate
in the ladies room.
I'll be back.
She's fantastic.
Yeah.
You guys are really clicking.
I love her.
What's the problem?
Maybe there isn't a problem.
There's no problem at all.
You should go back
to the hotel
and I'll stay with her and you know,
we'll just continue talking.
Oh, really? Yeah? Yeah, I mean, yeah.
This'll be great.
You sure?
I'll take a taxi back.
You know, you shouldn't worry
about it, it's totally cool.
Really?
Yeah, go back.
Yeah, it's fantastic,
I mean, this is great.
Okay, sounds great. Well,
good luck! Yeah, hopefully...
I don't think you
need it though.
Hopefully
I'll see you tomorrow.
Okay.
Yeah?
Hey, Rachel, it's me. Just calling to see
if you wanted to chat.
As the days go on here on the road,
I have more time.
It's given me...
...a little bit more
perspective on things,
and I'm slowly,
sort of, you know...
I'm sort of looking back on the...
On what happened, what went wrong and...
I feel like, you know,
I've had...
I've needed to have this, sort of,
vision of myself
as a more successful and more
established and more secure person.
I've been sort of fixated on the future,
you know what I mean?
And I felt... I've always felt like marriage
would maybe compromise
that possibility for growth,
if not annihilate it, you know?
I felt like marriage
was like...
Those amber drops
that they put on insects,
to make them specimens,
you know, that...
That was sort of
my fear of marriage.
It would sort of make me freeze...
Make me plateau.
So what
underlies that?
What underlies that
fear of stagnation?
What underlies... What underlies
that fear of stagnation?
What...
It doesn't...
Hello, front desk.
Yes, hi, would it be possible to get
a late checkout tomorrow morning?
Maybe an extra hour?
Sorry, sir,
we cannot do it.
Why not?
And ever since
that incident...
...the piano
playing ceased...
And as for
little Henry Holiday...
...he was allowed
to rest in peace.
And then his glasses are there
in front of the tombstone.
He's dead.
It's stupid.
Oh, no, it's actually
brilliant because... No,
it's too dark.
When do... No.
When do you ever see a kid die
in a children's book?
It's great, I mean,
I love that he's dead.
Really? I mean, not that I
wanted him to die
because he's a great
protagonist but, like,
kids never get
to see people die
and you know they get told all these lies,
like, their grandma went to the farm
or something... No, their dog
went to the farm,
and that's just not true.
I appreciate that,
I agree with that completely.
I think that the reason why I want
there to be death in a children's book...
I've never seen death so ostensibly
portrayed in a children's book...
Is so that kids
can be exposed
to bad things early in life so they're
more prepared to deal with it later.
You know? Yeah, no,
it's a public service.
This is really...
This is a good education.
Good heart inside
your chest, I can feel it.
It's bleeding right now, you probably
need a tampon for your heart.
Hey.
How'd you sleep?
I slept well.
I slept really well.
Yeah, River, she stayed
here last night.
Guys stayed here last night?
Yeah.
When did you guys get in?
Just a couple of hours ago.
I haven't even been
asleep yet. I actually...
Let's talk outside
for a second.
I don't want
to wake her up.
I had one of the greatest nights of my life
with her last night!
I mean, we just... We just connected.
It was incredible.
I've never had an experience
like this before.
It's like looking in a mirror
and seeing myself.
She's like the perfect height,
perfect intelligence.
It's hard to explain,
man, I would never
in a million years say
the word soulmate, but...
I think we're soulmates.
And she's got friends
in Shreveport
and I was thinking that she would
ride along with us
and we could stay
with her friends.
And you know, save money on the motel,
and you know...
You want her to go
on the tour with us?
Not the whole tour, just...
That's the thing, I feel like we've known
each other our whole lives.
I feel like this instant
kinda...connection, you know?
I've never had this happen before.
It's amazing.
You really
like this girl, huh?
Yes... I like her a lot.
It's incredible.
You know.
You know, what...
What does that mean?
That's what it is,
I think, you know?
And then an infinity symbol,
like the heart.
There's so many symbols and logos going
through my head right now, thinking of her.
Let me... Let me just
have a cup of coffee.
Let me wake up a little bit
and we'll go from there, let me just
think about it for a second, okay?
Yeah.
# If you want me,
you can have me
# Sideways, upside down,
any way you want
# Put it in all the way
# I love you and
I know you love me back
# Let me slide it in
# All the way
to your crack, is that?
# If you want me,
you can have me
# Sideways, upside down,
any way you want
# So come on
# Baby, come on
Alex, you know this shit.
One, two, three!
# Come on!
# Baby, come on!
# Stop!
We are gonna totally
start a fucking band.
It's gonna be awesome!
That was so good.
My heart was feeling a totally
different number, not 28.
I was feeling 33, that was the age
Jesus Christ was when he died.
That was the age of Chris Farley
when he died.
And I should have gone with that,
because Chris Farley's image...
His face just
popped in my head.
But 28 is what
I was feeling as well.
But 33 ultimately is what
I should have chose.
You got close, though. Do you think
the source that's telling you 33
is the number
you should have drawn
is the same source that told you initially
that 28 was the right number?
You never know.
I feel like...
Now I'm thinking
the source is 33.
No, now you think it's 33?
But what was the number?
It landed on 30,
which is between 28 and 33 almost,
so I should have chose 33.
You know what, stop the car...
What are you doing?
...because I'm going to do it again.
Close the door.
I think you guys stay in the car
this time.
Because I think you were distracting me,
because you're gorgeous.
Henry, please get in the car.
You were distracting me
because you're defeatist.
I'm going to do what I should
have done with all this money.
Henry! Rest of the money
I have, by the way...
What're you doing? ...on the age
of Jesus when he died, 33.
Your credit card debt, say goodbye to it,
because it's going to be gone.
You're going to thank me when
I come back! Henry, Henry!
Last night, did you guys...
When you were hanging out
last night, did you...
Does he know how we met?
Does he know
that we had sex?
No, he doesn't know.
You guys didn't
talk about it?
It hasn't come up. He doesn't know
that we hooked up?
a lot of fascinating, wonderful,
personal, intellectual ideas.
We haven't talked
about you, I'm sorry.
Mr. Self-involved filmmaker.
Okay, so...
Though he did mention that you
have a girlfriend back home.
So he doesn't know
we had sex on the beach?
No, he doesn't.
If it did come up, if he asked you,
would you tell him?
Yeah, I would tell him.
If he asks me, I will tell him.
Why? Because I don't lie,
I'm not a liar.
I don't lie to people, I don't lie to
them and take advantage of them.
You know, like some people...
Like some people who...
You know, they seem like
charismatic megafauna
and then you realize that they're
not really charismatic at all.
Nor are their films even that good
when you watch them a second time.
How did it go?
How'd it go?
Was Jesus 32
or 33 when he died?
Because I thought
he was 33,
but then, I read somewhere about the
Christian calendar being...
You know, the Christian calendar
is totally off...
Okay, so River has to go back to Jackson,
Mississippi, tomorrow
for her thesis class,
or she has to teach a TA class
or something like that.
Okay. I think I'm going
to go with her.
Back to Jackson? Yeah, I'm going to
get on the bus with her and go back.
And I don't want to leave you hanging,
'cause I know this is your trip,
and, well, we're doing this together
and I've had an amazing time.
It's been so amazing.
But I have to go with her,
I have to.
I keep thinking about Shel Silverstein
and the way he died.
You know who Shel Silverstein is?
Yeah, the comic.
No, he was...
The illustrator.
He was an illustrator, and wrote
children's books. A Light in the Attic.
Where the Sidewalk Ends,
The Giving Tree.
All these great children's
books that he wrote, amazing.
But when he died, he died alone,
of a heart attack, in his bedroom.
No one discovered him
for two days.
He was discovered
by his maid.
I keep thinking about that,
I don't want to be that person.
All the great children's books
that he wrote,
stories that he wrote, all the joy that he
brought to children's lives.
Ultimately, I'm just haunted by this
image of him dead alone in his bedroom.
I don't want that
to be me, you know?
I want someone to discover my body
relatively early after I die.
I think River could be
that person. You know?
I love her. And I'm lonely, man.
It's like, it's...
I've been waiting my whole life
to meet someone like this.
All the relationships
I've gone through,
they just don't work out,
you know, six months in, year in.
It's not the person for me. I get terrified
of the thought of being with someone.
After just a couple of days, I really think
I can spend the rest of my life with her.
You don't know what I'm talking about
'cause you have Rachel in your life.
You probably forgot what it's like to...
To be isolated or to be alone.
And I've always had my work to
fall back on, my illustrations,
but I want
something more now.
And I feel like she
could be the person.
If I don't go with her,
I'm just gonna be thinking
about her
the whole time anyway.
So, when she takes
that Greyhound bus tomorrow,
I wanna be sitting
next to her.
Mmm, I think
you should, man.
I think, you know... I think you should
be sitting beside her in that bus.
Yeah. Yeah, and I'm really
happy for you.
Like this is... And I don't wanna
leave you...
You don't have to ask my permission,
of course I understand.
Yeah. So, tomorrow night,
you're going to Jackson.
Go comb your hair.
What do you mean?
Go comb your hair, it's a...
It's a Johnny Cash song.
Oh, really?
Yeah.
Shel Silverstein wrote
A Boy Named Sue.
Shel Silverstein wrote that song?
Yeah, he wrote that.
Really?
Yeah.
There is a parade in
Baton Rouge in an hour.
It's a pre-Mardi bra.
Mardi Bra?
Mardi Gras parade.
She just told me. Let's go. Why don't...
Can we go? Can we go?
I don't know.
I'm not really a...
Oh!
Hey! Oh!
Fuck!
Easy!
Alex, you gotta stop
calling me.
Yeah, I know. But, look.
I really need to talk to you.
Okay, I've been doing
a lot of thinking.
I've had a lot of time
on the road
to just kind of look back
on our relationship.
It's given me a lot of
perspective on things and...
And I'm beginning to sort of see...
I'm beginning to sort of see,
you know, I'm beginning
to make sense of things.
Okay, now when I used to,
like, look up at the night sky
I used to kind of just see,
like, these little dots.
These little, like, points
of disagreement, and...
And the arguments
that we had.
But now I feel like I look up
and I see a constellation.
I'm trying to make sense of it,
so it's a constellation.
You know what I mean?
Does that make sense?
Look, Alex. I'm not ready
to talk about this stuff yet.
No, I know. But listen,
just hear me out here. I just...
I'm realizing that I've been really
sort of fixated on this future self.
Like a future version of myself,
a more successful, and established and...
A secure version of myself. I need that
just to make sense of myself, in a way.
And I've always feared
that marriage would somehow
just compromise that
possibility for that growth.
You know, so really,
there is a...
There's a fear of
stagnation in place.
But what underlies that
fear of stagnation? Right?
What's beneath it, what are
the roots of it? You know?
Death! Death is the
underlying root of all this.
This fear of commitment,
this fear of marriage,
it's a reverberation
of my death anxiety.
Okay, that's what's going on. It's
all around us. Death is everywhere.
It's the underlying fear and
that's the most... It's ridiculous.
There is no way
to stop death.
There is no way to really postpone
it for very long.
So if you realize the absurdity of the
underlying fear,
then, you know,
any reverberatory fears,
you know, quadruply,
astronomically more ridiculous.
Where are you going
with all this?
That's what I'm saying. We all are,
we're all gonna die, okay?
By denying that, we misdirect
our search for happiness.
I'm ready to die. Which means
I'm ready to live.
And I'm ready to love you. Which is
actually why I need you to fly down
to Louisiana
tomorrow afternoon.
So I can ask you something in person.
So I could ask you something
I really, really, really don't
wanna ask you on the phone.
What are you
talking about?
You want me to drop everything,
get on a plane,
and fly halfway
across the country?
Yeah, just come down
for 12 hours.
I don't care
how much it costs.
I'm just begging you, please,
please, please, come down.
I'm on my knees. Okay, look,
I'm on my knees.
I just... I'm begging you
to please come down.
Alex, I'm tired.
I'm just driving back from work.
I've had a really long week.
Maybe this is something we can talk about
when you get back. Okay?
No, look. There's a moment
happening here.
Okay, there is a moment that
I cannot risk evaporating, okay?
And I need to seize
the moment.
Okay? Please. Look,
I'll fly you in,
spend one night,
and then you can fly back.
Rachel, come on!
I'm begging you.
I see the constellation, okay?
Just give me
a second chance.
Okay, I'm begging you.
All right? I...
Just... Just get
on the fucking plane.
I don't understand the rush. I mean,
why don't you just ask her when you're back...
I don't know. I just thought it'd
be romantic and...
You know, spontaneous,
impulsive...
Impulsive...
You know what I mean?
Yeah!
Impulsive, you know?
I don't think
it's that impulsive.
He's been dating her...
It's a little impulsive.
...for three, four
and a half years.
Constantly? Perpetually?
Oh, yeah, yeah.
Alex is not a compulsive person.
Impulsive and spontaneous.
What have you done impulsive?
Oh, I don't know, but...
This week, what have you done...
I just think it would be nice,
if you know, I can tell my kids
down the road, "Hey, guess how I proposed
to your mother?" You know?
On a whim, I just called her up.
It'll be a nice story.
That's cool, because we're part
of the story, you know.
And you guys
are part of the story.
On the southern director's tour and...
Yeah.
And 80 years from now,
when you're on your third marriage,
and you talk to your grandkids about
your first wife, you know.
We'll be part of that, part of the story.
That'll be amazing.
That's great!
That's fantastic, man.
Congratulations.  Kanpai!
Kanpai!
Empty. Sorry, bad luck.
Oh, okay.
Would you guys mind if I dropped
you off a little bit early
at the bus station tomorrow,
like, around 2:00 or 2:15?
That way I can get to the airport
without being late.
Yeah, that's fine. No problem.
All right.
Oh!
It's not letting me click on 3:00.
I think it's actually...
On a Tuesday, they're sold out
at 3:00 already, really?
Strange. There's another
bus at 8:00.
Going to Jackson,
we could do that.
You think it allows you to click
on the 8:00 but not the 3:00?
Yeah, it does, it's weird.
So, how much
is this one here?
This one here
is sold for $8,550.
The only thing that
I can think of that we have
that will go in that price range
will be maybe this, I mean...
It's emerald, as far
as your color.
The stone itself,
I think it's...
A gem stone, but...
Okay. Okay.
So I mean, if that's her birthstone,
I think that would be nice.
Okay, yeah. And how much
does this go for?
$24.99.
And the box is included?
I got it. Let's see it.
Let's see it.
Check it out. You guys ready?
Yeah.
Oh, look at that.
Ah!
That's pretty. That's nice.
You guys don't like it?
I like it.
No, it's very green.
So, that's something.
I mean... Well...
What does that mean?
Well, it's a green box
and a green stone.
Like, probably, what?
A gem stone.
It's an emerald,
it's her birthstone.
I think it looks nice. That's not
an emerald, that's a gem stone.
That's like,
that's some kind of...
Emerald is a type of gem.
How are you?
Good.
It's nice to see you.
You too.
I'm sorry I'm late.
It's okay.
Thank you so much for coming.
Sure. No problem.
You want me to get your bag?
No.
I got it.
You sure?
Yeah, no, no. I got it.
I can grab it.
You're a wild boy,
you're a wild boy.
All right, so the co-op is...
No, they...
Do you like arugula and
quinoa and stuff like that?
Hey, guys.
They have all that kind of...
How's it going?
Rachel...
What's up? You look great.
I'm good.
And this is River. Rachel, River.
Hi.
Hey, so you guys
want to get going?
I got a studio space,
but I don't really use it that much.
I try to go on location as much
as possible when I'm working.
Like I actually went,
believe it or not, to a graveyard when
I was doing a lot of
the conceptual sketches
for the book.
Actually, it was there,
around, surrounded
by death constantly
to the right of me, to the left of me,
in front of me.
It was cool. I actually was inspired.
I could see, I've never...
Draw the... I drew the graveyard,
of course,
when I saw it was great from 360 angles,
and that kind of thing.
But there's something else, something morbid,
that kind of seeped into me.
I felt like I was possessed or something
while I was writing.
Do you think it's that building?
That kind of looks like...
I can't see.
Oh, Atkinson, this is it.
It's Atkinson. See, it's on the inside.
Okay.
Okay, all right.
This is it, Atkinson Hall.
All right! So...
You know, intro is gonna be a few minutes
of Q and A. You wanna meet here...
What time?
Let's meet here at 4:30.
Okay.
Does that work for you?
Yeah.
You guys know where you are?
Uh-huh.
You're not gonna get lost?
No.
See you later.
Okay.
I'm gonna go introduce the movie.
You wanna come in or...
Uh, yeah.
You sure?
You don't have to.
No, no, no. I'll come in.
Okay.
Okay, class. We're going to watch
the  Woodpecker,
and as an added treat,
we have the writer and director,
Mr. Alex Karpovsky,
here to watch it with us and answer any
questions afterwards.
So everybody give him
a round of applause.
Thanks a lot. Thank you.
All right. Well, thank you. Thank you very
much for coming here, for watching my film.
I really appreciate it.
Most of the venues
where I've been showing my film
on the tour
have been little
art house theaters
and auditoriums
in college campuses,
where we show
the film at night.
So, it's kind of a...
It's a treat for me.
It's nice to do
something different,
to show the movie
in a classroom environment.
With a production class.
But I hope you enjoy it. I'll be here
for a Q and A after the film
where maybe we can get into some of the
details about the film and the process.
Okay, enjoy the film. And I'll see you
soon. Bye-bye.
Did you get the sense that everyone
in that classroom was high?
There was this look in their eyes
where they all just seemed
totally glazed over
and baked.
Or maybe that's just an old
man looking upon the youth.
I kind of almost even think
of those as sister
anxieties,
or companion anxieties,
because one, like,
ricochets off the other.
When one is affected, there's
kind of a ripple or trickle down.
And in a way, I kind of
think of those two
as almost like
a binary star system.
It's like one kind of just orbits the other.
But there's still a kind of...
They're still part of the
constellation as a whole.
You know, they're still part of the
whole framework. You know what I mean?
I don't care about constellations
and reverberations
and ricocheting.
How do you expect me
to believe that after
seven years of being
in a relationship,
that you've had these epiphanies
and you've become this new man?
You're telling me
that all of your fears
that have fully informed
you and your personality
are now just
completely gone?
That now you're just ready to just
jump back into the relationship
as this new person?
Yeah, epiphanies happen.
You know, sometimes I think,
especially in extraordinary situations,
you know, you can have
real breakthroughs like...
Look, the last week, for better or for worse,
has been, you know...
In a way, it's been
an extraordinary week.
We've never fully properly
broken up before.
You know, and it's
forced me to think
in a very unfamiliar,
unexplored place
that has turned over
a lot of stones for me.
It's been very
illuminating, you know...
It's been a week.
Look, I'm not saying
Rome was built...
Okay, I know Rome wasn't built in a day.
I know it's gonna take time.
I feel like I'm making very significant
insight that's gonna lead to very...
You know, various...
Significant progress.
But, look, I also think
you know, if you...
If you really just sort of...
Spotlight...
Put all the spotlight
and focus on certain fears,
then they can evaporate,
you know...
I don't care about
any of that stuff.
Do you love me?
Do you wanna spend the rest of your
life with me?
Are you gonna be
fully honest and open?
Am I gonna stifle you?
I love you with every part of my heart,
every part of my being.
Okay?
I wanna spend the rest
of my life with you.
I think being with you will be
the opposite of stifling.
I think it will open up a whole new
world to explore.
And that's why I wanted to fly you down here.
Okay, to tell you all this.
And also to ask you, you know,
a very important question, which I didn't...
Kind of wasn't preparing
to do it anyway.
Just... So I wanna
ask you something.
I don't want you
to answer now.
'Cause I don't wanna put
that pressure on you.
Within the next few days.
Whenever you're ready.
I'm glad you flew down.
I'm glad you're here.
It means so much to me. I'm glad
I was able to tell you this in person
and finally ask you
this question.
So...
Rachel, will you marry me?
Okay?
Is it too tight?
Yeah.
I don't think it's gonna...
Well, if you...
Does that hurt?
Yeah.
That's good.
It's...
It's fine, it's fine.
It's emerald,
it's your birthstone.
Matches your eyes nicely.
It looks really nice.
I think if you...
If you actually
hold it the other way...
What's wrong?
It's just a spasm.
All right, it'll go away.
Since when do you get
back spasms?
I hurt my back.
Actually I hurt it...
Oh! I better just try sitting
somewhere. There's...
There's, like, scratches all over your back.
Is that where it's from?
Scratches?
Yeah.
They're all over
your back.
Well, I don't
really see them.
Oh, I see them
a little bit.
No, I mean they're
like all over.
Oh, in the back.
Yeah. I wonder...
Oh, you know what?
I think me and Henry were...
We were driving and we pulled off on
the side of the highway to try to pee.
But we pulled in this terrible spot,
there was all these...
...bushes, like these scratchy bushes,
and I think I kind of...
I had to get in there
to get out of the highway
so people wouldn't
see my dick, you know, so...
Got all scratched up.
I mean, you can't
even see it though.
Have you been with anyone since
you moved out?
Have I been with anyone?
Like, have I hooked up
with someone else?
Yeah.
Or anything like that.
No.
You promise?
Yes!
Okay.
It looks really nice on you.
It matches your eyes.
Does  Cat in the Hat... Like, was that
a euphemism for something?
How is it disgusting?
You're wearing...
Hey, guys, how's it going?
...new dresses...
Good, how are you?
All right, we've got
a few minutes.
Yeah? Hey, can I talk
to you for a second?
Let me talk to you for a second.
Come here, come here.
For a second. I'll be right back.
What?
- What did she say?
- What's that?
What did she say?
Did you ask her?
She said, uh...
Hmm.
You're so pretty.
And you look beautiful
with that ring on and...
Congratulations.
Uh...
It's a little complicated.
Hmm.
But I asked her not to answer
the question.
But she allowed me to put the ring
on her finger.
She's wearing the ring?
She's wearing the ring right now.
That's great. You're engaged!
Yeah, it's like a soft yes.
That's awesome.
Give me a hug. Yeah.
That's fantastic. Congratulations.
You're a husband.
Well, yeah!
She is... This is...
It's exciting in a lot of ways.
It is exciting.
Tragic too, in some ways.
Yeah.
But there's a 50% chance
it's gonna work out for you.
You know, that's
really great!
So you've been
traveling with them long?
Like three days.
Few days, few days.
Like a lifetime though,
you know.
You're having
a good time?
Um, it's a little...
It's interesting.
Hmm.
Good.
Do you know anything about
scratches on his back?
Is that a band?
No, like...
Like scratches. Like, Alex has scratches
all over his back.
Do you have any idea
what that's from?
I don't know,
they could be from anything.
You have no idea?
Hey, I mean,
I have a few ideas.
I always have
ideas about things.
Like, I have a very vivid imagination.
Well, I mean...
I can imagine a lot of things.
I know.
But do you know
where they're from?
I was thinking maybe I would do
the invitations to the wedding.
Oh, that's a great idea.
The illustrations.
Maybe do art cards. Maybe do like
an actual... That's a good idea.
Look, I'm asking you, do you know
about the scratches on his back?
Do you know
where they're from?
Why can't you
just answer me?
I don't know where
they came from exactly.
I can't be sure.
Because I haven't seen them.
Did you fuck Alex?
You're asking me that?
You just got engaged.
Okay?
You don't wanna ask me
something like that.
That's not what a person
who's just got engaged...
Did you fuck him?
Did you fuck my boyfriend?
So, this is awesome, man.
Yeah, I'm really excited.
She doesn't look
excited, though.
What's going on over there?
Is she excited?
Why would you ask me...
Why won't you answer me?
Did you fuck Alex?
Yes, I fucked him, okay?
And he fucked me right back.
That's what happened.
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey!
Relax. What's wrong with you?
You couldn't keep your mouth shut,
you fucking evil witch!
You fucked her?
Okay, well, it looks like
Alex isn't here yet.
Does anybody have anything
they want to mention?
Hey, Rachel.
Rachel, could you
stop, please?
Rachel?
Hey!
Where are you going?
Open the car and get my bag.
I'm leaving.
You going to the airport
and you're gonna fly away?
Yeah.
Open the car.
Look, I'm sorry.
Okay?
I'm sorry.
In the grand scheme of things,
I didn't think it mattered.
Okay?
You asked me if
I hooked up with anyone.
In the grand
scheme of things,
in terms of what I was trying to
communicate to you
in the moment, in terms of our plans
for our future together,
my hopes for my future with you,
it did not matter.
And I still feel
like it doesn't matter.
Just give me my bag.
You're sick.
Here you have this incredible,
glorious creature,
one of the most beautiful birds
to ever fly in North America.
And then, because of
our own stupidities,
deforestation,
our negligence,
it was allowed
to fade away.
It disappeared,
it went extinct.
And then we find out
60, 70 years later,
that, perhaps it's been
miraculously revived.
And, uh...
Here we have an unbelievable
opportunity to...
To learn from our mistakes.
To find the bird,
to protect its habitat,
and perhaps, set an example
for other endangered species.
However, more recently,
I realized that there's no such thing
as second chances,
because we're gonna make
the same mistakes again.
Sooner or later,
it's gonna happen.
And if we're doomed to make
the same mistakes again,
then in principle,
we can't really have a true
and free second opportunity.
And the reason we're doomed to
make the same mistakes again is...
Is because we don't change.
Fundamentally, we'll never
be able to change.
We're all going to make the same
mistakes again in one form or another,
until we die.
A great poet once said,
"Hope is the thing with feathers."
A great, glorious thing
that allows us to fly
high above the thought
of our imminent extinction.
Now, my feathers
have been plucked,
my feathers
have been scattered.
But maybe one day
they will find me again.
Somehow, somewhere down this lonely
American road.
I understand,
but I still can't give you
a late checkout
tomorrow morning.
Why not? After everything
I've told you.
After explaining to you that my heart
has been ripped out of my chest, okay?
I've been abandoned
by everyone I know,
that I'm gonna have to continue the
rest of this frittata tour all by myself.
My back is
raging with pain.
Okay, I'm not gonna be able
to sleep comfortably
for more than 20 minutes
in a row tonight, okay?
You can't give me one extra hour
to lick my wounds?
That's correct, sir.
Those are the rules.
Right.
Right, rules are rules, right?
Gotta follow the rules, right?
Rules and regs.
What's the point of living
in a world that's this cold,
this unforgiving,
this harsh. Hmm?
What happened to a random
act of kindness to a stranger?
What's the point?
Look, if you wanna stay an extra hour
tomorrow morning, I'm gonna
charge you for an extra day.
Okay. Well, you know, I...
I guess I'll take my
pain killers and hope,
you know, my back pain isn't
too terribly excruciating.
And, you know, if I end up needing
an extra, you know,
half an hour or hour
of sleep tomorrow morning,
you can go ahead and charge me for the
whole day rate, just charge it on my card.
Go ahead, use the card.
Okay.
Mmm-hmm, yeah.
Charge...
Put it on the card.
Yeah, charge it up. Okay, sir,
you have a great night.
All right,
have a better night.
Okay.
Thank you for calling
Bank Of America.
This is Barbara,
how may I help you?
Hi, Barbara. I seem to have
misplaced my credit card.
And I was wondering if you could
maybe freeze it, you know.
Put a freeze on it and
maybe send me a new one?
"Goodbye, everyone.
"Some of you
"will remember me
"as a kind friend,
"a caring brother,
"or a..."
Something filmmaker.
What kind of a filmmaker?
"Gifted."
"Adroit."
"Or as an adroit
filmmaker.
"But most of you
"will remember me as..."
As what?
Global network that supports our lives
can act as a conductor.
...240 nano-Tesla is going
to be mind-boggling,
leaving us fully exposed
to the fury of the sun.
A nano-Tesla is a measure
of electro-magnetic power.
The biggest solar storm
recorded in 1859
is estimated to have been
around 200 nano-Teslas.
The one now moving towards Earth
is unprecedented.
Housekeeper.
It's 12:30.
Sir, checkout time is 12:30.
It's 12:30 now?
Yes.
Am I dead?
Get out of here. Because
the police is on its way.
I told you,
you couldn't do it.
Hey, excuse me.
Excuse me.
You forgot something.
This is yours.
What's that? This is yours.
You left this.
Oh, yeah. I was...
I was writing down
some notes last night.
It's for a project.
Internet was down,
so I had to...
Mmm-hmm.
Do you know why they never
give people late checkouts?
Rules are rules.
Applies to everybody.
Even for adroit
filmmakers like yourself.
Got it.
Is everything okay?
Yeah, everything...
Everything is fine.
Things are horrible.
Do you need a hug?
Do you want a hug?
Okay.
Do you wanna come
to Shreveport with me?
How long are you going for?
Preuzeto sa www.titlovi.com