A billionaire playboy...
(Sara screams)
Lost at sea.
(Gasps)
Compelled by his father's
dying confession...
I didn't build our city.
I failed it.
No!
Oliver Queen made a promise
to one day right
his father's wrongs.
(Robert's voice) This is
your responsibility now.
My responsibility?
But first...
(Whoosh)
Aah! Aah!
He had to survive...
You want survive? You kill.
To forge himself into a weapon.
Five years later...
(Reporters) Mr. Queen!
He returned home...
(Man) Oliver Queen is alive.
But not as Oliver Queen.
As something else.
What happened to you
on that island?
How did you survive this?
He punished the wicked
and corrupt...
What do you want? Aah!
Delivering justice
outside the law.
I do what's necessary.
(Brakes screech)
You're no hero.
You're a killer.
His allies were few.
There's more than one way
to save this city.
(Laurel) What makes you so sure
I'm gonna help you?
His enemies many.
Who needs two bullets
in the chest?
(Oliver)
Are you ready to die?
It soon became clear
that the real threat
to Starling City...
Oh, my God.
Was far more deadly
than he had ever imagined.
In six months,
the organization's vision
will be complete.
And it would take everything...
You might just
have a chance.
He learned.
No, you can't!
Why should I trust you?!
You should make up
your mind.
You have failed this city.
♪ Arrow 2x00 ♪
Year One
Original Air Date on October 2, 2013
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
Oliver Queen is alive.
The Starling City resident
was found by fishermen
in the North China Sea.
(Reporters shouting at once)
Queen is the son
of Starling City billionaire
Robert Queen,
who was also onboard
but now officially confirmed
as deceased.
When Oliver Queen returned home
to Starling City,
he was not
the same spoiled rich kid
who had disappeared at sea.
The Oliver you lost might not be
the one they found.
The lavish life
he had once taken for granted
now seemed foreign.
(Tommy) Okay,
what else did you miss?
Super Bowl winners--giants,
Steelers, Saints, Packers.
A black president--that's new.
What was it like there?
(Water lapping)
Cold.
Everything around him
had changed,
beginning with his mother.
Walter and I are married.
And I don't want you to think
that either one of us
did anything
to disrespect your father.
His sister Thea
had grown up fast.
Where did you get these?
Thank you,
daddy's A.C.L. tear.
Ollie!
No one's called me that
in a while, Speedy.
Worst nickname ever.
Thea had been managing
her grief
in less than healthy ways.
My brother and my father
died.
I went to your funeral.
You can't come back here
and judge me,
especially for being
just like you.
This me--the best I could do
with what I had to work with.
So what'd you miss the most?
Steaks at the Palm?
Drinks at the Station?
Meaningless sex?
Laurel.
Everyone is happy
you're alive.
You wanna see the one person
who isn't?
Hello, Laurel.
Hunt has an army of lawyers,
and they are ready to bury us.
You and I against many.
I love those odds.
Why do you hate me?
Oliver's ex-girlfriend
Laurel Lance
had become an attorney,
going after Starling City's
corrupt and powerful.
Laurel was tough.
Why are you here, Ollie?
She had to be...
To apologize.
After what Oliver had done.
I never meant--
she was my sister.
(Sara screaming)
Sara!
Aah!
I couldn't grieve
because I was so angry.
That's what happens
when your sister dies
while screwing your boyfriend.
It should've been you.
I'd hoped that
you'd rot in hell
a whole lot longer
than five years.
No! No! Help!
Dad, she's out there!
She's not there!
She's gone.
Laurel wasn't the only one
who was angry.
Did you even try to save her?
Did you even try to save
my daughter?
(Lucas)
Okay, let's go, partner.
Fine.
Her father,
Detective Quentin Lance,
never recovered from the loss
of his daughter Sara.
Let's go.
(Clears throat)
He wasn't ready to forgive,
but Oliver was much better
at letting go.
How much do you know about your
own so-called friends over here?
His best friend
and former girlfriend
had grown close.
Well, I guess
they never told you
that they've been screwing
while you were gone.
Look, man, I--
Tommy...
It's okay.
Oliver's homecoming attracted
all types of attention...
What the hell?!
Including the wrong kind.
(Thud)
Mr. Queen!
(Taser crackles)
Did he make it to the island?
Did he tell you anything?
(Crackling)
Uhh! Aah!
(Robert grunts)
I'm not the man
you think I am.
I didn't build our city.
I failed it.
(Groans)
Did you father survive
that accident?
(Exhales deeply)
You can survive this.
Make it home.
Make it better.
Right my wrongs.
But you gotta
live through this first.
Survive.
(Gasps)
No!
(Gunshot)
What did he tell you,
Mr. Queen?
He told me
I'm gonna kill you.
Oliver's time on the island
changed him,
and his assailants
were the first to find out
just how much.
But he couldn't allow anyone to
know what he was capable of.
Nobody can know my secret.
(Bones crunch)
Aah!
(Thud)
Robert Queen had left his son
with a list of names--
people who had done wrong
by Starling City.
It was his dying wish
that Oliver would make them pay
for their crimes.
Five years on the island
of Lian Yu
had prepared him mentally
and physically.
It would his mission
to rid his city, one by one,
of those who were using
their powers to destroy it.
You remind Grell, I put him on
the bench, I can take him off.
I will turn him into
a cautionary tale.
Yes, Mr. Hunt.
And this attorney--
(electricity crackles)
Uhh!
Get in the car!
Oliver wouldn't be able to
carry out this justice
as himself.
He needed to live
in the shadows.
He would have to become
someone else...
something else.
You're gonna transfer
$40 million
by 10:00 p.m. tomorrow night.
Or what?
Or I'm gonna take it,
and you won't like how.
(Slaps hand)
He was wearing a hood.
A green hood.
And he had a bow and arrow.
We'll put out
an A.P.B. on...
Robin Hood.
He said he would be back here
by 10:00 p.m.
Make sure you're here first.
He's never gonna get in.
(Electricity powers down)
(Elevator bell dings)
Uhh! Uhh!
You missed.
Really?
(Metal clanks)
(Helicopter whirring overhead)
Tell me you saw that.
Untraceable?!
It is $40 million!
Find it!
(Exhales deeply)
How did he do it?
His war on Starling City's
cancerous criminal elite
had begun.
But Oliver never imagined
the extent of the disease...
or just how far it had spread.
My son knows nothing.
You know, Robert didn't tell him
anything that could hurt us.
And he has no idea that
the yacht was sabotaged.
(Man) Who's that?
Where'd he come from?
Working from his father's list,
Oliver Queen systematically took down
the worst of Starling City's
corrupt and powerful...
Please! No, please!
Marcus Redmond,
you failed this city.
Please don't! Please don't!
Administering brutal justice.
Aah! Aah!
You're gonna testify
in that trial.
You're gonna confess to having
Victor Nocenti killed.
Please, no! Aah!
No one knew
who the vigilante was,
but his exploits
quickly became notorious.
This guy gets more airtime
than the Kardashians.
This city used to be different.
People used to feel safe.
Afraid we're gonna be next?
(Siren wailing)
He gained the attention
of the law...
Freeze!
Bow down, hands up.
(Clank)
And earn notice from enemies
he didn't yet know existed.
A modern day Robin Hood.
Jason Brodeur.
Adam Hunt.
Warren Patel.
Tell me you see a connection,
Moira.
He's not targeting the rich.
No, he's not.
He's targeting the list.
Secrets and lies were critical
to survival,
so to the public,
he was the rich playboy
he had always been.
I miss Tequila!
(Cheering)
To the Russian Bratva,
he was a captain.
And after earning
their trust...
Pleased to meet you.
They provided
valuable information
about the criminal underground.
But to Oliver's family,
he was a ghost.
I felt closer to you
when you were dead.
Look, I know it was hell
where you were,
but it was hell here, too.
You gotta let me in, Ollie.
You gotta let someone in.
(Moira) Oliver.
I wanna introduce you
to someone.
(Oliver) What do I call you?
(John) Diggle's good.
To his new bodyguard
John Diggle...
So...
Oliver would be an extremely
difficult assignment.
You're ex-military?
Yes, sir.
105th Airborne
out of Kandahar. Retired.
I don't want there to be
any confusion, Mr. Queen.
My ability to keep you from harm
will outweigh your comfort.
(Car door opens and closes)
(Car horns honk,
tires screech)
Years before,
Diggle's brother was murdered
by a vicious assassin
called Deadshot,
who had recently returned
to Starling City.
(Gunshot)
Aah!
(Woman screams)
Oliver faced off
with the killer...
Uhh!
(Thud)
And took him out,
but not before
one of Deadshot's
signature poison-laced bullets
ended up in Diggle.
After saving
his bodyguard's life,
Oliver decided it was time
to let him in on his secret.
You're that vigilante.
Starling City is dying.
It is being poisoned
by a criminal elite
who don't care
who they hurt.
And what are you gonna do?
Take 'em all down
by your lonesome?
No, I want you to join me.
Here's the security footage
from the Exchange building
shooting.
While investigating
the Deadshot incident,
Detective Lance made
a shocking discovery.
Hey, whoa, whoa, whoa.
What?
Wait, go back 10 seconds.
What is that?
(Taps button)
I'll be damned.
(Oliver)
What the hell is going on?!
(Thea) What's happening?!
Oliver Queen, you're under arrest
on suspicion
of obstruction of justice,
aggravated assault...
What?!
Acting as a vigilante,
and murder.
Who's your attorney,
Mr. Queen?
The accusation made for
an unlikely alliance...
Dinah Laurel Lance, Your Honor.
And drove a wedge
between father and daughter.
You hate the hood
and you hate Oliver,
and you want more than anything
for them to be the same person.
Oliver managed
to beat a polygraph.
Are you the man in this picture?
No.
The truth he did tell...
I didn't want to talk about what
happened to me on the island
because the people that were
there tortured me.
Had an effect on Laurel.
(Gasps)
How did you survive this?
There were times
when I wanted to die.
(Gasps)
In the end, there was something
I wanted more.
You don't--
Laurel, you don't have to go.
House arrest provided Oliver
an opportunity
to prove he wasn't the Hood,
with a little help...
From Diggle
as the vigilante.
An arms dealer was attacked
across town tonight
by the vigilante.
In light of that,
all charges against your son
are being dropped.
Thank you.
Once he was free,
Oliver and Diggle went
back to work.
Ow! Uhh!
Variable acceleration.
Fighters work
at the same pace.
You switch it up, throw your
opponent off his game.
That was nice.
Where'd you learn that?
His name was Yao Fei.
(Thunderclap)
After the shipwreck,
Oliver landed
on the island of Lian Yu.
He soon discovered...
Aah! Aah!
He was not alone.
First he met Yao Fei...
(Speaks indistinctly)
Ex-Chinese military
exiled to the island
for a crime he didn't commit.
Also on the island?
Do you know what
this island is named?
Lian Yu.
Mandarin for "Purgatory""
a mysterious militia
with bad intentions.
Aah!
After Yao rescued Oliver...
He sent him to meet
another ally.
(Gasps) Twitch and I will open
your throat.
(Strained voice)
Yao Fei sent me here,
and I'm pretty sure it wasn't
so you could kill me.
Slade Wilson was Australian
secret intelligence service,
stranded on the island
after a failed operation
to extricate Yao Fei.
Everybody is in this life
for themselves.
Learn that
at Australian spy school?
No. I learned that here.
He taught Oliver that to
survive and escape the island,
he would have to fight.
You have no skill,
no strength,
no training.
I told you,
I'm not a soldier.
Aah!
(Laughs)
(Panting)
There might be a fighter
inside of you after all.
You know, one of these days,
you're gonna be straight with me
about what really happened
on that island.
Absolutely.
Aah!
But not today.
Diggle was the only one
who knew the truth
about Oliver's double life,
but there was another
who Oliver turned to regularly.
Felicity Smoak?
Felicity Smoak--
Queen Consolidated's
I.T. superstar.
I was at my coffee shop
surfing the web,
and I spilled a latte on it.
These look like bullet holes.
My coffee shop is
in a bad neighborhood.
So a friend of mine is running
a scavenger hunt.
I first need to get
through this.
This is a military-grade
cryptographic security protocol.
My buddy Kevin is starting
an energy drink company.
Could you please do
a spectral analysis?
If it's an energy drink,
why is it in a syringe?
I ran out of sports bottles.
Felicity was also a resource
for Oliver's stepfather
Walter Steele.
I was hoping you could
look into something for me.
Discreetly.
I'm your girl.
When Walter found a mysterious
diary in his wife's possession,
Felicity helped him decode it.
It was information
too dangerous to hold.
(Moira) Let me talk to him.
I think we're past the point
of conversation, Moira,
which means something
must be done about it.
(Man) Please help me welcome
Mr. Malcolm Merlyn.
Malcolm Merlyn was a titan
of Starling City industry.
He was also Tommy's father.
My wife would've liked you,
Laurel.
Their relationship was complex.
Well, I wish I would've
known her.
She passed away before
Tommy and I became friends.
She was killed, Laurel.
There's no need
to be polite about it.
Merlyn was also
a man with secrets...
Secrets he would do anything
to protect.
(Grunts)
(Malcolm) It's done.
And he won't be harmed?
Nor will he ever discover your
involvement. You have my word.
What's done is done.
No, Moira.
It's just beginning.
(Man, modulated voice)
We must send a message.
(Arrows whoosh)
(Squish)
When the dark archer
first appeared,
it seemed he was just
an imitator
in a different color hood.
But when he drew Oliver
into a fight,
his purpose was
curiously specific.
I know about the list,
and the man who authored it
wants you dead!
Aah!
Uhh! Aah! Uhh!
Oliver knew he was dealing with
somebody more than a copycat.
The other archer told me that
somebody compiled the list.
I always assumed
it was my father.
I think there's someone else
out there,
someone who's more of a danger
than the archer.
And I am gonna take him down.
While Oliver was focused
solely on the list...
Leo Mueller,
you have failed this city.
Others expected more of him.
Maybe you can
make a difference
if you think beyond the scope
of those pages.
I'm sure your father
wouldn't mind.
No, you don't get it.
My father died
so that I could live.
Every name that I cross off
this list honors that sacrifice.
Oliver, there's more than
one way to save this city.
Not for me.
It sounds like you have a narrow
definition of being a hero.
I'm not a hero.
Hero or not,
more of his missions took him
outside of the list.
Aah!
He took down drug dealers...
Enjoy
the fruits of your labor.
(Groans)
Psychopathic murderers...
A family of thieves.
Drop your weapons!
I got this!
No! Uhh!
And at times,
he showed compassion
towards those driven to crime
by the city his father failed.
It wasn't his fault.
(Breathes heavily)
I turned my son into this.
If your dad could've
seen you this week,
the way you cared about
the people he had hurt,
the way you stepped up
to try to help them...
I'd say he'd be
pretty damn honored.
I can't imagine
you want the death
of an innocent young woman
on your hands,
not with your principles.
Aah!
(Yao Fei) No!
Hey!
Uhh!
Shado was Yao Fei's daughter,
brought from mainland China
to Lian Yu
to use as leverage against Yao.
No.
It soon became apparent that
Shado was not an ideal captive.
Let the girl go.
(Fyers) Kill her!
No!
And she proved she was
her father's daughter.
Shado, along with Slade Wilson,
trained Oliver to fight.
She coached him in skills
she had learned
from her father.
Showoff.
(Man) Missile one locked
on the jet's heat trail.
(Fyers) Prepare to launch
on my mark.
When the island militia
attempted to down
a commercial airliner...
We need to reprogram
the missile.
Oliver and his allies...
(Beeps)
(Missile whistling)
Let her go.
And when tested,
Oliver put everything he had
learned from Slade and Shado
into practice.
Uhh!
I got your message.
Is there a reason we can't
do this face-to-face?
Oliver, as the vigilante,
began covertly helping
Laurel Lance
to defend people
the law couldn't protect.
What's in here?
Leverage. Enough to help save
Peter Declan's life.
As an attorney, I never would've
gotten a file like this.
I always thought the law was
sacred. You fixed everything.
Now what do you think?
I think there's
too many people in this city
who only care about
themselves.
They need someone like you.
Her connection to the Hood
complicated
Laurel's relationships
with her father...
He's a damn criminal,
and you've worked with him.
That makes you an accessory.
I am trying to save
an innocent man's life.
No.
You're breaking the law.
And her boyfriend.
So you met up with
the hood guy? Knowingly?
Laurel, he's a murderer.
You sound like my father.
Well, I hate to break it to you,
but he's right.
She's been working with
the hood guy.
And there's some sort of
infatuation thing going on here.
I--
fix this.
Before it becomes something
that's unfixable.
Oliver had trouble
being honest,
but that didn't
stop Felicity...
Hi.
From coming to him for help.
Can I trust you?
You've dropped some
fairly ridiculous lies on me,
and...
Yet I still feel like
I can trust you.
You can trust me.
Then I have something
to show you.
Where'd you get it?
From your stepfather.
He said it belongs
to your mother.
This is
your father's notebook.
He kept a list of all the people
in Starling City
who owed him favors.
I've been researching some of
those names online,
and, uh,
they're not good people.
The only way
to keep this family safe
is for everyone in it
to stop asking questions,
including you, Oliver.
But there were still
too many questions left to ask.
I made it clear to him
persuasively
that his plans endanger
the undertaking.
I didn't have to make
the usual threats.
(Malcolm) Excellent.
Oliver was concerned
about his mother...
What's the Undertaking?
I don't know.
But with all this talk
about threats, it can't be good.
And determined to find out
everything she knew.
What are you gonna do?
(Gasps)
Moira Queen,
you have failed this city.
Please don't kill me.
Do you know anything
about the Undertaking?
I am a mother.
Please don't take me
from my children.
Oliver couldn't help
but show his mother mercy.
I'm not gonna hurt you.
He should've known better.
(Siren wailing in distance)
After he escaped...
(Car alarm chirps)
He went to the one person
at Queen Consolidated
he could trust.
Whoa!
(Strained voice) I'm not gonna
hurt you, Felicity.
How do you know my name?
Because you know my name.
Everything about you just became
so unbelievably clear.
(Exhales)
The Starling City Vigilante
attacked Mrs. Queen...
(Felicity) Excuse me.
Can you help me?
He's... really heavy.
(Felicity) I should've
taken him to a hospital.
Felicity, listen. Trust me.
He'll be fine.
He's been through a lot worse
than this.
Once Oliver was stable,
Diggle and Felicity
addressed the obvious.
I was thinking all this
would be more of a shock.
Oliver brought me a laptop
riddled with bullet holes,
had me trace the black arrow,
and research a company involved
in armored car heists.
I maybe blonde,
but I'm not that blonde.
(Monitor beeping steadily)
I guess I didn't die. Again.
Cool.
Felicity was officially
part of the team.
The Glades is a notoriously
rough side of Starling City...
Hey!
Known as a breeding ground
for all manner of criminal.
(Scoffs)
(Thea) I found the dirtbag.
His name is Roy Harper.
(Knocks on door)
(Roy) How'd you know
where I lived?
A little thing called
the Internet.
Thea Queen was not
a cooperative victim.
You know, you showed
some real sac coming down here,
the Glades in the middle
of the night...
You must not know the value
of a vintage purse.
Hey, can I give you
some advice?
Stay out of the Glades.
As it turns out,
Roy's advice was sound.
Where's downtown at?
I-I-I don't know.
Maybe you can give us
some directions.
Or better yet, some money.
(Panting) Ow.
You're bleeding!
Yeah, I know.
That's what happens
when you get stabbed.
(Man)
This could sting a little.
Oh, don't tell me
a tough gangbanger like yourself
is afraid of
a tiny little needle.
Well, just think about
something else.
Like what? (Inhales sharply)
Thea was charmed
by Roy's bravery...
(Roy)
I was waiting for this.
Waiting for what?
But not by his life
as a petty crook.
This is home, sweet home
for me.
You either starve
or you do things
that mean you're lucky enough
to make it to 21.
(Man) Roy Harper?
Yeah?
Uhh!
Roy!
A deranged vigilante
called the Savior
looked to make an example
of Roy.
More on the story
out of the Glades.
The kidnapper seems to have
another victim.
You know him?
Uh, Roy. He's my friend. (Sniffles)
I promise you
he's gonna be okay.
Felicity, show me a map...
(Taps key)
Of sites of the abductions
and where we've seen the signal
so far. (Typing)
Diggle and Felicity traced
Savior's location
to Starling City's
abandoned subway.
Don't do it!
After Oliver rescued him,
Roy reconsidered
his life's purpose.
(Roy) I thought
I was gonna die.
But you didn't.
Yeah, because of him.
I can't go back to the way
things were, Thea.
I c-can't just go back
to being nothing.
I can't explain it,
but it feels like my life is
connected to his.
The incident provided clarity
for Oliver as well.
I've seen that map before.
It's an old map of
a decommissioned subway line.
It runs underneath the low-rent
district of the city.
(Oliver) It was right in front
of our faces the entire time.
My father, the other archer,
the Undertaking...
Whatever the plan is, it's all
connected to the Glades.
(Malcolm) The Undertaking,
which we set for ourselves,
is only months from fruition.
There's hope on the horizon
for everyone in Starling.
(Chuckles)
We won't fail this city.
And I think I speak
for everyone here
when I say we're all with you,
Malcolm.
But privately,
Moira had misgivings...
I wanna get out.
That's, uh, a lot to confide
in me, Moira.
As did a colleague.
I've gone along with this
for as long as I can stomach.
Frank Chen recommended you.
He said you could help us
with our problem.
How can we be of assistance?
Malcolm Merlyn.
I want you to kill him
for me.
(Malcolm, amplified voice)
The true humanitarian
in the Merlyn family
was my wife Rebecca.
I like to think that if the man
who murdered her knew her,
he would've helped her to
her car, made sure she was safe,
instead of stealing her purse
and shooting her.
(Beep, alarm blaring)
(Smack) Ladies and gentlemen,
please exit calmly...
Malcolm Merlyn was not
an easy target.
Tommy.
Come with me.
He would not go down
without a fight...
A fact that took his son
by surprise.
Wait!
Let's go!
How did you know
how to do that?
What?
Kill.
(Explosion)
(Rapid gunfire)
Dad!
(Gasping)
Oliver arrived in time.
Stay back.
I'm not here to hurt you
or your father.
I said stay back.
If you don't let me
help you now,
he's dead before
anybody gets here!
Why should I trust you?!
But there was no time left
for secrets.
'Cause you always have.
Oliver.
(Gasps and groans)
Dad. Oh.
Take it easy.
Thanks to Oliver...
The Vigilante saved you.
He did?
Malcolm Merlyn was alive.
But thanking him wasn't
foremost in Tommy's mind.
I know you have
a lot of questions.
Yeah.
(Inhales deeply)
Yeah, but for now,
just the one.
Were you ever gonna
tell me?
No.
Tommy's distrust of Oliver
quickly grew to include Laurel.
When you first got home,
I didn't think that you had
changed much.
But you have, and...
It's nice to see.
(Whispers) Thank you.
(Thunderclap)
You still love her,
don't you?
It doesn't matter how I feel,
because of what I do,
I could never be with her.
So you don't have anything
to be afraid of.
She is never...
ever going to know
my secret.
It doesn't matter.
She knows.
I know.
But if she ever found out
who you really are...
She would choose you.
(Laurel whispering)
You can't be serious.
I'm not sure that I'm ready
for the kind of commitment
that you're looking for.
And I don't want to hurt you
in the long run, so--
(voice breaks) You're lying.
I am not a liar.
If you've changed,
and I know that you've changed,
you would never do this.
Well, then I guess
I haven't changed as much
as we all thought then.
And Tommy's rejection...
Will you please
go talk to Tommy for me?
Produced
a self-fulfilling prophecy.
And say what?
Say that
you and I are over,
that you're not
still in love with me.
I can't do that.
Why not?
Because it wouldn't be true.
(Moira)
Thank you for coming, Frank.
Merlyn's survival forced Moira
to cover her tracks.
Malcolm knows.
(Whispers) What?
I had no choice
but to turn over what
they've discovered... (Exhales deeply)
The money that you paid
the Triad to assassinate him.
(Arrow whooshes) The money I--
(Inhales sharply)
Moira!
Mr. Merlyn thanks you
for your loyalty.
Moira's paranoia
began to boil over...
(Sobs)
You lied to me.
We had a deal!
And so did she.
You promised if I cooperated
with the Undertaking,
Walter wouldn't be harmed!
He hasn't been.
I'm a man of my word, Moira.
I think we both know better
than that.
Turn on the camera.
Oh, Walter.
Like you said, Moira,
we have an agreement.
Walter would stay
in my custody
until the Undertaking
was complete.
We're both in this together.
And Oliver learned
the startling truth
about his mother.
She's working with
Malcolm Merlyn.
And they're
planning something.
Something...
Terrible.
Hey, mom.
After uncovering
his mother's involvement
with Merlyn's plot,
Oliver confronted her
yet again.
Tell me the truth.
I don't know what you mean.
I think you do.
Couple of months ago, when
I showed you Dad's notebook,
you seemed to know
something.
When she continued
to be evasive...
You need to stop asking
these things.
I can't.
I need to know.
(Electricity powers down)
Oliver used
more drastic measures.
(Dart whooshes)
Oh.
Oliver.
(Dart whooshes)
Ohh.
(Breathes heavily)
Moira Queen,
you have failed this city.
Please, do not hurt my son.
Tell me what the Undertaking is,
and I won't have to.
(Moira) No! (Gasps)
Uhh!
No!
Malcolm is planning
to level the Glades!
How?
There's a device.
He says that it could cause
an earthquake.
Why would you get involved
in something like this?
My husband.
He was lost. He...
His decisions left me
vulnerable to Malcolm.
And I had no choice.
I had to protect my family
and my children.
This device, where is it?
I don't know.
If you don't tell me,
I can't stop Merlyn.
Oh, you can't stop him.
It's too late.
Finally, Oliver understood
his true mission.
It's the Undertaking.
I was just treating the symptoms
while the disease festered.
I stop the Undertaking,
I wipe out the disease.
Merlyn's plan is what I returned
from the island to stop.
For the past five years,
under the threat for my life
and the lives of my family...
Moira finally decided
to come clean.
I have been complicit
in an undertaking
with one horrible purpose--
to destroy the Glades
and everyone in it.
The architect of this nightmare
is Malcolm Merlyn.
(Screams)
Yes, and I have proof
that he has killed dozens
in pursuit of this madness.
Is it true?
Did you kill all those people?
I did what I had to do.
Malcolm Merlyn,
you are under arrest!
Don't move!
Dad, no!
Stay back.
I don't wanna hurt you.
You can't,
and you can't stop me.
This red line here
is a known fault that runs
right below the Glades.
For about a mile,
the fault runs underneath
the old
10th Street subway line.
Dollars to doughnuts,
the seismic device is
somewhere along there.
(Cell phone chimes and buzzes)
I know were Merlyn is
keeping the device.
I need someone I can trust
to deactivate the device.
(Sirens wailing)
(Man on TV) Earlier today,
Moira Queen, C.E.O. of...
News of the impending disaster
had already reached the Glades.
As Detective Lance searched
for the device...
(Man on TV
speaking indistinctly)
Everyone prepared
for the worst.
(Man, amplified voice)
Proceed out of the Glades
in an orderly manner.
Oliver and Diggle moved in
to take Merlyn down.
Welcome, gentlemen.
I've been waiting for you.
I wanted to see you watch
your city die.
Uhh! Aah!
Aah!
(Beeping)
(Gasps)
(Felicity)
You should see something
that looks like a circuit board.
Okay.
Felicity talked Detective Lance
through disarming the weapon...
Do you see a timer?
(Continues beeping)
7 minutes.
Okay.
While Oliver battled
to stop its damage.
Cut the blue one.
All right, I got it. I got it.
(Snips)
Oh!
(Whirring)
(Beeping resumes)
Holy God.
(Tires screech)
Roy!
Thea tracked down Roy Harper...
Roy, stop! Look!
(People screaming at once)
The device is about to go off
any second!
But she couldn't persuade him
to abandon his home.
I leave any of them behind.
Look, I-I know you said
you have something to prove,
but you're not the vigilante.
I can't do this unless
I know you're safe.
Then you better haul ass
out of here, too.
With chaos erupting everywhere,
Oliver had one final chance to
prevent complete destruction.
Don't struggle.
It's over.
Don't worry.
Your mother and sister will
be joining you in death. (Groans)
Aah!
(Groaning)
(Beeping continues)
(Powers down)
(Felicity)
Oliver, Lance did it.
It's over.
If I've learned anything
as a successful businessman,
it's... (Exhales sharply)
(Coughs)
Redundancy.
(Groans)
(Electricity humming)
(Oliver) There's another device.
There's two of them.
(Explosion)
Oliver Queen came back to right
his father's wrongs.
He couldn't have imagined
how severe they were.
(Laurel) Go. Go!
Uhh! Aah!
He returned to a city
suffocated by corruption
and violence...
Laurel!
The damage seems to be
contained
on the east side.
Laurel.
Go. Go, go, go.
And he fought
to make it better...
Please! Help me!
To make the people around him
better.
(Strained voice) Tommy.
What are you doing here?
I love you.
True heroism is defined
by sacrifice...
(Grunts) Go! Go!
I'm right behind you!
Dad!
And real heroes...
No!
No, Laurel!
Are the ones
who give up the most.
Come on. It's too late!
It's too late. (Sobbing)
(Speaks indistinctly)
Tommy.
(Whispering)
Is--is Laurel safe?
Is Laurel safe?
Yeah. You saved her.
I'm--I'm sorry.
(Voice breaks) No.
Don't apologize.
And--no.
Tommy. (Crying)
After the tragedy
in the Glades,
we must wonder...
(Whispers) Open your eyes.
What will Oliver Queen
become now?
Something else yet again?
Perhaps something...
Better.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man