NO TIME
You're making a sausage
out of your eye?
A crazy person!
A mishugina!
- It's our city hall.
- Ooh ooh ooh ooh...
Ooh ooh ooh ooh....
This is a movie! This is
the universal sign for a movie!
- Oh, it's a movie.
- It's a movie.
I need a mircale.
Who's got my extra ticket.
Redrum. Redrum.
- Trade your Friday for Saturday.
- Redrum.
Oh, a crazy person pointing!
You're pointer!
Where is pointer?
Here I am.
Heroin!
It's Mr. T.
Mr. T and D.C. Cab.
Oh you're a crazy person chomping!
You got a horn on your head...
Hornhead!
Hornhead! Hornhead!
Ooh ooh ooh ooh...
Your sideburns.
George Burns.
The Sunshine Boys.
A crazy person with sideburns!
Roadhouse!
It's Karen Carpenter!
A crazy person eating their fingers!
Roadhouse!
Jeffrey Dahmer!
Oh, a crazy person
touching their teeth!
Charles Manson!
Roadhouse!
A crazy Yul Brynner!
It's not Roadhouse!
It's Jaws!
It's a movie about a shark!
Jaws!
Dude, you're not supposed to talk.
Somebody else do one!
Alright, I've got one.
- Gone with the wind!
- Yes!
Eww!
Eww...
I got 08.
I got 06 yesterday.
Billy stole the cookie
from the cookie jar?
- Who me?
- Yeah you!
- Couldn't be.
- Then who?!
Rob stole the cookie
from the cookie jar.
Who me?
Yeah you.
Couldn't be!
Then who?
Billy stole the cookie
from the cookie jar.
- Who me?
- Yeah you!
- Couldn't be!
- Then who?
Rob stole the cookie
from the cookie jar!
- Who me?
- Yeah you!
- Couldn't be!
- Then who?
Billy stole the cookie
from the cookie jar.
- Who me?
- Yeah you!
- Couldn't be.
- Then who?
Rob stole the cookie
from the cookie jar!
- Who me?   - Yeah you!
- Couldn't be!   - Then who?
Billy stole the cookie
from the cookie jar!
- Who me?   - Yeah you!
- Couldn't be!   - Then who?
We've got to get the TV fixed.
Oh Steven, I had such
a wonderful time tonight!
I'm so glad you didn't get upset
when I asked the waiter my fish...
...but there was a hair in it! Did you
see the hair? - Yeah I saw the hair.
It was all long and black and shiny.
It was like a horse hair.
I think it really might have been a
horse hair. - Yeah it might have been.
Listen I had a great time tonight
Elissa, but I really gotta get going.
Wait! Don't you want to come inside
and see my kitty Noodles?
Don't you remember I told you
about her? Oh Noodles is so cute...
...Noodles goes 'Meow meow meow'
Yeah I'd love to but I've gotta to go
meet some friends of mine that...
...are coming in from out of town.
Oh I have a couple sorority sisters
coming down...
- ...we can go on like a triple date.
- Umm, these guys have got scurvy.
- So it's probably not a good idea.
- Oh Steven wait!
Steven don't you want to give me
a kiss goodnight before you go home?
I mean that's how you end a date
officially you know.
I mean not officially, it's not in any
book but, you would lean in and-
I'd love to but this might be a
contagious strain of scurvy...
- ...so it's probably not a good idea.
- But wait!
Can I just ask you one question
before you go? - Yeah sure.
Is there something wrong with your
eye? Because all night when...
...I've been talking to you, one eyes
been looking at me, but one eyes...
...been looking away and I don't know
which one to talk to.
Do you know what I mean?
It's kind of unnerving.
Yeah it's not big deal really
I just have a glass eye.
- You have a glass eye?!
- Yeah.   - I have a glass eye!
Oh my god this is incredible!
It happened when I was a little girl...
...and my mother always told me
never to play dress-up in her closet...
...but I did and I put on one of her
big hats and that hat came down and...
...struck me through the eyeball.
But that's not the worst part!
My little brother picked up
the hat with the eyeball on it...
...ran around the house
screaming 'Barbeque Barbeque'.
It was awful.
How did you lose your eye?
- It was a lawn dart. I gotta get going.
- Oh wait! Steven wait!
Steven I feel so close to you now.
Can I see your eye?
- Will you take it out? - Well listen,
I don't like to take it out because of...
- ...get germs on it. Well
it's just an eye. - Oh please!
Steven it's not just an eye, it's your
eye and that's why I want to see it.
- Please Steven it would be
so much to me. - Okay fine but...
- ...then I gotta go. Okay?
- Okay.
You carry your patch with you? So do I.
Ever since I was in 4th grade...
I sneezed, my eyeball flew out and hit
the kids head in front of me.
Oh it was  just awful! The kids called
me sneeze eye all year!
Oh my god. Steven,
this is the same color as my eye!
- I'm gonna take my eye out and compare
them. - No no Elissa please don't...
...don't take out your eye. I've seen
eyes before it's not big deal.
Oh my god! There the same color!
Steven, there the same eye!
Can I just have my eye back please?
Oh I have a great idea!
- Let me try your eye on. Here hold
my eye. - No no Elissa don't...
...put that in, it's got
scurvey on it. Elissa!
Oh my god!
It's a perfect fit!
I'm like looking at the world
through Steven's point of view!
Oh my god it's incredible! Steven,
put my eye in your socket...
...and then we'll be like
blood brothers forever.
Elissa, I don't want to put your eye in
I want my eye back now.
Oh c'mon Steven, it will be
so much fun. Please!
Elissa, take my eye out and
give it back to me, now.
Oh you never know until you try.
Just like when I was in summer camp...
...and my counselor told me don't
get into the canoe and-
Look you stupid whore, would you just
shutup and give me my eye back!
If you don't give me my eye back,
I'm gonna take your eye...
- ...and I'm gonna throw it out
the window!   - Don't be silly.
- Give me back my eye!
- No stop being mean.
My eye!
I'm gonna suck that eye out of your
head like it was a freaking olive!
Oh my god, you're choking on my eye!
You're choking on my eye!
Oh my god! Steven! Steven!
Oh my god, I'm so sorry!
- Are you alright?
- I'm alright.
It's just when that eye flew out of my
mouth I think it chipped my dentures.
You wear dentures?! Oh!
White.
Cracker.
Can't play. Can't dribble.
Can't shoot.
Honkey.
Play hockey. Play hockey.
Play hockey. Play hockey...
Good morning.
C'mon fish!
C'mon fisherman.
- C'mon fish!
- Excuse me.
Over here.
If you yell loud like that,
you're gonna scare all the fish away
Where are they gonna go?
C'mon fish.
C'mon fisherman!
Fishy fishy fishy fish.
C'mon fish.
Come come come come
c'mon fish!
Fish. Fish. Fish.
Fish. Fish. Fish. Fish. Fish.
Fish. Fish. Fish. Fish.
Anchor. Anchor fish. Anchor. Anchor.
Anchor fish. Ugh Anchor. Anchor fish.
Anchor. Anchor fish.
Anchor fish.
Look you took my spot alright.
Switch places with me, I was here first.
C'mon fish.
C'mon fish. C'mon fish.
C'mon fish!
Fishy fishy fishy fish.
Su madre pessay!
Fish. Fish. Fish. Fish.
Fish. Fish. Fish.
Fish. Fish. Fish. Fish. Fish.
C'mon fish.
C'mon fish!
Fish. Fish. Fish. Fish. Fish.
Fish. Fish. Fish.
C'mon fish!
C'mon fish.
C'mon fisherman.
- Fishy fishy fishy fish.
- Su madre pessay!
C'mon fish.
- Fish. Fish.
- Fish! Fish!
C'mon fisherman! Su madre pessay!
F-f-f-fish!
C-c-c-c-c-c-c'mon fish!
Fish! Fish!
- Fish. Fish.
- Fish. Fish. Fish
Fish. Fish.
Fish.
C'mon fish.
- C'mon fish!
- Good morning.
Ow.
Peanut butter mustache!
Grape jelly eyebrow.
Peanut butter goatee.
Grape jelly sideburns.
Peanut butter noseplugs!
Grape jelly toupee.
Put the bread, on your head!
Wonderbread! On our head!
We are a sandwich. Olay!