ALL RIGHT NOW GENTLEMAN, BRING
ME UP TO SPEED ON YOUR MEETING
WITH HALLSWELL'S
PEOPLE THIS MORNING.
SENATOR, WE'RE GOING TO HAVE TO
MOVE FAST TO GATHER THE SUPPORT
WE NEED.
SENATOR HALLSWELL IS DETERMINED
TO REIGN ALL THOSE REGIONS IN
THE MIDEAST.
IF WE'VE LEARNED ANYTHING IN THE
PAST 50 YEARS, IT IS THAT EVERY
GUN, LOCKET AND TANK WE SELL
WILL EVENTUALLY BE USED AGAINST
US.
SCREW HALLSWELL.
WE HAVE ENOUGH SUPPORT TO GET BY
HIM AND THE VICE PRESIDENT HAS
BEEN MAKING CALLS.
THAT IS WHAT I'M AFRAID OF.
SON, YOU FORGOT MY GLASS.
EXCUSE ME.
LISTEN RICHARD, YOU CAN THINK
WHATEVER YOU WANT OF THIS GUY.
BUT JUST REMEMBER HE'S GOT A
LOT OF FRIENDS IN THIS TOWN.
YEAH, AND MOST OF
THEM DEMOCRATS.
THAT'S FUNNY.
DID YOU HEAR THEY'RE MAKING A
MOVIE ABOUT DAN QUAIL'S MILITARY
CAREER?
IT'S CALLED FULL DINNER JACKET.
SENATOR?
JUST A HOT FLASH.
ARE YOU OKAY?
SENATOR!
JESUS HE IS HAVING A SEIZURE.
CALL THE PARAMEDICS!
I KNOW CPR.
AMAZING, IT IS
EXACTLY WHAT WE NEED.
AND YOU SHALL HAVE IT ALRED.
YOU SHALL HAVE IT.
WELL, FOR THE DOG DAYS,
IT'S ANOTHER BEAUTIFUL DAY
IN THE CAPITAL CITY.
IT'S HOT.
AND WE'VE JUST BEEN INFORMED
THAT POLICE HAVE COMPLETELY SHUT
DOWN ALL LANES ON THE WHITEHURST
FREEWAY BETWEEN PENNSYLVANIA AND
THE 3RD STREET EXIT.
WE ARE TOLD THAT IT IS
SOME SORT OF BOMB SCARE.
EMERGENCY VEHICLES ARE ON THE
SCENE AND AS YOU MAY IMAGINE,
TRAFFIC IS ALREADY BACKED
UP ALL THE WAY TO VIRGINIA.
THIS IS WNLC AND I'M
TERRY IN THE MORNING.
WE'LL KEEP YOU POSTED FOR
ANY FURTHER DEVELOPMENTS.
AM I GOING TO?
DIE?
YES.
I MEAN TODAY.
WE'VE GOT ONE ECCENTRIC HUSBAND.
DO YOU BELIEVE THIS?
HAVE ONE LITTLE AFFAIR..
AND THIS IS WHAT HE DOES.
HOW DOES IT LOOK?
YOUR HUSBAND CERTAINLY
KNOWS WHAT HE'S DOING.
WHICH COLOR DO YOU PREFER?
RED OR GREEN?
WHAT?
RED OR GREEN.
GREEN.
NO, WAIT, WAIT, WAIT.
RED.
TOO LATE IT'S GREEN.
OH GOD...
GIMME YOUR GUM QUICK.
YOUR GUM!
I GOT AN IDEA.
YOU'RE CHEATING ON YOUR HUSBAND.
PUT ON SOME UNDERWEAR.
¶.
NICE JOB EDDIE.
WAY TO DO DAN.
WHAT YOU THOUGHT MY BECOMING
A FED WOULD CHANGE ANYTHING?
I WAS HOPING.
WHAT'S THAT?
YOU EVER SEEN THIS?
WHAT'S THIS YOUR LUCKY CHARM?
NO...
I JUST LIKE TAPING
PICTURES TO MY CHEST.
ARE YOU DANNY O'NEIL?
THAT'S RIGHT, WHY?
DOES THIS HAVE SOMETHING TO
DO WITH THE EDWARDS MCMAHON
SWEEPSTAKES OR SOMETHING?
IT'S A RESTRAINING ORDER TO
KEEP YOU AWAY FROM YOUR WIFE.
HAVE A NICE DAY.
THIS IS A SECURED AREA.
NO ONE!
NO ONE IS ALLOWED IN HERE.
SORRY ABOUT THIS DAN.
THERE WAS A DETONATION AT
A RESTAURANT ON DELAWARE.
THEY SENT IN A COPTER FOR YOU.
OH MAN, LOVE MONDAYS.
MOBILE CAPTAIN
61 THIS IS CHOPPER 14.
WE'RE BRINGING YOUR MAN IN.
YOU GUT A PLACE FOR US
TO LAND OVER THERE, OVER?
ROGER, THIS IS 61
WE'RE AT 5TH AND DELAWARE.
LAND IN FRONT OF
THE TRACKS, OVER.
I COPY THAT OVER.
YOU GOT ABOUT
FIVE PEOPLE WITH...
WHAT'S THIS WRAPPING CERAMING.
BONE.
HAVE FUN IN THERE DANNY.
FIDELITY
INSURANCE STRIKES AGAIN.
WELL DANNY O'NEILL.
YOU GUYS ARE GOING TO BE
PAYING OUT BIG TIME ON THIS ONE.
TELL ME ABOUT IT.
FOUR DEATHS AND 15 INJURIES.
MAYBE IS WAS A GAS LEAK?
WELL IF IT WAS A GAS LEAK,
SOMEBODY HAS SERIOUS GAS
PROBLEMS.
DID YOU REALLY TRY AND THROW
TRAVERES OFF THE BALCONY AT YOUR
HOUSE.
I COULDN'T GET HIS
FAT ASS OVER THE RAIL.
I JUST WANT YOU TO KNOW HOW
SORRY I AM ABOUT YOU AND YOUR
WIFE.
HOW COME EVERYBODY
KNOWS ABOUT THIS?
I MEAN WAS THIS ON
CNN OR SOMETHING?
I KNOW EVERYTHING THAT GOES ON
IN THIS TOWN DANNY, YOU KNOW
THAT.
REALLY?
WHAT ABOUT SENATOR WILKINS?
THE PINK PANTIES IN THE DESK.
SEE YA.
YOU'RE BAD.
SHANE!
WILL YOU GET THIS HORNY
CAN OF TUNA AWAY FROM ME?
WHAT CAN I SAY DAN?
MADONNA WANTS YOU.
GO!
I'M NOT DOING IT DAN, I SWEAR.
I DON'T KNOW WHY SHE
REACTS TO YOU THAT WAY?
WELL YOU MUST NOT BE
TREATING HER RIGHT.
PICK YOURSELF UP A CAN OF
WD40 AND GO TO TOWN WITH IT.
JAMES IS LOOKING FOR YOU.
WHERE IS HE?
RIGHT BEHIND YOU.
JAMES, JAMES.
TERRORIST ATTACK
IT LOOKS LIKE HUH?
WHERE'S THE DEVICE?
CAN'T FIND IT.
EXCUSE ME?
THEY SAY THAT SENATOR VICTOR
HAD A SEIZURE AND THEN BOOM.
BOOM?
YOU MEAN HE
SPONTANEOUSLY COMBUSTED?
YOU TELL ME.
OKAY WHAT DO YOU KNOW GUYS?
NOTHING.
NO METAL, PLASTIC
OR CHEMICAL RESIDUE.
C'MON WHAT IS THIS GUYS YOUR
FIRST DAY ON THE JOB, KEEP
DIGGING.
PEOPLE DON'T JUST EXPLODE.
I MEAN IF THEY DID, I WOULD HAVE
HEARD ABOUT IT A LONG TIME AGO.
WHAT DO WE GOT HERE?
JESUS.
SHANE, LOOK AT THIS.
LOOKS LIKE THE FINGERS
HAVE BEEN BLOWN RIGHT OFF.
EITHER THAT OR HE
SHOULD FIRE IS MANICURIST.
TERRY, WHAT I'M SAYING
IS THAT I SUPPORT YOU.
I JUST WANT YOU TO BE HAPPY.
AND WITH DAN, UNTIL
RECENTLY YOU WERE SO UNHAPPY.
THIS ISN'T ABOUT ME.
I KNOW.
I THINK SENATOR
TRAVERES IS GOOD FOR YOU.
YOU JUST SEEM HAPPIER WITH HIM.
MOM...
FRANK AND I ARE FRIENDS.
HI HONEY, I'M HOME.
TERRY, I'LL CALL THE POLICE IF YOU WANT.
- NO, MOM
HI MOM.
GOOD TO SEE YOU.
LISTEN, YOU'RE STILL MY WIFE
AND THIS IS STILL MY HOUSE.
COURT ORDERS HMMM?
AND THIS IS STILL
MY GARBAGE PAIL.
DANNY, I'VE BEEN THOUGH THIS TOO
MANY TIMES BEFORE AND I'M SICK
OF GETTING HURT.
I'M ALWAYS THE
ONE WHO GETS HURT.
LISTEN, HOW ABOUT THE ONE
THAT IS SEEING OTHER PEOPLE?
FRANK TRAVERES IS NOT
THE PROBLEM WITH US.
I THINK MOST PEOPLE IN
WASHINGTON, D.C WOULD DISAGREE
WITH THAT.
MOM, COULD YOU DO SOMETHING?
THANKS MOM.
FRANK AND I WORK TOGETHER.
WE GOT TO BE FRIENDS.
I CAN'T LIVE WITH YOU ANYMORE.
NOT SINCE...
C'MON SAY IT FOR GOD'S SAKE.
IT WAS AN ACCIDENT.
OH GOD..
MANDY?
DADDY WHEN
ARE YOU GOING TO BE UP?
IN A MINUTE SWEET PEA.
PLEASE, OKAY.
C'MON DADDY CAN WE PLAY?
AMANDA, PLEASE JUST GO TO
YOUR ROOM, OKAY DARLING.
GO TO YOUR ROOM AND I'LL BE THERE.
- OKAY
OH JESUS CHRIST NO!
DON'T' PLEASE
BREATHE, PLEASE BREATHE.
HOW'S THE TEMPERATURE?
76 DEGREES, PERFECT.
DR BERNARD?
OH MIKAIL.
HOW DO YOU LIKE YOUR NEW JOB?
IT'S FINE.
GOOD.
MIKAIL, JUST
HEARD IT ON THE NEWS.
NOW YOU HAVE THE PROOF YOU
WANTED SO WHEN DO I GET PAID?
I'VE GIVEN YOU THE FORMULA
NOW I WHAT ABOUT MY MONEY?
WHAT MONEY?
WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
JUST KIDDING.
PATIENCE DR BERNARD, PATIENCE.
YES, BUT YOU ARE NOT PATIENT
WHEN YOU WANTED THE FORMULA.
YOU KNOW YOU'RE
ABSOLUTELY RIGHT.
I'LL TELL YOU WHAT, I'LL
GIVE YOU A CHECK RIGHT NOW.
DO YOU HAVE A PEN?
YES, OF COURSE, THANK YOU.
I'LL BE OUT OF YOUR WAY SOON.
YES!
THAT FOOL WAS RIGHT, IT IS
COMPLETELY UNDETECTABLE.
WITH THE POWER THIS FORMULA CAN
GIVE US, NOTHING WILL STAND IN
OUR WAY, NOTHING.
SOMETIMES I WONDER.
WHAT IS IT ALL FOR?
REALLY?
NO...
HMMM...
AND WE'LL SET THE PRESS
CONFERENCE FOR FIRST THING
TOMORROW MORNING.
YEAH, I WANT SOMETHING PREPARED.
SOMETHING UM,
SOMETHING EMOTIONAL.
SENATOR VICTOR WAS A FRIEND.
I CAN'T BELIEVE THIS HAPPENED.
REMEMBER EMOTION, FEELING.
YEAH.
I THINK WE BOTH KNOW
JUST HOW SERIOUS I AM NOW.
UH, SENATOR VICTOR'S WIFE, JUST
LET ME TAKE THIS IN PRIVATE.
YOU GOT BALLS CALLING ME HERE.
AND YOU DISPLAYED YOURS WHEN
YOU CUT ME OUT OF 10 MILLION
DOLLARS.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT
YOU'RE TALKING ABOUT.
WELL LET ME REFRESH YOUR MEMORY.
THE ARMS SALE.
I DON'T HAVE YOUR MONEY.
DO YOU KNOW THAT'S
WHAT VICTOR SAID.
AND LOOK WHAT HAPPENED TO HIM.
VICTOR WAS RESPONSIBLE FOR
CUTTING YOU OUT OF THE DEAL.
YOU GOT YOU'RE RETRIBUTION.
YES, BUT YOU CAN'T BUY
ITALIAN VILLAS WITH RETRIBUTION.
I DON'T HAVE YOUR MONEY.
DO YOU KNOW WHAT IS
STOPPING ME GOING PUBLIC?
MANNERS.
I CAN MAKE SURE THAT
YOU NEVER GET TO ME.
NOBODY WILL BELIEVE
ANYTHING THAT YOU SAY ANYWAY.
I CAN SEE THAT YOU
HANG FOR KILLING VICTOR.
NO DAMN IT, I'M WARNING YOU.
NO MATTER WHO YOU PUT AROUND
YOU, OR HOW MANY PRECAUTIONS YOU
TAKE, YOU'RE A DEAD MAN.
I COULD GET TO YOU
WHEREVER AND WHENEVER I WANT.
AND I SHALL ENJOY DOING IT.
OKAY, NOW.
WHAT DOES R2D2 THINK?
STONE RAT.
DISHES.
GREAT, OKAY SO
HOW DID THEY DO IT?
I BEEN DOING THIS
FOR 10 YEARS DAN.
I'VE ALWAYS FOUND SOMETHING BUT
WE CANNOT FIND ANYTHING MAN, I
DON'T KNOW, WHAT THE HELL.
VICTOR WAS HERE, HAD A
SEIZURE FELL THIS WAY.
THEN WHATEVER IT WAS EXPLODED
UNDER HIM OR AROUND HIM.
IT DOESN'T MAKE ANY SENSE.
IT DOES IF HE HAD A
PACEMAKER MADE OF PLASTIQUE.
GENTLEMAN WHAT YOU GOT?
WELL UH, MADONNA AND I HAVE
ANALYZED THREE QUARTERS OF THIS
MATERIAL AND THERE IS ABSOLUTELY
NO TRACE OF ANY KIND OF
EXPLOSIVE OR FRAGMENTS FROM A
DETONATING DEVICE, NOTHING.
WE'RE MAKING A LOT OF HEADWAY.
DANNY, I WANT TO TALK WITH
YOU OUTSIDE JUST FOR A MINUTE
PLEASE.
YOU'RE NOT SUPPOSED TO BE
DIFFUSING EXPLOSIVES FOR METRO
ANYMORE, YOU KNOW
THAT DON'T YOU?
KEEPS ME IN PRACTICE.
SOME PEOPLE PLAY GOLF,
SOME PEOPLE PLAY TENNIS.
I DIFFUSE HIGH EXPLOSIVES.
YOU'RE WORKING FOR ME NOW DANNY
AND WE DON'T DO THE DIRTY WORK
WE LEAVE THAT FOR METRO.
I'M NOT AN AFTER
THE FACT KIND OF GUY.
C'MON, YOU'VE PAID YOUR DUES.
FBI IS A PROMOTION.
IT MAY NOT FEEL
LIKE IT BUT IT IS ONE.
SO I DON'T THINK YOU OUGHT
TO TAKE ANYMORE UNNECESSARY
CHANCES.
I CAN HANDLE MYSELF.
I KNOW THAT.
BUT I'M A BIT WORRIED ABOUT
YOU DAN WITH MANDY AND NOW WITH
TERRY.
JESUS...
YOU KNOW IT'S REALLY TOO BAD
MORE PEOPLE DON'T KNOW ABOUT MY
MARITAL PROBLEMS.
THIS IS ME TALKING TO YOU.
IT'S COMING FROM ME.
I'M FINE.
IN EVERY WAY I'M FINE.
I'M NOT LOSING IT.
JUST LET METRO DO THEIR WORK.
¶ ¶
HOLD IT RIGHT HERE SIR PLEASE.
OKAY.
SIGN IN SIR.
DOUBLE ON SECURITY TODAY?
WE'VE BEEN ON BLUE ALERT
SINCE SENATOR VICTOR'S DEATH.
SPEAKING OF WHICH I HAVE AN
APPOINTMENT IN HIS OFFICE.
4TH FLOOR TO YOUR RIGHT, 407.
THANK YOU.
WIFE.
EXCUSE ME, MA'AM.
SO NEXT TIME YOU GO
SPREADING RUMORS ABOUT MY WIFE.
CHECK THE FACTS WITH ME FIRST.
YES SIR.
MIRA, THANK YOU.
WAY TO GO STU.
MAN'S NOT DEAD A DAY AND THEY'RE
ALREADY MOVING SOMEONE ELSE INTO
HIS OFFICE.
THAT'S NOT TRUE.
HE WAS DEAD A DAY.
THEY SHOULD USE THE VULTURE.
HI JAMES.
TERRY.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?
I UH, WE HAVE BUSINESS.
LISTEN, UH.
I'M SORRY.
I'M SORRY ABOUT THE
OTHER DAY, I DIDN'T THINK.
I'M SORRY.
YOU LOOK GREAT.
YOU WANT TO GO AND HAVE SOME
LUNCH, MAYBE SOMETHING LIKE
THAT?
UH, I CAN'T I'VE GOT MEETINGS.
I GOT A MEETING TOO.
I GOTTA GO.
OKAY.
SORRY I'M LATE, SORRY.
I HOPE IT IS BECAUSE MADONNA HAS
COME UP WITH SOMETHING NEW.
NO, NO SHE'S RECHARGING.
WE'RE STILL PICKING UP PIECES OF
THE SENATOR.
THE GUYS HAVE NEVER
SEEN ANYTHING LIKE THIS.
WE'RE TALKING
PIECES, PIECES THIS SMALL.
I MEAN WE'RE TALKING
ABOUT HIS YOU KNOW WHAT.
GENTLEMAN, WE'RE READY FOR YOU.
HE HAD NOT
HAD TIME TO FILE THAT...
FINE WHY DON'T YOU JUST
READJUST HIS SCHEDULE.
TRAVERES...
MR. O'NEILL.
DID YOU KNOW ABOUT THIS?
I FOUND OUT THIS MORNING BUT
I DIDN'T THINK YOU WOULD COME.
I WOULD HAVE COME
WITH A BLOWTORCH.
SENATOR TRAVERES IS
HEADING UP THIS INVESTIGATION.
THAT'S RIGHT.
NOW I DON'T HAVE TO TELL YOU
THERE IS A LOT OF CONCERN UP ON
THE HILL ABOUT THIS.
A LOT OF PEOPLE ARE SCARED.
THERE ARE LOTS OF RUMORS.
YEAH, THERE ARE A LOT OF RUMORS.
HAVE YOU READ THE
REPORT SENATOR?
YES, I HAVE READ THE REPORT
EXCEPT I DON'T KNOW WHAT THE
HELL IT MEANS.
I MEAN WHAT DOES IT MEAN
THAT THERE IS NO TRACE OF A
DETONATING DEVICE.
WELL...
NO, NO, LET ME FIELD THIS ONE.
LOOK MR. O'NEILL I KNOW YOU
HAVE A PERSONAL PROBLEM WITH ME.
YOU AND MY WIFE?
THAT'S NOT A PERSONAL PROBLEM.
EVERYBODY IN THE GOD
DAMN CITY KNOWS ABOUT IT.
IT'S A VERY PUBLIC PROBLEM.
LOOK, I'M RESPONSIBLE FOR
DELIVERING ANSWERS TO CONGRESS.
UNTIL I HAVE THEM, I AM GOING TO
BE WATCHING EVERY STEP OF THIS
INVESTIGATION VERY CAREFULLY.
WELL THEN WATCH VERY CAREFULLY
AS I STEP OUT THE DOOR.
O'NEILL THIS IS BUSINESS.
NOW YOU BETTER LEARN TO SEPARATE
IT FROM THE OTHER PROBLEMS IN
YOUR LIFE.
YOU TOUCH MY WIFE AGAIN, I'LL
SEPARATE YOU FROM THE REST OF
YOUR LIFE.
YOU UNDERSTAND?
IF MR. O'NEILL IS THE BEST
EXPLOSIVE EXPERT WE HAVE
THE FBI IS IN PRETTY SAD SHAPE.
DAN IS THE BEST.
AND SHANE IS A TOP
MATERIAL ANALYST.
AND I'M NOT MARRIED SO I'VE
GOT NOTHING TO WORRY ABOUT, SIR.
WE'RE GOING TO GO OVER THAT SITE
AGAIN AND WE'LL KEEP ON GOING
OVER IT UNTIL WE
FIGURE THIS OUT.
I'LL HAVE SOMETHING
FOR YOU VERY SOON.
IS EVERYTHING ALL RIGHT?
I THINK TAKING VACATION
IS EXACTLY WHAT YOU NEED.
YOU'RE RIGHT.
GETTING AWAY WOULD BE GOOD.
WHO'S DRIVING?
SALVATORE SIR.
SALVATORE?
WHO THE HELL IS SALVATORE?
HE HAS BEEN DRIVING FOR US FOR
THE LAST THREE WEEKS SIR, IT'S
OKAY, REALLY.
HE'S LOSING IT.
GOOD AFTERNOON SIR.
I WANT THESE FILED BY THE
TIME I LEAVE FOR VACATION THIS
AFTERNOON.
YES, I'M CALLING TO CONFIRM
SENATOR THYME'S RESERVATION THIS
AFTERNOON.
GREAT, THANK YOU.
YOU'RE ALL SET SIR.
OH EDDIE.
ONCE THE FUNERAL IS OVER, I WANT
YOU TO ARRANGE A QUICK MEETING
WITH TRAVERES.
BUT YOUR PLANE BOARDS AT 4,
I'M AFRAID THERE IS NO TIME.
JUST MAKE THE TIME.
YES SIR.
WHY THE HELL IS IT
SO DAMN HOT IN HERE.
THE AIR CONDITIONER
SEEMS TO BE BROKEN.
I WILL TAKE CARE OF IT TOMORROW.
DAMN THING.
SALVATORE, WHAT THE HELL IS
WRONG WITH THE REFRIGERATOR.
I DON'T KNOW SIR, THE LIMO IS
SCHEDULED FOR MAINTENANCE BUT
THEY'RE BACKED UP.
ARE YOU TELLING ME THAT
NOTHING IS WORKING IN HERE?
WATER SIR?
NO, I DON'T WANT ANY WATER.
GIMME SOME POWER
ON THESE WINDOWS.
YES SIR.
OH AND DON'T MENTION
MY TRIP TO TRAVERES.
OH!
GOD!
MY EYES.
OH MY GOD.?
EDDIE?
SALVATORE CALL THE PARAMEDICS.
CALL AN AMBULANCE.
EDDIE!
HEY!
GET ME OUT OF HERE.
HEY WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
OH MY GOD!
THE SENATOR IS HAVING A SEIZURE.
QUICK!
PLEASE!
EDDIE!
MOBILE SIX, MOBILE SIX THIS IS
DISPATCH DO YOU READ, DO YOU
READ?
MOBILE SIX COME IN.
WHAT'S GOING ON THERE?
MOBILE SIX.
HE WORKS FOR YOU
AND HE WAS CAUGHT.
YOU DON'T KNOW MY MEN.
THEY HAVE A CODE OF SILENCE.
THEY'RE ABSOLUTELY LOYAL.
OH THAT'S TOUCHING.
REALLY!
I KNOW SAVIO, I CAN ASSURE...
ENOUGH.
KILL HIM.
LET ME GUESS, YOU
COULDN'T FIND A DEVICE.
THIS IS GETTING PRETTY HAIRY.
YOU ARE HERE FOR THE ARRAIGNMENT
THE ALLEGED BOMBER WHO KILLED
ONE OF YOUR CLOSEST
FRIENDS, WHAT ARE YOU FEELING?
WHAT AM I FEELING?
I FEEL RELIEF THAT
JUSTICE WILL BE SERVED.
ARE YOU STILL
PLANNING ON OPENING THE D.C.
KIDS CENTER ON SATURDAY?
ABSOLUTELY, THAT IS
VERY IMPORTANT TO ME.
THERE ARE THERE ARE HUNDREDS OF
KIDS FROM ALL OVER THE COUNTRY,
WE'VE RAISED $1000 OF DOLLARS.
I WOULDN'T DISAPPOINT THEM.
AREN'T YOU SCARED?
NO, I DON'T HAVE
TIME TO BE SCARED.
O'NEILL.
WHAT DO YOU HAVE FOR ME?
YOU?
NOW GET AWAY FROM ME, I DON'T
WANT ANY TERRORISTS MISTAKING US
FOR FRIENDS.
THE DRIVER IS STILL NOT TALKING.
I KNOW ALL ABOUT IT FRANK.
THAT STILL DOESN'T TELL US WHAT
HE USED OR WHO IS BEHIND IT.
LOOK, I KNOW YOU GUYS LIKE
CONSPIRACY THEORIES BUT IT IS
POSSIBLE HE ACTED
ALONE ISN'T IT?
UNLIKELY.
ESPECIALLY IF HE'S NOT TALKING.
THAT MEANS HE'S SCARED.
SO WHAT ARE YOU THINKING?
I'M THINKING I
GOTTA TAKE A PISS.
YOU WANT TO HELP ME OUT?
NO.
THAT'S GOOD.
OKAY, THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
MORNING.
I'M WITH SENATOR
TRAVERES WITH TWO FBI AGENTS.
MORNING SENATOR.
HOW ARE YOU DOING?
ALL RISE.
SUPERIOR COIRT DISTRICT OF
COLUMBIA IS NOW IN SESSION.
THE HONORABLE VERA
BLAIR PRESIDING.
PLEASE BE SEATED, COME TO ORDER.
GOOD MORNING.
ANY OUTBURST OR TALKING IN THE
COURT ROOM AND I WILL STOP THE
PROCEEDINGS.
HAVING SAID THAT,
THIS IS CASE 7487-4.
THE PEOPLE OF THE DISTRICT OF
COLUMBIA AGAINST SALVIO CAPELLI.
SINCE THE DEFENDANT DOES NOT
HAVE A LAWYER, THE COURT HAS
APPOINTED MR. LEWIS.
MR. LEWIS ARE YOU READY TO
ENTER A PLEA ON THE CHARGES OF...
MR. LEWIS.
ARE YOU READY TO ENTER A
PLEA ON THE CHARGES OF...
NO!
A PLEA ON THE...
GET THE SENATOR OUT
OF HERE RIGHT NOW.
RIGHT NOW MOVE.
MOVE OUT OF THE COURTROOM.
GIMME OUT, GIMME OUT OF HERE.
MOVE OUT!
OFFICER MOVE!
DON'T GO THERE,
DON'T, SHE'S GONNA BLOW!
I'VE NEVER SEEN
ANYTHING LIKE IT.
THERE WAS NOTHING.
NO DEVICE.
SHE WAS THE DEVICE.
SHE TOOK A DRINK OF
WATER, STARTED TO SPEAK.
STOOD UP AND THEN
STARTED CONVULSING.
THAT'S IT?
NO.
I LEFT OUT THE PART WHERE
SHE SWALLOWED A GRENADE.
SHE DRANK THE WATER, SWEAT,
SHOOK THEN BOOM, HERE COME THE
JUDGE.
THERE WAS NOTHING.
NOTHING BUT...
WHAT?
DO YOU THINK IT
COULD BE THE WATER?
WHOA.
OR IT WASN'T THE WATER AT ALL.
YOU OKAY?
MIKE, GET YOUR GUYS OUT OF
HERE, THIS IS THE EXPLOSIVE.
BEST BACK OFF DAN, WHATEVER
THIS IS, IT ISN'T WATER.
AREN'T YOU SCARED?
NO, I DON'T HAVE
TIME TO BE SCARED SUZY.
WILL YOU EXCUSE ME.
WELL AFTER THE BOMBING THIS
AFTERNOON SENATOR TRAVERES MAY
BE SACRED.
THESE TERRORIST ATTACKS AGAINST
THE MEMBERS OF THE SENATE COME
JUST A WEEK BEFORE THE
REVOTE AN THE ANTIARMS BILL.
THE SECRET SERVICE WILL
KEEP EXTRA SECURITY AROUND THE
PRESIDENT UNTIL THEY FIND OUT
WHO IS ACTUALLY BEHIND THESE
BOMBINGS.
SUZY BRYANT CHANNEL 7 NEWS.
AND IT'S A BEAUTY.
AND I PUT THE
WINGS AND GO WHONG.
WE'RE HERE AT THE FEDERAL
COURT HOUSE WHERE A MYSTERIOUS
EXPLOSION HAS LEFT 3
PEOPLE DEAD AND 10 WOUNDED.
WHO IS IT?
IT'S ME.
YOU REALIZE OF COURSE YOU'RE
DEFYING YOUR OWN COURT ORDER.
I HEARD WHAT
HAPPENED, ARE YOU OKAY?
I JUST WANTED TO MAKE SURE.
YOU WANT TO COME IN?
I PROMISE I WON'T TURN YOU IN.
SOME OF THE SENATORS HAVE
HIRED THEIR OWN BODY GUARDS.
THE NATIONAL GUARD IS ON ALERT.
OPINION POLLS ARE RUNNING 3:1
IN FAVOR OF THE TERRORISTS.
IT'S TRUE, IT'S TRUE.
THERE IS A CHART IN USA TODAY.
YOU WANT A DRINK?
NO, THANKS.
NICE PLACE HUH?
THERE IS A CHAIR
SOMEWHERE OVER HERE.
I'M SORRY IT'S A MESS.
IT'S THE MAID'S YEAR OFF.
I SHOULD HAVE CALLED FIRST.
OH GOD, SHE LOOKED LIKE YOU.
TESS, IT'S GOOD TO SEE YOU.
IT'S REALLY GOOD TO SEE YOU.
TESS YOU'RE MY WIFE.
I NEED YOU
I NEED TO HOLD YOU.
I ACHE FOR YOU.
WHY DID YOU COME?
WHAT IS IT?
I KNOW WHAT YOU ARE FEELING?
WE BOTH HAVE TO DEAL
WITH THE SAME PAIN.
LOOK AT YOURSELF.
TERRY...
I'M NOT AS GOOD AT
THIS AS YOU ARE.
WELL YOU CAN SIT HERE, GET DRUNK
AND FEEL SORRY FOR YOURSELF,
THAT'S FINE.
NO ONE BUT YOU IS BLAMING YOU.
GAME!
REMATCH NEXT WEEK?
YEAH, YEAH, YEAH.
GOOD GAME FRANK.
HOW THE HELL DID
YOU GET IN HERE?
I WALKED.
NOW THERE IS A MATTER OF
MY 10 MILLION DOLLARS.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT THE
HELL YOU'RE TALKING ABOUT.
WHAT MONEY?
MUST THIS BORING GAME GO ON?
FIRST, VICTOR, THEN
THYME, AND NOW YOU.
THEY SAY DEATH
ALWAYS COMES IN THREES.
ARE YOU FAMILIAR FRANK
WITH THE ROAD TO HELL.
AND PLEASE DON'T THINK ABOUT
GOING PUBLIC BECAUSE YOU'LL HAVE
A SLIGHT DIFFICULTY EXPLAINING
A 50 MILLION DOLLAR PROFIT
STEMMING FROM AND ANTIARMS DEAL
THAT YOU AND THE OTHERS PUSHED
THROUGH CONGRESS.
I DON'T THINK YOU'D GIVE UP YOUR
SEAT IN THE SENATE FOR 40 YEARS
IN PRISON.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT THE
HELL YOU'RE TALKING ABOUT.
I SIGNED ON BECAUSE IT
WAS A HIGH PROFILE BILL.
I DIDN'T INTEND TO GET
INVOLVED WITH ANY OF THIS STUFF.
SOMEONE HAS GOT MY MONEY
FRANK, AND YOU'D BETTER FIND IT.
OTHERWISE, I'M GOING
TO BLOW YOU WIDE OPEN.
QUITE LITERALLY.
THANKS.
EXCUSE ME.
GOOD AFTERNOON GENTLEMAN.
WHAT'S THE GOOD WORD?
WELL, I SHOULD HAVE TEST
RESULTS BY THE END OF THE DAY.
YOU KNOW IF IT IS SOME KIND OF
FACSIMILE OF WATER THEN THEY CAN
PUT IT ANYWHERE.
WHAT DID YOU GET FROM YOUR...
SHANE PLEASE, WILL YOU
TURN OFF YOUR ROBOT.
I FEEL LIKE I'M
IN LOST IN SPACE.
WHAT DID YOU GET
FROM YOUR BRIEFING.
WELL IT'S REALLY VERY
INTERESTING BOTH SENATOR THYME
AND SENATOR VICTOR SPONSORED THE
MIDEAST ANTIARMS BILL WHICH IS
COMING UP FOR A REVOTE.
WHAT?
TRYING TO SCARE THE
SENATE INTO A VETO?
MAYBE.
BUT HERE I THINK IS
THE INTERESTING PART.
THERE IS ONE SENATOR LEFT WHO
SPONSORED THAT BILL WITH THEM.
WHO'S THAT?
GOD MN IT.
DAN...
DON'T DO ANYTHING STUPID.
LOOK IT THEY'RE PISSED BECAUSE
WE HAVEN'T COME UP WITH ANY
ANSWERS.
HE IS YOUR ANSWER.
TELL TRAVERES TO
STAY AWAY FROM MY WIFE.
SO WHAT ABOUT SATURDAY?
YOU GOING TO COME?
YOU SAID YOU WOULD.
I'D LIKE YOU TO.
I DON'T KNOW IF I SHOULD.
WHY, WHAT ARE YOU THINKING?
I DON'T KNOW WHAT
I'M FEELING HERE.
NICE SECURITY PAL.
IT'S ALL RIGHT, IT'S OKAY.
NO, NO, NO IT'S NOT OKAY.
YOU'RE A TARGET.
LISTEN YOU PRICK.
LISTEN TO ME, ANYONE WITH HALF A
BRAIN AND A GUN COULD WALK RIGHT
STOP IT.
COME HOME WITH ME.
I DON'T NEED YOU TELLING
ME WHO I AM SAFE WITH.
TERRY, PLEASE,
COME HOME WITH ME.
TERRY!
O'NEILL YOU ARE ALREADY IN
THIS DEEP ENOUGH, C'MON.
GENTLEMAN, WHY DON'T YOU
ESCORT MR. O'NEILL OUT.
I DUG AS MUCH AS I COULD, IF I
HADN'T BEEN SO BUSY, I WOULD
HAVE GOTTEN THIS TO YOU SOONER.
FRANK TRAVERES IS A
REGULAR BOY SCOUT.
HIS TAX RETURNS ARE IN ORDER.
HE OWES FAVORS TO A FEW
PEOPLE, BUT THAT IS NOT UNUSUAL.
YOU SURE THERE IS
NOTHING IN HERE.
NOTHING THAT I COULD FIND.
WHERE IS A CORRUPT POLITICIAN
WHEN YOU NEED ONE HUH?
FEEL FREE TO PERUSE THE GOODS.
IT SAYS HE IS ONLY
CLAIMING 122,000 A YEAR.
WELL THAT'S ALL HE MAKES ON
SALARY PLUS A FEW SPEAKING FEES.
THE MAN HAS A CAMPAIGN
HE IS STILL PAYING OFF.
HOW'S HE PAYING FOR THAT HOUSE.
HE DIDN'T PAY THAT MUCH
FOR IT, IT WAS IN BAD SHAPE.
HE GOT A GOOD DEAL.
WHAT ABOUT THE INSIDE.
I MEAN THERE IS A LOT
OF FROO-FROO THERE.
WELL THERE WERE
SOME REPAIR WORK.
NO, NO I'M TALKING ABOUT
MARBLE COLUMNS, HARDWOOD FLOORS.
HE'S STILL PAYING
A FEW THINGS OFF.
MARION.
ANY GUY WHO MAKES $130,000 A
YEAR DOESN'T LIVE LIKE THIS.
WHAT YOU THINK THIS GUY IS
STUPID ENOUGH TO FLAUNT HIS
MONEY?
HE IS FROM MIAMI.
YOU'RE RIGHT, LOOK, I GOTTA GO.
BIG DATE?
BIG I DON'T KNOW YET, I JUST
FIGURED I COULDN'T WAIT AROUND
FOR YOUR FOREVER.
YOU'RE CRUSHING ME,
YOU'RE CRUSHING ME.
YOU'RE THE BEST.
I KNOW.
ALL RIGHT, THANK YOU.
GOOD LUCK SHERLOCK.
HUH...
HI...
WHA...
SHANE WHERE ARE YOU?
AT THE LAB?
ALL RIGHT, ALL RIGHT,
I'LL COME DOWN, OKAY.
JUST CLEAR ME WITH UM, WITH
SECURITY OKAY SO I DON'T GET
HASSLED.
THANKS BYE.
WATCH THIS.
ALL RIGHT.
C'MON, C'MON IT
ONLY TAKES 30 SECONDS.
SO WHAT THE HELL IS IT?
IT'S UH, A WEIRD HYBRID COMBO OF
LIQUID EXPLOSIVES THAT HAVE BEEN
PUT THROUGH A PROCESS I
HAVE NEVER SEEN BEFORE.
ACTIVATED, IT'S LIKE A
COMBINATION OF NITRO, NAPALM,
HYDROGEN.
IT'S COMPLICATED.
IT IS...
WAIT A MINUTE, WAIT A MINUTE.
WHAT DO YOU MEAN ACTIVATED, HOW?
WHEN YOU DRINK IT, IT'S
LIVE RIGHT WHAT THE HELL.
BUT IN THE STOMACH
IT BECOMES A DEVICE.
THEN IT HIT ME.
IT'S ACID.
STOMACH ACID.
YEAH, I THOUGHT MAYBE IT WAS
STOMACH ACID BUT I DIDN'T HAVE
ANY.
SO WHAT YOU GOT IN THERE?
ORANGE JUICE.
CAN YOU BELIEVE THAT.
AND IT WORKS WITH
BORIC ACID AS WELL.
WELL HOW DO WE DIFFUSE THIS?
ROLAIDS?
THAT'S NOT THAT FAR FROM RIGHT.
A CRATER OF ANTACIDS,
ALKA-SELTZER, ANYTHING ALKALINE
WILL NEUTRALIZE THE ACID.
NO ONE IS SAFE.
TRAVERES, HE IS OPENING
THE KIDS CENTER TODAY.
I SAW TERRY GET IN HIS LIMO.
HI, WELCOME TO THE
OPENING OF THE DC KID'S CENTER.
THE DC KID'S CENTER IS A
NONPROFIT ORGANIZATION.
IT WAS FOUNDED TO ASSIST IN
THE HEALTH AND WELL BEING...
HI.
HELLO.
WE ARE VERY PROUD OF OUR
CENTER AND WE'RE VERY GLAD TO
WELCOME YOU HERE TODAY...
WE WERE ESTABLISHED IN
1983 TO HELP EASE THE PLIGHT OF
UNDERPRIVILEGED CHILDREN
THROUGHOUT THE COUNTRY.
WE ARE FUNDED SOLELY THROUGH THE
GENEROUS SUPPORT OF INDIVIDUALS
ARE YOU ENJOYING YOURSELF?
SUCH AS SENATOR TRAVERES.
YES, BUT YOU SHOULDN'T BE
INTRODUCING ME TO PEOPLE LIKE
WE'RE A COUPLE.
WISHFUL THINKING.
LOOK FRANK, I.
WHAT?
WHAT'S THE MATTER?
WE JUST NEED TO TALK.
OKAY LET'S TALK, I LOVE TO TALK.
THAT'S WHY I GOT INTO POLITICS.
EXCUSE ME SENATOR,
WE'RE READY FOR YOU.
OH, OKAY, BACK IN A MOMENT.
AND NOW I'D LIKE TO INTRODUCE
YOU TO THE MAN WHO MADE THIS ALL
POSSIBLE, SENATOR
FRANK TRAVERES.
I THANK YOU, THANK YOU
ALL FOR BEING HERE TODAY.
GET ON YOUR RADIO
OFFICER, WE HAVE A BOMB THREAT.
WE'RE GOING TO HAVE
TO CLEAR THE AREA.
IT'S DANGEROUS, GIMME YOUR ID.
STEP AWAY FROM THE COOLER, IT'S
OKAY.
DO NOT LET ANYBODY
DRINK FROM THESE COOLERS.
HE SAYS THERE IS A BOMB.
A BOMB?
OH MY GOD!
WE HAVE A LITTLE PROBLEM
SENATOR, WE GOT TO GET YOU OUT
OF HERE.
LADIES AND GENTLEMAN
THERE IS NO REASON TO PANIC.
WE ARE HAVING A
SECURITY PROBLEM.
YOU ARE IN ABSOLUTELY NO DANGER.
PLEASE REMAIN CALM AND EVACUATE
THE PREMISES IN AN ORDERLY
FASHION.
LADIES AND GENTLEMAN
THERE IS NO REASON TO PANIC.
I REPEAT THERE IS
NO REASON TO PANIC.
THERE IS NO REASON TO PANIC.
TERRY, TERRY!
DON'T DRINK THE WATER!
DON'T DRINK THAT!
DID YOU DRINK THAT?
NO, WHY.
THE EXPLOSIVES
WERE IN THE WATER.
WE FOUND OUT THIS MORNING.
WHAT THE HELL ARE YOU DOING?
DANNY NO.
WE ANALYZED IT.
IT'S JUST WATER.
YOU MEAN TO TELL ME YOU CAUSED
THIS WHOLE GOD DAMN THING AND
THERE IS NOTHING WRONG HERE.
MIKAIL!
IT'S TOO LATE.
NO, WE CANNOT WAIT ANY LONGER.
HE'LL GET THE MESSAGE.
I'LL KILL THEM ALL..
YOU BASTARD. I WILL SHOW
YOU, YOU BASTARD
- GET BACK!
YOU WILL SEE. YOU ARE DEAD.
SHANE IT'S IN THE FOUNTAIN, THIS
GUY IS GOING TO BLOW!
I GOT YOU DAN, I'M COMING.
WE'VE GOT 10 SECONDS.
WHAT!
WE'VE GOT TO GET
HIM OUT OF HERE!
LET ME ASK YOU THIS
BEFORE I CUT YOUR BALLS OFF.
WHY DID THIS HAPPEN?
HEY, IT WASN'T MY FAULT.
I DIDN'T SAY IT WAS YOUR FAULT.
IT'S INTERESTING THOUGH YOU
SHOULD EVEN BRING THAT UP.
LOOK, I DID EVERYTHING
I WAS SUPPOSED TO DO.
I GOT YOU THE VIP PASS.
I GOT ALRED THAT JOB.
I CAN'T HELP IT THAT
O'NEILL SHOWED UP.
YOU SHOULD HAVE BEEN LESS
WORRIED ABOUT YOUR OWN LIFE.
I KNOW I'M LESS
WORRIED ABOUT YOUR LIFE.
LOOK...
I'M ONLY HERE BECAUSE
OF WHAT YOU OFFERED ME.
I AM NOT HERE TO DIE.
THIS IS NOT A GOOD DAY.
OH JESUS.
I WAS THERE TO TELL FRANK I
WOULDN'T SEE HIM ANYMORE.
WHY?
BECAUSE I'M YOU'RE
WIFE, WHY DO YOU THINK?
TERRY, WHY DON'T
YOU GO WAIT OUTSIDE.
I'LL BE DOWN IN 10 MINUTES.
JUST LET US KNOW IF
YOU NEED ANYTHING.
GUESS WHO.
LOOK, I'VE ALERTED MY SECURITY.
I ALSO HAVE A MAN IN THE HOUSE.
YOUR SEXUAL
PREFERENCES DON'T INTEREST ME.
YOU KNOW YOU COULD HAVE KILLED
100S OF INNOCENT PEOPLE TODAY.
WELL ONLY BECAUSE
THEY MATTER TO YOU.
NOW, I'M NOT IN THE
MOOD TO WAIT ANY LONGER.
I HAVE A LIFE YOU KNOW.
YOU KNOW IF YOU KILL ME,
YOU WON'T GET ANYTHING.
NOT TRUE.
I GET TO KILL YOU.
YOU WON'T GET YOUR 10 MILLION.
I'M SORRY THE SENATOR CAN'T TALK
RIGHT NOW, HE'S GOT A GUN TO HIS
HEAD.
WELL YOU SHOULD KNOW WHOEVER
YOU ARE THAT THE SENATOR MEANS
NOTHING TO ME.
HMM, I'M NOT SURPRISED.
I SAW WHAT HAPPENED AT
THE CHILDREN'S CENTER.
DANNY O'NEILL.
AND SPEAKING OF YOUR WIFE, SHE
SHOULD BE THERE ANY MINUTE NOW.
SHE WOULDN'T TAKE ANY OF FRANK'S
CALLS, SO I DID HIM A FAVOR.
ISN'T IT IRONIC?
I ONLY DID IT
BECAUSE I LIKE HIM.
I'M THAT KIND OF GUY.
NOW.
ANYMORE GUNS IN THE HOUSE?
DO YOU HAVE ANOTHER GUN?
HELLO TERRY, GWEN,
GWEN PUT TERRY ON.
GO ON CAPTAIN GO PLAY.
GWEN PUT TERRY ON GOD DAMN IT.
WHO WAS THAT?
JUST SOMEONE TAKING A POLL.
THEY WORK FAST,
THEIR LINE IS DEAD.
DO YOU KNOW
ANYTHING ABOUT TERRY?
YOU'VE GOT
SECURITY OUTSIDE RIGHT?
YES, I DO.
OKAY.
I WAS JUST GETTING...
SO WHAT MAKES YOU THINK
THINGS WILL BE ANY DIFFERENT?
MOM, IT WASN'T JUST HIM.
NOW YOU BLAME YOURSELF.
DON'T LET HIM DO THAT TO YOU.
YOU NEVER GIVE UP DO YOU?
GOOD EVENING.
BEN, WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?
MR. TRAVERES ASKED ME
TO COME AND GET YOU.
HE REALLY NEEDS TO SEE YOU.
I DON'T THINK SO, TELL..
IF HE WANTS TO SEE
YOU, YOU SHOULD GO.
LIGHTS.
JESUS CHRIST,
THEY'VE HAD YOU STAKED.
YOU'LL NEVER LIVE THROUGH THIS.
YOUR SUCH A PESSIMIST.
IT'S MY UPBRINGING.
LOOK, I'M SORRY YOU HAD TO DRIVE
ALL THE WAY UP HERE BUT JUST
TELL HIM...
I'M NOT ASKING TERRY.
LET GO OF MY DAUGHTER!
DON'T SCREAM OR I USE IT.
WHAT THE HELL ARE YOU DOING?
JUST LOOKING THROUGH YOUR STUFF.
WHO PAID YOU TO PUSH
THE ARMS DEAL THROUGH?
THE MONEY CAME FROM AN ARMS
SALES TO THE COUNTRIES WE CUT
OFF WITH THE BILL.
IT'S NOT UNCOMMON YOU KNOW.
IT'S AN AMERICAN TRADITION.
VICTOR AND THYMES SET IT UP.
I JUST SIGNED ON AS A CO-SPONSOR
BECAUSE I THOUGHT IT WOULD RAISE
MY VISIBILITY IN THE
SENATE THAT'S ALL.
YEAH, SURE AND YOU PAID FOR
THIS ENTIRE HOUSE WITH CASH.
NO RECEIPTS.
I SUPPOSE THAT IS AN AMERICAN
TRADITION TOO, HUH FRANK?
YOU'RE NOT DOING WHAT I
THINK YOU'RE DOING ARE YOU?
YOU'RE INSURED RIGHT?
NO, I'M NOT.
C'MON.
THE CAPITAL CITY'S
ONLY ALL NIGHT TALK SHOW.
IT'S 4:45 AM PEOPLE.
THE SUN WILL BE UP IN ABOUT 20
MINUTES SO IF YOU'RE NOT ASLEEP
YET, YOU MIGHT AS
WELL JUST STAY AWAKE.
LET'S GO BACK TO THE PHONES.
GO AHEAD CALLER,
YOU'RE ON THE AIR.
HELLO DAVID.
GO AHEAD CALLER.
YEAH, THIS IS JIM FROM
ARLEY, I JUST WANTED TO...
AFTER YOU LOVER BOY.
YOU SURE IT IS SAFE OUT THERE?
DAMN SAFER THAN HERE.
OH HI, UH, THIS IS YVETTE...
YOU'RE DEAD!
SO THIS IS WHERE IT
ALL HAPPENS, HUH FRANK?
ANY CONGRESSIONAL
PAGE BOYS UNDER THE BED?
VASELINE.
OKAY, MOVE.
MOVE, MOVE C'MON.
WHERE?
OVER THERE.
DOWN HERE?
HEY, HEY, HEY...
C'MON WHERE YOU GOING?
GET BACK IN HERE.
GO.
I WAS GOING TO GO OUTSIDE AND
HAVE A CIGARETTE, THAT'S ALL.
YOU KNOW THIS HOUSE, I DON'T.
I CAN'T BE TOO HELPFUL
BEING HANDCUFFED HERE.
PLANNING A PARTY?
WHAT THE HELL IS GOING ON HERE?
OH...
LOOK.
THE OBJECT OF
EVERYONE'S AFFECTION.
GO UPSTAIRS AND
HELP ALRED'S MEN.
NO WAY.
YOU PAID ME TO KEEP
AN EYE ON TRAVERES.
THIS IS YOUR FIGHT.
YES, YOU'RE RIGHT, I'M SORRY.
THANK YOU.
I'LL KILL YOU RIGHT HERE!
LET'S GO FIND THE TWO
MEN IN YOUR LIFE, HUH?
TOO BAD YOU'RE NOT INSURED.
LET'S GET OUT OF HERE,
C'MON, C'MON, C'MON.
NO!
WAIT, WAIT, WAIT
WHERE DOES THIS LEAD TO?
THE ATTIC.
SLOW DOWN.
YOU WANT TO JUMP?
CMERE, CMERE, CMERE.
ALL RIGHT.
C'MON.
YOU CERTAINLY DID PUT ALL YOUR
MONEY INTO THIS HOUSE DIDN'T YOU
HUH?
LOOKS LIKE YOU'VE GOT OVER 10
MILLION IN INSULATION RIGHT
HERE.
C'MON, COME OVER HERE.
WHAT ARE YOU A
BOY SCOUT OR WHAT?
YEAH, I'M ABOUT TO
EARN ANOTHER MERIT BADGE.
CALVARY, C'MON.
HEY, HEY UP HERE.
ALL RIGHT SEAL OFF THE
WEST SIDE
MR. O'NEILL.
NO...
STAY RIGHT HERE.
JUST LET HER GO, OKAY?
THERE IS NOTHING
YOU CAN DO RIGHT NOW.
THE POLICE ARE DOWNSTAIRS.
THERE IS NO WAY OUT.
DIFFUSE THIS ONE MR. O'NEILL.
NO!
COME HERE, GO.
DANNY!
EASY WATCH YOURSELF.
GET THAT LATTER OVER HERE QUICK.
SET IT UP THERE.
DANNY!
DANNY...
I'M HERE, I'M HERE.
WE'LL TAKE CARE OF EVERYTHING
DANNY, YOU JUST GOT TO GET
BETTER.
ANYTHING YOU WANT?
I WANT A RAISE.
FORGET IT.
WHERE WERE YOU
WHEN I NEEDED YOU?
HONESTLY, PROGRAMMING MADONNA
TO ASK JAMES FOR A RAISE.
OH GREAT.
GUYS, MY WIFE.
WHY DID YOU GUYS CALL ME HUH?
I MEAN YOU KNOW I
DON'T DO THIS ANYMORE.
SHE ASKED FOR YOU
PERSONALLY DAN.
HI...
I THOUGHT I TOLD YOU TO
GO BACK TO YOUR HUSBAND.
I DID.
MY BOYFRIEND DID THIS.
WHAT ARE YOU BETTING
ON TODAY, RED OR GREEN.
GOD..
NOT THIS AGAIN.
GREEN.
NO MORE GUESSING.
I ONLY BET ON SURE THINGS.
FRED, I'M CUTTING THE WIRE.
HAVE YOUR GUYS
READY WITH THE BARREL.
CUT QUICK DAN, WE
JUST HAD A CALL.
YOUR WIFE'S WATER BROKE.
HEY, PAL, YOU'RE
GOING TO HAVE A BABY.
YOUR LUCK HAS CHANGED.
I'M OUT OF HERE.
THANK YOU.
AND BY THE WAY, I LIKE THE
UNDERWEAR BY THE WAY DON'T EVER
CHANGE.
TAKE CARE GUYS SEE YOU.