Woman: Okay?
♪ giddy-yup, giddy-yup
giddy-yup, bup-bup ♪
- Yeah!
- ( giggling )
( laughter )
- More!
- More?
All right.
Well, you just sit up here,
up higher.
( giggles )
Okay, you ready?
♪ giddy-yup, giddy-yup
giddy-yup, bup-bup ♪
Yay!
( mumbling )
( grunts )
I'm--I'm- I'm cold.
Okay.
Um, let's just sleep
a little bit more.
Why?
Because I'm still tired.
Five more minutes?
- No!
- Please?
- No.
- Five more minutes.
- No!
- Please.
- No.
- All right, come here.
Can we wake up?
Yes, we can wake up.
We're waking up.
( grunts )
( urinating )
( toilet flushes )
What do you dream about?
Hmm, just some stuff.
What stuff? Some trains?
Yeah,
I dreamt about trains.
What can we eat, dad?
- Hmm?
- What can we eat?
How about some cereal?
- Oatmeal.
- I want oatmeal.
Oatmeal?
Well, I'll take some
of that cereal.
You want oatmeal?
How about--
this cereal is really good.
Let's get your table ready.
There you go.
( coughs )
You all done?
Let's dry you off.
Come here.
- I want hugs.
- Morning hugs.
- No!
- Morning hugs?
- But my shirt is wet.
- I don't care.
( makes sound )
Hmm.
( car beeping )
- I'm hungry.
- You're hungry?
- Well, we should eat
as soon as it's over.
- Mm-hmm.
I promise, okay?
( imitates elevator bell dings )
- ( hums )
- um, uh, push three?
Good job.
I said who is aubrey,
you little piece of shit?
- Who is aubrey?
- ( babbling )
I'm sorry.
Isaac, shh, please?
Wait a second, so you're--
You're going
through my phone now?
This is fucking crazy.
You have 10 seconds before I rip
your fucking face off.
( mumbling )
I met her at the grocery store.
- ( babbling )
- isaac.
She came on to me and asked me
if I went to penn state
Because I was wearing
your sweatshirt.
So I said, "no,
it's--it's my friends."
You said it was a friend's?
Well, yes, I mean, bernadette,
it wasn't like that.
It was super quick.
Okay, will I see you later?
Yes.
- A monster, dada.
- I see the monster.
I'm almost done.
This is so embarrassing.
Woman: Oh, no,
don't worry about it.
- Let's get back on track.
- I'm so sorry, you guys.
Big teeth, dada!
Yeah, look at his big teeth
and I'm almost done.
I'm going to explain
that obviously,
But you keep cutting me off.
Don't look at me like that.
I don't want to talk to you
about this
If you keep looking at me
like that.
Leave.
Baby!
- Okay, pause scene.
- Thank you.
- Great, thank you
so much, mark.
- Mark.
- So second scene?
- No, no, no.
I think we're good.
We got everything we need.
- Okay. Great.
- Yeah.
- Um, really good
to see you, ma'am.
- Of course.
-Tamika[ph], great meeting you.
- Hey, nice.
- Amanda, you are unbelievable.
- Thanks.
- Thank you.
I think that you're absolutely
fucking amazing in chloe.
- Okay, thanks.
- And I love this movie,
And you're amazing
and this would be amazing.
Anyway, I'm sorry.
Isaac, we should go.
Can you say bye?
Can you say bye to amanda?
Can you say, "bye, amanda"?
- Can you say bye to amanda?
- It's okay.
Isaac. Isaac, you're ripping
the whole book.
Yeah.
( indistinct chattering )
Isaac: Come to the warship!
Come to the warship!
Mark: There's a big wind coming!
( imitates wind gusting )
I can fix the sails, buddy.
Oh, the storm's coming.
Fix the sails.
( imitates wind gusting )
Can you put some more gasoline
in there, please?
( imitates wind gusting )
( woman screams )
Daddy, there are balloons
floating away.
Whoa!
- The balloons float.
- The balloon is floating.
- Uh, lady.
- Thanks.
She lost the balloon.
I'm gonna sing stone the ship.
- You wanna help me make dinner?
- Uh, no! No?
No?
Nothing.
I'm gonna sit down
and eat with you.
Do you want anything to drink?
Yeah, I want a drink.
What color of cup?
- Blue, pink, yellow or orange?
- Green.
Green!
Pick a choice.
Yellow!
I'm really thirsty.
Oh.
Okay.
Remember to chew them well,
okay?
Why?
'cause if you take two big bites
and just swallow it,
It could get stuck
in your throat.
So you chew up with your teeth.
( teeth grinding )
Yes.
That's it.
Daddy, I'm done.
You're done?
Hey, isaac, can you eat a little
bit more, please?
- No.
- Isaac, you're not finished.
Isaac,
you still have more to eat.
But I'm through!
( crying )
Isaac, isaac, isaac, isaac,
But I need you
to eat your dinner.
No.
Okay, fine.
( sighs )
- I'm gonna eat it then.
- Chew it, dad,
And, uh, 'cause if you swallow,
it could stuck in your throat.
So don't do it.
Don't swallow it!
( teeth grinding )
Okay, a couple more minutes
and it's time for bed.
Ah!
( crying )
Okay, it's lights out.
( babbling )
( crying )
Oh, no.
Isaac, come on now.
I'm not playing games right now.
Oh, no!
( crying )
Once upon a time,
There was a little boy
named isaac,
And he had a spaceship.
And isaac started flying up
To the sad broken star.
It's time for bed.
( sighs )
( makes sound )
( imitates whooshing )
♪ I realize that I need you
♪ and I wondered
if I could come home ♪
( guitar strumming )
Woman: Thank you.
♪ I remember the time
you drove all night ♪
♪ just to meet me
in the morning ♪
♪ and I thought it was strange
you said everything changed ♪
♪ you felt
as if you'd just woke up ♪
- How are those crackers?
- Good, daddy.
- You still have more room?
- Mm-hmm.
What's your favorite food?
Is ice cream your favorite food
Or is peanut butter
your favorite food?
Peanut butter and crackers
and ice cream.
Yeah.
( giggles )
( sighs )
Is it this park
with the flowers?
Yeah, this park
has a lot of flowers.
Why did you go?
Can we stay at this park?
Yeah, we'll stay at this park
for a little bit.
Everywhere.
Yeah.
( humming )
Mark: Hey, baby.
( humming continues )
So he's doing pretty good.
I'm sure you can see that,
though.
He's talking a lot.
It was like overnight,
he just--
He's talking so much now and...
He's such a little man.
Well, if he can...
It's kind of the hardest part
of all these 'cause he doesn't--
He don't know why we're here.
He just knows
it's our special park and, um...
You know, that's what's fucking
killing me about that.
( sobbing )
Just one of the few,
He gave me a little bit
of...Strength 'cause...
I'm just starting
to feel like...
Pretty alone.
- Come on, daddy.
- It's like I don't really
got the energy, you know.
- ( sobs )
- daddy.
- Yeah, bud? ( sniffles )
- come on.
Thanks.
Are you okay?
What's wrong?
Tell daddy what's wrong.
( sobbing )
Are you upset?
( crying )
Okay? What?
45 bucks, that was really good.
Get it?
Hello? Hi. Great.
- How are you?
- Thank you.
- What will we buy here?
Oh, we're not buying anything.
See, all that coins
that we put in there,
- Now we get actual money.
- Oh, right.
Here you go.
Yeah, not bad.
How about yourself?
- Cool.
- Good.
Just emptying out
his piggy bank.
- Right.
- Yeah.
- There you go.
- Thank you.
Look at it, isaac, you got $45.
Cool, thank you.
- Thank you.
- We'll get some ice cream?
- Yeah!
- Yeah?
- Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
- Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Strawberry
and some cream in there.
- What?
- All right.
Shit, I'm sorry.
- Hi!
- Woman: How are you?
Um, I need a lot of ice cream.
- Okay.
Do you want these on pints?
- Yeah.
- Uh, yeah,
let me just look here.
- Okay.
- Honey, strawberry.
- Oh, no.
Oh, it's all in your shoe, bud.
( babbling )
- It's kind of like...
- ( screaming )
No, no, don't hit--
don't hit daddy.
Don't hit daddy.
- Isaac, don't hit...
- Oh, good.
- Okay.
- We need more napkins.
- Are the cones inside?
- Woman: Yes.
- Wonderful. Okay.
- ( babbling )
( imitates monkey gibbering )
- Sorry, just took the last.
- Oh, it's monkey.
- Hmm.
- ( imitates monkey gibbering )
- Oh, monkey.
- ( laughs )
Mark: Hey.
- Mark.
- What's up?
- Having dinner.
- Cool.
- This is juice?
- Yeah.
- Can I get some?
- Sure.
Thanks.
Tim home yet?
Yeah, he's up in his room.
( sighs )
- Hey, tim.
- Tim: Yeah?
- You got a minute, man?
- Yeah.
All right, cool.
I'm in the kitchen with ray.
All right.
I want to talk to you guys
for a second.
- Hey.
- Sit down.
What's up, man?
( sighs )
I thought I got some good news.
I had an amazing audition
the other day.
Amazing.
There's a huge movie,
shoots in two weeks,
And I feel like I'm definitely
gonna get callbacks
So I got something good
on the horizon.
And I'm also doing a couple
of other things
And I'm probably
gonna have some money
To give to you
by the end of this week.
Yeah, like hell.
Jason?
Hey!
- I'm sorry, man.
- No, no. No problem.
- Hi, mark.
- He is about to pass out.
- Hello?
- Hey, remember jason?
Isaac, remember me?
- He really wants a nap.
- ( laughs )
I know how you feel.
Hey, isaac,
I need a nap too, man.
Jason needs a nap, too.
( laughs )
- Uh, here's, uh, here's this.
- You're a godsend.
- You're saving my life
literally.
- No problem. And I--
That was the only one
I could come up with,
Uh, today...
No, no, that's gonna be more
than enough.
- Isaac.
- It's just buy me
a little bit of time
- And then I'm gonna
get this right back.
- Dude...
Who's that handsome guy
in that mirror, huh?
Who's that?
( laughs )
- Man, he is a lot bigger.
- You grow an inch every night,
don't you?
- Man.
- How's the show?
It's great, it's great.
We have, uh, like we have a lot
of--a lot of stuff today.
- I think we're doing
eight-paged.
- You just look great.
Thanks!
- Yeah, always get to dress.
- Nice.
Ouch!
Ouchies.
Ouchie? Ouchie what?
My finger got bited
from my mouth
With my teeth.
Your finger got bited
from your mouth with your teeth?
Uh-huh.
( laughter )
Whoa!
- Hey, hello.
- Woman: Hello,
how are you doing, sir?
- Good, how are you?
- Fine, thank you.
- Just, uh, this guy.
- All right,
that'll be just $9 for him.
( children laughing )
- They're cool.
- All right, buddy.
- ( babbling )
- peek-a-boo later.
- Take my jacket off.
- Lydia: Hi!
Hey.
Ah, the ice cream shop.
Hi.
- Nice to see you.
- Nice to see you, too.
- I'm mark.
- I'm lydia.
It's nice to meet you.
This is crazy.
You have to take off your shoes.
Sorry.
This is, uh, for us.
- ( babbling )
- is that your daughter?
No, she's at school.
So you just hang out
and keep a look at kids?
No, um, it's my place.
- What? This is your place?
- Yeah. Yeah.
- Wow, excuse me!
- ( chuckles )
- Stop!
- It's incredible.
It's an amazing place.
I really like coming here.
It's good to just sit down
and, uh--
- And relax
and let them play and...
- Relax, yeah.
- Yeah, we love there.
- Yeah.
I, uh...
Yeah.
Um...
- Okay, you have fun.
- All right.
- Okay.
- It was nice to meet you, mark.
Isaac: What are you doing?
Lydia: I'm just looking
at all these pictures
And deciding which ones
to hang up.
- You wanna help me?
- I'm driving.
Okay, you're driving right now.
You have to focus on the road.
I'm trying to focus
on the road.
- Yeah.
- You can't tell anybody.
I still want to run it back.
- That's a twist.
- Oh, a fruit twist?
- I pick those, too.
- Oh.
- Those are my favorite.
- Really?
See they're sweet, daddy?
I don't know if we can do that
with the real thing.
I mean, just maybe a couple
of cooking there.
Lydia: Coffee over there.
- Really?
- Yeah.
- That'd be great. Thank you.
- How do you take it?
Ah, just like that.
Maybe I'll put some
of this agave in there.
- This is great. Thank you.
- Cheers.
All right. Cheers.
How old are you?
- ( babbling )
- it will be fun have one
of these in your house.
Mm-hmm, I do.
Coming here after hours.
( laughs )
- Bounce around.
- Really party it up.
Maybe I'll invite you
to one of my after hours,
- Adults-only-bouncy-ball party.
- That'd be amazing.
I'm just kidding.
I don't do that.
It'd be fun. Thank you.
I wanna try green.
You can try blue!
You can try blue.
- Well, you want green?
- Mm-hmm.
It's a pretty green, huh?
Well, this looks like
a cool color.
I think for the color.
Okay.
This looks like a cool color.
That's my favorite color.
- Red?
- Mm-hmm.
Can I borrow that orange
for a second?
- No.
- No?
Can I borrow that black
for a second?
Yeah.
Can I borrow that orange?
And you borrow my red.
( chuckles )
- So do you draw all the dads
and their kids?
- ( chuckles )
No.
It's a no.
Sorry, that was stupid.
( chuckles )
No, it wasn't.
This is how they're drawing
the likeness with anybody
In a really long time.
( laughter )
( train bell ringing )
Oh, my...
It disappeared.
Oh, my god!
What?
What, daddy?
They towed our car, isaac.
- ( sneezes )
- bless you.
- Hi.
- Did you forget something?
Um...
- What's wrong?
- Our car got towed.
Oh, sh--
I'm sorry.
- Thank you so much.
( sighs )
- mm-hmm.
I feel like such an idiot.
Why?
- Oh, it's just like...
- I'm still hot, daddy.
- A lot to put on somebody,
you know?
- Cool.
- I'm still hot!
- You're still hot? Okay.
Well, we got the air
on full blast.
It just takes a second
to get cold, I know.
This is an old car.
What kind of car
do you guys have?
Do you know what kind of car
we have, isaac?
- Prius!
- Yeah, prius.
Well, that's nice.
That's--
It's, uh, I sold my stuff out.
Besides I'm scratched up and...
Sorry if it got towed.
Well, it's not your fault.
- ( laughs )
- daddy?
- What, bud?
- Are you afraid of snakes?
Am I afraid of snakes?
I'm not that afraid
of snakes.
- Are you afraid of snakes?
- Mm-mm.
- A little bit, yeah.
- You do?
- Yeah.
What did you ask up, buddy?
'cause snakes are scary.
Oh, you're just thinking
about that?
Some snakes are scary,
but not some.
- Sure.
- What are snake noises, daddy?
They go...
( hisses )
- Will you do it again?
- ( chuckles )
- ( hisses )
- ( laughs )
How long have you lived here?
Um, it's been about, uh...
2 1/2 years now.
Um, I drove cross country.
- With isaac?
- Mm-hmm.
Well, isaac was, uh,
in his mom's tummy then.
Oh, okay.
- Yeah.
- You guys drove...
She's about eight months
pregnant and, uh...
Are you and his mom--
are you still...
We're not together. No.
You're not together.
Yeah, yeah.
Um, just to make it
Figuring out a way
to make it work and...
You're doing good.
I'm all right.
Dad, why is this car so old?
( chuckles )
Why is there old--what?
Why is there old what?
- Why?
- It is old.
I've had it for a long time.
It's my friend, though.
Oh, here we are.
- Oh.
- Are we here at the mechanic?
- The tow place?
- Yeah. Great.
- Yeah.
- Thank you so much.
- Sure.
- I really, really,
really appreciate it.
- Here we are, buddy.
We are here.
- No, please, don't--
I didn't mind at all.
It's a break for me
from the chaos.
- Oh, he's so precious.
- Thank you.
Well, are your--
all your friends here?
Well, the tall guy
is not really a friend.
Do you have a phone?
Yeah, I do.
I, you know, I do.
Can--I was gonna ask you
if I could give it to you?
- Oh, that's good.
- No!
Yeah. Uh, let me--
let me give it to you.
Let's see where...
- Hello?
- Man: What can I do for you?
Uh, a friend
just drop me off here.
I'm pretty sure my car
was towed here.
- What kind of car?
- It's a black prius.
Yeah, we got it.
Okay.
It's $480.
Jesus fucking christ.
- $480?
- Yes, sir.
Is there any way I can pay
a little less than that?
- There's no-
- no way.
( mumbling )
( buzzer )
Why did they tow it?
They towed it because--
I have no fucking idea
why they towed it.
We parked in a place that no one
is supposed to park in.
Maybe they towed it.
- Yeah.
- Oh, no.
Oh, no.
Thanks, man.
Go fuck yourself.
They're pretty here.
We push, push,
Push, push, push, push.
No!
( imitates train chugging )
( grunting )
- Ooh.
- ( chuckles )
No, don't! Not this one.
Two tattoos.
I won't give you two tattoos.
There, that one's finished.
Do you like that one?
- Yeah.
- Okay. What would you like?
A garbage truck and trash can
and garbage can.
Whoa, that's a lot.
Garbage truck, a trash pan
and a garbage can?
I don't think I can draw
that on your arm.
- Yes.
- Can you think
of something else?
No!
Okay.
Here is a garbage truck.
I make the wheels.
I make the front part.
That's not a garbage truck.
That's a pick-up truck.
Now, I'm gonna give you
a tattoo.
You're gonna give me a tattoo?
Well, I'm gonna do it
on your forehead.
On my forehead?
I don't want a tattoo
on my forehead.
How about my wrist?
Hmm.
- There's a airplane on you.
- You drew an airplane on me?
- Yeah.
- Wow.
( humming )
That's okay.
( chuckles )
I'm pregnant.
( knocks on door )
-Oh, hi.
- Hi.
- Hey. Hi. Hi, what's your name?
- Isabel: Hi.
- Welcome.
- My name is isabel.
- Isabel, I'm mark.
- Hi, nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you.
- Oh, my gosh.
- Their flowers are dead.
- ( mumbles )
- lydia: Hmm.
- Perfect.
- Mushy broccoli.
- Melts in your mouth.
- Mm-hmm.
Let me draw
on this paper right here
And you draw right here.
You know the table is good.
We should write right here
because you can draw right here.
I set up.
You wanna put some of these
down here
So you can move around here.
- Here.
- Mark: Are you gonna have one?
- Lydia: Maybe.
- Okay.
I'll have one
if you'll have one later.
- So I'll have orange juice now.
- Follower.
- Can I have some more?
- Yeah.
Isabel,
you look very lovely tonight.
You do, you look amazing,
isabel.
- You did good, girl.
- Thank you, mommy?
If I would have known, I would
have come more coordinated.
- Huh?
- ( chuckles ) yes.
Because the guys wearing like
this would have him in sweater.
- ( isaac crying )
- it's cranky time.
Do you want macaroni and cheese?
Do you like macaroni and cheese?
Isabel: It's the only thing
we have, too.
No, we have this other stuff
that you're not gonna like.
So that's why I made macaroni
and cheese.
- Oh, macaroni and cheese.
- Same old story.
- Is that what you want?
- Oops.
- Mama.
- Lydia.
Thank you.
On a scale of 1 to 10,
How much do you love
being a parent?
- Um...
- Right now.
- Right now?
- ( chuckles )
- I'm just gonna keep
that to myself. Yeah.
- Okay.
This is like the best thing I've
ever eaten in my entire life.
- It makes it yummy.
- Mm-hmm. Mm-hmm.
- It's very yummy, isn't it?
- Do you feel better now
that you're eating?
- Mm-hmm.
- I feel bad.
What?
I said to mama
I don't feel good.
Hmm.
Looks cute.
- ( laughs )
- hey, what's so funny?
I don't know.
What's so funny, babel[ph], huh?
Thank you. Huh?
I'm just thinking
of he said mama. ( chuckles )
- Oh.
- It happens all the time.
Hey, I'm a mama.
Daddy is looking for a worm.
If daddy gets some worm,
I'm gonna win.
- Lydia: Duck!
- I knew you were
gonna get that?
- How?
- I do just tell in my mind.
- Do you want to play again?
- Sure, let's do it.
Do you want to play again?
Oh, yeah,
unless more a wine?
- Yeah.
- That's it.
Isabel: That's fun.
Did you guys have fun?
- It's a lot of fun. Thank you.
- Sure.
I want the worm.
- One more to go, chicken.
- I have the worm.
Hey! Hey, you? Yes, mark?
- Yeah.
- Mark, I was the one
who had the worm.
Thank you.
- Welcome.
- Now, you get to...
- An apple.
- Yummy apple.
- You need to get it
from the same.
- Yummy apple.
- ( mumbles )
- they're really gonna go along?
She's an angel.
I think--I was worried
of the age difference.
- House and ball?
- Ball. Ball.
- Oh!
- A house.
"you do just what the list
says," said mrs. Rogers.
And mrs. Rogers got into the car
with mr. Rogers
And they drove away.
Who's gonna have that pie?
I don't know.
I wanna eat it.
I think I'm gonna have it.
These are drawings.
( laughter )
- This is drawing.
- It is just a drawing.
- We're not drawing.
- He's so cute.
We're not drawings.
We're not drawings?
We're not?
- Mm.
- I thought we were.
- No.
- No?
No.
Oh, you taught me
something today.
Mark: Once upon a time, there
was a little boy named isaac
- And he was isaac the dreamer.
- ( yawns )
He made everybody's dreams
come true.
So one night,
he saw lydia sleeping
And lydia was dreaming about...
( chuckles )
Oh!
( laughs ) I hope isaac
is a deep sleeper.
( laughs )
I just don't like her
a hurricane.
( chuckles )
( music playing over player )
- Hi.
How are you doing?
I'm okay.
Where are you from?
I'm from sacramento.
- Philadelphia.
- Oh.
Thanks for having me over.
Sure.
( sighs )
- Did you just put that on
'cause you're nervous?
- Oh, not really.
Yeah.
( music playing over player )
I love you.
I love you so much.
I wanna marry you.
Will you marry me?
Mm. Oh, I feel better.
All right. Okay. Okay. O
kay.
What?
Nothing, just--I just hold on.
Oh.
- No.
- Oh, god, I'm sorry.
Fuck!
- Thanks.
- Sure.
- Oh.
- Are you drunk?
Did you get--
did you drink too much?
I just want you to feel not bad.
I don't--
I feel...Bad.
I feel bad.
I don't feel sorry.
I should go.
I should probably get him home.
What just happened?
I should get him home
right now.
Well, okay.
- So I'm gonna go.
- Okay.
Um, are you sure?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I have to shit.
Okay.
- You know,
I should give my sweater.
- Oh.
( music playing
over the kiddie ride )
Yeah. Look, it's you.
That's fine, huh?
No? Okay.
You wanna get out of it.
All right. All right.
Mark: He's looking at us.
Do you see that?
- ( screams )
- hey, he's looking right at us.
Who you looking at?
Are you looking at us?
( hums )
Whoa. Whoa.
Whoa, look at that fish.
Goldfish!
- Whoa!
- A goldfish.
That's a big goldfish.
That's a little too big for us.
Oh, there we go.
Look at that.
Well, that's a lot of them.
Whoa.
Touch it and they move.
Think you can pick one of them
out of there and be your pet?
Which one?
Yeah, very first goldfish.
Any one in particular or...
- ( laughs )
- anything is fine.
Whoa, look at that.
Wow!
That's perfect.
- What should we name her?
- Isaac: Daddy.
You want to name her daddy?
- Okay. That's a good name.
- No.
Yes, we can build a house
for her at home.
Yeah, we're gonna build you
a house at home,
And your name is now--
what is it?
- Daddy!
- Daddy, your name is daddy.
We love you, daddy.
So we got to remember,
we got to feed daddy every day.
- The fish, not you.
- Yeah, the fish.
- Not you.
- Not me.
We have to talk to her.
Why is she--
we have to talk to her?
So that--so she stays happy.
We've got to keep...
Keep daddy happy.
She's sad right now.
She's sad right now?
Yeah, 'cause she's
in this plastic bag, huh?
- Daddy?
- Yeah?
Are you talking to me?
You're talking to the fish?
You talking to daddy the fish
or daddy your dad?
- Daddy the dad.
- Okay, yes?
What's the fish's name again?
You named it.
- Daddy.
- ( chuckles ) yeah.
That's right.
I'm gonna name her mama now.
I'm gonna name her mommy.
You'll name her mommy.
I will name her mommy!
I named her mommy, daddy.
- You did?
- Yeah.
- Mommy.
- I like the name daddy.
Let's keep it daddy, okay?
What?
Let's keep
the fish's name daddy.
Why?
'cause that was
the original name.
We should stick
with the original name.
No, mama!
Hold the fishbowl.
Hold it.
Okay, that's good.
- There she went!
- Look at her.
Give some give food.
Yeah, are you gonna feed her?
Yeah, I'm gonna feed her.
I like feeding stuff.
For sure.
- I can do it, daddy.
- Okay, just a little.
Just take just a little bit,
a little pinch. Pinch.
That's--
are those chips?
Those are fish chips.
Yeah, she's gonna love that.
See, she's eating it already.
Look, can you see?
Can you see?
- Yeah.
- ( chuckles )
- ( squeaking )
- I think you're
gonna eat me, daddy.
- I'm gonna eat you.
- No!
Don't eat me!
I'm gonna eat you,
you're fish food.
Warren (over the phone):
Hi, mark. It's warren.
I got your messages.
It's a very busy time
right now.
Yeah, no,
it's not gonna go any further
In the paul thomas
anderson project.
I'm sorry about that,
but best of luck.
All right, you take care.
Michael (over the phone):
Hey, mark.
It's Michael Cera.
How's it going, buddy?
Listen...
I just--
I did some really stupid things
And I don't know.
I can't say it on the phone,
but I need you to help me.
I need you to come down here
And pick me up
from the station.
Um, bring a change of clothes
And some hair gel, please,
and a condom.
Um, I'm just kidding.
How's it going, buddy?
I was just calling because
I'm having a game night.
A little gathering kind
of thing at my house tonight
And we're gonna play
boulder dash and we're gonna--
I'm gonna serve also
some exotic cheese
And there are gonna be
some good friends there.
Mike's gonna come,
and allie is gonna be there.
Some other people
you don't know,
But you don't have to talk
to them.
The best of you
didn't probably.
Um, but come on by, man.
It'd be fun to see you.
( doorbell dings )
Hello? Hi, come in.
- Hi.
- Hi. How are you?
- I'm good.
- I'm mark.
- Maria.
- Maria, nice to meet you.
- Do you speak english?
- ( speaks spanish )
- A little.
- Oh, good.
- He's a very good sleeper.
- Okay.
So he should sleep
the whole time.
( indistinct chatter over tv)
( sighs )
Okay.
Thank you so much.
- I will, uh,
I'll be back in two hours. Okay?
- Okay.
♪
( phone rings )
( music playing )
Hey, buddy.
Hey, come on in.
- Get in here.
- Okay.
- It's freezing out here.
- Oh, jeez.
I've got to move this plant
Every time I open the door,
it's like....
( crowd cheers )
we started--
we've got to turn it, though.
( indistinct chattering )
- Hey, buddy boy!
- How are you?
What's happening?
Oh, my fucking god,
are you kidding me?
Hi!
- Hi!
- What the fuck
are you doing here?
- Jesus christ, man.
- It's nice on a clearer night.
It's a little foggy
that you're pissed about
'cause I thought--
But, yeah, another thing,
there's no railing so...
- Jesus!
- They keep telling me
I got to put railing in,
But I'm like, you know,
don't make me.
- He's very smart.
- Did you got, like,
baby einstein show with him?
No, I made him lots
of flat seats.
- I got a little dressed up.
- Yeah, you're making me feel
like crashing as well.
- Cheers, man.
- Yeah.
- Like I haven't seen you
so long.
- I know, dude.
I think I'm gonna be doing
Paul Thomas Anderson's movie.
Uh, ryan gosling
and james franco.
- Are you fucking kidding me?
- No, man.
PT Anderson's movie.
- Man: That is incredible.
- Yeah.
- Yeah, and james franco.
With ryan gosling.
- This guy is here.
- Yeah.
- You're having red?
- You're sticking
around tonight?
- Yeah.
- Right.
- Boy, your teeth got...
- Bruised.
- ( chuckles )
That's great 'cause if you spill
on your shirt, you'll...
( piano playing )
( sighs )
Think it was like...
( piano plays )
Right?
Michael, I'm gonna get next.
- What?
- I'm gonna get next.
- Both?
- ( chuckles )
Okay, who wants to go
in the balcony?
Who wants to go take a look
at the city?
- I wanted to go to the city.
- Breathe some air.
- They only make it in melanie.
- It looked like a cheese wheel.
- Hmm.
- Ramos.
Just--
oh, so we have to split one.
- No, please.
- No.
- Don't, uh...
- I'm not going over there.
You know, crazy things
can happen here tonight
'cause there's no railing,
if you'll notice.
- Michael, stop it!
- ( chuckles )
- Man: We have a bar or, uh...
- 'cause crazy things
happen here every night.
- Woman: Absolutely.
- Everybody,
form a circle around mark.
( indistinct chattering )
- Go, go, go.
- Give her a tail.
- ( woman laughs )
- Whoo!
Okay. $2,000.
Oh, my god!
For $2,000, anyone who put--
puts this here
- And pulls the trigger.
- ( laughs )
I dare you. No, no, no.
Really think about it.
There's $2,000.
I'll give you 2,000--
There.
In fact, here's the clip.
There's the clip.
$2,000.
- No, don't do it.
- Give me 4,000.
But you have to promise me
that you'll take 10 seconds
- To think about it.
- Okay.
And we have--
no, slower, slower, slower.
Really think about it.
Let me say the password.
( laughter )
♪ I love my life
woman: We love it!
- ♪ I love my...
- Michael, no!
( indistinct chattering )
Mike, you should really spend
for a railing around here.
Yeah, $80,000.
Maybe you could spend for it.
- Really?
- And that's for
the cheapest grade of aluminum.
( laughter )
so I can't fucking do it.
And if I got one,
it couldn't not be marble.
( thuds )
That is the best way to blow
your imaginary balls out.
Does that make you
more comfortable?
- Man: There could be one
in the chamber.
- Is--is mark okay?
- Yeah, he's, uh,
getting it another.
- Why is he being sick?
- Yeah, he's...
- Not too well.
Talking about the strange one,
you know.
- Where is he? You okay, buddy?
- So yeah, I'm gonna sit down.
Hey, where are you going?
( laughs )
hey, where are you going?
- Where are you going, man?
- I was gonna sit--
I'm gonna sit down.
- I'm not gonna lay down.
- You need anything?
- You want any medicine?
- I'm fucking great.
- Water?
- No.
Just some water, dude.
- Damn. Fucking over!
- ( man hums )
- Brian.
- All night.
- Asshole.
- Unlucky charm man.
- Let me watch--
this is how you--
- You're my unlucky charm man.
- How I'm gonna get it in there?
Okay, well,
it doesn't really matter now.
No,
we haven't started boulder dash.
We're gonna play
in a few minutes.
- Do you know these people?
- No, I don't think I do.
Okay, I'll introduce you
to people.
- Hey, everyone,
this is Jocelin.
- Hi!
People are ready, yeah.
That's jo--
- You guys know Jocelin?
- Nice to meet you, guys.
- Oh, my god.
- Mark?
- Hi.
- Oh, my god!
What are you doing?
What are you doing here?
- You're really close
to this guy?
- How do you know each other?
- We...
- We know each other
from new york.
- Yeah.
- No way.
- Yeah, yeah.
- Mm-hmm.
It's been a hot minute.
Gurning,
a german wheelbarrow.
( laughter )
Gurning. Okay,
we got a lot more. A lot more.
Yearning for a gur noise.
Gurning, a ride to the hospital
on a gurney.
( laughter )
( indistinct chatter )
It could be.
Gurning, a french camera doll...
( sighs )
- Good to see you.
- It was good to see you.
It's like...
What happened with us?
I don't know. We were good.
You were so good.
I feel like I messed it up.
No, you just kind of moved.
Yeah. Yeah.
I mean, it's the right thing,
you know.
You're--you're making moves.
- Now you're here.
- Mm-hmm. ( chuckles )
Now.
I just...
Do you have a boyfriend?
I don't.
- Well, neither do I.
- You don't?
- No.
- Oh. ( laughs )
You should move out here.
Mm, well...
I know it's cliche, but I don't
know about the driving.
Hmm, you know,
that's what everybody says,
But it really is kind of nice
to see your own little bubble
And it's just kind of good to
be--have your own little bubble
And just getting your bubble
And the bubble takes you
to the next little thing
And then you--
- I like the bubble.
- Yeah?
Hmm. Hmm.
I mean, the train
is so...Stupid.
- No, it's not.
- The train is so stupid.
- Public transportation
is not stupid.
- Do you like the train?
I like the train.
- You still like the train.
- Mm-hmm.
Oh, I have something to say.
- ( laughs )
- I would say...
I love you.
How much do you love me?
Up to the room in the back.
- I love you.
- How much do you love me?
To infinity and back.
My god, I am still in love you.
- No, you're not.
- I am. I love you so much.
Where did you hear?
This is I love you.
( giggles )
oh, you don't.
Can I just kiss you one time,
please?
One time.
That didn't count.
I love you.
I've missed you.
I wish we get married.
( giggles )
Do you wanna have kids?
Whoa. ( giggles )
Not right now.
I have a kid. I have a kid.
- Hmm?
- I have a kid.
You have a kid?
- Mark, you have a kid?
- Yeah.
Since when?
Since--what?
Since...
He's 2 years.
Whoa!
I thought we we're catching up.
Yeah. What?
Oh.
I remember it, mark.
It's...Not that big a deal.
Um, it's a big deal.
- Why?
- ( sighs )
- Listen, I came out...
- Mark, it was--
No, that came out wrong.
- No, Jocelin, listen to me, I--
- no, it's just--
( sighs )
Look, it was great
to see you again, okay?
I just--
We need to talk
and actually catch up,
But...I feel weird about this.
Call me, okay?
Fuck!
Woman: Hello.
Hello.
- Hi, maria.
- ( sighs )
I am so sorry.
Hi, buddy! I've got cookies!
- I just went to the store
for the cookies.
- ( speaks spanish )
Oh.
Please, there's extra, extra.
I am so sorry.
- ( whines )
- thank you.
- Huh?
- I'm peeing my pants.
Oh, you got to pee?
Well, let's go pee.
- Thank you.
- No, I just peed.
- You just peed a little? Okay.
- ( mumbles )
All right, thank you.
- Adios.
I peed here.
You peed there?
I named her mommy.
I thought you named her daddy.
- Mommy!
- Where is the fish food?
Okay, that is too much.
That's too much.
That's...
That's a lot.
Is she eating it?
Yeah! Yeah, daddy!
She eats, daddy!
- Oh.
- She eats!
Look.
- She doesn't make noise.
- We can't really hear them.
I mean, they make noise,
but they're under water
So it's hard to hear them.
If we're underwater,
you can hear them?
- Hmm.
- We're not underwater.
Yeah.
But when they're underwater.
Hey, hey!
I'm so glad we could talk.
Do you have a minute
right now?
Okay.
Well, I just--I wanted to...
I wanted to apologize
for the other night
And I was wondering
if I can have an opportunity
To see you again today
and--and just talk.
I need you!
I need you, daddy.
I need you.
But I didn't sleep yet.
Can I sleep for five minutes?
- No!
- Please?
No!
( children frolicking )
( baby crying )
That baby's crying.
She's--her dad--
I wonder if she's okay.
Why is she crying?
I don't know.
She's upset about something.
Hey, daddy's friends are here.
- Hey, babel[ph].
- Isabel: Hi!
- How are you?
- Good.
Good. Good to see you.
- Hi. Hi, these are for you.
- Hi.
Oh, thank you. This is...
Isaac's over there.
Um, can we sit down
and talk for a second?
- Yeah.
- Okay.
Hey, isaac, lydia is here.
Hi, isaac.
You're gonna keep digging?
( laughter )
Careful. Wow!
Wow.
How's your day going?
Good. Tired.
- Yeah.
- Consumed.
( sighs )
You're just not have the energy.
- ( laughs )
- ( chuckles ) it's like--
- Uh, yeah.
- Yeah.
It's really good to see you.
I...Wanna apologize
for the other night.
I was...
I was a bit much.
Oh, it was a lot.
- I'm sorry.
- Yeah.
Okay.
I haven't been,
uh, entirely honest
With you, and, uh...
( isaac screaming )
Uh...
Hey.
Uh, when isaac was a year old,
I was, uh--
So, when he was just
about a year old,
I was sitting with him
on a the bouncing ball,
Like one of those exercise balls
in our apartment in beachwood.
Okay.
And it was really early
in the morning
And I was really upset
Because he'd been up
the whole night before.
He didn't sleep.
And his mom had to go.
Then she went to kiss me
And I didn't kiss her back
'cause I...
And she got in a car accident.
Car in the carpool lane,
Clipped the motorcycle
And the motorcycle...
Went to her lane
and her car flipped...
And then snapped her neck
and she died on impact.
Daddy,
I'm digging for treasure.
I'm digging for treasure!
( sighs )
So, I'm a mess
and, uh...
I shouldn't touch you
with 10-foot pole.
- ( chuckles )
- yeah.
( snoring )
( gasps )
- Hey.
- Sorry.
- Sorry to wake you.
- Sorry, are you gonna watch tv?
- No, no, no.
- Oh.
Okay, what's up, man?
Shit.
Oh, what time is it?
Okay.
- Some news, I just needed
to tell you right away.
- What's going on?
Um, I found someone else
to--to take your room,
So I have to have you out
by the end of the month.
I'm really sorry, mark.
It's just, everything,
it's too much.
Why, I--I told you I was getting
everything sort a bit.
I know, man,
but I just can't afford it.
We'll help you,
whatever you need.
Okay, well,
this isn't...Helping me.
This isn't helpful.
I -I told you
that I'm getting money together.
You owe me so much money, man.
It's not happening.
I have to, you know,
so I could come pay the rent.
You're gonna kick me
and isaac out in the street?
Come on, man.
I feel fucked up already.
- If there's anything--
- this is fucking ridiculous,
man!
You can't just
fucking kick me out.
We don't--we don't wanna do this
but...
Yeah,
but you're fucking doing it.
I mean, you guys, you got
to give me a fucking chance
- To give you the money that
I said I was gonna give you.
- It's been months.
Months, mark.
I've paid your rent
out of my own pocket.
You have the rest
of the month, man.
You got, like,
I don't know, two weeks.
I can't believe
you guys are doing this.
Maybe we could find
some place more--
You know, maybe some place
more affordable for you,
Even better for--for isaac.
You're a fucking piece of shit.
And you're fucking piece
of shit!
( bell rings )
( isaac mumbling )
( mumbling )
( shushes ) we're just gonna
take a little drive.
( crying )
( shushes )
it's okay.
( crying continues )
It's okay. ( shushes )
It's okay.
You don't have to go.
Shut the fuck up!
- Where are you going?
- ( crying )
( shushes )
- We're going out.
- ( crying continues )
( shushes )
- It's okay.
- Stop it!
- ( shushes )
- no!
No! ( crying )
We'll go, uh, night picnic,
okay?
( breathing heavily )
Big crack.
What?
Yeah.
What's a big crack?
- There was a big crack there.
- Where?
When we stepped over.
Where?
Right back over there.
You see?
Look at the moon.
You see the moon out there?
We're gonna go camping tonight.
- This is my tent.
- Yeah.
This is really cool right here,
huh?
- ( mumbles )
- yeah.
I think we could sleep out here,
huh?
What do you think?
Let's try it.
Yeah, get on the pillow.
Yeah.
Here you go, bud.
( babbling )
I don't know if this is
such a good idea, isaac.
( sighs )
( fins flaps )
( grunts )
( sobs )
goddamn!
( sobbing )
Mark: ♪ a super duper, duper
duper, duper bubble bath ♪
♪ super duper, duper, duper
duper bubble bath ♪
♪ a super duper, duper, duper
- ♪ a super duper, duper, duper
duper bubble bath ♪
- ( chuckles )
Why did you take them out?
Because--I took them out
so you can put them back in.
- ( chuckles )
- but first,
I need to turn on the water.
- Not the--not the bubble bath.
- Uh!
( chuckles )
Isaac: My fish
doesn't feel good anymore.
Mark:
Something happened to her.
What?
It's called dying.
What's dying?
Dying are when things
stop living.
You see, she's not moving.
Why?
Why, dada?
There's something called life
And something called death.
Do you know
what those things are?
- Mm-hmm.
- You do?
Can you tell me
what you think those things are?
It's when you don't feel good.
Mm-hmm, that's close.
Me and you are alive.
All the trees
and plants outside
And the animals
are alive, too.
- The tree is alive?
- Yeah, the trees outside
are alive.
- Houses are alive?
- No, houses aren't alive.
- Why?
- Well, houses are just things.
And when you stop living,
it's called dying.
Animals die and people die
and plants die.
Why people die?
Sometimes they get sick.
Sometimes they have an accident.
And the fish had an accident.
And when things die,
they go some place else.
Where?
Some in there
and your finger here.
There we go.
There, you did it.
Oh.
She's sad.
There you go, dada.
Thank you.
What is that for?
And what this little thing is,
is called a coffin.
And sometimes,
what people do when things die
Is they bury them in the ground.
Where we gonna bury.
Are we going to bury something?
- Mm-hmm.
- Are we gonna bury our fish?
Yeah, we're gonna bury the fish.
- In what?
- In the dirt.
- But there's no dirt in here.
- I know.
We have to go some place
to do that.
( humming )
It looks pretty good.
Okay.
Oh.
♪ take me
♪ make me
♪ empty inside
♪ hold me tight
♪ I'm too weak
♪ baby
♪ only wanna lose control
♪ melt with you
We are finished.
You got a little bit more
to do?
Mm-hmm.
Cover that hole.
Hmm, go for it.
♪ for a moment in time
( mumbles )
♪ let me forget
I--what shall we do?
♪ my distrust
- ( laughing, mumbles )
- ah!
♪ kill the demons
♪ make them weep
♪ clean the mirror
♪ make me see
♪ myself in a different way
Whoa.
♪ wanna taste your sweetness
♪ in my bitter tea
- Mark: Thank you.
- Isaac: Came from that tree.
( laughs )
♪ take my frightened heart
♪ and let it blossom
♪ into a star
♪ give all my fear
♪ to the wind
♪ with your skin
♪ soft and warm
♪ baby
♪ high
♪ higher than the black sky
♪ through the stars
♪ I'll learn to fly
♪ will I, will I
♪ get to say good-bye?
♪ above
♪ above all the fear
♪ we go, ooh
♪ where love it fades
♪ like a rainbow
♪ will I, will I
♪ get to say good-bye?
♪ I understand
♪ that I'm going away
♪ far away from here
♪ but please
♪ understand
♪ that I won't be gone
♪ alone
♪ we, we're here
♪ so don't cry
♪ all, all the pirates
♪ and I
♪ will I, will I
♪ get to say good-bye?