No way.
Come on up.
Feed the clowns, lady.
For $3, everybody wins a prize.
Feed 'em up.
Here, hon. Here, hon.
Feed those clowns!
Hey, here, boys.
Come here, boys.
All right!
Hey, lover boy!
Quit eyein' up the jills.
Go get ready!
Keep moving, missy.
Right this way...
Hey, hey, hey.
All right.
No, thank you.
The road to excitement
starts right through
these doors.
The world's strongest man!
And jugglers!
The terrifying face mangler!
Unicyclists and our main acts,
which you have to see
to believe.
Can you feel the heat,
ladies and gentlemen?
Prepare to be amazed,
terrified.
Titillated and amused.
From all corners of the globe,
the deepest jungles,
the driest deserts,
the highest mountains,
we've got you
the best of the best,
the greatest of the great,
the most marvelous
of all the marvels.
Our jugglers were trained in
the royal courts of the czars.
Our beauties were chosen
from the finest
Europe has to offer.
So sit back,
relax,
and get ready
for Circus Marvelous!
And now, ladies and gentlemen,
the moment you've
all been waiting for.
No noise.
No photographs.
Let your heads and minds fly
with a man
who defies gravity.
Who defies science.
Who defies your imagination.
Our one,
our only
death-defying.
Lady-sighing.
Trapeze-flying
aerialist!
Look!
Yeah!
Him?
Do you know him?
Have you seen...
Hi!
Help!
Mia!
Mia?