Britain and America.
Two great nations,
linked throughout history.
We discovered America,
even though it was already there.
We deliberately let you win
the War of Independence,
because you threatened to cry
if we didn't.
And you very kindly joined us
for the last few minutes
of the Second World War,
for which we thank you.
But what about the people
of these two great nations?
How are we alike?
How are we different?
Let's find out
as Little Britain comes to the USA.
We begin our cross-cultural
examination here,
on the Gulf Coast of Mississippi,
where British tourist, Lou,
is taking his friend Andy
on an American vacation.
I got you! I got you! I got you!
Oh, Mr Cab Driver,
could you help me with the...?
I need to use the toilet.
Can you hold on?
We'll be in the room in a minute.
- I wanna go now!
- In a minute!
Hello there,
do you have areservation
under the name Todd?
- Lou Todd?
- Todd?
Yes, that's my name, Lou Todd.
Or it could be under my
friend's name, Andy Pipkin.
- I have a Todd here.
- Excellent.
And now is it a first floor room?
- I don't have first floor.
- I did ask for a first floor room.
Well, I'm sorry,
I got second floor,
a man's coming to fix the elevator
on Monday, I believe, so...
I guess I'll be having to
carry him up those stairs myself.
Thank you for your help, sir.
Right!
Here we go!
Oh, look, Andy,
they've got a pool here,
you can have a swim in there later.
Nah! I bet people piss in it.
The British pride themselves
on being the rudest, most unhelpful
people in the world.
Receptionist Carol Beer is working
at this hospital in Pennsylvania.
Hello!
This is my daughter,
she's a big, brave girl
and she's gonna have an operation today.
Name?
- Tell the nice lady your name.
- Danielle.
Danielle what?
Danielle Lloyd.
Age?
Nearly six.
You're five!
Well, say five then.
Address?
Where do you live?
With Mommy and Daddy.
1772 Lincoln Road.
We got there!
Just putting your details in now.
Danielle's going to have
her tonsils removed.
I've got her down
for a double hip replacement.
Oh, no, there must be
some kind of mistake.
Computer says no!
Well, that must be some
other Danielle Lloyd.
Computer says no!
There's only one Danielle Lloyd
on the system.
Do you want the
double hip replacement, or not?
No! Clearly she doesn't need it!
Well, she may do in the future.
Look, we saw Dr Phillips last week
and she definitely has an appointment
for today to have her tonsils removed.
Computer says no!
Well, could you speak with somebody?
I could, but...
Well, thank you so much.
You've been just great.
Could I borrow
a moment of your time
to fill out the customer
service questionnaire?
Would you say that I've been:
a) very helpful,
b) extremely helpful
or c) fucking helpful?
In America,
a child is born every eight seconds.
Oh, that poor woman
must be exhausted!
You're gonna have a great time
at Brownie camp, Ellie-Grace.
I'm so excited,
but I'm really gonna miss you, Mom,
because I love you so much.
I love you too, Ellie-Grace.
I love you more than Gummi Bears!
I love you more than puppy dogs!
No, I love you more than smiles!
I love you more than raindrops.
I love you more
than transsexual porn!
Miss Ellie-Grace!!
Where did you hear that?
Julie's older brother said
he saw some on the internet.
Oh, did he that?
Yes, Mommy, on a site
called chickswithdicks.com.
I'm gonna have a word
with Julie's mom.
OK, everyone on board now, please.
You'd better get on the bus
before it leaves, Ellie-Grace.
I love you more than kittens!
I love you more than roses!
I love you more than cotton-candy!
I love you more than cumshot!
There are more fat people in America
than there are people.
That's why weight-loss instructor,
Marjorie Dawes,
has come from Britain
to dispense some dietary advice.
Hello, fatties!
Lovely to see you.
Now, those of you who read
the Fat Fighters Newsletter
will be aware that Fat Fighters
has a new spokesperson,
and we are very lucky because
she's paying a visit
to our branch tonight!
So, will you please give
a very warm
Fat Fighters welcome
to Rosie O'Donnell?
- Nice to see you.
- Take a seat.
- Thank you.
Lovely! So, Rosie O'Donnell!
So, Rosie-O.
Just Rosie.
- Rosie? Rosie, Rosie.
- Rosie.
So, Rosie, I've been reading
all about you
in the Fat Fighters Newsletter.
I know you had
your own talk show.
Until Ellen DeGeneres
filled your slot.
And then...
And then it says here...
It says here also that you've been
in some movies.
League Of Their Own,
The Flintstones...
What's this one?
Sleepless In Seattle? I've seen it,
I don't remember you in it,
but we'll take your word for it. And...
It says here that you are a lesbian,
and there's absolutely
nothing wrong with that.
Thank you very much, Marjorie.
Now, Rosie. You... And I know
you won't mind me saying it...
you have had issues with your weight.
- I have.
- You have. She has!
She's big.
She's a big lady.
She's a big, lesbian lady.
Well, Marjorie, here in America,
a lot of us have weight issues,
it affects...
Are you fat because you're a lesbian,
or are you a lesbian because you're fat?
What does that mean?
What do you mean by that?
I mean, did you find it hard
to get a man because of the weight,
and then you think,
"Maybe I'll go lessie,"
- or...
- Marjorie, Marjorie, no, no!
Personally,
I think that you're born gay,
but I'm proud of who I am, I'm a lesbian
woman, I'm in a relationship,
my partner and I have four
beautiful children, so...
Thank you, thank you very much.
She must have bought those
in Africa.
But, you know, Marjorie,
I'm actually here to talk about weight,
so could we just maybe
talk about that?
- Please?
- Yes! Yes!
Yes! Could we just stick
to weight, please?
Thank you.
OK, so let's open it up to the group.
Who's got a question for Rosie?
But can we just not go on about
her sexuality, please?
- Thank you.
- Let's just stick to why she's so fat.
Anna.
Lost cause.
- Hello, Rosie.
- Hey, Anna! Hi.
Do you have any advice
for people like me who are on
different diets year after year
and never seem to lose any weight?
You know, the important thing, Anna,
is that you're healthy and happy.
Are you happy with your size?
- Well...
- No, she's not. She's very fat, Rosie.
I am happy with my size.
Well, good for you!
That's great and you're beautiful.
She's not a lesbian, Rosie.
Right, let's think.
Another question.
Yes, my illegal friend, yes.
I often find I'm doing
really good with my diet,
and then I go on myself
and buy a big bar of chocolate.
Rosie, what's your weakness?
- Well...
- Couldn't understand a word!
Sorry, Rosie, I should have
warned you, she's Philippino.
- Mexican!
- Same thing, innit?
Let's have another question.
Let's have one from the
morbidly obese contingent.
Yes, the dangerously
fat man over there.
OK, you know what, Marjorie, I really
cannot believe how you treat people!
You're absolutely rude!
You're homophobic! You're racist!
You're meant to help these people
and you keep ridiculing them
about their size! It's disgusting!
And licking another
woman's vagina isn't?
One thing Americans
can be very proud of
is that they have
more death from firearms
than any other country in the world.
The standard issue gun
for anyone
in the Sheriff's department
is a Colt 45.
It's a simple blow-back pistol,
with a single action trigger.
It's a good gun.
The Winchester 70,
this is a bolt-action rifle,
which we'd use for
long-range coverage.
Sure is a big heavy one,
but it shoots a good load.
As you've probably realised,
this is a machine-gun,
the Bushmaster A3.
You really gotta know what to do when
you hold a big powerful weapon like this
or it'll spray everywhere.
And finally, I thought y'all might
like to see one of my own guns.
I've got a small personal
collection of 2,000 guns.
This...
is the Barrett 50 calibre,
the biggest semi-automatic weapon
you can buy.
It's a beast!
I'm completely bored of guns now,
I need to go and do something
totally different.
One thing that's currently
all the rage with teenagers,
on both sides of the Atlantic,
is Grandmas.
They're the latest must-have
fashion accessory.
Those who don't have
their own Grandma
can bid for one on eBay.
Now, what's all this your Mama
tells me about you being caught
- smoking cigarettes?
- I was just trying it.
Connor, cigarettes
are very bad for you.
You used to smoke.
Sure, when I was your age,
we all smoked.
Used to say smoking was good for you,
we didn't know any different.
I'm sorry, Grandma.
Same with that cocaine,
we just didn't know,
we thought it was a pick-me-up.
I used to go around all day
hoovering up the booger sugar.
- You took cocaine?
- Oh, sure!
And heroin.
Yeah, you used to get home
from church on a Sunday
and your Grandpappy used to say,
"Mildred, let's chase that dragon!"
We used to spend the rest of
the week out of our tiny minds.
I never knew people
took drugs in them days.
There's a lot you don't know!
I've still got my old
crack pipe somewhere.
Your Aunt Dorothy gave it
to me for my 18th birthday.
Aunt Dorothy gave you a crack pipe?
Sure she did!
She even had it engraved:
"My face is on fire, yours, Dorothy."
How could you take that stuff,
Grandma?
We didn't know it was bad for you!
Every morning we used to cook up
that crystal meth,
we thought it was like
having a glass of milk.
Is there anything you
didn't take in them days?
Now let me see,
I did MDMA,
acid, GHB,
magic mushrooms, glue, mescaline,
poppers, Quaaludes,
angel dust.
You ever smoke pot?
Pot's for pussies!
Wow!
You've lived some life, Grandma.
Considering you've taken all them drugs,
you don't look too bad on it.
I'm 28!
The Scouting movement
is very popular in America,
though it was started in Britain
by Lord Baden-Powell,
who was keen to justify his hobby
of sharing a tent
with young boys in uniform.
This Scout pack is playing host
to retired astronaut:
Bing Gordon.
One small step for man,
one giant leap for Bing Gordon!
I'm on the moon!
I'm on the Goddamn moon!
So one day,
you can all tell your grandkids
that you met Bing Gordon,
the 8th man on the moon.
Thank you, Bing, I'm sure we will.
OK, Pack, does anyone
have any questions?
- Put your hands up, please. Nathan.
- How many people been to the moon?
Nine men have been
to the moon, no women.
I was the 8th.
And I'm also the only man with
a moustache to have been to the moon,
so, in a way,
I can say I'm the first man
on the moon who had a moustache.
Yes, Bradley.
Have you ever met Neil Armstrong?
Yeah, I know Neil,
but he's kind of a bore.
You know,
"I was the first man on the moon!"
Get over it! Move on!
Yeah, you, freaky-looking boy.
What's Buzz Aldrin like
in real life?
Bitter!
- Is he?
- Yeah, I actually trained at NASA
with Neil and Buzz.
I was passed over for the first moon
mission, but I've gotten over it.
Maybe I would have been first
if I'd given the Head of NASA a blowjob.
- That's not really appropriate here.
- Well, it's true.
Does anyone know the name
on the Apollo 11?
Yeah, I do, Michael Collins.
Right.
- What's he doing now?
- Who cares?
He didn't even get out of
he freakin' spaceship thing,
he just sat there,
scratching his ass.
I actually got out
and had a walk around, OK?
Now, as far as I know,
and correct me if I'm wrong,
I'm the only guy here who's done that.
Have you walked on the moon?
Have you...
... rode on the moon?
No! Hands up anyone here
who's been to the moon.
Just me!
George!
You have a question.
Have you been to any other planets?
First up, the moon is not a planet.
That's why it's called the moon,
it's a moon, the moon.
Second, no-one has been
to any other planet,
so it's not like I'm not the first guy
not to do that, OK?
Third, I went to the moon, OK?
I went there!
I don't know why,
it's real boring, there's no TV,
no stores, no restaurants, you can't
even get a decent cup of coffee.
There's shit-all there,
but I went, to the moon!
Thank you very much, Bing Gordon!
Moon!
Now, before you go,
we would like to present you
with something special.
In recognition of your achievement
in space exploration,
Webster Grove Pack 315
would like to present you
with the Cub Scout Explorer Badge.
What a great honour!
You're an asshole!
The number one pet in America today
is the dog,
which is very much in demand
with those who enjoy
picking up animal excrement.
It's a little bit chilly today,
isn't it, Mr Doggy?
Oh, yes, Mommy.
Maybe...
Mommy needs to buy Mr Doggy
a little doggy coat
to keep Mr Doggy nice and warm.
Oh, yes, Mommy,
that would be wonderful.
I do love you so much.
And I love you too, Mr Doggy.
Take off your clothes.
Excuse me?
I said, take off your clothes.
No, Mr Doggy, it's cold
and you're not allowed
to take your clothes off in public
or they take you away
and lock you up.
I said take 'em off.
Now, listen, Mr Doggy,
Mummy's had quite enough
of your silly ideas,
you're going to get Mummy
into trouble.
- Take 'em off!
- No!
If you love me, you'd do it.
Oh, well.
Very quickly then.
This is awfully embarrassing!
Happy now?
No. Go and stand in the trash.
Certainly not!
I won't tell you again.
Is this what you wanted?
Why on earth would anyone
want you to do that?
Lady, you're outta your fuckin' mind!
Move outta the trash, please.
Come on, lady.
- My dog!
- I'm not with her!
She is one crazy bitch!
More and more British people are
spending their holidays in America.
We enjoy the food, the weather
and the fact that the dollar
is now worthless.
Happy anniversary!
40 glorious years!
Nice hotel, isn't it?
Food will be along any minute, so...
Oh, here it comes!
Oh, no, somebody else's.
Nice cutlery, innit?
40 years.
40 years of this, hey?
Oh, here it comes.
Hello there, that must be yours
and putting mine down there, yeah.
Don't go!
Looks very nice, doesn't it?
And all the food's been nice,
hasn't it, really?
Might have a bit of the old beef,
putting that on the fork now
and in it goes.
Bit of a pause there while I chew.
Think I might have a bit of the old
mash now, the old mashed potato.
Putting it on the old fork,
using the knife to balance it
on the fork and in it goes.
Shorter pause on that occasion,
less need to chew.
So...
Help me out here,
you boring old cow!
People in Britain like to keep fit
by taking long walks
and regular masturbation.
Whereas in America,
people like to attend gyms,
like this one.
Incredible workout!
Incredible workout.
So, did you close the deal
with that girl, last night?
Which one?
- The one you were with last night.
- Mo?
The one you says looks like Gisele.
She is exactly like her, man.
She's black
and four foot six.
But people ask her if she's
Gisele Bundchen, like, all the time.
Nice.
Double nice.
So this black dwarf Gisele look-alike?
- You gave it to her?
- She got it.
She got it good,
I gave it to her so hard.
I pounded her, man!
Pounded her.
I pounded her
for like nealy a minute.
I had sex last month.
On your own or with someone else?
With a woman.
I love sex with a woman.
- It's one of my favourite kinds.
- Me too.
I gave it to her,
I gave it to her real good.
She couldn't walk
when I was done with her.
- She's the one in a wheelchair?
- That's the one, yeah.
Man, she got it, she got it good.
I bent her over, I was like,
"Can you take this, yeah?"
"Can you take this bitch?"
What are you looking at?
Nothing.
What are you?
A fag?
No.
Hey, man, I'm going to the beach.
- Can you do my bikini line?
- Sure.
That guy is still looking.
Fruit.
And so, our cultural exchange
is at an end.
But what have we learnt?
Well, that although the people
of our two great nations
have many differences,
we also have many differences.
Join us next time
when we'll do more finding out
<>about Britain and America that,
and we'll carry on learning about all
that sort of stuff and what have you.
Goodbye!
Transcript: chocolate
Subtitles: Benj!