- HONOR, INTEGRITY, ENTHUSIASM,
COURAGE UNDER FIRE,
A DECENT THROWING ARM--
THOSE ARE ATTRIBUTESYOU KIDS ARE GONNA NEED--
ALL RIGHT, THAT'STHE ENTHUSIASM PART, BRYCE,
BUT WE HAVEN'TACTUALLY STARTED YET.
WHEN I BLOW THIS WHISTLE...
ALL RIGHT, GAME ON.
- MADRE MARIA, JESUS, EL SENOR,
YOU GUYS ARE NOT GETTING IT,OKAY?
IT'S PRONOUNCED "MADRITH,"NOT MADRID,
AND I'M GONNA NEEDTO HEAR THAT "TH."
HERE'S AN EXAMPLE.
MARITHA, THANCHO, ANDMI BITHABUELO, THANTIAGO.
- NOBODY TALKS THAT LIKE, BUD.
- CORRECTION, EVERYBODY IN SPAINTALKS LIKE THAT, BUD.
HEY, CLASS, POP QUIZ.
WHAT HAPPENED IN SPAIN AGAIN?ANYBODY REMEMBER?
I DO.
THE ENTIRE LANGUAGEWAS INVENTED THERE,
NOT BY THE AZTECS,LIKE YOU THOUGHT.
I KNOW YOU GUYS THINKTHAT BECAUSE YOU WERE TAUGHT
A BASTARDIZED VERSIONOF THIS BEAUTIFUL DIALECT
YOU GONNA BE ABLETO SKATE THROUGH THIS CLASS.
BUT IN HERE, IN MY ROOM,WE SPEAK THE QUEEN'S SPANISH,
AND THAT MEANS VOSOTROS.
- YOU'RE A QUEEN, MARICON.
- OKAY, SEE, I JUST HEARDSOMEONE CALL ME A BUTTERFLY,
SO GRATHIAS!
- YEAH, I KNOW IT'S HOT, GUYS.
I'M THE ONE THAT TURNED UPTHE HEAT AND LOCKED THE DOORS.
I WANT YOU GUYS TO UNDERSTANDTHE WORKING CONDITIONS
THAT THESE MEN HAD TO ENDURE.
OH, BETH, I'M SORRY, SWEETHEART,DO YOU HAVE TO USE THE RESTROOM?
- YEAH.
- I THINK YOU SHOULD PROBABLYCHECK WITH YOUR BOSS MAN
DOWN AT THE MINE TO SEEIF THAT'S ALL RIGHT.
HEY, BOSS MAN,COULD BETH USE THE BATHROOM?
- OH, I'M SORRY, BETH,
THAT LOOKS LIKE THAT'S A BIG NO.
TAKE YOUR SEAT!
- THERE YOU GO.
- WOW, YOU READ ALL OF THESEIN ONE NIGHT?
- YEAH, I DID.THOSE BOOKS RULE.
HIGH-FIVE LITERACY, HUH?- ALL RIGHT.
- THAT'S WHAT I'M TALKING ABOUT.
HOW SEXISM KEPTTHE FIRST WOMAN OUT OF SPACE.
- HAVE YOU READ THAT ONE?IT'S SO UNFAIR.
YOU'LL BURN YOUR BRA.
- ARE YOU JUSTCHECKING OUT BOOKS
THAT YOU THINK WILL IMPRESS ME?
- NO, ARE YOU KIDDING ME?THIS IS THE STUFF I'M INTO NAT--
WHY, IS IT--DID IT IMPRESS YOU?
- YEAH.OH, YEAH.
BIG TIME.
- IF I WAS TRYINGTO IMPRESS YOU,
IT'D PROBABLY BE SOMETHING ALONGTHE LINES OF, LIKE,
A COUPLE PITCHERS OF MARGARITAS,SOME KARAOKE.
I DO EMINEM; YOU DO LIZ PHAIR,WHATEVER YOU'RE INTO.
- IS THAT WHATYOU REALLY FIND IMPRESSIVE?
- I FIND ALL SORTSOF THINGS IMPRESSIVE.
THAT WATCH IS IMPRESSIVE.- THANK YOU.
- HOW DOES A WATCH WORK?THAT'S IMPRESSIVE TO ME.
- I THINK YOU NEEDTO GET TO CLASS.
- WELL, THAT'S COOL.
I'LL JUST TAKE THESE, AND WE'LLJUST TALK ABOUT THEM TOMORROW.
SOUND GOOD?- OKAY.
- SWING AND A MISS, FAGGOT.
- WELL, YOU KNOWWHAT THEY SAY, BRYCE,
THE MOST HOMOPHOBIC PEOPLEARE THOSE TRYING THE HARDEST
TO COVER THEIROWN HOMOSEXUAL TENDENCIES.
- DID YOUR HUSBANDTEACH YOU THAT, LOREN?
- ALL RIGHT,NOW YOU LISTEN TO ME, BRYCE,
I'VE HAD MORE PUSSY THAN YOU'VEHAD WET DREAMS ABOUT, BRAH.
SO WHY DON'T YOU CALL ME WHENYOUR RIGHT TESTICLE DESCENDS?
SHOULDN'T BE TOO HARDTO FIND ME.
JUST LOOK FOR THE BIGGEST CABINON PUSSY LAKE, BITCH.
YOU TOO, TALL BITCH.
OH, PRINCIPAL QUINN, HEY.- OKAY.
- HOW--HOW LONG YOU BEENSTANDING THERE, BARRY?
- LONG ENOUGH TO PRETENDI DIDN'T JUST HEAR THAT.
- THAT'S COOL.
I'M PRETENDING I DIDN'T JUST SAY THAT.
SO WE'RE ON THE SAME PAGE.
- CAN I TALK TO YOUFOR A SECOND, MR. PAYTON?
- ALL RIGHT, MAN.- JUST RIGHT OVER HERE.
- YEAH.- OKAY.
YOU KNOW, LOREN, I LOOK AT YOU,
AND I JUST SEE THIS CLOUDOF NEGATIVE ENERGY
BUILDING INSIDE THERE.
AND I SEE YOU TAKINGTHAT NEGATIVE ENERGY,
AND I SEE YOU THROWING ITAT YOUR STUDENTS.
BRYCE BEING A PRIMARY EXAMPLERIGHT NOW.
- BRYCE DESERVING IT.
- I WANT TO FREE THAT UP.
I WANT TO GETTHAT NEGATIVE ENERGY OUT.
I WANT TO CHURN ITINTO SOME ICE CREAM--
SOME POSITIVE ICE CREAM.
AND YOU DO THAT
BY TAKING MY 90-MINUTE,FACULTY-ONLY YOGA CLASS.
- BARRY, I WAS TALKING TO PEOPLEON THE FACULTY.
THAT CLASS WAS 180 MINUTES.
YOU HAVE NO CONCEPT OF TIME.
THE FACT THAT IT WAS HOT YOGA.
OTHERWISE, WE HAD A LOT OF FUN,OKAY?
- ALL RIGHT.
- A LOT OF TEACHERS HAD TO GOTO THE HOSPITAL.
AND YOU KNOW HOW THEY CAME OUTOF THE HOSPITAL?
FEELING BETTER.- OKAY.
- YOU KNOW AT THE ENDOF THIS YEAR,
I GOT TO GET RIDOF SOME TEACHERS, RIGHT?
QUITE A BIT.- I KNOW.
- AND I ASSUME, LIKE ME,
YOU PROBABLY DON'T WANTYOUR NAME ON THAT LIST.
- NO, I DON'T WANT MY NAMEON THAT LIST, BARRY.
- OKAY, SO LET'S WORK ON THISTO TRY TO MAKE SURE
THAT DOESN'T HAPPEN.
- I CAN DO THAT.I CAN GIVE YOU THAT.
- YOU KNOW WE'RE FRIENDS, RIGHT?
- I WOULDN'T CALL US FRIENDS,BARRY.
- BUDS, PALS, IT'S ALL THE SAME.YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN?
- IT'S NOT ALL THE SAME.- CHUMS.
- WE'VE KNOWN EACH OTHERFOR A WHILE.
THAT'S IT.- I'D SAY THAT'S FRIENDSHIP.
- OKAY, THEN YEAH, FINE, BARRY,WE'RE FRIENDS.
- YOU KNOW WHAT FRIENDS DO--THEY SQUEEZE EACH OTHER.
- FRIENDS DO NOT SQUEEZEEACH OTHER.
- COME HERE, COME HERE.- BARRY, EVERY--
- GET 'EM UP. GET 'EM UP.I'M THE POLICE. I'M KIDDING.
PRINCIPAL QUINN.GET IN HERE.
- HA, DUTY.
DIDN'T ANY OF YOU THINKTO ASK YOUR COMMANDING OFFICERS
WHY YOU WERE EVEN OUT THERETO BEGIN WITH?
YOU WERE A PUPPETFOR THE OLIGARCHY.
- DON'T YOU TALK TO MEABOUT DUTY, ALL RIGHT?
I WAS CALLING IN AIR STRIKESON THE HIGHWAY OF DEATH
WHILE YOU WERE STILL JACKING OFFYOUR LITTLE PECKER
TO J.C. PENNEY CATALOGS.
- REAL NICE.
I'M SURE YOU WERE A WONDERFULAMBASSADOR FOR THIS COUNTRY
SITTING ON TOP OF A TANK,OLD BEARDED HELL.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
- I GOT TO TAKE THIS.- WHAT IS THAT?
- YEAH, THIS ONE'S IMPORTANT.
- OH, HOW MUCH ARE YOU GONNA--- THE WHOLE CALL.
- YOU SMELL LIKE JIMMY BUFFETT.
- CHEESEBURGER IN PARADISE, PINKO.
- NOT AT ALL.
DODGEBALL AGAIN, HUH?- YUP.
- WHY DO YOU STILL CONTINUETO TEACH THAT?
- WELL, IT TEACHESA LITTLE THING
CALLED "SOCIAL HIERARCHIE," BEN.
I THINK YOU OF ALL PEOPLECOULD APPRECIATE THAT.
- I APPRECIATE THE FACT
YOU TAKE THE JESTER ROLEIN THAT HIERARCHY.
- WELL, THANK YOU.
THAT BRYCE TURNER'SA PSYCHOPATH.
- WAIT, BRYCE DID THAT TO YOU?- YEAH.
- DUDE, THAT LITTLE FUCKERGOT ME IN TROUBLE
AT THE LIBRARY EARLIER TODAY.
PRINCIPAL QUINN REMINDED MEABOUT THE STAFF CUTS AGAIN.
- WELL, I DON'T HAVE ANYTHINGTO WORRY ABOUT.
P.E. AND HOME EC.ARE WHAT WE CALL "LIFE SKILLS."
- PLEASE, DUDE,YOU'LL BE THE FIRST TO GO.
- YEAH, SAYS THE GUYWHO TEACHES SPANISH
TO SPANISH-SPEAKING STUDENTS.
- IT'S A CORE CREDIT,SHIT FOR BRAINS.
- NOW, HISTORYON THE OTHER HAND--
THAT'S INDISPENSIBLE.
- YEAH, NOT THE HISTORY WHEREYOU BREAK A KID'S COLLARBONE
THROWING DESKS AROUND.
- HEY, YOU WANT TO TEACH KIDSABOUT SLAVE INSURRECTION,
YOU GOT TO CRACK A FEW EGGS.
- OR JUST A BOOK, HENRY ROLLINS.
- ALL I KNOW IS THAT BRYCE
IS GONNA GETWHAT'S COMING TO HIM ONE DAY,
'CAUSE I'LL BE THE ONEHOLDING THE DODGEBALL.
- YEAH,NOT IF I GET TO HIM FIRST.
- WELL, I HAVE THE KEYSTO THE ATHLETIC SUPPLY CLOSET.
- YEAH, OR HOW ABOUT THIS, GUYS?
HOW ABOUT YOU TWOCOULD ACT LIKE ADULTS
AND NOT LET A 16-YEAR-OLD CHILDGET UNDERNEATH YOUR SKIN?
HOW ABOUT THAT?
- HE WHO SEEKS REVENGEDIGS TWO GRAVES.
- DOES SHE MEAN, LIKE,A GRAVE FOR HERSELF?
- I--I DON'T KNOW,BUT SHE WEIRDS ME OUT.
I'M--I'M GONNA GET OUT OF HERE,GUYS.
I'LL SEE YOU TOMORROW.
- HEY, YOU WANT TO GO CHECK THELOST AND FOUND FOR COOL HATS?
- YEAH, I NEED SUNGLASSES TOO.- RACE YOU.
- ALL RIGHT,NO CHEATING THIS TIME.
- NO CHEATING THIS TIME.ONE...
TWO, THREE.
- BRYCE, BRYCE, BRYCE, BRYCE!
BRYCE, BRYCE, BRYCE, BRYCE!
- BABY?- HUH, WHAT'S UP?
- WHAT IS THAT?- WHAT IS WHAT?
- THAT NOISE.
- OH, HANG ON.WHAT IS THAT?
WHAT IS THAT?
AW, YOU LITTLE SONS OF--
OH, YOU WANT TO PLAY WITH FIRE?
I'M COMING FOR YOULITTLE BASTARDS.
SONS OF BITCHES.
WHAT THE HELL ARE YOUDOING OUT HERE, BRYCE?
OH, YOU S--
ALL RIGHT, I WANT YOU TO KNOWTHAT I KNOW WHAT'S INSIDE THIS.
AND I'M ONLY STEPPING ON IT
'CAUSE I DON'T OWNA FIRE EXTINGUISHER.
OH, DAMN, I'M COVERED WITH SHITALL OVER MY FUCKING--GOD!
- FUCK YOU, SHOEMAKER!
- ALL RIGHT,LET'S GET THIS FUCKER.
- SEE, I TOLD YOUHE WOULD COME AROUND.
- YEAH, WHY THE SUDDEN CHANGEOF HEART, MR. MATURE?
- WHAT, CAN'T A GUYBACK HIS PALS?
- OH, BOTH OF YOUSHUT UP, SHUT UP.
IT'S HAPPENING AGAIN.
- ANYWAY, IF WE'RE GONNAHIT THIS KID,
WE GOT TO HIT HIMWHERE IT HURTS.
- EXACTLY WHATI'M TALKING ABOUT.
AND WHAT DOES BRYCE LOVEMORE THAN ANYTHING?
LACROSSE.
AND WHAT CAN'TLACROSSE PLAYERS DO?
- PLAY BASEBALL?- HAVE CONSENSUAL SEX?
- BOTH GOOD GUESSES.THE ANSWER IS DRUGS.
STUDENT ATHLETES HAVETO BE DRUG-FREE.
SO IF SOMEBODY JUST HAPPENEDTO GET BUSTED WITH DRUGS...
- SO WHAT, I COVER A RAGIN CHLOROFORM, KNOCK HIM OUT,
STUFF HIM FULL OF DRUGS,
AND THEN MARIA FULL OF GRACE HIMACROSS THE BORDER?
- JESUS CHRIST, SHOEMAKER.NO, WE PUT DRUGS IN HIS LOCKER.
- YEAH, I'M PICKIN' UPWHAT YOU'RE PUTTIN' DOWN.
- WELL, THAT'S GOOD, 'CAUSE I'MPUTTING IT DOWN PRETTY THICK.
THE ONLY PROBLEM'SGETTING THE ACTUAL DRUGS.
- I CAN GET DRUGS.
- WE'RE NOT TALKING ABOUT
YOUR BLOOD PRESSUREMEDICATION HERE, MAN.
- NEITHER AM I.
I'M TALKING ABOUT TAKING ITTO THE STREETS WHERE I CAME UP.
- YOU DIDN'T COME UPIN THE STREETS.
YOU GOT THOSE TATTOOSWITH STUDENT LOAN MONEY.
- I CAN GET DRUGS.
- YOU COULDN'T SCORE HASHIN AMSTERDAM.
- YOU KNOW THAT'S ACTUALLYHARDER THAN YOU'D THINK.
I'LL TELL YOU WHERETHEY'RE NOT SELLING IT--
THE ANNE FRANK HOUSE.
NO, I'M GOING RIGHTTO THE SOURCE.
- DEALERS?- PEE.
LIPS LIE, BLADDERS DON'T.
- OKAY, WELL, WHILE YOUTWO DEA AGENTS ARE OUT THERE
FUMBLE-FUCKING THIS UP,
I'LL JUST GO TO MY SATURDAYDETENTION KIDS TO GET DRUGS.
SHOW UP HERE MONDAY MORNINGWITH EVERYTHING YOU'VE GOT.
WE'LL JUST COMPARE.- ALL RIGHT.
- SOUND LIKE A DEAL?- OH, THERE'S ANOTHER.
- OH, YEAH.
- MM-MMM.- OH, NO, THERE IT IS.
- I'M NOT INTO THIS ONE.THIS ONE'S MAKING ME SICK.
- OH, THAT'S STILL HOT,STILL 100% HOT TO ME.
DICK DOESN'T LIE, DUDE.
- ALL RIGHT, I'M GONNA GIVE YOUONE LAST CHANCE.
RAISE YOUR HANDIF YOU HAVE DRUGS,
AND YOU WON'T GET IN TROUBLE.
OTHERWISE, IT'S A PEE TESTRIGHT HERE IN THIS GYM.
YEAH, GROSS.
LOOK, I KNOW ONE OF YOUIS ON DRUGS.
IT'S A SIMPLE STATISTIC.
NOBODY?
OKAY, THIS IS YOUR LAST CHANCEFOR REALS-REALS LAST CHANCE.
OKAY, ACTUAL LAST CHANCE.
THREE...
TWO...
ALL RIGHT, OPPORTUNITY GONE.
GO GET A CUP.FILL IT UP TO THE BRIM.
- YO, IS YOU MOTHERFUCKIN'STEPPIN', SON?
'CAUSE IF YOU COME AT ME,MOTHERFUCKER,
YOU BETTER BE READYTO BLAZE, SON.
OH, YOU RAIS--
- HEY, SWEETHEART, HAVE YOU SEENMY FUZZY PINK SLIPPERS?
- UM, MM-MMM.NOPE.
- WHAT ARE YOU TRYINGTO PSYCH YOURSELF UP FOR?
- OH, I'M NOT PSYCHINGMYSELF UP FOR ANYTHING.
I'M GETTING READYTO TAKE MILO TO THE PARK.
- WELL, YOU LOOK LIKETHE RHYTHM GUITARIST FROM KORN.
- WHAT'S WITH THISPARK BULLSHIT?
YOU SAIDWE WERE GONNA BUY DRUGS.
- SHH, GOD.JUST GET IN THE CAR.
GO.
- A LOT OF PEOPLE ARE GOINGTO TRY TO TELL YOU GUYS
THAT SATURDAY MORNING DETENTIONIS A PUNISHMENT, OKAY?
BUT NOT ME, NOT MR. PAYTON.
I WENT TO THE JOHN HUGHESSCHOOL OF DISCIPLINE
WHERE DETENTION ISN'TA PUNISHMENT, YOU GUYS,
BUT AN OPPORTUNITY.
AN OPPORTUNITY FOR THE JOCKTO MAYBE GET TO KNOW
THE GOTH CHICK IN THE BACKWITH ALL THE DANDRUFF.
AN OPPORTUNITYFOR THE DANGEROUS HEARTTHROB
TO GET TO KNOW THE FOXY CHICK
WHO'S ALSO KIND OF A BITCHA LOT OF THE TIME.
BUT MAINLY AN OPPORTUNITY TO,I DON'T KNOW,
MAYBE BREAK OUT A JOINT OR TWO,SMOKE 'EM.
'CAUSE THE GUY RUNNING THE CLASSIS GONNA BE GONE FOR,
LIKE, THE NEXT 20 MINUTES,
AND YOU COULD TOTALLYGET AWAY WITH IT.
OKAY?
DO IT.
BE YOUNG, YOU GUYS.YOU'RE GONNA GET OLDER.
IT'S UNAVOIDABLE.IT JUST HAPPENS.
- WHAT THE FUCKARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
- TALKING ABOUTWHEN YOU GROW UP,
IT'S LIKE A PIECEOF YOUR HEART DIES, MAN.
ANYWAY, 20 MINUTES,SMOKE JOINTS.
I'LL BE BACK.
OH, MY GOD.
OH, GLADYS, I'M SO SORRY.
OH, MY GOD, GLADYS,YOU ARE A HUMAN FOSSIL.
DON'T DIE, GLADYS.STAY ALIVE.
- YOU WAIT HERE, ALL RIGHT?
DADDY'S GONNA GO GET SOMEILL PRODUCT FROM THESE GUYS.
- ARE THEY A RAP GROUP?- OH, BUDDY, NO.
YOU KNOW IT'S NOT OKAY
TO GENERALIZEA GROUP OF PEOPLE LIKE THAT.
NO, I'M COMING HERE BECAUSETHEY PROBABLY HAVE DRUGS.
WHAT YOU GUYS DOING--PLAYING A LITTLE YAHTZEE?
WHOA, WHOA, WHOA, WHOA,WHAT UP, BLOOD CLOTS?
JUST WANTED TO POP BY.
MY BOY AND I ARE OUT TROLLINGFOR SOME OF THAT SWEET CANDY
TO BRING BACK TOOUR NUBIAN QUEEN AT THE HIVE.
YO, I WAS JUST TRYING TO SEE
IF ANY OF Y'ALL GOT A LINEON SOME OF THAT NEW JACK SHIT?
- WHAT?
- YOU KNOW WHATI'M TALKING ABOUT.
SOME OF THAT--SOME OF THAT ILL SHIT
THAT MAKES YOU ALL MAD FOUL,YOU KNOW?
- HEY, YOU A COP?- AM I A COP?
MAN, NO, I'M NOT A...
NO, I'M NOT A COP, MAN.I'M A TEACHER.
- WHAT YOU WANT SOME XANAX,SOME RITALIN OR SOMETHING, MAN?
- XANAX?NO, HEROIN.
DO ANY OF YOU ALL HAVE HEROIN?
- 150 BUCKS.
- $150?YOU GUYS HAVE--
YOU KNOW, THIS IS THE REAL PRICEOF THE WAR ON DRUGS RIGHT HERE.
$150?HOLD ON.
LET ME GET, LIKE, LIKE,$40 UNTIL TOMORROW.
COME ON, I'M GOOD FOR IT.
LOOK AT...
YOUR PAPER ROUTEIS KILLING IT, MAN.
DAPS, THANKS A LOT.
OH, IT'S NOT FOR HIM.IT'S FOR A DIFFERENT KID.
ALL RIGHT,WE GOT 100, 140, 150.
BOOM.- GIVE HIM THAT SHIT.
- ALL RIGHT, MAN.
WHOO, LOOK WHAT I GOT.
WHAT?WHAT, MAN?
NAH, IT'S COOL.I'M DOWN.
ALL RIGHT, BIT.ALL RIGHT, GUYS.
THANKS A LOT AGAIN.I REALLY APPRECIATE THIS.
LOOK AT WHAT DADDY DID, HUH?
- WHAT, Y'ALL WANT TO GET BACKON THAT YAHTZEE?
- TWO TO THREE, LET'S GO.- THAT'S RIGHT.
- OKAY, YOU GUYS, I'M BACK.
ANYTHING HAPPENWHILE I WAS GONE, HUH?
CERTAINLY DOESN'T SMELL LIKEANYONE SMOKED ANY WEED IN HERE.
ANY DRUG USE WHATSOEVER?
NOBODY'S MAKING NEW FRIENDS?
NOBODY'S MAKING OUTIN THE BACK OF THE LIBRARY?
- NO, BUT HE FINGERED ME.
- JESUS CHRIST, YOU GUYS,
THAT'S NOT WHATI'M TALKING ABOUT.
I'M DISAPPOINTED IN ALL OF YOU.I WEEP FOR YOUR GENERATION.
NOW, WHO'S GONNASELL ME A JOINT?
THAT'S MORE LIKE IT.
- BRYCE TURNERTO PRINCIPAL QUINN'S OFFICE.
BRYCE TURNERTO PRINCIPAL QUINN'S OFFICE.
- UH-OH,MCGRUFF THE CRIME DOG HERE
TO TAKE A BITE OUT OF SOMETHING.
- LOOKS LIKESOMEONE'S IN TROUBLE.
- GENTLEMAN, IS THERESOMEWHERE BETTER WE COULD BE?
- LITERALLY NOWHERE.
- THANK YOU.
BRYCE, LET'S GO AHEAD ANDHAVE A LOOK INSIDE YOUR LOCKER.
- UH-OH, LOOKS LIKE I SEESOME SUDAFED IN THERE.
DON'T PEOPLE USE THATTO MAKE METH?
- BARRY, THESE ARE NOT MINE.
- THEY'RE--WELL, THEY'RE IN YOUR LOCKER.
LITERALLY EVERY PILLI'VE EVER SEEN IN MY LIFE.
- IS THIS--IS THISIS A REEFER STICK, BRYCE?
IS THAT A REEFER STICK?IS IT?
LOOK AT ME.
NO, NO, NO, NO.NO, NO, NO, NO, NO.
IS THAT BLACK TAR HEROIN?
- GUYS, I THINKTHAT'S FELONY POSSESSION
OF A SCHEDULE I CONTROLLEDSUBSTANCE ON SCHOOL PROPERTY.
I THINK THE HANDBOOK SAYS THAT
THAT'S AN AUTOMATIC ACADEMICAND ATHLETIC SUSPENSION,
IF I'M NOT MISTAKEN, OF COURSE.
- YEAH, REMEMBER YOU TOLD US INTHE PARKING LOT BEFORE SCHOOL?
- I WISH WE COULDHARD-TALK THIS OUT.
I REALLY DO, BUT WE CANNOT.THOSE GUYS ARE RIGHT.
WE'RE GONNA TALK IN MY OFFICE,AND WE'RE GONNA SORT THIS OUT.
WHY DON'T YOU GO AHEADAND LEAD THE WAY?
- SEE YOU LATER, BRYCE.
- BUENO SUERTE, MUCHACHO.
- HEY, BRYCE, HEADS UP.
FAIRBELL, GET OVER HERE.
WHAT WAS THAT?- HE STARTED IT.
- HE STARTED IT?THAT'S YOUR EXCUSE?
- YES, HE HIT ME IN THE FACEIN GYM CLASS.
- OKAY, YOU KNOW WHAT?SHHH.
I HAVE TO LOOK COOLIN FRONT OF THESE KIDS.
- YOU STILL LOOK COOL.- DO YOU MEAN THAT?
LOOK AT MEWHEN I SAY THAT TO YOU.
ARE YOU LY--NO, NO, NO.
HEY, HEY, STOP IT RIGHT NOW.STOP IT.
THE THREE OF YOUIN MY OFFICE RIGHT NOW.
I'M GONNA DEAL WITH YOUAFTER I DEAL WITH BRYCE.
THIS IS OUTRAGEOUS.
LET'S GO.
- ARE YOU GONNA GET THAT, TAMMY?
- THAT'S THE PROBLEM.
YOU ACT LIKE CHILDREN.NOW, YOU IN CHARGE OF CHILDREN.
IT'S A DAMN SHAME.
- HEY, TAMMY,DID I EVER TELL YOU
THAT I VALUE THE OPINIONOF A CHILI'S WAITRESS
MORE THAN THE SHITTHAT COMES OUT OF YOUR FACE?
- OH, HELLO,THAT'S HOW WE GONNA BE?
Y'ALL WANT TO WRESTLE?
- TAMMY, TAMMY, TAMMY, TAMMY,HE DIDN'T MEAN IT.
HE DIDN'T MEAN IT.HE DID NOT MEAN THAT.
OKAY, WE DON'T NEEDTO DO THIS AGAIN.
- YOU NEED TO KEEP A LEASHON YOUR BOY.
COME AT ME LIKE THATIN THE PARKING LOT,
IT'S GONNA BEA WHOLE DIFFERENT STORY.
OH, SURE, JUST STROLL ON IN.
- BRYCE, LET'S GO!- MR. TURNER, HELLO.
- WE'RE DONE HERE.
- BRYCE HAS TO GO,ALL RIGHT.
OKAY, GOOD TO SEE YA.OKAY.
YOU THREE,IN MY OFFICE RIGHT NOW.
- THE PRINCIPALWILL SEE YOU NOW.
- YOU SERVE AN INVALUABLEFUNCTION AT THIS SCHOOL, TAMMY.
- HUM...
GENTLEMAN, PLEASE,HAVE A SEAT.
COACH FAIRBELL,
I ONLY HAVE THE TWO SEATSSO PLEASE TAKE THE FLOOR.
I WOULD ALSO OFFER YOU
SOME OF MY SPICED GINGERCAFFEINE-FREE TEA,
HOWEVER, I DO NOT BELIEVE
IN POSITIVELY REINFORCINGNEGATIVE BEHAVIOR.
- YEAH, WHATEVER.HOW LONG IS BRYCE SUSPENDED FOR?
THREE WEEKS?THREE WEEKS.
YOU IRON-BALLED SON OF A BITCH.
I DIDN'T THINKYOU HAD IT IN YOU, BARRY.
GOOD WORK.
- HOW ABOUT YOU GUYS STOPWORRYING SO MUCH ABOUT BRYCE
AND YOU START WORRYINGABOUT YOURSELVES?
- WAIT, DON'T TELL MEHE GOT OFF, BARRY.
- YEAH, STUDENT'S ACTIONS HAVETO HAVE CONSEQUENCES, BARRY.
- BARRY.
- COACH FAIRBELL, WHAT'STHE NAME OF YOUR GYMNASIUM?
15 STUDENTS ENTER, 11 LEAVE.
- THE ACTUAL NAME, PLEASE.- TURNER GYMNASIUM?
- AS IN ZEBULON TURNER,
AS IN BRYCE'S GREAT-GRANDFATHER.
HUH, LOOK AT THAT.
- I THOUGHT IT WAS TINA TURNER.
THAT'S WHERE I CAME UP WITHTHE WHOLE THUNDERDOME THING.
THAT'S FUNNY.- NO.
LOOK, GUYS.
WE'RE ALL TRYING TO KEEPOUR JOBS HERE, RIGHT?
- SO THAT--SO THAT'S IT?
THE STAR LACROSSE PLAYERGETS CAUGHT
WITH A BALLOON FULL OF HEROININ HIS LOCKER
AND GETS OFF SCOT-FREEBECAUSE DADDY HAS MONEY?
WE'RE SUPPOSED TO JUST SIT HERE
AND TAKE THATLIKE THAT'S JUSTICE?
- NO, NO.YOU'RE SUPPOSED TO SIT HERE...
YOU'RE SUPPOSED TO SIT HERE
WHILE I ADD YET ANOTHER WARNINGTO YOUR FILES,
AND YOU'RE LUCKY THATTHAT'S ALL YOU'RE GETTING.
- I DON'T THINKTHERE'S ROOM IN MY FILE
FOR ANOTHER WRITTEN WARNING,BARRY.
- OH, DON'T WORRY,I'LL START ANOTHER ONE FOR YOU.
- NOW, I BELIEVE YOU GENTLEMENHAVE CLASSES TO GET TO, OKAY?
SO THANK YOU FOR COMING.- FINE.
♪ I'M LIKE A BIRD
♪ I'LL ONLY FLY AWAY
♪ I DON'T KNOWWHERE MY SOUL IS ♪
- HEY, ABBEY, I GOTTHAT LATEST BATCH FOR YOU.
- THERE IS NO WAYYOU READ THESE ALREADY.
- WELL, I MEAN,DO YOU KNOW
A LOT OF THESEARE ACTUALLY MOVIES?
GOOD TIP.
SPEAKING OF MOVIES,
I WAS WONDERING THIS WEEKENDIF YOU'RE NOT DOING ANYTHING--
- LISTEN, LOREN.- YEAH?
- YOU'RE SUPER CUTE.- YOU'RE RIGHT.
- I DON'T DATE COWORKERS.- OH, THAT'S NO PROBLEM.
'CAUSE I'M DEFINITELY GETTINGFIRED IN A FEW DAYS, I THINK.
- OKAY, WELL, THEN WHEN YOU GETFIRED, MAYBE GIVE ME A CALL.
- DEAL.THAT SOUNDS LIKE A DATE.
- IT IS NOT.
- WELL, YOU JUST PROPOSEDA MEETING FOR A FUTURE DATE.
SO THAT'S A DATE.- I DIDN'T AGREE TO ANYTHING.
I SAID, "CALL ME."
- AGREE TO DISAGREEON THAT ONE, ABBEY.
- OH, WAIT.DID YOU HEAR ABOUT BRYCE TURNER?
- WHAT?BRYCE BRYCE?
WHAT,DID SOMETHING HAPPEN TO HIM?
- APPARENTLY, THEY FOUND,LIKE, DRUGS IN HIS LOCKER.
- OH, WHOA.- LIKE, A LOT.
LIKE, HEROIN,WOMEN'S MULTIVITAMINS,
LIKE, WEIRD STUFF.
I CAN'T BELIEVE YOU HAVEN'THEARD ABOUT THIS ALREADY.
- OH, I MAKE IT MY POLICY NOTTO MEDDLE IN STUDENT AFFAIRS.
TREVOR,ARE YOU DATING TRISH NOW?
ARE YOU KIDDING ME?WHAT HAPPENED TO HEATHER, DUDE?
YOU GUYS WERE SO GOOD TOGETHER.
THE WHOLE SCHOOLWAS BEHIND THAT.
GOOD LUCK IF THINKTHAT'S BETTER THAN HEATHER.
YOU...
I--I SHOULD PROBABLY GET GOING,RIGHT?
- YEAH.
- YEAH, YOU GOT A LOT OF STUFF.I GOT A LOT OF STUFF.
I'LL JUST--WHAT--I'LL JUSTTAKE WHATEVER YOU HAVE.
BYE, ABBEY.
- SO I HAVE THE RESULTSOF YOUR PEE TESTS HERE.
FIRST OF ALL, TURNS OUT NONEOF YOU ACTUALLY ARE ON DRUGS.
SO THANK YOU FOR BEING HONEST.
WE DO HAVE SOME ISSUESTO ADDRESS, THOUGH.
HARRISON,TURNS OUT YOU'RE HYPOGLYCEMIC.
DON'T WORRY,I HAD TO LOOK IT UP TOO.
JUST MEANSYOU'RE NOT EATING ENOUGH CANDY.
I BROUGHT YOU SOMEMIKE AND IKES.
JOEL, BUDDY, YOU NEED TO STARTDRINKING SOME MORE WATER, OKAY?
YOUR PEE WAS LIKE GRAVY.
SIP ON THAT.
UH, OKAY, BETH...OH!
CONGRATS, YOU'RE PREGNANT.-
- I DON'T KNOWIF YOU KNEW THAT OR NOT.
CLASS, EYES UP HERE.
THIS IS A PRIVATE MOMENT.
THAT INFORMATION IS CONFIDENTIALBETWEEN BETH AND HER DOCTOR...
AND ME AND NOW ALL OF YOU.
DOESN'T LEAVE THIS THUNDERDOME.
ALL RIGHT, FLOOR HOCKEY.
BETH, I DON'T WANT YOU RUNNING.YOU'RE GOALIE.
- YOU KNOW, HONESTLY,
I THINK YOU GUYS ARE BEINGA BIT HARD ON YOURSELVES.
WE--WE EXECUTEDTHAT PLAN PERFECTLY.
- YEAH, EXCEPT NOW I'M OUT20 BUCKS FOR "REEFER STICKS."
- YEAH, WELL, I'M OUT 40 BUCKSTO MY KID FOR THAT HEROIN.
- YOU KNOW, I ACTUALLY THINKI LIKE THIS BETTER.
- I TOLD YOU SALLIESYOU SHOULD HAVE DONE IT THIS WAY
IN THE FIRST PLACE.
- DID YOU TELL THEMTO LAY OFF THE FACE?
'CAUSE THEY ARE DEFINITELYNOT LAYING OFF THE FACE.
- WHY WOULD HE TELL THEMTO LAY OFF THE FACE?
- WHY WOULD I TELL THEMTO LAY OFF THE FACE?
- * HEY, HEY, HEY, HEY
- YOU GO HORIZONTAL.I GO VERTICAL, RIGHT?
SO WHAT'S THAT?
- WHAT?- YEAH.
- DUDE, IT LOOKS LIKE A VAGINA.
- YEAH, I KNOWIT FUCKING LOOKS LIKE A VAGINA.
- A KID SHOWED YOU THAT?- YEAH, A KID SHOWED ME--
YOU DON'T TALK TO YOUR KIDSABOUT THIS STUFF?
- WELL, NOT THAT COOL STUFF.
- IT'S IMPORTANTTHAT THEY LEARN, DUDE.
- * THE WAY I DO
♪ THE DOG GIVE ME THAT
♪ KEEP ME LOOKIN'FOR SOMETHING NEW ♪
♪ SMOKING, OOH
FOR ALLTHE TIMES YOU WATCHED A SHOW
AND SAID OUT LOUD TO YOURSELF...
HERE IS YOUR CHANCETO FINALLY HAVE SOMEONE LISTEN.
TELL US WHAT YOU THINKOF THE SHOW.