Two days ago, I received a letter
from a lawyer in Europe.
It regretted to inform me my mother
had died in a helicopter crash.
She was returning from her sold out
farewell concert in London.
Her estate was to be turned over
to me, the letter said,
but my physical presence was
required immediately...
Everything had been arranged,
a plane ticket to Heathrow,
a car waiting...
only the timing couldn't
have been worse.
Last month I released
my first album,
it got rave reviews in the US
and we were just starting our
debut American tour.
Maybe this sounds a little
cold-hearted,
but the fact is, she has refused
to see me
or even speak to me ever since she
left home when I was only three.
I never knew why...
Everything I knew about her came
from the tabloids,
how she'd become a
recluse rock star,
hiding out in a castle
nobody'd ever heard of.
But why did she want to give this..
this place to me?
She never returned a single letter
I wrote,
never helped with the band,
even indirectly.
And after we worked so hard to
finally get our big break
now she calls me from the grave...
Well, I hope what they say isn't true
about curiosity killing the cat
Hello?
Hello?!
Hello, anybody home?!
Anybody alive in here?
What in the...?
Uh... What's goin on here?
Okay, this is getting a little weird.
Hey... What do you want from me?
Whoah, guys.
Look, can I help you with something?
Fellas?
Oooooh...
Hey... Watch it!... Listen,
I think we have a
misunderstanding here.
Little help here!!
Wooooooo...
Little help in here please
That felt so good.
Huh? What is this?
We have an uninvited guest.
Let me take care of you,
little bird.
Now for you, Johnny.
Welcome. We've been expecting you...
Go upstairs, Johnny.
Mr. D is waiting for you!!!
Looks like I have no choice.
Okay, either I've lost my mind or
I'm having really bad jet lag...
Now what?
Where the heck am I?
Wait a minute. I know that voice..
Mother?
Johnny, your mother was beautiful
when she was young.
And she was good, very good,
Johnny.
You're mother could have been
a superstar.
She had the talent.
But she drove a hard bargain.
One of the conditions of
her contract was that
you were strictly off limits.
You were her baby.
A rather touching performance
really.
Anyway I kept my end of the
bargain of course.
Alas, she could not keep hers.
So you've been summoned,
and what was once hers I can now
offer to you.
I know exactly what
you're getting at.
Really. Enlighten me.
I'm having a really weird dream,
and I can't wake up.
This is better than a dream,
Johnny.
This is immortality.
I can make you the the greatest
rock legend of all time.
All you have to do is sign on
a little dotted line.
Now I know who you are.
No way! I'm not sign-
That's what they all say...
at first.
You really believe you have talent
to make it on your own?
That's the dream Johnny.
In the real world, you need Mr.D.
He can make you everything
you ever wanted to be.
But we understand if you
have some... reservations.
Well, perhaps you better
look around
before you make your
final decision.
Just to be sure
Johnny, You must find
your way out.
Don't let them get to you.
Don't...
Who are you?
Oh, God!
What have I gotten myself into?
Interesting place
don't you think?
Here's the lowdown, Johnny.
Centuries ago, music played
a relatively minor part
in the larger scheme of things
within the corporation.
It was so difficult to find good
recruits, not like politics.
We barely met our quotas.
Every now and then a client
would try to reneg on his deal-
Musicians don't read contracts
very carefully you know -
so we would dig a new cave down here
and confine the subject
to a life of total anonymity
and of course perpetual noise.
Drives ya nuts.
Long story short, music just wasn't
much of a draw.
At some point there was even a plan
within the corporation
to scrap our division altogether.
So, fast forward, the Big Idea.
It was really my idea but...
Not important.
At first we wanted to call it
Twist and Burn - little too obvious
so we settled on Rock and Roll.
Business went through the roof.
By the time the sixties rolled around
our little division was on fuego.
Huge growth.
Our only problem was space.
Let me tell you, when you're
dealing with damned souls,
storage is always a big problem.
So Mr.D. had to come up
with a new scheme.
This you gotta see.
Funny thing about rock stars,
the instant they become
rich and famous,
they tend to think
their invincible.
Stop living up to
their commitments.
Even have the audacity to try to
break their contracts.
But let me tell you, one does not
break a deal with Mr.D.
But they tried and we build
this place all for them.
You see we use the deal-breakers
to provide entertainment
for members of the corporation.
Works out rather well.
From time to time Mr.D.
gathers the troops
- a little attitude adjustment
party we like to call it
- and we have one hell of
a good time...
Have fun. AHAA...
Welcome to our show.
If you like the band
please applaud as hard
as you can.
If not... applaud anyway.
Turn around Johnny.
You must leave this place.
I came this far,
I might as well see the show.
This is not a show
you want to see, Johnny.
Once they get to you,
there is no turning back!
Don't do it for me,
do it for yourself!
But wait, who are you?! Mom?
Man, this is getting too weird.
Welcome to our show.
If you like the band please
applaud as hard as you can.
If not... applaud anyway.
Johnny! What are you
doing down here?!
I don't know. I just...
This place is off-limits.
Way off-limits.
I HATE this place.
Let's get out of here.
Opera isn't very popular here,
is it?
HAAA... you don't know
the half of it.
Mr. D used to love opera too,
hardcore opera fan.
Then he got involved with an
opera star.
Long story, but she left him,
broke her deal.
Mr. D went totally berserk.
Opera is now officially taboo
upstairs.
Whenever any opera singers
break their contract,
he gets a little...
out of control
Never mind.
Nothing to do with you, Johnny.
Now you must go.
Mr. D is getting impatient.
The time has come...
Good.
Come here, Johnny...
I want to show you something -
your future.
You know you have a good voice,
but would you like to be
a great guitar player as well?
I'll make a Rock legend out of you,
it would be all yours,
everything you ever wanted,
let me show you.
Yes. Good. Goooood. Good.
Johnny?
Mom... this one's for you.