Bring your boat is fine.
I like it anyway.
Father, do you think it fine?
- I love it, Laura.
- Come on. Dad likes it.
- Who wants breakfast?
- I!
I want pancakes.
Dressed up situation.
I thought you already started to come back to haunt.
- Please.
- Certified and all.
Navigator two of the best days.
Name has not been changed. This is
door and the motor.
- Good luck.
- Thank you.
Are you divorced?
- I do not.
- A divorced will be here...
Between the foot of chicken legs and lives in a boat
YOU a couple of months and go away.
For all get used to it. Here is the time
peaceful.
- Do you want to know something else?
- I'll take things clear.
Okay. See you later.
I have a boat, boating
if I were a man, but when I'm not.
- Have you?
- We'll see.
Do not forget. In that order.
I could not help looking.
You will need such a... not good.
You might have a little to do.
I'll be Windissä West.
Do you live in it? - Yes. Since June
since I left.
I've always wanted to do this.
The summer was great.
As late has been great.
I'll be right.
- Have you divorced?
- I do not.
Good, if you put the boat in order.
Women like sailing.
In fact, I  harder sailing. There is no
patience. Too much work.
But it all works, right?
Duty calls. See you later.
- Thanks for the beer.
- Please.
- Good evening.
- How are you?
Thank you, Lauren. "
Lauren...
Lauren, do not run to the bathroom
...
Oh, God...
Can not...
He bought Hesperus.
Damn.
Hello?
You seemed a little tense in the morning.
- What is it?
- yesterday I made a deal.
One place Charlevoix.
Too Cold too... rain.
All too quiet.
Forced to leave.
- I'll see you.
- Good luck.
When are you going to go?
See you later.
Good... Take it easy, son.
Calm down.
All is going well.
Take it easy. Spit it out.
You're doing just fine.
- More coffee?
- Thank you.
You do not like homemade food.
Did you hear last night bagpipes
call?
I did not hear anything.
- Is this acceptable?
- No, of course not.
I'm trying to quit, but I want to
ever enjoy.
Is there a garden break,
and a cigarette break?
Right.
- Does the engine still does not work?
- It started almost last week.
Are you going to take it as soon as the open sea?
Hesperus is not afraid of cold water.
- How long have you been on the boat?
- 51 days.
Who  those days fall?
Not worth
mixed with alcohol and drugs.
Lotus eaters called
residents. They were friendly
and gave sailors fruit.
They did not want anything bad...
... but thought that it was
the best thing for them... can give.
The boat is there.
This we have. You see,
Lauren?
When the wind died down, they took
oars and rowed for several days, -
until they reached the ground,
cyclones in which to live.
Cyclops, just . One of the eye...
On the island...
Are you there?
Wait a minute.
Lootuksensyöjät called
inhabitants...
See, I'm being ripped off!
Let the whole shit!
Oh, God...
- I did not know where else to go.
- Sit. You need to warm up.
Put ​​this on.
You get a warm drink.
This.
It should help.
- Do you like tea?
- I have never tasted.
Teetäkö? Really?
Once I called you, I liked
break and I followed you.
- Is not that clever?
- It's all right.
Joey does not mean anything by it.
Be here as long as you want.
Sleep here. I sleep at the bow.
Lauren?
I'm going to the bow, so you
a moment in peace.
Do you put the sail?
Harbor is a great sail maker.
- I want to do it yourself.
- It's your business.
The place is closed today, however.
Less on your back, the more
feet.
Good way. In that way, you keep going
to row all day.
I wanted to ask what the two
sailors are the best days.
Day, when he buys a boat and the
day when he sells the boat.
- One of life's truths?
- I do not know. I have experienced only one.
Oh, no.
Come on.
Do I need a permit to enter the ship?
You are already on board.
When you put your cell phone
out of the earth? - Halloween season.
I've been coming here after
twice a week talking to you.
- What are you doing?
- I'm trying to clean the fuel line.
This is a sailing ship.
Why does the engine have to fix it?
90 per cent of sail boats passing
75 percent of the time engine.
Engine.
When are you coming back?
I do not know.
How much time do you need?
You can work remotely.
We'll leave you alone.
- There is a huge amount to do.
- We are four months behind.
- You've got a great team.
- It's no longer about what you have left.
- There will always be new product launches.
- Not us.
Homma is to see over.
Out of stock.
How much time has passed?
Eight months?
I still do not understand.
Just incomprehensible.
Forget about the program.
We are worried about you.
I'm worried about. You just
disappeared.
I'm here.
It is no wonder that you're here.
Not quite at their leisure.
Are you going to give up?
- Where's the sail maker is?
- Across the street.
In there?
Thank you.
We can not change the direction of the wind, the sail
but we can control. "
I gave myself a good recommendation.
Sure.
Well...  let's see what you got.
Bagpipes
can save a person's soul.
- Do you like salmon?
- Yes.
Good. We get Marie salmon.
An old family recipe.
He may look like Hesperus
Norwegian fishing vessel.
No. Well it is.
I took the salad and wine
Marie's companion manual.
- As long as you do not only brought tobacco.
- I stopped smoking.
Really?
Then someone else to steal from me.
- This time I'm serious.
- Good. Did you quit the drinking?
- Do not be silly.
- Search glass. Raise a toast.
- Cheers.
Open the bottle, so
get up to speed.
Where is your boat?
Let me show you something, when we are
eaten.
There it is. Marie.
- Ongoing project.
- Really beautiful.
My wife and I came to ten o'clock
years ago St Laurence River.
We had to bypass the Great Lakes.
Sailed Mackena Bay,
when he had a brain hemorrhage.
We did not get to this place
further.
I was last on the boat when I threw
Marie's ashes.
He has been in my heart ever since
.
And I am grieved.
I do not recommend the same for a young man of
.
- Coffee?
- Breakfast, if that's okay.
- Of course.
- Great.
Hesperus is the evening star
spirit of Greek mythology.
He first rose to -
Atlas mountain, but the storm brought him to -
and he disappeared without a trace.
Goodness of why he became a
-friendly evening star.
He gives every night nocturnal peace.
- You're gonna always be here?
- I like it here. It is peaceful.
The place is remote and people are
interesting.
- Everywhere is the same thing.
- Water plays a role.
I can go to Cape Town, South Africa
Mackena through the gulf -
and continue the lakes and the sea
along the coasts of Nova Scotia.
South east along the seashore, and
, then north, away from the golf stream.
Panamankanavaa south along the trade winds and the
to Hawaii.
Equatorial crack,
west of Fiji.
For a while,
in Darwin Australia.
Indian Ocean. Weather and ocean currents
must occur properly.
Sailing 160 miles south of Madagascar in Durban.
Last piece of south-west along the coast of Africa.
One and a half years and 3,200 miles later, I am in Cape Town
.
- Are you going to do it sometime?
- I may have already done.
The material is still late.
Just a few weeks.
A few weeks? A few weeks
was a few weeks ago.
- Time flies like the wings.
- Yes.
When the season until you
you could do other stuff.
- What?
- The cover boards need to hone.
But it is not my
boat.
He has slowed down the pace.
We can help.
Hello.
What's up?
- We made it here in the winter?
- I made it alive.
- Boat starting to be okay.
- Yes. Slowly, but surely.
You change the name.
It is no longer appropriate.
Name begins to be known.
Are you going to stay for a while?
Thought I'd
for a few weeks at the end. Calmness.
Be careful.
Great.
Come on, sweetheart.
I'll see you later.
Dark and the light of day, between
when night begins to descend countries, -
is the time to take a break day at work,
in children's hour.
You are my forever.
Always and day, -
The walls are damaged, decaying, and
flying away.
Are you okay?
I should have known that he was ill
.
We were on board.
Deep sea and distant islands.
Why do we sailed the Great Lakes Region
?
It was his idea.
He did not want to, that I would be alone in the sea
if something happens.
He knew what was going to happen.
I do not even think about it.
I should have guessed.
I would have been able to help.
But I did not understand.
Bagpipes never
other things.
- Sounds around the clock.
- All over the world, all the time.
There is a Grand Traverse.
The Indians hunted
canoe, and passed along Lake Michigan.
Bay was a barrier. They paddled along the beach to the south of
-
and to the north along the other shore
. Long way to go.
Or they were able to walk half a mile coast to the open sea
-
Leelana-Peninsula,
a shorter distance, but the treacherous waters.
When they left the continent, they saw the
of the peninsula from a distance.
Indians said seats at
"Oh Me Nah I", a place far away.
French fur traders used the same route.
They said it "Le Grande
Traversée" long route.
Then came the other. Missionary,
continued, settlers, farmers.
And finally came the tourists.
The name came from the Grand Traverse.
I have to back row. If you start to blow, we can end up with
Magna country.
Please wait. There is something for everyone.
It's a Grand Traverse, son.
- What is it?
- All.
I'm almost done.
You are ready.
It's really beautiful.
Do you take it up the field?
You should be.
Sometimes when you are out there, what should be
, -
it is too early.
I left it on the counter.
- Do not smoke?
- The burner package yesterday to finish.
The two happiest days in a sailor's life
.
You are a prisoner of the fortress,
and I will not let you leave.
I'll put you in my heart
a round into the chamber of the tower.
Do not be angry, but change the name of
.
Hesperus as the evening star is the spirit that will bring peace to the night
, -
Greek mythology.
If you say so.
- Please. As we agreed.
- No it did not have to be certified.
I do not want to lose this, and
I know the situation, in this condition.
Do not forget that.
It belongs to the boat.
And a half years, 2,700 miles,
and I am in Cape Town.
- Are you going to do it sometime?
- I may have already done it.
- Good luck.
-, Too.
- PLAYER 25/04/2013 -