*****DINO TIME*******
Hello !!!!!!!!
**********Edited by Honey-ghy*********
Measurements skill of 1 to 10, total
value to the board this rocket is 37!
This is Terra Dino Park!
A comfortable place to stay.
Especially for fans
dinosaurs, like me.
You know, dinosaur fossils were found in the
us more than any other place on earth?
If you visit, I will
be your tour guides were great.
Sorry Mr. Hodges!
Ernie Fitzpatrick!
How dare you!
Hello, sister?
How to practice soccer balls?
Mother would be very upset with you!
Again!
You know, you're supposed to keep the store?
This is for you, 25 cents. Contact
someone you loved.
If you can find a pay phone.
He will soon tell my mom.
His head will explode when he saw me!
But I'm not Julia.
Mom was busy to attend
awards show exemplary parents.
Important part of a person
parents are making the rules.
Thank you for this award.
Ernie, do you
on the way?
Yeah, I had to stop because
Julia wants to borrow my money.
Well, mom to go now. Maternal leave
sign waiting for 15 minutes in front of the door.
-- You know what you must do, Ernie?
-- Leave a message.
15 minutes means you will
arrived at exactly 2:53, okay?
Yes, I understand.
I'm very familiar with my mother,
he's always watching me.
I have never tasted freedom.
31,
Hello?
-- Ernie if you have to store?
-- Soon to enter.
-- Okay, do the best you can do.
-- Back in 15 minutes.
Both Mom.
"Back in 150 minutes."
You heard him, he said
as fast as I could.
Ah ...
National Museum of Terra Dino.
The only places in the world.
And that this is the Mystery Stone.
You see the carvings?
've Been there since the time of the Cretaceous.
Very strange, because who
who will carve it?
No man alive
at 145 million years ago!
Only dinosaurs.
Is not it mysterious?
Well, that's what we know in there.
Restore.
It is my best friend Max.
He always had a way of
make something cool.
Which makes it look cool ...
... But sometimes, other children
did not see it that way.
Do you think Leonardo da Vinci
never painted his own son?
What? Pal?
See, there are gorgeous.
What? Where?
Basic Suck!
Hahaha ...
-- Ernie, how to board the rocket?
assessment 1 to 10 ... -- 37, a friend.
Buuyaa!!
You and your dad really
make this amazing thing.
Hey, talk about my father ...
According to him, there are examples of new fossil
which has been excavated in 2329.
You'd better come on
opening ceremony tomorrow.
Fabulous! I've recorded it?
I can not wait anymore.
Wait ...
But the show has not been opened.
Are not you supposed to keep the store your mother?
Friends ...
You're like my mother who always
tell me what to do this and that!
Do you know, breaking the rules is wrong
the best part of us as children.
The most important thing to be
parents are making the rules.
Once the rules have been made ...
... The key is to make them obedient.
Exactly as you wish.
Doing all things as he wishes,
and not what I want to do.
It is a compromise.
There is no compromise!
This goal will be achieved if both
all family members to participate.
Of course, that does not mean we
become abusive parents.
Ready to begin. Mission
Arrest Large--Magnitude!
The beauty of this is when the ancient objects ...
It is Gallimimus. He could
run as far as 20 miles per hour.
25 miles per hour. You have to
read more.!
And it is the super--duper--saurus opinion.
Well, we continue
to another place.
Sometimes kids think they
knows better than in adults.
-- They do not know more than adults
"Just For The Stakeholder"
-- We should not.
-- But we have to.
Stay alert!
It seems fairly complicated.
With the right algorithms and variable
possible key combination can be found.
What about the possibility of
the door is not locked? Buuyaa!!
Buuyaa ..
What if they follow us?
Tyrannosaurus!
The most deadly predators.
Attacked without mercy
It's just a T--Rex statue, Max.
Let's go.
Always keep an eye on.
That's our baby.
If we get complacent a little while!
Who knows chaos
what will be done.
Hey, Max look.
He's definitely in there.
Yeah, but this thing covered.
pity.
Let's get out of here.
I'm not here just to infiltrate
to see the giant cover!
Let us remove the lid.
-- I do not know Ernie ...
-- I pull this section, you pull in there.
Be careful!
-- Hey, what are you doing?
-- Infrared motion detectors.
Wait!
Watch this!
Can I get into?
Ernie, I'd love to be
like before I was an adult!
Cool!
Now it's time.
One, two, three!
-- Very scary.
-- 900. No offense to board a rocket!
Not a problem.
Sarcosuchus.
I'm sure you do not want
met him in the darkness.
With teeth like that? I
do not want to meet at any time.
You can not lie
again to me, Ernie.
It's your 25 cents.
You'd better call a lawyer!
Secure location.
Shut up the kids.
I smell a spy
in the museum.
Let's go!
Goodbye forever!
Alright.
Ratings of 1 to 10?
Minus 50! You drive it without notice
and do not know where to go.
Calm Max.
I've been very familiar with this place.
I get it,
I get it.
You think you can?
Do not believe you underestimate me, Max.
I'm a little hurt!
Exit on the left.
I guess not.
Thank you for this award.
You back ...
Now I introduce the ...
"Boy--saurus is the problem."
Well ...
Could explain, technically
I did not violate orders.
Ernie ...
You asked me to go to the store after school.
And I've been there.
There is proof. I
leave a note.
"Back in 150 minutes."
You see, I'm not breaking orders.
I just went to study at the museum.
You know you've been violated.
Plus, the damage at the museum. They
announcement of their new pair robbed.
I know Mom, I'm sorry.
Deeds cause harm to
others, you must learn to fix it.
I should have been able to count on,
another party and one day will be.
I just wanted to see the skeleton.
They are just fossils millions of years,
they are not going to go anywhere.
Okay, now I
punish three weeks.
This peraturanku Ernie,
and there is no compromise!
Go into your room, close the door
until I call you for dinner.
Hemh, Mother of the Year, Haa ..
No one
requesting choice.
Can not you make your life
interesting than just bugging me alone.
Three weeks? It was a penalty
toughest you've ever received.
I would not be caught
if the alarm is not turned on.
And I know Max very thorough ...
Tarraaa ...
-- You!
-- I'm what?
You will receive a reply.
Enjoy your week sentenced to three.
This is not fair.
It never ends.
Ernie's time to go to the store.
Ernie's time to practice violin.
Time to clean up your room, Ernie.
What about the time Ernie?
When can I have my own rules.
There is an open window beside me.
At other times I would think twice.
I can not.
I do not want to.
But I have to!
Ernie, can not be trusted!
Max, open the door.
I came.
There are still weaknesses in the
door opener equipment my father.
Think.
Not your mother ...
Your mother does not punish you?
Stop it, stop it!
Yeah, he's punishing me for three weeks.
But you're here.
-- What about your father?
-- I had to help him after school a few months.
Open up your mind.
Friends, who else can.
No, not Mrs. Ernie
allow it to drink soda.
Ernie Her mother is not here.
Hehe ...
Is getting bigger garage?
True. We sell cars and
made a study room.
Father, Ernie is here.
Here!
Hey Dr. Santiago, how
development of its Time Machine?
Four years and still does not work.
So long, I think its key
not connected properly.
Now I think the problem
in the control panel.
Look.
Function relaynya functioning normally.
Transfer mode location, function.
I do not know.
You must be the father.
We certainly can.
You know the robot vacuum?
I'm sure, could probably use
as a time machine so that power can be.
Time in which I could
make my own rules?
Ratings of 1 to 10 ...
-- You can not do it.
-- No doubt.
Sneaking out and drinking soda.
Double trouble!
Basic handyman stalker!
Three weeks is not much. I will promise
make in the law for three years.
You guys be careful!
These items belonged to my father,
stop fighting.
Give the phone.
I do not do it!
Sneaking out, drinking soda ...
And damage the engine ... Dr. Santiago.
Ernie, you got three problems!
So this is my fault? I think not!
You came and suddenly the fun ...
... Stop.
Maybe there is construction work on the road.
What is it?
Max, do you have a dog that
you never tell me?
This is so weird.
Well, do not have the touch
I think the control panel is problematic.
Julia, are you okay?
-- Is he still there?
-- Yes, but ...
Look ... he's not going to hurt us.
She looks like ...
He smiles?
Good, now may we go home?
It was a real T--Rex.
Cool!!
Ernie!
Look out!
Calm down, he did not look
being caught.
Possible. But you can not
make our heads ... ducking.
Just relax. Do not you
look how cool this.
Ernie, he can bite and we
could not get out of this place.
I think ...
Museum has been doing the job ...
great to make this sculpture.
Feels very alive.
It's real ..
It's so real?
He licked it, like a newborn.
It makes sense.
This form of time machine
like a dinosaur egg.
It makes sense.
Hello ... Are we like a baby dinosaur?
He did not call all of them
for dinner, right?
No, he called all of them to
look at that cute baby.
And it looks like they're talking.
We are happy you joined Tyra.
Yeah, it looks like your eggs do not
've got a hitch.
The way you treat us like
your son is so wonderful time.
And you're entitled to
have your own child.
You're still keeping us?
I mean, maybe Sarco settles
then takes us.
Come on Neo, do not worry.
I'm not going anywhere.
You all are my family.
I'll take care of Sarco brothers.
And when my babies large
he will take care of you too.
-- What do we have here?
-- There is food? I'm very hungry.
What's the matter with you, are you nuts?
Do you want to get caught?
He can hurt you.
There's something happening here.
What do you see?
That's not me. I never
lose anything! Really!
Stand up!
Then why are here to
stinks, tell me?
I think his voice will not be hard.
Will you shut up?
Sarco brothers want to know
all about Tyra.
I have a plan!
We must immediately inform him about this.
Yeah, right.
Amateur basis!
Do not make them a voice,
they do not sound like us.
They look very strange.
They are gorgeous. And they will grow
big and strong like his mother.
Now everything is gone,
the baby should sleep. Go.
Alright.
This is our chance.
July, come on, we live a little while.
We can set the time machine to go home and
mother would never realize if we go.
We're not going to get in trouble.
This is not about negotiations, Ernie, this
on our return home.
Max, do you know how to work this thing?
Let me see.
Should be in the process of initialization ...
And the counting process is not working
because no power locks.
You mean we can not come home on time.
It could be any where and anytime.
I'll give it to them later, okay?
I mean, the mother dinosaurs must have been very
angry when the baby suddenly gone.
Do not worry on Jul ...
I'm sure it must exist in
about where we landed.
We'll find it.
Soon ...
Ernie, we're stuck here.
Everything will be fine.
Look around our July
This is Tyra Dino in the Cretaceous period.
And?
And everything is really great!
This is the story of our history.
Millions of years before we were born.
See, it was Stone Mystery.
And the nest is definitely his garage
Max, and we may be very close.
Home ...
Ernie? Dinner time.
Ernie Come on, I know you're angry,
but at least open your door.
Julia, did you see where your brother?
Go to catch Ernie.
Well, about where he was going.
He probably went to the usual place.
moment.
Hello Sue ...
Hello Dr. Santiago ...
Please, I hope he
called Diego ...
Can you come down?
Yeah sorry, I'm trying
improve robotku
Sorry.
-- Is Ernie here?.
-- Yeah, he's in the garage Max, I think Julia was there.
They're looking at Time Machine.
Time Machine?
When he was busy, let's explore.
To search for power key.
Ernie, if you were there,
I'll say to the mother.
It's up to you.
I'm having fun.
Hi, Mom .. Mother ...
Can I go out? Not!
Right, you should not go anywhere.
There is always a way out, we
look lived alone.
Oh yeaah.
What is it?
Yuuki ... Your brother brought gifts.
-- Let me see, where is it? Where are they?
-- Orphan.
Good for you Mom, let me see them.
Let me see them. Where are they?
They're what?.
They have different colors.
Had a brother, I finally had a brother.
I know one day it will get it.
Who will be sleeping next to mom ...
And of course it was me.
She will sing songs
The most I usually prefer.
Mutual love among friends, good friends,
you know now or not at all.
One question, why
they look ... weird?
What kind of dinosaur is that?
Do not know, but it's not the T--Rex.
Of course, safe place.
Keamanananya guard I painted recently.
Well it's not that I'm worried about.
What is it?
The kids are not here, as did
with a time machine.
So, this is what?
This dinosaur eggs.
If I'm not mistaken, this T--Rex.
Mean?
No eggs in my garage
of Cretaceous age.
It means the transfer system ...
function correctly.
That means the kids succeed
create a functioning time machine.
Sorry?
They go back to the future
millions of years ago.
Sorry???
-- Do not panic Sue ...
-- What exactly are you saying?
-- I really hate this place.
-- Will you shut up!
Mr. Sarco, Mr. Sarco more!
We are back.
Your right hand is back.
Mr. Sarco, Mr. Sarco Others?
Ah, finally you're here too.
Why are you guys so long?
They go out for a walk.
Let's meet, before
we eat them.
Do not eat me, I'm just fat.
If we do not immediately move out of here,
we had no choice.
Without the presence of the earthquake and Tyra.
Immediately, and there will not be any
in this valley will survive.
When we get Tyra, then the
will we get the other as well.
We need eggs,
That is what you've come.
You'd better bring good news.
Or you would hope we take
you in just one bite.
Boss we have some good news.
The news that will make you happy.
I saw the baby, it's all three.
Yeahh ..
They are really funny.
You'll want to squeeze his cheeks.
Another adoption?
Instead, he said they were his own son.
And it seems there is still one more egg in there.
Another egg?
If the egg is taken, he will look for it here.
Then we will get rid of
him forever.
The first night my babies.
I can not wait to teach
I know nothing.
And one day see them
saurus being his first defeat.
Looks like they will be hard to do
it, but it may be?
-- All right, go to sleep.
-- No it does not.
Now it's time to go to
search for power key.
No way!
You will not leave me alone,
millions of years ago and in the middle of the night.
All right, but we left early.
Before the mother dino up.
Sue, could you a little peace of mind!
No, I would mengguncangmu
again, after I took a breath.
Hear.
Time machine has a system for
re automatically in three hours.
... To reduce unnecessary distractions.
Thus, the time machine will
appeared in, five ...
... Four, three, two, one!
I think the clock is broken.
Okay, now we're into Plan B.
-- What is plan B?
-- Start thinking about a plan C.
Hear, as scientifically.
Is not the key to better search
performed three people than just the two?
-- Did you see something?
-- There was nothing here.
Did you hear it?
Hear what?
It!
I'm sure a strange dinosaur again.
Her voice is very strange, they came!
Maybe you're right.
Hey, wait for me!
I caught you!
You can thank me later.
Oh mother would be very upset.
Ernie, what would we do?
Capture the tree!
I do not want to lose my brother.
I've just met, wait for me!!
What will we
do now?
Enjoy the journey!
Look out!
Great rock!
Max, hold on to Julia.
What would you do?
I'll show you a new kind of sport.
Gosh.
Ernie!
Perfect!
Well, once again I explained the plan.
I swear, if you do not get it.
You will feel the consequences.
Even though you do not understand, pretend.
We will be sneaking into the nest,
when he went we took the eggs.
I'll settle for looking for something,
I was a good penyelinap.
Aw, something bit me.
Where the poor animals
who want to bite you?
Help him to pull.
I? Why should I do it?
And not you?
Because I was the leader, understand!
Not you.
One day I'm gonna slap him.
Geli ... amused ..
Be quiet, big feet.
This thing involves
between your fingers.
I think the gecko.
Why did you not immediately
Interesting that thing!!??
We have jobs.
Yeah, we never fail.
-- Skill?
-- 350!
Buuyaa!
Ernie? Is he being
joking with me?
Ernie, Ernie, Ernie?
Wow, he can talk.
He repeats what we say.
Incredible!!
Good work, helping us
from the rocky waters earlier.
I'll call you, Dodger!
Dodger? Dodger, Dodger!
See it, Alamosaurus!
The creature was like to live forever.
I told Tyra, do not eat when pregnant
red meat. Now, they are at blurred.
Lambeosaurus, calm them vegetarian.
Dude, now you're diligent exercise?
I will be able to survive.
Once completed.
Hey, Pterodactyl!
The creatures will protect
us from Sarco, I doubt it?
Enough to protect her, let's go.
This incredible great!
And you'll never see it,
if I do not break the rules mother.
Well, all of this really worth it.
Now we can go back home.
-- What? Back to the nest?
-- No, go back to ...
-- Ha?
-- What is it?
No, I think I'm ...
Apparently, the mother managed to find us.
We recommend that you regret
deeds, Orphan.
I thought I could trust
my babies to you
-- They can get stuck in the bottom of the valley, and if Sarco ...
-- Hey, I always notice them.
At least my eyes keep eye
other malicious ...
But Mom, the kids are testing you,
you're a good mother, so do I.
Then?
If they begin to wonder
to play itself ...
.. Time to teach them survive
without me, they are keepers.
Mom, they really liked me, and they
Dodger call me, I love it.
-- Ernie, Ernie, Ernie?
-- I'll be there Dodger, but I have to find ...
-- I have to find its key.
-- Key to Power!
Do not misunderstand me, you and your mother both
once, and this place was incredible.
It's about the other house.
Home? Home, home ...
Anyone who says that her babies
Tyra could scare ...
Yeah!
Fabulous!
Buuyaa!
've Thought of something?
I'm afraid Max stuck in
Among the many dinosaurs, and you?
Did not you become scientists?
Yeah, I'm the scientist.
And I had to think of a way to restore
children like my way of solving scientific problems.
Alright.
Time to move to the side of the machine
others in the same position.
-- So that the kids get back to us.
-- Wait!
Why do they have to come back to us?
Is that a trick question?
Instead, we can
come to them.
We do not have a time machine to another.
But you managed to get it.
Yeah, but it took four years of probation.
That's because you do not have
an exemplary mother with you.
"Mother Rule"
Please, give me half an hour
to find its key.
I had to find its key, and
I do not want you to forbid it.
-- Max, where Ernie?
-- Ernie?
-- I do not know.
I do not know!
Ernie, what happened to you?
Him, punishing ...
Ernie, Ernie, Ernie ...
Ernie, Max, Max again, dino mom ...
I ..., Dodger.
Hey, look!
Did you ever find
trail like this before?
-- Not.
-- They are all around the nest.
There seems to be a
're stalking us.
I know where they go.
Julia, come here!
The traces are from
river, let us follow.
Hey Mom, are you going to let
we leave the nest?
Well, I also want to see
where did this trail.
And, good enough for their practice.
Exercise, nice bu.
That's why you become a mother!
The place is secure.
Come down, fast fast!
Fast, calm down.
Be careful not to drop it.
Try not to ...
I caught it, take care of their eggs.
If you mess it up, then
you're in trouble. Come quickly.
Hold up, hard to manage them.
Do not stop,
you should fast.
Are there tracks, Julia?
Yes, this trail is much longer, and
I think there are three different tracks here.
And they walked together.
You're terrific.
Almost everything I know,
I learned while spying on Ernie.
Ernie what's up?
You are acting strange.
-- Listen friend, I actually have ...
-- Hey, look at this!
Friends, friends, friends ...
The trail comes
from down there.
Located on the valley floor.
Let's check it.
Apparently not.
What's the problem? We can handle
whatever is down there.
I guess he will not be
let us go.
Is this what you feel when
mother said no, Ernie?
He really knows the place
this, we should stick with it.
Does your head hit something?
If it is better than the nest.
Listen, we have to keep
baby better.
-- Once they get down to the valley floor.
-- Not!
Not to the valley floor, Sarco
brothers there.
They have teeth, sharp teeth.
And claw for tearing apart!
Then the earthquake, and the magma
boiling, and the temperature is very hot.
We will find a way out.
I can not believe my car?
Yes, it looks good does not it?
You know I never worked
this fast in my life.
Besides, I never saved
my son at the time of the Cretaceous.
Simply wonderful to see you work.
You know, you make me do it.
I've given up, before
you yell loudly at me.
Sorry.
I can see where Ernie
gain energy.
True.
For team work?
Oh, I do not ...
But why not?
Maybe we should sneak
and go down there.
Julia!
Max, they are dinosaurs.
They can not understand us.
We could be in trouble.
The power key.
I thought it would never
get it again!
I mean ...
Wait, you think you do not
will get it again?
What do you mean?
I saw and took it, then
keep it in my pants pocket.
You what?
You're in a hurry to go home while
I still want to be here.
I'm not ready to go back to the mother,
regulations, and be punished.
Can you trust me?
So in other words, you
keep us here?
We could have been eaten by something.
And almost wish we
stay here forever.
It's like the mother says Ernie ...
You do not care what happens to
others as long as you can have fun.
Well, I found the key to power.
So let's go.
Time machine!
Hey, I do not hide it.
We'll never get home.
Julia, we'll be fine.
It's all your fault.
I miss mom, and you
no, right Ernie?
Of course I miss him.
-- My baby is unfortunate. -- What's the problem?
It's just an egg--shaped object.
Tyra Why not come here?
I think he's concerned with this thing.
It could be because we do
good job.
Our team of experts, until he
do not know the eggs disappeared.
Are not we great?
He did not come, because he
more concerned with her babies.
They are really funny.
And so pink.
Let me eat it.
If they fail to
The next mission.
Give our babies
Tyra, then he will come.
Well, should we
not planning something?
Like what?
Wish we could live 100 years
again, so that we can meet the mother?
Wait ...
Ernie, you're a genius!
What are you talking about?
Julia, the mother asked what we do
if we leave the house when she was not there?
Leave a message?
True!
What if we carve
message to his father Max ...
Shows ... what to do
that time machine works.
Functioning ...
That?
Splash of soda in the control panel.
True, we'll carve
in a place easily seen.
Prominent place, such as a building.
Always place we see every day.
Mystery rock!
Exactly!
Alright.
It is finished? Are you ready? It is finished? Can be tried?
I mean, this started to affect me soda.
Now we just try it.
Come on!
Hopefully these things work.
I do not understand.
I made the same
with the previous one.
Which previously was
does not work, is not it?
You're right, it means that the children do
something on his time machine.
Oow ...
Wow, Dr. Santiago careful, we are in a hurry
but these houses are our neighbors.
Call me Diego.
Be careful Ernie, I hate you but
I do not want to see your legs broken.
Julia, it certainly succeeded.
I'm sure.
-- I want you to catch it.
-- Go, rock climbing it.
I think it should
he did it.
Ernie!
Ernie.
Thank you.
Julia!
-- Hold this ...
-- It?
Here you are.
Hang in there, Julia!
I never omit
key, then the time machine.
But I'm not going to
to miss my brother!
Ernie!
Let's quickly run!
Before we catch something.
Restore my baby!
Restore my best friend's sister!
Oh no!
Follow the thief!
Oh great!
Sorry ...
Have you ever seen a baby reptile times
pre--history with sharp little teeth?
Right over there.
Oow ..
Call for animal catcher!
Hold on.
This way, right?
My shop, my stuff!
We should set him up with something.
Go to the "Drive Thru"!
-- Welcome to Burgersaurus.
-- I need 50 burger, do as fast as you can!
-- Are you going to buy a promotional pack or regular.
-- You hear, 50 burgers!
And two large sodas.
Thanks for the ride.
Trail, I could follow it.
No, it's a trap!
Welcome to our home, Tyra.
Note, you need
more than courage.
Julia?
Julia!
Masamu in this valley is over, Tyra.
We will take over the place, now.
The time machine.
You've got two babies to be protected.
It will make you hard
protect yourself.
-- Sorry, Julia. I can not save you.
-- Where's Ernie?
I do not know.
Geez, I must be doing something.
Come on Tyra.
Give it up, and we'll make it easier.
Not ever!
If so, we would
doing it the hard way.
Come on, get outta here!
Find out where the noise was.
Try not to eat.
That's a great suggestion.
Come on!
Let's take, little baby.
Rightly so.
Hemh, if you see me gathering,
they would cancel my appreciation.
What are friends for?
-- Come on, take it.
-- Almost there ...
A few steps away.
Got you!
Tyra baby!
Oh no.
-- Finally, I know we can ...
-- Handing on Sarco.
I assure you it and of course.
Tyra would jump in front of me?
Wait, Tyra will jump in front of me?
Buuyaa!
-- Dodger!
-- Ernie!
The final goal!
Let's find a mother dinosaur!
I wish there was a female voice on the island.
Perfect, should you
do in this situation?
Does it smell?
Yeah!
It was brilliant!
It's like the Max plan
he learned from Ernie.
He was a smart kid
and I let him down!
Alright, let's settle this problem.
Let's go.
We found a starting place it happened!
Ernie!
Hey friends!
Friends ... friends.
He continued to take care of you.
He fights for us.
Objects against which we
look at the museum, Sarcosuchus.
I knew. And I would like
them in the form of fossils.
Ernie!
Earthquake began.
Time machine!
But Mrs. Dino.
Ernie, we do not have much time.
Let's go home.
-- Wait, we can not leave it.
-- No Ernie, let's go!
You guys, come on!
Ernie, give me the key!
Dino mother.
Are we sinking?
-- Moderate earthquakes.
-- Let's get out of here!
-- Ernie, Ernie, Ernie!
-- Ernie, what is it?
Friends! I know how
meaningful home for you ...
... But we can not just leave.
You know Ernie, I will always
is right behind you.
Hemh, watch this!
Dino--Rex Hey, over here!
Was not hit!
Right here!
Earthquake!!
You hurt my brothers basis ugly!
Max!
Not!!
Dodger!
Julia, his use of light!
See you at the museum.
Oh tidaak!
Sorry Sue, this machine does not work.
As usual, the failure
Another of Dr. Santiago.
Very difficult to control my son.
You know the dinner hour? And when I looked,
how often they were not in his room.
And if Ernie's out, though only in
backyard ... I always make it ...
Leave a message ...
Sue?
Wait!
Wait ...
Let's go!
Ernie?
Dodger?
Ernie!
Julia!
-- Max!
-- Dad!
Mother!
-- Oh dear.
-- I thought I would never see you again.
Look out!
Everything is down!
You're in trouble with the wrong family.
And now you're gonna die!
Let me know if magmanya too hot Sarco.
Children, sheltering behind me!
Mother, do not!
Ernie, shut up in the back!
You're not going to have my daughter.
Mom, this is not what you think.
Mom, stop!
He found us, he treats
we like his own son.
What?
That's right, he even
to lick our faces.
-- Like that.
-- Disgusting, but very unusual.
You saw bu, wow,
he is their size version.
-- Mom!
-- Dad! -- Max.
Functioning time machine,
as you've said.
And I get the idea
new, namely Sarcosuchus?
-- Yeah.
-- Cool!
He looks sad.
This will make it back smiling.
Let's get out of here!
Thank you for taking care of us.
And to not eat us, of course.
Thank you, ma'am.
You know, I'm going to miss this place.
You kissed my plan, sounds of the forest ..
Dinosaur ... battle.
I'll miss you too.
Come on, Ernie!
Once again, thank you for everything.
And beware the threat magmanya.
-- Good--bye! Adios!
-- We will miss you. Good--bye!
How do you know that you must
soda splashed on the control panel?
I see the engraving on the stone.
I do not have time to carve!
Because I have to catch Julia, so ...
Who carved it?
Dodger, Dodger, Dodger.
Oow ...