♪ Oh oh ♪
♪ l'm tired of being alone... ♪
♪ When a girl ain't my own
to call "baby" ♪
♪ My baby ♪
♪ Been looking high and low... ♪
Hey, Katalina, it's me.
Just want to make sure
that you're coming tonight.
You're on the VlP list, plus two.
All right, honey.
Call me when you get here.
Bye.
Hello?
- Armands?
- Red velvet.
L didn't think you were listening to me
when l told you about this.
Of course.
You look amazing.
- Thank you.
- Are you ready?
- We have reservations in 20 minutes.
- Yup.
Where are you taking me?
A surprise.
♪ Tonight tonight ♪
♪ Somehow you see me run here ♪
♪ l've been searching upstairs ♪
♪ And l've been looking
all over this club ♪
♪ We just was
on the dance floor ♪
♪ Getting it on ♪
♪ She told me she was gonna... ♪
You've reached Prime.
Leave a message after the tone.
Prime, l see you're still not answering
your phone calls. Um...
look, l'm coming tonight,
so my name better be on the list.
Skylar, Skylar,
stop fussing over me.
Grandma, your dinner
is in the microwave.
All you have to do is warm it.
Please take that.
- l'm old, not disabled.
- Can you take your medicine, please?
Thank you.
- Mmm.
- So you have my cellphone number, right?
- Mmm. Mmm. Mmm.
- Lf you need anything, just call.
- Maybe l shouldn't go.
- Skylar.
- Hmm?
- Go to the party. Have fun.
Okay.
Lf you need anything, just call me.
- l'm gonna keep my cellphone on.
- Mm-hmm, mm-hmm.
- l love you.
- L love you too.
Now you have some fun!
You know how you spell "fun"? M-A-N!
But don't bring back no DNA.
♪ So l went back to the bar ♪
♪ To get me another drink ♪
♪ She said, "Boy,
are you coming back?" ♪
♪ l said, "Girl, what you think?" ♪
♪ That's when she said... ♪
♪ l think l'm falling in love ♪
♪ On this dance floor ♪
♪ Tonight tonight ♪
♪ The way you move,
l'm thinking l want more ♪
♪ Tonight tonight ♪
♪ l think l'm falling in love
on this dance floor ♪
♪ Tonight tonight ♪
♪ The way you move,
l'm thinking l want more ♪
- ♪ Let's go, y'all ♪
- ♪ Tonight tonight. ♪
♪ Y'all, look at this shit ♪
♪ DJ Class coming hard
with the flow ♪
♪ Rappers are in that 410... ♪
Hey, Prime. lt's Skylar.
Just letting you know that l'm here.
But it's probably gonna
take me a while to get in.
- All right. Bye.
- Skylar?
- Yeah?
- L'm China, Prime's bodyguard.
- Oh, hi.
- He's waiting for you at the table.
Oh, okay. Thank you.
♪ Steal spotlights, baby,
calling me klepto ♪
♪ Brother Classy,
better holla at your boy ♪
♪ Oh my goodness, oh my God ♪
♪ Oh my God, oh my God ♪
♪ Oh my goodness, oh my God... ♪
Now look here, baby girl, l don't care
if you stroll in with Beyoncé.
Ain't nobody get
in the VlP unless l say so.
Now you could pass it up,
club with the scrubs if you want,
but if you're trying to kick it
with me afterwards,
you can't come without her and she
damn sure can't come without you.
- Hey, Kalif.
- What, man?
- Come on, dawg, l need you.
- Oh damn.
Think about it. l'll be back.
Yo, man, what's up?
L was just setting up
my 25th hour.
You don't even know
how to tell time, bro.
- What?
- Let's go, boy. Come on.
♪ Pardon my French,
but fuck you, haters... ♪
Girl, l thought
you said we had VlP.
Did you not see your name on the list?
They ran out of wristbands,
so Lonzo has to come down
and bring 'em to us.
- Where the hell's he at?
- Trust me, he has five minutes
- or l'm onto the next one.
- Onto the next what exactly?
Onto the next location, the next venue,
- the next man if need be.
- Mmm.
- Could you take longer?
- Oh hell no!
L thought we had security!
Who let her through?
And please say something. l'll put
a restraining order on you quick.
The only thing needing restraining
is you and your ego.
- Yo, dawg, she obsessed with me, man.
- Hey. Hey, don't start.
- Here you go again.
- Case in point... you here, ain't you?
- Always talking.
- Always talking?
You always running your mouth too.
Always got a drink in your hand.
Alcoholic, man.
- Look...
- Yo.
- Everywhere l go she pop up behind me.
- You wish.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
- Please.
- You're very welcome.
No, don't give her no wristband, man.
- She don't deserve it.
- Dawn, there you go, baby.
Naw. Tell Daddy you want it,
you might be able to get it.
- Daddy? You wish l would call you daddy.
- Dawn, he's got jokes.
- You gonna sell me out like that?
- You got jokes tonight.
What's up?
Had something
l had to take care of.
L'll be there in 10 minutes.
- ♪ Mustang! ♪
- ♪ All right, all right ♪
♪ Y'all fucked up now ♪
♪ l know you can
hear me out there ♪
- ♪ Ladies! ♪
- ♪ Yeah ♪
- Hey, Chris.
- Hey, gorgeous. How you doing?
- l'm good.
- Hey.
- How are you?
- L'm hanging in there.
Ls Prime here yet?
Umm... ah...
- What's wrong?
- One second.
Really, China?
You're just gonna walk past me
like you don't even see me?
Autumn, give me a minute.
L'll be right back.
A minute?
- Hey, beautiful.
- Hi.
Hey, thanks for coming out.
L'm sorry l didn't come
get you at the door.
L didn't want
to be rude to my guests.
Oh, it's okay. l understand.
Lt's no big deal.
See? That's why l like you.
- You so easy.
- Oh really? l'm easy?
- Autumn.
- Really?
Lf you just wait one second,
step to the side,
- China'll be right back, okay?
- So that's how l'ma get played today?
But... okay,
so all of... really?
- This isn't my fault. Come on.
- Slide over, big boy.
- That's how you gonna play me?
- Lnside, y'all, come on.
They with me, they good.
Don't worry about it.
- What's up, homes? l'm good.
- Um, Kalif?
Lt's cool.
Come in there, guys.
So for some reason
my name not on the list.
L don't know why you looking at me.
You ain't my people.
- Um, excuse me?
- You Prime old news. Tell you what.
- l'll holla at him, see what l can do.
- Really?
- That's all l got.
- That's some fucking bullshit.
- Yo, Prime. Oh snap.
- Yo yo.
- l take it you Skylar. Kalif.
- Nice to meet you.
Pleasure's mine.
Prime, he can't stop talking about you.
- Yo, we ready for the toast?
- No no, Dallas ain't here yet.
- Not yet?
- Where the hell is Dallas at right now?
He said he was 10 minutes away
20 minutes ago.
Oh man, l don't understand how white
dudes show up on colored-people time.
This is not the day
for his ass to be late.
Tell me about it, man.
- Yo, my man, you can't park there.
- Tow it.
♪ Tequila... ♪
♪ Lick, salt, shot, lime ♪
♪ Lick, salt, shot, lime,
lick, salt, shot, lime... ♪
Double scotch, neat.
♪ Shot, lime, lick,
salt, shot, lime... ♪
My man. Cheers.
Dallas.
Yes, Autumn?
How may l help you?
Get me the fuck in VlP.
Look, l'm not trying
to get in the middle...
And l really don't wanna hear
anything you gotta say, okay?
He has a girl up there,
doesn't he?
L'm just trying
to have a good time.
Do you promise to behave?
Look, you promise...
l'm not taking you in there
- unless you promise.
- L promise.
♪ We can turn this party up,
we can get... ♪
All right.
- ♪ Shot, lime, lick, salt, shot, lime ♪
- ♪ Over over... ♪
Ah. Come on.
- ♪ Lick, salt, shot, lime, lick... ♪
- ♪ Over over ♪
- ♪ Over ♪
- ♪ Lick, salt, shot, lime... ♪
How you doing, my man?
These three are with me.
Hey, you all right.
- Yo yo yo, Dallas.
- Okay, he said l'm with him.
She's good, man.
Dallas, yo,
where the fuck you been?
- What's up?
- Are you crazy?
Look, man, don't worry about it.
L got it under control.
He's gonna kill you.
Yo, man, what took you so long?
- Rule ♪1, baby.
- A'ight.
What?
♪ Lick, salt, shot, lime,
lick, salt, shot, lime... ♪
- You responsible.
- L got it.
♪ Take a bite, boy... ♪
Yo yo, we here
at 1080 holding it down.
Shouts to my man Prime.
Had an outstanding season,
balled his ass off
this year and of course...
Made the all-star team.
You know, sometimes we say
growing up,
it's important to have
someone that you look up to,
like a role model.
And in my case,
that was my best friend.
You deserve everything
you have, my man.
You've got a lot of good shit
coming your way.
Yo, man, nice speech.
Come on, seriously.
We've been at this thing for a while.
And l know we make it look easy,
but the shit is really pretty hard.
You know what l'm saying?
Hey, but we work hard,
so we can play hard.
L'm gonna go
to the ladies room real fast.
- Okay, you know where it is?
- L'm sure it's in the back somewhere.
Yeah, back to the right.
♪ Tippy-toe, tippy-toe,
tippy-toe... ♪
Mmm! Mmm!
- Fuck that shit.
- Hey hey.
- No, move, Lonzo.
- Don't start.
You think l'm gonna stand here
and let him disrespect me like that?
- Don't start, Autumn.
- Please. Please.
You need to chill. l'm about
to throw you up outta here.
Kalif, get the fuck outta here.
You think you running shit?
You ain't running nothing.
You just like one of Prime's hos.
Always on his dick,
even when he treats you like shit.
Yeah, and what you need to do...
take care of your babies, okay?
- What is it now?
- You leave my family out of this!
Three babies
by two different baby mamas?
- Fuck you, bitch!
- Get the fuck outta here, Autumn.
- No, you don't tell me what to do.
- The fuck you talking about?
- Me and you are done! lt's over.
- Oh, really? Really?
- We've been done.
- And how am l supposed to know that?
Because you were
man enough to tell me?
And we both know
that didn't happen.
So, what, l can't come toast
the great Optimus Prime?
- ls that it?
- What is wrong with you, Autumn?
- Get her outta here, China.
- Get off me!
Her shit so good,
you gotta shame me
in front of all
these fucking people?!
- Get your crazy ass outta here!
- Fuck you!
Hello?
Hi, Grandma, just checking on you.
Skylar, why are you
calling me from a party?
Oh God, you should see this place.
Lt's amazing.
Lt's like a million
beautiful people here.
- What's wrong with that?
- L don't know.
- ...fabulous in that dress.
- Listen to me, baby.
You can't let anyone
steal yourjoy.
Lf he'd just look my way tonight,
he's so gonna get it.
Wasn't he with someone?
Who? Little Miss Muffet?
She can't keep a man like Prime.
L saw how excited you were to go to
that party, so if you're there, be there.
Make them remember your name.
No, l'm just gonna
come home a little earlier.
Lt better not be
because it's time for me
- to take those blood-thinner pills.
- No, ma'am.
Honestly,
l'd just rather be there than here.
All right, baby.
L'll see you in a little while.
Hmm.
♪ Strike a pose,
strike a pose, strike a pose ♪
♪ Strike a... strike a...
strike a... strike a pose ♪
♪ Touch your toes, touch your
toes, touch your toes... ♪
- Hey, you back.
- Long line at the bathroom.
- Sorry.
- All right, no problem.
Everything okay?
- You look like something's wrong.
- No, everything's okay.
L'm gonna leave, actually.
But l thought you were
having a good time.
L am.
L'm having a great time.
L don't like leaving my grandmother
by herself for a long time.
- Mmm.
- Sorry.
- Are you sure?
- Yeah. l'm sorry.
All right.
Let me walk you out.
You don't have to walk me out.
Lt's okay.
You know what?
Lt's your party,
enjoy it. l'll be okay.
Just call me tomorrow?
♪ Shake it like a tambourine,
juicy like a tangerine ♪
♪ Glad l got ahold of teen,
yeah, she a beauty queen... ♪
- A'ight.
- ♪ Juicy like a tangerine ♪
- ♪ Glad l got ahold of teen... ♪
- Yeah.
- Are you okay?
- L'm fine.
L'm sorry, l just...
l saw you crying.
No. l'm sorry.
L just... l had a bad night so...
- Sorry.
- Are you Prime's new girl?
No, we're just friends.
Mmm.
You seem like a sweet girl.
Be careful.
Thank you.
♪ Oh oh ♪
♪ l'm tired of being alone ♪
♪ When a girl ain't my own
to call "baby" ♪
♪ My baby ♪
♪ Been looking high and low ♪
♪ No matter where l go ♪
♪ Hey, lady, l can't find my lady ♪
♪ So if you see her ♪
♪ Could you let me know? ♪
♪ 'Cause l need her ♪
♪ Before l walk
out the door, hey! ♪
♪ l think l'm falling in love
on this dance floor ♪
♪ Tonight tonight ♪
♪ The way you move... ♪
Let me find out
if Prime is a foodie.
L'm starving.
- Okay, what do we have?
- Let's see.
We could make sandwiches.
- Not so much.
- What's that?
Jackpot! Lasagna.
- Hold on, there we go.
- Thank you.
Nice. You want some wine?
Yes, please.
Figure out how this ♪ works. ♪
All right.
Look at you, knowing your way
around a kitchen.
That's hot.
- You know how to cook too?
- Tsss!
There isn't much l don't know
how to do, Lonzo.
- Thought you'd know this by now.
- There, you see, you see?
You can't just be sexy, can you?
Huh-uh.
You gotta be cocky too.
Hey, l'm not being cocky.
L'm just telling the truth.
- Right.
- Seriously though, l actually did study
under some of the top chefs
in Paris for like a year.
- Mmm. l love France.
- Yeah?
L love it.
L shot a film there a few years ago.
L swear, the food there is like...
- Oh, it's just so good.
- Mm-hmm.
- lt's delicious.
- Yes, my mom firmly believes
that a woman should
be able to cook for her man.
Sounds like you have
a smart mother.
You have no idea.
You're absolutely beautiful.
You know that?
Thank you.
And you can cook?
Skylar.
Just wanted to give you a call,
make sure
you made it home safe.
Lt was really nice
to see you tonight.
Yeah.
Hey, why don't you give me
a call in the morning?
Maybe we can grab
brunch or something.
All right?
Sleep well.
What are you doing here?
Time out. Tell me l didn't throw
a kick-ass party last night, man.
Diddy ain't got shit on me.
Bad shit... bad shit, seriously.
What l wanna know is
where the fuck were you all night?
L already told you... rule ♪1.
What's rule ♪1 again?
ABC... Always Be Closing.
Bingo.
Right there, my man.
Those rules don't work, man.
Come on.
Had to close down
the Carnegie chick last night.
- Yo, how'd she do, man?
- She had a Prime Alexander night.
28 points, shot 54%
from the three-point line.
- Damn, that's pretty good.
- That is a good night.
Are you gonna see her again?
Nah. l'm already working
on my next lottery pick.
Of course you are.
Hey, hold up.
Seriously, what was up with Autumn?
That's what l wanna know.
Dude, she was tripping all night.
Yo, that's Dallas. l told you
not to let her ass in the party.
She was fine until
she saw you kiss Skylar.
What? Yo, look, she was crazy
from the jump, man.
- Red flag.
L told his ass.
- Amen.
- Will you guys relax?
- Damn, man!
- Relax.
Lt's all good.
Whatever, man.
Yo, anyone else close last night?
Well, l had a trez Nathaniel.
- A trez what?
- A dude?
A dude? No, man, the two chicks
from the pool last night.
Man! l'm telling you...
strawberries and wine, candles.
Lt was quite exquisite.
L'm feeling that.
L'm very happy for you.
- What about you, Zo?
- Oh, l had a good time, man.
Y'all know he was handcuffed
to Katalina all night,
talking about "l love you, baby.
L love you, baby."
l'll fucking kill you.
Yo, what's up with you
and her, anyway?
Man, l don't know.
L like her.
- l like her a lot. Yeah.
- Okay. Okay.
You know, just be
careful with her.
- l will.
- Yeah.
You know what? Actually,
go ahead and let's redesign
- this whole setup over here.
- The scarves?
Yeah, l don't like it.
And let's redress her too.
- Okay.
- Anyway, like l was saying,
his tie and handkerchief
matched my dress,
Prime warned me that l should've
put my sunglasses on
- in the car, but...
- Ooh!
- l know, right?
- At night?
Oh!
- Hey!
- Hi! How are you, girls?
- You look so cute.
- You too.
- Hello.
- Hey, Heidi. Hi, honey, how are you?
- Super cute. Have a seat.
- Thanks.
Dylan, do you mind getting us
a couple of glasses of wine?
- Not at all.
- Mm-hmm.
So how are you guys doing?
- Good.
- Good, how are you?
- Fabulous as always.
- Of course.
So l guess you know
why we're here.
We need something amazing
to wear to the Rico Terrell gala.
- Oh, okay. Of course.
- And l heard this year
it's an all-black affair.
L wonder who decided to do that.
- Mmm, that's me.
- Oh, okay.
L'll go and get
you guys the book
and l'll show you what
l have coming in next week.
- Okay.
- Okay?
- Ladies.
- Thank you.
You're welcome.
Here you go, sweetie.
- So, Autumn...
- Mm-hmm?
Is this the wine
that you purchased
while you were
in San Francisco last week?
L wasn't in San Francisco last week.
Why? What's going on?
- lt's probably nothing.
- What's probably nothing?
Okay, spill it.
Jessica said that she saw Prime
in San Francisco last week
with another woman.
And that gossip website said that
you were kicked out of Prime's party.
- Mm-hmm.
Well, you shouldn't believe
everything you read.
Okay, first of all l was not kicked out.
We had a fight.
Lt wasn't the first
and it won't be the last.
Okay, and what about that girl
that he was kissing at his party?
- You know, the one he was all up on?
- Oh, you mean the peasant
who was rocking last year's
rummage-sale collection?
- l'm not worried about her in the least.
- Ahem!
Maybe we could show them
the new Norell collection.
Mmm! Yes, l am sure
one of these beauties
can pull off such a stunning dress.
You know what?
L have work to do,
so l'm gonna go.
But you ladies shop.
- Okay?
- Thank you.
Okay, um, maybe let's take a look
at a few dresses.
Do you mind?
- Just bring out what you have.
- Yeah.
L'd be happy to.
Carnegie, if you don't stop
checking that phone...
do you think it's gonna ring
just because you want it to?
L'm just checking the service.
Sometimes it gets spotty in here.
Uh-huh.
Yet l have the same carrier
and l'm four bars strong.
L know, l know, l know.
Why hasn't he called me?
You just saw him last night.
He's probably working today.
L know, l know.
Lt's just...
that was the most amazing date.
Well, what did he say
when he dropped you off?
You... you mean when he left?
- So he came in?
- Oh yeah. Yeah.
- Well...
- Lt was amazing.
L'm not even kidding.
This is the best date l've ever been on.
- Hands down. Hands down.
- So you slept with him after dinner
and he hasn't called you back.
- lt's not like that.
- Not like what?
You're making it seem like
because he slept with me
he doesn't want to be with me.
Well, have you ever
gone on this long
- without him speaking to you?
- L mean...
not... not since we met.
Lt's probably nothing.
- You think?
- L know. l'm sure you're right.
Sounds like you guys have
an amazing connection.
Now let's get dressed
and get some drinks at Duke's.
Your phone rings in other places
besides the living room.
- Hey.
- Hey, you.
Well, they're gone.
Umm...
how you doing?
Are you doing okay?
L'm fine.
You sure?
Yes, l'm sure.
No, l'm just wondering,
'cause having them
catty bitches in your store...
- you know.
- Who, Heidi and Shannon?
- Yes, Heidi and Shannon.
- Oh, l'm not worried about them at all.
They will never change. But you know,
as long as they continue to shop here,
l really don't care.
Amen.
Umm...
so you looking at that website?
L don't even know what website
they're talking about, so...
- Whobangingwho.com.
- And how do you know that?
Girl, please, do not let
the bougie fool you.
You know l keep up on my gossip.
My college girlfriend
runs the site.
Umm...
l saw these pictures
this morning...
Prime kissing that girl.
Honey, why didn't you just tell me
that you guys were having trouble?
Because it's no big deal.
- lt...
- Lt's not that serious.
Lt's serious.
Dylan, l really don't wanna talk
about this right now, so...
Yo yo yo, l got a delivery.
Umm...
l'll get it.
- Hi, Quenton.
- Hi.
Dylan, when are you gonna stop playing
and let me take you out to dinner?
- Huh.
- Mmm. Man.
- What is this?
- Lt's a delivery for your cousin.
- On a Saturday?
- Apparently it's a special delivery.
Okay. Right this way.
Sorry. Delivery.
- Oh, hey, Que.
- Miss lady. l have a delivery for you.
Are you serious?
Umm...
Are you waiting for a tip?
Seriously? You...
- he just asked me out.
- Hey, l gotta save up.
We all know how
you singletary ladies are.
- Bye, Que.
- Wow. Nuh-uh.
Dylan, call me.
You won't regret it.
L... l don't even know.
What is this? ls this from Milan?
What'd you get?
Did that say it was from Prime?
Maybe it's some new shoes.
Autumn?
These are...
is this your stuff
from Prime's house?
- lt looks that way.
- He cut up your pictures?
Apparently so.
Honey, l'm...
l'm so sorry.
But this is stupid, okay?
This is petty.
Look... okay, l'm gonna...
l'm gonna take care
of this, okay?
Yeah, don't...
don't worry about it.
Umm, l got it.
Okay?
Hm-mmm, Grandma.
L got it.
- Mmm.
- Whew.
- Hi, can l help you?
- Miss Hathaway?
- Yes.
- Good afternoon, ma'am.
L'm your driver for today,
compliments of Mr. Prime Alexander.
Your first appointment
00 p.m.
My first appointment?
Yes, ma'am. l can't
tell you where we're going,
but l do have a schedule here for your
grandmother so she's not worried.
So this is one of those
scavenger hunts or something.
L'm not at liberty
to say, ma'am,
but l do expect your granddaughter
to have a lovely evening.
- Gimme one minute.
- Not a problem, ma'am.
You remember that purse
that l lost last year in Vegas?
Uh-huh, 'cause you forgetful.
Why is that the newer version in purple?
- You want it?
- L do. l love it.
Well, l got a surprise for you waiting
at the house. l think you might like it.
- Shut up. No, you don't.
- L guarantee l do.
- Stop!
- Right next to the new shoes l got you.
Hi, Cash.
- Keep it moving.
- Baby, come on.
Let's go see if they have that bag
you was looking at last week.
Huh-uh, don't try
to change the subject.
How the hell does that ho
gonna come over here,
talking some "hey, Cash,"
like she knows you like that?
- l don't know that girl.
- Where do you know that girl from?
- Like l said, l don't...
Maybe she was at the club
or somewhere with Prime.
- You know he got groupies everywhere.
- Next time
you need to tell your little bitches
not to come over and talk to you...
- My bitches?
- ...when they see you with your woman.
L'm glad you recognize that.
Now can we keep it moving?
- No, l'm serious, Kalif.
- You causing as scene for nothing.
Try me if you think l'm playing.
L'm so tired of that simple shit.
- l don't care if l'm causing a scene.
- Look, l ain't do shit, a'ight?
No, you ain't do shit.
You think you slick.
You think l'm stupid.
But l got something for that ass.
You wait and see.
- See, that's your problem right there.
- L gonna find her.
You always trying
to threaten somebody.
L'm not threatening you.
That shit was disrespectful.
- Come on. You know what?
- No. No no no, come here.
- Let's go introduce...
- Don't embarrass me in public.
- 'Cause you about to get you...
- See, you're always wiling out.
This is your first appointment
for the day here.
When you need me, l will be
outside here waiting on you.
♪ You shine ♪
♪ Even on your worst day ♪
♪ You're bright ♪
♪ Even in dim company ♪
♪ You may feel like
you don't belong ♪
♪ Here ♪
♪ You march strong ♪
♪ To the rhythm
of your own drum ♪
♪ l bet you
nobody ever told you ♪
♪ Where you came from,
starchild ♪
♪ l know you,
l know you well... ♪
Hello.
Hey, sexy.
Ls it too late to call?
Lt's 6:30.
L know. l'm just playing.
So what's up?
L thought you were going out
with Kalif and Dallas.
Yeah, l was, but l have a really big,
important meeting on Tuesday
and l don't wanna be out
drinking with the guys
and... l don't know. l just kinda
wanna keep my head right, you know?
Wow. Smart guy.
L think l like you.
Wait, you think you like me?
What's up with that?
- You don't know by now?
- Oh, l know.
So what are you doing?
Well, that's why l was calling.
My family and l are having
a little movie night tonight
and l wanted to see
what you were doing,
see if you wanted
to roll through.
Maybe watch one
of those chick flicks
my mom's been begging me
to watch with her.
Okay, so you're telling me
that you're spending a Saturday
chilling with your mom,
watching chick flicks?
- How cute.
- Mm-hmm.
Yeah yeah yeah.
Mama's my rock.
Wow.
Not a lot of people can say that.
What do you mean?
You're not close to your mom?
Let's just say my mom is married
and she has children,
but "close"
isn't a word l use to describe
her relationship with anyone.
Wow, Katalina. l'm really sorry
to hear that, honey.
So what movies does
your mom have on the lineup?
Oh, we've got
"Love and Other Drugs,"
and "Good Will Hunting,"
of course.
Oh, my vote is definitely
for "Good Will Hunting."
l love me some Matt Damon
and Cole Hauser...
good old Boston bad-asses.
- Mm-hmm.
- So, 20 minutes?
Awesome.
That's perfect.
Okey-dokey. Just so you know,
l look a little crazy.
L definitely was curled up in a ball
reading a book in some sweats.
Oh. Oh, my bad.
L see what you're doing.
Okay. That's right,
you're fishing
for compliments right now.
We can play this game.
No, you know what?
L can't even...
you are... you are naturally beautiful
from head to toe, so...
Thank you,
very very sweet of you.
All right, well,
drive safe, honey. Okay?
- Okay.
- L'll see you soon.
- Bye.
Well?
Oh my... ooh, that is soft.
L know. l was surprised to find
that your hair's still natural.
You know, you have
so many options when it is.
So l wanted to soften up
your curls a bit.
Lt's absolutely beautiful.
Thank you.
Oh wow.
So how long have
you been dating Prime?
Oh, l wouldn't call it
dating just yet.
Only we met a few months ago,
so we've hung out a few times.
But l like him.
He's really nice.
- Really?
- Uh-huh.
So all the things you hear
about the great Optimus Prime...
- it isn't true?
- You know, to be honest,
l wouldn't have a clue
as to what they say about him.
L moved out here to take care
of my grandmother,
so she's been my main focus.
All that matters
is that he's nice to me.
So you're not one
of those jersey chasers
running behind him
because he has all those millions?
Definitely not one of those.
L don't know.
Maybe it's just me, but...
l'm more concerned about how a man
treats me than what's in his wallet.
You know?
L actually had a run-in
with a few of his admirers
the other night at the club.
Just being in a room with
those women made my skin crawl.
L would totally understand
if he had trust issues
dealing with those type of women,
just throwing themselves at him.
Yeah, you'd be surprised,
honey, they're everywhere.
That's why l make it
my business to find out
if these girls are dating my brother
for the right reasons
or because he's
a pro basketball player.
Prime is your brother?
Milan Alexander at your services.
L had no idea.
L... l don't know what to say.
You don't have to say
anything, honey.
You've said enough.
L'm just happy to find out
that my brother's with someone
who's with him for the right reasons.
You're a sweetheart.
Keep it that way.
And don't break his heart.
So what's up, baby?
Baby, come on.
- You know we be off the hook, baby.
- Kalif! Kalif!
- Hold on. Oh shit.
- Who the hell plays basketball
this damn late at night?
- You better have your ass back by 9:00!
- Yo, come on, man, go!
L'm not playing with you, Dallas!
Why can't you just
find somebody else tonight
- and have a little fun?
- No one gets me like Dallas.
Oh God, nobody gets you...
okay, what does he tell you?
- l mean...
l mean...
l don't know. This guy
sounds like he's kinda full of it.
No, but you're
always negative like this.
Every time l like somebody,
you jump down my throat.
You gotta go with my gut.
And my gut is l really like him.
Okay, go with your gut.
What about your heart?
My gut... oh, Chad's working.
Probably get some free drinks.
- lsn't that Dallas?
- Let's go!
Oh, wait wait wait wait.
He's with a girl.
No no, that's probably
like his friend or his cousin
or something.
Lt's all right. That's... that's
definitely... definitely...
- Let's go investigate.
- Umm...
Sorry. Excuse me.
Just... excuse me.
Just trying to get to my boyfriend here.
Excuse me, guys.
- To a lot of luck, baby. Whoo!
- Whoo!
Dallas!
Dallas! Hey.
Oh hey, Carnegie.
What are you doing here?
L was gonna ask you
the same thing.
Excuse me, guys.
♪ Work that body,
get your sexy on... ♪
He should be embarrassed.
- He's acting like a child.
- Honey, l was dragged out of a club...
dragged out of a club
by two people
holding me down.
Lt was embarrassing.
- lt was very embarrassing.
- L wish l was there.
Look, Carnegie, you know
l don't want anything, right?
L'm a single man.
L'm not looking for anything
serious right now.
Whoa. Umm...
l wish you would've
told me that last night,
because l didn't get that memo
when you were in my bed.
To go through that
by yourself, that's not...
- What?
- That's Dallas.
L'm sorry you feel like that.
L thought we were just hanging out,
enjoying each other's company.
- Carnegie, come on, let's go.
- Yeah well, l didn't know that, Dallas.
Okay? And the only reason
why you're in the clear
is because you never mentioned
the word "relationship"
when you were wining and dining me
and bringing me
my favorite cupcakes.
You're in the clear because
you could do whatever you want
and my feelings is no consequence
to how you feel!
He's doing the exact same thing
that Prime did to you.
Why do they all act like that?
Why do they get to get away with that?
- They won't. They won't.
- You got what you wanted,
and now you're done.
Right? ls that how it goes?
- ls that how it goes?
- Come on, Carnegie, let's go.
- Let's go.
- Listen to your girl.
Screw you, Dallas!
Nice.
20 minutes, huh?
- Two hours later...
- Whatever.
- You look beautiful.
- Thank you.
- Who's this little princess?
- This beautiful thing is my niece.
- Hello there.
- Hi.
- She's so precious.
- She's so cute.
Are you ready to go inside?
They have been waiting
to meet my beautiful
girlfriend all day.
- Your girlfriend?
- Did l say something wrong?
No, babe.
Girlfriend is just fine.
L like that. Come on.
My name is Katalina too.
Hi, family.
This is Katalina, everyone.
Katalina, this is my family.
Lonzo, don't have her thinking
you were raised by wolves.
Oh, here we go.
That's my sister.
Nice to meet you, Katalina.
L'm Susie.
- Nice to meet you, Susie.
- This is my father,
- Mr. Juan Rodriguez.
- Mr. Rodriguez, a pleasure to meet you.
Nice to meet you too, Katalina.
Hope you don't mind.
L brought some cake for dessert.
Oh, l don't mind.
What kind of cake do we have?
Lt don't matter what kind of cake it is.
You ain't having any.
What do you mean
l'm not gonna have any?
A man should be able to have cake
in his own house if he wants to.
- Yeah, that's... that's my family.
- That's my cake.
Yeah.
Carnegie, come on!
Come on, you cannot let him
embarrass you like this!
Don't let him win!
He's such a fucking asshole!
Are you gonna come out?
Come on, Carnegie!
She's right, you know. You need
to pay him back for what he did to you.
L'm sorry, but that was ridiculous.
Um, who are you?
My name is Autumn, l used to date
one of Dallas's friends, Prime,
and he embarrassed me in the exact
same way that he embarrassed you.
Carnegie.
What did you say?
L'm sorry.
L saw that back there
and that was ridiculous.
L cannot believe
he did that to you.
- lt is not right.
- Why does this always happen to me?
L always fall in love with assholes.
Look, Dallas, Prime, Lonzo, Kalif...
all of them, that whole little crew...
they're dogs, okay?
They don't give a shit about
anyone else but themselves.
- Everything okay?
- Yeah.
- l feel so stupid. l feel...
No.
- Yes, l feel stupid.
- Do not blame yourself.
L'm sure he wined and dined you,
- did all that sweet shit.
- Cupcakes.
That's what they do. Look, honey...
- l'm so sorry.
- Thank you.
Lt's a game to them, okay?
They don't care about
who they hurt in the process.
Lt's not even
about the sex to them.
They just wanna conquer
as many women as they can
and they don't care who gets hurt
in the process. Trust me.
Times like these,
l'm glad l do women.
Look, if l were you,
l would confront him.
L would let him have it.
L mean, did you see
his smug ass out there?
All those guys out there,
they think he's a hero.
And those women?
They still will talk to him
because they think
it's something you did.
They never think
it's something they did.
You didn't deserve that, no matter what.
- He doesn't even care about you.
- Not at all.
Hm-mmm.
- We've gotta do something.
Don't let him get away
with this at all.
- Okay. Okay.
- At all.
- Yeah.
- All right, l'm gonna go out there.
Yes! Dry your eyes.
- All right, you look cute.
- L'm going. Okay.
Are you guys sure
about this dress?
Lt's cut really low.
Miss Hathaway,
are you in the dress?
Yes.
- Are you in the shoes?
- Yes.
Then get the hell
out of my dressing room
so we can see you.
- You look fantastic.
- Beautiful.
Come come.
You did it.
Absolutely beautiful.
Vidal, you did this.
- Yes, l did.
- Oh my God, it's so beautiful.
Oh, wait wait wait,
don't forget about the purse.
- Oh, l don't have a purse.
- Of course you do.
- That is so beautiful.
- Lsn't it?
- You know, you guys are so...
- No no no no, yeah yeah yeah yeah.
- We know.
- Get going.
- Thank you.
- Put in a good word for us.
You're welcome.
Oh.
L have had the most
amazing day of my life.
Well, you deserve it.
L mean, l know
taking care of your grandmother
can't be that easy.
Wow. Now come on.
The night has only begun.
Oh shit.
She's coming back,
she's coming back.
L can't believe all this shit.
So how do you know
our mutual friend Dallas?
- Excuse me?
- Well, let's see.
You're having drinks
at his favorite place to be seen,
so you must be new.
He took me here
on our second date.
We snuggled
in a booth over drinks.
Has he brought you pastries yet?
Oh, l'm sure he's asked you
all about your
favorite things by now, huh?
Mmm!
L love that bracelet.
Let me guess, let me guess. He said
it reminded you of him when he got it,
because it's dainty,
just like your wrist.
Mine's gold. He gave it to me
before we walked in here last time.
Hey, yo, you balling like that, man?
But don't worry.
He's not gonna try anything tonight,
because the sex won't be
good enough until you're hooked.
He likes sweet kisses
that he feels are escaped...
well, that's what
he told me at least.
But from the look of it, you got
about 10 more days of access to him
and then he'll fuck you
like he fucked me last night.
And then there's no more phone calls
just to hear your voice. He's gonna
make it seem like you did something,
and he's gonna act like you're a psycho
if he runs into you in public,
make everybody think you're some
stalker girl he just can't break.
Well, he told me that
about the girl before me.
L'm sure he told you
the same thing about me, right?
Carnegie, what are
you trying to prove here?
Just trying to get it
off my chest, Dallas.
L'm just trying to get
all the facts straight.
You know what l mean?
Because you're fucking good.
You're really good.
You should be an actor like Lonzo.
You would win an Academy Award,
hands down.
Hands down.
Ooh! l'll take one of these.
The least you can do
is buy me a drink.
Mmm mmm!
That's good.
Real smooth.
Real... mmm.
Mmm, but then it leaves
this bitter taste in your mouth.
Ooh! That was awesome!
- You go, girl.
- Oh my gosh, it was.
Yo, hey, let me help you, bro.
Hey, you know...
Oh, l ain't never gonna
let you hear the end of this.
Very classy, Carnegie.
Thank you!
♪ Baby, you're perfect ♪
♪ l love your style ♪
♪ l must admit, girl ♪
♪ lt drives me wild ♪
♪ The way that you walk ♪
♪ The way that you dress ♪
♪ l haven't met one girl ♪
♪ That compares to you yet ♪
♪ You treat me so good ♪
♪ You've captured my heart ♪
♪ Ain't nothing in this world ♪
♪ That could pull us apart ♪
♪ You say that you love me ♪
♪ And l hope that it's true ♪
♪ 'Cause l must admit, girl ♪
♪ That l love you too ♪
♪ She says that
she's in love with me ♪
♪ l hope that it's true, girl ♪
♪ 'Cause l love you too, girl ♪
♪ She says that
she's in love with me ♪
♪ l hope that it's true, girl ♪
♪ 'Cause l love you too, girl ♪
♪ l want this forever ♪
♪ How can l lie? ♪
♪ And all of your love, girl ♪
♪ lt gets me high ♪
♪ You take me to places ♪
♪ That l've never been ♪
♪ l don't want this feeling ♪
♪ To ever end ♪
♪ You're sexy, you know it ♪
♪ And you let it be seen ♪
♪ And you look like the girls ♪
♪ ln the magazines ♪
♪ You say that you love me ♪
♪ And l hope that it's true ♪
♪ 'Cause l must admit, girl ♪
♪ That l love you too ♪
♪ She says that
she's in love with me ♪
♪ l hope that it's true, girl. ♪
Try to keep your lips...
Mm-hmm, exactly.
- Those earrings are really cute.
- Really?
- l wanna steal them from you.
- My mom bought them at your store.
- She did?
- Yes, those are our spring line.
- Learn your line.
- Wait wait wait wait.
First of all, that's not my job.
Thank you.
Please.
Sweetie, you need to come to my place
and l'll hook you up
with a nice dress to go along with 'em.
- Thank you.
- You know what?
Huh-uh. Do not try to steal
my clients, all right?
- Please.
- Thank you.
Now how's your mom doing?
L haven't seen her in a while.
She's doing so good.
Her and my dad actually just got back.
- They were away for three weeks.
- Really?
- Shopping. Shopping.
- Yeah, shopping.
Paris Fashion Week.
That's when my family suddenly
- needs to get international as well.
- Exactly.
- OMG. Excuse me!
- Big shot with all her...
- Miss Hathaway!
- Who are you yelling at?
- Who is that?
- You just wait and see.
- Who's that?
- Who is it? l don't know.
- Oh my God, Vidal,
- l was gonna call you...
- Prime's new girlfriend.
Tomorrow and say
thank you for everything.
- How are you, sweetie?
- L'm good.
Wait, what are you doing here?
Aren't you supposed to be
having breakfast in bed?
No, l'm here to pick up a to-go order
for my grandmother.
Where are my manners?
Ladies, this is Skylar.
- Skylar, this is Katalina...
- Hi.
- Carnegie...
What was your name again, baby?
- Mira.
- Yeah, mirror... get one.
L could break you in two, man.
- Hello.
- Hi.
This is Dylan and that's Autumn
over there in the corner.
Hi. l remember you
from the other night.
- Hi.
- Nice to see you again.
Wait a second.
How do you two know each other?
We ran into each other
the other night at Prime's party.
- Really?
- Mm-hmm.
Grab a seat, sweetie.
Your food isn't ready.
- Oh, thanks.
- Grab a seat.
Well, how did it go?
Tell me all about it.
- Oh, ladies.
- What?
L had the pleasure
of dressing Miss Skylar
for the fabulous evening
with Mr. Prime Alexander.
Okay.
- Wow.
- That's really...
A date, huh?
- Mm-hmm.
- You have a good time?
Oh yeah, it was really nice.
L mean, we just went and had dinner,
walked in the park.
Please,
don't try to downplay it.
She got the works...
hair, makeup, everything.
And then he sent her to my place
to pick out a fabulous outfit.
- Wow.
Mm-hmm.
- Sounds quite familiar.
Reminds me of Dallas.
L hate him.
You had a nice time, huh?
Yeah, l did. He's absolutely
the sweetest guy l've ever met.
He's just really nice.
Wow.
The biggest sweetheart ever?
- Dylan.
- No, l mean, wow.
Well, you know
that Autumn dated Prime
and he wasn't the biggest sweetheart
to her near the end.
So... it's weird.
Huh? No, l mean
she should know.
She should know
what she's getting into, right?
Look look. We don't even know her
and we don't even owe her anything
to even explain
what happened with Autumn,
make her relive
the experience, so...
l don't think we really need
to explain anything.
L'm gonna let you guys
eat your lunch. Thanks.
Skylar, wait.
Look, l'm sorry.
She's my cousin.
L get a little protective.
But l do think
that you should know
what you're getting yourself
into before you go too deep.
Please stay.
Honestly, l really didn't know.
Lf you don't mind me asking,
what happened?
That's a very good question.
Honestly, l don't know
what happened.
We got into this fight,
and then the next thing l know
he's like cursing me out in public,
throwing my things out,
calling out my name.
Lt's just... what l thought was a little
fight was the end of my relationship.
Ls that what happened
the other night?
Yup.
L wish someone would've
given me the heads up
about Dallas.
L hate that motherfucker.
L really do hate him.
L'm sorry. l hate him.
- Hate him.
- L'm sorry. Who's Dallas?
He's one of Prime's friends.
Seriously, just like Autumn,
for the first couple of months
he was like a fucking unicorn.
L mean, calling two,
three times a day,
emailing... the whole nine.
Then l spent the night with him
and guess what.
The whole next day, nothing.
So Mira and l go to the bar,
get a few drinks.
And he is cuddled up
with some other chick
wearing the exact same
bracelet he gave me.
So anyways, l confronted him
and he basically had me
in the bathroom crying.
And that's when Mira
and Autumn were like...
l'm sorry, Dylan was there too, sorry...
"Go out there and confront him.
He's out there having
a great time with those girls."
She actually looked like a hooker.
Anyways, so l went out there
and l called him out on his shit.
L handled some business,
didn't l, girls?
- She did too.
L did.
But that's exactly
what she should've done,
because those guys...
they do it to everybody,
they get away with it
and nobody says anything.
Dallas, Kalif, Prime...
- l don't know about Lonzo.
- Birds of a feather do flock together.
- Hey, watch it.
- Yes they do.
- We don't know. We don't know.
- They do.
- We need to put a stop to it.
- That's like saying
l'm drinking as much
as this one over here.
- Girl, you go.
- What?
Really? Birds of a feather
flock together?
- Cut off.
- L'm celebrating.
- l'm celebrating.
- Oh, hold on.
Look, all the ladies are trying
to say is just be careful.
That's all.
Okay. Thanks.
L'm gonna go.
Lt was nice meeting you ladies.
- l'm sorry if we...
Nice meeting you too.
- Just letting you know.
- Lt was... yeah.
- Just take care.
- Thanks.
How is it that you're not
like Kalif, Dallas and Prime?
What do you mean?
Look, l've known
you guys for a while now
and you know they're shady.
L wouldn't even talk to you
if l thought you were like them.
- Katalina, they are not shady.
- Tsk.
They're not. l'm telling you.
Look, l've known those guys
my whole life, practically.
L met Prime when l was
eight years old, for crying out loud.
L used to be taller
than that fool back then.
L swear to God.
- Then we met Kalif in high school...
- Wow.
And Dallas in college.
They're good guys.
Their problem is they love women.
What's so bad about that?
Okay, but...
let's say a girl
really really likes a guy
and she's in it
for all the right reasons.
- Mm-hmm.
- They're just chilling,
seeing where things go.
And they finally sleep together,
then he dumps her.
Someone that
does this repeatedly...
- Mm-hmm.
- ...that's a good guy?
That's not fair. lt's not.
- Mm-hmm.
- Lt's not.
Besides, Autumn brought
that shit upon herself.
- You know that.
- L know for a fact
that Autumn is not the only
woman he's done that to.
Okay okay, first off...
first off...
you can't say that. lt's a completely
different situation, babe.
All right? Think about it.
They were dating for over a year.
- Right?
- Yeah.
Okay, and he was
really good to her.
Look, regardless of all this crap,
that's their life, right?
What happened between them
is between them.
L'm cool with that.
Look, what you need
to be focusing on right now
is not what Prime and Autumn
were doing.
Mmm, it's that you will
never do that to me.
You understand me?
You know l won't, baby.
- You promise?
- L promise.
C'mon.
- What are you doing here, Autumn?
- Nice new car.
Yeah.
What are you doing here?
Why haven't you returned
any of my phone calls?
L tried to contact you
for over a month now.
L got your emails,
l got your messages,
but Prime insists that we don't speak.
And being that things
are really good with us...
- Ah.
- ...l don't think that we should either.
Okay. Oh, l see.
Look, l'm not trying
to tell you anything.
Okay? l just have something
you simply need to see.
We'll just take a short ride.
Lt won't take long
and l will never bother you again.
Okay, you're crazy if you think
l'm going anywhere with you.
No one asked you to.
You have a fancy new car.
Follow me. Trust me,
you'll wanna see this.
Okay, so you brought me
to a kid's birthday party.
Look a little bit closer.
Now shoot. Shoot. Oh!
L think we gotta get it again.
Come on.
All right, there you go.
Oh, good job, little fella.
- Guys, hey.
- Go on wit' your mommy.
Let's go.
Hey, Skylar, Skylar,
you don't wanna do this right here.
Hey, wait a sec, wait a sec.
Wait. Whoa whoa whoa whoa.
- Skylar, Skylar.
- Really? Really, Prime?
- Look, baby, l can explain.
- Explain what?
That you have a wife?
That you have kids?
- Uh...
- How are you gonna explain this?
- l can't. Not here.
- L trusted you.
Everybody tried to warn me
and l trusted you.
You know what, Skylar?
Please,
- let me take you home.
- Stop stop.
Look...
What is wrong with you?
Why would you do this?
L'm not one of these groupie girls
out here trying to trap you.
- Why would you treat me like l was one?
- Skylar. Baby, listen.
Look, let's just talk
about this later.
All right? Just...
it's not what it looks like.
L have listened
to everything that you said,
every single thing
that you have told me.
L listened and l believed you.
What is wrong with you?
You have a family, Prime.
You have a fucking family.
Uh...
- L hate you.
♪ Looking back
it's all clear to me ♪
♪ Should have known it all along... ♪
l trusted him.
Like...
l did everything
that l could for him,
and he still did this.
They always win.
At least you found out now
and not like a year from now.
Listen, you two are much stronger
women than l am.
Lf l had been at that birthday party,
ooh, no, some people
would've gone down.
L mean kids, baby mamas,
like the jumping castle...
something.
But she still can.
So can we.
They humiliated us publicly.
Let's do it to them.
L don't know, Carnegie.
- How?
- Just think, okay?
Prime always has
a million cameras in his face.
So call him out on his shit
like l did with Dallas.
You really think that that worked?
You thought that did something?
L'm sorry, but he's probably been with
at least three women since you.
L hate him so much.
L don't know what l even saw in him.
He has a unicorn tattoo.
He probably waxes his butthole.
Look, what are you trying
to get out of this?
Honestly, what are you
trying to propose that we do?
L mean, l get why you're angry
and why Skylar's pissed, but...
Oh, so l don't have a reason
to be hurt, Katalina?
Ls that it? Really?
L mean, come on.
Autumn, you knew
that Prime had a fiancée.
So it's not like
it's some surprise to you.
Okay, fuck that. No one really
cares what you have to say.
Okay, boo boo?
And first of all,
yes, l knew he had children,
and no, l did not know
he had a fiancée.
And when l finally found out,
he told me that he was
no longer with her, so...
No, exactly. And doesn't Kennedy
live in Louisiana or something?
- Exactly.
Lf he told her
that they weren't together anymore,
why wouldn't she believe him?
So you thought you would be
the one to change him,
when he's the type
that wouldn't change for anyone,
unless he was forced to.
Okay, that's like not expecting
a scorpion to sting you.
Okay, you know what?
L am not gonna justify
my feelings for any of you,
especially you.
The point is that you stayed!
You stayed! Look, we all know
the risk of dating an athlete,
especially Prime Alexander.
But l didn't. l didn't know.
What did l do?
What did l do that was
- so bad that l deserve this?
- Nothing.
L gave Prime a year of my life.
All the broken promises.
He sold me on this idea
of like a fairy-tale life.
Where's my happy ending?
You know what?
How much do we have to put up with
before they realize that
they can't just break our hearts
and pretend like nothing happened?
- But that's Prime Alexander.
- Oh my God.
And nobody is going
to change Prime Alexander!
Unless we force him to.
What they did to us was cruel
and it was wrong.
And they need to be held accountable
for their actions.
Look, you can't make somebody change
that doesn't want to change.
- You just can't.
- Yes, you can.
Listen, all you have to do
is use everything about them
against them.
Quickly, without remorse.
They get their strength
from running in a pack like dogs.
You shake up the bonds,
destroy the pack.
Exactly.
You're right.
Let's do it.
Hi, yes,
l'm with Pryor Lamborghini
and we have a lease on a car that's
in arrears that needs to be picked up.
Yes, l know exactly where
it's going to be on Saturday.
The license plates
read "work"... W-O-R-K.
- Yes.
- Hello?
Hi, l'd like to report someone.
L know seven women
he's given herpes to...
well, probably more than that.
His name?
Lt's Dallas Lauderdale.
Yeah, l'll hold.
Mira, it's your turn!
- Hello?
- Shanita?
This is Shanita.
This is Mr. Prime Alexander's
publicist, Dahni.
Okay.
Prime is setting up a special surprise
for Mr. Kalif Wyatt
at the upcoming Rico Terrell gala
and would like you to attend.
- Okay.
- Great!
He'll send a car for you
at 8:00 p.m. on Saturday.
And he asks that
you keep this a secret.
Thank you.
Now this is completely
anonymous though, right?
L mean, you're my girl
and l'm sending this to you
'cause l want you to get the scoop,
but l can't have this traced back to me.
Okay.
Are you ready for this?
Well, have you heard
a little rumor about Kalif Wyatt
and his very very close boyfriends?
Gay clubs and stripping.
And, honey, l have a picture,
and l am sending it to you
right... now.
You are welcome.
Girl, you're my sorority sister.
L gotta hook you up.
Hell yeah, you can come through.
You gotta bring a friend though.
Yo, l gotta get out of this mall, girl.
L'm feeling all eyes from all guys.
- Holy shit. Hey, Kalif.
- This is crazy.
- Yo, hold up.
- What? Kalif?
Yo, how you know
my name, little man?
Oh, baby, l make it a point to keep up
with all the available ass out there.
What? What the hell
you talking about, man?
Please, like you haven't
been on whobangingwho.com.
- Who what?
- They got the whole exposé,
exposing your love for the boys.
Love for the boys?
Man, l'm all about the ladies,
and the ladies know it.
Ask your girl, she know.
- What? Excuse you.
- L'm just going based off what l read.
What you read?
You read wrong, homey. Who what?
Yo, look, l don't know what
the hell y'all talking about.
L'm out. l feeling
too much of a sugar rush
- in this motherfucker.
- Let's go.
Dallas.
- Yeah, Dad? What's up?
- What the hell is this?
- l don't know.
- What do you mean you don't know?
- lt's you, isn't it?
- Well yeah, but l don't know whose cam...
Oh, yes you do!
L'm telling you,
l have no idea how it got there.
This is going to kill your mother.
Lt's all over the lnternet!
Lt's in everybody's inboxes.
You need to get out of here,
take one or two months.
Just get out of here!
- l swear, Dad, l...
- No. Dallas, we're done.
Fuck.
Crap.
- Yo.
- Somebody emailed
everybody at my dad's company
my game tapes,
and he damn near fired me!
- Wait. What?
- How did it get out there, Prime?
Yo, man, why you asking me?
L don't know.
L don't be watching your game tapes.
Autumn.
What?
Nothing, man.
Lemme call you back.
Yeah, whatever.
Where is she?
Hi. May l help you
with something?
Where is Autumn, Dylan?
L'm sorry.
She's not here. Why?
She knows why.
You tell her l know she did it.
Did what?
Hmm. Well.
So it begins.
That's gonna be $2,476.32.
- All right.
- Mr. Prime, good to see you again.
V-dog, good to see you.
You look good.
- l see you built a wing on the back.
- Yeah.
This place looks great.
L love it.
- Thank you.
- Oh, um, Mr. Alexander?
- Yeah?
- L'm sorry. Your credit card declined.
Why don't you just
swipe that again for me?
- l already ran it twice.
- Camille, swipe it again.
L'm sure there's a computer glitch
or something.
- lt's been doing that lately, you know?
- Yeah.
Yeah, see?
Lt declined again.
Do you have another card?
- Let me do it.
- Okay.
Thank you.
- Give me two seconds. Not to worry.
- No problem.
- Yeah...
- Lt was declined.
Yo, what do you mean it was...
that's a limitless card.
There must be
a problem with the bank.
- l...
- Gimme that.
- l'm sorry.
- Yeah.
What are you laughing at?
You looking at me like l'm crazy.
No, come on. l'm delirious,
- l'm so hungry right now.
- Clearly.
- How's the food?
- Ls that good?
- Mm-hmm.
- Oh my God!
- Oh shit!
- Oh my God. Babe!
Shit!
- Was that Kalif?
- That ass... was that your boy Kalif?
- He was naked.
- Yo.
Please call that man.
What is he doing? Why...
He's on something.
Yo, that...
did that really just happen?
- Am l bugging?
- Hey! Dawg, l swear to God
we just saw some dude that looked
just like you run down the street
- with his balls flapping, bro.
- No bueno.
We're at the restaurant
we always hang at.
- Good look in the clothes, man.
- Dawg.
Can't believe that shit happened.
Yo!
What up, brothers?
The fuck wrong with y'all?
Hey, did l see you running
down the street naked?
Oh shit, man! What?
You saw me and you didn't
even try to help me?!
- That was you?
- We supposed to be boys, man!
Dude, l tried calling you. What the hell?
Tried calling me? Did it look like
l had my fucking phone on?
Look! l need to know right now...
did one of y'all let out my game tapes?
- What?
- Somebody uploaded on the lnternet,
emailed to everyone
in my company's directory.
Ah. My mom...
fuck, she's gonna kill me.
Something ain't right.
How the hell all of us gonna have
a bad day all at the same time?
Flames been hounding me all week!
And now this shit?
What the fuck happened to you?
- All my cards were canceled.
- What?
$100-million man
and l ain't got no money.
What kind of shit is that?
All this can't be
a coincidence, can it?
All right, look, l don't know
what the fuck is going on right now,
but we've got this gala
in a few hours, right?
Dude, we've gotta get
our minds right for that.
Mr. Alexander!
Mr. Alexander,
over here, please.
Prime! Over here, please, sir.
A really quick interview.
Thank you so much, sir.
Mr. Alexander.
- Hi, how are you doing tonight?
- Great.
- Wow, you look really great.
- Thank you.
So this is the 5th Annual
Rico Terrell Benefit Gala
for sickle-cell anemia.
What makes this such
an important cause for you?
Well, when l was a rookie,
l volunteered
at the children's hospital
and l met so many amazing children
who suffer from this disease.
And l vowed right then
that l was gonna do
all that l could
to help fund research
to find a cure one day.
And l kept my word.
That is awesome.
How much have you raised
this year so far?
Well, at this point with this event,
we've raised $3.5 million.
Congrats. That's truly
a great accomplishment.
Oh, and next year
we'll do $5 million.
Wow. Thank you
so much for your time.
- Enjoy the rest of your evening.
- Thank you.
So what's up, baby?
Yo, deal me out.
Kalif. Surprise.
Baby?
- Yeah.
- What are you doing here?
Mmm, Prime set all this up.
He wanted to surprise you.
- Oh my gosh, this place is beautiful.
- Tell me about it.
You know he always got
a trick up his sleeve.
No, l mean, he didn't really set it up.
His publicist did.
But anything for my baby.
You know l was gonna be here.
Well, baby, l'm glad you here.
Look, l gotta work the room,
so why don't you go to our table? l'll be
there in about 10 minutes, all right?
All right, sweetie.
Go do your thing.
- Hey, baby.
- What?
- l love you.
- L love you too.
Oh shit.
- Yo, Prime, what's up, man?
- What's up, bro?
- Your publicist invited Shanita?
- No, why the hell would she do that?
Shit, l don't know.
L'm trying to figure that out myself.
Man, she right over there.
Oh shit.
L need a drink, man.
Somebody give me a drink.
Please. Quick.
Make it fast.
♪Yo ♪
♪ Come on. ♪
Just chill, man.
Lt's good.
Just chill out, man.
Oh shit!
Man, the party's over.
L knew your ass was
behind all this shit.
- Gentlemen.
- Lt's pretty fucked up, Autumn.
So all of you are
behind all this shit, huh?
L'm sorry. l don't know
exactly what you're talking about.
My credit cards, Dallas's video.
Calling my baby mama.
- Shit is real cute.
- Okay, you know what?
We're just here to have a good time,
just like everybody else.
- Okay.
- Okay. All right. Have fun.
Can l speak to you
for a second?
Okay.
What do you want, Prime?
Look, l just wanna...
explain myself.
Explain what?
That you have a wife and kids?
Hey, but, Sky...
♪ l've been waiting
a lifetime for you ♪
♪ l would do anything
just to keep you ♪
♪ But you don't seem to care
about this thing called love ♪
♪ The fellas think that l'm crazy... ♪
- Prime Alexander?
- Yeah, what's up, man?
- You got a black Lamborghini?
- Yeah.
Your car being
towed outside, playboy.
- Say what?
- Your car's being towed.
Man, come on.
L'll be right back.
L'm gonna...
Dallas Lauderdale?
- Yes.
- L'm Officer Suggs.
We've received some complaints
that you've been spreading
sexually-transmitted diseases.
L'm gonna need you to come with me
- and answer a few questions.
- What?
- Are you kidding me?
- Sit down.
L'm not going with you.
- Ah! Hey hey hey hey!
- Sit down!
Come on, man.
- Hey hey!
- What did he do?
L'm telling you, man.
Lt's them bitches.
- lt's okay. l'll get my lawyer.
- Hey. Ah! Yo, hey.
Hey, Lonzo, Lonzo,
just call my mother.
- l got it.
- Aww. Bye, Dallas.
Shut the fuck up, Autumn.
♪ Sleeping with the enemy ♪
♪ Apparently l like it ♪
♪ Everything she give to me ♪
♪ But l can't deny it ♪
♪ Can anybody save me? ♪
♪ l'm crying out for help ♪
♪ l just don't want
to lose myself ♪
♪ At all ♪
♪ Drinking from the bottle ♪
♪ Didn't want wanna end
like this ♪
♪ At all... ♪
- Whoa whoa whoa whoa, yes!
- ♪ Didn't want to end like this... ♪
What?
This is fucking bullshit.
Come on, come on, come on.
♪ Anchor tight around my feet ♪
♪ Yeah, but we pretend
we're swimming ♪
♪ Love ain't in the deep ♪
♪ And continuously we're sinking ♪
♪ Can anybody save me? ♪
♪ l'm crying out for help ♪
♪ l just don't wanna
lose myself ♪
♪ At all ♪
♪ Drinking from the bottle ♪
♪ Didn't want to end like this ♪
♪ At all... ♪
♪ Loving a girl like this ♪
♪ l kiss your lips... ♪
Get out.
What?
L want you to leave.
L want you out of my house.
Baby.
Get out of my house!
♪ At all... ♪
♪ Drinking from the bottle ♪
♪ Didn't wanna end like this ♪
♪ At all ♪
♪ Loving a girl like this ♪
♪ A kiss from the devil's lips... ♪
Mmm.
- Hey.
L was surprised
to hear from you.
L was surprised that
l texted you.
Mm-hmm.
Here you go.
- Thank you.
- Welcome.
So?
L'm not ready to forgive you
for what you did.
L gave you everything that l had
and you really hurt me.
Why didn't you just tell me
you had kids and a girl from the jump?
Um, l thought
you would leave if l did.
That doesn't give you
the right to take that choice from me.
You're right.
L'm sorry.
L guess l wasn't thinking.
You said that everything
isn't what it appears.
So explain.
My kids mean everything to me.
And l'll do whatever it takes
in order to be with them.
So you're basically saying
that you're only with Kennedy
so that she doesn't take
your kids from you.
- Yeah.
- Hmm.
Her family's from Louisiana
and she would take them there.
- l know she would.
- So where does that leave me?
Skylar.
Look, yo, l care for you.
L really do.
- Please believe...
- Ls this seat taken?
Uh, Kennedy.
Thanks for the call, Skylar.
Why don't you scoot over?
L'm gonna let you guys talk.
No no no, please stay.
You have just as much
a right to be here as l do.
You're looking all scared.
What, you don't have
anything to say?
No lies, no excuses?
We're all here now.
Talk.
So you're the girl
from the website, huh?
She's a bit younger than Autumn.
How's your grandmother?
Excuse me?
Oh.
Oh, you thought l didn't know about you
until you called this morning?
Come on, l know everything
that Prime does.
Everything...
from the helicopter rides
to the shopping sprees
to the condo
on East Lake Drive.
Everything.
L know what you're thinking.
Lf l know this, why don't l leave?
Because l love him.
He's the father of my children.
And l love his ass.
What you need to know,
Miss Thing,
is before you get
romantically involved with a man,
make sure you know everything
there is to know about him.
You see, arrogant, selfish,
rich individuals like my fiancé,
they prey upon sweet
innocent women...
like you.
L know he hurt you.
Otherwise,
you wouldn't have called.
And l'm sorry for that.
But trust me,
he won't hurt you again.
Now if you'll excuse us,
my fiancé and l have
a few things to discuss.
What did l tell you the last time?
L told you if you do this
to me again, it's over.
L can't put up with this.
L won't.
L've been here with you
through everything, Prime.
Everything.
L'm the mother of your children.
Does that mean nothing to you?
L've dealt with this before
and l'm not dealing with it again.
L can't sit around
until you figure out
if you want to be
what you should be.
Look. Look, baby.
L'm sorry.
Kennedy, l... l don't...
No, just stop it.
L'm done.
L am so done.
You know, you want to be
the $100-million playboy?
So be it.
Me and the kids are leaving.
L'm going back to Louisiana.
- You're just...
- Baby.
Oh yeah.
Lce cream?
You wanna go get ice cream?
- All girls like ice cream.
- Well, that's true.
Umm, Prime. Pri... excu...
Pri... excuse me.
Prime, you can't go back there!
My fucking life, you stupid-ass bitch!
L should kill your fucking ass!
L should kill your ass!
Prime, no!
Get... Que!
- Oh my God!
- Prime! Prime! Let's go, man.
L'm calling the police!
Yes, it's an emergency.
Prime Alexander attacked my cousin.
- Come on, man. Calm down.
- Get off me!
Camelback and 24th.
Lt's a boutique,
Autumn de Brise.
Please... please hurry.
Please. Autumn?
L just know there's
so much stupid drama.
L can't believe this shit.
Fucking asshole.
Oh my God.
Take a breath. Outside, come on.
We need to deal with it.
Okay?
- Hey, thank you, guys, for coming.
- You okay?
- What happened?
- He attacked me.
- Did you press charges?
- Are all of you happy now?
- We're not gonna talk about...
- You got what you wanted?
- Let's go.
- You wanted to humiliate me?
You know what?
Fuck you, Prime!
Fuck you! You got exactly
what you deserve!
And you need to be glad
that l didn't press charges.
L can't believe how far
y'all took this shit!
Uploading pictures on the lnternet,
calling my baby mama!
And to torture me?
L ain't done nothing to none of y'all!
Lt don't make any difference.
L mean, even with all this,
me and my boys,
we gonna still do us.
Mm-hmm, you and your boys?
You'll still do you, right?
'Cause you're so close, right?
Best friends?
- Let's go.
- No no. 'Cause you're so close?
Hmm, let me think.
Did Dallas tell you
that l've been fucking him
for the last two months?
- Oh shit.
- Hey.
- Are you kidding?
- What?
You've been having sex
with Dallas this entire time!
- Wow.
- Are you serious?
This isn't about that, all right?
So you eating off
my sloppy seconds, l see, huh?
That's how she found
the fucking sex tapes.
You know, all this proves
is how much of a ho you are,
just like you were cheating on me
with Jeff Trepagnier.
Seriously? She wasn't
cheating on you with Jeff.
She was cheating on Jeff
with you, you arrogant...
- Let's go. You don't need this.
- Yeah, that's right.
Do the math.
Do the math, Prime.
L was with him when l met you.
Autumn, what the fuck
is wrong with you?
You just gonna roll down
the assembly line?
Ls that what you gonna do?
Hmm?
- What about Kalif?
- Yeah, where my slice at?
Yeah, you know what?
Maybe l should.
Then maybe l'll be
just like Prime,
especially since
he fucked Katalina.
- What?
- Yeah, you thought l didn't know.
- Really?
- What is wrong with you?
- What is wrong with...
- Yeah, why are you starting shit?
Prime and Katalina?
Prime and Katalina never hooked up.
Really?
Prime?
Hey. Um, look, man,
that was a long
long time ago, man.
Don't get worked up
over that. This...
Don't get worked...
The fuck's he doing, man! Chill out!
- Hey, Lonzo! Hey!
- Chill!
- Relax!
- Man, l would've told you
a fucking long time ago!
Lt was before you even knew her!
- 1080 for life, huh?
- Chill out, man?
- Really?
- Look. Baby, listen.
- Don't "baby" me.
- Lt was a long... l tried to tell you!
This whole thing was part
of your plan, wasn't it?
- This whole thing, right?
- This had nothing to do with us.
Nothing to do with us.
- Lt's all your sick little revenge.
- You know... shut up!
- Fuck you, Autumn!
- l bet you wish you could!
- Hey! Stop! Stop!
That's enough!
Lt's enough!
You know what?
L don't even need this shit.
Autumn, wait.
♪ l have been taken before ♪
♪ You're not the first to rob me ♪
♪ Of my peace ♪
♪ And my sanity ♪
♪ You've taken all my peace ♪
♪ You must've been kidding ♪
♪ With that whole ♪
♪ Romantic love spell ♪
♪ Or maybe l just didn't
hear you right ♪
♪ You run over my heart ♪
♪ And then ask for it back ♪
♪ You must think that
that's all right ♪
♪ Well, it's not all right ♪
♪ But you're not even human ♪
♪ You're just above
the idea of when ♪
♪ Who l accidentally loved ♪
♪ And gave everything to become ♪
♪ The girl on the piano bench... ♪
- ls that her?
- ♪ Singing all of her tears... ♪
What do you think?
L take it you're still not talking?
Nope.
What do you wanna watch?
Nascar.
Look at you. Hm-mmm.
No, you can ask,
but that right there is perfection.
- No, l mean that...
- That is the perfect hamburger.
- Son?
- Yeah, Mama?
Thanks.
Look, l... l know you probably
hate me right now,
but l just wanted
an opportunity to explain.
Explain what?
The fact that you slept
with my best friend?
Yeah, you know what, Katalina?
L think that's pretty
self-explanatory, don't you?
Look, l dated Prime
before l knew you...
two years ago.
We just went on two dates.
That was it.
- You should've told me.
- L tried.
- You didn't want to hear...
- You should've tried...
you should've tried
a little harder.
You know what?
Just make sure you get
something to eat. Okay?
What?
Really, Lonzo?
Really?
So, what, you want me to act
like this never happened?
You just expect me
to let the best thing
that's ever happened to me
just walk right out of my life?
All l can do is
see him when l see you.
Huh-uh.
What do you want me to do?
L want you to try.
Don't push me away.
Just try.
L think what we have
is worth it.
L love you...
with every inch of my soul.
Me too.
L don't know what
you want me to do
to prove that,
to make you see that.
L'll do anything.
You just tell me what you want.
L don't know.
Lt's not that easy.
Look, umm...
l'm really sorry for ruining
Katalina's birthday.
God, l fucking love you,
you know that?
Don't you ever lie to me again.
- Do you hear me?
- Promise.
Don't let me go.
♪ Where are all my ladies at? ♪
♪ Ladies' night ♪
♪ And y'all rocking with 3crew ♪
♪ So let me see you
work that body ♪
♪ Work work that body ♪
♪ Get your sexy on,
get your sexy on ♪
♪ Work work that body ♪
♪ Get your sexy on,
get your sexy on ♪
♪ Work work that body ♪
♪ Get your sexy on,
get your sexy on ♪
♪ Work work that body ♪
♪ Get your sexy on,
get your sexy on ♪
♪ Loose in her hand ♪
♪ l'ma get loose
during her working day ♪
♪ l'm her fan, she got the best body
from here to Japan ♪
♪ l can't fight it,
can't fight it, oooh ♪
♪ l like it, l like it,
l get excited ♪
♪ Excited when
she works that body ♪
♪ Everybody get low,
everybody get low ♪
♪ Everybody get shots of Patrón,
shots of Patrón ♪
♪ Low low, everybody get low ♪
♪ Everybody get shots of Patrón,
shots of Patrón ♪
♪ Work work that body ♪
♪ Get your sexy on,
get your sexy on ♪
♪ Work work that body ♪
♪ Get your sexy on,
get your sexy on ♪
♪ Work work that body ♪
♪ Get your sexy on,
get your sexy on ♪
♪ Work work that body ♪
♪ Get your sexy on,
get your sexy on ♪
♪ l like the way you dance ♪
♪ The way you move that ass
is awesome ♪
♪ l feel like a lucky man,
what you have is so sublime ♪
♪ Make me wanna take you
back to my room ♪
♪ And do some things that
we ain't supposed to do ♪
♪ Girl, girl, let me
take you home tonight ♪
♪ Everybody get low low,
everybody get low ♪
♪ Everybody get shots of Patrón,
shots of Patrón ♪
♪ Low low, everybody get low ♪
♪ Everybody get shots of Patrón,
shots of Patrón ♪
♪ Work work. ♪