Remember when they let commercial airlines land in this town?
Yeah, I don't understand where we're going...
or why we're bothering anyhow.
- You're doing a good deed. - Wanna give us a better reason.
Yeah. A maniac hijacked a municipal bus with 30 passengers on it. That's a pretty good reason.
And I got a real bad hunch where those passengers are and who that maniac is.
You wanna share it with us.
Phoenix.
Simon Phoenix.
Send a maniac to catch one.
Phoenix!
Don't move, Phoenix.
You're under arrest.
Arrest? Shit.
And you're trespassing.
Where are the passengers?
Oh, yes, the passengers.
Well, they're...
Fuck you.
The passengers are gone.
See, I told the city, I said, "Look, nobody comes down here."
Postmen figured it out...
policemen figured it out.
But the goddamn bus drivers just wouldn't listen.
Last time, Phoenix.
Where are the hostages?
To hell with the hostages! This is between you and me!
Yeah.
What, what, what you got soldier boy?
Do something.
Go ahead.
You're up to your ass in gasoline.
I'll set your ass on fire.
Is it cold in here?
Or is it just me?
Where are they, Phoenix?
Now, where did I put them?
I swear, I'd lose my head if it wasn't attached.
I'll keep that in mind.
Damn it, John, I'm tired of this demolition-man shit!
You were not supposed to come down here!
You were not supposed to attempt the arrest of Phoenix alone...
and you were not supposed to blow anything up!
It wasn't me this time! He dumped the gas and rigged the place to blow!
Right, you weren't involved.
I know you've tried to nail this psycho for two years.
But remember a thing called...
official police procedure?
- Where are the hostages? - They're not here.
What do you mean they are not here?
He must've stashed them someplace else!
So how do you know they weren't in there. Are you sure?
Because I did a thermo check and there was eight of them, all part of his gang.
Wrong again!
You got something to say, scumbag?
Get him out of here!
Motherfucker!
You and I are going to have a nice long chat.
Captain!
Over here! There're bodies everywhere!
There must be 20 or 30.
They're everywhere.
See that, captain? I told him!
He said he didn't care!
Oh my god. How could you sacrifice all those innocent people for me!
What kind of man are you!
We'll spend a lot of quality time together. See you, sweetie!
Honey! Sugar!
If you got a lawyer, better call him.
John Spartan, you've done great deeds for the city of Los Angeles.
So it is with some regret that I, William Smithers...
acting as Assistant Warden, hereby carry out this sentence.
Skip it.
Sergeant Spartan, you've been sentenced to 70 years...
sub-zero re-habilitation in the California Cryo-Penitentiary...
for the involuntary manslaughter of 30 innocent civilians.
Skip it.
You'll be placed in cryo-stasis for the duration of your sentence...
during which your behavior will be altered through synaptic suggestion.
You'll be eligible for parole no earlier than the year 2046.
I'm sorry, Sergeant.
All personnel...
the next scheduled parole hearing for prisoner Gilmour...
will take place at 07:15.
Warden William Smithers, report to Level A, conference room.
Mellow greetings, Warden William Smithers.
Be well, Lieutenant Lenina Huxley.
As it is a beautiful...
Monday morning and as my duty log ...
irrationally requires it. I'm querying you on the prison population.
Does the tedium continue?
Your question is amusing but irrelevant.
The prisoners are ice cubes. They never move.
I find this lack of stimulus to be truly disappointing.
- Don't you think? - I try not to.
However, you're young, think all you want.
Things don't happen anymore, we've taken care of all that.
I'll fiber-op you back after the parole hearings.
Have a peachy day, Lieutenant.
Be well.
Vector 137.
Upcoming, Santa Monica Boulevard.
Retina coding accepted.
Warden William Smithers, be well.
Go on.
Self-drive on.
Self-drive engaged.
Coding on.
No police presence is requested in the city at this time.
Report to the station.
Oh, boy, how exciting.
EF
That's it.
Food, glorious food.
There'll be another one in about 12 hours.
These assholes are predictable.
God, I love to hate this place!
There's not enough of us, Friendly.
That doesn't really matter anymore.
People are hungry.
We've nothing left to lose.
Greetings.
Lovely Lenina.
Greetings, welcome to the emergency line of the SAPD.
If you prefer an automated response, press one now.
Be well.
Mellow greetings, Lenina Huxley.
Let me guess, all is serene?
On the contrary, it's been a horrific a.m.
There were defaced public buildings.
Walls smudged with...
scandalous graffiti.
Really?
Brutal. Why wasn't an "all cars" notified?
Because there was no need to create widespread panic.
Lieutenant Huxley...
I monitored your disheartening and distressing comments...
to the warden this morning.
Do you really long for chaos and disharmony?
Your fascination with the 20th century seems to be affecting your better judgment.
You realize you're setting a bad example for other officers and personnel.
Thank you for the attitude readjustment.
Info assimilated.
Sanctimonious asshole.
Lenina Huxley, you are fined 1/2 credit...
for a 'sotto voce' violation of the verbal morality statute.
Thank you.
That was tense.
- That was tense? - Yes.
Tell me something, Garcia...
Don't you get bored code tracing perps who break curfew and tell dirty jokes?
Actually no. I find my job deeply fulfilling.
I just can't get over the reality of this office, Lenina Huxley.
You're still addicted to the 20th century.
High from its harshness. Buzzed by its brutality.
Holy smokes!
Is there anything in this office which doesn't violate Contraband Ordinance 22?
Only you, Alfredo Garcia.
Don't you ever want something to happen?
Goodness, no.
I knew you'd say that.
What I wouldn't give for some action.
Mr. Simon Phoenix.
One of our first and most illustrious members.
Allow me to...
welcome you to your parole hearing.
Let's get this over quickly.
Twenty-nine years ago, the parole system, as you know it...
was rendered obsolete.
Federal Statute 537-29...
Stop it!
Do you have anything fresh to say on your behalf?
I thought not.
Yeah, I do.
Teddy bear.
How'd you know the password?
I wish I knew.
Simon says, die.
Warden...
let's get this over quickly.
Retina coding accepted, Warden William Smithers.
Be well.
Yeah, you too.
187. 187.
Northwest quadrant. 187. Northwest quadrant. 187.
Oh, my!
I don't believe it!
Northwest quadrant. 187.
What's a 187?
I don't know.
Cryo-prison.
Level 6.
Identify code 187.
MDK.
MurderDeathKill.
Last recorded offense, September 25, 2010.
Initiate search, confirming location.
Cryo-prison, Level 6.
Two code 187's. Officer John D'Argent, guard.
Officer Alfred Pamela, guard.
Tracking.
Live transmission diagnostic check, Warden William Smithers.
Injuries: severe eye trauma, ruptured spleen...
punctured lung...
broken rib, internal bleeding.
Condition critical.
Vital signs failing.
Imminent death.
Subject deceased.
187, Warden William Smithers...
born February 14th, 1967...
died August 4th, 2032.
What's the matter with all of you?
The cryo-prison, sir. Three non-sanctioned life terminations.
Do you wish to assign a coroner?
MurderDeathKills?!
Three MDKs!
Access for me the cryo-pen's morning hearing schedule.
And display for me the list of people interviewed for parole.
Accessing cryo-prison processing. Restricted information.
Cocteau Cryo-prison, morning hearing schedule.
August 4th, active file.
7:00 a.m., Hyde, Quentin.
8:15, Peterson, Scott.
- 7:30, Phoenix, Simon - It's Phoenix!
Who?
Simon Phoenix.
- Phoenix, Simon. - I knew him.
He's evil in a way you've never read about.
He's a criminal the likes of which you have never seen.
Hold that thought, Zachary Lamb.
Simon Phoenix's code, now.
Access code for Phoenix, Simon.
- No code found. - L7, are you coming down with another virus, are you?
- Of course not. - You don't get it, Lenina Huxley.
Phoenix isn't coded.
He was chilled in the 20th...
before they started lo-jacking everybody.
Declared his own kingdom in South Central L.A.
In a bad time...
- he was the worst. - Emergency, code 187.
Emergency, code 187.
Locating stopped code.
MurderDeathKill. MurderDeathKill.
Location, Cryo-prison, parking area. Cryo-prison, Level 6.
- No. - Main cryo-prison parking zone.
Enhancing image.
Tracking Dr. Mostow.
187, deceased.
Do you wish to assign a coroner?
Tell me L7, is the doctor's conveyance still in the parking zone?
The answer is no. Car missing.
Doctor's conveyance is not in parking zone. It is in motion.
Locate precise code-fix on doctor's conveyance.
Fixing location. Beverly Hills.
Robertson.
Doheny.
Beverly Drive.
Doctor's vehicle has been code-fixed.
Approaching the corner of Wilshire and Santa Monica Boulevard.
Glorious.
Fine work.
All nearby units, ProtectServe...
Wilshire and Santa Monica.
- Unit 12 ProtectServe. - Apprehend fugitive.
Proceed with extreme assertiveness.
Doctor's vehicle has been code-fixed.
Approaching the corner of Wilshire and Santa Monica Boulevard.
I don't know. Lately I just don't feel like there's anything special about me.
You are an incredibly sensitive man...
who inspires joy-joy feelings in all those around you.
- Get out of here! - Excuse me.
I'm sorry.
Greetings, Citizen! How are you feeling on this glorious day?
You look great today!
I feel good too.
Angeles Information Network. Automated banking.
Damn, I'm possessed.
I wonder if I can play the accordion too.
File code accepted.
Friendly, Edgar. Code level 60.
Listed offenses: civil unrest...
Don't you hear a thought repeating in that barbaric brain of yours?
The name Friendly, Edgar?
Edgar Friendly.
Don't you have a job to do?
Don't you have someone to kill?
Someone to kill.
Gun noun. Portable firearm.
This device was widely utilized in the urban wars of the late 20th century.
Referred to as a "pistol".
Look, I don't need a history lesson. Come on, hell. Where are the goddamn guns?
You are fined one credit for a violation of the verbal morality statute.
What? Fuck you.
Your repeated violation of the verbal morality statute has caused me to notify the police.
Please remain where you are for your reprimand.
Yeah, right.
Fuckers are fast too.
You are fined one credit for violation of the verbal morality statute.
ProtectServe in place.
4 minutes, 15 seconds lapse.
Maniac is imminent. Request advice.
With a firm tone of voice...
demand maniac lie down with hands behind back.
Simon Phoenix!
Lie down with your hands behind your back!
What's this?
Six of you. Such nice tidy uniforms.
Oh, I'm so scared.
What? You guys don't have sarcasm anymore?
Maniac responded scornfully.
Approach and repeat ultimatum...
in an even firmer tone of voice. Add the words, "or else".
Simon Phoenix! Lie down on the ground...
or else!
Anti-Graffiti Activation Program...
activated.
Aborted.
Human presence detected.
Safety override code accepted.
Lucky number seven.
We're police officers!
We're not trained to handle violence!
Wait for me!
Stupid.
Simon says, everybody sing!
"And the home
Of the brave"
Play ball!
We've lost every camera for six blocks.
Go to Century City, 1200 millimeters.
He's going for the vehicle's battery coil.
It's pure capacitance gel.
The problem is not the defacement of public buildings or...
the noise pollution caused by the exploding devices.
Allow me to explain.
The real problem lies in the man whose initials...
mark the detonating graffiti...
on the streets of our peaceful city.
The man behind the "EF"...
Mr. Edgar Friendly.
For a sadly extended period of time...
we in San Angeles...
have been plagued by a pack of subterranean hooligans.
You will come to know them as "scraps".
Men and women who have left the comfort of our society...
only to spew hostility...
at the very bottom they have relinquished.
There was a time when we used to look upon these scraps...
as rather pathetic and relatively harmless.
Now they have a leader.
Mr. Friendly seems relentless in his ambition...
to infect our harmony with his venom.
He must, of course...
be stopped.
This radical terrorist behavior, led by Mr. Friendly...
must not be allowed to undermine our safety.
Safety Above All.
I expect your trust, confidence and certitude.
Excuse me.
Dr. Cocteau...
a cryo-con has effected self-release from the penitentiary.
It's quite horrific. MurderDeathKills, all categories of chaos.
Enhance your calm.
Be well them for me.
Get me Captain George Earle immediately.
It was just...
I mean it was so...
How can a man be so blatantly sadistic?
It was fun for him.
I want you to do everything in your power to snare this agent of destruction.
You have my utmost confidence.
It will be done, Dr. Cocteau.
Be well.
"Utmost confidence."
"Everything in our power".
What else is there?
Zachary Lamb...
how was the fiendish Simon Phoenix apprehended back in the 20th?
Twelve-state manhunt.
Satellite surveillance.
A video bite on "Unsolved Mysteries".
None of them worked.
In the end, it took just one man.
One cop.
John Spartan.
John Spartan?
That's right.
They called him the "Demolition Man".
Spartan file 98345, LAPD.
Spartan file 98761C, LAPD.
Are you sure this is real life?
Barely.
Spartan's a legend.
I've been doing a historical study. Over 1,000 arrests over three years.
All authentic criminals.
There was a lot more business back then.
How can you justify destroying a $7 million mini mall...
to rescue a girl whose ransom is only $25,000?
Fuck you, lady.
Good answer.
This is your recommendation?!
The Demolition Man's an animal.
He's clearly the man for a job such as this. You could reinstate him.
He's a muscle-bound grotesque...
who hasn't worn a shield in 40 years.
Simon Phoenix is an old-fashioned criminal.
We need an old-fashioned cop.
Biofax 312-618 is ready for regular routine inspection.
John Spartan, 5864.
Pulmonary activity approaching normal.
Body temperature, 63% and rising.
Biolink engaged.
Laser defibrillation sequence started.
Plasma transfer in 15 seconds.
Plasma transfer, 10 seconds...
8 seconds...
6 seconds...
Plasma transfer complete.
MTL complete.
Hunting down an escaped cryo-con...
by releasing another one?
I am unconvinced.
This is within the powers of the police charter, sir.
He can be released on limited parole and reinstated to active duty.
It's not enough to collect the '90s, you have to bring the man's life?
Dr. Cocteau said everything within our power.
I can't think of a better idea.
That still doesn't mean it's a good one.
This man comes from a dissimilar method of law enforcement.
I'm not sure he's any different than Simon Phoenix himself.
Detective?
Detective, I am Lieutenant Lenina Huxley.
The year is 2032.
Now, the reason you have been released is...
How long have I been under?
36 years.
I had a wife.
What happened to my wife?
Her life was extinguished in the Big One of 2010.
She died.
In an earthquake.
The earthquake.
I had a daughter.
What happened to her?
John Spartan.
I am Chief of Police George Earle.
We didn't thaw you out for a family reunion.
Consider it fortunate that the lieutenant even bother did a probe on your wife.
This is about you and the cryo-con Simon Phoenix.
What?
This morning Simon Phoenix escaped from this cryo-facility.
We've had 11 murderdeathkills so far.
You see, we've become a society of peace-loving...
and, and understanding and we are, quite frankly...
not equipped to deal with this situation.
There have been no deaths of unnatural causes in San Angeles for the last 16 years.
Where?
The Santa Barbara, Los Angeles, San Diego Metroplex were merged in 2011.
You are in the center what used to be Los Angeles.
That's great.
- You, get me a Marlboro. - Yes, of course. Right away.
What's a Marlboro?
It's a cigarette. Any cigarette.
Smoking is not good for you. Anything not good for you is bad.
Hence, illegal. Alcohol, caffeine, contact sports, meat...
Are you shitting me?
John Spartan, you are fined one credit for violation of the verbal morality statute.
What the hell is that?
- John Spartan, you are fined one credit... - Bad language...
chocolate, gasoline, uneducational toys and anything spicy.
Abortion is also illegal, but then, so is pregnancy if you don't have a license.
Caveman...
let's finish with all the Rip Van Winkle and get moving.
Our Mr. Phoenix has risen from the ashes.
I tracked that dirtbag for two years...
when I finally bring him down you turn me into an ice cube for my trouble.
Thanks, but no thanks.
The conditions of your parole are full reinstatement into the SAPD...
and immediate assignment to the apprehension of Simon Phoenix.
Or...
you can go back into cryo-stasis.
Not many people get a second chance, John Spartan.
Any new inforama on Simon Phoenix?
There is nothing, Lenina Huxley.
Where's John Spartan?
He went to the bathroom. I guess he got all thawed out.
Sir, I formally convey my presence.
How are you doing?
We're not used to physical-contact greetings.
I don't know...
if you guys know it but...
you're out of toilet paper.
Did you say toilet paper?
They used handfuls of wadded paper...
back in the 20th.
I'm happy that you're happy, but the place we used to supposed to have a toilet paper...
you've got a little shelf with three sea shells.
He doesn't know how to use the three seashells.
I can see how that'd be confusing.
I don't believe it. Is that you, Spartan?
Zach? Zach Lamb?
What happened to you?
I got older.
My God, I remember when you were...
a rookie pilot.
They finally grounded me.
Shit, you were a damn good flyer.
You're fined two credits for violation of the verbal morality statute.
I'll be right back.
They seem to be friends...
yet he speaks to him in the most profane manner.
If you'd read my study, you'd know this is how heterosexual men bonded.
I knew that.
Thanks a lot you shit-brained, fuck-faced, duck-fucking...
- pain in the ass. - You're fined five credits...
for repeated violations of the verbal morality statute.
So much for the sea shells.
See you in a few minutes.
Unfortunately Simon Phoenix was not coded.
While you're sleeping, everyone in the city was installed code.
It was a brilliant idea by Dr. Cocteau. An organic microchip...
is sewn into the skin.
Sensors all over the city can zero in on anyone at any time.
I can't even conceive what you police officers did before it was developed.
We worked. This fascist crap makes me want to puke.
What do you think you're scratching?
You really think we'd let you go without control?
Your code was implanted the second you thawed.
Why not just shove a leash up my ass?
You dirty meat-eater!
No matter how Viking your era was...
I cannot digest how you ever wore a badge!
You're going back, John Spartan, oh, yes, you're going back!
Could you two please dump some hormones?!
We need every cortex we can get in this situation.
We don't need the Neanderthal.
Our computer has already examined every scenario...
resulting from the appearance of Simon Phoenix.
It's determined he'll try to set up a drug lab and form a crime syndicate.
That is correct.
I hate to interrupt you two...
but that's fucking stupid.
You think he wants to start a business?
Phoenix is going for a gun.
Plain and simple.
Trust me.
He's going for a gun.
Who cares what this primate thinks?
Resonate some understanding.
The only place a person can even view a gun in this city...
is at a museum.
Welcome to the San Angeles Museum of History.
Beneath you you'll see an excavation...
of an actual 20th century street scene...
in downtown Los Angeles, preserved since the earthquake of 2010.
For specific information on objects featured in the exhibit...
Firearms are displayed in the Armory...
located on Level A.
You are now entering the Hall of Violence...
a visual representation of the primitive behavior prevalent...
during the late 20th century.
Home, sweet home.
John Spartan, even if Simon Phoenix was able to locate the cache of firearms...
it'd be impossible for him to remove them.
She's right. They're located in a maximum security armory exhibit.
Just a hunch. Trust me.
It's a cop thing.
And what am I, a frog?
Excuse me.
I'll drive.
Resetting all bio-links for new driver.
Weight, height, peripheral vision set.
If you would like...
to commence transportation, John Spartan, initialize sequence now.
You drive.
Welcome, Lenina Huxley.
You seem very much alone, John Spartan, but...
things aren't all that different.
Perhaps you'd like to hear an oldies station?
Oh, what a relief it is.
This is the most popular station in the town.
Wall to wall mini-tunes. You called them "commercials".
The classic you've all been waiting for.
The number one request today: "Armour Hot Dogs".
"Kids eat Armour Hot Dogs..."
This is my fave!
"Skinny kids, kids who climb on rocks"
"Tall kids, sissy kids, even kids with...
chicken pox love hot dogs"
"Armour Hot Dogs"
"The dogs kids love to bite."
Someone put me back in the fridge.
You are now entering the armory exhibit.
Here you will find displays in the cabinets and walls...
So sorry. Didn't see you there.
Sweet baby.
Oh, shit.
Yes. Now this is what I'm talking about.
How do I get in here?
Is there a 15 day waiting period? Or can I just take one now?
Motherfucker.
Oh, fuck it.
Mellow greetings.
What seems to be your boggle?
My boggle?
How much do you weigh?
I weigh...
Please vacate the museum, patrons.
Be calm.
Please vacate...
the museum, patrons. Be calm.
Wait a minute, this is the future.
Where are all the phaser guns?
Mellow greetings, sir.
What's your boggle?
Warning, please exit rapidly.
The magnetic accelerator gun...
the last hand-held weapon of this millennium, displaced the flow of neutrons...
through a nonlinear cycloid electromagnetic accumulator.
So, what? It needs batteries?
What size? I mean where the fuck do you find batteries?
Is there a battery store around?
Excuse me, museum patron. Can l...
Where's Radio Shack?
Sweet music to my ears.
The magnetic accelerator gun will achieve fusion in 2.6 minutes.
I was thinking about leaving quickly. Patience is not one of my virtues.
Did you see that?
What?
Never mind. I give up trying to figure this place out.
Excuse me, Rambo. I need to borrow this.
Access and correlate procedure.
Establish communication with intruder.
Wrong.
- Luke Skywalker, use the Force. - Oh, dear.
- What the hell is this? - It's a glow-rod. It's what we got.
Does it work?
Guess so.
He's trapped in section 8.
I doubt it, Huxley. Make sure the building's clear.
Done. I want a visual.
Now, every corridor of the museum, I want full sensors routed to me.
You guys wait here. Give me 10 minutes.
Museum patron, you are now confined to the armory.
Museum patron, you are now confined to the Armory.
The armory exhibit is now sealed.
All museum patrons still in the facility should remain calm.
Help is imminent.
This museum is no longer sealed, isn't it?
What can I say? I'm a blast from the past.
You should've stayed there.
That voice sounds familiar. Who is that?
Bad aim, blondie.
Spartan? John Spartan?
Oh, shit. They let anybody into this century! What're you doing here?
Simon says, bleed!
Great. Just great.
You're making it too easy for me, Phoenix.
Come on, you piece of shit!
So let me get this right.
They defrosted you just so you could lasso my piddly ass?
I've dreamed about killing you for 40 years.
Keep dreamin'!
Magnetic accelerator activated.
About time.
Past is over!
Time for something new and improved!
Oh, hell.
Shit! I love this gun!
How do you like the future?
Come on!
Oh, I know that must hurt!
Huh, soldier boy?
You're on TV!
Oh, shit!
You're dead!
Forgot to say, "Simon says".
Oh, shit.
Good one.
Such a brand new world. Sorry you must go!
Shit!
Our noble facility has been desecrated by hooligans.
Someone will pay dearly for this.
Sir, the stress breeder is inside being demobilized as we speak.
Shit. Being frozen must have thrown my aim off.
Don't wrong. I'll get you with the next shot.
I don't think so.
No kiss-kiss, no bang-bang.
You were doing so well.
Now don't you have a job to do?
Isn't there a thought repeating in your barbaric brain?
The name Friendly.
Mr. Edgar Friendly.
Don't you have someone to kill?
- Yeah, I do. - Excellent.
Then go and do your job.
Shit.
Saved by the bell.
Shit!
Damn!
You don't know how lucky you're he didn't whack you.
Well, I must say that whacking, whatever it is, sounds most disagreeable.
You scared him away.
I don't know how to thank you. You saved my life.
No problem.
Not bad for a 74-year-old.
Simon Phoenix knows he has some competition.
He's finally matched his meat.
You really licked his ass.
That's "met his match"...
and "kicked his ass."
"Met his match and kicked his ass".
Captain Earle...
Who is this man?
Detective John Spartan, temporarily reinstated to the San Angeles...
Police Department to pursue the cryo-con Simon Phoenix.
You told us to do everything in our power to capture the bad man.
Oh, Yes, yes, I did, I did.
Yes, I do recall the exploits of Mr. John Spartan.
Yes, of course. The Demolition Man.
That's quite all right.
Unexpected. Creative.
But quite all right.
John Spartan, welcome.
In honor of your arrival...
and your protection of the sanctity of human life...
namely my own...
I would like to invite you to join me for dinner tonight.
The both of you.
Please, I insist.
I would like you to accompany me...
to Taco Bell.
Look forward to it. Thank you.
- Taco Bell? - Yes.
So let me get this right:
Spacely Sprockets here, who's now the man in charge, the Mayor-Gov...
who wants to take me to dinner to Taco Bell...
and I wouldn't mind a burrito...
who is also the guy builts the goddamn cryo-prison?
John Spartan, you are fined one...
Dr. Cocteau is the most important man in San Angeles.
He practically created our whole way of life...
- savage. - Yeah.
He can have it.
Now, Phoenix could be anywhere...
but not being coded can limit him.
That is correct. Money is outmoded.
All transactions are through codes.
So he can't buy food or a place to stay for the night.
It'd be a waste of time to mug someone.
Unless he rips off someone's hand.
But with officers patrolling...
it should be just a matter of tick-tocks before...
We already have a backup plan.
We can wait for another code to go red.
When Phoenix performs another MurderDeathKill...
we'll know exactly where to pounce.
Great plan.
Thank you.
I've been an enthusiast of your escapades for quite some time now.
In fact, I perused some visuals from the Schwarzenegger Library.
Hold it.
The Schwarzenegger Library?
Yes, the Schwarzenegger Presidential Library.
Wasn't he an actor?
- Stop. He was President? - Yes.
Even though he wasn't born in this country, his popularity caused the 61 Amendment.
I don't want to know.
President.
What hell is this? No door? No welcome mat?
What is this?
How do they expect you to kill somebody?
Oh, shit, I love that smell. Reminds me of biscuits and gravy.
All right. A job is a job.
Edgar Friendly, whoever the fuck you're, prepare for Simon Phoenix.
So what's with the Cocteau guy anyway?
He says I saved his life, which I'm not sure I did.
My reward is dinner and dancing at Taco Bell?
I like Mexican food, but...
Your tone is quasi-facetious. But...
you do not realize that Taco Bell is the only restaurant to survive the Franchise Wars.
- So? - So.
Now all restaurants are Taco Bell.
No way.
Welcome to Taco Bell.
Enjoy your meal.
"Valley of the Jolly Green Giant"
"Good things from the garden"
"Garden in the valley"
"Valley of the Jolly Green Giant"
Here comes the Neanderthal.
Mr. Spartan over there please, and Lieutenant...
Thank you.
How are you doing?
Enjoy-joy your meal, sir.
Good thing I'm hungry.
Ladies and gentlemen, please raise your glasses to the hero of the hour...
my savior
Detective John Spartan.
Appreciate it.
Greetings and salutations.
I'm Associate Bob.
We met before, ever so briefly. I was so, probably in fear at the time.
Do you have the salt?
Salt is not good for you, hence it is illegal.
So, John Spartan, tell me...
what do you think of San Angeles, 2032?
I thought the future would be a rotten cesspool.
You weren't here when the real disturbances began.
Civilization tried to destroy itself.
The city degenerated into a total fear zone.
People stayed home, afraid to go out. People wanted the madness over.
When I saw the chance to make things right...
I seized it.
If I had not, the radiance of San Angeles would not be here.
Just your rotting cesspool of hate and suffering. Which would you prefer?
Can you book me a flight out of here when the sermon's over?
John Spartan...
for your crimes you would surely have died...
in jail before now.
Even you must appreciate the persuasively tranquil humanity...
of the cryo-prison system?
I don't want to spoil your dinner, but my cryo-sentence was no sweet lullaby.
I had feelings and thoughts.
A 36-year nightmare about people caught in a burning building.
You were awake? I don't think so.
I think so.
My wife beating her fists against a block of ice that used to be her husband.
Then you're nice, wake me up and let me know everything that meant something to my life is gone.
It would have been more humane to leave me to the fucking crows.
What would you say if I called you a brutish fossil...
symbolic of the decayed era gratefully forgotten?
I don't know. "Thanks"?
I thought during rehabilitation...
the prisoners were not conscious. A person would go insane.
The side effects of the cryo-process...
are unavoidable.
You were found guilty of a crime.
You owed and still owe a debt to society.
There's nothing I can do.
Yes, call for backup. I'll be across the street.
Where're you going?
Bad guys about to do bad things. It's just one of those hunches.
Go for the truck!
The food's in the truck!
Grab the big box! Come on, move, move, move!
You'll regret this all your life. Both seconds of it.
Good night!
Get him!
What a fucking hero. Come on.
Please, don't.
What the hell?
Such reckless abandonment.
Looks like there is a new shepherd in town.
That's "sheriff". Who are those guys?
They're known as scraps.
Outcasts and deserters who choose to live beneath us...
in sewers and abandoned tunnels.
They're a constant irritation to our harmony.
They're nothing but thugs and hooligans.
A society of thieves. The last remaining criminal element in the city.
But plans are in progress to purge this peril from our day.
You're even better live than on laser disk.
The way you paused to make a witticism before doing battle...
with that Scrap...
Huxley, this isn't the Wild West, okay?
The Wild West wasn't even the Wild West.
Hurting people isn't a good thing.
Sometimes it is, but not...
when it's people looking for something to eat.
San Angeles time is now 22:15.
Coding off.
Auto-drive.
Auto-drive engaged.
Look I'm sorry I yelled at you.
No need for a de-hurtful retraction.
I assimilated too much contraband.
I fleshed you out as a blow-up-the-bad-guy-while-grinning type.
But I realize, you're the moody-gunslinger-who-will-only-draw-when-he-must type.
Stop.
What?
I just do my job and things get...
Demolished.
You know I keep looking around, I think of my daughter growing up in a place like this.
I'm afraid she'll think I'm some kind of primitive.
As much as I want to see her, I almost don't want to.
Because I don't think I'll fit in well.
Not at all.
- It'd be a minor misuse of police powers, but I could do a search for you. - No.
Sorry.
Subject change. I got what you wanted.
Great.
What do you need that for?
It's just one of those cop hunches.
Lights.
No. I've changed that.
Illuminate.
Deluminate.
Isn't that nicer?
Go ahead, you try.
Illuminate.
Raymond, Raymond, we've got to talk.
How did you get in?
Wish I knew. I got pass codes.
Routes to underground kingdoms.
Complete access to the industrial data-grid interface.
I don't even know what that means.
But I've been meaning to ask you.
Because I like it! I like it a lot!
You have these skills for a reason.
Not for your personal amusement.
Your job is to kill Mr. Edgar Friendly and stop a revolution.
That is why you were rehabilitated.
All right. I'm going to do your dastardly deed for you.
But it'll be more difficult than you thought.
I'm going to need some help.
I'll need about five or six more "special" men.
And I just so happen to have a list.
You see, I wouldn't want you to defrost any of those maddog killer types, you know what I mean?
And none of those motherfuckers from New York. They're too uptight.
So you're going to be the only maddog killer type?
Fine.
Take care of it.
Just get it over with.
You're beginning to be more trouble than you're worth.
Oh, Raymond, don't say that.
And what do I get out of all this?
What do you want?
Malibu.
Santa Monica. Hell, what about all the coastal cities?
I'll bear it in mind.
- Good, I'll send you a memo. - Just do your job!
What is John Spartan doing here?
Did you invite him to this little party of ours?
Look, you finish your business...
and I'll stuff him back in the freezer.
Think of him as a guarantee.
A guarantee?
You don't have much of a guarantee.
I took care of Spartan once, I'll take care of him again.
Now we need those men defrosted.
So this is where you live, Huxley?
Very not bad.
Thank you.
Where will I be staying?
I've procured you a domicile down the corridor from my own.
Everything is voice coded, so if you need something, just ask.
Lights.
What do you think?
Clicked off a lot of credits to create a 20th century apartment.
It's very...
Isn't it?
John Spartan...
There's a course say, well-known...
and documented connection between sex and violence.
Not so much a causal effect...
but a general state of neurological arousal.
And...
after having observed your behavior this evening and...
my resultant condition...
I was wondering if you'd like to have sex?
With you?
Here?
Now?
Great!
I'll be right back.
Love boat?
Here.
Now, just relax. We'll begin in a few seconds.
Begin what?
Having sex, of course.
What's wrong? You broke contact.
Contact? I didn't even touch you yet.
I thought, you wanted to make love.
Is that what you call this?
Vir-sex produces high alpha waves during transference of sexual energies.
All right. Let's do it the old-fashioned way.
Disgusting!
You mean...
- fluid transfer? - No, I mean boning, the wild mambo.
That is no longer done.
The exchange of bodily fluids, do you know what that leads to?
yeah, I do
Kids, smoking, desire to raid the fridge.
Rampant exchange of bodily fluids was one of the major reasons of the downfall of the society.
After AIDS, there was NRS, after NRS, there was UBT.
One of the first things Dr. Cocteau was able to do was outlaw...
and behaviorally engineer all fluid transfer out of socially acceptable behavior.
Not even, not even a mouth transfer's condoned.
Kissing's not allowed?!
Damn, I was a good kisser.
What about kids?
Procreation?
We go to a lab.
Fluids are purified, screened...
and transferred by authorized medical personnel only.
It is the only legal way.
What're you doing?
Breaking the law.
You are a savage creature, John Spartan.
And I wish you to leave my domicile. Now!
You know...
Code accepted. Be well, John Spartan.
Lights.
"He doesn't know how to use the three sea shells."
"Behavioral engineering"?
Hi, Marty, I was thinking... Oh, my God, I'm sorry, wrong number.
Our noble facility has been desecrated...
Someone will pay dearly for this.
Sir, the stress breeder is inside being demobilized.
Shit! Being frozen must've thrown my aim off.
The next shot.
I don't think so.
No kiss-kiss, no bang-bang.
- Detective. - I'm sorry about last night.
This is for you.
For me?
Thank you.
I'll drive.
- I must learn to do this once in my life. - OK.
Thank you for the gift.
Look I don't know what you guys do in my cryo-sludge but when I thawed, the first thing I wanted to do is knit.
I mean, how come I know what a zipperfoot, a shuttle and a bobbin is?
I could weave a throw rug now with my eyes closed.
It's part of your rehab program.
For each inmate the computer draws up a skill or trade...
which best suited to their genetic disposition.
It implants the knowledge...
and the desire to carry out whatever, the training assigned.
I'm a seamstress?
That's just great.
I come out of cryo-prison and I'm Betsy-fucking-Ross.
Phoenix comes out, can access computers, operate all vehicles...
knows the location of every damn thing in town...
and three times stronger than when he was in.
- Can you get me Phoenix's rehab program now? - Sure.
- I'm a seamstress. - Access code for Simon Phoenix.
Access Simon Phoenix.
Accessing.
Access denied.
- What? - Security override.
It can't be right.
Access granted, Officer Huxley.
Accessing Simon Phoenix, Deepfile rehab 65-R.
Urban Combatkill.
Torture Methodology. Computer Override Authority.
- There must be a mistake. - Survival Tactics.
Terrorism Tactics. Weapons Training. Martial Arts. MurderDeathKill.
Explosives technician. Violent Behavior.
- This isn't a rehab program. - No kidding.
This would create a monster.
Who develops these programs?
Cocteau Industries of course.
But why would the benevolent...
Dr. Cocteau send such a brute savage into our midst?
Good question. Let's go ask him.
No, John Spartan. You do not accuse our savior of being connected with a...
multi-murderdeathkiller like Phoenix.
It's, rude.
I'll be subtle.
I'm good at subtle.
Mellow greetings.
We are happy to welcome you...
to the Cocteau Behavioral Engineering Complex.
Be well.
Enhance your calm, John Spartan.
Mellow apologies for my lack of physical disposition, detective...
but I do have a entire city-gov to run.
Well, run this.
You programmed Phoenix's rehab to turn him into a terrorist.
And I don't think his escape was an accident.
- Very subtle. - Thank you.
Outside the museum, why didn't he blow your brains up?
What did you say?
I don't remember. Does it matter?
Yeah, it matters. I saw the security disk.
He had 10 seconds to figure out where to put the hole in your fucking head.
- John Spartan, this display of barbaric behavior was unacceptable even in your time. - Yeah
But it works.
When a man like Phoenix has a gun near your head, 10 seconds is 9.5 seconds longer than you live.
Not everyone is as eager as you...
to resort to violence to solve all the difficulties in life.
Even now, I begin wondering if the chaos in the museum was the result of Mr. Phoenix's presence or your own.
Wonder about this, shithead.
If you think you got this maniac under control, trust me...
you don't.
- Is there something specific you plan to do with that archaic device? - John Spartan
No, I didn't think so.
Detective, the only thing I haven't got under control is you.
But that can be solved.
You, my Cro-Magnon friend, are dead.
Your family's dead, your past is dead.
Dead things cannot affect the living. So...
enjoy your moment...
of prehistoric bravado because after you leave here it will be over.
Like everything else in your life.
Officer, return this man to cryo-stasis immediately.
Be well.
Be fucked.
You are fined one credit...
I'll wait here.
Let's go.
- I don't know. - I do know. Turn that thing on.
I hope you know what you're doing.
You're asking me to disobey a direct order.
I'm to escort you to the cryo-prison.
You do what you gotta do, I know what I gotta do. I gotta get that maniac and put him on ice or that's where I'll be.
- Enhance your calm, John Spartan. - Look I've had it with enhancing my calm.
I'm gonna find that psycho Phoenix, enhance his calm. Then I'll turn all my attention to Cocteau.
You don't have to come with me. I'll do it alone. OK?
Even if Phoenix was programmed to escape, kill and steal...
why are you going to the wasteland?
Your city-wide manhunt didn't work because Phoenix was in a place...
you can't monitor...
afraid to go and see, don't give a shit about.
I wanna go down there, I wanna find Phoenix and I wanna put him in a hurt locker.
So, you wanna come with me? Or you wanna arrest me?
I'm with you.
Let's go blow this guy.
Away.
Blow this guy away.
Whatever.
She has a way with words.
What's wrong, Huxley?
It's not very clean.
A real garden spot.
All right. Which way?
Over there.
Okay, you guys be ready for anything.
My dog's better than your dog
My dog's better than yours
My dog's better 'cause he gets Kennel-Ration
I'm sorry, when I'm nervous, I...
Sorry.
Over here.
What's that emanation?
Come on guys.
No. Hey, just relax. All I want is a burger and a beer if you got one.
How will I pay?
Huxley, it's better to give.
Want a slug?
No, thank you.
I think I'll be sick.
Oh, God.
It's fantastic. You guys must try one.
Just don't ask where the meat comes from.
Huxley, what does that mean?
Do you see any cows around here, detective?
Rat?
This is a rat burger?
Not bad.
It's the best burger I've had in years.
See you later.
They don't seem very hostile, John Spartan.
No, they don't.
Now that's a thing of beauty.
Huxley, do you know what this is?
A 1970 Oldsmobile 442.
With a 455-cubic-inch engine.
Radial tires and bucket seats.
I'm impressed.
I studied.
So did I. Hand over the glow-rod.
Your friends too. Come on, move.
You got balls, coming down here.
We're looking for a MurderDeathKiller.
Can you help us or just bully us with your primitive weapons?
Or maybe they're not so primitive.
So you think you're taking me in?
Guess what?
Not happening.
You tell Cocteau he can kiss my ass. Yeah. That's right.
You tell Cocteau, it'll take an army, asshole, to get rid of me.
I don't give a shit. I got nothing to lose.
I don't know who the hell you are, let alone want to take you anywhere.
So stay here, be well and Cocteau's an asshole!
Let's dump them up top. They're only here to spy on us.
Wait a minute.
- You're the guy outside Taco Bell. - Yeah.
What do you want?
I guess you weren't part of the Cocteau plan.
Greed, deception, abuse of power. That's no plan.
- That's why everybody is down here? - That's right.
See...
According to Cocteau's plan...
I'm an enemy because I like to think.
I like to read.
I'm into freedom of speech and freedom of choice.
I'm the kind of guy who likes to sit in a greasy spoon...
and think, "Should I have steak or barbecued ribs with gravy fries?"
I want high cholesterol.
I want to eat bacon, butter and cheese.
I want to smoke a cigar the size of Cincinnati.
I want to run through the streets naked...
reading Playboy magazine because I might need to.
I've seen the future. You know what it is?
It's a 47-year-old virgin...
drinking a banana-broccoli shake and singing "I'm a wiener".
Up top, you live Cocteau's way.
What he wants, when he wants, how he wants.
Your other choice: come down here.
Maybe starve to death.
Why don't you take charge and lead these people out of here?
I'm no leader.
I do what I have to do.
Sometimes people come with me.
All I wanna do is bury Cocteau up to his neck and let him think happy happy thoughts forever.
Then I got bad news.
I think he wants to kill you.
All right gentlemen, let's review.
The year is 2032.
That's 2-0-3-2. As in the 21st century.
And I'm sorry to say that the world has become a pussy-whipped...
Brady Bunch version of itself run by a bunch of robed sissies.
All we have to do to run the whole thing...
is to kill a man named Friendly, who put it all together.
But there's an extra added bonus.
We get to kill...
the man who put most of us in the freezer.
You mean...
we get to kill John Spartan?
Exactly.
I want you to loot, pillage, plunder, I want you to steal.
I want you do all the wonderful things that we used to do before any of this happened.
This world will be ours!
Let's bring back the good old days!
- Are you with me? - Yeah.
Let's do it!
It is a curious conclusion which you have deduced, John Spartan.
But I can find no fault in your logic.
Simon Phoenix is the perfect weapon to send into these savage regions.
I'm impressed, John Spartan.
They thawed him out just to kill me?
- I'm flattered. - Don't be flattered. Be frightened.
This guy's a certifiable nightmare.
- That's why you're down here? - Yeah.
I must have done something right in the previous life.
Can't imagine what that could have been.
Two for the price of one.
Let's take them.
Stay down!
I'll be goddamned. Like a New York cockroach.
Everything's going wrong.
There's an elevator shaft at the top.
Does that mean we're going up?
Momentito, Senorita Huxley. Come on.
How nice! Must've been expecting me.
Now what?
Buckle up.
There he is! He is in my car!
I'll be goddamned.
What's happening to cops today?
Don't you know you are endangering civilians?
Auto-inflate!
Auto-inflate.
That was lovely.
Huxley, drive!
Okay, I've read all about this.
What do I do now? Push this pedal?
Okay, I got it.
Punch it! Huxley!
Excuse me?
Push the pedal as hard as you can!
No free rides!
Emergency, doors open.
Doors opening.
Say hello to my friend.
Doors close!
Malfunction.
Computer, auto-drive.
Auto-drive engaged.
Going to cut your hair!
Remember the 40 bus passengers...
you blew up trying to get me?
They were already dead.
Cold as Haagen-Dazs!
I went to jail with a 36-year smile.
You're dead.
Speak for yourself.
Self-drive!
Unable to execute.
- Self-drive! Now! - Malfunction.
Emergency!
Brake!
Self-drive engaged.
Brake! Brake!
Brake now, you, Mickey Mouse piece of shit!
John Spartan, are you in there?
Who do you think it is, Huxley?
I thought your life force had been prematurely terminated!
I thought I was history too.
What the hell happened? All of a sudden, this car turned into cannoli.
It's the securefoam. It saved your life.
Look at you, you're in shambles.
Don't wrong. I can fix it later. All I need is a needle and thread.
I really said that, did I? Damn.
John Spartan, you caveman, you're under arrest!
Return to the cryo-prison. Immediately!
I heard all that. We'll talk later, Chief.
Right now, I need something. A shotgun, a flare gun.
Shit!
Defensive red alert!
Stun batons on.
Relax.
Look at you, you got bump your noggin...
and think you're Pancho Villa?
Who?
Never mind.
Time to take a stand.
Good. While you're doing it, loan me a gun. Two guns.
You'd use these weapons against men and women who uphold the law?
We use these weapons to shop for groceries, dick.
You can't leave.
You're under arrest. This very concept negates the possibility of your leaving.
Skip it, Chief.
Lieutenant Huxley!
Chief...
you can take this job and you can shovel it.
Take this job...
and shovel it.
Close enough.
I hadn't counted on this but I must say, you worked out beautifully.
People are terrified of you.
What's new? People have always been terrified of me.
But this time they're really intimidated.
Now...
I'll have carte blanche to create the perfect society.
My society.
San Angeles will be a beacon of order...
with the purity of an ant colony.
And the beauty of a flawless pearl.
Look, you can't take away people's right to be assholes.
That's what you remind me of...
an evil Mr. Rogers.
Will you please kill him?
He's pissing me off.
Put another log on the fire!
I'll love running this place!
Well, now...
what shall I do with you?
I am an excellent associate, sir.
I'd be delighted to continue my services with your administration.
That's the man we'd use...
Excuse me, the police are here.
Oh, man!
What the hell are you doing?!
I'm impressed.
That man has died by my hands.
It was him or us.
There is that.
Where'd you learn to kick like that?
Jackie Chan movies.
Looks like the Cocteau plan went up in smoke.
Rest in peace, Raymond Cocteau.
John Spartan, civilization as we know it will come to an end.
What will we do?
I don't know. But trust me, this is better for you.
What's that?
This is bad.
This is very bad.
He's accessed the cryo-prison and is about to defrost multi-lifers.
Most of them don't like you.
Most of these guys don't like their mothers. They're bad boys.
How many are they?
Eighty.
All without rehab.
They'll be re-animated within the hour.
We must stop this.
I'm not at all pleased about having caused the fatality of a convict.
I now understand that under certain circumstances violence is necessary.
Good.
I hope you understand this.
I hope my butt didn't look like that.
Okay, who do we have left that's good?
Let's see...
Foulks, Patrick.
Jeffrey Dahmer? I love that guy.
How long before the rest are done?
They're in the final stages of reanimation.
Great. Absolutely great.
Gentlemen!
Thank you very much, but your services are no longer required.
Send a maniac to catch a maniac.
Attention.
Cryo-prisoner defrosting re-animation sequence...
now entering final stage.
Count down to reanimation of prisoner batches...
290, 310, 480...
570.
10 minutes.
- That's it. The very last one. - Excellent.
Accessed.
What the hell is that?
Didn't expect that, did you?!
Where're you going?
I wish you the best of luck.
Stupid.
How's it hanging?
I'm sure you're familiar with the long arm of the law.
Why don't you struggle a little bit? Make me work for it!
What do you say? How about...
a little target practice. What do you say?
Did that hurt your head?
Shit! Goddamn!
Fuck!
That's it!
You won't get out of this one!
I'll drop you in that vat of defrost...
and fry you like a chicken...
or with my little pinky, drop your monkey ass...
I'll be damned.
Shit! Goddamn!
What am I doing wrong?
Cryo-prisoner re-animation...
sequence now entering final stage.
Is it cold in here, or is it just me?
Good memory.
Come here!
Shit!
I hate cops!
Look into my eyes. I'll see you in hell.
Not.
This is the best day of my life.
Heads up!
Did you apprehend the villain responsible for murdering of Dr. Raymond Cocteau?
I wouldn't exactly say apprehend.
But he's a history.
And the cryo-prison...
That is history too.
What'll we do?
How will we live?
We'll go out drinking, get shit-faced and paint the town.
Graffiti slogans, it'll be a blast.
I'm gonna tell you what you gonna do.
Why don't you get a little dirty...
you, a lot clean.
And somewhere in the middle...
You'll figure it out.
Fucking-A.
Well put.
Greetings and salutations.
I'm Associate Bob. And may I say...
it would be a pleasure to assist you creating a more humane...
Let's talk about the hair, okay?
Pick a color. And lose the kimono. You look like a couch.
Thanks for rendering me unconscious.
Huxley, I did it for your own good.
- We're supposed to be a team. - We are.
Oh, my.
Are all fluid transfer activities like this?
- Better. - Better?
Oh, my.
I think I'll like the future.
Now that you've demolished everything.
But there's one thing I want to know.
How did damn there sea shell you work?