Nibiru, M class planet
Damn it man,
that was our ride.
You just stunned our ride.
Great...
Run!
- What the hell did you take.
- I have no idea but they were valued to him.
Kirk to shuttle 1, both
of us is out of the kill zone.
Your are clear, repeat...
Spock, get in there and neutralize
the volcano let's get out of here.
We have do this now!
I told the Captain, the shuttle
was not built to this kind of heat.
Captain, did any one
indigenous life forms see you.
No, Mr. Spock they did not.
The prime directive clearly states
that there cannot be no interference,
with the internal development
of alien civilizations.
I know what it says which is why
I'm running through jungle, wearing a disguise.
Now, drop off your
super ice-cube, and let's go!
- Kirk out.
- You are good.
If we are going to do this,
we got to do it now.
Ash is killing our coils.
Are you sure you don't
want me go instead.
That would be highly illogical as I'm
already outfitted in heat resistance...
Spock, I was kidding.
- You got this.
- Guys, we have to go, now!
They are trying to kill us!
I'll see you in 90 seconds.
Do it... do it!
H-two, seven, three...
I can't hold this position,
Spock, I'll got to pull you back up!
Negative. This is our only
chance to save the species.
If this volcano erupts,
the planet dies.
Pull back up! Now!
Spock, are you okay?
I'm surprisingly, alive.
Standby.
We have to get him back!
I suit up and go down.
- We have to abandon the shuttle.
- We cannot just leave him there.
We don't have a choice.
Uhura, I'm sorry.
Spock, we are going back to the Enterprise.
We get you out of there.
Captain, I'm ditching the shuttle.
- You must make it to Enterprise
on your own. - Wonderful.
- Uhura, are you ready to swim?
- I'm ready.
Jim, the beach
is that way.
I know, we don't
going to the beach!
Oh, no, no!
I hate this!
I know you do!
Do you have any idea, how ridiculous is
to hide a starship on the bottom of the ocean.
We've been doing this since last night.
The salt-water is going to erodes...
Scotty! Where is Spock?
Still in the volcano, sir.
Captain on the bridge!
Lieutenant, do we have
an open channel for Mr. Spock?
The heat is frying his comms
but we still have a contact.
Spock!
I activated the device, Captain.
When the countdown is complete
the reaction should render the volcano inert.
Yeah, that's going
to render him inert.
- Should we have use of the transporters?
- Negative, sir.
- Not with this kind of magnetic field...
- I need to beam Spock back to the ship.
Give me one way to do it.
Maybe if we have
direct line of sight...
No way. You are talking
about an active volcano.
Sir, if that thing erupts, I can't guarantee
that will withstand the heat.
I do not know if we can maintain
that kind of altitude.
Our shuttle was concealed by the ash cloud,
but the Enterprise is too large.
If utilized in a rescue effort,
it would be revealed to the indigenous species.
Spock, nobody knows the rules better than you,
but there got to be an exception.
Non. Such action
violates prime directive.
Shut up, Spock!
We are trying to save you, damn it!
Doctor, the needs of the many
out weight needs of the few.
Spock we are
talking about your life.
The rule cannot be
violated in any case...
Spock!
Try to get him back on-line.
90 seconds to detonation.
If Spock were here
and I was there, what would he do?
He lets you die.
Spock!
You are all-right?
Captain, you let them
see our ship.
He is fine.
- Bridge to Captain Kirk.
- Yes, Lieutenant.
- Is Commander Spock on board, sir?
- Safely and sound.
Please notify him that,
the device successfully detonated.
You heard that?
Congratulations, Spock!
You just saved the world.
- You violated the prime directive.
- Ah, come on Spock, they saw us big deal.
-Subs  by the 24hpie-
Corrected and synced by: Szaki
I can save her.
What did you say?
Your daughter.
I can save her.
Who are you?
Jim, come on,
Let it go.
You are not actually
answer that, are you?
San Francisco,
Starfleet Headquarters
Spock, I'm telling you
this why he called, I can feel it.
Your feelings aside,
I consider highly unlikely,
we will be selected
for the new program.
Why else would Pike
want to see us?
Forget about seniority, they gave
us the newest ship in the fleet.
- And who else they going to send out.
- I can think numerous the possibilities...
A five-year mission, Spock.
That's deep space, that's uncharted
territories, think incredible that's going to be.
Hello, ladies!
Jim Kirk.
- Uneventful.
- Admiral?
That's the way you describe
the survey in Nibiru in Captain's log.
Yes sir, I didn't want to waste your time
going with the details.
Tell me more about this volcano.
Data says was highly volatile. If it would
be erupt, it would wipe out the planet?
- Let's hope it doesn't, sir.
- Something tells me it won’t.
Well sir, volatile is all relative.
Maybe our... data was off.
Or maybe it didn't erupted, because Mr. Spock
detonated a cold fusion device inside it,
right after a civilization that's
barely invented the wheel,
happen to see a starship
rising out their ocean.
That's pretty much how
you describe it, is it not?
- Admiral... - You filed a report?
Why did you not tell me?
I correctly assumed that you would
be truthful in your Captain's log.
Yeah, I'd would been
if I didn't have to save your life.
A fact for which I'm
deeply grateful
and very reason I felt necessary to take
responsibility for the actions taken by...
Oh, yeah don't be so noble pointy
if you also throwing me under the bus.
- Pointy? Is that a derogative
reference? - Gentlemen.
Starfleet's mandate is to explore-
and to observe, not to interfere.
Had the mission had
gone as planned, admiral,
Indigenous species would be never
been aware of our interference.
- That's a technicality.
- I am Vulcan, sir.
- We in-praise technicality.
- You giving me attitude, Spock.
I'm expressing multiple attitudes
simultaneous, sir.
- To which you are referring to?
- Out.
You're dismissed, Commander.
- Do you have any idea what
a pain in the ass, you are? - I think so, sir.
So, tell me what did you wrong?
What's the lesson to be learned here?
- Never trust a Vulcan. - I see,
you cant even answer the question.
You lied on a, official report,
you lied.
You think the rules don't apply to you
because you disagree with them?
That's why you talk me into signing up in first place.
That's why you gave me your ship.
I gave you my ship because
I saw a greatness in you...
And now I see you don't
have got ounce of humility.
- What I suppose to do? Let Spock die?
- You are missing the point.
I don't think I'm, sir.
What would you have done?
I would not risked my first officers
life in the first place.
You suppose to survey a planet
not alter its destiny.
You violated dozens starfleet regulations and
almost got everyone under your command killed.
But except I didn't, you know
how many crew have I lost since...
- That's your problem! - Since I took command?
- This and the defect is.
- You think you're infallible. - Not one.
- You think not you can't make mistakes,
It's a pattern with you.
- That the rules are for the other people.
- Some should be.
And what's worse is you using
plain luck to justify, you playing God!
Given the circumstances, this has been
brought to admiral Marcus attention.
He convened a special tribunal
to which I was not invited.
You understand what's starfleet
regulations mandate be done in this point?
They taken Enterprise
away from you...
They are sending you
back to the academy.
Admiral, listen.
No, why should I listen?
You don't listen anybody but yourself!
Every decision I've made...
I can't listen.
You don't comply with the rules,
you don't take responsibility for anything,
and you don't respect the chair.
You know why?
Because you're not ready for it.
LONDON
Transmission sent
to: admiral Marcus
- How did you find me?
- I know you better than you I think you do.
When I first time found you
was in a dive-bar like this.
Remember that? Got your ass
handed to you.
- No it didn't.
- You don't?
- No, it wasn't what happen...
- That was an epic beating.
No, it wasn't.
You had napkins hanging
out of your nose... did you not?
Yeah, that was a good fight.
A good fight?
I think that's your problem
right there.
They gave it back to me.
The Enterprise.
Congratulations!
Watch your back with
that first officer, thou.
Spock not going to work
with me, he is been transferred.
USS Bradbury.
You are going to be
my first officer.
Yeah, Marcus took
some convincing...
But any now and then
I can make a good case.
- What did you tell him?
- The truth...
That I believe in you.
And if anybody deserves
a second chance, it's Jim Kirk.
I don't know what to say.
That is a first.
It's going to be okay, son.
An emergency session
at the Daystrom.
- That's us.
- Yeah.
Suit up.
- Captain. - Not any more,
Spock, first officer.
I was demoted
and you were resigned.
It's fortunate that the consequences
were not more severe.
You gotta be kidding me!
- Captain, my intention was not...
- Not Captain.
I saved your life Spock. You
wrote a report, I lost my ship.
Commander, I see now I should
alerted to the fact I submitted the report.
Now I'm, familiar with your compulsion to follow
the rules, but, see I cant do that.
Where I come from, if someone saves
your life you don't stab him at the back.
Vulcan's cannot lie.
Then I'm talking to
the half-human part of you.
Do you understand
why I went back for you?
Commander Spock?
I'm Frank Abbott, USS Bradbury.
Guess you are with me.
Yes, Captain.
The truth is
I'm going to miss you.
Admiral Marcus, sir.
Thank you for meeting
on such short notice.
Be seated.
By now some of you heard
what happened in London.
The target was a starfleet data archive,
now it's a damn hole in the ground.
42 men and women are dead.
One hour ago, I received a message
from starfleet officer,
who confessed to
carrying out this attack.
That he been forced to do this by this man,
Commander John Harrison.
He's one of of our own and he's the man
responsibility this act of savagery.
For reasons unknown, John Harrison has just
declared one man war against starfleet.
Under no circumstances are we to allowed
this man to escape Federation space.
You here tonight represent the senior
command of all the vessels in the region.
And in the name of those
that we lost...
You will run this bastard down.
This is a manhunt, pure and
simple so let's get to work.
Earth perimeter sensors hasn't detected
any warp signatures leaving the system,
so we know he cannot be far.
You park ships at
blockade formation,
and deploy search vehicles
and landing parties,
to run down every lead.
This man has shown willingness
to kill innocent people...
so rules of engagement are simple
if you come across this man
and you or your life
lies those nearby
you are authorized to use
deadly force on the subject.
- What's in the bag?
- James, not now!
Does it seem odd that he targeted
an archive? It's like bombing a library.
Chris, is everything okay there?
Yes, sir. Mr. Kirk is just acquainting
to his new position as first officer.
If you have something to say,
Kirk, say it tomorrow is too late.
I'm fine, sir,
my apologies.
Spit it out son, don't be shy.
Why the archive?
All that information is public record...
if he really wanted to damage starfleet.
- This could be just the beginning.
- Beginning of what, Mr. Kirk?
Sir, in event of attack,
protocol mandates...
that senior commands gather,
Captains and first officers
at Starfleet Headquarters,
right here.
In this room.
It is curios Harrison would Commander
a jump ship without warp capability...
Clear the room!
We need air defense team,
Daystrom conference room.
Go, go, hurry!
- Yeah? - Commander, Mr. Scott has found
something in wreckage of Harrison's ship,
He asked to see us right away.
Captain, I found this in the crashed jump ship, sir.
This is how the bastard got away.
- What do you mean?
- It's a portable transwarp beaming device.
- Can you figure out where he went?
- I already did, sir and you are not going to like it.
He gone to the one place
we just cannot go.
Admiral, sir, he is
not on Earth.
He is on Kronos, sir.
I request my command to be reinstated
and your permission to go after him.
Give us a minute.
- Kronos?
- Yes, sir.
So Harrison has gone
to the Klingon home world?
- Is he defecting?
- We are not sure, sir.
He has taking refugee in the Keth
province, region uninhabited...
He got to be hiding there, sir. He knows if we even
go near Klingon space, it will be all out war.
Starfleet can't go
after him, but I can.
Please, sir.
All out war with the Klingons
is inevitable, Mr. Kirk.
If you ask me,
it's already has begun.
Since we first learned
of their existence, the Klingon Empire,
conquered and occupied
two planets that we know of,
fired on our ships
half a dozen times.
They are coming are way.
London was not an archive.
It was top secret branch of starfleet
designated to Section 31.
They were developing
defensive technologies,
training our officers to gather
intelligence on Klingons,
And any other potential enemy
means to do us harm.
Harrison was one of
our top agents.
Now he's a fugitive and
I want to take him out.
Pike always said you're one
of our best and brightest.
You should have heard him
defend you.
He was the who talk you
to joining starfleet, wasn't he?
Yes, sir.
Did he ever tell you
who talk him into joining?
His death is on me.
And yours won't be.
Sir, please, all I...
Mr. Spock, you said that the province
where Harrison is hiding uninhabited?
Affirmative, sir.
As part of our defensive strategy,
31 developed a new photon torpedo.
Long range, untraceable.
You will be invisible
Klingon sensors.
I don't want you hurt,
but I want to take him out.
You park on the edge of the Neutral Zone,
you lock on to Harrison’s position,
You fire, you kill him
and hall ass.
Permission to restate Mr. Spock
as my first officer.
Granted.
Jim?
- Where were you?
- For what?
Your medical exam. 10 hours ago,
you were at damn fire-fight.
- Now, It's my duty to...
- I'm fine, Bones.
Hell you are!
I'm fine.
Status report, Mr. Spock.
The Enterprise should be ready
for launch by the time we arrive.
Good, good.
Captain.
Thank you requesting
my reinstatement.
You are welcome.
As I'm again your first officer, it is now my duty,
strongly object to our mission perimeters.
Of course it is.
There are no starfleet regulations
that condemns a man to die without trial.
Something you and
admiral Marcus are forgetting.
Also, preventively firing torpedoes
at the Klingon home-world.
You yourself said that the area is uninhabited.
There is going to be only one casualty.
In case you weren't listen our orders
have nothing do with starfleet regulations.
Wait a minute, we are firing
torpedoes at the Klingons?
Regulations aside this
action is morally wrong.
Regulations aside, pulling your ass
out of the volcano was morally right.
- And didn't win any point for that.
- Jim, calm down.
I'm not going take
ethic lessons from a robot.
Resorting to name calling suggest that you are
defensive, therefore find my opinion valid.
I wasn't asking for your opinion.
Bones, get that thing off my face!
Captain, our mission could
start a war with the Klingons,
and is by very definition
is immoral.
Perhaps, you should take requisite time
to arrive to this conclusion for yourself.
Captain Kirk.
Science officer Wallace. I've been
signed to Enterprise by admiral Marcus.
These are my transfer orders.
- You requested an additional
science officer, Captain? - I wish I had.
Lieutenant Carol Wallace
doctor in applied physics,
specializing in advanced weaponry.
- Impressive credentials.
- Thank you.
But redundant now that I'm back
on-board the Enterprise.
And yet, more than merrier,
have a seat, Doctor.
Shuttle crew, standby for lift off.
No, I'm not signing anything, now,
get these bloody things off of my ship.
- Is there are problems, Mr. Scott?
- Aye, sir,
I was just explaining
to this gentlemen,
I can’t authorize any weapons on board this
ship without knowing what's inside them.
- Mr. Scott rises yet another point.
- Report to the bridge.
Captain!
Mr. Scott, I understand your concerns
but we need these torpedoes on board.
Due respect, sir, but
photon torpedoes run on fuel.
Now I can not even detect
the type what fuel
is in compartments, on these
torpedoes, because they are shielded.
Now I asked for the specs,
but he said...
- Classified.
- It’s classified.
So, I said, no specs,
no signature!
Captain.
- Flight checks completed. We are good
to go, sir. - Thank you, Mr. Sulu.
Now, if will you excuse me, sir,
I' have warp core to prime.
Get down.
- Jim, your vitals way off.
- Report to med bay.
Scotty! I need you to approve
those weapons.
- Do you know what is this, Captain?
- I have no time for a lecture, Scotty.
- Do you know what is this?
- Its a warp core.
It's a radioactive catastrophe
waiting to happen.
A sudden shift in magnetic
output from, say,
firing one or more of 6 dozen
torpedoes with unknown payload,
could start a chain reaction which will
kill every living thing on this ship.
Letting those torpedoes on board
Enterprise is the last straw.
- What was the first straw?
- What was the...
There are plenty of straws,
How about starfleet confiscating
my transwarp equation
now some madman using it now
to hop a cross the galaxy.
- Where do you think he got it from?
- We have orders, Scotty.
That's what scares me.
This is clearly
a military operation.
Is that we are now?
Cause, I thought we were explorers.
Sign for the torpedoes.
That's an order!
Right, well you don't leave me
no choice than resign my duties.
- Come on, Scotty.
- You are giving me no choice, sir.
- You don't give much of a choice.
- I will not stand by...
Make an exception
and sign it!
- Do you accept my resignation or not?
- I do!
I do.
You are you're relieved, Mr. Scott.
Jim.
For the love of God.
Do not use those torpedoes.
Captain, I'm so sorry
about admiral Pike.
We all are.
- Are you okay?
- Fine, thank you, Lieutenant.
Actually, Scotty just quit,
and your boyfriend second guessing
me every chance he gets.
I'm sorry, that was impropriety.
It just some times I want to rip
those thing of his head.
- Hell maybe it's me.
- It’s not you.
It’s not?
- Are you guys, are you guys, fighting.
- I'd rather not talk about it.
Oh, my God, what is it even like?
Your ears burning.
Captain on the bridge.
Mr. Chekhov.
You've been shadowing Mr. Scott, you are
familiar with Engineering systems of this ship?
- Affirmative, sir.
- Good.
You are my new chief,
go and put on a red shirt.
Aye, Captain.
Re-tract all moorings, Mr. Sulu.
Yes, sir.
- Lieutenant Uhura, open a ship
wide channel. - Yes, sir.
Mr. Chekhov, how are
we looking down there?
- All systems nominal, Captain.
- Copy that.
- Warp available at your command.
- Thank you, Mr. Chekhov.
- All right, let's ride.
- Yes, sir.
Channel open, sir.
Attention, the crew of the Enterprise.
As most of you know, Christopher Pike
former Captain of this ship,
and our friend,
is dead.
The man who killed him has fled our system,
and hiding in the Klingon home-world.
Somewhere he believes
we are unwilling to go.
We are on our
way there now.
For admiral Marcus it is essential
that our presence go undetected.
Tensions between the Federation
and the Klingon Empire have been high,
any provocation could
lead to all out war.
I will personally lead
a landing party,
to abandoned city
on the surface of Kronos.
There we will capture
the fugitive John Harrison,
and return him to Earth so he can
face judgement for his actions.
All right, let's go get this
son of the bitch! Kirk out.
Captain, I believe you
made a right decision.
If I can be assistance, I would be happy
to accompanied you to your away team.
You happy?
I was simply attempting to
use your way to convey an idea.
Thank you, Mr. Spock.
Spock, you startled me.
- What are you doing, doctor?
- Verifying the torpedoes and...
You misunderstand. What are you
doing on board this ship?
There is no record of you
being signed to the Enterprise.
- Really, that must be some sort of mistake.
- My conclusion as well, Dr. Marcus.
Except that you have lied
about your identity.
Wallace is the sir name
of your mother.
I can only assume that,
admiral is your father.
Mr. Spock.
I am aware that I have no right
to ask this of you...
But please...
He cannot know that I'm here.
Engineering manually
dropped out of warp, sir.
- Mr. Chekhov, did you brake my ship?
- Sorry, sir I do not know what happened.
The core overheated.
I had to activate the emergency stop.
It must be a cooling leak,
I need time to find it.
- Sorry, Captain.
- Dammit.
- Mr. Sulu, time down to our destination.
- 20 minutes, sir.
It's 20 minutes in enemy space
that we weren't counting on.
We better hop to it.
- Where is Spock?
- Here, Captain.
You coming with me to Kronos.
- Lieutenant, how is your Klingon?
- It's rusty but it's good.
Good, you are coming too.
Is this giving me any problems,
is it, you two working together?
Absolutely not.
Unclear.
I'll meet you
in shuttle bay.
Jim, you are not actually
going down there, are you?
You don't rob a bank, when
a getaway car has a flat tire.
I'm sure engineering will have us all
patched up, by the time we get back.
- Is that right, Mr. Chekov?
- Yes, Captain.
I'll do my best, sir.
Mr. Sulu, you have the com.
Once we are on route, I want you to transmit
a targeted comm-burst to Harrison's location.
Tell him you have bunch of real
big torpedoes pointed at his head,
if he doesn't play nice
we are not afraid to use it.
- Is there a problem?
- No, sir.
But I have never sat
on that chair before.
You going to do great.
Jim, wait.
You just sat that man down
on high stakes poker game,
with no cards
and told him to bluff.
Now, Sulu is a good man,
but he is no Captain.
For next 2 hours he is, and enough with
the metaphors, all-right. That's an order.
Mr. Sulu, make sure that
the knormian ship is ready to fly.
Acting Captain Sulu
to shuttle-bay 2.
Please have the trade ship we confiscated
during march-man incident last month.
Fuelled and flight ready. Captain Kirk
is on route to you right now.
- Ready to Deploy, Captain.
- Lieutenants loose the red shirts.
- You are knormien arms
dealers, put those on. - Sir?
For this thing goes south, there
can be nothing, tying us to starfeet.
Unless of course you want to
start a war, Mr. Hendor.
- No, sir.
Good, me neither.
I'm detecting a single life sign
in Keth province.
Given the information
provided by Mr. Scott,
this is most likely
John Harrison.
Mr. Sulu, I think we found our man
you let him know you mean business.
Aye, Captain.
Attention, John Harrison.
This is Captain Hikaru Sulu
of the USS Enterprise.
A shuttle of highly trained officers
is on it's way to your location.
If you do not surrender
to them immediately,
I will launch entire payload of
advanced long range torpedoes,
currently locked on
to your location.
You have two minutes
to confirm your compliance.
Refusal do so will result
in your obliteration.
If you test me,
you will fail.
Mr. Sulu.
Remind me never
to piss you off.
KRONOS
We arrive at Harrison's location
in three minutes, Captain.
It's unlikely that he
will come willingly.
I calculate the odds him to
attempting to kill us 91.6%.
- Fantastic.
- Good thing you don't care about dying.
I'm sorry, Lieutenant
I couldn't hear what you...
Oh, I didn't say anything.
Actually I'll be happy to speak
if you are willing listen to me.
- Guys.
- I'd prefer discuss this in private.
You'd prefer not to
discuss this at all.
- Our plans...
- Are you really going to this now?
You never seems to require
my attent...
- Miss Uhura...
- I'm sorry, Captain just two seconds.
Okay. It's us. At that volcano you
didn't give a thought to us.
What would it do to
me if you died, Spock.
You didn't feel anything.
You didn't care.
And not I'm  the only-one whos is upset
with you, the Captain is too.
No, no, don't drag me into this.
She's right. Your suggestion that
I do not care about dying is incorrect.
Te sensitive beings optimal chance
to maximizing utility is long and prospers life.
- Great.
- Not exactly a love-song, Spock.
You misunderstand.
It is true I chose not to feel anything
upon realizing that my own life was ending.
As admiral Pike was dying
I join in with his conscience,
and experienced what he felt
at the moment of his passing.
Anger, confusion, loneliness.
Fear.
I had experienced
those feelings before,
multiplied exponentially on the day
my planet was destroyed.
Such a feeling is something
I choose never to experience again.
Nyota, you mistake
my choice not to feel,
as a reflection
of me not caring.
While I assure you, the truth
is precisely the opposite.
What the hell was that?
What happen?
Where is the signal?
They are cut out,
I'm working on get them back.
We are pursued by
a D-4 class Klingon vessel.
- I thought this sector was abandoned.
- Is must be a random patrol.
Hold on.
This ship has no
offensive capabilities.
- She got us, give me all six fuel cells.
- Aye, Captain.
Dammit!
They are closing fast.
bearing 2-8-5.
Right there! There,
we can loose them there.
If you are suggesting we utilize passage
between approaching structures,
- the ship will not fit.
- Will fit.
- Captain, we will not fit.
- Will fit, Will fit!
- I told we fit.
- I'm not sure that qualifies.
- Any sign of them?
- No, which worries me.
- We lost them.
- Or they are jamming our scanners.
Or we lost them.
They are ordering us to land.
Captain, they are going want
to know why we are here.
And they are going to
torture us, question us,
and they are going to kill us.
So, we come out shooting.
We are outnumbered,
out-gunned.
There is no way we survive
if we attack first.
You have me here
because I speak Klingon.
Then let me speak Klingon.
This is not going to work.
It is our only
logical option.
And if you interrupt her now you
will not only wrath of the Klingons,
but that of Lieutenant Uhura as well.
I'm here to help you.
- Lieutenant.
- Thanks, Captain.
With full respect.
A terrorist is hiding here
in the ruins.
He has killed many of our people.
Why should I be interested
into a human who kills humans?
Because you believe in honor.
This man doesn't have honor.
You and your people
are in danger.
- Stand down!
- How many torpedoes?
Stand down!
The torpedoes! The weapons you threaten
with me in your message. How many are they?
72.
I surrender.
On the behalf of
Christopher Pike,
my friend,
I accept your surrender.
Captain!
Captain.
Cuff him.
- Bones, meet me at the brig.
- I'll be right there.
Lieutenant, contact starfleet. Let them know
that we have Harrison in custody.
- And we will be on our way
once the warp core is repaired. - Yes, sir.
Why the hell did he surrender?
I don't know. He just took out squadron
of Klingons single handedly. I want to know how.
Sounds like we have
a Superman on-board.
You tell me.
Put your arm through that hole.
I'm going to take a blood sample.
Why aren't we moving, Captain?
An unexpected malfunction
perhaps in your warp core,
immediately stranding you on
the edge of the Klingon space.
- How the hell do you know that?
- Bones.
I think you would find my
insight valuable, Captain.
Are we good?
Let me know
what you can find.
Ignore me, and you will get
everyone on this ship killed.
Captain, I believe he will only
attempt to manipulate you.
I would not recommending
engaging prisoner further.
Give me a minute.
Let me explain what
is happening here.
You're a criminal.
I watched you murder
innocent men and women,
I was authorized to end you.
And the only reason
why you are still alive
is because
I am allowing it.
So shut your mouth.
Captain, are you're going to
punch me again over and over,
till your arm weakens?
Clearly you want to?
So, tell me,
- Why did you allow me to live?
- We all make mistakes.
No.
I surrender to you because, despite
your attempt to convince me otherwise,
you seems to have
a conscience, Mr. Kirk.
If you did not, it would be impossible
me to convince you of the truth.
2, 3,
1, 7,
4, 6,
1, 1.
Coordinates not
far from Earth.
If you want to know
why I did, what I did
go and take a look.
Give me one reason
why I should listen you.
I can give you 72.
And they are on-board
your ship, Captain.
They have been all long.
I suggest you open one up.
You know what really
bothers me, thou?
It's the modifications,
you know the enhancements.
Right, and like that
I'm off the ship.
Just trying to do
what's right.
And what did you do anyway? You just
stood there like an oyster, looking at me.
- What?
- Scotty, it's Kirk.
Oh, well now.
If is it Captain James
Tiberius perfect hair.
Did you hear that,
I called him perfect hair?
- Where are you?
Are you drunk?
What I do in my private time
is my business, Jimbo.
I need your help me
with something.
Will you take these coordinates
down 23, 17, 46, 11.
- Are you writing? - What, you think
I do not remember 4 numbers?
You have little faith.
- What was the third one?
- 46.
Don't know exactly what
you are looking for but...
I have feeling you
know when you see it.
May been right
about those torpedoes.
I will consider that an apology,
and I will consider that apology.
- You are the one who quit.
- You make me quit!
Mr. Scott! Scott!
Enough with that guy.
I'm not doing that
man any favors.
No!
All-right then.
Are you out of corn-fed mind?
You're actually not going
to listen this guy?
He killed Pike,
he almost killed you,
And now think it's a good idea to pop open
a torpedo because he dare you to do it?
Why did he saved
our life's, Bones?
The doctor does have
a point, Captain.
Don't agree with me, Spock,
it's make me very uncomfortable.
Perhaps you two should learn
governing yours emotions, doctor.
- In this situation, logic dictates...
- Logic! My God!
There is a maniac trying to make us
blowing up our damn ship, and you all talking about...
I don't know why he
surrendered but that's not it.
So, if we are going to open
a torpedo the question is how?
But Jim, without Mr. Scott on board
who's exactly qualified
to just pop-up a four ton
stick of dynamite?
Admiral's daughter appear to be have interest
in torpedoes and she is a weapon specialist.
Perhaps she could
be some use.
- What admiral's daughter?
- Carol Marcus.
Your new science officer concealed
her identity to board the ship.
- And when were you going to tell me that?
- When it became relevant, as it just did.
- Are the torpedoes in the weapons-bay?
- Loaded and ready fire. What are they?
I do not know. So I transferred
to your ship to find out why.
I do apologize for that.
By the way, if I cause you
any problems I'm sorry.
- I'm Carol Marcus.
- James Kirk.
Torpedoes.
My father gave me access
to every programs, he had control.
So when I heard he was developing
these prototype torpedoes
when I went to confronting him
about it, he wouldn't even to see me.
That's when I discovered that torpedoes
had disappeared from all the official records.
And then he
gave them to me.
You much clever than your
reputation suggest, Captain Kirk.
- I have reputation? - Yes you do,
I'm friend of Christine Chapels.
- Christine, yes. How is she?
- She transferred to frontier to be a nurse.
- She's much happier now.
- That's good.
You have no idea who
I'm talking about, do you?
- What are we doing in here? - Is this shuttle
prepared to fly? - Of course it is.
- Would you please turn around.
- Why?
Just turn around.
It's too dangerous to try open one
of these a torpedoes on the Enterprise.
But there is a nearby planetoid,
I can open up one there.
But I will need some help...
Turn around.
Now!
Captain on the bridge.
Mr. Sulu, Dr. Marcus and McCoy
landed on the planetoid, yet?
Yes, sir. They are moving
the torpedo into the position now.
Good, any activity
from the Klingons?
Not yet, but if we are stuck here
much longer they will find us.
Lieutenant Uhura, did you let starfleet know
that we have Harrison in custody?
Yes, sir.
No response.
Engineering to bridge.
Hello, Captain, can you hear me?
Mr. Chekov, give me some good news.
We found the leak, sir,
but damage is substantial.
- We are working on it.
- Any idea what caused it?
No, sir but I except
full responsibility.
Something tells me that
it wasn't your fault.
- Stay on it.
- Shuttle is standing by, Captain.
Bones, thanks for helping out, Dr. Marcus
asked for steadiest hands on the ship.
You know, when I dreamed about being stuck
on a deserted planet with a gorgeous woman,
there was no torpedo.
Dr. McCoy, may I remember you
that you're not there to flirt.
- So, how can these legendary
hands help you Dr. Marcus? - Bones.
To understand how powerful these
weapons are we need to open the warhead.
To do that, we need to access the fuel compartment.
Unfortunately for us, warhead's on these weapons are live.
Sweetheart, I once performed
an emergency c-section on a pregnant Gorn.
Eight cubs, let me tell you
those little bastards bite.
I think I can work some
magic on your missile.
Dr. McCoy, there is a bundle
of fiber optic-cables against the inner casing.
You need to cut the 23th wire down.
Whatever you do, do not touch anything else.
- Do you understand?
- Right. That thought never crossed my mind.
Dr. McCoy, wait for my word.
I'm re-routing detonation processor.
- Are you ready?
- Born and ready.
Good luck!
- Sir, torpedo just armed itself.
- The warhead is going to detonate in 30 seconds.
What the hell happened?
I can get my arm out.
Aim their signal!
Beam them back right now?
Transporter can not difference
between Dr. McCoy and torpedo.
We can not beam back
one without the other.
- Dr. Marcus can you disarm it?
- I'm trying. I'm trying.
- Jim get her hell out of here. - No, if you
beam me back, he dies. Just let me do it.
10, 9, 8...
Standing by to transport
Dr. Marcus on your command, sir.
4, 3...
Shit!
De-activation successful, Captain.
Dr. McCoy, you all-right?
Bones.
Jim?
You gonna
want to see this.
Coordinates 23.17.46.11
Jupiter
... loading dock 12.
USS Vengeance bridge crew requesting
entry to the construction hangar.
You are clear enter the hangar.
I need a welding-team
on number one cell.
Holy shi...
- What do we got?
- It's quite clever actually.
This fuel container has removed from torpedo
and retro fitted to, hide this Cryo-tube.
- Is he alive?
- He is alive.
But if you try revive him without
the proper sequence, could kill him.
This technology is beyond me.
- How advanced, Doctor?
- It's not advanced.
That Cryo-tube is ancient.
We have not needed to freeze anyone,
since we develop warp capability.
Which explains the most interesting
thing about of our friend here.
He is 300 years old.
Why there is a man
in that torpedo?
There are men and women in all those
torpedoes, Captain. I put them there.
Who the hell are you?
"A remnant of the time long past."
Genetically engineered to be superior, as
to lead others to peace in a world at war.
But we were condemned as
criminals, forced in to exile.
For centuries we slept.
Hoping when we woke,
things would be different.
And as result of
the destruction of Vulcan,
your starfleet began to aggressively
search system quadrants of space.
My ship was found in-drift,
I alone was revived.
I looked up John Harrison.
Until a year ago he did not exist.
John Harrison was fiction created the moment
I was awoken by your admiral Marcus,
as to help him in
advance his cause.
A smoke screen to conceal
my true identity.
My name is Khan.
Why would a starfleet admiral
ask a 300 year old
frozen man for help?
Because, I'm better.
- At what?
- Everything.
Alexander Marcus needed to respond
to uncivilized threats in civilized times.
For that he needed
a warriors mind.
My mind,
to design
weapons and warships.
You are suggesting the admiral violated
every regulation he vow to uphold,
simply because he wanted
to exploit your intellect.
To exploit my savagery.
Intellect alone is useless
in a fight, Mr. Spock.
You, you can not even break a rule
how would you be excepted to break bone?
Marcus used me
to design weapons.
To help him realize
his vision of militarized starfleet.
He sent you to
use those weapons
to fire my torpedoes on
an unsuspecting planet.
And then he purposely crippled
your ship in enemy space,
leading in one
inevitable outcome.
The Klingons would come searching
for whom ever was responsible,
and you have had
not chance of escape.
Marcus...
would finally have the war he talked
about the war, he always wanted.
No. No.
I watched you open fire in a room full of
unarmed starfleet officers.
You killed in cold blood!
Marcus took my crew from me.
- You're a murderer!
- He used my friends to control me.
I tried to smuggling
them to safety
by concealing them in
the very weapons I had designed.
But I was discovered,
I had no choice,
but to escape alone.
And when I did, I had
every reason to suspect,
that Marcus had killed
every single one
of the people
I hold most dear.
So, I respond it in unkind.
My crew...
is my family, Kirk.
Is there anything you would
not do for your family?
Proximity alert, sir. There is a ship
at warp heading right for us.
- Klingons?
- At warp?
No, Kirk.
We both know who it is.
I don't think so, it's not
coming at us from Kronos.
- Lieutenant, move Khan to med bay, post six
security officers on him. - Yes, Captain.
Captain on the bridge.
- ETA on incoming ship?
- Three seconds, sir.
- Shields.
- Aye, Captain.
They are hailing us, sir.
On screen.
Broadcast ship wide
for the record.
Captain Kirk.
Admiral Marcus,
I wasn't excepting you.
Hell of a ship you got there.
I wasn't expecting to get word
of that you taking Harrison to custody,
in violation of your orders.
Well, we have to improvise when,
our warp core unexpected
malfunction.
- But you already know that, sir.
- I don't take your meaning.
Oh, that's why you are here isn't?
To assist with our repairs.
Why else would the head of
starfleet personally come to,
the edge of the neutral zone?
- Captain, they are scanning our ship.
- Is there something I could find, sir?
Where is your prisoner Kirk?
Per starfleet regulation, I'm planning
on returning Khan to Earth
to stand trial.
Well, shit.
You talked to him.
Exactly what I wanted
to spare you from.
I took a tactical risk and
I woke that bastard up.
Believing that his superior intelligence
could help us protect ourselves,
from whatever
came after us next.
But, I made a mistake.
And now the blood of
everybody's kill is on my hands.
So, I'm asking you,
Give him to me,
so, I can end what I started.
And what exactly would you like
me to do with the rest of his crew, sir?
Fire at them to the Klingons
and end 72 lives?
To start a war in process?
He put those people in those torpedoes.
I didn't simply wanted burden you
with knowing what's inside of them.
You saw what this
man can do all by himself.
Can you imagine what would happen
if we woke up rest of his crew?
What else did he tell you,
that he is a peace keeper?
He is playing you, son.
Don't you see that?
Khan and his crew were condemned
to death as a war criminals.
And now it is our duty
to carry out that sentence
before anybody else dies
because of him.
I'm going to ask you again.
One last time, son.
Lower your shields.
Tell me where he is.
He is in Engineering, sir.
But I have him moved to
the transporter room right away.
I'll take it from here.
- Do not drop those shields, Mr. Sulu.
- Aye, Captain.
Captain given your wearness
Khan's true locations in med bay,
may I know the details
of your plan?
I told Marcus we will bring
a fugitive back to Earth,
that is what
we going to do.
Mr. Chekov, can we warp?
Sir, if we go to warp, we runs
a risk of seriously damaging the core.
Can we do it?
Technically yes,
but I would not advise it, Captain.
Noted.
- Mr. Sulu, set a course for Earth.
- Yes, sir.
Pparte'.
Well, at least we are moving again.
If you think,
you are safe at warp,
you are wrong.
Lieutenant Uhura, contact starfleet.
Tell them we are pursued into the neutral-
zone by unmarked Federation ship.
Comms are down, sir.
- Permission to coming on the bridge.
- Dr. Marcus.
He is going to catch us and when he does the
only thing that's going to stop his ship is me.
- So you must let me talk to him.
- Carol, we are warp.
- He can't catch up with us.
- Yes, he can.
The ship has advanced
warp capabilities.
Captain, I'm getting a reading
I don't understand.
- Where are we?
- 237,000 Km from Earth.
- Damage report.
- Weapons are not working.
We have a bulk head-breach.
- Where is the damages?
- Major hull damage, Captain.
Evasive maneuvers,
get us to the Earth, right now!
Stop! Everybody on
this ship is going to die,
if you don't let
me speak to him.
Uhura, hail them.
Sir, it's me, it's Carol.
What are you doing on that ship?
I heard what you said.
That you made a mistake and now
you are doing every thing you can to fix-it.
But, Dad...
I don't believe that, the man who
raised me is capable,
of destroying a ship
full of innocent of people.
And...
If I'm wrong about that, then you going
to have to do it with me on board.
Actually Carol, I won't.
- Jim.
- Can we intercept the transport signal?
No, sir.
Carol!
Captain Kirk without authorization, in league
with the fugitive John Harrison,
you went rogue in
enemy territory.
Leaving me choice, but hunt
you down and destroy you.
- Lock phasers.
- Wait, wait, wait!
I make this quick, target all out door
torpedoes on the Enterprise bridge.
Sir, my crew was just,
just following my orders.
I take, I take full responsibility
for my actions,
but they were mine,
and they were mine alone.
If I transmit Khan's location to you now,
all that I ask is that you spare them.
Please, sir.
I'll do anything you want.
Just let them live.
That's a hell of an apology,
but if it is any conciliation...
I was never going
to spare your crew.
Fire at will.
I'm sorry.
- Weapons aren't firing. - There is
a problem down here. Energy going down!
Someone in engineering just
manually reset our systems.
What do you mean,
someone! Who?
Their weapons
are powered down, sir.
Enterprise, can you hear me?
Scotty!
- Guess what I found behind Jupiter?
- You are on that ship!
I sneak on it, seems that I just committed
an act of treason against a starfleet admiral
and I really like to get off
this bloody ship. Now beam me out!
You're miracle worker, we are little low
on power right now. Just standby, standby!
What do you mean low on power?
What happened to the Enterprise?
I call you back.
Scotty!
Spock, our ship,
how is she?
Our options are limited, Captain.
We cannot fire and we can not flee.
There is one option.
Uhura, when you get Scotty
back, patch him through.
- Yes, sir.
- Mr. Spock, you have the com.
Captain, I strongly object.
To what? I haven't
said anything yet.
Since we cannot take the ship from the outside,
the only way we can take it is within.
And as large boarding
party would be detected,
it is optimum for you take
few members of crew as possible.
You will meet resistance,
requiring personal,
with advanced combat ability's
and big knowledge of that ship.
This indicates that you
planned to align with Khan,
the very man we were
sent here to destroy.
I'm not aligning with
him, I'm using him.
The enemy of my enemy
is my friend my.
An arabic proverb attributed to an prince
who was betrayed and decapitated by his own subjects.
Still, it's a hell of quote.
- I will go with you, Captain.
- No, I need you on the bridge.
I can't allow you to do this.
It's my function on this ship to advise
you making wisest decisions possible,
something I firmly believe you
are incapable doing in this moment.
You are right!
What I am about to do doesn't make
any sense. It’s not logical, it is a gut feeling.
I have no idea what I suppose to do.
I only know
what I can do.
The Enterprise and her crew needs
someone in that chair who knows what he is doing.
And it's not me.
It's you, Spock.
Tell me everything you
know about that ship.
Dreadnought class two times the size
three times the speed, advanced weaponry,
modified for minimal crew.
Unlike most Federation vessels,
it is built solely for combat.
I will do everything I can
to make you answer
for what you did.
- But right now I need your help.
- In exchange for what?
You said you would do
anything for your crew.
- I can guarantee their safety.
- Captain.
You cant even guarantee
safety of your own crew.
Bones, what are you
doing with that tribble?
Tribble's dead, I'm
injecting Khan's platelets
into the deceased
tissues of necrotic host.
Khan's cells regenerate
like nothing I ever seen.
I want to know why.
You coming with
me or not?
You want to do what?
We are coming over there, Sulu is maneuvering
the Enterprise in position as we speak.
To this ship? How?
There is a cargo door,
hanger 7, access port 101A.
You need to find a manual
override to open that airlock.
Are you crazy?
Whoever you are.
Just listen to him, Scotty.
It's going to be all right.
It is not going to be all right. You want me
to open an airlock into space
where upon I will freeze,
die, and explode?
Lieutenant, from our current position is it
possible to establish contact with the new Vulcan.
- I'll do my best.
- Thank you.
Mr. Sulu, what is
the status of the other ship?
Their systems are still off-line.
I'm aligning our ship now.
- Scotty, how are we doing over there?
- Captain, I wish I had better news.
They blocked our access
to the ship's computer.
They will have full weapons
in three minutes.
So next time I will not be able to stop
them destroying the Enterprise. Standby.
Commander, our trash chute is aimed at
access port 101A on the other ship.
- Captain the ships is aligned.
- Copy that.
- Scotty!
- I'm in the hangar, give me a minute.
I'm running, standby.
Whoa, whoa! I do not know, Captain.
This door is very vee, I mean small.
It's 4 square meters tops.
It's going to be like, jumping
out of a moving car,
off a bridge
into a shot-glass.
It's okay.
I've done it before.
Yeah, I was vertical
we jump down to a...
- It doesn't matter. Scotty! - Did you find
manual override? - The manual override, Scotty?
Not yet.
Captain, before you launch,
you should be aware,
that there is a considerable
debris field between our ships.
Spock, not now.
Scotty, are you good?
It's not easy just, give me two
seconds all-right? You mad bastard!
Tell me this going to work.
I have neither the information
nor confidence to do so, Doctor.
Okay Captain. Standby.
You are real comfort.
Come on, come on!
Yes! Okay, okay I've set
to open the door.
- You ready?
- Are you?
Spock, pull the trigger.
Yes, Captain.
Launching activation sequence on 3...
2...
1...
Sir, Kirk is heading
for a collision at 0.32.
- Captain, there is debris directly ahead.
- Copy that.
Wow, Jim you way off course.
I know, I know. I can see that.
Don't move.
Use the display compass, Captain.
You must correct precisely 37.243 degrees.
Got it! I'm working
my way back.
Scotty, are you going to be
ready with that door, right?
What are you doing here?
Little bit of maintenance
on the airlock console. You're big.
Mr. Scott, where are you?
Captain, he can't seem to hear you.
I'm working on getting his signal back. Stand by!
- Damn it!
- Captain, what is it?
My helmet was hit. Uhura, tell
me that you have Mr. Scott back.
Not yet. I'm still working
on the signal.
His communicator is working,
I don't know why he is not responding.
- What is that? - Are you starfleet
or private security?
- Show me your other hand.
- Because you look like private security.
Impending collision detected.
Khan use evasive action
there are debris directly ahead.
I see it.
Mr. Sulu did we loose Khan?
I don't know, Commander, I'm having
trouble tracking him in all this debris.
- Was Khan hit?
- We are trying to find him now.
Captain, you need to adjust your target
destination 183 by 473 degrees.
Spock, my display
is dead, I'm flying blind.
Captain, without
your display compass,
hitting your target destination
is mathematical impossible.
Spock, if I get back, we really need
to talk about your bedside manner.
Commander, he is
not going to make it.
My display is still function.
I see you Kirk. You're 200 meters
ahead of me in mine one o'clock.
Cut to your left few
degrees and follow me.
Scotty, we're getting close,
need welcome. Do you copy?
Do you copy, Scotty?
If you can hear us, Mr. Scott,
open door in 10...
- Scotty!
- 9.
- The person counting down, what is that?
- I think you hear things, mate..
7.
- Mr. Scott, where are you?
- 6.
- 1800 meters, 1600 meters.
- 5.
- Scotty, where are you?
- 3.
- You copy? Please!
- 2.
- Sorry about this. - For what?
- Mr. Scott open the door!
- Open the door!
- Mr. Scott, now!
Welcome aboard.
It's good to see you, Scotty.
Who is that?
Khan, Scotty,
Scotty, Khan.
Hello.
They know we are here.
I know the best way to bridge.
It's locked to stun.
- Theirs won't be.
- Try not get shot.
Commander, I have that
transmission as requested.
- On screen, please.
- Stand by.
Mr. Spock.
Admiral.
I'll deal with
you in moment...
I'm ashamed to
be your daughter.
Sir, we did have a hangar
door open on deck 13.
Khan.
They are going to have full
power, and we are walking?
The turbo-lift is easily tracked, and
Marcus would have us in a cage.
This path right takes us
to the engine room.
And won't be able to use their weapons here
without destabilizing the warp core.
- Which gives us the advantage. - Where
did you find this guy? - It's a long story.
I'll be brief.
In your travels, did you ever
encounter a man named Khan?
As you know, I have made a vow
to never give you information,
that could potentially
alter you destiny.
Your path is yours to walk,
and yours alone.
That being said,
Khan Noonien Singh is the
most dangerous adversary,
the Enterprise ever faced.
He is brilliant, ruthless,
and will not hesitate to kill
every single one of you.
Did you defeat him?
At great cost,
yes.
How?
I don't need to temp faith here
but where is everybody?
The ship was designed to flown with
minimal crew, one if necessary.
One?
- You all right?
- Yeah.
Where is Khan?
Lieutenant, I need you to assembly all senior, medical
and engineering staff at the weapons-bay.
All right.
Dr. McCoy, you inadvertently activated
a torpedo, could you replicate the process?
Oh, why the hell would I want to do that?
I'm not a torpedo technician.
The fact that you're doctor is precisely
why I need you to listen very carefully.
Where is he?
Shit!
This way.
The minute we get to
the bridge, drop him.
What, stunning Khan?
I think he is helping us.
I'm pretty sure
we are helping him.
- Are we coming on-line, sir.
- Re-target Enterprise, now. - Aye, sir.
Make sure he stays down.
Excuse me.
Admiral Marcus,
you are under arrest.
You are not actually
going to this, are you?
Admiral get out of the chair.
You better stop and think about
what are you doing, Kirk.
You better think about
what you did on Kronos.
You made an incursion
on an enemy planet.
You killed a Klingon patrol.
Even if you got out
without trace, war is coming!
And who's going to lead us?
You?
If I'm not in charge our entire
way of life is decimated.
So, you want me off this ship,
you better kill me.
I'm not going to kill you, sir.
But I could stun your ass
and drag you out of the chair.
But, I'd rather not do that
in front of your daughter.
- You all-right?
- Yes, Captain.
Jim!
Listen!
Wait!
You should have let me sleep.
Where's the Captain, Mr. Sulu?
Our sensor arrays are down, sir.
I can't find him.
I'm going to make this
very simple for you.
- Captain!
- Your crew for my crew.
- You betrayed us.
- You are smart, Mr. Spock.
Spock, don't...
Mr. Spock, give me my crew.
And what will you do
when you get them?
Continue the work we were doing
before we were banished.
Which as I understand it involves
the mass genocide
of any being you find
to be less than superior.
Shall I destroy you, Mr. Spock?
Or will you give me
what I want?
We have no transporter capabilities.
Fortunately, mine perfectly functional.
Drop your shields.
If I do so, I have no guarantee
that you will not destroy the Enterprise.
Well, let's play this
out logically then, Mr. Spock.
Firstly, I will kill your Captain
to demonstrate my resolve,
and then if yours holds,
I'll will have no choice,
but to kill you and
your entire crew.
If you destroy our ship,
you will also destroy your own people.
Your crew requires oxygen
to survive. Mine does not.
I will target your life support
systems located behind the arcne cell.
And after every single person
on-board your ship suffocates,
I will walk over your cold
corpses to recover my people.
Now...
shall we begin?
Lower shields.
A wise choice, Mr. Spock.
I see, all the 72 torpedoes
are still in their tubes.
If they are not mine,
Commander I will know it.
Vulcan's do not lie.
The torpedoes are yours.
Thank you, Mr. Spock.
I have fulfilled your terms.
Now, full-fill mine.
Well, Kirk.
It seems right
to return to your crew.
After all...
no, ship should go down
without her Captain.
He has locking phasers on us, sir.
Get us out here, now!
Shields at 6%.
- The torpedoes, how much time,
Lieutenant? - 12 seconds, sir.
The crew of the Enterprise, prepare
for immediate proximity detonation.
What are he talking about?
What detonation?
He just armed
the damn torpedoes.
No!
Sir, the weapons
have been knocked out.
- Not bad, Commander.
- Thank you, Lieutenant.
- Bones!
- Bones, nurse!
- Good to see you, Jim. - You helped
Spock detonate those torpedoes?
- Damn right I did.
- He killed Khan's crew.
Spock is cold, but he not that cold...
I've got Khan's crew.
72 human popsicles.
Safe and sound
in their Cryo-tubes.
Son of a bitch!
Sir, the central power grid is failing.
- Switch to auxiliary power.
- Auxiliary power failing, sir.
Commander, our ship is
caught in Earth's gravity.
- Can we stop?
- I can't do anything.
Clear the area!
Engage emergency lock-down!
- I hope you don't get seasick.
- Do you? - Yeah.
- Lieutenant, sound evacuation to all decks.
- Aye, sir.
As active Captain I order
you to abandon this ship.
I will remain behind
and devote all power
to life support and
evacuation shuttle bays.
Evacuation to all crew!
I order you to abandon this ship!
All due respect, Commander,
but we are not going anywhere.
One day I've been off this ship.
One bloody day!
Gravity systems are
failing. Hold on! Hold on!
There will be no time for evacuation
if don't get power to stabilize the damn ship.
- Can we restore it?
- Only from engineering.
We have to get back
to the warp core.
Jim.
Scotty, we must get
the power back on. Come on!
- We got to jump! - What?
- Jump! Jump!
Oh, God!
Emergency power
at 15% and dropping.
- Jim.
- Hold on!
I can't.
I got you, Captain.
- Chekov.
- Don't let go.
Even if we get the warp core on-line
we still need to re-direct the power.
- He's right, Captain.
- What are you talking about?
Someone have to hit
the manual override.
- Lad there is a switch.
- Behind the deflect dish.
- I bridge the switch.
- Let's go.
Oh, no!
Mr. Sulu, divert every remaining
power to the stabilizers.
I do what I can, sir.
I do what I can.
Core misaligned.
- Danger.
- Oh, no! No, no, no!
- Core misaligned.
- Housings are miss-aligned.
There's no way we
can re-direct the power.
The ship is dead, sir.
She's gone.
Danger.
- No, she's not.
- Wait, Jim.
If we go in there, will...
Will you listen to me?
What the hell are you doing?
- I'm opening the door. I'm going in.
- That door is stop us to get irradiated.
We will be dead before
we made the climb.
You are not
making the climb.
If we don't get power and shields back on-line
we going to be incinerate at re-entry.
- Warp core is back on-line.
- Maximum thrusters, Mr. Sulu.
Standby, standby.
- Shields restored.
- Commander, power on-line.
Mr. Spock, altitude stabilizing.
It's a miracle.
There are no such things.
Engineering to bridge, Mr. Spock.
- Mr. Scott.
- Sir, you better get down here.
You better hurry.
- Open it! - The decontamination
process is not complete.
You will flood the whole compartment.
The door is locked, sir.
How's the ship?
Out of danger.
You saved the crew.
You used what he
wanted against him.
That's a nice move.
It is what you would have done.
And this, this is what
you would have done.
It was only logical.
I'm scared, Spock.
Help me to not to.
How do you choose not to feel.
I do not know.
Right now I'm failing.
I want you to know
why I couldn't let you die...
Why I went back for you.
Because you're my friend.
Khan!
That was close.
Set destination
starfleet headquarters!
Engines compromised.
Cannot guarantee destination.
Confirm order.
Confirmed.
Search the enemy
ship for signs of life.
Sir, there is no way
anyone survives.
- He could.
- Yes, sir.
Wow, he just jumped 30 meters.
- Can we beam him up? - There is too much
damage. I have no incoming signal.
But it maybe possible
to beam you down, sir.
Go get him.
- Standby for coordinates.
- Yes, sir.
- Enter 3517 by 2598.
- Coordinates confirmed.
Get me a Cryo-tube, now!
Get this men out of Cryo!
Keep him in an induced coma!
We are going to put Kirk inside.
- It's our only chance to preserve his brain
function. - How much Khan's blood is left?
None.
Enterprise to Spock.
Spock!
Activate the cryogenic sequence.
McCoy to bridge.
I can't reach Spock.
I need Khan alive, you get that son of
the bitch on-board, right now!
I think he can save Kirk.
- Can we beam them up to the ship? - As they
keep moving, I cant get lock on either of them.
Can you beam someone down?
Spock! Stop!
Stop! He is our only
chance to safe Kirk.
What is it?
Who are you?
- This coming to... - Your father was Captain,
only for 16 minutes and he saved his crew...lives.
***
Don't be so melodramatic,
you were barely dead.
It was the transfusion
that really took it's toll.
- You were out cold for two weeks.
- Transfusion?
Your cells were heavily irradiated.
We had no choice.
Khan?
Once we caught him, I synthesized
serum from his super blood.
Tell me, are you feeling homicidal
power-man, despotic?
No more than usual.
- How did you get him?
- I didn't.
You saved my life.
Uhura and I has something
to do with it too, you know?
- You saved my life, Captain and
life of many on the ship... - Spock, just...
Thank you.
You are welcome, Jim.
There will always be those
who mean to do us harm.
To stop them, we risk wakening
the same evil within ourselves.
Our first instinct
is to seek revenge,
when those we love
are taken from us.
But that's not who we are.
We are here today
to rechrist an USS Enterprise.
And to honor those who
lost their life, nearly one year ago.
When Christopher Pike first gave me his ship
he had me recite the Captains oath.
Words I didn't appreciate at that time.
Now I see them as a call
for us to remember...
who we once were...
And who we must be again.
And those words...
Space, the final frontier.
These are the voyages
of the starship Enterprise.
Her five year mission,
to explore strange new worlds...
to seek out new life
and new civilizations...
To boldly go where no one
has gone before.
Captain on the bridge.
It's hard to get out of it
once you got a taste.
Isn't that right, Mr. Sulu?
Captain does have
nice ring to it.
Chair is all yours, sir.
Mr. Scott, how's our core?
Purring like a kitten, Captain.
She's ready for a long journey.
Excellent. Come on, Bones,
it's going to be fun.
Five years in space,
God help me!
Doctor Marcus.
- I'm glad you could be part of the family.
- It's nice to have a family.
- Spock.
- Captain.
Where should we go?
As a mission of this duration
has never been attempted...
I prefer to your good
judgement, Captain.
Mr. Sulu, take us out.
Aye, Captain.
-Subs  by the 24hpie-
Corrected and synced by: Szaki