ANNOUNCER: It's an honor to announce
this year's Blossom Queen winner.
The most important crown
that any girl can ever wear.
Dylan Schoenfield.
[CROWD CHEERING
AND APPLAUDING]
[CAMERAS CLICKING]
GUTHRIE: Dylan.
[MOUTHING] Thanks.
GUTHRIE:
Dylan.
- Dylan!
- Yes, Principal Guthrie?
The Blossom Queen
campaign application.
- Oh.
GUTHRIE: I need your signature.
[BELL RINGING]
Oh, thanks.
Ahem. Next.
This year's going to
be très fantastiquè.
- Know why?
LOLA & HANNAH [IN UNISON]: Why?
Because once
I'm crowned Blossom Queen,
I will be the most popular girl
at Woodlands Academy ever.
[GIGGLING]
GIRL:
Class is downstairs.
Drama Club.
Easy votes, they like my dramatic flair.
Oh, the very shirt
I introduced last semester.
Followers. Easy votes.
Film Club nerds.
- You're like a movie star to them.
- Totes.
Indie rock wannabes.
What's with the guitars, people?
This isn't a campfire.
I can't believe you used
to be friends with Amy Loubalu.
DYLAN:
Alas, it's true.
Until I traded up to you two.
Dylan.
I took your suggestion
and got my hair cut into a bob.
Definitely cuted up.
See? People know I care.
Easy vote.
But what about Nicole Paterson?
She's major competition.
Lola and Hannah see me
as their leader
and a leader
should never show weakness.
That would be très mauvais.
That's French for "ew."
[SIGHS]
What and ever.
A good candidate likes competish.
If I ran for Blossom Queen unopposed
and won, boring.
And who has the number one seat
on The Ramp?
[SPEAKS FRENCH]
BOY:
Dude, hey.
Oh, look, Asher's holding it for me.
Oh. So sweet.
[ALL GASPING]
Oh, my.
Oh!
You... You geek!
This is designer!
No, it's tuna noodle casserole.
You are so gross.
Gross is just one syllable.
I can't believe that popular people like me
are forced
to share the same air
as nerd herders like you.
What?
Forced to share the same air as me?
Okay, you wear so much perfume,
you need a gas mask just to survive.
Watch.
[SPEAKING IN REVERSE]
Is this yesterday's fettuccine Alfredo
- recycled?
- No paparazzi.
Oh.
So sweet.
Oh, my. Oh!
You... You geek!
This is designer!
No, it's tuna noodle casserole.
You are so gross.
Gross is just one syllable.
Oh!
That's classic.
- Look what you did to my friends.
- But I didn't...
I can't believe that popular people like me
are forced
to share the same air
as nerd herders like you.
- Ugh!
- I prefer the term "film geek."
Ugh!
They must practice that.
Casablanca. Curtiz is the director.
It also stars Ingrid Bergman, Peter Lorre
and Claude Rains.
As Bogart's best film? I fully disagree.
The African Queen with Katharine
Hepburn, directed by John Huston.
I mean, it's miraculous.
I mean, it's unbelievable. Hi.
Oh, look. Film Club president
finally decided to show up.
Sorry, guys.
I got stuck in traffic on the diva freeway.
- Where's your lunch?
- Dylan Schoenfield's wearing it.
Yeah, my food went where no mere mortal
has ever gone before.
The Ramp.
You need a passport to go in there.
Passport? You need a robot army.
With level 83 "Dragon Slayer" skills.
Okay, guys, seriously,
it's a whole other alien world.
A mystery species.
We'll never fully understand the Populars
and the way their strange vortex works.
[ALL SHOUT]
Okay, what are you inventing now?
Artificial Intelligence chess.
Hey, Amy.
That's a cool guitar case.
Never gonna happen, friend.
Thanks for the support, pal.
Calculate this, Josh.
You've been crushing on Amy Loubalu
since third grade.
We're juniors.
That's approximately 2,268 school days,
minus summer breaks,
that you could have asked her out
and haven't.
I'd go out with you.
Guys, I don't have time for dating,
okay?
The Puget Sound Film Festival
is only six weeks away.
And he's our school's best shot at total
domination of the city's student film scene.
- You better win.
- No. I gotta win.
Okay, first prize is a summer
at a Hollywood film camp in Los Angeles.
All right, I wanna make
this groundbreaking documentary
that truly changes the bar.
- You know, a film that establishes me
[MOUTHING] I love you.
As the next cinematic genius.
So, what's the documentary about?
No idea.
You have no idea.
So wanna go out with me?
[ALL YELLING]
- What...?
- No.
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
FARLEY:
Come in.
Mr. F.?
FARLEY:
Oh, Josh.
Brought my application.
My favorite student and great, great.
I like this.
I can't wait to see what my star student
has come up with, huh?
It's a documentary about the evolution
of robot voices
in the science-fiction genre?
Yeah. You know how no two robots
ever sound the same in any sci-fi movie?
You know, you have your,
"I am a robot."
Then you have these futuristic, like:
[BEEPING]
Josh, your artistic vision
is robot voices?
Yeah. Mr. F., I'm struggling here.
I... I've got all these great ideas,
but none of them are good enough.
You really would like to win that trip
to Hollywood film camp, huh?
More than anything.
Then challenge yourself, Josh.
Choose a documentary subject matter
where you stretch your limits.
Explore new territory, discover the truth.
How about, instead of robots,
a human subject?
A human.
Okay, so challenging, truthful,
but human.
- Got it.
- Right.
Now, I will need a real proposal
by tomorrow.
Otherwise, I will have to give
our school's slot to another student.
Okay.
ALAN: No, I am not taking a dollar less
than listing price.
Well, that's great.
I can have the paperwork sent right over.
Great. Talk to you soon.
Well, sweetie, what do you think?
Do we turn this place
into a Sparkles Cupcakes
or Accessories Barn?
Dad, anyone who buys their accessories
in a barn is totes tragique.
I vote for cupcakes,
gives it more of a glam factor.
And that is why you're my top advisor.
[PHONE BEEPS]
You know what? I am gonna have to head
back to the office for a late meeting.
Whatevs.
Oh, I need to borrow your marketing team.
Marketing team? Why?
Blossom Queen. It's essential.
I need signs, brochures, headshots.
Oh, well, absolutely not.
But Nicole Paterson
has the whole varsity
and JV football team
making posters for her campaign.
Yes, and you have ingenuity.
If you wanna win,
you need to do this on your own.
You're a smart girl.
Gotta pull yourself up
by your bootstraps.
[CELL PHONE RINGING]
Yes, this is Alan.
Bootstraps?
What does that even mean?
Um, hello, boots have zippers.
I should know, I tried on 17 pairs
at Shoes Unlimited last week
and none of the 16 pairs I bought
had straps.
Bad reception?
BOY:
Yeah, I, well...
Dude, seriously, this is not refundable.
Tell you what, here's 20 percent off
on your next phone.
Thanks.
It's imported leather.
Imported from where?
Somewhere foreign
with lots of shipping costs, duh?
Yeah, probably Italy, duh?
[BEE BUZZING]
Bee?
Bee. Oh, my gosh, a bee.
Bee. Bee. Oh!
[DYLAN SCREAMING]
DYLAN:
Oh, no. Oh, my God.
Stop. Oh, my gosh.
Oh, my.
[SCREAMS]
DYLAN:
Oh! Oh, no. Oh, my gosh.
My purse.
Help. Somebody help.
Someone turn the fountain off.
Chop-chop.
Help. Help me, my purse. Ah!
It's a Serge Sanchez.
Will somebody help me?
Someone turn the fountain off.
Mr. Farley said that my movie subject
should be human.
Dylan Schoenfield's human.
Sort of.
She's definitely a challenge.
Big challenge.
Someone turn off the fountain, now.
Why aren't they listening to me?
Give me your phone.
- Who are you calling?
- 911.
It's that geek from lunch today.
He's saving your purse.
What?
Wait. Wait, wait, wait.
Really?
[SQUEALS]
Oh.
[SQUEALING]
Ugh!
[SQUEALS]
Ew!
JOSH: What?
- Go, Woodlands.
Vote Paterson.
Imported leather
needs specialty cleaning.
When my cell phone got wet, I...
My Serge Sanchez.
You named your purse?
Not so fast.
I have a proposal for you.
Whatever it is, the answer is NO,
spells no way.
Can I at least propose
the proposal first?
[GROANS]
I want you to star in my movie
for the film festival.
Oh, what? Star?
Uh, what's it...? What's it about?
You. Your life.
You know, what it's like to be popular
and run for Blossom Queen?
Nicole Paterson might have buttons
and posters,
but what's that compared to a movie?
Especially if it's about me.
Deal.
Once you lose this.
The competition just got serious.
It's always been serious for me.
Thad?
[DYLAN CLEARS THROAT]
Tomorrow. Lunch. The dining hall.
We can start filming my movie then.
Actually, it's my movie.
Where are my shoes?
You need some major CPR, Serge.
Marta.
I need help carrying.
Marta?
"Dylan, went to dentist,
dinner's in the fridge.
Love, Marta."
You'll be as good as new, Serge.
[TENDER ROCK MUSIC PLAYING]
[COMPUTER BEEPING]
"Amy posted a picture of Dylan."
What?
Why'd she do that?
My mom took that photo when Amy and I
won the second grade science fair,
back when we were besties.
Mom died later that same year.
Sometimes I like
to look through her old stuff.
Makes me feel like I'm still with her.
[CAR ENGINE REVVING]
[DOOR CREAKS]
SANDY:
Josh, is that you?
No, Mom, it's a burglar who just happens
to have keys to the front door.
[GROANS]
Hey, Mouse.
Who'd you bark at today, buddy?
Who'd you bark at today?
Oh, yes, you're a good boy.
Let's go. Come on. Come on.
Come on. Look at me. Come on.
Come on.
[SPEAKING JAPANESE]
Same to you, I think.
Hey, guess what?
I found my new documentary subject.
Dylan Schoenfield.
- Oh, that is wonderful, hon.
- Yeah.
- Who is he?
- She, Mom.
- Oh.
- One of the most popular girls at school.
I was gonna follow her around,
shoot her Blossom Queen campaign.
I'm thinking a hard-hitting exposè
on popularity.
Huh. Well, that sounds like
an ambitious project.
Yeah. Speaking of projects, Mom,
what is that?
Sushi-making class.
I am making a spicy dragon roll.
Great.
There we go. That's that.
[WATER BOILING]
Oh, no, my miso.
[SANDY YELLING]
Hey, Mom, you just wanna phone in
for pizza instead?
Oh, yes.
So much better.
No. No, no, no. Give me...
Go and get him.
Hey. Paul, it's Sandy.
Oh, I like this, huh?
An exposé on popularity.
Yeah. You told me to challenge myself
and Dylan Schoenfield's proving
to be a big challenge.
Don't forget what else I said.
- Seek out the truth, huh?
- Right.
The best documentarians leave
their preconceived notions at the door.
Uh...
Totally, Mr. F., yeah.
Dylan Schoenfield, huh?
Popularity could turn out
to be more complicated than you think.
Welcome to the competition, Josh.
Next stop: Hollywood, huh?
- Yeah.
- Little bit of the action.
GIRL:
I'll see you there.
Hey. You ready to start?
- Almost. Hold this.
- Mm.
First, some ground rules.
One, we need
to set a strict filming schedule.
No hanging around me before or after.
Sure. Like I'd want to.
Two, I need a beauty budget.
So $50 a week should suffice.
Beauty budget?
I only get $5 a day for lunch.
Three, no filming from my left side.
Ever.
It's my bad side, see?
They're exactly the sa...
Are you always this high-maintenance?
It is not high-maintenance
to want to look nice.
Voila, now I'm done.
Hey, don't you want this?
Oh, you can just set it down at my seat.
- The Ramp?
- Duh, where else would we eat lunch?
[GASPS]
Dylan?
We're shooting a movie.
Excuse me.
One small step for geeks.
One giant leap for geek-kind.
Not now.
JOSH: Why so determined
to be Blossom Queen?
Because it's the best way
to ensure lifelong popularity.
Aren't you already popular?
Let me ask you this,
does Sunshine Lemonade advertise?
Yeah, they have the commercials
with the waterskiing penguins.
LOLA:
Oh, I like the penguins.
Sunshine is already number one.
They don't need to advertise.
But they do it to stay number one.
Get it?
- Got it.
- Good.
Everyone thinks
it's so easy being the popular girl.
- It's so not easy.
- Girls, this is moi's movie.
- If they wanna add something, that's fin...
- But being popular is so not easy.
It's like royalty.
Or being the first lady.
You have to live up
to impossible standards of beauty
and you're expected
to be a good influence.
Like I help out the less fortunate.
Oh, you have a charity.
Absolument, fashion victims.
[SPEAKS FRENCH]
Hannah, the yellow scarf you're wearing
is washing you out.
Here.
Wear mine instead.
See?
I just sacrificed my own outfit for hers.
But it was worth it.
Oh!
Josh.
Sorry.
Oh!
Hey.
If you're a ten, you can only date a ten,
like Asher.
- Coming to watch me play volleyball?
- Mm-hm.
Dylan, he's blocking your light.
Why is there a talking nerd here?
Asher, we downloaded this.
Josh is making a movie
about me winning Blossom Queen.
Play nice?
Does it mess with my volleyball sched?
Oh, never. We'll work around it.
Got it. Thank you.
So this is what you do after school?
Shopping improves the economy.
Oh, how thoughtful.
I know, right? I care.
Right. So in a scientific sense,
how does popularity work?
Are the other Blossom Queen
candidates...?
DYLAN:
There are levels of popularity.
Anywhere from
student-council-president popular
to only popular with your parents.
Sure, Nicole's cheerleader popular,
but is she Blossom Queen popular?
Doubtful.
So how does one move up
this social scale of popularity?
Well, one way
is hoping it'll rub off on you.
Popularity's contagious.
What? Like a cold?
Duh.
It's why Hannah and Lola battle
to be my better friend.
Their popularity comes from mine.
- Six-point-five percent sales tax on 395...
- Um...
Twenty-five sixty-seven.
Hate it, have it, have it, have it, have it,
hate it, I'll try some on just for fun.
How many shoes do you need?
One pair for each day of the year.
Why, how many do you own?
You're looking at them.
Clearly. Totes tragique.
JOSH:
So how long's this gonna take?
No filming in here.
Hey, here's your chance
to tell me something about Dylan.
Oh. Like what?
Like does your popularity really come
from hers?
We may not be as popular as Dylan,
but we do know some stuff.
Like, when Dylan doesn't get her way,
she goes full-on DQM.
Drama queen mode.
And Asher only dates Dylan
because she worships him.
And Asher loves being worshipped.
Ta-da!
So, what do we think?
[BOTH SPEAKING IN FRENCH]
Guys, French is my trademark, duh?
JOSH:
So Populars only hang with Populars?
Cats don't hang with dogs, right?
Really?
That's your argument?
It's better this way.
If everyone stays with their own group,
there's no chance for misunderstandings.
Like, what kind of misunderstandings?
Take you and me, for instance.
If we mingled outside
of doing my movie together,
you might get the wrong idea
and ask me out.
Imagine the horror.
- You'd be so embarrassed.
- Ahem.
- Did we get it?
- Yep.
We got it.
Ow!
- What are your plans after school?
- Uh, Pilates.
But not on Tuesdays, that's yoga.
After you graduate.
Hopes? Dreams?
What's your life goal?
Blossom Queen.
- After that.
- After?
If I don't win Blossom Queen, my
life is officially O-V-E-R, over.
Oh, you missed a spot.
I have no words. Nothing.
Josh?
[SIGHS]
Snack break? It's satay.
It's from my Thai cooking class.
Uh...
It's not good.
How's the big movie coming?
DYLAN:
Josh.
Get my shoes. My feet are cold.
Well, she's...
- Well, I don't...
DYLAN: Josh.
- Diva?
- Yeah.
Yeah. You know, I wanna make this true
documentary about high school popularity,
but, Mom, this is a joke.
Well, I mean, sometimes people behave
a certain way
because they have something else
going on.
What's the real Dylan like?
Real, Mom?
Okay, the only real thing
about Dylan Schoenfield
is that she's really annoying.
You have to give her
the benefit of the doubt.
- Mom.
- You have to be an archeologist.
Dig deeper.
[CROWD CHATTERING]
ALL:
Oh!
This is going to look fantastic.
I can't believe we were invited
to a beach party with the Populars.
It's strictly work, okay?
Heh. Nice bonnet.
Sun is evil.
Well, I, for one, plan to have fun.
JOSH:
Hey.
Oh, finally.
I see you brought your non-tourage.
This is Ari, my second AD.
He's in charge of all the B-roll.
Whatever all that means.
Okay, well, you know, I'm going
to take some, uh, additional shots.
Sorry we were late,
I had to get directions.
Directions? You've never been
to the beach? Everybody likes the beach.
Not me.
Shocker, not everyone's
into the same things you are.
I find that hard to believe.
Heh.
Come on.
Okay.
[CROWD CHEERING]
ASHER:
Come on, Eagles. Let's go.
Next time, baby. It's okay.
We're still two points behind.
ASHER:
Go, guys, come on.
- Water, babe?
- Yeah.
Excuse me.
Hi. Despite our northern latitude,
the sun still emits dangerous UV rays.
It's like sitting in a fryer at Burger
World without the side of onion rings.
SPF 80?
Oh, yeah.
Come here.
[BOY LAUGHING]
[THUDS]
Hey, Amy.
Nice, uh, stick thing.
Thanks. It's called a Gator Grabber.
Gator? Like alligator. Whoa.
- Ha, ha.
- That's weird.
- Saving the environment?
- Yeah.
Yeah. Go green.
Hey, doing okay.
Amy and I
had our first real conversation.
Should be called a Croc Catcher
because crocodiles
actually do eat garbage.
- Oh.
- Yeah.
AMY:
Josh.
Josh? Josh?
Josh,
enough with the unscheduled break.
It's time to get back to work.
AMY:
Hi to you too, Dylan.
How are you these days?
I'd be better if strangers didn't tag me
in ancient pics online.
- Come on, Josh.
AMY: Strangers?
Gee, as I recall it,
we used to be friends.
Josh, come on, let's go.
Chop-chop, time is money.
Bye, Amy.
Bye, Josh.
Oh, I so saved you back there.
You should have been focused
on filming me, instead of flirting.
Flirting?
I wasn't... I wa... No, no, no.
I don't flirt.
Oh, clearly. It was totes tragique.
It's more obvious
that you like Amy Loubalu
than Nicole Paterson's hair extensions.
Yeah. I mean, no.
Wait.
You two used to be friends?
Ugh. I know, hard to believe.
Back in elementary school.
Are you getting my good side, right?
Over here.
JOSH:
Yeah, yeah, yeah, I'm getting it.
So, what happened?
Look at her and look at me.
Life happened, I.e. I'm popular.
Amy's popular.
We've gone over this, Josh.
She's "I'm in a girl band" popular.
Not Blossom Queen popular.
[CROWD CHEERING]
Oh, no, the volleyball game's over.
Asher.
Ash.
- Hey, where are you guys going?
- The movies. It's dark.
And no one steals our snacks.
Victory means Pizza Land.
Two large Meat Volcanoes,
triple cheese. You ready, Dyl?
Oh, well, Marta made me a pizza
last night,
so I called ahead
and got us all reservations
to the new sushi place downtown.
Raw fish?
Ralph.
Have fun with that.
- I'm outtie with my boys.
BOY: Yeah.
Yeah.
I don't like fish either.
I could eat pizza every day. Heh.
DYLAN:
Wait.
Wait, wait, no, no, no.
Call 911. Call 911.
Someone's stealing my car.
What are you doing? Stop, what is this?
Six unpaid parking tickets.
Oops.
- Seven.
- Ugh.
When? You mean those little flyer thingies
on my windshield?
- They ain't greeting cards, lady.
- Oh, no.
Please?
Oh...
You surely have a car, right?
Yeah.
This is yours?
And it runs? On real gas?
So she's a little old.
Old? This thing is, like, prehistoric.
You know, somewhere a caveman
is missing his car.
Hello?
Thank you.
[ENGINE STRUGGLES]
Why are you hiding?
DYLAN:
It's called shame.
Well, they're gone now.
[SIGHS]
[MAN SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY
ON RADIO]
Okay, turning on the radio
isn't gonna help our battery situation.
News? Gross.
What, the news bores you?
Ever heard of pop music?
We're young, live a little.
[DANCE MUSIC PLAYS
ON CAR RADIO]
[HISSING]
- Uh-oh.
- What "oh"?
What's that?
Josh, that never happens to my car.
What is that? That's smoke.
How are you gonna fix it?
[JOSH COUGHING]
We're gonna need to find a gas station.
- We?
- Fine.
Stay here.
[SCOFFS]
There is no way I am risking
being seen hanging out in this thing.
Josh.
Ugh. Stupid phone.
Who are you so busy texting?
The girls.
Telling them that this is the W-O-R-S-T,
worst day of my life.
Yeah? Ditto.
Ow! Oh! Ow, ow, ow.
My ankle. I think it's broken.
You probably just twisted it.
Well, I can't walk, it could swell up.
You know, this is all your fault.
If you didn't have a junker car,
this never would've happened.
Sorry we don't all have nice BMW's.
Which you'd be driving right now
if you weren't such a diva.
- What did you call me?
- Nothing.
You said something. I heard.
- Fine.
- Ow.
Diva. I called you a diva.
Precious cargo here, buddy. And don't
ever call me that word ever again.
What? Diva? D-I-V-A, what's that spell?
Oh, that's right, diva.
Diva? I'm a movie star.
You said so yourself.
No, what you are is a selfish whiner.
I'm talented. Take that back or I'll...
- Or what?
- I'll fire you from my movie.
It's my movie. I'm the director.
If anyone's fired, it's you, you diva.
- Ew. You're fired.
- No, you're fired.
Wait. Where are you going?
I always get the last word.
Nope, not today.
But how am I gonna get home?
Uh, there's this thing called the bus.
Enjoy the ride.
Bus?
I got rid of the drama queen.
I'm sure it's not too late
to change documentary subjects.
Right?
I'm afraid it's too late for you
to change your documentary subject.
- You'll never get a new film done in time.
- Yeah.
You're not a quitter, Josh.
What happened?
It's Dylan Schoenfield, all right?
She's too much of a challenge.
Sometimes the truth isn't easy.
It's a shame to think Woodlands
won't even have an official entry
in the film festival this year.
Now, will it?
Okay, you can do this.
- Knock them dead.
- Thanks.
Thank you. Thank you, everybody,
and hello, fellow Woodlanders.
Dylan Schoenfield here,
like you don't know.
Anyway,
vote for me for Blossom Queen
because this school deserves to be ruled
by something sweet.
Whoo! Who wants candy?
Everybody loves chocolate, right?
It's sweet and it's me.
Everyone gets their turn.
Hi, everyone, it's me, Nicole Paterson,
your next Blossom Queen.
[GIGGLES]
[CROWD CHEERING]
Ready, okay.
N stands for nice.
I stands for integrity.
C stands for cool.
O stands for original.
L stands for loyal.
And E stands
for extremely delicious cupcakes.
[BOYS WHOOPING]
Go, Woodlands.
[CROWD CHEERING]
Vote Paterson. Ha-ha-ha.
Whoo! Cupcakes for everyone.
NICOLE:
Come get your cupcakes.
Oh, no, she did not.
Oh, yes, she did.
- Can we get a cupcake too?
NICOLE: Oh, vote for Paterson.
Vote for Paterson.
Dylan.
Ian Green complimented my new haircut
and then he asked me to spring formal.
Awesome, right?
Oh, Olivia, that's great.
So I can count on your vote?
Uh...
[MUMBLING]
What and ever, Dyl.
Cupcakes are lame.
You have a movie
being made about you.
Yeah, you're gonna be a star.
Yeah, like Nicole Paterson
can compete with that?
TEACHER: The soldiers of ancient Greece
fought in a phalanx.
Latin for finger.
A phalanx
is a rectangular mass military formation,
usually composed entirely
of heavy infantry.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, we get it.
The Spartan hoplites combined
with the narrow space of Thermopylae
made for
a seriously not-glamorous battle.
But I've got my own battles.
I'll never win Blossom Queen
without my movie.
TEACHER:
The persuasive qualities of the phalanx
were its relative simplicity and low cost,
as well as being a source
of political influence.
As well, sometimes when the phalanxes
were pushed at top speed,
they would ram.
Thus we learn
the term Greece Lightning.
Heh.
Bela Lugosi, Frank Langella,
Gary Oldman, Christopher Walken...
Christopher Walken. He played the
Headless Horseman in Sleepy Hollow.
- He would never be Dracula.
- Christopher Walken.
You know, I'm gonna suck your blood.
Gonna do it. Gonna bite your neck,
it's gonna hurt. Put a Band-Aid on.
Just don't stab me in the heart,
it's rude. Blah. Blah, blah...
Steven.
I'm with them.
Hey, can I cutsies in line with you?
What are you doing here?
I'm here to see Flight
of the Navigator.
Duh.
Wait, you're into sci-fi?
Who doesn't like science?
And fiction? Together?
Wow, it's like skinny jeans
and ballet flats. Heh.
Speaking of, I'm liking the new look.
Oh, move up.
Thanks.
Um, what's Dylan doing here?
I'm supposed to be the only girl.
The Film Society has an open policy.
Right?
Right. It's in our bylaws.
You know, we don't wanna
be exclusionary, like the Populars.
So, what are we talking about?
Not you. I mean...
The movie. What else?
I question the notion
that the protagonist didn't age.
There is no plot if he did grow older.
It's called a movie.
They didn't explain
that in the exposition, did they?
- Where's your suspension of disbelief?
- You know...
You wanna halfsies, Caitlin?
Anything to add, Dylan?
It's called time dilation, people.
As Einstein theorized
in the twin paradox,
the passage of time
is linked to the speed of the observer,
that traveling to and from the planet
Phaelon 250 times the speed of light
would virtually suspend aging, duh?
So I've discovered
that there is such a thing as a bus.
I've been taking it everywhere lately,
it's green.
Okay, so my dad grounded
the Dylish-mobile
until I can pay off my parking tickets.
It's all good, I'm parked down here.
So, what's with the secret smarts?
Exactly. They're secret.
Now, let's keep it that way.
Yeah, heaven forbid anyone thought
you had a brain
in that pretty little head of yours.
Only nerds get A's.
You think I'm pretty?
Sure. Doesn't everyone?
[SPEAKS IN FRENCH]
Okay, so look, I was thinking
I could nicely un-fire you from my movie.
Really? You mean,
I could nicely re-hire you for my movie?
Word on the street is that you had
to drop out of the film festival
because you don't have a film anymore.
I'm guessing you wanna win that just
as bad as I wanna win Blossom Queen?
Fair enough. But under one condition.
No more diva.
What? I was never a diva.
Bus stop is that way.
Fine. Deal,
part two.
Deal, part two.
So is your car gonna start
this time or...?
The fun is in the mystery.
Come on.
DYLAN:
Okay.
Home sweet...
Wow.
It's big.
Real inviting, right?
Is your dad at work?
Yeah.
Where's your mom?
She passed away.
I was 8.
I had no...
- I'm sorry.
- It's okay.
So you wanna come in? Hang for a bit?
Sure.
Okay, so, what does your dad do?
Oh, he owns a bunch of real estate
around town.
So he's either always working
or hanging with his girlfriend.
Yeah. My dad lives in San Diego.
Guess we both only have one parent.
Come on,
I wanna show you something.
What I'm about to share with you
is a highly top-secret recipe.
The everything-but-the-kitchen-sink
sundae.
Yeah, I've never heard of that before.
Duh, what do you think "top secret"
means?
And that secret is you find every sugary,
gooey substance
you could possibly find in the kitchen
and mix it all together.
What are we waiting for?
Welcome to the
everything-but-the-kitchen-sink sundae.
You wanna get your ice cream in there.
You want a variety of ice cream.
You think that's enough ice cream?
Gummy bears.
I love gummy bears.
You want a gummy bear?
Sprinkles.
Ooh.
Worms.
Gross.
Ooh.
Gummy bears
and chocolate chips together?
What you gonna do?
What you gonna do about it?
What you gonna do about that?
Oh-ho-ho.
Dylish.
So, what's the 411 on your Amy crush?
Although I don't know
why you're crushing on her.
Where's the peanut butter?
You know,
I didn't even think that nerds dated.
Geeks.
Okay, and we are people too, Dylan.
Since we're talking
about personal 411s,
what's with you and Asher?
- What about us?
- Well, he's kind of an idiot.
Gee, I don't remember asking you
your opinion.
Hey, you started it.
Talking about me and my "love life."
Exactly. "Love life" implies you're dating,
which you are not.
I know what my movie needs.
A makeover.
No, please, no more shopping footage.
Not for me, for you.
Here, I can get some before footage
of my work.
I'm not one
of your fashion victim charities.
Okay, Dyl? I like the way I am.
You would.
More whipped cream?
Snoop much?
Is this your mom?
[SIGHS]
Yeah. She met my dad
at the Woodlands Spring Formal.
Crazy, huh?
Wait. Was your mom Blossom Queen?
Back in the olden days.
1985.
Wow.
I bet you miss her.
Lots.
This house gets kind of lonely
with just me and my dad.
So when you said there's nothing more
to life than winning Blossom Queen...
[SIGHS]
Yeah, because of my mom.
If I win, it's like we're still connected.
Like she's still with me.
You know what, I'll do it.
I'll do the makeover.
- Really?
- Yeah.
[SQUEALS]
Let's start with this.
I'm getting so excited.
[UPBEAT ROCK MUSIC PLAYING]
[SPEAKING IN FRENCH]
Knees higher. Chin up.
Make sure your elbows move
with the rope.
That's pretty good.
Okay, let's go, let's go, come on.
I'm not used to sweating.
Yeah, it shows,
but girls like a sporty guy.
I don't think jump roping
is my thing. Ugh.
Up. Up.
Oh, Serge Sanchez's new cologne,
Man Power.
Man Power?
[CHANTING]
Turn him around, I wanna see the front.
[SPEAKING IN FRENCH]
Hey, turn it off,
I'm the only documentarian here.
Now show him.
Ridiculous.
Wait, is that a compliment?
Josh, upload on the lingo already?
- Thank you, it looks fantastic.
- Mm-hm.
Now, go see the finished look.
Oh, wait.
See? It's not so high-maintenance
to wanna look nice.
And now, for the finishing touch.
What?
A second pair of shoes,
since I ruined the first. Heh.
Really?
Awesome. Thank you, Dylan.
We'll tell my dad it's beauty budget
for the movie.
[CELL PHONE RINGING]
My mom.
She wants me to pick up naan bread
on my way home.
I love Indian food.
I have to go to dinner with my dad
and his stupid girlfriend.
Thanks.
Well, you can come over if you want.
Oh, no, you don't have to.
I know, but you're welcome to.
Okay, what's the hold up?
Thank you.
- After you.
- Oh, thank you.
So, this is it, home, sweet home.
Hey, you get to meet Mouse today.
Who's Mouse?
Oh, hey, buddy.
[SCREAMING]
[LAUGHING]
Oh, Josh, new hair...
Oh, my gosh, a girl.
- Hi.
- The first Josh has brought home.
- Mom.
- Oh, I need to get my camera.
- No, you don't.
I bring girls home. Tons.
Oh.
- Oh, wait, you're...
- Dylan Schoenfield.
Oh.
- Hi. Ha, ha.
- Hi.
[TIMER DINGS]
Oh, my samosas.
Hey, Mom, I'm gonna go give Dylan
the tour.
Okay.
- Nice to meet you.
DYLAN: You too.
Okay.
Mom.
[ALL LAUGHING]
Delish.
This is the best Indian food ever.
- Really?
- Mm-hm.
Thank you.
Way to play my mom, Dyl.
Oh. No, not at all. These samosas
are très bons, Mrs. Rosen.
Oh, please, it's Sandy.
I stopped being Mrs. Rosen
two years ago.
- So are you two dating now?
- Ahem.
- Uh, no. I didn't te...
- I'll help.
Josh, will you take out the garbage?
Yeah.
- Josh and I are just friends, Sandy.
- Oh.
I thought maybe
because he brought you here to meet me,
I thought maybe something else
was going on.
No, I already have a boyfriend.
And Josh likes someone else,
so I don't know.
Don't get me wrong, though,
Josh is totes awesome.
SANDY:
Well, I think so too.
Mouse. Chow time.
Were you spying on us?
What? No.
Girl talk? Gross.
Give me the towel, I'll dry.
What do you think about that?
Is that gross?
Oh, my gosh. Don't do that.
No.
[DYLAN SCREAMS]
DYLAN:
Don't do that.
These are designer! Stop it.
[DYLAN LAUGHING]
No.
Of course boring old walking
would turn out to be your thing.
What? It's green to walk to school.
You sure this isn't too much?
[SPEAKING IN FRENCH]
Huh?
- It means good.
- Okay.
Oh, wait.
[SPEAKING IN FRENCH]
- Now, go.
- Okay.
[SCHOOL BELL RINGS]
GIRL:
You know what? I took that last semester.
- Hey, Josh.
- Hey.
CAITLIN: New clothes?
- Yeah, I, uh, did my laundry.
Doing laundry's a good look for you.
Josh, right?
Digging the vibe.
Hey, Josh.
See you in AP English.
What?
So...
It's kind of nice having girls talk
to me for something
other than help on their homework.
Yeah.
Wonton Wednesdays.
The mathlete scavenger hunt
is on Saturday.
Outstanding, I'm in. Josh?
Um, Josh, nice haircut.
That's it. Josh, you've been more MIA
than the final digit of pi.
Then you show up with a fake-over.
What's going on?
Relax, guys. It's just a new haircut
and some new shoes.
Dylan thought it would be fun
for the documentary.
When did the documentary get fun?
Isn't it supposed to be
a hard-hitting exposé on the Populars?
It will be. It's just Dylan turned out
to be more interesting than I thought.
Losing focus, my friend.
- First Amy Loubalu and now Dylan.
- What do you mean?
Girls you have crushes on,
who are never, ever gonna date you.
JOSH:
Okay, I don't have a crush on Dylan.
Please. What and ever.
Josh, what are you doing?
Come on.
We're on for Saturday, okay?
It's gonna be ridiculous.
Lates.
Ridiculous?
Lates?
It's like
Invasion of the Body Snatchers.
Directed by Philip Kaufman.
Looks like Josh, but it acts like
it's morphed into a Popular.
- Wow, Josh. You look...
- Adorkable.
My handiwork, naturellement.
Amy's sitting over there.
And if you're so determined
to ask her out, you better do it now.
- I'll save you a seat.
- Yeah?
- Okay.
DYLAN: Go.
Here.
So this is what you did all weekend
without us?
Josh's makeover?
No, we were filming too, but whatevs.
You can make him over all you want.
But he's still Count Dorkula.
We're just saying.
You better watch it or...
- Or what?
- Just or.
Okay, look. Josh is strictly a brofriend.
I figured if he's gonna hang around us,
then he might as well look the part.
Thanks.
When's this stupid dorkumentary over
anyway?
You missed my game.
I had to get my own water.
DYLAN:
Spring Formal is two weeks away.
And once I'm Blossom Queen,
everything will go back to the way it was.
Swears.
[LAUGHING]
My band, Blue Tangerine,
is playing a free show.
Bring a friend?
Actually, I was gonna ask you.
Ask me to go to my own show?
No, I was gonna ask you on a date.
Really?
How's Saturday? It's my day off.
- Sounds great.
- Great.
Cool.
[BOTH LAUGHING]
ALAN:
Josh Rosen.
I'm Alan Schoenfield.
I just wanted to meet the young man
my daughter's been spending
all of her time with.
Oh, and I've never really approved
of that Asher kid, I mean, "Asher"?
What kind of a name is Asher?
- Actually, sir, Dylan and Asher are still...
- I like that you have a job.
In my mall.
What time do you get off work?
Considering it is your mall, sir,
whenever you say.
- You have dinner plans?
- No, sir.
You do now.
Okay.
- Thanks for the ride.
- No prob.
That outfit is gonna look so cute,
I'm so totally jealous.
Oh, thanks.
[SPEAKS IN FRENCH]
Bye.
What?
But I can't believe
I've never seen this before.
No? It's a classic.
Now, what's with the rings of fire?
They were created
by using two circular neon tubes.
And they were moved up and down
using elevator mechanics.
Fritz Lang was most interested
in exploring the intersection
between magic and technology.
- Should I be taking notes?
- Yes. Yeah.
It's like I entered an alternate universe.
Oh, no, wait, worse,
an alternative alternate universe.
Hey there, pumpkin.
Since you missed dinner with Amber
and me the other night,
I figured it was time
to meet this new boyfriend of yours.
- Oh, and we got you turkey chowder.
- Dad.
- What? It's your favorite.
- Josh is not my boyfriend, d'accord?
I tried to tell him that, Dyl.
What is it with parents?
We're just friends,
he's making my movie.
My movie.
And actually, sir, your daughter
helped me land a date for this Saturday.
Oh, really?
[BURPS]
- Gross, Dad.
- What, that was barely a burp.
Oh, yeah? Was that a challenge?
All right.
[BURPS]
- Men, so juvenile.
- Oh, you're just jealous.
- Of what?
- Because you can't let loose.
Oh, I've actually heard Dylan burp a lot.
Dad. Mute button, please.
In fact, she used to like
to try to out-burp me
- so we'd have these contests. Uh-huh.
- No way.
That's classic.
I cannot believe you, Dad.
Yeah, I can barely believe it myself.
Really? Okay, fine.
You both wanna hear
what a burp really sounds like?
- Please.
- Okay.
Here we go.
[BURPS]
- Ah, bravo.
- Oh, the master has spoken.
Thank you, thank you,
I'll be here all week.
[LAUGHS]
So your dad was really cool.
I knew you two would get along.
You both like
those old black-and-white movies.
Classics.
I can't believe he gave me the keys back
to my Dylish-mobile.
Maybe he should think
you're my boyfriend more often.
Ha, ha. Maybe he should.
So you're, like, totally erasing
that footage of me burping tonight.
Why? It's the real you.
Real is overrated.
I think I like the real Dylan
more than the cover story.
What and ever. Heh.
So Amy.
Where are you taking her
this weekend?
Uh, I haven't really thought about it yet.
Do I have to do everything myself?
Okay, so Asher's having a party
this weekend.
I can get you on the invite list. Done.
I'm not sure that's my thing.
- I know what girls like, remember?
- Yeah.
- Bye.
- Later.
Some great stuff here, Josh.
How's editing?
Uh, I've just been crammed lately.
Between shopping with Dylan
on Saturday
and she came over to my place
for dinner the other night.
It's... Yeah, I'll get to it, okay?
I swear.
Right, well, the film festival board needs
to approve the rough cut
two days before the festival.
I'm on top of it, Mr. F.
All right, I know what movie I wanna make.
Good.
Yeah.
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
AMY:
Hi.
- Oh, here, listen to this.
- Okay.
- It's Blue Tangerine's new demo.
[HEAVY METAL MUSIC PLAYING
OVER HEADPHONES]
- It's not for everyone.
- No.
I could get used to it.
[LAUGHS]
So...
[AMY LAUGHS]
- Shall we go?
- Oh.
Of course, yes. Right, sorry.
After you.
[LAUGHS]
So, what's the plan for today?
I was thinking if it's not too much
to ask on the first date,
- take you home, meet my mom?
- Oh.
She's taking Greek cooking classes.
She's making lamb kabobs for lunch.
And I'm sure they're delish.
It's just that I'm a vegetarian.
- Right.
- I'm sorry.
No, it's okay.
Except when you're craving a burger.
Ha-ha-ha.
- How about a movie?
- Two hours in the dark?
On a day like this?
Okay, how about a party?
At Asher Dumetz's place?
- You're friends with the volleyball dudes?
- No. Not at all.
I'm glad we cleared that up because...
I don't know, I don't usually roll
with that crowd.
Perfect.
But should be fun for a laugh.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
All right.
One second.
- Thank you.
- Yeah.
Really?
[POP MUSIC PLAYING
OVER SPEAKERS]
Oh, wow.
GIRL:
Whoo!
BOY:
Here we go.
I'm coming.
Wanna dance? Wanna dance?
- What?
- Wanna dance?
I'm busy. Maybe later.
You're late.
Wait, you invited us?
Ugh. Oh, I knew Josh would have
nowhere hip to take you, so, yes.
You can hang with Asher and me.
I think I'd rather dance.
Dancing isn't really my thing.
Just go.
Show-off.
I'm happy to see Josh,
but I kind of wish he was on his own
so we could hang out more.
Weird, right?
Okay, I'll stop torturing you.
We got dates to the Spring Formal.
With the twins.
They're matching. I'm with Jay.
And I'm with Danny.
Excellent, ladies.
We can triple date, with Asher and me.
Anyone thirsty?
What are you looking for?
- Lemonade.
- Oops.
Took the last one.
Get used to that loser feeling.
[BOTH LAUGHING]
AMY:
So I was doing my guitar solo
and then an elephant joined in
on the drums.
Wow, that's awesome.
Go check on her.
Wait, what?
Sorry, it's just...
It's fine.
- Are you sure?
- Mm-hm.
I'm gonna go see if the DJ
will let me spin a few.
Okay.
Hey.
Why are you by yourself?
Oh, I was just taking a breather.
Where's Amy?
Okay, what's your deal
with her anyway?
Kind of ditched her in the sixth grade.
Why? Amy's great.
Amy is great.
I was afraid of always living
in her shadow.
You?
So I guess no threat of that
with Hannah and Lola.
Anyway, Amy's downstairs
checking out music.
Uh-oh.
- What "oh"?
- That means she's B-O-R-E-D, bored.
Seriously? What should I do?
Be romantic, dork. Hold her hand.
What, do I just grab it or...?
Like this.
Then what?
Well, when she talks to you,
you wanna lean in.
Like this.
- Hello?
- Uh...
JOSH: Uh...
DYLAN: Uh...
Dylan had something in her contact.
You wear contacts?
No, don't be silly. Contacts?
I have totes perfect vision.
Josh was just...
Yeah, just leaving.
All right, who invited him anyway?
Asher, wait, nothing was happening.
Asher.
Excuse me, sorry. Asher.
Asher, wait.
Call you later, Ash.
What's going on?
Oh, nothing, I'm just très fatiguèe.
- But you never leave parties early.
- Well, I am now, okay?
[DANCE MUSIC PLAYING
OVER SPEAKERS]
Look, there's nothing going on
with Dylan, okay?
I believe you.
Um...
Would you wanna go
to the Spring Formal with me?
Thanks, Josh.
But, no.
Why not?
Look, I don't think
you're secretly dating Dylan.
But I think you want to.
What?
Okay, N-O spells no.
Never.
You even sound like her.
I'm sorry.
Yeah.
Now back away, go away.
And look.
And I'm free.
At the beach. Ha-ha-ha.
[DYLAN SNORING]
No, no, no.
[GASPS]
No.
No, no, no.
Here you go. Vote for Paterson.
Hi, guys, don't forget to vote.
For Paterson.
There you go.
Hello. Vote for Paterson.
Okay, here you go,
you have to vote, okay?
Dylan, what are you doing?
Hannah and Lola.
Duh, I'm standing right here.
What's with the fire hydrant?
Oh, I was just checking it.
You know, safety first.
We don't have French class
until after lunch.
Yeah. I was just gonna study
for the pop quiz.
We have a pop quiz in French?
You never know, right?
Hi, Principal Guthrie.
The pressures of Blossom Queen.
It's made her totally snap.
[SCHOOL BELL RINGING]
Look, I know the rough cut deadline
is tomorrow,
but is there any chance
I can get an extension?
I'd like to, but you know I can't, Josh.
As chair of the film committee,
it would look like I'm playing favorites.
What's really going on?
Honestly? I need help finishing the film.
Josh,
just tell the truth.
Then your artistic vision
will shine through.
Artistic vision. Got it.
Listen, I'll talk to the
film festival board.
If you can edit something by tomorrow
morning, I'll get them to save your slot.
But I'm afraid
you haven't given yourself enough time
to make something worthy of first place.
He's right.
The post-republican period
of the ancient Roman civilization
was characterized
by an autocratic government.
An autocratic form of government.
In the late third century AD,
Diocletian established the practice
of dividing an order between four...
Here, a note from Asher.
What does it say?
Oh, you know, the usual.
He adores me, et cetera, et cetera.
Actually, it says he's breaking up
with you. Like, now.
What?
You wear glasses?
TEACHER:
This will all be on the midterm.
Submit, submit.
Asher.
You look, Asher.
- Asher, s...
- Dude.
- Asher.
- What?
You're breaking up with me in a note?
What about Spring Formal?
Maybe Josh can take you. Whoa!
What's that supposed to mean?
You've changed.
You hang with nerds now.
You're even dressing like one.
Oh, no. Look, look, see?
I'm the same old Dylan.
Yeah, I'm not so sure about that.
Lates.
- Hey.
- I need to talk to you.
- Great. I need to talk to you too.
Let's eat outside.
No, that's what
I wanna talk to you about.
Okay, I can't have lunch with you today
or any day until after the film festival.
What?
I haven't finished the movie yet.
Okay. And I gotta stay focused.
And I really, really wanna win
that film prize.
And I really wanna win Blossom Queen.
So you better not mess this up,
geek, or I'll...
Or what?
You gonna ban me from The Ramp?
Your seat's already been taken.
The Mummy. Original or remake?
Original, directed by Karl Freund,
remake directed by Stephen Sommers.
- I would say original.
- Remake.
Well, look who deigned to join us.
Well, as president of the film club,
I think that...
Not anymore.
What?
It's just you've been so busy going
to parties with the Populars lately...
Instead of coming
to the mathlete scavenger hunt.
Guys, I am so sorry, okay?
I completely forgot.
Okay.
We decided to re-elect a new film club
society president in your absence.
- What? Who?
- Me.
Really?
Why don't you go cry
on your new BFF's shoulder?
I heard Dylan and Asher
are D-O-N-E, done.
He dumped her.
[SCREAMS]
SANDY:
Dare I ask?
How's it going?
[SIGHS]
My friends expect one thing
and Dylan expects another.
Mr. Farley wants me to tell the truth.
That's good advice.
Hey, Mom, do you think it's okay
if my artistic vision has changed?
Well, I mean, yeah, I think it's okay
if your feelings have changed.
I mean, your film should be about
the Dylan that you've come to know.
Good night.
Night.
- Hey, don't stay up too late, okay?
- Yeah.
Stop it.
Testing, one, two, three.
LOLA:
I love it.
It feels like a cupcake.
- What do you think about this one?
- It's so cute. I love the sparkles.
- Do you like my glove?
- Oh, I love those.
Dylan.
What are you doing here?
This is my favorite boutique,
I'm always here.
You're shopping
for Spring Formal without me?
Well, you're forever off shopping
with Josh these days.
Besides, we have dates to the dance
and you don't anymore.
Lola,
defs get that dress. You look gorgeous.
[SPEAKS IN FRENCH]
Marta, I'm home.
ALAN:
Hey, sweetie.
No plans with Josh tonight?
- I think Josh and me are in a fight.
- Over the movie?
I'm starting to wonder
if it was such a stellar idea after all.
Tell you what.
Why don't we have dinner,
just the two of us?
I was supposed to see Amber, but I can
quickly give her a call and cancel.
We'll order in.
I suppose your girlfriend can join us.
Just once.
Really?
You are the best.
[GIGGLES]
I know.
So I noticed that you have
some Serge Sanchez heels on.
Oh, you noticed.
I love Serge so much.
Maybe you can borrow them.
That would be awesome.
So maybe Amber's not my mom,
but she's not so bad either.
And they convinced me
to have a little bit more faith in Josh.
The movie will be fine.
Right?
[CLASSICAL MUSIC
PLAYING ON SCREEN]
As they say in show business,
break a leg.
Wait, you guys still mad?
No. Geeks stick together.
Hi.
[CROWD APPLAUDING]
Right.
Well, thank you, Josie Bel Bruno,
for that fascinating film
about your pet hamster.
I certainly didn't know
that they were that vicious.
[CROWD LAUGHING]
Right, well, I would like
to take this opportunity
to thank all the participants
in the festival, thank you.
Well, without further ado,
it gives me great pleasure
to introduce Woodlands Academy's
official submission, Josh Rosen
and his documentary
called The Popularity Project.
Popularity.
What is it?
According to Dylan Schoenfield,
one of the most popular girls
at Woodlands Academy,
it's a lot of things.
Being popular is so not easy.
- We're in the movie.
DYLAN: It's like royalty or the first lady.
You have to live up
to impossible standards of beauty
and you're expected
to be a good influence.
Like I help out the less fortunate.
Fashion victims.
[CROWD LAUGHING]
Popularity's contagious.
JOSH: What, like a cold?
- Duh.
It's why Hannah and Lola battle
to be my better friend.
Their popularity comes from mine.
[CROWD LAUGHING]
JOSH:
What are your plans after school?
Uh, Pilates. But not on Tuesdays.
That's yoga.
[CROWD LAUGHING]
JOSH: I mean, when you graduate.
You know, hopes, dreams?
- What's your life goal?
- Blossom Queen.
[CROWD LAUGHING]
JOSH: After that.
- After?
If I don't win Blossom Queen,
my life is officially O-V-E-R, over.
[CROWD LAUGHING]
JOSH:
So Populars only hang with Populars?
Cats don't hang with dogs, right?
JOSH:
Really? That's your argument?
It's better this way.
If everyone stays in their own group,
there's no chance of misunderstandings.
JOSH: Like, what kind
of misunderstandings?
Well, take you and me, for instance.
If we mingled outside
of doing my movie together,
you might get the wrong idea
and ask me out.
[CROWD LAUGHING]
- Imagine the horror.
- You'd be so embarrassed.
[DYLAN CLEARS THROAT]
[CROWD LAUGHING]
Did we get it? Was that good?
So is Dylan the cat or the dog?
[CROWD LAUGHING]
Are you getting my good side?
This one right here?
JOSH:
Could one person be this shallow?
I chose Dylan as my documentary
subject because I wanted a challenge.
To uncover the truth
about popularity.
But I also wanted
to make something real.
I was determined to discover
the real Dylan Schoenfield.
Oh, no. The volleyball game's over.
Asher.
[CROWD LAUGHING]
Goodbye.
[DYLAN SPEAKING IN FRENCH
ON SCREEN]
Dylan, stop.
Stop.
- What's wrong?
The entire movie is what's wrong.
And it wasn't enough for you
to embarrass me in front of my friends.
You embarrassed me
in front of the entire city.
Embarrass you?
But I was trying to show the real you.
And the real me is humiliating.
I've spent all of middle school
and high school
trying to get rid of the real me
and perfect the new Dylan.
- Dylan, I...
- You don't get it and you never did.
I trusted you,
but you never cared about me.
All you cared about
was that stupid movie.
- That's not true.
- It's not?
Just leave me alone, Josh.
And by that, I mean for and ever.
JOSH: So the more I got to know Dylan, I
found out there's lots of sides to her.
She can be funny and normal
and full of life.
Josh, Josh, look at this.
Zoom in and look at it.
Josh, zoom in right here, right here. Look?
Zoom in. Do you see that?
What's that say?
Hmm?
A plus.
Whoo!
Yes. Stop it.
[DYLAN SCREAMS ON SCREEN]
[CROWD LAUGHING]
JOSH: She can also be sensitive
and vulnerable and compassionate.
Is that your mom?
Yeah, she met my dad
at the Woodlands Spring Formal.
Crazy, huh?
JOSH:
Wait.
Was your mom Blossom Queen?
Back in the olden days, 1985. Heh.
JOSH:
Wow.
I bet you miss her.
Lots.
It gets kind of lonely here
with just me and my dad.
JOSH: So when you said there's nothing
more to life than winning Blossom Queen...
Yeah,
because of my mom.
If I win,
it's like we're still connected.
Like she's still with me.
JOSH: And as I discovered
the real Dylan Schoenfield,
I figured, yeah, she
might be popular,
she might really like shoes,
but she's more than that.
She's smart and cool and real.
And that's the Dylan
I wanted to show the world.
Yeah, so maybe the truth didn't turn out
to be a hard-hitting exposé on popularity,
but I don't care.
I have a new friend.
That's what really matters.
[CROWD CHEERING]
MAN [ON TV]:
Are you ready?
WOMAN [ON TV]:
Whoa. Here we go.
Whoa.
[GUITAR PLAYING ON SCREEN]
AMY:
Hey.
Still hidden under the frog planter,
like in middle school.
What are you doing here?
Look, Dylan, just because you stopped
being my friend in sixth grade
doesn't mean I stopped being yours.
I know you went through a lot
when your mom died.
I get it.
I still get it.
I don't know what to say.
Which, you know, for me,
never happens.
[BOTH LAUGH]
Josh is worried about you.
Yeah, right.
Josh's terrible movie ruined me.
My life is O-V-E-R, over.
Josh's terrible movie won
the film festival.
You're more popular than ever.
Josh gave me the DVD for his movie.
Watch all of it
and then tell me if you're ruined.
[BOTH GIGGLING]
[POP MUSIC PLAYING
OVER SPEAKERS]
OLIVIA:
Dylan.
Dylan, you're the most popular girl
at Woodlands ever.
There you are. You don't have to hang
with the riff-raff anymore.
Look, I got the dress.
You're right, your charity is fashion.
What and ever, it's nothing compared
to your dress, Dyl.
Oh, vintage is so in. Like you.
ASHER:
Hey, Dylan.
Looking, uh, smoking.
AMY:
Dylan.
GUTHRIE:
If I could have your attention.
Oh, it's starting.
GUTHRIE:
Ladies and gentlemen.
It's time, people.
The moment I have...
The moment you have been all waiting for.
It's time to announce
your Spring Formal Blossom Queen.
And let's just see.
And the winner is:
Dylan Schoenfield.
[CROWD CHEERING]
Go. Go.
Well played, Schoenfield. Well played.
Whoo!
Woohoo!
[SIGHS]
Recently, a documentary
was made about me
and I know some of you
may have seen it. Heh.
Um...
I would like to give you all an update.
I was wrong about
that cats and dogs stuff.
Popularity isn't about having everyone
know who you are or what you're wearing
or even winning Blossom Queen.
Popularity is about having real friends
who like you for you.
Not faux ones who ditch you
because a better offer came along
or bailed on you
because you became single
and didn't have a date
to Spring Formal anymore.
It's about real friends.
Who you can count on.
Even if it's been, like, forever
and they have pink hair and stuff.
Friends who might not always be
into the same things as you,
but who will always be there
to share an
everything-but-the-kitchen-sink sundae.
It's not about being popular or a geek.
It's about being around people
who make you happy,
Like how I feel about Josh Rosen.
[TENDER ROCK MUSIC PLAYING]
DYLAN:
Oh.
- Hi.
You won the film festival.
And you won Blossom Queen.
I couldn't have done it without you.
Same here.
Amy showed me the whole movie.
Oh, you finally called it "the movie."
Our movie.
So does it have a happy ending?
You tell me.
True love prevails.
Gross.
I think it's kind of romantic.
You wanna dance, Steven?
- Does E equal MC...
- Squared?
- Hi.
- Hi. Heh.
- Wanna dance?
- Huh?
What? Are you scared or something?
Me? Scared?
So that's our story.
The princess and the geek.
Film geek.
I'm sorry I called you a nerd.
Sorry I called you a diva.
So I'm thinking, sequel?
Sequels are never
as good as the original.
Everyone knows that.