Octonauts, to your stations.
Barnacles!
Kwazii!
Peso!
- Explore!
- Rescue!
- Protect!
I wonder what those little lights are up ahead.
Shellington?
It could be a group of tiny firefly squid, Captain.
They glow in the dark.
- Dim the lights to get a better look.
- Already on it, Captain.
I can't tell what they are for certain.
They're not moving.
Then let's get a little closer. Closer...
CRASH!
- Jumping jellyfish!
- Dashi, put us in reverse and pull away.
I'm trying, Captain, but... Something's got us.
- CRASH
- Switch to steering wheel mode, now!
Argh! Mustn't...break...free!
Oh! Oh, dear!
Miaow! Mioaw! What?
Shiver me whiskers!
Flappity flippers!
Ooooh! Argh!
CHIRRUPS
It's no good, we held tight. Dashi, lights. Let's see what got us.
Aye-aye, Captain.
It's an enormous eye!
The little lights around my eyes fooled you, didn't they?
You didn't know they belonged to big, old me.
We mean you no harm. Please, let go of us at once.
No!
I grab it, I keep it, you weird looking squid.
- Dashi, slam the Octo-Alert.
- Whoa!
Octonauts, to the HQ!
Shellington, any idea what's grabbed us?
Yes, it's a colossal squid.
It's like my cousin, the giant squid, only bigger.
It's the biggest squid in the ocean!
I wish it would stop shaking us!
No more shaking.
Phew, that was easy.
Time for squeezing!
Yar! He'll crush the Octopod!
We'll match him tentacle for tentacle. Tweak?
I've got just the thing, Cap.
Wearing this tentacle suit, Professor Inkling will be able
to move the arms of the Octopod as if they were his own.
- Wow!
- I'm not good at pushing buttons
but I'm an expert at tentacle wrestling.
Excellent! Activate tentacle suit!
Ee-haw-pow!
Twist to the side.
Now, down.
That's it!
Ha! You're swashbuckling like a proper pirate, Professor.
Oh, my! I need to break free before he gets his hooks in us.
- Hooks?
- What hooks?
The squid has hooks on the ends of his tentacles.
So it's quite a challenge to get away from him.
Almost there. Just a few more twists and turns and we'll be... Argh!
Ink cloud! A classic move from the squid playbook.
Oh, no! I can't see where his tentacles are.
That's right! Eat my ink!
I'm taking you down.
Way down!
CHIRRUPS
I'm afraid he's hooked us.
Understood. Kwazii, to the launch bay.
Here's the plan. We'll swim outside and use our paws...
To pry those hooks off the ship.
Ha! These hooks are no match for a swashbuckling pirate!
For each hook we loosen, two more move into place.
This will take all my polar bear strength.
- Got it!
- Captain, incoming tentacle!
- Thanks, Kwazii.
- Any time.
Better keep moving.
There's something heading straight for us.
It's a pod of sperm whales. And sperm whales love to eat colossal squid.
Ooh, I don't like the sound of that.
If the sperm whales eat the colossal squid...
...they might bite the Octopod, too!
It's every squid for himself. I'm getting out of here!
Stop holding on to me. Let go!
You're the one hooked on to us.
I'm stuck. I'll never get away from the sperm whales
if I can't move fast enough.
The sperm whales are getting closer.
We're doomed!
We'll keep you and the Octopod safe from the sperm whales.
Octonauts, prepare all GUPS for launch.
There you are, our colossal dinner!
Octonauts, let's do this!
- SQUID:
- Oh, hey! This is fun.
- Everyone, pull up!
- Uppy, up, up, up, up. Ooh!
- Now, back down.
- Oh, down! Weee!
Whoa!
They're still chasing us.
Yes, Peso. But, sperm whales breathe air, so sooner or later,
they'll have to swim to the surface to breathe.
- WHALE:
- Can't...keep...going. Must...go up for air.
- Good work, Octonauts.
- Oh, thank you! You guys saved me.
I'm sorry about almost crushing your ship and stuff.
No harm done. Well, not much, anyway.
Let's help you unhook yourself from the Octopod.
No, no, you just take it easy. Really, I can do it.
Ooph! Ooph! Ooh!
Watch out. Your hooks are digging in deeper.
Just a little tentacle trouble, that's all.
Are you sure you don't need help?
Hold your seahorses, I can do it. I'll just brace myself...
..and give it a good, strong...YANK!
- No!
- Oops, sorry.
Tunip and the Vegimals are in there!
They're sinking fast!
We've no time to lose. Everybody, dive!
It's too dark. I can't see the pod.
I see it! I see it!
You're pulling me paw, it's too dark down here to see.
I have the biggest eyes in the ocean.
I can see just fine without light.
Let's use your squid vision. Where are they now?
I'm looking... I'm looking...
Uh-oh! Down! Go down!
Everyone, dive!
- Not that way, the other way!
- Bring the GUPS around.
Hurry! They're heading for some sharp rocks.
You've got a free tentacle, reach out now and grab them if you can.
All right, I think I got it.
- Oh! I got it.
- Octonauts, pull up.
Well done! Sometimes, a spare tentacle comes in handy.
CHIRRUP!
I'm great at grabbing but I have a hard time letting go.
I could use some help after all.
Operation Untangle-Tentacles begins now.
Now your tentacles are where they belong,
it's time to return one of ours. Tweak?
OK, big guy. Bring up the pod.
That's it, up a little more.
Wee!
Down a little. Little more. Now to your left.
To your other left.
- Got it!
- Super super!
Good work, everyone.
I think this calls for a tentacle bump.
Yeah!
- Easy, now.
- Watch the hooks, matey.
Ha-ha-ha!
Subtitles by Red Bee Media Ltd