Hey, you guys hear of
the Dirty Sanchez?
It's good shit, good shit.
You're fingering a chick,
right?
Two, even three fingers.
When you slip
another finger right in her ass
and then, bang, you stop.
As soon as
she turns to see why,
you take
that special little finger,
and you wipe it
right across her upper lip.
She looks like
a damn Dirty Sanchez.
Gross, Alphonse.
Just your typical
disgusting chauvinist pig.
Dallas, baby
if you don't like
disgusting chauvinist pigs,
you're with the wrong crowd.
Exactly.
Dirty Sanchez.
That's fuckin' funny, man.
Hey, Fats
why don't you stop jerking
that camera off, man,
and start filming
these beautiful girls, huh?
Alright.
Debbie, what got you
into amateur porn?
Porn?
I'm just here to
have a kickass time
with my favorite girl.
We can't help
what gets caught on tape.
Yeah, but I can.
Here, let me tell you what
we're gonna do here, girls.
Okay?
We are gonna make history.
We're making a film.
Yeah, it's gonna have action.
It's gonna have drama.
It's gonna have
thrills and chills,
but mostly
it's gonna have a lot of sex.
Beautiful.
Now let's talk to Daisy.
Daisy?
Forgive her.
She's a little camera shy.
It's been a while since
you've seen one of those, huh?
Now here's Jimbo.
Hey, Jimbo
what the hell
are you dong here?
I don't know.
Alphonse was,
like, I need a van.
I was, like, I got a van.
And then,
he was telling me he was gonna
make nudie photos
with my sister,
and that's just not cool, man.
Next thing you know I wake up,
I'm in Mexico.
Keep smoking that stuff, Jimbo.
Next time you wake up,
you're gonna be in Africa.
Now let's get back to Dallas.
Dallas, what brings you to
the wonderful world of porn?
Let me tell you
something about Dallas, baby.
She may look like a damn troll,
but she can get her legs
so far behind her head...
How the hell would you know?
If I could do some of
the shit she pulls,
I'd never leave the house.
Yeah.
Dude
okay, dude
I'm telling you were
supposed to get on that freeway
like, 12 miles ago.
Which freeway?
The one.
Yeah, fat man, which one?
The one, dude.
There is only one freeway,
and it is the one.
You know I don't even see
Cabo on this map.
We're dying back here.
Yeah, can we stop?
I totally have to pee.
Do you see
somewhere to stop, huh?
Please. I really have to go.
You know what?
Why don't you girls
take a lesson
from Daisy back there. Huh?
Don't say a word.
She doesn't complain.
She just lays there with
her ass hanging out.
This map is a piece of shit.
Dude, what the, what,
what are you doing?
What? You know,
you know your way
around this crap hole country,
Fats.
We don't need a map.
What are you talking about?
Aren't you Mexican?
Yeah, but I was born
in Seattle, dude.
Whatever, still Mexican.
You know you could find
your way to a taco stand.
Hey,
look there's a gas station.
Oh.
Right there.
Thank God. Can we please stop?
No way, chickadees.
We got places to be. Alright?
It's the first place
we've seen in
like, six hours.
Stop the van, Alphonse
unless you wanna swim
in my piss.
Stop the van now!
Okay boys and girls,
here we are.
You are a dick.
Hey, hey, hey.
I just didn't want my princess
to bare her precious tulip
in a craphole like this.
Hello?
Damn it.
I smell gringos.
Dude!
Dude, that's the great
Diablo Negro mask, man.
And so it is, puny gringo.
El Diablo Negro, best Mexican
wrestler of all time.
Bullshit!
Nobody can beat El Tigre.
You creeps!
May I remind you,
I have to go to
the bathroom.
There's an outhouse
in the back.
I haven't used it in years.
Me, I just piss
against this wall.
Lovely.
So, where you gringos headed
with such sweet cargo?
We got the beach, daddy-o.
Oh, beautiful.
Me, I ain't into that shit.
Too much pussy is
bad for your heart, amigo.
Blow, on the other hand
doesn't want you to call
the next day.
You know what I mean?
Precisely.
Hey, might you
be able to point us
in the direction
of the freeway?
You guys are nowhere
near that stretch
of dirt that we natives
call the freeway.
Dude, uh, where
where are we?
Well, we locals call
this the middle
of no-fucking-where.
That's where you are.
Fuck.
Amigo, don't feel bad.
If you have enough gas,
the town's about 100 miles.
A hundred miles?
Yeah, we ain't got
but 50 miles of gas, pops.
How 'bout these pumps?
Those?
They haven't pumped since
Mexico was Spanish territory.
Shit, you could
take that road south
but then you'd have to
drive by La Sengre De Dios.
La Sengre De Dios?
Dude, are you fucking serious?
It's real, amigo.
No way, man. No way.
You're...
you're messing with me, man.
That shit is not real.
Guys, guys, what in the fuck
are you talking about?
La Sangre De Dios.
La, what the fuck?
La Sangre De Dios,
the Blood of Christ.
It's this,
it's this old ghost town, man.
And they say that nobody's
lived there for,
like, 40 years.
So?
So, it's wherethey
put El Mascarado
after he gouged
a man's eyes out
with his bare hands.
What?
It's this legend, okay?
It's just this
old Mexican legend.
The thing
about Mexican legends is
that sometimes
they turn out to be true.
That's gotta be some real good
shit you got there, pops.
Find out for yourself.
For the road, amigo.
Now, if you take that road,
you'll find gas,
but do yourselves a favor.
Do not stop.
Just keep driving
'til you get there.
Do not stop for any reason.
Drive.
Hey, hey, man.
Where the hell are we?
Well
the natives like to call it
the middle of no-fucking-where.
How's that strike you?
And in the middle of
no-fucking-where
we got ourselves
the daddy-o of all locations.
Oh, yeah?
It's a, whoo
it's a ghost town.
Well, no,
it's not just any ghost town.
It's La Sangre De Dios.
It's where
they brought El Mascarado
after he went crazy.
Who?
El Mascarado.
El Ma-dude, dude, the best
Mexican wrestler of all time.
Ooh, was he cute?
Was he cute?
Who, El Mascarado?
Fuck, no. He looked like hell.
Alright,
he came out in the early '60s.
See, the President of
Mexico loved wrestling,
was obsessed with winning gold
at the 1968 Olympics.
Now the problem was
Russia was kicking
major ass at the time
and Mexico didn't
stand a chance, right?
But, then, out of the blue,
El Mascarado appears,
and, man, the guy was a badass.
Ooh! Yeah, tell 'em,
my burrito brother.
Yeah, the thing is,
this guy came out of nowhere.
I mean,
he didn't even exist before.
That's creepy.
Fuck, yeah, that's creepy.
And around the same time
he appeared,
three of the best Mexican
wrestlers disappeared.
They just, pff, vanished.
Now legend goes,
they all ended up
in the hands
of these scientists.
Scientists?
Yeah, dude.
Scientists hired
by the President,
and these guys created
the perfect wrestler
out of the missing dudes'
body parts, man.
Anyway, right before
the Olympic trial
something snaps.
El Mascarado starts killing
his opponents in the ring.
He became a monster,
just nuts, dude.
After that, details
get a little bit sketchy.
But rumor has it,
they brought him
to this small town,
out in the middle of nowhere,
to fix him up.
And the name of that town
La Sangre De Dios.
Okay, am I the only one
who noticed
the guy back there was crazy?
Oh, I know. I know.
But if La Sangre De Dios
is there, we're stopping.
You're Goddamn right.
Holy shit, dude.
Whoa, daddy! Check that out.
That's creepy.
I say we keep going.
Blondie,
did I bring you on this trip
to talk or to fuck, huh?
Look out!
Watch the damn road, idiot.
Whoa, yeah!
Ow, hey, hey, man.
Did you just fuck up my van?
Nah, it's all good, baby.
She's running smooth.
Smooth as a shaved bush.
Fuck!
Bravo. Bravo.
Hey, Fats, did you bring
those bolt cutters?
One step ahead of you, dude.
Ladies and Gentlemen
bitches and 'hoes,
I give you
the ghost town. Whoo!
Dude, it's fucking real.
Yeah, this is one hell
of a location.
Oh, man. Oh, man. This is...
What is it, my boy?
It's, it's fucked up, man.
This place is just fucked up.
This place better get ready
for some good hard core
crotch-on-crotch action.
Camera, huh?
Let's see what we got here.
Little ass smacking okay?
Just like that.
Okay.
Fats.
Fats! Let's go. Let's go!
We're losing light here.
Well, looky here, Miss Daisy.
What a surprise. Hi.
Hi.
Get in there.
Get in there, drunky.
Get your sweet ass up there.
Listen up, ladies.
Listen up. Alright?
You girls, you're waiting
for the plumber, okay?
He's not showing up,
and you're getting bored.
The plumber?
You are such a dork.
And, action!
That's it.
Yo, excuse me ladies.
Did somebody call a plumber?
Oh, yes, baby.
We're in desperate
need of your plumbing
Desperate.
Hey, guys.
Sweetie, you okay?
Grab a breath. Huh?
Hey, Daisy
Daisy?
Daisy, where...
where the fuck are you going?
Shit.
Hey, Fats, keep shooting.
Keep shooting.
Why the fuck are you stopping.
I'm rolling. I'm rolling.
I got some good stuff.
Good angles,
good, good angles there.
Fuck.
Alphonse
tell us when you knew
you wanted to make porn.
What the fuck kind of
question is that?
I never wanted to make porn.
You see, I wanted to be
the next Scorsese
but I came to realize,
there's just more money
in this business.
I mean, who gives a shit
about Taxi Driver today?
But Deep Throat?
Now, that's a fucking classic.
Where the hell you guys been?
Can we go now?
This place is creepy.
So soon?
My beautiful dolls?
Don't you
wanna see what the great
Mexican wrestler
here is packing?
Dude!
Okay.
He might not be a wrestler
but I'm sure
he knows a couple of moves.
Come on.
Dallas, Dallas
oh, you and Steve,
the wrestler
and the contortionist.
Yeah,
I'd rather put my own foot
up my own ass.
Whoa, dude. Check this out.
Yeah, I know, man.
No, dude. Check this out.
What?
Here, look. There's a shadow.
So?
So, it's not in this frame.
Yeah, that's the shadow cast
by my big dick.
No, dude
look outside the door
right outside the door.
There, there...
there's somebody else here.
Daisy?
No, look again.
Look again. Okay.
'Cause Daisy, Daisy goes,
Daisy goes out the door
right here
and then, it, right there.
You see that?
There's a shadow right there.
Hey, hey
where is Daisy?
She's probably passed out
somewhere in this shit hole.
She took my weed, man.
Good boy, Jimbo. Go find her.
And tell her
if she's not back at the van
with her skirt up
in five minutes,
she can spend the night at the
uh, ghost town hotel.
Thank you.
What was I doing?
Daisy.
Daisy?
Whatever
feel some wicked
munchies coming on.
Can't believe she took my weed.
Where are those two assholes.
I warned them.
Fuck this.
What a day!
Fuck.
Oh, fuck, fuck, fuck
fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck.
You fucked up the van, man.
I did no such thing, daddy-o.
Dude! What, are,
you hit a rock the size
of my ass,
like, 20 feet from here.
Say one more word, fat man,
say one more fucking word.
Yo, pop the hood open.
Hey. Baby
baby, baby, hey.
Keep your panties on, huh?
What are you trying to do?
Hey, asshole
I'll let you know
that my daddy-o's
a mechanic, okay?
And I'm not
just a pair of tits on legs.
Now, if you don't mind?
Oh, I beg your pardon.
Excuse me.
Jimbo!
Hey, wh..., where is she going?
Steve
Steve!
Where are you going?
What the fuck
is up with everybody?
Where did she go?
Who the fuck knows?
Women are trouble.
That's all they are.
Yeah, dude.
Yeah. I mean,
you gotta put in all this work,
and then all you
get is more trouble.
Fucking lights work
in the fucking ghost town?
What is the fucking story
of this place?
I'm telling you, dude,
if any of that story is true,
there is some real bad
mojo in this town.
Oh, and why is that?
What?
Did you hear that?
There's, there's something
behind this wall.
Rats?
I don't think so.
Oh, fuck you.
It's you.
Yeah.
I thought
I saw Jimbo in the window.
Oh?
Yeah, it wasn't him, I guess.
But I can't find him.
Shh!
What?
That noise.
It's...
it's over there now.
Well, it's Jimbo.
Wait.
What is it?
I don't think we're alone.
I can't see
the van from here, man.
Hey, Fats, what do you say
we start heading toward
the van, man, huh? Huh?
We are. We doubled back
on the main road.
We're headed toward
the entrance of town.
Excuse me, sweaty Fats,
but you just know your way
around this fucking hell hole?
Dungeons & Dragons, man.
You're looking at
a level 14 warrior, here.
I made it through
Gauntlet's Maze
of Death in under six hours.
Jimbo!
Jimbo?
Oh, my God.
Jimbo!
Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
Oh, my God.
What the fuck happened to
his fucking face? Aw, shit!
His face is gone, dude?
Where is his fucking face?
It's El Mascarado, dude.
He took his face off.
What?
That's what
Mexican wrestlers do
when they win a fight.
They, they rip their
opponent's mask off.
It's the ultimate humiliation.
Oh! You are fucking crazy,
fat man!
You are both fucking crazy.
I'm leaving.
I'm done.
Fucking fuck, fuck you,
fucking fuck
fucking faceless motherfucker.
Oh, shit!
Hey, some... some...
somebody's out there, man.
I told you, dude.
He is still here!
Who is still here, man?
Is he gone?
Christ! Woman!
You guys, hold the door.
Come on!
Yeah, hold the fucking door,
Debbie.
Hold the door. Hold it!
Shit, dude!
He's gone.
I think he's gone.
Go, go, go!
Oh, sh...
Open the door.
Dude, open the door.
You crazy?
You think I believe in
this sack of shit?
You're fucking crazy, fat man!
Open the door!
Open the fucking door, dude.
Go away.
Stop banging
on my fucking door.
Steve?
Fuck!
Shit!
Do you think he followed us?
No, we lost him.
God damnit!
Oh, are we gonna die?
No, no, we are getting out
of this town.
How?
I don't know.
What is this?
What are you doing?
Dude!
This is about El Mascarado.
Fif..., hol...
dude, they gave him, like,
50 lobotomies,
and it didn't help for shit.
They used human test subjects.
They, they used
people from this town.
They
oh, shit,
he killed them all.
He just tore them to shreds.
His, his only, his only, uh
objective is, uh, the complete
uh, dest...
destruction is, uh,
do, no entre
do not enter, quadrilateral.
His only objective
is to destroy
do not enter quadrilat...
Quadrilateral
Quad...
That's it.
He follows the rules.
He what?
He follows the rules,
the rules of wrestling.
We're gonna retire
that son of a bitch tonight.
Steve!
No, it's okay.
It's okay. We got him.
I know how to stop him.
Shit!
Let' go.
Yeah, whoo.
Who's your daddy?
These never end.
Listen to me. Listen to me.
We have got to
take his mask off.
What?
Alright, look. Uh, the rules
of Mexican wrestling state
when a...
a wrestler's face is,
is revealed to the public,
he must retire
in humiliation forever
and never show his face
to the world again.
What are you talking about?
If we take his mask off,
he's done. He's finished.
How do we take
that thing's mask off?
That I don't know.
Holy shit!
I can't see anything.
What the fuck was that?
Oh, shit. Oh, shit.
I, I've got a switch.
Oh, my God.
He's coming. He's coming!
Move, move!
Get away from the door.
Okay, I got it.
Okay.
We've got to get to the van.
I know.
What are we gonna do?
We gotta get out of here!
Holy shit!
Quadrilatero
it's a ring.
It's a wrestling ring.
What are you talking about?
Oh, my God!
Oh, shit.
My God!
What...
Oh, my God, we're gonna die.
We're gonna die.
What are you doing?
Oh, no. Steve
what are you doing?
Steve!
Come on, you fucker!
Oh, no!
Oh, my God. Oh, God.
Oh, my God!
No, no!
No!
Hey, guys!
Hey, I fixed the van.
Where are you?
Guys
what the hell?
Hey, if you're not out here
in five minutes,
I'm gonna leave.
You hear that, Alphonse?
Where are you guys?
Hello?
Jimbo?
You guys can't be too far.
Guys?
Shit
oh, shit.
Shit!
Steve?
You...
you gotta...
you gotta take his mask.
Oh, what
it's okay, Steve.
It's okay. No!
Take...
his...
mask...
off.
Hasta la vista, you fuck.
And, and then, I'll start over,
rapping about
how he killed each character.
He's like,"I beat up Steve
in a record pace.
If you step to me, I'm gonna
take your face. "You know?
If you vulgar,
and you got no respect,
you're gonna end up
with a nail through your neck.
Alphonse, he's dead as hell.
I found Jimbo,
and that's all she wrote-a.
That's what you get
when you smoke the mota.
I'm going to remodel
my Mexican palace.
I'll wallpaper my rooms
with Debbie and Dallas.
I own this town from
the church to the steeple.
I made mincemeat out
of all the townspeople.
With his muscles
of steel and big cojones,
El Mascarado heats up
my pantalones.
I took your life. Now I ta...
now I take your van.
This is El Mascarado saying,
"Peace out, man."