-Maybe Wilbur...
- Shut up!
Damn it, damn it!
Shut up!
Shut up, you crappy alarm!
Oh, yeah, Pickles!
- Pickles wakes up just like everyone else!
- What the hell are you people doing here?!
- Hi, Pickles!
- Oh, God! I forgot.
- Will you be the father of my kids?!
- I hate Fan Day.
Do anything for Dethklok
Dethklok, Dethklok
I'll teach you
Who rock
Dethklok! Dethklok!
Skwisgaar Skwigelf
Taller than a tree
Toki Wartooth
Not a bumble bee
William Murderface
Murderface, Murderface
Pickles the Drummer
Doodily doo
Ding-dong,
Doodily doodily doo
Nathan Explosion
It's being called the ticket of the century.
Mordhaus, the home of Dethklok will
be open to the public for the first time...
in celebration of this year's
lnternational Dethfan Day.
Banks have closed because customers
are withdrawing all their life savings...
in an attempt to purchase
one of these coveted tickets.
An official statement
from Dethklok calls this...
"a psychotic day of insane celebration
for regular jackoffs."
Dethklok is opening
their home to their fans.
It seems that their popularity
is still growing at an alarming rate.
We get most of our Dethklok information
by monitoring over 100,000 fan web sites...
the biggest of which being
Diefordethklok.com...
run by the Jomfru brothers
Eric and Edgar.
They dropped out of Harvard
to become dedicated Dethklok fans.
Their web site alone gets
more hits than all of South America.
We can interrogate them later
and find out what's really inside Mordhaus.
Yes.
Hey, pals!
It's me...Face Bones.
Welcome to Mordland...
home of the international
metal band Dethklok.
Now, we got a big list
of dos and don'ts because...
we at Mordland like
to run a really tight ship.
Remember: our snipers
have new.50 caliber rifles...
that can kill you from almost 3 miles away.
And remember: deadly force
is authorized, so do not ever enter into...
And you have to use the restroom,
make sure and don't go into the...
And remember:
no recording devices
or cameras will be allowed...
or your life will be terminated.
Now, Dethklok has decided
to allow you to listen to one secret song...
to be played one time only
for you, the fans!
Fan song!
You hear that?! High-five!
Why do I drink so much
before stupid Fan Day?
I believe you drink
because it's Fan Day.
Don't talk to me about that.
Wait, where's Skwisgaar?
Oh, I don't think
he's gonna be here for a while.
He have a very big night
with a very huge fan.
- Yeah, we were all up late.
- Not me.
- I actually gots good rest.
- Will you please just be quiet?
What's wrong, Pickle?
You just need to eat something.
Your name is Pickle. Maybe
you should try a pickle-herring sandwich...
Famous from Oslo!
Oh, yeah, Pickles!
God! Everywhere I go,
there's fans everywhere.
Can't I just throw up in my own house?!
Oh, God!
Don't! What are you, bulimia?
Oh, great. Now you're gonna
start a whole chain reaction puke-a-thon.
Oh, blood puke!
Good song title.
Someone write that...
Oh. That's right.
We already wrote that.
Good song though.
It should go back in the set list.
Oh. I think I need
another liver transplant.
Prepare to see one
of the greatest sights you've ever seen...
The fastest guitarist alive
in his natural habitat.
Need paper towels.
OK.
My face is stucks to the wall.
Oh, crap.
In order to keep
Nathan Explosion healthy...
and because of the tremendous drinking
it takes to entertain all Dethklok fans...
Nathan must undergo
a series of liver transplants.
- Have you eaten anything this morning?
- Nope.
- Are you sure?
- I mean, yeah. I mean, no.
OK. Anesthesia, please.
Hey, guys!
It's me, Face Bones!
Now is the time you've
all been waiting for...
your very own exclusive,
super duper exclusive...
fan song and one-time-only song video!
Roll it.
You people out there give us something
more than just record sales...
you give us something to hate.
And we hate you, you brainless mutants.
Hate, hate, hate, hate
You hunched and blinded mutants
Living in chat rooms
You masturbate on the sheets
Your mothers clean for you
You have lined my pockets
Overflowed with gold
You're living with your parents
And you're 35 years old
You're a bunch of banks
That I'd like to rob
You're my online cash transaction
You're my future stocks
Transfer you like money
To a Swiss account
Spend you on an impulse buy
And zero you all out
Hate, hate, hate, hate
I would like to get some sleep
But you keep buying all our things
My overhead is way too deep
For us to not keep making these
It's way too cynical, you see?
Hating what's supporting me
I am not you
I thank the gods
And if I were,
I'd die like dogs
Die, die, die, die, die
I'll be very glad when this is over with.
If they only knew
how much we hated them.
I mean, they just keep crawling back
like groveling putrid stupid zombies that...
well, just want to eat
out brains that is our art.
- Hey, what are you doing?
- He's in a wheelchair, my lords.
I did not know what to do.
That does not means you get free lunch
for entrance to everything.
We are the Jomfru brothers,
proprietors of Diefordethklok.com.
Really? That's interesting.
What are you selling?
You know, handicap stuff?
No.
We want you to pay
for a good review on our web site.
That's rich.
We are the fans.
We are the power.
Without us, your precious
brutality means nothing.
Take a walk before I kill you.
Not so fast, Mr. Explosion...
though I do appreciate
your simplistic views...
of smashing that
which you don't understand.
Effective.
Oh, come on!
Screw that lnternet crap.
I mean, come on, what is the lnternet,
you know?
Seriously.
What is the lnternet?
Perhaps you will give us more than a link
when we debut this on our web site.
Hate, hate, hate
Hate, hate, hate, hate...
We've taken the liberty of appropriating
your exclusive song which is ready...
to be hyperlinked and sold exclusively
on our web site with a single keystroke.
How about we have a link
to the bottom of the stairs...
by me throwing you to
the bottom of the stairs?!
I think not.
We'll give you the song back when we get
the money and not a moment before.
Oh, whenever.
So...
Where are you guys from?
Sandusky, Ohio.
There's an amusement park there, right?
Yes, there is an amusement park.
Well, that's always fun.
Your money's way down there...
behind that door. Can you see it?
Hey, you better hurry up.
Closing time is in two minutes.
All the way over.
I'd serpentine if I were you.
It's showtime.
Why should we serpentine?
Serpentine!
Merci.
Bon café, Jean Pierre.
Thank you, my lord.
You give us something to hate.
But we hate you, you brainless mutants.
You hunched and blinded mutants
Living in chat rooms
You masturbate on the sheets
Your mothers clean for you
You have lined my pockets
Overflowed with gold
You're living with your parents
And you're 35 years old
You're a bunch of banks
That I'd like to rob
You're my online cash transaction
You're my future stocks
Transfer you like money
To a Swiss account
Spend you on an impulse buy
And zero you all out