Man: As a kid, it baffled me
how God could know so much.
Not only past and present,
but the future as well.
The stories were beautiful...
austere...
terrifying.
And one loomed
over all others...
the story of Abraham.
God sends a man...
to slaughter his own son...
only to stop him
perilously close to the act,
to reveal it's all been a ruse.
Deedee, It's me.
Man: To me that story was,
and always will be,
not Abraham's story,
but Isaac's.
This boy must grow with the image
of his own father poised above him...
without it ever explained
why he's a victim.
Woman: You'll be
all right in there?
Man: I always knew I would devote
my life to clarity.
I would save the world's
uncomprehending victims.
What I never knew is,
when dealing with matters
of life and death...
as policemen inevitably do...
there's no way around
the question of God.
In fact, there are moments
when there's nothing else
that can be thought of
to say but, why?
And like Isaac found...
there's only silence
in response.
Lonely...
indeterminate silence.
Officer:
Hey, you all right?
Hey, stop walking!
I said, stop!
We called an ambulance.
It'll be here quick.
Is that your blood on you?
Damnit, answer me!
Hey!
I need to see your hands
in the air, slowly.
Do it now!
There's two of us back here.
Let him know
there's two of us.
- Officer #2: Hello!
- You heard that.
Bring up your hands.
Ease on up around him.
Kid, my partner's coming around
to get a better look at you.
Tommy?
Les, it's Tommy Spencer.
Is it his blood?
Well, he better hope not.
Okay, Tommy...
I need you to please
turn around for me, okay?
We ain't going to hurt you.
Just please turn around.
Tommy?
Just hold still.
Okay, Tommy?
We'll figure all this out.
Okay? Just...
just hold still.
Man: This story
has many beginnings.
We're going back six months
to the front end of spring.
I think there's going
to be two of us.
Waitress:
I'll fetch you another menu.
- Nothing doing at the Red's?
- I'm off this morning.
- I sure like your ribbon.
- It's yellow.
- I can see that.
- No. Like in the song...
It's Tony Orlando and Dawn.
- It was my favorite growing up.
- You don't mean it.
My man got out from
McAlester yesterday.
- He's meeting me here.
- Why didn't you go down there?
Woman: He thought
it'd be better this way...
- if I waited up here.
- All by yourself,
- while he travels half the state?
- Yes.
Bless your heart.
- Does this man love you?
- I don't know.
What do you mean?
- I think that's him.
- You think?
- We never met before.
- Should I point you out?
He knows I'm wearing
this ribbon.
I'll scoot out of your way.
- You Ainsley?
- Yes.
Ain't you gonna
look up at me?
That'll do.
- I can't do this.
- What?
Hey.
How will I feel
if you run off on me so quick?
I need you to give this a chance.
If you leave now,
it'll be the end of me.
Come on back inside, please.
I'm begging you.
All right.
I haven't had you on my mind
for six months
- for you to be scared of me so quick.
- I won't leave.
- I ain't gonna let you.
- Don't.
All right, then.
- Is this menu for me?
- Yes.
I can't get used to all this.
It's the weirdest thing
about being out... choices.
You know,
we've got choices in life.
One of the things
prison's about is...
taking choices away from folks
incapable of making the right ones.
I ain't looked at it that way.
I reckon you ain't had to.
- So this here is Kingfisher?
- Mm-hmm.
It's just like you said...
- quiet and friendly.
- Lots of oil pumps.
Lots of oil pumps.
Different than McAlester?
There's no oil pumps
in McAlester.
I so wish
I could have seen it.
No, you don't.
It's where you lived.
All them letters come from there.
Them letters come from me.
- You know what I mean.
I do.
Me and her had a talk
before you come in here.
Is that right?
You make sure
and treat this one right.
- Okay.
- She deserves it,
waiting on you like she did.
I can pick 'em,
and she's a keeper.
An angel from Heaven.
The Lord sent her
to watch over you.
I need that.
I don't know.
That boy in our line?
- You ain't got to tell me.
- Y'all are early.
- Ain't seen Sam, have you?
- Ain't been in yet.
You two sit on down.
- Hi, Ainsley.
- Hi.
I'll be with you in a minute.
You two want to order anything?
Uh, give me
the Cattleman's Breakfast here.
How do you like your eggs?
Scrambled, I guess.
- And for you?
- I can't eat.
- You have to eat something.
- I'm too frazzled.
Come on now.
How do you like your eggs?
Fried.
- Two eggs.
- Fried it is.
Sunny-side up.
Hey, just the way
my boy likes them.
But don't get me started
talking about him.
Oh goodness.
I'll be back with your food.
- She's lonely.
- Yeah, I can see that.
I've got to be at work
in 20 minutes.
Sorry I couldn't get off.
Lee, my manager, is strict.
That's all right.
It's just...
I've been waiting
a long time for this.
Me too.
I've got to meet my parole officer
this afternoon anyway.
- You do?
- I do.
But I'll meet you
when you get off.
- Take me somewhere tonight.
- All right.
I don't care.
Just some place special.
Special to you.
All right.
- We're together now.
- Oh yes.
Thank God.
We're together.
Parole Officer:
So you found religion, too?
Yes, sir.
That's neither one way
or the other with me, religion.
If Christ died for my sins,
I ain't seen the benefits.
But if you get satisfaction
from praying, so be it.
Yes, sir.
- So why Kingfisher?
- There's a girl up here.
You knew her
before you went in?
We met through a magazine.
- You see her yet?
- This morning.
- Sort of a blind date.
- I guess.
My wife and I met
on a blind date.
Getting involved
real quick after doing time
- can be a very serious thing.
- I know.
Particularly with
your kind of background.
I know that.
- What's her name?
- Ainsley.
Ainsley...
Ainsley Dupree.
- Works over at the Red's?
- That's right.
- Officer: I used to work with her dad.
- Really?
He was foreman at the pipeyard
during the boom.
- She told you how he died?
- No, actually.
When the yard closed down,
he'd became a tool-pusher.
He got caught in a rig fire.
Janice?
I need more of these.
In a minute!
Officer: He burned alive,
with three other guys.
She ain't said anything about it.
He was a son of a bitch
to work for.
Hard as nails.
Real religious, too.
It might interest you.
That was the joke.
He talked about hell so much,
he went that way.
You know, fire...
I get it.
She seems all right, though.
Homespun, reliable.
They make a good burger
over there.
So, how's the job situation?
You know,
I just came into town today.
Any special skills?
I like cars an awful lot.
Ainsley: Janice!
All right.
Fries.
Customer:
There's eight of us.
- Six kids?
- You betcha!
- Ainsley: What's that like?
- I wish I had two more.
What's it like for your wife?
She's always kept
her maternity clothes.
- I bet.
- She's got another one in the cooker.
- Really?
- You betcha!
What's all this
going to run me?
$21.83.
Hon, you have another $10?
Officer:
You gonna live with her?
- As long as she'll have me.
- She agreed to that?
- She agreed to let me stay there.
- Meaning?
Meaning, she agreed
to let me stay there.
This the address
you wrote down here?
Yes, sir.
Okay, Jack.
We'll put you on
our electronic monitor program.
You'll be wearing
this device around your ankle.
Whenever you progress
beyond 100 feet of the home,
we get a signal here
at the station
alerting us you've crossed
the boundaries of your parole.
I didn't how I had to do
a monitoring program.
You got four years
took off your sentence.
- Yeah?
- Consider yourself lucky.
- I consider myself blessed.
- Call it what you will.
This is not to confine you,
this is to monitor you.
Ainsley and me
were going out tonight.
We don't get
to her house till morning.
We'll need to get this
on your ankle right away, though.
We'll know where you are
tonight at all times.
In fact, we'll always
know where you are.
I need to know
where church is in town.
That should be easy enough.
Pick and choose.
Unless you're a Mormon or a Jew.
Hello?
Yeah, I know.
I'm on my way.
Okay.
It was my wife.
Trying to have a kid all year.
I'm even taking lunch at home
at certain times of the month.
Very frustrating.
Takes all the romance out of it.
Here's a card with
all my basic information.
I'll walk out with you,
get you set up,
get this put on your ankle
so I can get home.
Duty calls.
- It ain't weird?
- Weird?
- Him being in prison.
- He ain't in prison.
He was in prison.
I don't know, Janice,
it ain't weird, yet.
What did you talk about?
We weren't together an hour
before I had to come here.
You've got plenty of time.
Be patient.
He's lucky to have you.
You look like you'll give
yourself all up at once.
- I do not.
- Yes, you do.
I guess you'd know.
Uh-huh...
- What's that supposed to mean?
- Nothing.
I want to know.
I'm sorry.
It don't mean nothing.
You can have whatever
opinion you want.
- All I'm saying...
- Lee's here.
It ain't no hurry.
I'm happy for you,
you hear me?
And maybe I'm a little jealous.
Lee: Get your ass
off the counter.
- What you girls talking about?
- Nothing.
- Bullshit.
- Nothing, Lee.
Get back to work,
why don't you?
Janice: I won't be in,
in the morning.
Lee:
What do you mean?
I've got some business
to take care of.
- What kind of business?
- My business.
- Ow!
- It's my business
- if there ain't nobody here.
- Ainsley: I'll open.
Yeah?
It's all right.
What have you got?
Uh-huh.
I'll be right over.
No, wait on me.
Wife: What is it?
They got little Tommy Spencer.
Wife: Is he all right?
Is he ever?
- Nobody knows what to do.
- Shh.
Tommy?
He ain't spoke
since we found him.
- Ain't a scratch on him?
- Not a one.
- Is this blood being checked?
- Les: It's at the hospital.
It's human. They don't know
the type yet.
We cleaned him up pretty good,
short of a shower.
- Give them a call. Hurry up.
- Who?
The hospital.
See what they've got to say.
You want us to call Dorothy?
No, I'll do that.
Go on, git.
Both of you.
Tom?
Do you recognize me?
How's your aunt?
Is she doing all right?
Tom?
Can you talk with me?
You've got this whole building
in a stir, you know that?
Tom, do you understand me?
Do you hear me?
Just nod your head
if you hear me.
Just nod your head.
Tom, do you hear me?
Good.
That's all you've got to do.
Now...
whatever you've seen tonight...
wherever you've been...
it's over.
But we can't figure out
where all this blood comes from.
If this person is still alive,
maybe we can help them.
Tom, you understand?
Who were you with tonight?
Where were you?
Can you take us there?
Tom?
Can you take us
to where you were?
You can take us there?
Good boy, Tom.
Good boy.
Les?
- You and Bobby got the left shore.
- Get it, Bobby.
- He didn't want to call state?
- No.
I'm sick of feeling
sorry for this kid.
- What does that mean?
- Why ain't we calling the state?
- The kid's half crazy.
- Sam's got his reasons.
- What are they?
- Glen, what do you want?
Tom, what have you got there?
Tom.
Tom?
God damn it.
Somebody help me.
- Tom.
- It's all right now.
Let it go, Tommy.
- Let it go, Tom.
- Easy, Tom.
Take it easy, son.
Les: It's okay, Tommy.
Sam: Damn!
All right.
Les, get him
back in the car,
and have a doctor
meet us at the station.
- Les: What is it?
- Sam: Can't you do what I ask
without pestering me
with questions?
All right, this is it.
You boys mark off
this whole area.
- It's out here in the water.
- What is it?
What have you got?
Sheriff!
Come on, give us
a hand over here.
Jack: You know,
if you don't marry me
after spending all my time
in the house...
Ainsley: No.
Look out there.
Ain't this beautiful?
Jack: Yes.
- Thank you, Ainsley.
- Let's get out.
I spent a lot of time
as a child on this lake.
- You know what else?
- What?
My mama swears
I was conceived here.
What?
Her and my daddy used
to come up here on weekends.
One time in their senior year,
it happened.
- You mean...
- They got married and had me proper.
I think that's where birth happens
not in some hospital.
- Yeah.
- I was born right here.
My parole officer told me
how your daddy died.
- He did?
- Why you never mentioned it?
Me and my daddy
never got along too good.
- I met the preacher today.
- The preacher?
A preacher.
- He seemed eager to help me out.
- Good.
You don't go to church?
You never wrote about it
in your letters.
No.
What else did
your parole officer say?
He says it won't be
easy finding work.
He says lots of folks
are moving away.
But I'll find something.
I promise.
Jack, I know you will.
Jack?
Yes?
Will you tell me
why you was in prison?
- We've been over that.
- But that was the letters.
Are you afraid
I won't love you?
As far as you and me
are concerned,
I ain't never been to prison.
If you hadn't been to prison
we'd have never met.
I reckon not.
So?
Can I kiss you now?
Yes.
Here I come.
- How was that?
- It was tender.
I ain't done that
in a long time.
- You want to do it again?
- I do.
What's your favorite part of me?
I don't know.
Tell me. And I'll tell you.
Your chest.
Your most beautiful part
are your eyes.
Even my parole officer said so.
He's seen you over at the Red's.
What?
There's something I ain't told you
in the letters.
What?
One of them is glass.
One of your eyes?
- Which?
- This one.
Why?
It got cut out when I was 12.
Me and my friend were playing
with an electric knife.
It don't look glass at all.
It ain't supposed to.
For near two years
I wore a patch,
'cause my daddy said
if God wanted an eye in there,
he wouldn't have let
the real one get cut out.
You wore a patch?
You didn't have nothing in there?
What changed his mind?
When he died...
my mama said, "I'm tired
of looking at you like that. "
So she carried me
down to Oklahoma City
and got me one of these.
It's the only time
I ever been there.
I'm going to take care of you.
I know.
Ainsley?
Yes.
Will you marry me?
- Oh my God.
- I know it's quick.
- You don't have to answer now.
- Shh. No, I will.
I will marry you.
I want us
to have children, Ainsley.
- A family.
- Yes.
- I owe the Lord for setting me free.
- Jack...
I owe him.
It's the most important
thing... children.
Yes.
Jack: Children.
Give us some room now.
Everybody out but Les.
- I'll get the tape on.
- That ain't necessary.
- But...
- Get a notebook.
He's scared enough already
without his every move
getting sucked up
by a video camera.
Hey, kiddo.
The doctor said
you'll be all right.
You're safe here,
you know that?
Tom, you know you're safe?
Now, Tom...
I've got to ask you something.
You just nod yes and no,
but I have to ask you.
Did you do that
to this person?
All right.
I know you didn't.
Did you see it happen?
Did you know that...
All right.
So, the first time
you met was tonight?
What about the person
who's done it?
Did you know him?
Was it a man?
And you didn't know him?
Had you ever seen him before?
Did...
all right.
That's all right, Tom.
Shh.
It's all right.
That's fine for now.
That's just fine.
Get the mug books,
and someone get
his aunt on the phone.
We'll bring some books in here
and then this'll be over.
You've done good.
We'll figure all this out.
Ainsley: Here it is.
This here is the kitchen.
I've got a microwave...
and a four burners,
plus this toaster oven.
Down here is the real oven.
Up here's all the dishes.
You keep a clean house.
And, uh...
through here is the bedroom.
Well, no...
tonight I'll stay on the sofa.
Okay.
Ainsley, keep away.
Ainsley.
All right now.
No, no, no.
That's it. No more.
You're aggressive for someone
who ain't made love ever.
That's why I'm aggressive.
Listen...
I've been locked up
for three years.
I feel that way too.
What happens between
a man and a woman is sacred.
Jack:
It can't be took lightly.
Ainsley: All right.
Jack: We've got to do
everything proper.
Jack: Everything.
- Where are you going?
- Out and around.
Where out and around?
- I don't know.
- Taking Jimmy's car?
Yeah.
When did you say he
and his daddy was coming home?
He didn't say.
Where do you go
when you go off driving?
You're 14 years-old.
Will you answer me, please?
You think it makes me happy
to have another kid to take care of?
I don't know.
What do you want me to do?
Talk with me sometimes.
I got no one to talk with.
My sister's gone,
and I don't ever see my husband.
Stay home tonight.
"CHiPs" in on the cable,
and "Knight Rider"...
you liking cars so much.
I'd rather go out.
- I'll go with you.
- No.
Then you're grounded.
How's that?
I'll microwave us some popcorn...
- and we'll look at the cable.
- I'm leaving.
Tom, I said we're spending
the evening together.
Mind me! I mean it!
I said, mind me!
Get back right now
or don't come back at all.
Come back in right now
or don't come back at all!
Tom!
Woman:
Answer the phone, Will.
Hello?
Hello, Will.
Sorry about the hour.
Will: It's all right.
- How is it with the wife?
- Oh, same.
You'll sort it out.
Listen...
do you mind coming down
to the station?
- Will: What's up?
- It's a little complicated.
We've got a body.
And...
look's like Claire Spencer's boy
got wrapped up in it somehow.
Will?
I'll be right there.
Hey.
Where have you been?
I was worried crazy.
I got a job.
Hello?
Yeah, on for tonight.
All right. Bye.
- Where?
- The DX station.
- We both work on the highway now.
- Doing what?
Mechanic.
I worked all day.
I changed the transmission;
rebuilt two alternators...
- One of them was a Honda.
- That's great, Jack.
Are you all right?
- Red's is closing down.
- What?!
- Red's don't close down.
- They do if nobody's buying burgers.
It may take a while,
but I'll find something else.
Me and Janice will
start looking this weekend.
Why?
I got a job.
We'll be fine.
No, Jack.
I started my period today.
You don't got to say it
outright like that.
I'm sorry.
It's a natural thing.
I told the preacher
I'd bring you to church on Sunday.
Why you told him that?
He keeps asking about you.
I ain't been since I was 14.
Ainsley...
- I want a Christian home.
- It can be as Christian as you like.
I just don't want to go to church.
Ainsley...
things are going so good,
with the job and everything.
Going to church is the only time
I can leave here, except for work.
I want you with me.
All right.
- Is it?
- Yes.
I love you.
Hey, Tommy.
New shoes?
Tom: No.
They're just hand-me-downs.
- Your cousin?
- Yeah.
Listen to me.
Who else, right?
You have a new car?
Are you all alone?
Yeah.
Hey, how's your aunt?
Fine.
She's worried about you.
She said you ain't been coming
to church lately.
- Yeah.
- Come to our church.
- I'll bring you.
- No. I don't think so.
Well...
the Lord help us.
- That'll be all for you?
- Yeah.
You want some beef jerky?
How about jaw-breakers?
Let me show you this.
What do you think?
Nothing else for you then?
No.
Slush Puppy? Coolie?
Slim Jim?
Are you okay?
Who's that lady?
Will: She's going
to church with you?
Jack:
Sunday'll be the third week.
Will:
So married life's all right?
Jack:
Couldn't be better.
I wish
I could say the same.
I'm sorry.
These are strange times
in these parts.
They say, ain't been
this kind of migration out
since the dust bowl.
Almost everyone we service at
the station is just passing through.
They don't live here.
Sometimes I think the reason
she wants a kid so bad
is to have something
to do with her time.
- It's mighty tragic.
- Not that I don't want a child.
I'd love a son.
You and Ainsley
want a family?
There's nothing
more important to me.
All right. That's right.
I just...
you're a lucky man
to have a second chance.
I know that.
I think we'll get
a separation over this.
- That's awful.
- You ain't kidding.
That's all we talk
about anymore.
I'm tired of taking the blame.
I'm sick of playing defense,
you know?
Yeah.
It's...
you don't want to hear this.
Oh, say...
I might be doing that spot check
on you the next couple of weeks.
- You keep saying that.
- It'll happen.
I'm hoping to get your wife
to broil me up a burger.
What, with them
closing down Red's.
Okay.
Do you believe that?
Even Red's turned his back on us.
Oh.
Jack: You know what
I think making love is?
- Ainsley: What?
- Prayer.
When you make love proper...
prayer floats up away from it.
There's no prayer more beautiful
to God than what we've just done.
Do you believe that?
Ainsley: I believe I've never
been happier than right now.
I get restless around the house...
without work.
I miss you.
But you come home and...
hold me.
We make love...
cradle me like you do.
I feel there's nothing left
in this world I can possibly want.
Only to feel your touch.
Jack?
Can I tell you something?
Yes?
Ainsley?
I don't think I believe in God.
That's all right.
It is?
You just ain't found Him yet.
He's in your life.
You just can't see him.
- Don't nobody see God.
- But we see what he do.
That's what faith is.
How do I get faith?
You just got to let go.
Ainsley.
You've got goodness in you.
Whether you believe
in Him or not,
You're as close to God
as near anyone I've met.
I love you.
I mean that.
An angel like you.
He's there.
Ainsley: I hope so.
Jack: Make love
with me again, Ainsley.
- All the blood's off him.
- Sheriff: Uh-huh.
But he still
ain't spoke a word.
He's locked himself
in his room.
When do you have
to go to work?
I got today off.
My husband called a while ago.
Him and Jimmy will be
at the yard all day.
You reckon if this child
had a man figure around
for one day of his life,
he'd be so odd
and in trouble
with the law all the time?
- He ain't in trouble with the law.
- You know how many times
he's been picked up on the highway
for driving that car underaged?
And them patrollers
let him go out of pity.
You'd think a car would be
the last thing he'd want to get in.
Can you explain that one?
A car?
Aunt:
What kind of photo?
We ain't took none recently.
I got some his mama had.
Sheriff:
That'd be fine.
As recent as possible, though.
Someone will be right over.
Aunt: Okay.
Clerk:
You've never seen her?
No.
Clerk:
Her name's Ainsley.
She works at the Red's.
She's married to an ex-con
from McAlester.
He wears a beeper on his leg
so the police
always know where he's at.
I used to always
see her in here.
I ain't seen her lately.
- What is she doing?
- Clerk: What does it look like?
Sitting.
The Oklahoma City bus
dropped her off an hour ago.
Stop staring or
she'll call you over.
So?
Ain't I just told you
her husband's an ex-con?
She looks so sad.
I'm telling you, stay away.
She's a talker.
Why do you keep looking at me?
- Clerk: Too late.
- I don't know.
Come over here.
Don't be afraid.
He's just a kid,
he ain't looking for no trouble.
Ainsley: Come on over.
A closed-circuit TV signal that takes
what happens here in Denver
and sends it all the way back
to a court room in Oklahoma City
appears to be
on the way to reality...
Hey.
RJ say he's been seeing you over
at the Total on his lunch hour.
Ainsley:
I guess so.
Says you sit and talk to folks.
I get lonely.
I have nothing to do all day.
So you hang out at the Total?
I've been going there since
I was old enough to drive.
What do you say to folks?
Is there a problem?
Jack:
No. No problem.
Just...
what do you say to folks?
I ask where they're going
or something.
Just small talk.
I miss people.
- Any news?
- You ask me every day.
Jack:
I want to know.
Christ, we've been
married five months.
- Don't say that word like that.
- What word?
- You know.
- Christ?
- Yes.
- Fine.
- I'm sorry.
- No, I am.
I just want a family.
I want that for us.
So do I.
All my prayers and thoughts
come to what can make us happy.
We'll have a family.
That's all I want.
I want what's best for us.
- You know that?
- Yes.
Listen to me...
I don't want you to leave this house
unless I know where you're going.
- What?
- I mean it.
I want you here.
- I am here.
- I want you here.
I don't want to be wondering
where you are.
- Jack.
- Ainsley, no.
I want a proper home.
A home God would want
to give a family to.
- I'll leave here whenever I like.
- You sure won't.
What you gonna do to me
if I do leave?
I'll bolt these doors.
I mean it.
I could do that.
- You think you're lonely now...
- Jack.
No, that's it.
The discussion's over.
Come here.
I'm Ainsley.
Tom.
I could use some company
for a while.
I don't mean no harm.
I think I might have
left my husband tonight.
Del said...
you've been to Oklahoma City?
It's the second time in my life.
How long was you
and your husband married for?
About six months.
Where are you going?
Just out and around.
Just out and around?
Driving.
I want to go up to the lake.
Are you by yourself?
Yeah.
I don't know is it too safe
up there nights.
Will you come with me...
to the lake?
Yeah.
You take me then.
You take me up there.
Ainsley:
It's where I was born.
You ain't gonna get
to see the Pope.
If you see that Pope,
you'll have to stand out there
with 100,000 other folks...
hoping that he walks
out on that shelf up yonder
on the side of the wall.
You ain't gonna get
to see that Pope...
Well...
Oh God.
Ainsley...
this is what
we've been waiting on.
I know we've been waiting,
Jack.
I met your parole officer.
What?
He came by last Tuesday
while you was at work.
Jack: Yeah?
Ainsley:
And I never let on about this.
- Will: Thank you, ma'am.
- Ainsley: But he told me things.
Will: This is what the state
calls a "spot check. "
The state feels
Jack is rehabilitated...
Rehabilitated. Uh...
but they always say
the spouse should know.
So you probably
know this, but...
- Jack used to live outside Tulsa.
- Yes.
And five years ago,
he was a very different man.
In fact, his turnaround
has been remarkable.
What did he do?
- I don't know what you know.
- I don't know much.
Well, he was
a regular shithead...
excuse me...
- who was going nowhere fast.
- What did he do?
You mean, you never...
you mean, specifically?
Well, I guess...
he nearly beat
a woman to death.
The gal was living
with at the time.
And...
What?
She was carrying
their child at the time.
And what happened to her?
The gal made it.
God.
- Jack.
- I ain't like that no more.
Jack, I told you
that first night we met
that what you did that got you in prison
didn't make no difference to me.
That officer could
have told me anything,
I'd still love you.
But that ain't the point.
I've got nothing left
to give a child.
Let me speak.
I sit here all day.
You won't even let me leave
my own home no more.
I can't even believe
I'm pregnant.
I feel so empty in here.
Keep away.
I've got to make it right.
I want to make it right.
And we ain't right.
I won't hear this.
How can you say
you won't hear this?
I don't want to hear this.
Then...
Jack, that don't make
no difference.
What are you saying?
- Janice told me...
- Don't you think for a second.
It ain't up to you.
- Like hell it ain't.
- Keep away from me.
I ain't going to touch you.
I wouldn't do that.
Honey, you're everything to me.
Look at me.
You're everything.
- Just let me know you hear me.
- I hear you, Jack.
Just tell me
we're going to do this.
- Jack...
- Say it.
- Say we'll do it.
- Keep away.
Say it.
Come on, say we'll do it.
Say we'll do it.
Say the words.
Ainsley: We'll do it.
Do what?
Say it.
We're going to have a child.
Will: It's standard procedure.
A wife should know.
I want another parole officer.
If you want to stay in this county,
you're stuck with me.
Since you're here,
I have some good news.
- You'll be taken off monitoring.
- You nearly ruined my marriage.
Well, take it up
with a marriage counselor.
Ain't you happy?
- Yeah, I'm happy.
- Will: Good.
- Come on in.
- I'd rather not. Thanks.
Fine.
Hello?
Hey...
I've got some good news too.
Janice?
I'm going to be a daddy.
- Is that right?
- Yes, it is.
Really, it's...
so how's Ainsley?
She's great.
- Says she's never been happier.
- That's wonderful.
You don't seem
sincerely excited for me.
What's that supposed to mean?
You just... you don't seem
truly happy for me.
Fuck you.
I didn't say nothing.
I just said
I was going to be a daddy.
You could put your own problems
aside and be happy for me.
- You'd better leave now.
- What?
Get out right now if you know
what's good for you.
Or I'll slap you back on monitoring
for five fucking years!
I'm leaving.
Jack, I'm Sheriff Rogers.
- What's this video camera?
- Standard procedure.
I understand you waived counsel.
- I don't need counsel.
- That's still your right.
You're waiving counsel
for this interview?
- Yes.
- Good.
I'd like to call my wife.
Officer Sprague tells me
you're a religious man.
Yes, I am.
You want to talk with me
about that?
Are you a religious man?
We ain't talking about me.
Jack: You believe in God?
All right, yes, I do.
You ain't got
the slightest idea.
I can hear it
in your voice.
Sheriff:
How should my voice sound?
I want to call my wife.
Sheriff:
How should my voice sound?
Simple. Clear.
Like to answer the question's
almost strange.
Is that how you believe?
Jack: You could never
understand how I believe.
Why?
You haven't been
as far gone as I have.
- How do you know?
- By looking at you.
Okay, fucker.
I've heard enough.
- Will...
- God damn it, I have!
He says another word
and I'll strangle myself.
- Will...
- The state gave you everything.
- It gave you your life back.
- It didn't give me my life.
- Les, get him out of here.
- You'll fry, you prick.
I'm gonna see you fry
if it's the last thing that I do.
"... Fear none of those things... "
- Will...
- Take your hands off me!
I'll be there in the front
fucking row when you go!
You're going to hell!
"Revelation. "
Jack:
You've read the Bible?
It's more
than most Christians.
He's right.
If this goes to trial,
we'll win.
You'll get the chair.
I want that.
I want your life to end.
I used to think
a man's life was God's domain.
But you've changed that.
You remember this child?
He's picked you out
of a mug book.
He looks at your picture
and starts to tremble.
He trembles at the sight
of your photograph.
Tom?
Sheriff:
His name is Tom Spencer.
Will you let me in?
Sheriff:
He's 14 years old.
Aunt: Look, you're gonna
have to say something.
I won't tolerate this no more.
That sheriff keeps calling
and asking how you are.
Tom?
He sent someone over
for a picture of you.
Fancy that, Tom.
Tom?
I'm all right.
Well, okay, then.
I'm going to the kitchen now.
Sheriff:
A year and a half ago,
his mother finished
cooking dinner for him
just after the evening news.
Deedee,
I've got to go out.
Sheriff: And she went to the phone
to call her sister.
A lady who works
at the diner here in town.
And she said,
"Take care of my boy. "
It's yours.
She walked out of her house...
she stepped to the garage...
closed all the doors...
and started her car.
It took 48 minutes.
The boy was a wall away.
When he turned off the TV,
he heard the car.
I wish I could describe to you...
the confusion and terror...
I saw in his eyes
when he'd seen her
being drug out of the garage.
That boy got
nothing to do with me.
We found her body, Jack.
You confess on this tape.
He won't have
to be part of a trial.
The state will use him up
to get to you.
I want him spared that.
I'll get to you anyway.
I won't put this boy
through more.
Maybe God wanted him
to have seen what he's seen.
This got nothing
to do with God.
Everything's got
It's that you
and this whole world's forgot.
Was God with you
on Friday night?
You don't believe that?
I don't see why he'd let that
happen to one of his children.
God ain't about asking why.
You never ask why?
Even if I did,
think I'd hear an answer?
No, I don't.
I can save your life.
I spoke with the DA.
He says if we get a confession,
they won't go for the chair.
You said you wanted me dead.
It's a trade I can live with.
You live, and the boy
is spared all that.
I'll turn this on now.
Jack?
I'll turn this on.
Sheriff: I'm asking you
to see how he is.
I'm tired of this.
All I do
is do for that boy.
This boy ain't got a mama.
Who do you think
has been his mama?
I'm making his favorite supper.
I'm gonna fetch him
when it's ready.
Sheriff: You can't check on it
real quick; right now?
- Aunt: Oh, mercy.
- Sheriff: Please...
I'd like to hear how he is,
and sometimes it's hard to know
through a closed door.
- Aunt: Fine.
- Sheriff: Call me right back.
Hi.
We advise you
to come back in another day.
I can't afford a baby.
I can't afford another
round trip bus ticket.
And you say you're not married?
I'm not married.
- Is that the truth?
- Yes, it's the truth.
Tom?
Your supper's ready.
Aunt: Tom?
Say it to the camera.
It was me who killed her.
You came down from Kingfisher?
Sheriff: Killed who?
Jack:
I killed my wife Ainsley.
Sheriff: Did you know
what you were doing...
and why?
Yes.
I did.
Watch her heel.
Oh God.
Up.
Aunt: All right,
that's enough of this.
I'm coming in.
You hear me? I'm coming in.
Tom?
Tom!
I'll get you down!
Sheriff: Faith.
God tells a man
to sacrifice his son.
The man has faith,
and he will do it.
He doesn't ask why.
At least, Abraham...
as he binds his son,
knows why they're there.
I don't anymore.
I see him everywhere...
a boy I hardly knew.
He doesn't become...
vague...
like most memories.
But clearer...
a ghost...
in perpetual approach.
It lingers in the faces
of my children,
grandchildren...
You drive good.
Sheriff:
And she lingers...
in every woman I'll ever know.
Hey.
Hello?
Ainsley?
- Ainsley: Ain't you gonna get out?
- Tom: You want company?
I don't want
to stand out here alone.
How did you find this place?
My mama brought me here
the day my daddy died.
She knelt right there,
and she prayed.
And her and him
used to come here...
in high school...
for privacy.
How old are you?
- Just turned 14.
- 14?
You don't get pulled over?
Sometimes.
I drive friendly.
Yes, you do.
What do you want to be
when you get older?
I like cars an awful lot.
Oklahoma City?
- A mechanic?
- Yeah.
I was going to open
my own restaurant...
where the oilmen
could come
for steak and potatoes.
I was going
to marry one of them,
have big strong boys.
Is that who you're running from?
- Is it an oilman you married?
- No.
Where did she go?!
A mechanic I married.
So what are you going to do now?
I was hoping coming up here
would help me figure that out.
What are you staring at?
Your eyes.
What about them?
One of them keeps moving off.
- It does?
- Right there.
You want to see something?
- What have you done?
- Don't be afraid.
It's just a glass eye.
Don't get it near me.
It's glass.
It's not my real eye.
Where's your real eye?
It got cut out
when I was a little girl.
When my mama told me
I was going to get a new eye,
I said, make it purple.
'Cause that was
my favorite color.
- The eye ain't purple.
- Of course not.
You're lucky for that.
The preacher says,
people with two different
colored eyes are the devil.
I didn't know that then.
You want to put it back in me?
Not so fast.
Wipe that smudge
from your hand.
Ain't no smudge.
Here.
Hold it soft.
Slow yourself.
- Does it hurt?
- No more than usual.
You've done it real gentle.
Would you come into my arms?
Ainsley: Yes.
Just children.
That's all we are, Lord,
if you're out there at all.
Children.
Your children.
Boys and girls.
Forgive us.