man: Wake the hell up!
You're gonna be late,
doofus.
Sis?
Oh, there you are.
Get your lazy ass goin'.
You're gonna miss
the cheese wagon.
And, no, you can't borrow
my BMX.
It's got a flat.
Jesus, kiddo.
You've seen that movie
damn near 50 times.
You're gonna
wear out the VHS.
Go on.
( school bell ringing )
girl: This is my life.
I'm a 14-year-old girl.
Or... actually,
a hybrid..
girl and boy.
When my mother was alive,
she told me
I was a hermaphrodite.
But my brother just always
called me...
Spork!
( children laughing )
( toilet flushing )
Hey.
The name's Chunk.
Kind of like "chink," but
instead they call me Chunk.
Hi.
My... my name's Spork.
So, Spork, why are you cRyin'
like a little bitch?
Because I'm sick
of being me.
Hey, fuck that shit, man.
Next time
somebody bothers you,
all you gotta do is
close your eyes
and think of something happy.
# Spork and Chunk
sittin' in a tree #
# E-A-T-I-- ##
( giggling )
That's...
- Oh, wow.
- Oh, my gosh!
That is terrible.
I think I can see her
ding-a-ling through her shoRts.
( laughing )
Seriously.
Just close your eyes and think
of some happy shit.
Wow.
( gasping )
... basketball.
Oh, I did not...
( whispering )
She went on
a psychopathic rage.
Nobody even knows
why she did it.
Nobody even
knows where she lives.
I think she's emo, or she,
like, she's crazy.
And maybe she'll...
( rock music playing )
Hey, Spork.
Proud of you today.
School, I mean.
Don't take shit
from people like that.
Oh, yeah,
I fixed my BMX, too.
So take that to
school now.
See, Buster?
Things are already
staRting to change.
Oh, are you hungRy?
( phone ringing )
Hello?
Hella-hella-hello, girl!
Oh, hey, Tootsie Roll.
I heard about your little
run-in with Betsy Byotch.
Mmm!
Can I just say damn!
I'm so proud of you.
And you
got off scot-free.
I don't know, that big brother
of yours is mad fly.
Principal Tulip.
Spit.
"Anyhoo," I'm proud
of you, okay?
About time you
grew a pair of balls.
Oh, uh...
You know what
I mean, girl.
So, listen up.
The school dance-off
is comin' up,
and "yous" knows
I'm all up in that.
Better come this year
and cheer me on.
Hey!
I don't know, Tootsie Roll.
I've never really been
to a school dance or--
or dance-off thingy.
Spork, we're
1 4 years old now.
About time you grow up and stop
playin' with them little,
you know, bonk-ass
toys and get out more.
Damn.
How do you know what I do?
'Cause I live right
next door to you, ho!
"Anyhoo," I need to win
this dance, okay?
'Cause it be
a cash prize of $236.
Oh!
Wait.
Why $236?
Why not 250--
I don't know!
The point is,
with that bling,
I could go see my daddy at
the CherRy Lane PenitentiaRy.
Oh, my mama ain't never
gonna take me.
And I know he'd be happy
as hell to see me up in there.
Girl!
You really think you'll win?
Spork, ain't nobody can
shake their shit in a can
Iike Tootsie Roll, okay?
Shake their what?
So we fittin' to go
and "cele-brizzate"
your victoRy or what?
I don't know.
I mean, I... I still have
some homework to do.
Bitch, please!
Homework can wait, okay?
You kicked a girl's ass today
for the first time.
I'm comin' by after
eight-o-clocky-clock
and pick you up
on my bike.
I just got pegs.
And this Afro Sheen
is off the hook.
Mm-hmm, make my hair
all shiny and shit.
Okay, later, ho.
Ahh!
Oh, yeah, girl!
( knocking )
Oh, my God.
You can't even tell.
I am going to chop off that
bitch's little pecker
the next
time I see her.
Chill out, drama-rama.
At least now you have an excuse
to get a nose job.
I never
wanted a nose job!
"Whatev."
You know what I mean.
I am cereal,
Loosie Goosie!
I have to get her back
somehow.
I am Betsy Byotch!
Nobody gets away
with this.
Even if she is a gimp.
Well, why don't you pants her
in front of the whole school?
That'll upset her.
I could,
but that's not mean enough.
I mean, who cares about her
fucking wee-wee, okay?
I need to
scar her for life.
Like she did moi!
Just wait 'til
I think of something.
She is gonna get it.
( thundering )
Oh, wow, J.Lo used to be a
dancer on "In Living Color"?
So ghetto.
Hey, Spork.
You plannin' on
going somewhere?
Tootsie Roll's gonna take me out
to some place called
Booty Ballroom.
Oh, yeah.
That's a pretty cool shindig,
I mean, if you're
a coal miner at least.
I never hooked up with
no black chick.
Well, don't be
home too late, kiddo.
It's a school night.
Hey.
Spit.
Candice just told me
she's pregnant.
Is it yours, you big idiot?
Does a chicken
have a pecker?
Goddamn it, man, again?
Goddamn it.
Ooh!
Girl, you gotta tell
that hick of a brother of yours
to take a shower.
Damn!
I don't have
anything cool to wear.
Maybe I should just
stay home.
Oh, no, uh-uh.
Let Tootsie Roll
have a look at you.
Girl, you're gonna take all
the attention away from me.
But it is
your night.
Come on, let's go.
( dance music playing
in distance )
Hey, hey!
Oh!
You must be trippin'.
Oh, oh, no.
Twix, this is
a big day for Spork,
and I'm fittin' to show her how
to break it off tonight.
Now move out of my way,
or I'm gonna tell Mama!
( dance music playing )
All right, let me get two
Yoo-hoos, LarRy.
Are you sure
they came in here?
Don't question my logic,
Loosie Goosie.
( dance music playing )
Oh, no.
Oh, no, she stole
that move from me.
Hey, Tootsie Roll,
want to give it a go?
Huh.
Oh, now you all up on me
like we friends?
Let me show you how you're
supposed to break it down.
Ho!
Move out of my way.
Clear the dance floor, hos.
Come on, chocolate.
Move back, chocolate.
Oh, y'all know
the regular.
Back it up more,
back it up more.
Okay.
All right, come on,
play that track, Deejay.
The butterfly
uh-uh that's old
Let me see the Tootsie Roll
Yeah 1994
69 Boyz backed up by
- The Quad City D.J.
- Move, ho!
One time cotton candy
sweet to go
Let me see
that Tootsie Roll
Come on, come on
Tootsie Roll
Just make
that Tootsie Roll
Here we go, here we go
Tootsie Roll
Just make that
Yeah Tootsie Roll
Let me see that
Tootsie Roll
Get off the floor
And make that
Tootsie Roll
To the left, to the left
To the right
to the right
Slide, slide
come on, come on
To the left, to the left
To the right...
Can I make
a request, please?
... to the front to
the back, to the back
Now dip baby come on now
dip baby
( dance music playing )
( record scratching )
( laughing )
I am gonna get that Spork!
Her little
colored friend too.
- What, bitch?
Ahh!
Hey!
# It's peRfect #
# You're in the club
eveRy night #
# 'Cause you love that ooh #
# You're in the club
tRying to fight #
# 'Cause you love that ooh #
#... MaRy Jane #
# I wanna
hit you with the #
# Wanna hit you
with the #
# I-I wanna
hit you with the #
# W-wanna hit you with the #
# I'm gonna
hit you with the #
# Wanna hit you with the #
# The... bass #
# The bass, the bass #
# It's just
the bass, the bass #
# The bass #
# It's just the bass
the bass #
# Bass, bass #
# Like, like, like
you like the bass #
# Bass, bass, bass #
# You, you, you
you like the bass #
# Bass, bass #
# Hey #
# You're in the streets
gettin' rough #
# 'Cause you need that ooh #
# The room goes round
spinning round #
# When you drink that ooh #
# You get kicked out
# 'Cause you're rowdy
when you hear that #
# And you love that #
# You just can't
stop that ##
SorRy.
I'm...
I-- I-- I-- I was just--
just looking at, um...
My tits?
No... I wasn't.
I was-- I-- I was just
looking at your necklace.
It's-- it's really--
it's really pretty.
It... Iooks expensive.
Where'd you get it?
I found it.
Why?
Then why do you wear it?
'Cause, kiddo...
people need to...
feel like they belong to
something in their lives.
You know?
Something bigger than
themselves.
Follow the rules
'cause their parents did.
Be told what to do,
what to believe.
Shit like that, you know?
Basically I wear it so...
I'll fit the fuck in
with eveRybody else.
So...
if I wear one,
then I'll belong, too?
I don't see why the fuck not.
Welcome,
my little stray lamb.
Welcome to salvation.
Today is the last day of your
sinner-life
and the first day of
your new life with Christ,
your Lord and Savior.
So, um, if--
if I join,
I'll belong with you guys?
( giggling )
Of course, silly.
You'll be my sister
in Christ.
Oh, it's so much fun!
And you'll soon learn
that together
we can spread Christ's
love to eveRyone we meet
and bring them to
salvation.
Together.
You-- you--
you really mean it?
Shh now.
I'm not gonna huRt you.
I'm your friend.
What's your name, sweetie?
Sp... Spork.
Well, a-a-actually,
it's more of a nickname.
Hmm.
That's an interesting name.
Why do they
call you that?
( laughing )
What?
Well, "Spark," or...
whatever.
I really don't
think someone like you
would make a veRy good addition
to God's army of goodness.
I mean, really now.
God made man
in his own image,
and I highly doubt that
includes you,
my dear, sweet harlot.
So...
Shut up!
SorRy, Spork.
Just tRying see
if I could cop a feel.
Please don't touch me.
( children laughing )
That's enough.
You brats!
Now show some "ratitude."
There will be a test
later on this week.
And none of you
can afford to fail.
All right.
Now this here is the uterus,
in which the fetal canal carries
a child upon biRth.
( sighing )
Can anyone tell me what we
learned in chapter one
about another
way to give biRth?
Yeah, from your ass.
( children laughing )
Maybe yours,
you little faiRy.
No.
Actually, there has never been
a case in which one was born
out of another's anus.
In any event,
the male reproductive organs
play just as impoRtant a role
as the female's.
ObseRve.
Here we have the penis.
Within the penis
is the urethra.
It's also...
( school bell ringing )
Hey, Spork.
You know, you shouldn't
be upset.
I mean, trust me.
People always knock me
because I have two gay dads.
Like, screw them, man.
I'm proud of
my gay parents.
And you should be proud of
being a lesbian.
I'm not a lesbian, Charlie.
Well, whatever you
wanna call it then.
Confused.
I'm not confused either,
Charlie.
Just because you're gay,
doesn't mean eveRybody else is.
Whoa, whoa, wait, wait, wait.
What?
I said my dads are gay.
I'm not a fuckin'
faggot.
Aw!
Screw you, you mutant.
Watch it, homo.
Look out, ho!
Ooh.
My bad, girl.
I didn't even see you.
Listen, me and my hos are gonna
practice a little booty shakin'.
Why don't you come with us?
I know you ain't
gonna let this white girl
come with us to practice.
You know whiteys
ain't allowed to pop it.
Bitch, silence that hole,
and respect my girl.
Okay?
She is my neighbor,
and I got her back.
Hear that?
Mmm, come on, let's go.
Come on, Spork.
# Ding-ding-ding-a-ling #
# Ding-a-ling #
Spork, let's go!
# Ding-ding-ding-a-ling #
# Ding-a-ling #
# Shake your
ding-a-ling #
# Ding-a-ling #
# Shake your
ding-a-ling #
# Ding-a-ling #
# Shake your
ding-a-ling #
# Ding-a-ling #
# Ding-ding-ding-a-ling #
# Hey little thing #
# Shake that
ding-a-ling #
# Shake, shake it just
don't break it #
# Hey little thing
shake that ding-a-ling #
# Don't fake it move 'til you
make it #
# Hey little thing
shake that ding-a-ling #
# Shake, shake it just
don't break it #
# Hey little thing
shake that ding-a-ling #
# D-d-ding-a-ling #
# Now left... #
The butterfly
uh-uh that's old
Let me see the Tootsie Roll
Yeah 1994
69 Boyz backed up by
the Quad City D.J.
One time cotton candy
sweet to go
Let me see that Tootsie Roll
Come on, come on
Tootsie Roll
Just make
that Tootsie Roll
Here we go Tootsie Roll
Just make that
Tootsie Roll
Yeah Tootsie Roll
Let me see that
Tootsie Roll
Make that Tootsie Roll
To the left, to the left
To the right
to the right
To the front, to the front
To the back
to the back
Don't be-- Oh!
Girl, you're gonna have to
turn your head that way.
... Just slide baby slide
just slide baby slide
Come on, come on
To the left, to the left
To the right...
Oh, shit, oh!
Damn!
That shit must've "huRted"
for "reals."
You okay?
Ouch.
Ow, ow, damn.
Ow, watch it, Spork.
Damn, you know my shit is
busted.
I-- I-- I'm sorRy.
Why you sorRy?
It was my damn fault I didn't
rinse all that Afro Sheen
before I went
and acted a fool.
You were amazing,
by the way.
I mean...
the way you dance, it--
It was like no other kind of
dancing I've ever seen.
Does it huRt?
Not like this.
Usually it's like...
it's like I'm not
Tootsie Roll no more.
Like I'm some other
person...
doing my thing.
Somewhere far, far away
from this shithole.
And I can be
anybody I wanna be.
You know?
"Anyhoo," I'm over this shit.
I don't wanna
see my daddy no way.
He's probably busy and all
tRying to hold down the Bloods.
He's their leader
on the inside.
- You know?
- Wow.
He sounds impoRtant.
Well, what-- what if--
what if one of your friends
could do the dance-off
for you...
and give you the money?
Girl, what kind of world
is you livin' in?
Ain't no girls of mine
gonna give me no money
to see my daddy.
They got
their own dreams.
But-- but, I mean, if they're
your real friends--
I got no real friends, okay?
None of us do.
That's the way
it is in the hood.
You know that.
You live here, too.
I mean, Spork, who you know that
would do that for you, girl?
I don't know.
No one, I guess.
Ooh, girl.
You just saw
a shooting star.
Make a wish, Spork.
Damn, I hope you made a wish
for both of us.
'Cause I'm definitely
getting up outta here
when I'm all grown-up like.
Girl, get your ghetto broke ass
in this house right now.
It's way past
your bedtime.
All right, I gotta bounce.
Thanks for
helping me home, Spork.
No problem.
I'm right next door
if you need me.
Yeah, okay.
Later, chickenhead.
You keep playing
with that he-boy-she-boy,
you're gonna fuck around
and grow a ding-a-ling.
Get in here.
- What's wrong with you?
- Mom!
Shut up, damn!
I read that on TV,
I read it on TV!
Spork: This is
where my mommy sleeps.
Spit didn't have any money to
buRy her proper-like,
so we put her back here
until we get some
money to do it right.
When our dog Buster died,
Spit tried to
throw him in the garbage,
but I pulled him out
and kept him.
Spit said he
doesn't care neither way,
'cause Buster was
better off dead
and Mom was just a stupid whore
who left us like daddy did.
But... sometimes
I hear Spit late at night,
coming out here and
talking to her.
I even heard him cRy once,
though he'd die before
he'd admit it.
When I dream some nights,
I see her.
She has long,
flowing brown hair
and big green-blue eyes,
Iike one of those pretty ladies
on infomercials late at night.
I used to lay right up
against the stone at night
when I couldn't sleep.
Pretend she was there
laying with me.
But now there's
all these weeds over her stone
that I'm allergic to.
Had to go to
the hospital once even.
Said I would have died if I
stayed around them long enough.
woman: Are you
tired of being you?
Then wake up!
Mama?
That's right.
I am here to
help you be the real you.
Are you tired of feeling down,
being laughed at?
Well, so was I.
I know it's hard to believe,
but, yes,
I was once ugly like you.
I, too, was like you--
alone, ugly, ethnic-looking
and sad.
You too, Mommy?
But not anymore!
Since Thermo Ball Blasting
Technique,
I've lost over
150 pounds in just five days!
With little or no scarring,
and minimal heart failure,
I feel great now!
Get off me, Buster!
It is you, Mommy!
This can make me
a real girl.
A pretty girl
like you, Mommy.
So call now.
Your dreams can
come true for you.
All you have to do
is dream them.
Financing is
available at only 200 down.
What are you waiting for?
The new world order
is coming.
Call now!
The dance-off prize.
Thank you, Mommy.
Thank you.
( whistle blowing )
All right, fellas,
come on, line up, quick.
Hustle, hustle, hustle.
All right, shiRts, skins,
shiRts, ski--
Hey.
Hey, Twinkle Toes.
Let's see that
body of yours.
( snickering )
Oh, my God,
look at this fag.
Looks like he's dead, bro.
- Are all fags this white, bro?
- It's major.
Come on, dudes.
I get pussy all the time.
Just don't wanna wrinkle
at a young age.
SPF, bros.
Hey, Sporky, wait up.
Listen, I'm sorRy for being
such a fag earlier.
Don't say that word.
Why not?
It's only mean
if you're a fag.
It's mean no matter what,
Charlie.
Okay... I'm sorRy.
Listen.
I saw you on
the dance-off list.
I can't believe it.
What are you
gonna do?
I... I don't know.
I mean, I-- I haven't really
thought about it yet.
Didn't sign myself up.
I'm not really
a dancer.
But, literally, I know all
the Justin Timberlake moves
by heaRt.
So, tell me
if you need any help.
Thanks, Charlie.
- Let's go.
- Oh, my God, they're coming.
Alli vienen las bitches!
# Is it 'cause
I'm cool? #
# Why you dress like me? #
# Is it honesty
or you just a fool? #
# Is it 'cause I'm cool? #
# Why the schoolkids
laugh #
# 'Cause the papers
got it wrong again #
# Is it 'cause I'm cool? #
# Take a piece
of me #
# SeRve me up
on a plate #
# In your restaurant #
# Is it 'cause I'm cool? #
# Is it 'cause
I'm cool? #
# Is it 'cause I'm fly? #
# 'Cause I said
what I said #
# When I said what I said #
# But I didn't say #
# Is it 'cause I'm hip? #
# Why you dig my shit
and you say I'm a fan #
# Now I understand #
# Is it 'cause I'm hot? #
# Why you mention me #
# In your
VIP memoRy #
# Is it 'cause I'm cool? #
# No one really
cooler ##
Oh, well, if it isn't
the little she-he
and the amazing Faggotron.
Shut up, Byotch.
You're just mad 'cause I took
your virginity and dumped you.
Please.
You couldn't get it up
if your daddies asked you to.
And I'm sure they do.
By the way, nice eye shadow,
Twinkle Toes.
So your color.
( laughing )
# Hit me baby
one more time #
Ooh, ooh!
That's not even Timberlake.
That's stupid Britney Spears,
a-holes.
Don't you dare
tell me about
Britney Spears.
She is a god to me,
you maggot.
Why don't-- why don't you
just leave him alone, Betsy?
Hmm, so "it" speaks.
I've been waiting for this for
some time now.
You and I have
a little unfinished business
to do, he-she!
Don't do it, Spork.
If you get in trouble, you won't
be allowed to do the dance-off.
Well, well, well.
So, Sporky the Dorky
thinks that she has a shot
at winning my dance-off, huh?
It's not your dance-off,
Byotch.
Oh, but it
will be, sister.
It will be.
Hey, you funny-lookin'
little white girls!
That's enough of that.
Get your little skinny asses
to class, pronto!
And that means you too, Spork.
( laughing )
Meet me after school tomorrow.
I'll teach you all I know about
Justin Timberlake.
There's no way
you're gonna lose.
Oh.
Hey, Chunk.
Hey, Spork.
So, um, thanks for
the advice the other day.
It kind of changed my life.
So I heard.
Got Betsy Byotch
dead in the face.
Pretty fuckin' rad.
( dance music playing )
Chunk?
Hey, were you
just gonna ride home,
or do you have time to hang?
Could maybe come
with me to my mom's restaurant
and help out in exchange for
some more advice.
( horn honking )
Holla!
So...
this is where
you work after school?
Kinda.
It's not like work-work.
I don't get paid
or anything.
I just fill out these little
papers with sayings and shit.
"Never take for granted
the things that matter
least in life."
My mom has me
help her with writing out
all the foRtune cookies.
- By hand?
- "Yeppers."
Cheaper, it keeps me busy
and out of trouble.
So, Spork, word is you're
hangin' with Twinkle Toes
and gearing up to tRy and win
the dance-off.
Don't be neRvous, kiddo.
You just keep doing
what you're doing,
no matter what anyone says.
Charlie, the dance-off--
none of it really matters.
All that matters is that you
give both a shot.
You hear me?
( woman speaking Mandarin )
Wh-- what was she saying,
Chunk?
She said you look
pretty dressed like that.
( dog barking )
# Hey #
# Hey ##
Hey, Spit, can I talk to you
for a minute?
What's up, kiddo?
Well, if you liked
somebody, what would you do?
Are you pregnant, Spork?
No, Spit.
Did you get someone
pregnant, Spork?
No, Spit.
Well, then, I guess
I'd probably tell 'em.
But tell them what?
That I wanted to
get 'em pregnant.
Look, Spork...
it just happens, you know.
Like...
when you're with someone,
it just happens or it don't.
There ain't no special words
or nothin' like that.
It's like, uh, us guys,
we just follow our dicks,
and you girls--
- Never mind, Spit.
- Oh.
I was gonna say...
you girls
follow your heaRts.
Hey, come here, kiddo.
Take this.
It'll help.
( sighing )
# One, two, three #
# So I woke up
early this morning #
# And I walked to the
five-and-dime #
# I saw this young lady #
# That's what she looked like
from behind #
# I tapped her
on the shoulder #
She's weird.
# Excuse me, ma'am #
# She looked back at me
and said #
# I'm half-man #
# Whoa #
# Spork #
# Phew #
# That girl #
# Whoa #
# Spork #
# Phew #
# That girl #
# That-that-that-that-that
that-that girl #
that-that-that-that-that #
# That-that girl #
# Spork ##
( phone ringing )
Y'ello?
I have a favor
to ask you, okay?
And-- and please say yes,
please.
Well, that
depending on what it be.
Um, can you teach me
to dance?
Dance like you do?
I'm-- I'm competing in
the school dance-off,
and I don't think I've ever
danced in my entire life.
Girl, you must be trippin'.
Of course I'll help you,
you my girl.
I am?
Yeah.
You brought my broke ass home,
didn't ya?
But I thought you said
that we didn't have any friends
in the hood.
Spork, I said I'd help.
This ain't no Oprah,
so shut the hell up.
Come by the gymnasium tomorrow
during lunch.
Me and my hos
will hook you up.
Thanks, Tootsie Roll.
Oh, and Spork?
Wear sneakers.
Okay.
We can do this, Dorothy.
We can do this.
Okay, now, Treena, show Spork
the dookie dump.
Girl, you better
ask somebody.
Mm-hmm.
# Hit it #
Now this is
the dookie dump.
Okay, now, Spork,
you tRy the dookie dump.
# It was me
and the posse with... #
Um...
I'm-- I'm--
Damn, bitch!
Do like I say.
# Lo and behold there
appeared a mirage #
# He was hooking up a car
in his daddy's garage #
# We stopped short #
Oh!
# Did a double take #
Th-that's it, girl,
you almost got it.
Okay, now tRy to
stick your ass out more.
( laughing )
N-no, no, no.
Like this.
Boom, boom, boom,
boom, boom.
No, honey.
You need to move it,
rock your hips.
Boom, boom, boom, boom.
Little-- little
bit better, but...
Yeah.
That's it, girl.
Now let's tRy this.
Move it to the side.
Okay, girl.
Go, girl.
You've gotta be kidding me.
They're teaching her
how to dance?
If you could call it that.
Looks more like
some tribal ritual.
I hope she's the sacrifice.
I just got an idea.
Let's go ahead and allow
Sporky Dorky to compete.
It might just be the best
peRformance yet.
( giggling )
You are so
over-the-top sometimes.
Hey, Spork.
Hey, Charlie.
You ready?
I don't know.
Tootsie Roll tried to teach me
during lunch,
but I just can't
get my ass to move like hers.
( chuckling )
Come on, Spork.
Don't be so hard
on yourself.
I'll teach you all I know.
I have the whole
DVD collection
of all the Justin Timberlake
conceRts.
He'll show us what to do.
Come on!
( dance music playing )
Okay, Spork, watch.
Watch.
There!
Did you just see that?
Oh, my God,
he's so utterly amazing.
Did you know he's actually
a natural blonde?
Oh, my God.
You know Dorothy?
Hmm, yeah.
My mom got that for me
for my biRthday.
Pretty stupid, I know.
But it...
Iooks different.
And...
why is Dorothy white?
And where's
the city skyline?
Spork, you're talking about
"The Wiz."
That's the black version.
Oh.
Really?
Wow, I-- I never knew.
That's... that's weird.
I have the same exact poster on
my wall, except...
"The Wiz" poster.
That's my favorite movie.
I've never seen
"The Wiz,"
but that one right there,
that's my favorite movie.
Sometimes I pretend I'm Dorothy,
and I sing.
# Troubles melt
like lemon drops #
# Far above the chimney tops #
# That's where #
# You'll find me ##
Wow.
I never knew I'd tell anyone
that before.
Me neither.
My mom, when I was four,
went to go see
the Land of Oz.
I was mad at her, 'cause she
wouldn't take me,
but...
now I know that
she's happier over there.
See, she's like Dorothy.
She wants to
help eveRyone,
so she's gonna stay in Oz so she
can help people.
She has friends like
Michael Jackson, Tin Man.
You know... friends.
But I don't-- I don't even think
she's looking for
the Wiz anymore.
She's probably happy.
I'm gonna go there
soon too.
I'll... take you
with me, if you want.
I-- I-- I mean, you don't
have to.
I just--
I mean, if you wanted to--
Spork.
Dorothy's black.
So what?
Maybe my mom is black.
You don't know.
Maybe-- maybe in Oz,
you turn black.
I'm just sayin'.
I mean, I wouldn't
mind being black.
That's not the point.
You're weird.
I want to go home.
Wait.
Don't go.
What's your favorite color?
- Green.
- Why?
Because without the green ones,
they're boring.
Yeah, they are kind of boring
without the green ones.
They all kinda look the same.
Is it true?
Is what true?
I wanna go home.
Then go.
# This heaRt is over
the stars #
# This heaRt
is over the moon #
# But fate is filled... #
Please don't
laugh at me.
I think you're pretty.
Do you think
I'm pretty?
I think
you're veRy pretty.
# They shout aggression
at me #
# This lands there
on the wall #
# This life
is far too... ##
I'm-- I'm gonna win
the dance-off, Mommy.
I don't know how, but...
I'm gonna win.
And I'm gonna use the money to
be pretty like you.
And I made a friend.
A real one
this time.
He's really nice, too.
Mommy,
he's coming with me...
to see you in Oz.
He... he already knew about it
even before I met him,
but... he--
Well-- well, kind of,
but...
it was some
other version.
But it was pretty close.
Thanks, Mommy.
Damn, Spork!
You don't know how to
tell no time?
I'm sorRy.
My book bag broke open,
and I lost one of my books.
( laughing )
Hey, shut them holes,
chickenheads!
Like any of y'all know how
to read a damn book no way!
Mmm.
"Anyhoo,"
you been practicing?
Well, yeah, but...
I just can't do it,
Tootsie Roll.
I practiced all night.
Damn, child!
Ain't you good at anything?
Well, I'm really good
at Twister.
Ooh, girl!
I think I got an idea!
# Supersonic #
Okay, here it be, girl.
I'm fittin' to
yell out these colors,
and you just gonna do
your thing.
You dig?
Spork: I-- I-- I dig.
Okay, all right then.
So let's do this!
#... rockin'
your world #
# Supersonic #
Right hand on red.
Right foot on blue.
Listen...
Right hand on yellow.
Left foot on green.
Right hand on blue.
Left foot on yellow.
Left hand on blue.
Right hand on green,
left foot on red.
Right foot on yellow.
Green, yellow, red.
Blue, yellow, blue.
Red, red.
R-R-Red.
Yellow, yellow, yellow.
Red, green, red, yellow, blue,
red, yellow, green.
Yellow, red, green.
Red, red, red, green,
yellow, red...
Damn, child.
You just might win this shit
after all, girl.
# Hey white spoRt #
# Do the funky Watusi #
# Hey little mama #
# Why you get
so funky? #
# Hey little mama #
# Why you get so funky? #
# Yeah white spoRt #
# Do the funky Watusi #
# Hey white spoRt #
# Hey little mama #
# Why you get so funky? #
# Why you get
so funky? #
# Yeah white spoRt #
# Do the funky Watusi #
# Hey white spoRt #
# Hey little mama #
# Why you get so funky? #
# Yeah white spoRt #
# Do the funky Watusi #
# Hey white spoRt #
# Hey little mama #
# Why you get so funky? #
# Yeah white spoRt #
# Do the funky Watusi #
# Hey white spoRt #
# Hey little mama #
# Why you get so funky? #
# Yeah white spoRt #
# Do the funky Watusi #
# Hey white spoRt #
# Hey little mama #
# Why you get so funky? #
# Yeah white spoRt #
# Do the funky Watusi #
# Hey white spoRt #
# Hey little mama #
# Why you get so funky? #
# Funky, funky
funky, funky ##
( laughing )
We are about to staRt rehearsals
for the dance-off.
I want each
and eveRy one of you
to understand
that this is
not a competition,
but simply
a means to have fun.
Of course, there will be
a winner
and a whole bunch of losers.
You will be judged by
the audience cheering,
so be sure to invite
all of your friends.
Now, remember, only those
competing can be in here.
The rest of you, wait outside.
Okay.
First up, we have Spork
and Her Only Friends.
My name is Spork
and that's no lie
If you don't like me you
should see my ride
( laughing )
But don't laugh at me
and be such a "meanie"
'Cause I got
a really small wee-wee
( laughing )
Gotcha.
Bitch.
( laughing )
Spork, wait!
Don't listen to them!
Hey, girl,
where you runnin' off to?
Hey, I'm talkin'
to you, ho!
( dog barking )
( dog yelping )
Ow!
You stupid ball!
You stupid, stupid ball!
I hate Spork!
I hate her!
And you're dead!
You're not real!
Nothing is real!
( cRying )
Why didn't you
take me with you?
Why, huh?
Why did you
lie to me?
You said I'd be pretty
like you!
I hate you!
I don't want you
to ever come back!
Ever, ever, ever!
I believed you.
Why did you have to
go without me?
I don't wanna
ever wake up.
Never, ever, ever.
Looks like
the champ is up.
What happened?
Well, I think you went and acted
a fool is what happened.
They laughed at me, Spit.
All of them.
I-- I have to move.
Go away somewhere.
Where you gonna go?
Oz?
There is no Oz, Spit.
Yeah.
I thought
you'd say that.
Saw your poster
on the floor.
Still, I figured you
might want it back up
before you woke up.
I don't.
Thank you for fixing it,
but it's just a stupid poster.
EveRything is stupid.
Is it now?
Oh, my God.
I'm-- I'm not dead.
But the weeds and...
I'm allergic and--
Well, last time, I--
That was then, Spork.
People change.
They grow up.
Get stronger.
I don't.
I won't change.
I'm just Spork forever.
And what in the hell's wrong
with that, little sis?
EveRything.
Is it now?
Well, seemed pretty tough
to me last night.
You could hear me?
Spork, I think the whole
trailer park could hear you.
Why didn't you
do something?
I did.
I let you give off some steam,
and there ain't nothin' wrong
with that, Sporky.
And I'll tell
you something else.
You're more like our mama than
anybody else I ever seen.
What was she like?
She was like you.
Different.
In more ways than one.
EveRybody thought
she was crazy.
Damn near was,
to tell you the truth.
Scared off Daddy real quick,
I used to think.
But...
she was...
different in a lot of
good ways, too.
Daddy used to
get pretty rough with me.
She'd come a-runnin' out,
hollerin', her hair all
frizzy-like,
and chase him
off with a shovel.
That was Mama for you.
And I'll tell you
something else.
When she was sick,
and you were just a baby,
she'd always tell me she wasn't
leavin' to go nowhere.
Just to go see Oz.
And that she'd be
waitin' for us there.
But there is no Oz, Spit.
I've looked,
and she's not there.
Sporky...
you just been lookin' in
all the wrong places.
You see, Oz...
... it's right here.
And that's where Mama's been
waitin' for you all along.
She ain't goin' nowhere.
And neither am I, Spork.
All right,
that's enough of that shit.
Clean up this
diRty-ass room.
Oh, and wipe your face.
You got
a milk mustache.
SorRy, Dorothy.
I was upset and...
I didn't mean to
take it out on you.
Oh, my God!
The dance-off!
( phone ringing )
Girl, I can hear you dialing my
number from out the window!
I need to
ask you another favor.
Can you help me pick out an
outfit for the dance-off?
You really
gonna do this?
Definitely.
Well, then come on, ho!
We ain't
got all day!
I like rainbow sprinkles on my
ice cream pie
Yeah right
Meet me at
the ice cream truck
I'll buy you an ice cream
I'll whip out
my drumstick...
Okay, honestly,
does it look any better?
Do you really want to know?
I don't seem to remember you
having that attitude
when I first met you, Loosie.
I sure hope you haven't
forgotten
the dark ages, Loosie Goosie.
You know, before I taught you
the effects of highlights
and bleached
teeth and eye shadow.
Or do I need to pull out
a photo?
Glamour Shots
circa '98 much?
Oh, I'd like to see that.
You know I've heard about
those photos.
I'm fine, Byotch.
I'm just totally over your
cunt-fest in the late.
Like, I love
my bitch points too,
but you've been acting
all "psycho-fied."
I mean, that shoe polish
really messed up my pores.
- Yeah, for sure.
- Def.
Sacrifices had to be made,
my little second-in-command.
Really?
'Cause I didn't
see you wearing any.
Ladies, let's not quarrel
before my--
our... big debut.
Tonight is about
Britney Spears.
Tonight is the night we show her
our gratitude for what
she's taught us.
And I know
I've been a bit harsh lately,
but now that Spork is over
and done with,
Iet's move on and remember
the sisterhood of the bitches.
And that Spork was just
a taste...
of my rage.
Now, are you
with me, bitches?
For sure!
# We like the cars #
# The cars
that go boom #
"Oh, that light is so harsh."
Blanche DuBois,
Tennessee Williams.
Thank you.
Welcome, all of you,
for the biggest moment
in all of your lives,
and one of mine,
the CherRy Lane Middle School
Dance-Off!
( cheers and applause )
Now, I know
that you are all
as excited as I am
to see our shining young stars
hit the stage
and show us
exactly what they're made of.
# Beat, beat, beat, beat #
# Beat #
# Hey, hey, hey #
# Come on eveRybody #
# Beat ##
So, without fuRther ado,
we kick off
the dance-off first with
Betsy Byotch
and the Bitches!
( cheers and applause )
# Oh baby, baby #
# How was I
supposed to know #
# That something wasn't
right here #
# Oh baby, baby #
# I shouldn't
have let you go #
# And now you're right out
of sight yeah... #
Okay, okay.
Move outta my way, hos.
Damn, that's
a big-ass hat.
- Whoo, that's a big-ass hat.
- Stupid hat!
This ain't no Vegas.
#... is killin' me and I #
# I must confess #
# I still believe #
# Still believe #
# When I'm not with you
I lose my mind #
# Give me a sign #
# Hit me baby
one more time #
# My loneliness
is killing me #
Okay, you ready for this?
A'ight then.
All right, I'm fittin' to be
right here,
yelling out the orders.
Whatever you do,
don't stop.
# And give me a sign #
# Hit me baby
one more time ##
( cheers and applause )
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
That was quite a show!
Let's hear it for
Betsy Byotch and the Bitches!
( cheers and applause )
The little bitches.
You've gotta be
kidding me.
What are those
things doing here?
Looks like not eveRybody
is scared of you.
Oh, uh...
Okay, okay, quiet now!
Quiet, quiet!
Now, there's been a change in
the schedule,
apparently, I believe.
Uh...
Well, yes.
There's been a change
in the schedule.
Hmm.
Next up will be
a peRformance given by J--
( feedback blaring )
What the fuck
is this about?
# Lady boy, lady boy #
# This groove
is for my girls #
# Little lady boys and girls #
# This groove
is for my girls... #
Right hand on yellow!
Right hand on red!
# This groove
is for my girls #
# Little lady
boys and girls #
Left foot on blue!
# Lady
boys and girls #
# This groove is for my girls #
# Little lady
boys and girls #
- Whoa.
- Whoa, girl.
# Nobody rocks like the girls
I'm running with #
Damn!
#... everybody's in on it #
# Some girls talk to the boys
in the chat room #
# My girls talk to
the boys in the back room #
# Hit me up I'm that chick
you know #
# That my world one stop
if you clock me #
# You got me #
# Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh #
# You got me going #
Damn, baby.
# Little lady boys and girls #
# This groove
is for my lady boy #
# Lady boys and girls #
# This groove
is for my girls #
# Little lady
boys and girls #
lady boys and... #
# This groove is for my girls #
# Little lady boys
and girls #
# This groove is for lady boys
lady boys and girls #
# This groove is for my girls #
# Little lady boys
and girls #
# This groove is for lady boys
lady boys and girls #
# This groove is for
lady boys lady boys and girls #
# Little lady boys and girls ##
( cheers and applause )
Shut up, shut up,
all of you.
Stop it!
( cheers and applause )
This is all 'cause of you,
Tootsie Roll.
Thank you.
Girl, don't even play.
I don't know what the hell you
did out there,
but it wasn't
for sure nothin' I taught you.
Get it, girl.
Get it for reals.
( cheers and applause )
Quiet!
Quiet, quiet!
Quiet, shh!
Shut up!
Thank you.
Well, I must say, this is
quite a surprise indeed.
In all fairness,
I think the winner has already
been decided.
Too bad, bunnies.
This was a real shocker,
wasn't it, kids?
The winner is...
( imitating fanfare )
The winner is Spork!
( cheers and applause )
all: Spork, Spork, Spork!
Spork, Spork, Spork,
Spork, Spork, Spork!
Spork, Spork!
Spork, Spork, Spork,
Spork, Spork, Spork, Spork!
Spork, Spork, Spork, Spork,
Spork, Spork...
( cheers and applause )
Tootsie Roll, um, I--
I know you said we're not
supposed to have
any friends in the hood.
But you're the closest thing
I've ever had to a real friend.
And...
I want you to have this.
Okay?
Spork, I--
I can't take this.
You earned it, girl,
you worked hard.
I'm cool.
I'm not
worried about that.
I-- I know you're cool.
But, again,
you're my friend.
And that's what
friends do.
At least my friends.
It's yours,
you earned it.
Sweet!
Oh!
You're the coolest white bitch
I know, Spork.
- Thanks.
- Hear that, okay?
Okay.
Come on, y'all,
let's go.
- Bye, Spork!
Later, Charlie,
bye, Spork.
This is it, tripod!
You may have convinced
the school that you're normal,
but I am so gonna pound
your face in!
Oh, shut
the fuck up already!
Jesus.
You are so drama-rama.
You know what, bitch?
I have just about had it
with your insubordination.
Uh!
Shit, dude, that bitch
was so annoying.
Wow, that was amazing.
The name's Chunk.
Kinda like "chink," but instead
they call me Chunk.
Loosie Goosie.
Kinda like Lucy,
but they call me Loosie.
So, what you did with
Tootsie Roll and the money--
that was pretty cool.
She's my friend.
That's what friends do.
Hey, Spork,
can I ask you something?
Sure.
If you've
never had a friend...
how do you know what a friend
would do?
'Cause...
it just feels right.
Yeah.
Spork?
Yeah, Charlie.
Will you be
my girlfriend?
Sure.
Yes!
Spork: And that was
my first boyfriend.
Made my first friend
and boyfriend
in one awesome day.
It's funny, really,
when Charlie asked me
how I ever really knew what
a good friend would be like.
'Cause I really never did know.
But there's a lot of things
I still don't really know.
Why people say mean things
or huRt other people when
they're different.
I don't think
I'll ever know.
The truth is...
I don't wanna know.
'Cause, you see,
it doesn't matter.
All that matters is the people
we care about
and the ones
who care about us.
See, Mommy...
you made it.
You made it
to the Emerald City.
I used to think that
my only dream
was to be someone else...
anything else
than what I was.
And somehow I got it.
I finally figured out
how to be somebody
I never really ever
got to be in my whole life.
Myself.
# Hey #
# Ooh-ah #
# Hey-hey-hey-hey-hey-hey #
# You you're such a freak #
# When you're at the paRty you
don't mess with a freak #
# Ooh you're such a dork #
# Nobody kisses you
on the dance floor #
# Pick your boogie #
# Then dance #
# Pop your booty #
# Throw up your hands #
# You don't hear them #
# When they
staRt to jam #
# Hey you you're
such a freak #
# When you're at the paRty you
don't mess with a freak #
# You ain't got no money #
# You ain't
got no friends #
# You just came to paRty #
# You just
want to dance #
# You don't even hear them #
# When they
staRt to jam #
# Ooh you're such a dork #
# Nobody kisses you
on the dance floor #
# You just want to join
the paRty #
# You just
want to do your dance #
# You ain't tRying to
huRt nobody #
# You ain't
tRying to make no friends #
# EveRything and eveRybody
always has to disappear #
# When you staRt
to feel your body move #
# And you don't even care #
# Hey you
you're such a freak #
# When you're at the paRty you
don't mess with a freak #
# Ooh you're such a dork #
# Nobody kisses you
on the dance floor #
# Hey ##
# Magic #
# Oh, oh, oh, oh #
# Oh, oh #
# Magic #
# Look what I got
in my bag of tricks #
# Magic hats and a house
of bricks #
# Now I can do
anything I need #
# All I gotta do
is believe #
# Wake up early
in the morning #
# I hear my world and it is
hollering #
# EveRything is
just bright okay #
# Thing are gonna be
all right okay #
# Oh, oh, oh #
# It's just
a little bit of magic #
# Just a little bit
of magic #
# And things will be okay #
# Oh, oh, oh #
# It's just
a little bit of magic #
# Just a little bit of magic #
# And we'll be
on our way #
# Let me pull this
rabbit outside my hat #
# Damn you ain't seen nothing
like that #
# I feel like
I'm on top of the world #
# With the stars in the sky
I'm the only girl #
# Time moves by so quickly #
# Something's
changed inside of me #
# I might not be what you
want to see #
# But eveRything
will be all right for me #
# Oh, oh, oh #
# It's just
a little bit of magic #
# Just a little bit
of magic #
# And things
will be okay #
# Oh, oh, oh #
# It's just
a little bit of magic #
# Just a little bit
of magic #
# And we'll be on our way #
# And it all
feels like #
# A little bit of magic #
# And it all feels like #
# A little
bit of magic #
# A little bit of magic #
# Well #
# I'm gonna see life
in 3-D #
# Daydream
covered in sunshine #
# Skies of bubbles #
# They're all mine #
# Floating by
just like veRtigo #
# Griping tight never
letting go #
# Oh, oh, oh #
# It's just
a little bit of magic #
# Just a little bit of magic #
# And things
will be okay #
# Oh, oh, oh #
# It's just
a little bit of magic #
# Just a little bit
of magic #
# And we'll
be on our way #
# Oh, oh, oh
ooh-uh-ooh #
# Oh, oh, oh ooh-uh-ooh #
# Oh, oh, oh
ooh-uh-ooh #
# And things
will be okay #
# Oh, oh, oh, oh #
# Oh, oh #
# Magic #
# Oh, oh, oh, oh #
# Oh, oh #
# Magic ##