I could have sworn
I nailed him.
Did you see the rack
on that sucker?
You scared him,
but I hit him.
I know. I know.
You got him.
What?
I nailed the buck?
Dude, I knew it!
What?
You see him?
I don't see anything.
I don't see shit.
I just see the stump.
Past the stump.
It's your birthday.
I'm gmng him to you.
You still see him?
Had him a second ago.
You can have him.
Being out here
with my big brother,
it's a pretty cool birthday.
Did you get him?
Oh, shit.
It's dick Cavanaugh.
You shot dick Cavanaugh.
Holy shit.
Just give me a second.
Let me think.
Is he dead?
Nate, what do we do?
Just give me a second
and let me think, okay?
Hey, dick,
you get that four-pointer,
you old son of a bitch?
This looks so bad, man.
I know.
Man, it's another beautiful
day here in guerneville.
77 degrees, from the back
of the post office here.
Looks like shorts
and t-shirt weather
is finally back
in the redwoods.
A reminder from pat Cavanaugh,
the annual Cavanaugh picnic
is coming up on the 23rd.
You can get your raffle tickets
at Cavanaugh's bait and tackle.
You don't want to miss out
on a chance
to light the Cavanaugh Cannon.
That sucker's loud.
Hey, Jamie.
Yip, yip, yip, yip.
- God damn.
- She's cute.
She's goddamn cute.
97.4 ktre, guerneville,
Rio nido, monte Rio,
where the river meets the trees.
Can't you shut the blinds?
Nope.
Okay...
Now, tell me again
what happened
after you shot the buck.
I was running, and...
- We were both...
- Skylar.
Let Nate tell it this time.
We were both running
after the deer.
He saw something and motioned
for me to stop.
And he got down on the ground,
and so did I.
Took aim and...
I didn't see what he saw, so...
He asked me what I saw.
Then he pulled the trigger.
Skylar... you fired the shot
that killed dick Cavanaugh?
Yeah.
Yeah, I did.
Okay.
- It was an accident.
- I know.
You're acting like
you don't believe us.
Doesn't matter
what I believe.
He shot the mayor, he's dead.
But he's only 17.
They can't charge him.
Look, we have to do everything
by the book here.
Come on, kiddo.
This is bullshit!
Nate, this isn't
a family matter.
This is police business.
Just go home.
Go home. Go home!
You all right?
Yeah.
Hey, guys.
Hey, Jamie.
Is your mother home?
Uh, yeah.
She's on the computer.
My dad's not here.
Yeah, I know.
You okay?
It's Nate towne's truck.
Son of a bitch.
This... is for Uncle dick.
Oh, shit!
- Nate.
- What?
- That's my cousin.
- Yeah. He hit my truck.
He'll see us.
Nate!
Hey, it's the morning breeze
with your favorite
tree-hugging dj,
Mr. cool breeze.
That last one goes out
to all you cavanaughs
in your hard time.
My thoughts and prayers
are with you.
This one's for Eric Cavanaugh,
going out to his lady love,
marina, with a reminder...
Marina, baby, pick up some milk
on the way home.
Lloyd.
Jack.
Jack...
I am truly sorry
about your brother.
Brass tacks, bloom.
Melanie believes
there's motive.
Well,
with all due respect, Jack,
Melanie is in mourning.
Whole town's in mourning
for its mayor.
Yeah.
By the way...
I've noted that
skylar and Nate's deposition
was taken by their father.
Melanie is eager to see
that skylar is treated
as an adult.
He is 17 years old.
Everyone in this room knows
there's history here.
My boys know nothing
about that.
Dad? What's going on?
I brought you
some fresh clothes.
Are they... are they
charging me with something?
We've gotta let Jack
and Melanie do their thing.
Okay? We've gotta let things
cool down a little bit.
If you're innocent...
And I know that you are...
Everything's gonna be fine.
Hey, bloom. Food's almost up.
You want a cup of coffee
while you wait?
Sounds good.
You know, when there's
only one game in town,
sometimes it's best
just not to play.
It's taken me ten years
married to duffie Cavanaugh
to figure that one out.
I'll check on your food.
Would you like anything else?
Nate. Nate?
Where's skylar?
He's at the station.
They're gonna take him
to county at 4:00.
Why?
Because they want to try him
as an adult.
Try him for what?
They're gonna try him
for murder.
Can't you do something?
The last thing
skylar needs is for me
to be gumming everything up
by pulling strings
trying to get him out.
You think if the tables
were turned,
and it was a Cavanaugh
sitting in that cell...
- We're not cavanaughs!
How does that big thumb feel
pressing down on your head?
Eat your hamburger.
That too tight?
No. I'm okay.
You want to grab a beer?
I thought you were on duty.
Yeah.
I just figured I'd watch.
Well, I'm gonna
get home early,
so I can get out to Santa rosa
for the arraignment.
Here, sign this.
- It's your report.
- Yeah.
I was over
at Randy's house last night.
I'm five minutes late,
brought the wrong kind of beer.
He chewed me out
for 20 minutes.
Hey, this guy's pretty close.
He's on my ass.
- Shit, he rammed us!
- Watch out! Watch out!
He's coming around the side.
Watch the road, man! Stay left!
Watch that tree!
Hit the brakes!
Oh, shit, we're going over!
Oh, my God!
Don't move. Nobody move.
Oh. Hey, Lloyd.
- Tom, Guthrie.
- Officer.
Why don't you boys
drink your beer in the bar
like everybody else?
You know it's a ticket.
Well, it is a beautiful,
sunshiny day.
It is lovely outside
today, isn't it?
Plus, bloom usually
just gives us a warning, so...
You've already been warned.
Oh, come on.
What?
Hey, Lloyd, we got a report
of an accident
up by the rock quarry.
Can you go check it out?
All right, I'm on it.
Come on, Lloyd,
don't give us a ticket.
We're family, man.
The law's the law, tom.
Family doesn't change that.
Have a nice day.
Give me the fucking keys!
You're digging yourself
the deepest hole, kid.
You want to talk
about deep holes?
Look down.
- Come on!
- Okay, okay, here.
- Don't rock it.
- Come on, get out.
- Watch it.
- Come on, get out!
- Nate?
- Shh.
Give me your hand.
What the hell
are you doing, man?
Trust me,
you're already screwed.
- Just don't rock the van.
- Hey, shut up!
- Hold on.
- Wait!
Shit. No!
Run. Run. Come on!
Nate, what the fuck
are you doing, man?
A bunch of bullshit
is going down.
I had to do something.
Give me your hands.
Now what the fuck
are we gonna do?
We'll go to Uncle Mike's.
Easy. Easy.
The last thing I want to do
is hurt you boys.
You know that.
Skylar, I want you
to hand me that pistol...
By the barrel, real slow.
Take your mask off, Nate.
All right, what happened
to those two deputies?
They're gone.
They kept going.
Probably in Santa rosa
by now, dumb fucks.
All right, I want you
to put these on,
one on each of you.
Get out of the car.
What were you thinking?
Huh? You trying to convince
everybody you're guilty?
They're already convinced.
Not me. I've been trying
to give you boys
the benefit of the doubt.
But you're making it
really difficult.
Innocent people don't bust out
of a police van
before they've even been tried.
Nate!
Come on, we gotta jump.
Come on, sky, you can do it.
- Hello?
- Bloom...
We got a big problem.
Hey, Lloyd,
where the hell are you?
The phones are going nuts
down here.
Looks like he's home.
I don't know if this
is such a good idea.
What if he calls dad?
Mike doesn't have a phone.
Aah!
Looking for a 20
on Lloyd or bloom.
Oh, shit.
Come on, help me.
Ow!
- Unh!
- Ow! Ow.
It's open.
I didn't expect
to see you tonight.
What's the occasion?
It's not my birthday again,
is it?
Nope.
I'm looking for Nate
and skylar.
You seen 'em?
I haven't seen 'em,
but if I do,
I'll let 'em know
that you're looking for 'em.
If they're here, Mike,
it's important
that you tell me.
Dick Cavanaugh's dead.
Are they here?
How many you got out there?
Just Lloyd.
The man who knew too much.
What a fuck.
Well, that's all water
under the bridge now.
Maybe under your bridge,
bloom.
Sarah is still dead.
Come on up out of there.
You guys all right?
Yeah, we're fine.
Lloyd Cavanaugh.
Well... this is
certainly an honor.
Michael Spencer.
I see you're still
digging foxholes
out in your front yard.
Waiting for world war III?
Lloyd, I asked you
to stay in the car.
Yeah, I just wanted
to make sure everything's okay.
- I got this.
- Good.
Let's take these boys down
to the station, then, huh?
You're not taking anybody
anywhere.
Lloyd, just go wait
in the car.
I've got this under control.
YOU DON'T HAVEANYTHING
UNDER CONTROL.
Look, Mike... I get it.
You're still pissed,
and you have every right to be.
Dad, what's he talking about?
Never mind, just, uh...
Go get in the car.
We'll talk about it
on the way back to town.
Boys, it's up to you.
Sometimes fighting
can put you in jail...
Sometimes it can keep you out.
We're not going to jail.
Look, I'm taking the boys
outside,
and I'll wait for you, okay?
Back off, Cavanaugh.
Lloyd, get outside!
Nate, skylar, run!
Mike!
Nate! Nate!
Skylar!
Where the hell
do you think you're going?
Put your seat belt back on.
I don't want to sound outside
the bounds of the law.
It's not as if I'm suggesting
a... a posse or something.
Getting a conviction
is not gonna be a problem.
I can hang a homicide
on both boys
for the deputies alone.
I'm not talking
about the courts anymore.
I think we both know why towne
might want to hurt dick.
I think justice needs
to be served for dick.
It's the situation with bloom...
- Bloom towne's not a problem.
Randy.
I'm so glad you're here.
Sit down. Good to see you.
Let me sit down there.
Now, bloom may be a fool,
but he knows his place.
And, Jack, we're gonna need
a little interference
down at the county courthouse.
It's not a problem.
Talked to Donald
a few minutes ago.
Said he's gonna try
to buy us a couple days.
This is a family issue now.
That's how we'll treat it.
It's not working.
What are you doing?
Gotta take a piss.
- Dude.
- Sorry.
What the hell
was Mike talking about?
What do you mean?
He was going on and on,
like Lloyd did something.
Hell if I know.
You know what Mike was like.
We gotta go back.
We gotta talk to dad.
Fuck that.
We gotta turn ourselves in.
What are we doing?
Where are we going?
What are... what are you gonna do
with that?
Remember mom's friend
jacylin?
The one in Canada?
She always said
she'd do anything for mom.
Canada's, like,
a thousand Miles from here.
Yeah, that's the point.
The farther the better.
Skylar, they were gonna
try you as an adult.
If I hadn't busted you out,
you'd be fucked now.
Totally fucked.
Just like Uncle Mike!
So what do we do?
We get to cloverdale,
hop a freight train to humboldt.
A freight train?
Okay... we steal a car.
Or, no.
What was that lady's name?
The one that dad did
a couple times,
with the big tits?
Susan?
Yeah. Remember, she took us
fishing on her boat?
400-mile range?
Boat, head up the coast
to Vancouver.
Stop for gas a couple times,
and boom, we're home free!
- Keys are in the flower pot.
- Oh, yeah. Thank you, Susan.
You'll find your boat
in Vancouver harbor.
- Hey, Jenny, anything yet?
- Nothing yet.
Thanks.
You get that filled out yet?
I'll take care of it.
You don't need to stay, Randy.
Listen to me, bloom. Okay?
Okay.
I imagine you're wondering
what you can do
to help your boys.
- Am I right?
- Yeah.
But you've got a dilemma.
A conflict of interest.
Correct?
You know, I don't know
if I'd call it that.
You've got two cop killers
out there
that just happen to be
your sons.
The details are sketchy.
You've got
a serious conflict here.
You understand?
You know, you could
look at is as though
we both have
a serious conflict here.
- Really?
- Yeah.
You know, you've done
all right by us, bloom.
I'm sure you'll do
the right thing here.
Get me that report
by the end of the day.
Whoa!
What do we do?
Now. Go!
Shit. Is that Lloyd?
Hey, Nate, did I get you?
Joel? Is that you?
Yeah. It's me and Tony.
You gotta be kidding me.
It's Joel Cavanaugh.
What?
What's your problem, dude?
You guys killed my Uncle.
My dad says it's open season
on you two.
You know that your dad's
an asshole, right?
Hey, what about yours?
I don't see him out here
doing you any favors!
- Come here.
- What?
Take this.
So you thought
just you and Tony
could take us out alone?
You're high.
Who says we came alone?
They're bluffing.
You want to give up?
Yeah, right. Suck it!
Give me an arrow.
Are you fucking kidding me?
Bows and arrows?
Aah!
Get me back, you fucker!
Oh, God!
Son of a bitch!
I'm gonna kill you now!
Nice shot.
Dude! Dude,
what are you doing?
Where are you going?
You stupid pussy!
I have the keys.
Hey, Nate?
Yeah.
I think I'm gonna die
if you leave me here.
You fucking assholes!
You shot first.
Holy shit, Joel.
Where'd you get an m16?
My dad's.
And a grenade?
It's just tear gas.
Tony really stood by you.
Friends till the end, huh?
Carry me.
Carry me back.
Are you kidding?
How am I supposed to get back?
I can't fucking walk!
You should have thought
of that
before you came out here,
dipshit!
Let's get these things off.
One, two, three!
Aw, fuck!
You literally couldn't hit
a fuckin' elephant
at point blank.
Shut your face, Joel.
Retard.
You think I can't
hit you from here?
Okay.
I will blow your head
clean off!
Okay. Come on, dude,
I was just fucking with you.
One more dead Cavanaugh
doesn't mean shit to me!
Come on, man, I was just
fucking kidding with you.
Nate, come on.
Let's get the cuffs off.
Tony, I'm over here. Come on.
Nate, get the cuffs off.
Get 'em off.
Okay.
Here, let me do it this time.
- I got it.
- Let me do it.
I got it! Ready?
Yeah.
Turn your head away. Ready?
Oh... aw, shit, it's empty.
Nate! You shot Joel.
He's bleeding really bad, man.
That's fucked up.
Okay, take it easy, Tony.
Put the gun down.
Put the gun down, Tony.
You know I'll shoot.
Okay, all right,
we're gonna do it together.
Ready? On the count of three.
One, two...
Finger off the trigger.
Three.
Okay. Okay. Okay.
You guys are
in so much trouble.
Yeah. Yeah.
- Unh!
- Uhh!
Shit. Tony!
Tony, you all right?
Unh. Yeah, I'm fine. I'm fine.
This is Ronnie.
You got your ears on, Eric?
I just pissed away
the last of my beer.
You got anything to drink
in the shit bucket of yours?
Well, I'm gonna run into town
and grab something.
You want anything?
That's bullshit, dude.
Randy's gonna filet your balls.
He said don't move
till he tells us otherwise.
What are we even
doing out here, man?
I mean, you really think
Nate and skylar meant
to kill dick... on purpose?
Come on.
Two words... filet... balls.
What the fuck, man?
This is my Uncle's
fuckin' truck,
you fuckin' shithead!
I return this thing
with a scratch on it,
he's gonna kick the shit
out of me.
All right, bitch.
Here ya go.
Damn it!
Damn, that dude's fast.
Shit.
That's Eric's truck.
That's Ronnie.
What are they doing?
All right, a sixer
of cold ones
if you can take the bottle
off my head.
Twelver for me if you can't.
You're on, dipshit.
Yeah!
Nice!
- Two out of three.
- No way, dude.
- Yeah, way.
- Get out there.
Ken, get that can on his head.
- No way.
- Rules are rules.
Two out of three.
You're a dick, man.
You aim low,
I'm seriously gonna
kick the shit our of you...
You know that, right?
Don't distract me, man.
How you gonna kick anybody's ass
if you don't have a head?
Hey, wait a second, wait,
wait, wait, Ronnie, turn around.
You're not getting out
of this.
- Keys! Keys! Keys!
- Nate and skylar.
Hey!
Dude, that's my truck.
They're gonna steal it.
They're not goin' anywhere.
Aw, shit! Come on.
Who the hell is that?
Shit, dude.
My bad!
Did you see Larry go down?
- You think he's okay?
- Who cares?
Fuck! Fuck! Fuck!
20 on the towne boys
is 5 to 1.
Nah, 20 on Randy.
You were jackin' off,
God damn it!
and those fuckin' towne
shitheads got away!
You, you dumb fuck, come here.
Look what the fuck
they did to Larry!
Look at him! Huh?
WHAT THE FUCK
IS THE MATTER WITH YOU?
What kind of shithead are you?
All of you.
They killed dick.
They killed two cops.
Now they fucked Larry up.
And what are you doing?
You're out here playing,
what, William tell?
You heard me at the house.
These boys do not need
to come back with us.
I thought I was clear.
We're not out here
to suck each other's cocks.
Fuck. Ronnie?
Don't worry, I got it.
Okay, that's better.
Now, you got
two teenage boys out there
making you all look
like a bunch of idiots.
If they reach the county line,
I'M GONNA LOOK LIKE AN IDIOT!
You understand?
Well, stop looking at me.
Go get 'em, God damn it.
Hurry the fuck up!
Move! Do some-fuckin'-thing!
Jesus.
Lloyd,
fuckin' get Larry some help.
In the paper today,
I see that Donald Cavanaugh's
gerrymandering case
came to a close yesterday,
which means we've got
a new congressman.
Congrats, Donald.
Fishing season is here,
so here's a reminder
from our chief of police,
bloomfield towne...
Fishing off our Bridges is...
- Hey, Travis, you still
up on sterrit hill?
- Yeah.
- You seen Ronnie?
I lost track of him.
They're headed west
along pocket canyon.
They're right behind
the towne boys.
- No shit.
- Yeah.
Randy says don't bother
bringing 'em back alive.
You wanna get a beer later?
If you could eat anything,
what would you have right now?
Mmm...
Mom's spaghetti.
This is Travis.
We're up at elephant Ridge.
The towne boys are down
below us in the canyon,
but we can't get down there
from here.
We gotta go around.
Anyone closer?
Uh, yeah.
I'm with Ronnie, we're on it.
How far do you think
we've got? Unh!
Maybe 12 Miles.
Boat had a bed underneath,
didn't it?
Yeah, and a little kitchen.
Hold up.
Dude, we gotta get going.
They're probably
right behind us.
It's all right.
It took us, like, 15 minutes
to cross that canyon.
What about the next Ridge?
What are we gonna do now?
We keep going.
Ow! Fuck!
Oh, sorry, man.
Where the fuck is dad?
Dad's a pussy.
They could parade us around town
on a couple of spikes,
he still wouldn't give a shit.
How come he's such a pussy...
Since mom died?
What the fuck happened to him?
Come on,
we gotta get out of here.
You know what Uncle Mike
was talking about, don't you?
They're coming, dude.
I don't care. Tell me.
Fuck it.
It was dick that hit mom's car.
- What?
- He hit it with his car.
Drunk.
He passed out at the wheel.
Dad and Lloyd found the wreck.
There was no way
dick was gonna do time,
so dad filed it
as a hit and run.
Bullshit.
Why do you think dad
made chief so easily?
Dad covered up mom's killing,
so he could be chief?
Basically.
No. No fucking way.
Fuck.
Got it?
Come on, we gotta move.
Why didn't you tell me?
Uncle Mike made me promise
not to tell.
Uncle Mike told you,
and you weren't gonna tell me?
He was gonna do something.
He was gonna get dick back,
and then...
What? And then what, Nate?
He was gonna do it anyway.
Do what?
Just fucking tell me!
You knew it was him.
You knew it was dick
in the woods.
Oh, my God, you saw him.
You let me tell everyone
I did it.
What the fuck, Nate?
I didn't plan it, skylar!
I saw him,
and I pulled the trigger.
I didn't even really
think about it.
You didn't think about it,
and you let me take the blame!
I told you not to.
That's why you busted me out,
because you felt guilty?
I busted you out
because neither of us deserves
to go to jail
for dick Cavanaugh!
I sure as hell don't!
Fuck this! I'm starving.
Oh, skylar, do you even know
where you're going?
We have to stick to the plan,
remember?
We have to head west
to the coast.
You took me hunting
on my birthday
to use me as an alibi
for murder.
I swear to God, dude!
I thought it was a buck!
I got it in my sights,
saw it was dick,
and I pulled the trigger.
He killed mom,
and he got away with it!
What don't you
fucking understand?
Dude, nothing has changed.
We can still make it
to the boat.
- Oh, yeah.
- Here we go.
That's bloom.
Go talk to him.
Don't tell me what to do.
Yeah, you'll do it,
won't you?
Exactly.
I'll stick this bottle
up your ass, dude,
and you'll like it.
Hey, bloom, what's happening?
- You're happening, Guthrie.
- Thanks.
What's with the roadblock?
Oh, we're not supposed
to let you go by.
Yeah? Just me?
Yeah, um, pretty much.
No offense.
Randy told us, you know,
most likely you'd be coming by,
and we're definitely
supposed to stop you.
You got room to turn around?
- Yeah, probably do.
- Okay, good.
- That's tom's Camaro.
- Uh-huh.
Yeah, that's his baby.
Randy specifically said
that we're supposed to stop you
from going past.
Hey, halt! Stop. Come on.
Stop! Whoa! Shit! God damn it.
Dude, what are you doing?
I mean, I would have
shot your tires out
if I could've got my stupid gun
out of my pants.
Well, I guess
I'll just go home.
You guys have
all the roads blocked, huh?
Yeah. You know,
we're just kinda circling
skylar and Nate
up on, uh, moscow road.
Got 'em...
- Okay.
Well, you stay warm, Guthrie.
And if you're gonna drive,
don't drink too much, okay?
- Okay. Thanks.
- Bye.
Thanks, bloom.
Shit ain't funny, bloom!
- Later, bloom.
- Back it on up.
- What'd he say?
- Nothin' much. He's cool.
- Nothin' much?
- Yeah, he's cool.
Couldn't stop him...
My gun got stuck. You guys
could've done something.
Just chill out, man.
Everything's fine.
It's a nice day out.
Maybe he's gonna...
- Shut up.
What are you doing, bloom?
Huh?
I think he...
Think he's gotta pee.
Dude, he's definitely got...
He's peeing.
He's messing with us
is what he's doing.
Hey. Bloom?
Bloom?
Officer bloom?
You guys check over there.
- Yeah.
- I don't see him.
He's gotta be here.
Where else would he be?
I don't know, but Randy said
if some shit like this happens,
we gotta shoot him.
He's a fuckin' cop.
We're gonna shoot him?
I'm pretty sure
Randy knows that.
Hey, skylar, you can't
just pull me around, man.
Bullshit.
You pulled me into this,
and I didn't know shit!
Now I'm gonna go get
some fucking food
and get
these fucking cuffs off!
COME ON!
What took you so long?
I'm starving.
Take it easy. Take it easy!
No!
We're not here to hurt you.
Just be cool, and everything
will be all right, okay?
They're in the old cerini
house up on greenwalt road.
We're outside.
What should we do?
Just don't let 'em go.
I'm on my way.
And stop saying where you are.
Radio silence from now on.
That goes for everybody.
Fuck!
What's your name?
Roroberta.
Roberta, why don't you have
any food?
Where's your food?
I'mi'm waiting
for my fiance.
He's getting pizza.
He'll be here any minute,
I swear.
Do you have a hacksaw
or an axe or anything?
No. I don't know.
Doesn't your boyfriend
have a toolbox?
Anything? Nothing?
You have nothing?
We don't live here.
It's just a vacation rental.
There's nothing.
Fuck this shit.
Let's get out of here.
Hey, we got the place
surrounded... they're inside.
No! No!
- Where are the car keys, lady?
- Nate, easy.
Where are the keys?
Where are the car keys?
- What do we need keys for?
- We need a car, man.
- Where are they?
- On the sofa.
Lady, would you please,
just...
Oh, my... seriously?
Go!
Go! Go, go, go, go!
Come on, skylar, come on!
Come on, sky.
Nate, grenade. The grenade.
Oh, shit.
Go to the right.
Come on.
You can give 'em a head start,
but you know
what's gonna happen.
Randy ain't gonna quit.
We'll find 'em.
I'm gonna turn around
now, Lloyd.
I don't believe you're gonna
shoot me in the back,
but if you feel you need to,
go ahead.
What the fuck you doing,
Lloyd?
It's bloom.
You have a shot?
You had a shot,
and you let towne go?
All right, Eric,
you're drmng.
What's the next road down
from here?
- Fullam.
- All right.
Get the boys together.
I want fullam road covered.
You're a moron.
What's going on?
Let's take five.
Chopper will spot 'em
before we ever do anyway.
What is it, Saturday?
- Yep.
There goes
the fuckin' weekend, huh?
I wish somebody'd put these
fuckers out of their misery.
You know? That's the only way
this is gonna end.
Let's just get it
over with already.
I'd rather be out here
than at the gas station any day.
Get ahold
of those two little maggots
and rip their little heads off.
Give me one of those bagels.
I'm gonna string 'em up
like mussolini,
by their balls.
Shave their bodies, strap 'em
to the hood of my car
like a couple of trophies,
drive around town
till their bodies rot off.
That's fucked up.
Can I get a juice box?
Shit, skip,
you got any more bagels?
No, man, that's it.
Holy shit!
Get my gun! Get 'em!
Services begin at 11:00
and continue all day.
The spaghetti feed
in dick's honor...
Will be hosted
by dick's brother Randy
at the town hall at 6:00.
Okay, you're listening
to the morning breeze...
You're a fucking asshole, man.
I hope you know that.
If we ever get these cuffs off,
I'm gonna kick
your fucking ass!
See,
that's why I didn't tell you.
You don't get it.
Get it-what?
You know what they did,
and you're still mad at me.
You're the asshole!
You're unbelievable, man.
You hate dad so much,
but you're just like him.
You let the cavanaughs
ruin your life.
That's bullshit, skylar,
and you know it.
You're bullshit, and now
you're just as bad as them.
Easy. Get up.
Turn around real slowly.
Come on, towne.
You're sloppy, towne.
You're a sloppy cop
and a sloppy outlaw.
That chopper spotted you
on the first pass.
I'm no outlaw.
I'm just here for my boys.
I'm gonna count to three...
And I want you
to drop your gun.
Randy, you know
I can't walk away from this.
You've done it before.
You're good at it.
Yeah.
One...
You punk. Three.
Aah!
Randy.
Fuck.
If you're having a hard time
hearing the breeze
this morning,
you are not alone.
We got a low-flying chopper
buzzing the neighborhood.
We're gonna have
to cross the river again.
No, fuck that.
They'll see us.
We gotta get to the barn.
No, fuck that, man.
We gotta keep going.
We can cross right there.
- We're not crossing the river.
- Skylar, come on.
There's someone over there.
We're not going over there.
Skylar, come on.
What the fuck is going on?
Who's over there?
Let's go, skylar.
Nate?
What is that?
Hey. Yeah, it's me.
We're just across the river.
We'll be there
in a minute, okay?
I can't believe
this is happening.
You had a fucking phone?
Jamie's coming with us.
- What?
- She loves me.
She wants to come.
No. Bullshit!
We're not going over there.
This is bullshit!
- Skylar.
- Nate!
Listen to me!
We're not going anywhere
if you don't cross that bridge.
I'll just sit down.
You fucker.
She's got a car.
Shit!
Damn it! Get down!
Hold your fire.
She screwed us, Nate.
She fuckin' screwed us.
Okay, sky, we're going over.
Come on, man.
- No! No!
- We're going over.
What the fuck are you doing?
- Put your arms up.
- What the fuck are you doing?
Fuck no!
We are not gmng up!
I know you think
I fucked you over, man,
but you gotta trust me.
They're not gonna let us
off this bridge alive.
All right, wait here.
- Hey! I said hold your fire.
- Come on.
Come on, sky. You can do it.
We have to.
Skylar, Nate, no!
We've got to, sky.
We don't have a choice, skylar.
Right here?
The truck's here.
Let's go, come on.
You see that?
Been down there a long time.
No way they made that.
Check the other side?
They're gone.
Look, there. Right there.
Come on, guys, let's go.
Come on.
Hey, this is tom.
I'm at the bottom
of caz highway.
Has anybody seen Randy?
He was supposed
to meet me here.
Aah! Oh, God!
Oh, that hurts.
Oh, my God, it hurts.
Oh, please.
Skylar? Oh, my God.
- Come here. Come here.
- Aah!
Shit.
I thought
you were coming alone.
I did. I swear.
I don't know what happened.
- Swear to God.
- Nate...
- Swear you didn't bring them.
- I swear.
Sky, you okay? Can you move?
Can you move?
What the fuck
are you doing here?
Oh, shit. Sky?
Jamie, I need your shirt.
Do you mind?
Cut the shirt in two.
We gotta stop this bleeding.
Nate...
Well, take the handcuffs off.
You're no good
with one hand tied.
Here.
- Tie it around his leg.
- Yeah.
- Up above the...
- Okay. Okay.
That's good. That's good.
Hold your fire.
Jamie's in there.
There are a lot of men
out there.
We got this far.
We need to start thinking
about an exit strategy.
You came all this way
to tell us to quit?
You've wasted your time.
- Nate.
- What, skylar?
I have a bullet in my leg.
I can't even walk.
Maybe he's right, Nate.
Bloom...
It's Lloyd.
Can you tell me
what you're doing in there?
I'm having a little talk
with my boys, Lloyd.
Now, we're gonna come walking
out of here in just a minute.
Why don't you
send Jamie out first?
Say whatever you want, dad.
We're not walking out of here.
Why don't we just let her go?
She came on her own.
I didn't force her to come.
Jamie, you wanna go?
Bloom, we don't have
a lot of time.
Now, if you and boys
are holding Jamie hostage...
- Hey, wait, Lloyd...
Lloyd, there's no hostage here.
Jamie came in here
on her own, all right?
You just... you have to give me
a minute or two.
All right,
you got two minutes.
You heard him, two minutes.
What's it gonna be?
Nate.
Fine. Why don't you
just turn yourself in?
You didn't do anything.
Nothing's gonna happen to you.
Oh, what does it matter now?
I shot dick.
Skylar didn't do shit.
What? You hated him.
You wished he'd drink himself
to death. Remember?
Well...
I didn't hate him.
They're gonna shoot us.
Yeah.
Yeah, they're gonna try.
They're gonna try
to fucking kill us.
- Nate!
- What?
It's true, dad,
and you know it.
You got one minute.
Jamie.
Jamie?
No. No.
Oh, fuck.
Jamie, sweetie, listen to me.
We're gonna walk out
of here, okay?
Have Lloyd come in.
If he comes in here,
I'll go out with him.
- Hey, Lloyd.
- Yeah?
How would you feel
about coming in here
and escorting us out?
Why?
You come in here,
and we'll go out with you.
The boys have already
killed two cops.
What's stopping them
from killing one more?
Me.
All right, I'm coming in.
Hey, Lloyd,
why don't you take off your gun,
so we don't have
another accident?
Good.
Shut the fucking door, Lloyd.
Holy shit.
Holy... oh, God.
Jamie, are you okay?
They didn't kidnap me.
I came on my own.
Yeah. I know. I followed you.
Hey. Nate!
- You cocksucker!
- Nate!
- He killed Uncle Mike!
- Nate, it's over.
Just let it go.
Let's get out of here.
Is this
why you brought me in here?
To kill me?
Nate, let's stick
with the plan.
WE MADE A DEAL.
YOU MADE A DEAL!
I know you're mad, Nate.
I know why you're mad.
But you brought this thing
to a fever pitch.
You made it this way.
Now you have a chance
to get out of here alive.
One chance.
So how about it?
Do you want to live?
You take Jamie out first.
Then dad and skylar and me.
Wait, no, Nate, Nate,
you should go out with skylar.
I'll go out with Jamie last.
Make sure you two...
- No. No.
Lloyd takes Jamie out.
- Nate...
- Dad, I'm not fucking around!
Jamie goes with Lloyd.
Then, once they're out,
you help skylar.
What about you?
I'm last.
We're coming out,
me and Jamie.
Go, go. Take her in your car.
Get her home.
I got some bad news.
Randy's dead. Bloom shot him.
What the fuck, man?
She was our ticket out of here.
I didn't want her
to get hurt.
These assholes
are gonna kill us.
Right here, one way or another.
They're not taking us
back to town.
Nate,
you better give me my gun.
We don't have a choice.
You don't have a choice!
We didn't sell our souls
to the cavanaughs!
We don't have to do
what they say.
What choice do we have?
Nate, they're gonna come in here
one way or the other.
How do we know
they're not gonna shoot us
if we go out?
Because Lloyd gave me
his word.
LLOYD IS ACAVANAUGH,DAD!
And you know as well as I do
that this is gonna end
right here!
You either go out there
and lick their boots...
Fuck it.
You don't have the balls.
Dad?
Did dick kill mom?
Bloom, it's time.