Man: ♪' On the California coast
in late December ♪
♪ It feels like the first day
of September ♪
♪ When every other place
is cold and frozen ♪
♪ I go down to the ocean
and I put my toes in ♪
♪ I guess we got it pretty nice ♪
♪ Some people call it paradise ♪
♪ But I wish
for a Christmas miracle ♪
♪ And I hope
it will come true... ♪
Boy: This is
a Christmas story.
Yeah, I know it doesn't
look like that.
You don't see a lot of big waves
and palm trees at the North Pole.
Man: ♪ Now there are plenty of girls
down on the beach... ♪
Boy:
This is my home-
Sunshine Beach, California,
where the sun shines
335 days out of the year
and it never snows.
Well, I guess it did once
back in the old-fashioned days,
like 1970 or something.
It was right on Christmas Day,
but we'll get back to that.
Man:
♪ The only one for me... ♪
Boy:
This is my house.
A little over a year ago,
Christmas morning...
Man: ♪ And I hope
it will come true...♪
Boy: I was 10--
just a kid, you know,
nothing like when you're 11.
Man: ♪ I'll spend Christmastime
with you ♪
♪ Sun, comin' down ♪
♪ Feel it shine ♪
♪ I wouldn't need the sun ♪
♪ If you were mine ♪
♪ I wished
for a Christmas miracle ♪
♪ And I hoped
it would come true... ♪
(alarm beeping )
♪ Now I got
my Christmas miracle ♪
♪ And I'm spending time
with you... ♪
Boy: I had a big Christmas list,
but there was one present
I wanted more than
anything else in the world.
Man: ♪ And I hoped
it would come true...♪
Boy: And I hoped
more than anything
that Santa brought his A-game.
Yes!
Man: ♪ I wished
for a Christmas miracle ♪
♪ And I hoped
it would come true ♪
♪ Now I got my
Christmas miracle... ♪
Father: Merry Christmas,
Bobby.
Awesome!
Bingo.
Wow, looks like Santa Claus was
pretty good to you this year, buddy.
So did-- did you open
everything?
Pretty sure.
Yeah?
Even that one over there?
It's em PW
What do you mean,
it's empty?
(dog whining)
It's a puppy. Cool.
- Hey, hey.
- Come on.
Bobby, be careful back there, okay?
You go that way.
- Hey.
- Come here, come here.
Father:
Here-- good boy.
- Bobby: The other way.
- Don't-- don't--
- Not that way.
- Just-- just-
- Bobby, don't chase him.
- Come on, puppy.
Hey, get him.
Come here, come here.
Get him. Get him.
Hey. hey. just-
Okay, okay.
Bobby, don't chase him.
- Bobby: The tree.
- Bobby.
(giggling )
Watch the tree.
Stop it.
He won't stop.
His tongue is so chilly.
Father:
Look at how cute he is.
That's what I'll name him--
Chilly, Chilly Christmas.
I was thinking more like
Destructo-Dog.
Bobby's voice:
Yeah, best present ever, right?
Dad said it's a Korean Sapsali,
one of the rarest breeds there is.
It's just like my mom
used to have.
My best friend was always my dad,
but now I had another best friend-
Chilly Christmas.
Singer: ♪ I wish
for a Christmas miracle ♪
♪ And I hope it will come true ♪
♪ If I get my Christmas miracle ♪
♪ I'll spend Christmastime
with you ♪
♪ Sun, comin' down ♪
♪ Feel it shine... ♪
Bobby:
I gotta tell you about my house.
My house is kind of weird.
Downstairs-
bedrooms and stuff.
Upstairs-- kitchen,
living room, dining room.
Singer:
.' And I hoped it would come true .'
♪ Now I got
my Christmas miracle... ♪
Chilly!
♪ And I'm spending time
with you ♪
♪ I wished
for a Christmas miracle ♪
♪ And I hoped it would
come true... ♪
Chilly, it's breakfast!
Where are you?
Chilly, come on!
Come on, boy.
(whining )
Father: Bobby, are you ready
for school?
(whimpering)
Do me a favor, feed that dog
outside, please.
Took me over an hour
to sweep up
all those broken ornaments
from yesterday.
- I got you covered, Dad.
- Hey.
(chuckles)
You know, yelling too loud can cause
phonotrauma and vocal fatigue.
Sorry about that, buddy.
I thought you were downstairs.
Hey, don't forget
about lunch, okay?
I won't.
Now, I know on Mondays
you prefer ham,
but I made you
a turkey melt on rye.
Ooh, with homemade
dill mayonnaise, I hope.
- Is there any other kind?
- Mmm-mm.
You'd better take a shower
when you're done.
- What for?
- So you don't smell like old socks.
-( laughs )
- I can't take care of you forever, Dad.
One of these days
it would actually be nice
if you would, you know,
date a girl.
Tell you what--
I will when you will, okay?
Okay. Gross.
Phonotrauma?
Is that even real?
(sighs)
Winter break, finally.
This is gonna be an even better
Christmas than last year.
No.
One-- you're never supposed
to be in the house,
and two-- you're never, ever ever
supposed to be in the house all wet.
Dad's gonna ground both of us
until we're as old as Dad.
And in dog years that's like, 300.
You need to dry off first.
(whines)
Oh, no.
Bobby, please tell me
you're leaving for the bus.
Right away, Dad.
( Spitting )
Oh, Chilly.
Oh--!
We should have named him
Destructo-Dog.
Argh.
Bobby's voice:
First, don't panic.
Chilly is keeping his name.
Qkay.
This is when my Christmas story
begins to get interesting.
But before we get to that,
you should probably meet
my best friend Caps.
I know, weird name, right?
You'll see.
Hey, Carl.
Hey, Caps, nice hat.
Do you mean nice for real,
like, "Wow, cool hat,"
or sarcastic nice, like,
"Wow, you're embarrassing me."
No, really.
I think it's really...
Lame?
If there was a Super Bowl
for stupid hats,
you would be
a world champion.
'Morning, Kizzy.
Tell him, Bobby,
that thing on Caps' head
is a bully magnet
for the Mahoney brothers.
Don't worry, Kizzy.
I can take care of us.
I'm pretty heroic.
Oh, you mean your dad's
pretty heroic.
If anyone's gonna take care of us,
it's gonna be me.
How many black belts in karate
do you two have?
Hmm-mm-mm.
Either way,
I've got a game today
and you're throwing off
my mojo.
She's scary.
You know,
I heard she bites too,
like a dog.
She does not.
Yeah?
Well, ask Timmy Johnson.
He borrowed her pencil
and forgot to return it
and she lashed onto his leg
like a hungry pit bull.
She called me Bobby.
That's your name, genius.
I know. I just didn't know
she knew it.
Oh my gosh, you like her?
No.
Uh-huh.
Advice-- she's a biter.
If I were you, I'd start carrying around
lots of Band-Aids.
♪ Oh, Mele Kalikimaka ♪
♪ Mele, Mele Kalikimaka ♪
♪ Oh, Mele Kalikimaka... ♪
Good morning, buddy.
Hey, I'm not sharing
Bobby's sandwich with you,
if that's what this is about.
What is going on around here?
'Morning, Lieutenant.
Mind telling me
what's going on around here?
- You didn't hear?
- Hear what?
Obviously we all remember
Detective Cole
catching a suspect
on the FBI'-s most wanted list.
Oh, come on, they don't want
to hear that story again.
Ah, but there's more.
I have something for you.
It's from the FBI.
"Dear Detective Cole,
once again,
the Federal Bureau of Investigation
is grateful for your acts--"
yadda, yadda, yadda--
"offering you the position
of Special Agent
leading the Robbery Task Force
in New York City field office."
( cheering )
"To take over a major investigation,
we need you immediately,
no later than December 28th
Whoa, whoa, whoa, wait a second.
I didn't say I was taking the job.
Are you crazy?
This is the FBI.
If you don't take this job,
I will fire you
- and then you will have to take it.
- Ha, that's funny.
Look, it's not just me.
I've got a son-- Bobby.
- I mean, you know, Chilly--
- The dog?
He poops, he eats,
he sleeps all day.
Come on, you don't need
to worry about him.
(Chilly whining)
(fast music playing )
Do you feel lonely?
Do your friends and family
sometimes leave you behind?
The new PX-35 diet and workout
make the perfect Christmas gift.
Eat and exercise your way
to better and positive energy.
And everybody
will want you around.
Remember, a high-protein meal
is important.
Don't be afraid to use
an exercise ball.
And keep your body clean.
And after your PX-35 workout,
you'll have the time to do the things
that make you feel great.
(trickling )
And isn't feeling great
what life is really all about?
Look, I was born
in Sunshine Beach.
I mean, that house has been
in my family for three generations.
Look, they're paying
for your whole move.
They even rented you an apartment
in Midtown.
All the memories of Bobby's mom
are here.
I mean,
it's just such a big move
in such a short amount
of time.
Look, change is good.
You need it.
You've outgrown this place.
And the only job left for you to take
is mine, and I'm not going anywhere.
It's definitely a big salary bump.
I could take advantage and put
a college fund together for Bobby, but--
I don't know.
Maybe you're right.
Maybe?
You know I'm right.
I'm always right.
That's why I'm the boss.
But he's lucky.
He's got a good dad,
got someone to look up to.
I just hope I'm making
the right decision.
Lieutenant: You know what my dad
used to always say?
"Bravery is not the absence of fear.
It is the action in the face of fear."
You must be Lieutenant Stone.
I'm Detective Jasper Harris.
I just transferred from
the Santa Barbara Police Department.
Detective Cole, meet your
new replacement Detective Harris.
Replacement? What made you think
I was gonna take the job?
Oh, please. I said if you didn't,
I was gonna fire you.
I know your record well, Detective.
I'm stoked about taking over.
That's great.
Here's your last case.
Dognappers?
Are you serious? This is the case you
want me to go out on-- a poodle pincher?
Somebody's been stealing
rare breeds of dogs
worth thousands of dollars
from kennels.
It's a good case for Junior here
to get his feet wet.
Jasper, ma'am. It's Jasper.
Why don't you go pull the car around
for you and Detective Cole?
You got it.
I'm gonna miss this place.
I might even miss you
a little bit, Stone.
It's the right decision
for you and for Bobby.
Now go on, go get me
one last bad guy.
Hey, I'm stoked.
Man: The thing you need to know
about me, Mr. Gribbling,
is that I deliver results,
period, guaranteed.
As a matter of fact,
I believe my colleagues
have secured some new
merchandise as we speak.
Excuse me. Well?
We had to break a window to get in.
I cut myself. It's not like the movies.
Not to worry, Mr. Quarterman.
We got the package.
(whines)
Merchandise in hand.
We'll have the rest of the items
on your list within a week
and we'll make the flight
on Christmas Day.
Michael Quarterman
always gets his dog.
Idiot.
( Horn honking )
( barks)
Winter break-
no school and no homework.
And no teachers.
Nothing's gonna stop this
from being the best Christmas ever.
( Rumbling )
(engine stops)
All right.
Looks like we got
a blowout, kids.
So everybody, sit still.
Oh, great-
only one block away
from freedom.
What else could go wrong?
Oh, no.
Shane and Jake-
the Mahoney brothers.
Don't they own any shirts
with sleeves?
Caps, the hat--
take off the hat.
I thought you liked the hat.
Bobby, not the hat.
Hey, somebody hit my brother
with a hat.
No, they didn't.
- Oh, I thought you said "with a cat."
- No.
Was it one of you?
Uh...
-( liquid trickling)
-( Chilly barks)
You even touch these geeks,
you half-brain bullies
are gonna get kicked
in the roasted chestnuts.
Dude, your girlfriend here
is tougher than you are.
Yeah, jeez, Cole, aren't you
supposed to be the one
with the big hero cop dad?
Yeah, come on, save the day.
Who are we gonna punch?
Um, may we propose
an option
- where no one gets punched?
- Yeah.
No.
I think I'll start
with you, Cole.
(Chilly barking. growling)
You know, I don't speak
dog language,
but I'm pretty sure
that's Chilly'-s way of saying
to back off his friend
or he's gonna bite you
on the roasted chestnuts.
Hey, this ain't
no pet store, man.
No dogs on the bus.
I'm sorry.
We'll all walk from here.
Come on.
♪ Sun, comin' down... ♪
Man, I've never seen
the Mahoney brothers
come close to peeing
their pants before.
I gotta admit, Bobby, I didn't think
you'd have a dog this cool.
Don't call Chilly a dog.
Then he's a freakishly
large hamster.
To Bobby,
Chilly'-s not just a dog.
Chilly'-s his best friend.
And you had my back, pal...
as always.
Maybe once I could be
the one saving you.
Yeah, right.
- Clumsy enough?
- Sorry.
Hey, thanks for, you know,
stepping in-- on the bus.
Whatever.
I just didn't want to get blood
on my new basketball jersey.
Are you seriously
gonna eat that?
Mm-hmm.
Aww, really?
We'd better clean up
before your dad comes home.
It's Friday.
His shift doesn't end till 6:00,
which gives us plenty of time.
Cole:
I'm home, buddy.
Quick, clean up.
(all overlapping )
Come on, hurry, get the pizza.
What are we gonna do?
Come on, Bobby, we gotta hurry up.
Hurry up, hurry up.
Wait, Bobby, stop.
Come on, there's so much.
Hurry, come on, guys.
Come on, hurry, hurry,
hurry, hurry.
Bobby's dad's coming.
Hurry.
No, no, Chilly, get off the table.
No, Chilly.
Chilly, Chilly.
Chilly, come on.
He's coming.
Chilly. Come on, Chilly.
Hurry, you guys.
Oh, no.
Chilly, come on, stop eating.
Not the ice cream, Chilly.
Not the ice cream, no.
Vanilla bean.
It's pretty good.
Come on, Tiger, there's something
I need to talk to you about.
(seagulls cawing )
Bobby: So when you were my age,
were you, like, you know, heroic?
Cole: When I was your age,
I was much smaller,
much skinnier...
and I was afraid of everything.
Bobby:
Really?
Cole:
But then my dad told me
that even a hero is just as afraid
as cowards.
Bobby:
What's the difference?
Cole:
Well, a hero steps forward
and a coward steps back.
So, speaking of
stepping forward,
I have something important
I need to discuss with you.
Okay, I didn't know Chilly peed
in your shoes until it was too late.
Okay-- two important things
to discuss with you.
But first, I was offered a job
to run the Bank Task Force
for the FBI today.
- I accepted it.
- Cool.
Okay, now we're federal agents.
I mean, technically you are,
but me and Chilly are too,
since we're all part of the family.
We are, right?
Of course we are.
It's just that...
this field office
isn't in Sunshine Beach, son.
It's in New York--
Manhattan, to be exact.
So we're moving?
When?
The day after Christmas.
What about Chilly?
Well, we're probably
gonna be living
in a small apartment, son,
in a high-rise
with no yard
and no place to run.
Dad...
Look,
Chilly is a huge Sapsali, okay?
He's not a baby Chihuahua.
He's meant to be outside,
running.
- That's what makes him happy.
- He'd be happy in an apartment.
He's in our house for 60 seconds
and he destroys half the place.
There's just-- there's just no way
we can take him.
I promise you we'll find
a great home for him,
somebody to adopt him
that will love him.
There's just no way
he can come with us.
(computer chirping )
Hey. Got your text.
Sorry about the move.
Does Chilly know?
Yeah, he knows.
Let's face it-- your dad's right
Chilly'-s no indoor dog.
Yeah, but Chilly would like
New York.
And I bet he'd totally
love the snow.
Actually, it snowed
in Sunshine Beach,
but only once in history.
Caps, me and Chilly are not in the mood
for one of your geek-o-rama jokes.
Seriously, in 1950.
The mayor's three-year-old son Sammy
lost his dog.
On Christmas morning, it snowed for
the first time ever in Sunshine Beach.
Sammy was able to follow
the footprints in the snow
and it led him
right to his lost dog.
They called it the "Sunshine Beach
Christmas Miracle."
That's what Chilly needs-
a Christmas miracle.
Your dad knows
how much Chilly means to you.
He's not gonna move until he's sure
you have found a home for him.
Yeah, Dad did say we'd find Chilly
a loving owner.
That's it.
That's it. That's it.
Who's it? What's it?
How's it?
If we cannot find somebody
to adopt Chilly,
we can't go.
He promised.
So all we have to do is make sure
that nobody adopts Chilly.
Interesting plan, has potential.
The question is, will it work?
It has to work.
Bobby's voice:
So that was the plan.
If Operation Christmas Miracle
was to be a success,
I'd have to make sure
nobody adopted Chilly.
It was time to begin
phase one--
what we kids like to call
"sucking up to your parents."
Wow, something
smells awesome-
omelet, delicious
cinnamon rolls, bacon.
Everything's better
with bacon, right?
What's the occasion?
Occasion?
Who needs an occasion?
Like I need a reason to make
the best dad a guy could ask for
a breakfast he deserves?
( Chuckles )
Okay, I suppose not.
Even when
I was spending hours
hand-making cinnamon roll batter
from scratch,
all I could think about
was how amazing it is
to have a heroic dad
who is the most heroic police officer
in the history
of law enforcement.
You know, it's illegal
to bribe a police officer.
I'm not trying to bribe you.
- Is it really?
- It is.
Now, son, listen to me.
Chilly'-s gonna get a great home.
I mean, I've already looked
at a pet adoption website online. Look.
We've got some potential new owners
coming by this afternoon.
Unfortunately,
I have to get going.
I got a call about another
kennel break-in.
Do me a favor, brush Chilly
so he looks nice and clean
for the prospective owners
that are coming by later, okay?
I want him to look good.
And thank you for this breakfast.
- I'll call you later.
- Have a good day, Dad.
Bobby, come here, please.
So I've reprogrammed
the motion detectors
and the door and window alarms.
So if anything funny happens,
I'm gonna get an alert
right to my phone.
( Beeping )
Oh, and on top of that,
Mrs. Hepacott
is gonna keep an eye on you
from next door.
Dad, I don't need a babysitter,
especially her.
She's really old
and she smells like cheddar cheese.
Ugh, she does kind of smell
like cheddar cheese, doesn't she?
I know, right?
Jasper: The break-in
was on Ocean Drive and 5th.
- We're two minutes out.
- Cole: Copy that.
- Can I turn on the siren?
- I don't think so.
Do you have a list of the dogs
that were stolen, Mr. Schmidt?
Yes, sir, Detective.
I knew you would be needing one.
Got one right here.
( Police radio chatter)
Oh, yeah. I recognize
some of these rare breeds
from the other two
crime scenes in the file.
- Valuable?
- Yes, sir. They fetch top dollar,
thousands even.
Even more if they're sold overseas.
This wouldn't happen to be your glove,
would it, Mr. Schmidt?
No, no, no,
way too fancy for me.
I use canvas-
works better on dog slobber,
urine, fecal matter-
- you know, doggy potty.
- Yes, sir, we got that.
How do we know
it wasn't your glove?
I don't think we need
to hear that.
You hesitated, Mr. Schmidt. I can tell
from the veins on your forehead
that your heart rate's
just increased by 22%.
Perhaps you're plotting what to say,
you're formulating an alibi.
Look, excuse us for a second.
Can I talk to you outside, please?
- What are you doing?
- What?
This is Sunshine Beach, not "CSI."
You need to lighten up a little bit.
I'm sorry
if I came on too strong.
It's just wearing down the perp
is how I caught the Cycle Stalker.
- Who's that?
- He stole over 100 motorcycles.
I chased him down 14 blocks on foot
and then I tackled him.
- 14 blocks?
- Yeah.
I was captain of the track team
in high school.
It's probably one of the reasons
why they wanted me to replace you.
I'm like the younger version
of you.
( Ringtone beeps )
- Something wrong, sir?
- No. Maybe.
A potential owner for my son's dog
is gonna be in my house.
If you want, you know, I can go down
to the station and analyze
the fingerprints on the gloves
while you deal with family business.
Whatever you need,
I'm there.
Whatever I need? Hmm.
( Knocks )
My dad called.
You must be Detective Juniper.
Jasper.
Ready to meet
Chilly Christmas?
Delighted.
Here he is.
This is how you want
your dog to look?
Look, nothing against your
canine fashion sense, kid,
but no one's gonna want a dog
that looks so...
- Ridiculous?
- Dorky?
Both. Your dad put me in charge.
Lose the outfit.
(whines)
You too, come on.
Whoo! Feel the burn.
(giggling )
Come on, arms up.
Arms up. Arms up.
Come on, guys.
Down on all fours.
(Chilly whines)
(sirens wailing)
Anything yet?
Well, I got a partial fingerprint,
but not enough to make a match.
- Dead end?
- Not exactly.
What do you mean?
This glove
is an Enzo Vattagio,
men's size extra-large.
They run about $3000 a pair--
not the typical accessory
you'd find on a dog thief, however.
So the question is, where is this guy?
He's probably 200 miles away.
No, I don't think so.
I don't think he's finished yet.
In fact, I think
he's right under our noses.
Caps:
Good job, Chilly.
Bobby:
Chilly, we did it.
Good afternoon. I'm here about
your Internet post on canine adoptions.
I would like nothing more
than to give
your rare Korean Sapsali
a warm, loving home.
You have the wrong house, sir.
This isn't 35 Bay-side Ridge?
Oh. Um, no.
- No, it's not.
- But it says so right there.
Sorry, Bobby.
He's good.
I'm sorry. Allow me to save you
from their juvenile antics.
So you're interested
in adopting the dog?
Absolutely.
Since our sweet little dog
Pickles passed on,
my three-year-old daughter Rebecca
has cried herself to sleep every night.
So do you like Chilly?
He's perfect.
We live on a beautiful,
huge farm
with lots of room for dogs
to run and play.
And of course I would pay you
handsomely for Chilly.
Jasper: Tell you what-- how about
I contact the owner right now,
and you can meet him.
I'm sorry, I didn't catch your name.
- Mr...
- Oh, my name? Uh, Nickels.
- Jasper Harris.
- So are you a neighbor?
Oh, no, I'm his replacement at
the Sunshine Beach Police Department.
He's moving to New York City next week
to join the FBI.
Wow, the FBI.
That's impressive.
Whoa, look at the time.
I gotta take my daughter Leticia
to a piano lesson.
Wait, I thought your daughter's name
was Rebecca.
You're a very observant little boy,
aren't you?
Of course I was talking about
my other daughter.
Well, it's been a pleasure
meeting you guys.
I'll be in touch.
( Door closes )
That guy was weird.
That's for sure.
What was the inside
of their house like?
Oh, did they have, like, a really big
Christmas tree or anything?
Where's the dog?
Complications,
to say the least.
The father of the house
is a constable.
Constable-
you know,
I had that too once.
I couldn't get off the toilet seat
for, like, an hour. It was terrible.
"Constable" in this case means
"Federal lawman," Mr. Hale,
the same way that "Hale"
means "idiotic fool."
So what's next?
Well, when I was on Wall Street,
and someone wouldn't
sell their company,
we'd do a hostile takeover.
So, gentlemen...
I guess it's time
to get hostile.
So you mean to tell me
that none of the prospective owners
- were any good today?
- Nope.
- Not even a little bit?
- Nada.
- Did you give them a chance?
- Nope.
- Aha!
- Dad, that wasn't fair.
You used that Jedi-mind-trick
detective interrogation thing on me.
That's right.
Are you sure you don't want
any help with that?
Cooking's not exactly
your thing.
I think you're right, buddy. I gotta
learn how to take care of myself.
Hey, you know something?
When you were little,
your mom used to prepare
a food theme
every night of the week
during Christmas.
- What kind of themes?
- Well, you know,
like she'd make a pear tart
for "partridge in a pear tree."
Or for "three French hens," we'd have
Cornish game hen, that kind of thing.
So what's the theme
for tonight?
( Hissing )
Whoa.
Clearly, tonight's theme is "seven
swans a-swimming in a grease fire."
You really miss her,
don't you, Dad?
Yeah... I do.
But you know what?
I'm lucky,
because I get to see her every day
when I look at you.
Oh!
I am making one heck of a mess.
You'd better take over, sport.
That's a good idea.
( Rapping )
Cole:
It's Lieutenant Stone.
- Hey, come on in.
- Hi. Sorry to interrupt.
I have a list of the stolen dogs
from the last kennel.
I tried to call you
on your cell phone, but--
Hey, Lieutenant Mel.
Hey, Bobby.
Anyway"
( sniffs )
Are you-- are you cooking?
Yeah, yeah, that's--
that's my attempt.
Are you busy right now?
- Come, come, come, come.
- Yeah, it smells really, really bad.
(whimpers)
So tell me how a tough cop like you
became an Iron Chef.
Stone: You don't know
that story?
My parents owned the most popular
restaurant in Little Italy.
It was their life.
Cole:
Now you're telling me this?
I would have had you come over
to prepare dinner a long time ago.
I love Italian.
I'm Italian.
Shh. Not a sound, Chilly,
or we're both in trouble.
So why didn't you become a chef
like your parents?
When I was 19,
thieves broke into my parents'
restaurant and stole everything.
And they couldn't afford to rebuild it,
so they had to close it.
And a week later I enrolled
into the police academy,
because I was gonna catch
those guys no matter what.
- Did you catch them?
- Not exactly.
But my partner tracked them down
and got the arrest.
You mean my mom.
I mean your mom.
I told you, Bobby, your mom was
a much better cop than I ever was.
Don't tell my new
partner that, okay?
Jasper? He's kind of weird.
Jasper's a little weird,
but he's a good guy
and everybody needs
a partner sometimes, huh?
- ( barks)
- ( coughs)
Sorry, I have a barking cough.
It's going around school.
( coughs )
You're on winter break, son.
It lingers.
( Barks)
What?
Aww. Oh, you're so cute.
Do me a favor, take Chilly
outside right now, okay?
Oh, for crying out loud,
let Chilly stay inside.
- He'll destroy everything.
- That's an order, Detective.
I like it
when she does that.
Hmm.
There you go.
Wow, I've never seen you
like this before, Stone--
gourmet chef, dog lover.
I always wanted a dog, but, you know,
puppies are so much work.
Mm-hmm.
What?
Well, I mean,
he's not a puppy anymore.
And he needs a loving home
with a loving person.
Are you suggesting
what I think you're suggesting-
- that I take Chilly with me?
- Dad.
It'd be like keeping him
in the family, right?
Besides, it'll make Bobby
so happy
knowing that he's with somebody
that really loves him. Right, Bobby?
- Well, sure, but--
- Stone, come on.
Clearly, you love the dog.
And he loves you.
Just take him, please.
It'll make our Christmas.
Huh?
Okay, okay.
Of course I will, Patrick,
of course.
Oh, I love you.
Thank you.
Bobby, is that the greatest
Christmas present in the world? Right?
We got a new home for Chilly.
It's great.
It's horrible.
So your dad decided to give Chilly
to Lieutenant Mel?
And now we're going
to New York.
I'm never gonna see my best friend
ever again.
Some Christmas miracle, huh?
Cole:
Bobby, I'm leaving.
So I'll be back later, buddy.
Do me a favor,
could you pack a little bit
until I get home, please?
- I will.
- And remember...
You and Mrs. Hepacott
are watching me. I know.
Too bad Chilly'-s an outdoor dog
too messy for inside.
Yeah.
Wait a minute.
If Chilly learns how to behave
in a New York apartment,
get his food and his exercise
and keep everything clean,
Dad would have to
take him with us.
But he can't do those things.
- We'll have to retrain him how.
- Are you kidding?
To be a dog trainer,
you have to be tough.
You have to be fearless.
You literally have to think
like a dog.
We don't know anyone
like that.
Maybe we do.
( Chuckles )
You said it yourself-
she bites like a dog.
Dude, don't even think about
thinking about
who I know you're thinking about.
You think?
(chuckles)
Oh.
-( Beeping )
- Okay, alarm and motion detector
deactivated.
Your dad's phone won't pick up
a single thing.
Awesome, Caps.
Okay, ladies, gentlemen,
- thank you for coming.
- Don't get excited.
I'm here 'cause you told me
I get a free lunch.
Caps: Yeah, and all
you gave us so far
are carrot sticks.
Without ranch dressing.
I don't do carrots
without ranch.
I will give you guys some
ranch dressing, okay? I promise.
But will you get us lunch?
Because carrots
and ranch alone
are technically an appetizer.
Welcome to Operation Christmas Miracle,
phase two.
What happened to phase one?
( Whistles )
( imitates explosion )
Our job..
Turn Chilly Christmas
into an indoor dog.
Uh-huh, and how are you gonna
pull that one off?
We will accomplish this task
by identifying
and teaching Chilly
the four main components
of a successful indoor dog.
Since we will not have
a huge yard outside,
Chilly will have to learn
how to exercise indoors.
(slurping )
All right, I'm out of here.
( Beeps )
Okay, so taking into account
the square footage of your property
and how many meters per second
Chilly can run,
I've preprogrammed
a workout regimen
which can keep him
at the exact same level
of cardiovascular conditioning
he can sustain
if living outdoors.
What's all that supposed
to mean?
I turned it on.
Then why isn't he moving?
The treadmill will begin
with the forward velocity of the user.
Meaning, he has to run.
Jeez, does anyone here pay attention
during science class?
No.
Bobby, I think there's a better way
of doing this.
Okay, Chilly,
on the count of three.
One, two, three.
Run, dash, sprint!
(whines)
Since all meals will be indoors,
Chilly will have to learn
how to access food and water
on his own,
without making a mess.
I call it
the Canine Cuisine-inator-
the ultimate self-feeding
and watering device
- for the discriminating doggie.
- Wow, Caps, I'm actually impressed.
- Well, thank you, thank you.
- You built this in one day for Chilly?
Well, not exactly.
I built it for my grandpa
for whenever we leave the house,
except for him it's filled with
warm milk and mashed potatoes.
So how does it work?
Simplicity in itself.
Chilly wants water-- he simply
taps his paw against the step here.
And same with the food.
One foot on the step,
take it off-- and pre-measured
amount of doggie diet.
Okay, Chilly.
Your turn, Chilly.
You thirsty, boy?
You thirsty?
He's doing it. It works.
Come on, boy.
Uh, that's enough
water, Chilly.
Chilly, just move your foot.
Bobby, I think there's a better way
of doing this.
Move your foot, Chilly.
- I'll disconnect it.
- Wait, no. Watch out for the--
- Aghh!
- (crashes)
...water.
I have to warn you,
this next lesson
might be kind of...
- Dangerous?
- ( giggles)
No, more like
kind of gross.
There's no way
you're getting me
in that bathroom
with that dog.
(Caps snickers)
Kizzy, we need it.
I'm no expert scientist
on dog pooping,
but shouldn't that
toilet seat be up?
Patience.
I just want to make sure that he
gets used to sitting up there first.
And then I'll teach him
how to use the tissue.
Just make sure
you teach him how to flush.
Never thought I'd say this,
but this makes me
miss school.
What if he does his business
on top of the toilet seat?
He won't.
(whines)
Oh, gross.
And now the final lesson.
And most important of all,
Chilly will have to learn
how to maneuver
around the house
without breaking stuff.
Yeah, right.
This I'd like to see.
( Both chuckle)
Bobby:
I've set up what I'd like to call
the 100-yard doggie dash.
Chilly has to get through
all six obstacles
without breaking
any of the ornaments
and then-- boom!
right on through to the finish.
( Whistle tweets )
Kids: Go, Chilly!
Go. 90. 90. 90. 90!
Oh.
-( Crashing )
- Oh, no. Oh.
Bobby:
Chilly-- oh, no.
No. no, no, no.
Careful.
Watch out for that--
-( clattering )
- Come on. Oh.
Hey, Sam.
Thanks for meeting us.
( Police radio chatter)
(toy squeaks )
Boy, they really
picked this place apart.
All right, rookie,
let's break down the crime scene.
What do you have?
Well, based on the deep scratch marks
on the door frame
and the fact that this is a Clark-370
deadbolt with a five-pin tumbler,
I'd say the perps used
a tension wrench,
anchoring a secure piece
of slump metal.
Then they bypassed the alarm system
using a wave jammer.
It's definitely a professional
break-in-
( grunts softly )
That's impressive, Detective,
very impressive.
Unfortunately,
you're completely wrong.
While the front is indeed
a five-pin tumbler,
the back door is a simple
two-pin lock
which you'll find on any ordinary
apartment door.
Those can be opened
by a simple turn of the key.
So they had the key?
The rest was just for show.
The suspects wanted everybody to think
this was a high-tech job.
So the perp didn't want anyone
to know he had a key
because the perp was the one
most likely person with a key.
A locksmith.
You have potential, Jasper.
Get some ice on that.
( Moans )
I'm okay.
(whines)
I don't mean to be
a pessimist here-
Uh, what's a pessimist?
Somebody who thinks
we're doomed.
Be a pessimist.
We're doomed.
(whimpers)
Some winter break.
I'd rather go out and play.
Hey, what are you doing?
I didn't do that.
This is no time
to play games
unless you're-
(whimpers, barks)
Play games.
What are you doing?
I knew there was a better way.
Don't you get it?
That's the answer to
Operation Christmas Miracle-
Play games.
( Machine buzzing )
(door chimes jingle)
( phone ringing )
Excuse me.
Sorry to bother you.
I have been in and out of locksmiths'
all day long.
I'm Detective Cole.
I'm looking for a Mr. Quartermain.
Quarterman.
Michael Quarterman.
Nice to meet you, Detective.
What can I do for you today?
Did you lock your keys
in your patrol car?
( laughs)
That's funny because it's true.
I have done that.
But no, I have a couple questions
I'd like to ask you if you don't mind.
I believe you have a contract
with the Sunshine Beach Plaza.
Is that correct?
Indeed I do.
And you have access
to several stores-
a women's shoe store, a card store
and a pet store, I think.
My brother handles
that job for me.
I'm not a big fan of pets-
you know, the mess,
the lack of discipline,
the disgusting odor.
I gotta ask you, if given a choice,
who really wants to clean up poop?
( laughs )
I'm not gonna argue with that.
But, you know, pets,
dogs in general-
they're pretty good companions,
I'd say, especially for kids.
Well then, I'm not overly fond
of children either
for pretty much
the same reason.
Listen, I got a busy
afternoon, Detective.
Is there anything else
I can help you with?
No, no, that's gonna be it.
I guess I'll let you get back
to locksmithing.
But before I go,
I'm moving to New York
and I'd like to get that sophisticated
big-city look that you've got going.
And would you happen to know
where I could buy one of these?
It's about your size, isn't it?
It's a Vattagio, very nice.
I don't shop locally,
so I'd have no idea.
Okay.
Well, thank you very much,
Mr. Quarterman.
Thank you.
- Merry Christmas.
- It's gonna be.
(door chimes jingle)
It's me.
Your boss. Who did you think
it was-- Santa Claus?
You probably did.
Listen, you got sloppy at the pet store
now everything's escalated.
That cop's dog is worth more
than the other dogs combined.
I need to know the status
immediately.
( Buzzing )
Kizzy: We are going about this
all the wrong way.
Why does Chilly tear everything up
while he's inside?
Scientists say high brain functions
in canines are underdeveloped-
Bzz-zz. Wrong.
It's because
he likes to play games.
( Barks)
I think she's right.
Duh. Of course I'm right.
Anyway, we turn all these
lessons into a game,
and bing, bang, boom!
you've got an indoor dog.
Kizzy, you're brilliant.
Thanks, Bobby.
Earth to Kizzy and Bobby--
nice theory, but how do we start?
-( Dance music playing )
- Come on, you guys, join me.
Show Chilly
this is all about fun.
♪ Five, four, three, two, one... ♪
( Barking )
That's it. It worked.
Okay, guys, let's do this.
It's time
to get Chilly with it.
- Get Chilly.
-( barking )
- ♪ Five, four, three, two, one... ♪
-( whistle tweets ) Let's go, Chilly!
♪ You want to see what I can do,
you just gotta ask... ♪
Yeah, Chilly, go!
Oh. Oh!
Come on, boy.
Come on, you can do it.
You can do it, boy.
Come on, come on.
Just keep running.
♪ Can you move it? Can you groove it? ♪
- .' Yes, I can .'
- .' Can you follow what I'm doing? .'
Come on.
See what Caps does.
- Okay. Oh, come on.
- ♪ This is the countdown ♪
♪ You know I won't let you down ♪
♪ Let's keep going another round ♪
♪ L'ma hit you with
the five, four, three, two, one ♪
♪ Yeah, this is the countdown ♪
♪ You know I won't let you down ♪
♪ Let's keep going another round ♪
♪ L'ma hit you with
the five, four, three, two, one... ♪
Bobby: Come on, Chilly,
shake the tail.
Yeah, good boy.
Yeah.
- Good boy.
- ♪ This is the countdown... ♪
He's dancing.
Awesome, Chilly. Good job.
( Barks)
♪ I'ma hit you with
the five, four, three, two, one... ♪
-( Whistle tweets )
- ♪ Yeah, this is the countdown... ♪
- Run, Chilly, run. Go!
- ♪ You know I won't let you down ♪
♪ Let's keep going, another round ♪
♪ L'ma hit you with
the five, four, three, two, one... ♪
See? You can do it, Chilly.
Good boy.
Go for it, Chilly.
Yeah. Good boy.
Yes! Go, Chilly!
Whoo!
He did it, you guys.
- Kizzy: That's disgusting.
- ♪ Five, four, three, two, one... ♪
- Bobby: Come on, Chilly.
- ♪ Want to see what I can do ♪
♪ You just gotta ask... ♪
Come on, one after the other.
You're doing it, Chilly.
Yeah, he's doing it.
You're doing it.
Yeah. Good job.
- Good. Good.
- ♪ My fears have gone away ♪
♪ It's time to fly ♪
♪ Can you move it?
Can you groove it? ♪
- ♪ Yes, I can ♪
- ♪ Can you follow what I'm doing? ♪
- ♪ Can you scream? Can you shout? ♪
Come on, Chilly.
You can do it.
♪ Three, two, one,
this is the countdown ♪
♪ You know
I won't let you down ♪
♪ Let's keep going another round... ♪
Yes!
♪ Yeah, this is the countdown ♪
♪ You know
I won't let you down ♪
♪ Let's keep going another round ♪
♪ L'ma hit you with
the five, four, three, two, one. ♪
(toy squeaking )
We're supposed to be working,
not playing with toys.
This is all the stuff
we stole from the pet store.
I thought the dogs could
play with it on the flight.
Oh, check this out, man.
It's a dog whistle.
Can you hear anything
on that microphone?
I can't tell what those kids
are up to in there.
Well, yeah.
Bobby and Kizzy and Caps
are teaching Chilly
a bunch of new tricks
so he could be an indoor dog
so Bobby could take him to New York.
Wait, you even know
their names?
Well, yeah. Keeping Chilly
is Bobby's Christmas miracle wish.
I really hope it comes true.
You idiot,
we're gangsters.
It's our job to make sure
the kid's wish doesn't come true.
You mean in this scenario
we're the Grinch?
If that kid talks his dad into
bringing that mutt to New York,
then we can't steal it.
Then we don't get our money.
That's not to mention
all the nasty things
Quarterman will do to us
if we screw this deal up.
( Puffs )
-( whistle squeals)
-( Chilly whining)
( Puffs )
-( whistle squeals)
-( whines, barks)
It doesn't even work.
What a rip-off.
( laughs)
Now that's odd.
Hey, blow the whistle again.
But it doesn't make a sound.
Hello.
It makes a sound at a frequency
only dogs can hear.
Just blow it!
( Puffs )
-( whistle squeals)
-( whines)
( snarls )
-( laughing )
- What? What is it?
Oh, I think I found a way
of making our little
Christmas miracle come true.
It's not even Christmas Eve.
Why are we making a fancy dinner?
Because we are
gonna be spending
most of our Christmas Day
packing up for the move, buddy.
And I wanted to spend some
quality time with my favorite guys.
Gosh, thanks, Lieutenant.
Well, not you--
you're welcome, Detective.
Actually, I'm glad
everybody's here.
Bingo, by the way.
After dinner I've got some
pretty cool things to show you guys.
A pretty cool thing, huh?
I can't wait to see that.
( Barks)
Everything points
to Quarterman.
Former New York
stockbroker,
then a suspect
in a bank fraud scheme.
He lost everything
and yet he can still afford
a millionaire's wardrobe
as a locksmith.
He had access
to the pet store.
We have no prints,
no physical evidence.
- This guy looks familiar.
- Only two more days.
- You're gonna be missed, Cole.
- You too, Stone.
( Door opens )
Hey, hey, Bobby, come on,
you know the rules
- about bringing Chilly into the house.
- Not to worry, Dad.
You're talking about
the old Chilly Christmas.
But now I'd like to introduce to you
the new Chilly Christmas-
indoor dog.
- Prepare to be amazed.
- Oh, yeah.
Hand me the dog whistle.
If it does what you say it does,
he'll probably send him right to
the pound and for $5 we'll get him out.
It's almost Christmas Eve. Isn't there
another way we could do this?
Indeed there is. I could stroll
in there, identify you two
as the thieves that broke into
three dog pounds and a pet store.
You'll be arrested
and I'll bring in two new blokes
who are complete imbeciles.
Would you prefer to do it that way?
And now for the ultimate demonstration
of indoor Chilly'-s talents...
He will maneuver himself
through the entire living room,
full speed, without breaking
a single thing.
That's it, Bobby.
You did it.
No, Kizzy, we did it.
I have a feeling
this is gonna be fun.
( Whistle tweets )
( high-pitched whistle
squeals )
- Stone: What's wrong with him?
- Come here. No.
All: Chilly, where are you going?
Chilly?
Come on, calm down.
Chilly, Chilly.
Cole: Okay, I think he wants
to go outside.
Kids: Come on, Chilly.
Chilly, where are you going?
No, Chilly, no.
-( Squealing continues)
- All: Chilly, no. Chilly.
Cole: All right, all right,
I got him. I got him.
Wait, I don't got him.
I don't got him.
(all shouting )
- Bobby: Chilly, no.
-( crashing )
- Oh.
- Bobby: Oh, no.
Not the trophy.
Perfect.
(Chilly whimpers)
Cole: And this is why I think
it's better if he stays outside.
Mission accomplished.
Let's go.
( Kisses )
♪ Oh, Christmas tree ♪
♪ Oh, Christmas tree... ♪
♪ Thy leaves are so unchanging ♪
♪ Oh, Christmas tree ♪
♪ Oh, Christmas tree... ♪
(dogs barking )
Ow.
That yappy little dog bit me.
I can't wait to shove them all
onto that cargo.
- Are all the dogs loaded up?
- Except for Chilly.
(cell phone ringing )
Quarterman.
Wait, the plane's coming now?
That's too soon, sir.
Understood.
Good news?
The plane leaves
in two hours.
We have to get the Cole dog now
or the whole deal's off.
Now? It's Christmas Eve.
That detective is gonna be
at home with the dog.
And detectives have guns.
I saw it on TV.
Detective Cole will not be home.
How?
Who are you calling?
The police, of course.
Bobby, we just got
an anonymous call
that the dog thieves are gonna
hit up another kennel downtown today,
so I-.
What's the matter, buddy?
Sit down.
You did your best.
Chilly knows that.
I know. I just...
wanted to save him.
You know? Be a hero...
like you.
Well...
you don't got to be anything
but yourself.
( Cell phone beeps )
Look, I gotta go. okay?
Make sure
you lock the door, please?
( Door opens, closes )
(dogs barking within )
There's a kid and a dog.
It's easy.
Lock the kid in the closet if you
have to, grab the dog and get out.
And don't even think of
coming back here without him.
- The kid?
- The dog!
You had to open your mouth.
I was just clarifying.
What's wrong with clarifying?
(dogs barking. Whining)
( police radio chatter)
Stone:
Anything?
Not a peep.
All clear.
What is it?
I don't know.
Something just doesn't feel right.
Jasper, call the office
and see if you can get a trace
on who called in
that anonymous tip.
I'm on it.
( Sighs )
It's our last lunch together, pal.
You should have
something good.
( Gate creaks )
I'm sorry, pal.
I really thought this could work.
I wanted this to be
our Christmas miracle,
like the time it snowed
for the first time in Sunshine Beach.
I'm really sorry.
(whines)
More than anything,
I really wanted to show you
that I could be as good a friend to you
as you've been to me.
Claus-sen:
That takes care of the alarm.
And that takes care
of the phone.
Come on, Chilly.
Wow, now this is a beautiful
Christmas tree.
Shh.
Oh my gosh, it's one of those
plastic Wiffle ball bats.
I've always, always wanted
one of these,
but my mom
couldn't afford it.
She probably wouldn't be
too proud of me right now.
For the last time,
can I please do the job
I've been hired to do
without being subjected
to your romantic ramblings
about a stupid holiday
centered around a fat man with a beard,
when all I want to do
is steal the flipping dog from the kid?
( Clatters )
Uh, Merry Christmas?
Come on, Chilly, run!
Get him!
Jasper: All right,
did you say 7th Street?
All right, copy that.
Thank you very much.
The tip came
from a cell phone
somewhere around the 500 block
of 7th Street downtown.
500 block of 7th Street?
That's about four blocks
from Quarterman's locksmith office.
Hey, do you still have
that file on Quarterman?
Of course.
It's in the car.
Is that a dog whistle?
Yes, sir.
We use them
for silent commands.
How would that affect a dog
that wasn't used to working with one?
Depends on the breed, sir.
Do you mind if I see it
for a second?
Sure.
Thank you.
(dogs barking within )
What's going on over there?
A dog whistle.
I think that's why
Chilly was going crazy last night.
Somebody was blowing
a dog whistle.
I remember this guy.
The picture's a little old, but he's
the guy that came to your house.
- Who?
- Quarterman. He tried to buy Chilly.
Bobby.
Come on, let's go.
(toilet flushes )
It's the kid.
How do you know
it's not just the dog?
Well, unless he's a magic
toilet-flushing dog from the circus,
I'm pretty sure it's the kid.
Boss said secure the kid first.
You go down to the end of the hallway,
- stop the dog from escaping.
- Okay.
I'm coming in, kid.
Behave yourself
and nobody gets hurt--
well, not much anyway.
(whimpers)
Now I've seen everything.
(grunts)
-( barks)
- (gurgles)
Come on, Chilly.
- Hale: Hey, hey, come here, come here.
- Bobby: Chilly.
Hale:
Stop running.
Hey, come here,
you little-- oh!
Bobby:
Run, Chilly, run.
Jasper: I should have recognized
Quarterman earlier.
It's my first case
and now your son's in danger.
I don't think I'm gonna be
much of a replacement.
Don't worry.
We're gonna save my son.
(siren wailing)
Um...
Chilly, do you remember
the obstacle course, buddy?
One, two, three, go!
( Waltz music plays )
How difficult is it
to grab a dog?
Come on.
(thumps)
( crashes )
Oh, no. We're trapped.
Chilly, what are you doing?
( Clatters )
Way to go, Chilly.
( Panting )
I'm really sorry
about all this.
I think you two
better get going.
Hey, here's hoping
your Christmas miracle comes true.
Christmas miracle?
I don't think so.
Come on, Chilly, run!
Cole: To all available units,
all available units,
we are code four
to the location on your screens.
Suspects are to be considered
armed and dangerous.
- ( Tires screech )
-( crossing bells ringing )
We are stuck.
- I have a confession to make.
- Now?
I'm not a hero.
L-- I didn't tackle
the Cycle Stalker.
I tripped and I fell on top of him
and I knocked us both out cold.
You weren't on the track team
either, were you?
I was on the chess team.
It's all right, Jasper.
You're a good cop.
You're gonna save my kid.
This is Cole.
We're blocked in right now.
We need about 60 seconds.
- Make that 30.
-( siren wailing)
Um...
- You'd better stop.
-( Chilly growling)
You're making Chilly mad.
I'm walking out of here
with that dog.
Sometimes in life
we must accept failure,
so my advice to you--
lock yourself in the restroom
after the dog and I leave.
That way you could tell everyone
that you're a hero
and no one will ever know
that you're just a scared little boy.
- ( Growls )
- Time to go, doggie.
Gotcha.
(screaming)
No!
Listen, you stay away
from my friend.
Police department!
Nobody move!
Officers, secure the two
in the kitchen.
Good job, rookie.
- Thanks, Dad.
- It was courageous what you did.
-( Chilly barks)
- My partner needed me.
Looks like you're gonna have to
get used to another hero in the house.
That's an amazing dog.
It's not just a dog.
It's his friend.
Bobby's voice:
My best friend.
By the time Christmas Day
rolled around a few hours later,
Sunshine Beach had the second
Christmas miracle in history...
with a fresh blanket
of new Christmas snow.
This year, it seems,
everybody got the perfect present.
Christmas. It's go time.
( Barks)
What's this?
And every man needs one of these
on Christmas morning.
Thank you very much, Chilly.
What happened to your bat?
Well, it's sort of a long story.
-( laughs )
- Stone: Merry Christmas.
Hey, hey, Merry Christmas.
- Hi.
- Hi. Hi. Bobby.
I'm glad you're here.
I got you something.
You didn't have to
get me anything.
No, no, that is a must.
I had to get you this.
You got me confetti.
Actually, that's my
resignation letter
for the Sunshine Beach Police.
- You're staying.
- Yeah, I am.
Dad, what about the FBI?
I told them I needed
another year to think about it.
I mean, it's the FBI, right?
They're not going anywhere.
Neither am I.
Bobby:
Yuck.
(Cole laughs)
Gross.
Merry Christmas.
- Stone: Merry Christmas.
- Whoo!
( Music playing )
♪ Oh, Christmas tree ♪
♪ Oh, Christmas tree... ♪
A dad who is
the most honorable-
Are you all right, kid?
- Sorry.
-( laughs )
♪ Oh, Christmas tree ♪
♪ Thy leaves are so unchanging ♪
♪ Not only green... ♪
Check this out.
Put that on real quick.
(screams)
♪ 'Tis cold and drear ♪
♪ Oh, Christmas tree... ♪
- Man: Oh, you have to say, "A-camera."
- Oh.
Take it again.
Wait, what is my line?
Man: "A-camera, holding mark,
second sticks."
- Yeah, here you go.
-( crew laughs)
♪ Oh, Christmas tree ♪
♪ Oh, Christmas tree... ♪
♪ Thy candles shine so brightly... ♪
Oh.
Oh, man, I hit too hard.
Sorry. Are you okay?
♪ There's only splendor ♪
♪ For the sight... ♪
Boo-yah! H00-ha!
♪ Oh, Christmas tree ♪
♪ Thy candles shine so brightly... ♪
( Dog barks )
- Man: Come on, dog, grab him.
- Woman: Hurry. Oh.
- Keep going.
- Come on, come on.
- Man: Reset.
- Man #2: Cut.
♪ Oh, Mele Kalikimaka ♪
Bobby.
( Screaming )
Bobby!
♪ Oh, Mele Kalikimaka ♪
♪ And a Happy New Year... ♪
Man:
Reset.
Man #2:
Say hi.
♪ Mele, Mele Kalikimaka ♪
♪ Oh, Mele Kalikimaka ♪
And a Happy
You stay away from my friend.
Argh!
(all laughing)
That was funny.
( Music continues)
This is Cole.
We're blocked in right now.
We need about 60 seconds.
Make that 30 seconds.
You gotta go forward, though.
Hey, Lieutenant,
all the dogs in the van
are present
and accounted for.
I just need your signature
on this--
Oh.
Yeah, I'll just-
I'll just file it myself
while you guys are doing
the thing that you guys are doing.
I'm just gonna-
all right, I'm gonna go.
- Say cut. ( laughs)
- Man: Cut. All right.