RADIO TRAFFIC
TV: 'Tonight's space shuttle
Challenger on launch pad 39B,
'as the mammoth spacecraft...'
'The countdown continues
for tomorrow's launch
'of the Space Shuttle Challenger,
with its crew of seven
'including New Hampshire
schoolteacher Christa McAuliffe.
'But a cloudy and...'
'As NASA ground crews
prepare the ship....'
'..officials believe
it will be a go...'
RADIO TRAFFIC
'The Challenger mission L51
has been...'
'The 51L mission, ready to go.'
'At seven o'clock,
the Challenger crew met
'for their traditional
pre-flight breakfast...'
RADIO TRAFFIC
Ladies and gentlemen of the faculty,
students, quiet, please.
Please welcome our esteemed
guest lecturer,
winner of the Einstein Award,
one of the ten most significant
physicists of all time,
winner of the Nobel Prize
in Physics, Dr Richard Feynman.
CHEERING AND APPLAUSE
I bribed him to say
all that nice stuff,
clearly I just escaped from jail.
LAUGHTER
Energy, from potential to kinetic,
gives you...
You see that?
No, don't write it down.
Not till you know what it means.
This will not hurt you.
It might hurt me.
APPLAUSE
Why didn't I have you
write down the equation?
You'd write it out.
La-di-la-di-la,
you'd feel pretty smart, right?
But now you understand it.
Mom! Hurry Up! I'm coming.
TV: ..'about three minutes,
and they think they can do it.'
'They are counting,
the ice is cleared away,
'and Challenger should be
going away very soon.
'Let's go down to
the Kennedy Space Center
'and take a look at Challenger
sitting on the pad
'as they continue the countdown.'
'Challenger's launch will be
the 25th space shuttle mission.
'It's estimated over 30,000 people
have been involved...'
Dale, you want some coffee?
Not now, Larry.
'..at a total cost
of nearly 40 million...'
PHONE RINGS
'There goes Christa McAuliffe,
first teacher in space.
'During the mission, McAuliffe will
be conducting scientific experiments
'which will be beamed live
to children
'in schoolrooms across America.
'The New Hampshire teacher
has described Challenger
'as the ultimate field trip.'
What is science?
Science is a way to teach
how some thing gets to be known.
In as much as anything can be known.
Because nothing is known absolutely.
It's how to handle doubt
and uncertainty.
RADIO TRAFFIC
'Ten, nine, eight, seven, six...
'we have main engine start.
'Four, three, two, one...
'Lift-off of
the 25th space shuttle mission,
'and it has cleared the tower.'
Yay!
'Roger roll, Challenger.
'Challenger, go with throttle.'
Science teaches us
what the rules of evidence are.
We mess with that at our peril.
'One minute, 15 seconds.
'We'll report more as
we have information available.
'Checking with the recovery forces.
'Obviously a major malfunction.
'We have no downlink.'
RADIO: 'The space agency NASA
has not yet confirmed the deaths
'of the schoolteacher
and six other astronauts
'who were on board the shuttle
Challenger when it exploded
'on take-off this morning in Florida.
'But there seems little doubt
that there were any survivors.
'NASA is conducting a news
conference at this moment.
'Challenger exploded
into a fireball
'and pieces came down
in the Atlantic Ocean...'
TV: 'Never in 25 launches of the
space shuttle had a life been lost.
'Today, that record
went down in flames.
'Tonight the search for survivors
turned up none.
'The search for answers
is just starting.
'Bruce Hall begins our coverage
'of a spaceship that became
a fireball and a national tragedy.
'Ready for launch.
'And lift-off.
'And listen to the cheers
of the young students
'of the first ever US
teacher-astronaut.'
'Moments later, a massive explosion.
'The cheering stops.'
I'm sorry, I can't watch this stuff.
'Seven Americans
with the highest hopes.
'A billion dollars worth
of the highest technology.
'Gone in seconds.
'The worst disaster
in the US Space Program ever.'
PHONE RINGS
JAZZ MUSIC PLAYS
Hello. Er, hold on, hold on. No...
Wait!
DOG BARKS
Feynman menagerie.
Sorry, who is it? Hold on, hold on.
TURNS MUSIC DOWN
Who's this?
Bill. Bill who?
Bill Graham?
I've got 15,000 former students.
Listen, pal, how did you get
a hold of my home number?
You're head of what?
NASA?
HE SIGHS
You got your results back yet?
Nope.
HE GROANS
What's bugging you?
Had a phone call this morning.
They want me to go to Washington
and sit on a presidential
inquiry thing.
What?
Find out why the shuttle exploded.
Did you say yes?
I'm not even that
into the space programme.
I know people died
and I'm very sorry about that, but...
Gwen...
I do my work, my teaching, you guys.
They just want to say that they
bagged the famous physicist guy.
They're a bunch of bureaucrats
and generals
with pokers up their asses, you know?
What?
You just said it.
They wouldn't know where to look.
You would.
You can't pass up a puzzle,
not as important as this.
I'm sorry, love, you're right.
I wasn't thinking.
Write and explain that
you're not fit enough.
I'm fit. I'm fit.
Who are you kidding?
I'm fit as a fiddle.
What do you Yorkshire folks say?
"I'm fit as a flea."
You want the proof?
Not especially.
Ohh...you smell so good.
OK, but...
Then you'd have no excuse.
SHE SIGHS
Damn you, woman.
SHE CHUCKLES
I'll have to wear a tie.
SHE LAUGHS
'The Captain has turned on
the no smoking signs.
'At this time, please extinguish
all smoking materials.'
Taxi!
It's cold.
NASA headquarters.
NASA, you got it.
Cold!
RADIO: 'With America still in shock
'after the world's worst
space disaster,
'the address given
by President Reagan
'in the hours following the accident
'now seems to have captured
the mood of a nation.'
REAGAN: 'We mourn seven heroes.
'We mourn their loss
as a nation together...'
So, sir, are you something to do
with the enquiry there?
Yeah, I'm on the presidential
commission.
Ah.
Alongside
some super-important people.
'..slipped the surly bonds of Earth
to touch the face of God.'
'Focus now turns to
the cause of the tragedy,
'as the Presidential Commission...'
They gotta get back up there.
Something went really wrong.
CAR HORNS HONK
Keep that. Thank you.
Sir...
Can I trouble you for an autograph?
Sure.
Who would I make it out to?
Oh...
Not you, sir.
I meant Mr Neil Armstrong.
First man on the moon.
You could mail it.
That's my driver number,
at that address.
OK.
I promise. Thank you.
Thank you.
So what do you expect to find?
Mr Feynman, what do
you expect to find?
Pardon me.
Mr Armstrong, I think we met...
Excuse me.
I'm Bill Rogers.
I'm chairman of the Commission.
We're very fortunate
to have you with us.
Hey, I've got somebody
who wants to meet you.
Dr Sally Ride.
Oh... Our first woman in space.
Well...
Nice to meet you.
You too. Mmm.
Good journey?
I took the red-eye from LA.
Don't ever do it.
Dr Alton Keel,
our executive director.
Nobel laureate, Richard Feynman.
Your name I recognise too.
Fellow physicist.
Formerly. I've been in Washington
several years. Oh.
HE CHUCKLES
How's your integrity?
That's just insulting. No!
Don't take me seriously.
Commissioners.
I appreciate you all coming together
at short notice.
We have a huge, vital task
ahead of us,
upon which might depend the future
of manned space flight
in this country.
Now, I intend for this investigation
to follow an orderly
and proper procedure.
We are not going to conduct it
in a manner that is in any way
unfairly critical of NASA.
Because we believe,
and certainly I believe,
that NASA has done an excellent job.
And I believe that the American
people think so too.
Anyone?
We have to accept the fact
that this shuttle
is the most complex machine
that's ever been built.
I understand it has more than
two and a half million parts.
It may be, after due consideration,
it's just not possible
to identify the cause.
Now...
In terms of scheduling...
That's nothing.
I'm sorry, Dr Feynman?
Two and a half million -
small potatoes.
No, really look - I don't know
much about space rockets,
but I know a little something
about probability.
Something I developed called, um...
path integral formulation.
It's quantum mechanics, yuck, yuck.
But, um...
Basically, what it means is that
you can figure out the probability
of something occurring,
not just when you get
two and a half million events,
but an infinity of possibilities.
However large
the number of causal paths
for whatever happened to Challenger,
an explanation can be found.
What are we doing here if
we don't think it's possible?
Right?
Er...Chairman Rogers,
I headed an investigation
into the failure of a Titan rocket,
and I suggest I outline
the procedure we used there.
I appreciate the offer,
General Kutyna,
but I think in this case there's
far less collectable evidence.
I don't like to contradict you, sir,
but in the case of the shuttle,
as there are human beings aboard,
it generates far more
database material.
Mr Rogers, what the general
said is the case.
There are external cameras,
there are black box recordings,
there are telemetry sensors,
there's a great deal of information.
Thank you, General Kutyna.
And Mr Armstrong.
I'm certain we can get back to this.
Please, anyone.
Chairman. Yes.
I don't know about anyone else,
but, um...
Coming in, I got
some major press attention.
I'd like to know what we're to say.
For the sake of
the astronaut families,
what are we saying at this point?
This is very important.
Any and all enquiries from the press
are to be directed
to Chairman Rogers's office.
So, the plan is...
lady and gentlemen...
we will reconvene
in five days' time.
But for the present,
enjoy your stay in Washington.
What?
We're not going to..? That's it.
Keel. We don't start right away?
(Great.)
Dr Feynman.
Bill Graham, head of NASA.
Thank you.
You're the guy that got me
into this.
Well, I took your physics lectures
way back, never forgotten.
I think you're going to bring
something unique to the Commission.
I abandoned my teaching and a lot
of important consulting to come here,
didn't imagine I was going to be told
to sit on my tush for a week.
So, here's what I'm going to need.
I'm going to need a crash course
in shuttle design.
I need to know everything on
how this thing was put together,
so if you can start supplying me with
the technical manuals and so forth,
and most of all, you gotta get me
straight on the factory floor.
Pretty new to NASA myself -
I actually only took over
two months ago.
That's bad timing.
We're based here in Washington,
but the shuttle engines and systems
are all out of the Marshall
Space Flight Center.
It pretty much takes care of itself.
You're the head of the whole shmeer,
I mean, you can get me
in this Marshall place,
otherwise I'm a busy fella.
I'll do my best.
I'll get on it right away.
Right, thanks.
I like that you didn't let up there
on the mighty chairman.
You take it.
I don't care for limousines.
Well, neither do I -
I'm just a two-star general,
don't get assigned a limousine.
Take the subway.
Hmm.
Pleasure. You too.
Taxi!
Oh, and there was a phone call
for you, sir.
Please call your doctor.
Dr...Weiss?
The elevator's just
to your right, sir.
'..to begin what may be
a lengthy process.
'Millions of Americans who watched
our heroes perish
'only 73 seconds after take-off
on that cold January morning
'are waiting for answers.'
'Nancy and I are pained to the core
about the tragedy
of the shuttle Challenger...'
PHONE RINGS
Hello.
Graham.
You got me in, great.
I'll take a plane down
in the morning.
Thanks.
Alpha plus.
'I've always had great faith in
and respect for our space programme.
'We don't hide our space programme.
'We don't keep secrets
and cover things up.
'We do it all upfront and in public.
'That's the way freedom is and
we wouldn't change it for a minute.'
Wow, it's immense.
This is an identical craft?
No, it's a training simulator.
but for your purposes, the flight
deck systems, the payload bay, etc,
virtually identical.
Want to see the flight deck?
You have four human beings
jammed in this space?
Can I sit here?
Yeah.
Wow.
OK. So...
they got S-Band
communication links...
environmental control systems...
cabin pressure gauges...
What is that? Emergency oxygen.
Don't touch things.
Hmm.
Come on.
Dick Feynman. I'm on the Commission.
I got nothing to hide.
If I was to ask you engineers,
never mind what the managers say,
but you guys...
Given all your experience,
what you thought the probability was
of an accident on any single launch,
what would you say?
I mean, if you don't want to say
out loud,
perhaps you could write it down
on a piece of paper.
So you're looking at the solid
rocket boosters.
OK, so...
They're not made here.
No - they're made by contractors,
Morton Thiokol in Utah.
Railroaded into Kennedy in sections.
That's a pretty standard
tang and clevis joint.
Look, there's no ways it
was the solid rocket boosters.
How so certain? Because they don't
fly with holes in them.
If it was the SRB, it would have
exploded on the launch pad.
These kept on flying,
you see it in the footage.
You watched the footage.
Tell me what you saw.
What went through your mind?
What did you think it was?
I thought it was the main engines.
OK. Why? Why the main engines?
Because of the complexity.
They're working at the outer edge
of any experience base.
In the blade technology?
No, no, no, it's more than
the blades, it's...
Hey...
There is no ways that I'm ratting
out my co-workers here.
Look, pal...
If we're not allowed to find out
what went wrong,
there will be no more co-workers.
All these jobs will be gone, kaput.
Won't be another shuttle launch.
TV: 'Of the events on the morning
of the 28th of January,
'the Presidential Commission
investigating the accident,
'headed by former
Secretary of State William Rogers,
'has met mostly behind closed doors.
'So far, it's given no hints
about what it believes
'may have been the cause.
'Meanwhile, off the coast
of Florida,
'the hunt for Challenger wreckage
continues.
'The combined NASA, naval
and coastguard operation
'involving 14 ships,
four submarines and 11 aircraft
'is combing
hundreds of square miles of ocean.
'Although NASA today released
pictures showing recovered debris,
'they've been unable to confirm that
they've found the crew compartment.
'In the absence of
detailed information
'about what happened to Challenger,
'speculation about the cause
of the accident continues to grow.
'Recent theories include everything
from a computer programming error
'to unusually strong winds.'
Chairman Rogers...
The boats just pulled in
the crew compartment.
Can you tell me,
was the oxygen activated?
Yes, Dr Ride.
It was.
We...
maybe won't make that public
straight away.
Excuse me.
Dr Feynman.
It's very important that this team
stays together all the time.
Why?
It's been reported to me that
you spent some time at Marshall.
Alone.
That's not very helpful.
Oh, Mr Rogers, I don't find it
helpful to stand around.
The other commissioners
are just being respectful.
And you're saying I'm not?
You understand the implications
of the oxygen being activated?
I do.
The astronauts
had to do that themselves.
Which means that they were alive
for at least some of those
two minutes and 36 seconds
before they slammed into the ocean.
Mr Rogers, I'm an atheist.
I personally doubt that
they're touching the face of God,
so I prefer to show my respect
by finding the cause
of their appalling deaths
and not stand around looking sad.
You know, I didn't even want
to be on this commission
but now that I'm on it,
I've got every intention
of finding out what went wrong.
You know, I don't know that NASA
did an excellent job.
The group will be leaving
in 30 minutes.
Except for General Kutyna,
who's made his own arrangements.
I also may have my own arrangements.
I can't force you to go.
Nope.
Are you going to work all night?
Er...if necessary. I don't know.
How do you plan to get back
to Washington?
Er...I got myself in
kind of a pickle.
I want to go back to Marshall.
Guess I'll hire a car,
but it's hundreds of miles.
I can give you a lift.
I'll drop you in Alabama.
Oh.
HE CHUCKLES
Thank you.
Here. 0600?
OK.
HE CHUCKLES
I may not get a limo,
but occasionally I get the use
of a government jet.
No..! You imagined I was going
to drive you 400 miles?
This is tremendous.
New for you?
You serious? No!
Whoa-ho-ho-ho!
Oh!
It's OK.
You know, what you have to realise
is that you are
uniquely independent.
Yeah, how's that?
Well...
everyone on the commission
has strong associations.
To whom?
Well, to NASA - Armstrong, Ride...
The government - Keel -
Rogers was Secretary of State.
And Bill Graham's even a personal
friend of President Reagan's.
And you?
Me, the Air Force.
BLEEPING
How does the Air Force...
Air Force three niner two six five.
INDISTINCT REPLY ON RADIO
Low on four three zero.
Heading three two zero.
Two six five.
How does the Air Force...
You're the only independent.
I'm independent.
I'm invincible.
Yeah...
but check six.
What check six? That's, um...
That's a fighter pilot's expression.
Six o'clock.
The blind spot. Directly behind you.
Uh-huh.
Watch my ass.
THEY LAUGH
OK, watch your ass here.
What? It's a little steep.
ENGINE ROARS
That's what we call the diamond.
Wow, now that is very beautiful.
RATTLING
What the hell?
You happy with that,
with that vibration?
Don't worry, it steadies again
after 65%.
But to get to 65%,
you gotta go through that?
Sometimes, yeah.
Can I see components, the blades?
Oh, what is that?
It's a crack...in this blade.
There's an obvious crack.
Yeah.
The blades often get those
after a flight,
but that's not
a flight safety problem.
Well, what is it, then?
We were told to log it
as a maintenance problem.
Only if it develops into a full
fracture, THAT would be a failure.
So a failure only happens
if it actually shears off?
Uh-huh.
Bull! The failure is the crack.
Well, you could argue that...
The failure is the crack - I mean,
because it's not in the design.
You know and I know
it's not supposed to crack.
Who has the rest of the test data?
Is that it?
I think we should start this
discussion on the step-by-step
process, so...
Concentrate the investigation
on the main engines.
There are cracked turbine blades.
As early as 1,375 seconds,
equivalent to full power level.
Also, at 4,000 hertz,
there are some nasty vibrations.
So you think the cause lies
within the engines?
I'd bet my last dime on it.
I just got back from Marshall.
I just heard an interesting new
definition of the word "failure".
Well, it's interesting that
you should say that, Doctor.
We've just received
the telemetry data from NASA,
and the sensors on the engines
show that they performed
absolutely perfectly.
Get out of here!
The engines began to shut down
as fuel pressure decreased,
exactly as designed.
That's extremely lucky,
because I'm telling you, those
engines have profound problems.
Now there is a step-by-step process
for us all to follow,
and I respectfully request
that from now on, you abide by it.
We're all trying to find the answer.
All right, we begin.
Step by step.
Crap.
Prof...
Don't let the chairman put you off.
Look, you should come by the house
some night for a bite,
if that appeals.
Yeah? OK, good.
Excuse me for a second.
(Listen...)
Graham, why didn't I know that we had
the results from the sensors
on the engines?
Is NASA drip-feeding us
information to suit itself?
I hear you. I'm doing this
with one hand tied behind my back.
I hear you, but...
RICHARD GROANS
Richard...?
RICHARD EXHALES LOUDLY
You OK?
I'll see you tomorrow.
I goofed. I thought I had the answer.
I was way off.
'So what are you going to do?
Are you going to stick with it?'
I don't know.
KNOCKING
Listen, there's a knock on the door.
I'll call you later. 'All right.'
I'm not sure why they chose to
just lay them in this order.
It's difficult to tell,
but this is...this is half that...
Chairman Rogers...
NASA's Failure Analysis team
supplied a still from camera E207,
trained on-flight.
It looks like it took a long time
for this photograph to appear.
Well, it's here now.
What is that?
A flame?
Coming from a position on the side
of the solid rocket booster?
Did we know that?
Did we know that already?
Did we get stills from other angles?
Am I right?
They had cameras all around?
Yeah. Yes.
Some of the cameras that were
looking directly at the area
were not working on the day,
I'm told.
Well, that's unfortunate. Hm.
May I have that, please? Of course.
DOORBELL RINGS
Am I super-late?
I had to pick this up at the lab.
No, no, it's not a problem.
Nice car.
You like it? Like it? I LOVE it.
I don't know if that enlargement's
going to tell us anything.
Let's see.
Well, it's somewhat clearer, no?
No, that just makes
the whole thing wider open.
But the flamer is sharper. But
that flame, where is it originating?
Perhaps what we're seeing
is the tip of a larger flame
on the other side
where there's no damned camera.
A flame is not a cause. A flame is
an effect, it's a symptom.
That doesn't tell us
which component split,
sheared off, cracked.
It shows us nothing.
It takes us nowhere.
I want to show you something.
Multiple successful launches,
identical components
and launch locations,
so what made that day special?
What were the variables?
Take a break, Prof.
Oh!
You lucky fella!
Yeah, I'd be luckier if I could get
it running. It's out of commission.
The carburettors seize
in this weather.
This must be how you stay calm.
Roger The Dodger's got me going
crazy with that process of his.
He's a lawyer. He's working it
through the way he knows.
Yeah, well, maybe some others
are kind of working it through
the way they know.
What? You think somebody's
working it for themselves?
Do you? It's Washington, after all.
I can't believe I got myself
back in this world -
government, politics...
And military guys like me.
You're surprisingly OK.
I guess you had your fill of
military personnel through the '40s.
What was your role back then?
When?
During the war, with the A-bomb.
I did the theoretical figuring.
It was the math.
I calculated how much fissionable
material would be necessary
to make an effective weapon.
It's not a good use of science.
You helped end the war.
RICHARD LAUGHS
Wow, this is beautiful!
Shall we try that Bordeaux?
You go ahead. I no longer drink.
If I drink, I can't think.
Oh, sir, we had maintenance
look at your heating.
Oh, thank you. Let me know
if you still feel chilly.
Could you help me find the number
of the National Weather Service?
There you go.
Can I borrow this? Sure.
Yeah, please. Not a forecast.
The temperature at Cape Canaveral.
Nearby?
Yeah, Jacksonville, Florida, on
the morning of the 28th of January.
Thank you.
That's the variable.
I got the variable.
It was freezing cold on the morning
of the launch. We need to focus
our questioning of the NASA managers
on stuff to do with temperature.
Temperature?
You're talking about ice?
I don't know.
Perhaps added weight of ice,
perhaps some metal component
becoming brittle.
I don't know which component.
There are only two and a half
million possibilities(!)
I'm pretty certain.
As certain as
you were about the engines(?)
Anything from NASA Failure Analysis?
Due this afternoon.
Dr Feynman's becoming
a real pain in the ass. >
Well, yeah.
You betcha.
MUTED DISCUSSION
Dr Weiss? Dick.
What are you doing here?
Well, if the mountain won't go
to Muhammad...
You didn't answer my calls.
So you tracked me down
all the way across the country?!
Nah, nah, nah. I'm at Washington
Hospital Center for a conference.
You got an hour to come over there?
Now? Yeah.
Sure. Hold on.
Um...I need to get this delivered
to Dr Keel, Presidential Commission -
this address.
It's extremely important
that it gets there.
Yes, sir. Thank you.
Good to see you!
With a vengeance? Mm-hm.
It's compromising
your remaining kidney.
Show me the cells. It's here.
RICHARD SNORTS
OK. That is not so pretty.
I read up on my chances
if my sarcoma recurred.
What's the deal
if we add in this lymphoma?
It's pretty difficult
to calculate the combined...
Don't weasel it, Doc. It's math.
Look, Dick,
it's not something we see.
The particular cancers you have,
they're...
they're extremely rare. The chance
of having them in conjunction...
Well, given what you were
doing during the war...
If it even matters.
What do you think?
Well, the radiation -
what safety precautions were there?
For the test, I...
For the test I had a pair of dark
glasses, which I never put on.
Jeez, they were...
they were crazy days.
We never slept.
We were on fire, you know,
getting the theory and the math
and the physics. It was a race. We
thought we were saving civilisation,
but then we found out the Germans
didn't have nuclear capability
and we kept on.
The science was...so exciting.
Should have stopped.
We threw a party. While people
struggled and died, we threw a party.
Hey, you were young.
I wasn't a child.
Yeah.
OK.
I guess we'll talk on the phone.
Sure.
I think there are probably
worse ways to go.
Hey, your hands are cold.
All the time. What is that?
It's possibly lymphoma.
The blood gets gummy.
Capillaries lose their flexibility -
they can't expand.
Thanks.
Yeah, just talk to me about
components that are flexible.
What about a solid rocket booster?
Go ahead.
Thank you, Louis.
Hey, I thought
this might be helpful.
It's a section model
of the SRB joint.
I don't want to see a model.
I want to see the real thing.
So there are two O-rings
and they squidge in here?
Correct.
Has there ever been
a history of problems with them?
Well, there has been some erosion,
even some blow-by.
"Blow-by" is what?
Soot getting past the first O-ring.
That would mean that
the seal is incomplete?
Right, but the manufacturer
said that... Morton Thiokol?
Right, Thiokol said that
the blow-by never got past
the second O-ring, never.
But if something prevented
the O-ring from doing its job...
..if it became rigid because,
for example, it was cold...?
I think what we're looking at
is the O-rings
within the seal of the SRB.
Lower temperatures would
diminish the flexibility.
Rubber would get harder,
less malleable.
At a certain point it would be
too rigid to move into the gap.
Bill...
I need any data NASA have
on the timings of spring-back.
Resilience of the SRB O-rings
in response to temperature.
Ladies and gentlemen, good morning.
Just a reminder that we have
many witnesses today
and the press will be in the room.
Ladies and gentlemen, I would like
to call the commission to order,
so please take your seats,
make yourselves comfortable.
Pilot to co-pilot, fix your hair.
Our first witness is Mr Mulloy.
Mr Mulloy, would you come forward
and identify yourself, please?
I am Lawrence Mulloy.
Solid rocket booster project manager
for NASA
at the Marshall Space Flight Center.
All right. Commissioners? Anyone?
Dr Ride?
Mr Mulloy...
in your position
at the Marshall Space Flight Center,
you'd be aware of
correspondence, memos, etc?
I guess I'm wondering
whether memos exist relating
to problems of launching with
O-rings at low temperatures.
I understand the morning of the
launch was exceptionally cold.
I'm not aware of such documents
at Marshall.
It's not correspondence, but
on the evening before the launch,
as a matter of routine, those of us
from NASA asked our technical people
and our contractors if there were
any concerns about low temperature.
Morton Thiokol, who make the solid
rocket boosters, presented us
with the fact
that the lowest temperature
we had ever flown an O-ring
was 53 degrees,
and they wanted to point out
that we would be outside
of that experience base.
But having heard the discussion,
we...we all concluded that there
was no problem with the predicted
temperatures, and I have
a document from the management
of Morton Thiokol to that effect.
Thank you. Thank you, Mr Mulloy.
You may stand down,
for the time being.
There's some guy in the back
who wants to say something.
I have something to add.
I beg your pardon? I...I need to add
to what he said, please.
All right, sir.
Please, step forward, step forward.
Identify yourself.
My name is Allan McDonald.
I work for Morton Thiokol.
I'm the director
of the solid rocket motors project,
so I was at the launch at Kennedy.
I'd like to say something
about the meeting
the night before the launch
that Mr Mulloy talked about.
Our Thiokol engineers...warned NASA.
They recommended NASA not to launch
below 53 degrees
and I agreed with them.
That was the coldest
that we knew was safe.
So you said not to launch
below 53 degrees?
And what was the actual
temperature that morning?
We believed that, at launch,
it was going to be much colder.
Below 32 degrees, below freezing.
NASA wasn't happy with that.
Larry Mulloy said, "My God, Thiokol!
"When do we launch? April?!"
Let me understand this -
now...are you saying
that NASA applied pressure
to change the launch recommendation?
Yes, sir, there was pressure.
They said, "Go review the data."
Our people in Utah came back,
and recommended to NASA to launch.
I refused to sign.
It is important that NASA be given
the-the opportunity to respond
to what's just been alleged.
We must allow...
What the hell is going on here?
Some people say
McDonald's doing a CYA.
"CYA". What is that?
That stands for "cover your ass".
But if they were warned...
The astronauts sure weren't.
I want to know what's happening
right here between NASA
and the contractors.
We need to talk more to HIM.
Richard. Richard,
the data you wanted
on the resistance timings
of the O-rings...
OK, thanks.
We need to hear more from him.
Can you stop Mr McDonald from...?
Damn.
Hi. I need to contact Allan McDonald
with NASA's Challenger
Failure Analysis team.
I phoned, but I was told
he's no longer in Washington.
That information is restricted.
He was on the team
but he's been removed?
I can't answer that, sir.
Look, all I want to do is speak
to Allan McDonald. What?!
So there's no-one I can talk to in
the whole entirety of Morton Thiokol?
There's no-one
who can answer my question?
Well, have a nice day(!)
General...
I tried to find McDonald.
No luck, and it's clear why
his bosses wanted to please NASA -
very big money at stake.
I'll catch you later.
Hey, Graham.
That spring-back on the O-ring
was measured over two hours.
It's useless information.
I'm really sorry.
That's what I got from Marshall.
Remember what it was to be
a scientist before government
got to you?
You don't think I gave you...?
On purpose...?
No.
Look, I have this grand title.
The NASA old guard,
they handed me a list
of who should be on the commission.
It was tough to persuade them
to take you.
I'm sorry to have gotten you
into this.
Well, when you read my notes
that I sent, you'll see the crap
that goes down at Marshall.
Notes? My write-ups.
Those analyses and my examination
of the crazy engineering.
Richard. Richard...
Sally, did you get a set of notes,
my observations?
No, I haven't had anything.
What the hell happened to my notes?
Sally Ride says she didn't get them.
Did the others?
OK. I had sent over from my hotel
a stack of typed-up notes,
wrapped in brown paper,
proper analyses
of all my observations
of the engineering so far,
with a request for you to have copies
made for each commissioner.
I have no knowledge of this.
No such notes ever arrived
on this desk. Perhaps you
can have them redone?
I don't have time for this!
You trusted your hotel
to deliver something so important?
Yeah.
Dr Feynman, please, as you can see,
NASA is now co-operating fully with
all of our requests for information.
Well, then,
have copies made of everything
and have it sent over to my hotel.
I don't know what's going on, honey.
I landed myself right back
in a load of political crap.
People seem to know a lot more
than what they're saying. 'Yeah?'
And I finally got
a ton of stuff from NASA.
It's full of anomalies.
How can that be critical one moment
and safe to operate the next?
Honey, I'm sorry.
It's best for me to call you later.
'Are you all right?' I'm fine.
'Honestly?'
No, I feel very well.
'Oh, all right. Speak tomorrow.'
Yeah.
"Ivory soap."
PHONE RINGS
General.
OK, look, this is driving me crazy.
I got a room full of NASA bullshit
that just makes me more sure certain
what caused the explosion.
The cold, OK?
We've got a guy who agrees with us.
He gets shoved off the enquiry.
We both know why,
but none of it answers.
There's a logic thing here
that I'm just not getting.
It's about
what is at the heart of this thing.
Why did NASA need to launch so bad?
OK, stop, Prof,
I can't answer this here.
Erm... I'll pick you up
in the morning. 8:15.
And bring full ID. OK?
Goodnight. Goodnight.
Where are we going?
We're going to the Pentagon?
ID, please.
Sir.
Thank you, sergeant.
Stand by outside.
Prof, why don't you
grab a seat down here?
Right there.
NASA. The agency of
the United States Government
responsible for the nation's
civilian space programme
and for aeronautics
and aerospace research.
Note the word "civilian" in there.
The project cost in US dollars
of running the space programme...
The actual cost, I get it.
And knowing this is unsustainable,
NASA needs to prove itself,
needs to bolster its purpose,
over and above civilian scientific
research and discovery, OK.
So park that for a moment.
The Air Force, meanwhile,
wants to upgrade Titan.
An efficient fleet of
unmanned rockets to deploy
spy satellites into space.
Paranoia. OK.
Whatever you civilians are told,
we are still deep in the Cold War.
What's it got to do with NASA?
NASA approaches Congress
with a deal.
That seems to make
great economic sense,
the government can stop funding
Titan and instead divert
the money to NASA, and the Shuttle
becomes sole access into space.
NASA knocks out the Air Force
and gets a funding boost.
Exactly. Yeah.
And the Shuttle
secures its raison d'etre.
Carrying spy satellites?
And NASA convinced Congress
that by 1986 they'd be able to
launch twice a month, every month,
and on each of these flights,
payload will be made available
to the Department of Defense.
Titan was my project.
But NASA reneges on its obligation
and instead of giving DoD priority,
they started taking Senators
up there, in...just
PR stunt after PR stunt.
And then,
launches start getting cancelled.
The press is beginning to notice...
Congress is getting jumpy.
Yeah, yeah, and the administration
is asking questions.
And then last December,
the launch is delayed six times,
and remember NASA had promised
Congress launch at any time,
under any conditions,
and then January 28th...
January 28th launch, it's cold...
It's very cold...
..and NASA feels
under extreme pressure.
And took the risk.
They took the risk.
Why did you tell me all this?
Do you wish you didn't know?
Downstairs, you made me sign
the classified information thing.
That's right.
So what's going on, Kutyna?
I mean, you got me trapped,
I can't spill any of this crap.
It would jeopardise national
security, the Soviets would know.
You guys can't launch
a damned thing in cold weather.
You've been playing me
the whole time. From the beginning.
That weird thing in the garage.
With the carburettor,
the carburettor and the cold,
I was supposed to take a hint. What
is this, some kind of game to you?
No, but it was a nudge.
I heard about the O-ring
via an astronaut friend of mine
who was tipped off, in secret,
by a NASA engineer.
This astronaut's career
has to be protected.
I had to let you get there
on your own, Prof.
Prof. Don't Prof me, you don't play
me, you don't screw around with me.
Listen to me and you'll understand
why I'm telling you this.
I can't do anything with it!
That's the point!
Don't ever tell me anything
I can't open my mouth
and blab to the whole world!
I got to... I gotta get out of here.
Listen...
Richard...
No-one plays me.
What is this, check six?
Remember, I told you that only you
are independent on this commission.
Do others on the commission...
Do they know stuff?
Everyone knows some, or all,
but they're all bound.
This is Washington.
What can be acknowledged,
how, by whom....
You go drag me into this?
No, it's absolutely not, you're
coming at it completely differently.
I told you, because I believe
that you, and only you,
can use what you have,
you can use the science
to cut through the bullshit,
to ensure that the real reason
for those deaths gets out.
That it's made completely
clear to the public.
NASA's forced to admit it,
and has to reform.
I wish.
Why can't people just say things
the way they are?
Cos it's politics, it's dirty, but
you can, you can drive through that.
You can... What's the, what's the...
Can I have your arm, please?
What's going on?
HE GROANS
No...
Not now. Not yet.
HE GASPS IN PAIN
Let's get a medic.
You get a medic right now. Yes, sir.
'80-yard touchdown!'
SWITCHES TV CHANNEL
'America is many things
to many people.
'To a 17-year-old kid,
it's the malt shop on the corner,
'to Grandpa, it's the front porch
in the Blue Mountains.
'To the mother and her family,
it's church....
'I'd Like to make it clear
that all procedures were proper.
'This is the same process
that was used in 24
successful shuttle launches
'as well as previous moon landings.'
'I know that...' Bunch of crap.
'..based on the data
up to January 27,
'right through the launch countdown
until the lift-off,
'all those actions were proper.'
'Do you believe you exercised good
judgement on the evening
'before the launch, regarding
the temperature? Absolutely.'
I thought I'd drop these to
the cleaners in the morning.
"Use Ivory Soap. 99.4% pure."
What? What did you say?
I was just, that old Ivory Soap ad.
"Use Ivory Soap, 99.4% pure."
Forget about the cleaners,
I got, I got notes
and stuff in the pockets, so...
You sure? Yeah.
'Perhaps it's time
to revisit the possibility
'that the Shuttle was a victim
of an act of sabotage or terrorism.
'NASA will present at
Wednesday's televised...' Jeez!
'..along with members
from Morton Thiokol.
'Both parties will detail...'
Only 99.4%, you bastards!
'..by the commission, is unclear
'whether we will ever have answers
as to what caused this disaster...'
Gwen!
Gweneth!
What's the matter?
Papa, what's wrong? What?
I have to go back to Washington.
Michelle, go back to bed, go on.
Go on, back to bed, it's all right.
You need to be here.
You need to be taken care of.
We can't come to Washington
with you. She has school.
She has no idea
how seriously ill you are.
I have to.
People died.
It will happen again. If I don't,
what have the weeks been for?
I mean, you're the one
who persuaded me.
And you said it yourself -
let someone else do it.
You can't,
you don't have to carry on now.
Nobody's got the right
to ask that of you.
I'm the one asking me.
I'm the one asking.
OK.
I just wanted to have you to myself
for as long as possible.
Honey, will you help me?
I got to get it all down.
My notes, everything I found out.
Got to be one hell of a paper.
The original tang and clevis seal
design failed to anticipate
the enormous pressure,
caused by the burning propellant,
would cause the walls to bow outward,
a phenomenon known as joint rotation.
OK? Swell.
My blood is freshly laundered.
Dick, you know the affects
of the dialysis are only temporary.
Life is pretty temporary.
'You're listening to drive time
on WTBX with Steve O'Brian.
'Power one-o-three on WTBX.
'We are definitely addicted to
our ten-in-a-row power play for all
'you folks in Washington, coming up
next, Miami Sound Machine...'
Dr Feynman, can you comment
on the progress of the commission?
What's your take
on the sabotage theory?
I'm not at liberty to speak.
The commission?
Through there, sir.
I'm sorry, sir.
You can't go in there.
Who says so?
Not without a tie, sir.
Give me strength.
I'm sure this is going to look
a lot more dainty.
Good evening, gentlemen.
My findings,
developed, processed, distilled,
I've saved you the trouble
of running them off
in case the copy machine's broken.
Hey, Bill. Will you do the honours?
Sure.
It's all here. Hi, Neil. Would you?
Design flaws in the boosters.
Management failure.
A cold day. You OK?
I had the flu, but now it's flown.
Why don't you just take this chair?
Thank you.
And thank you.
For your fine, patient,
methodical work over the last weeks.
It's been a difficult period.
Especially for Dr Feynman.
Welcome back, Doctor.
And Doctor, I'm sure that we'll want
to include some of your new material
in our final report.
Please remember this is
a very important hearing.
We're expecting a lot of press.
And it will be televised,
so please do be prompt. Thank you.
Prof.
It's happening again,
Rogers is going to bury my work.
Yeah, and I just got cornered
outside by the press.
Me too.
I think they're ready
to go with "unproven".
Yep,
or a sniper on the grassy knoll.
I eat a lot of pickled beets.
General, I haven't a damned clue
what we're going to do.
Despite what you may think,
I am pleased to see you back.
General. Chairman.
We have a major difficulty.
The people who best
understand the Shuttle are
the people giving evidence
but they have the most to lose
by explaining it clearly.
The public is simply mystified.
Somehow, we need
to penetrate the fog.
Welcome back.
We know what Marshall's
strategy's going to be.
Smokescreen. Manipulate the science.
Yeah, they'll make it
into a fuzz dazzle.
That kills me.
I have to go.
You OK? I am fine.
Neil.
I've been meaning to ask you.
Yes, Richard.
This is for a friend. An admirer.
Right. Of course.
Thanks so much, Neil.
Sorry, embarrassing but...
Anything for you, Richard.
Goodnight.
Take care of yourself.
You asked me for something, now
I'm going to ask you for something.
No, you picked me up
a couple of weeks ago.
Morning. Morning.
There's my end of the deal.
All right.
Here's what I need from you.
A hardware store.
A hardware store. Why would
a super important person want...
Do you know a hardware store
that opens early? I know a place.
Come on. Get out of bed.
The astronauts' families
will be seeking clarity
on what precisely caused
the deaths of their loved ones.
NASA witnesses
will be answering those questions...
Graham, make sure you have
a section model of a SRB joint.
Are we late? We're good for time.
Hey. Morning, General.
I guess this is it.
Good luck.
Would the witnesses please rise?
Do you swear that the testimony
you will give before this commission
will be the truth, the whole truth
and nothing but the truth,
so help you God?
I do. I do.
Mr Mulloy, did you have
any apprehension
that a delay in launch would reflect
badly on you or NASA Marshall?
No, not at all.
My decision to proceed with
the launch as recommended
by the Thiokol official
was based solely on the data
presented by Thiokol Engineering.
Here comes the smoke.
This is shot right about
August 19th,
and the thing of interest here is
what we have seen in the O-rings.
See, the fact is,
before Challenger, we had seen
no anomalous O-ring erosion
for about a year.
Mr McDonald stated that he thought
that what had been said was
very important - that the secondary
O-ring was in a position to sealed
during the time of blow-by.
So you interpreted
Mr McDonald's comment
as a statement in favour
of proceeding to launch?
Yes, I certainly did because
Mr McDonald was seated close by,
and it was clearly
a supportive comment.
I have a question.
Can you remind me what NASA
calculates the probability
of shuttle failure to be?
Failure meaning
the loss of the vehicle,
and the deaths of the entire crew.
Dr Lovingood.
Certainly. That would be...
..one in ten to the power of five.
Really?
Would you explain that?
Yes, that the probability
of mission success is 100%.
Minus Epsilon.
Epsilon. That's a pretty fancy word.
Well, let's put all that
you've said there into English.
So that's, that's one failure
in every 100,000 flights.
So you claim that the Shuttle
would fly every day for 300 years
before there would be
a single failure.
That's crazy, I mean,
how would you ever even test that?
NASA arrived at that figure
because it was a manned flight.
Because there are people on board
but that's not a scientific
calculation, that's...that's a wish.
And interesting.
But the figure is very different
from that of NASA's own engineers.
Based on their direct experience,
and observation of many known
component problems,
some of NASA's engineers
calculate the probability of success
as only 99.4%.
In other words, that's roughly
one flight in every 200 will fail.
AUDIENCE MURMURS
Rogers, time out.
I think this would be
an appropriate time to take a break.
One in 200!
Wow. That's not what
the astronauts were aware of.
Potential disaster
every three and half years.
It won't convince anybody,
there's no proof,
people don't get probability,
it's math.
But maybe...
The segment joint test we did,
the development
and qualification motor test we did,
as a basis for understanding
what we could expect
to happen on the joints.
Mr Hardy. Certainly.
As we see, the temperature
at which the O-rings
would lose their integrity
would be in the
minus 40 to 50 degree range.
Minus 40 to 50 degrees.
Fahrenheit? Sir.
So they'd maintain their integrity
down to 80 degrees below freezing?
That is correct.
Mr Rogers? Oh, yes. Thank you.
These O-rings are supposed
to expand to make a seal,
is that correct? Yes, sir.
So, for the people to understand,
what if we take the O-rings out?
Not have them.
Well, then hot gas would
expand through the joint.
For the seal to work correctly,
the O-ring has to be made of rubber,
not something like lead, which when
you...when you squash it, it stays?
Yes, sir.
Now if the O-ring weren't resilient
for a second or two,
that would be enough for
a very dangerous situation
and that could likely occur
at low temperatures.
No, as Mr Hardy has shown,
they are effective
down to minus 40 to 50 degrees.
Well, then I just have
one comment for the gentlemen,
that I have always believed
that any scientific concept
can be demonstrated
to ordinary people,
people with no specialist knowledge
or even much scientific education.
Co-pilot to pilot,
not yet, just wait. What?
HE WHISPERS: All right. OK, go.
See. I took some of...of this...
stuff from your seal.
And I put it in
nothing more than ice water.
And I discover...
..that if you put it
under pressure...
..for a while, and then undo it...
..it doesn't stretch back.
It stops. At the same dimension.
In other words,
for a second or two, at least,
and more seconds than that,
there is no resilience
in this particular material
at the temperature
of 32 degrees Fahrenheit,
the temperature of a cold soda.
I think that has some significance
for our problem.
AUDIENCE CHATTERS
REPORTERS JOSTLE AND SHOUT
Whatever the eventual
Commission Report, I will be writing
up my own independent appendix
with all my findings, all the design,
the engineering
and the management problems,
which I will be handing
to the President myself.
How much did NASA know about
the effect of cold, Dr Feynman?
Look. Ask him.
Let us make recommendations
to ensure that NASA officials
deal in a world of reality.
Understanding technological
weakness and imperfections
well enough to be actively
trying to eliminate them.
NASA owes it to the citizens
from whom it asks support
to be frank, honest and informative.
For a successful technology,
reality must take precedence
over public relations,
for nature cannot be fooled.
APPLAUSE
Dr Keel, please.
And Mr President, this appendix has
been prepared by Professor Feynman.
And by the way, I think I've
figured out who was your source.
You said, "This astronaut,
this astronaut."
If it was a guy,
you would have said "he."
It's OK. I can keep shtoom.
If you ever fancy
a ride in that old Buick...
Yeah. If the weather's warm.
It would have to happen pretty soon.
I'm sorry this is taking your time.
I'm not sorry.
I would have been tremendously
sorry if we'd lost
but as it is, it was...
Not a good use of science.
It's a good use of science.
I'm OK.
I'm OK with it.
I guess there is a kind of afterlife.
The few bits and pieces that we do
might get remembered.
General...
..fix your hair.
How would you react
to the kind of ethical
and political dilemmas
portrayed in this film?
Find out with the Open University's
online quiz.
Go to bbc.co.uk/challenger
and follow links to the OU.
Subtitles by Red Bee Media Ltd