"Taboo: A prohibition against
touching, saying or doing something...
...for fear of immediate harm
from a supernatural force."
It's creepy.
And I don't... I don't really get it.
The thing about taboos
is that society shuns them.
But there's something
very tempting about them.
The game will test whether
we succumb to the taboo.
- Such as?
- Such as:
Would you cheat on your spouse?
That's taboo? I thought that was
considered good country-club etiquette.
- You belong to some sick clubs.
- Everyone in?
- Oh, yeah.
- Yeah.
All right.
The rules are easy.
You get one card.
Don't let anyone look.
You answer "yes" or "no"
to the question on it.
How do we know who answers what?
We don't. Nobody reads their own card.
It's anonymous.
A total and complete lack
of accountability. I like it.
- Like voting.
After we've answered the cards, we'll
shuffle them and pick one to read...
...and we'll see
what we're all truly made of.
I'm not so sure about this.
- It's just a game.
- Rather play dress-up?
It'll be fun, trust me.
Oh, that's nasty.
This is the most disturbing question
I've ever been asked.
Is "maybe" a good answer?
Don't look at me like that.
- Who goes first?
- Not me.
Would you guys shut up, already?
Okay. Let's read them.
Question: "Would you have sex
with a minor?" Answer: "Yes."
We begin our slide into the moral abyss.
Oh, naughty, naughty.
Shit, I had sex before I was 14.
I don't see what the big deal is.
I didn't think they had altar boys
in the Jewish faith.
Okay, Piper. Your turn.
Question: "Would you sleep
with a person of the same sex?"
Answer: "Yes."
What a great game to play
with our best friends.
- Fuck Taboo. Let's have an orgy.
- Or enroll in group therapy.
Maybe you need new friends.
Actually, we all seem pretty
well-suited for each other, so far.
Your turn.
All right, the question is,
"Would you have a threesome?"
The answer is yes.
- Two girls and one guy?
- Does it matter?
Mr. Right-Wing Conservative
over there...
...looks like he might think
two girls would be fun.
Okay, my turn.
Question:
"Would you have sex for money?"
Answer: "Yes."
I like sex, okay?
That does not make me a hooker.
- It also doesn't make me a bitch.
- That's my baby.
Question:
"Would you sleep
with your partner's best friend?"
Answer:
A very disappointing no.
There is one good person
amongst us sinners.
Christian.
Don't you have to be less educated
to be in the Christian Coalition?
So says the prep-school anarchist.
No, I'm just a shallow,
materialistic party girl.
And at least I don't pretend
to believe in principles.
Well, I believe in principles.
True, he just doesn't have any.
Christian, stop pouting
and read the last question.
I think he's scared to read the question.
- Just read the card.
- Okay. "Would you sleep...
...with a relative?" Answer: "Yes."
That's fucking disgusting.
I'm glad that you all could make it.
We're glad that you all could make it.
That's so cute, Christian.
We're glad everyone could make it.
We are.
- Grow up, Piper. Things change.
- Easy for you to say.
Ladies, please. We haven't
seen each other since graduation.
Could you be nice?
Stop the whiny, insecure,
competitive bullshit. Please?
Yeah, I'm the Jew. It's my job.
Oh, you like that, Christian? Jew.
It's funny, Jewish. It's good. Right?
Yeah, I bet you know
a lot of good Jew jokes, huh?
- Yeah, there's the...
- Christian. He's kidding.
No, no, let him finish.
Hey, I mean, it's his new house, huh?
He owns this big thing.
He's the sole heir.
Who's the big winner, Christian?
Don't worry about him, Christian.
He's just a sore loser.
What the fuck did I lose?
The ultimate trophy wife. Elizabeth.
- Slut.
- Bitch.
- Like there's a difference.
- But there is.
You see, a slut gets to sleep
with anyone she wants to. Moi.
And a bitch...
...well, a bitch sleeps with no one.
Not even with her fiancé.
Vous.
Look at that. One minute.
One minute left
and this year is finally over.
- I thought it was a good year.
- Yeah.
No, baby, it was a great year.
Spare me.
Excuse me?
Fifty seconds.
Anybody have any New Year's resolutions?
Mine never come true.
Maybe you should shoot for something
a little more reasonable, like...
...stop drinking...
...every other day.
- There's always next year.
- Yes, there is.
Here. A toast.
To the four people in the world
that I most love to hate.
And to the one that I hate to love.
To relationships that last as long
as we live. As short as that may be.
- Another 12 seconds.
- "12 seconds."
I'd like to make a toast to bread.
Because without bread,
there would be no toast.
A toast for the cure to cancer.
And ending world hunger.
And everything else
I'll never be involved in.
To special people. And special times.
Special Olympics.
- Here, here.
- Lt is five...
...four, three, two, one.
Christian?
- Oh, my God.
- Christian?
It's really not a bad house. It's...
Here, I'll just light this.
Let's do this the right way.
Just relax, there's a storm
outside, remember?
Come on, let's do this right.
Toast. Happy New Year's.
Happy New...
For God's sake!
This is ridiculous.
- Are you expecting anyone?
- Not a soul.
How's work, Benjamin?
- I quit.
- Good for you.
Good for me because
I would have been fired.
Sorry, I didn't know.
I really didn't think you were cut out
for investment banking.
You're creative, and banking's
just about money and power, so...
What are you gonna do now?
Investment banking...
...at a firm where I'll make more money
and have more power.
What about you, Adam? How's Boston
and law school treating you?
Law school sucks.
I miss New York.
- Why?
- There's not enough hookers in Boston.
- It's a fucking Catholic city.
- Good drinkers though, right?
This is true. But what good is getting
drunk if you can't get a hooker?
- Piper, how's everything...?
- Elizabeth. I know what you're doing.
Trying to make polite, grown-up talk.
Stop. We hate it.
I'm sure we'd prefer uncomfortable
silence and shocking statements...
...to tiresome pleasantries
and chitchat banter.
- Well said. A mouthful, but well said.
- What do you want to talk about, then?
- Dirt.
- Gossip.
I like rumors. Anyone have any?
Benjamin and I are breaking up.
No shit. And why is that?
Benji?
It's because my penis is too big.
Yeah, it is.
Somebody rained on you.
Got a package marked
"personal and confidential."
I didn't think anyone delivered
on New Year's after midnight.
- Well, it's here.
- Well, what is it?
Christian, what is it?
"Prostitute. Infidel.
Homosexual.
Rapist. Hypocrite."
Which one of you did this?
Let me see those.
- Who sent it?
- There's no return address.
How do you know it's for you?
Let me see those.
Excuse me.
They're the answers to that
Taboo game we played.
They're not answers, Christian.
Those are accusations.
Somebody here is obviously
fucking with us.
Who would be so juvenile?
Not it.
- I hated that game.
- There you go, Piper. Revenge.
Now, that's a good motive.
No, it's probably someone
who enjoyed the game...
...and now they want
to play round two.
I liked it. I didn't do this.
Well, I guess whoever isn't either
a prostitute, a rapist...
...a gay, an infidel or a hypocrite...
...is, you know, the likely candidate.
Right?
Can I, please?
I'm gonna get some more wine.
Hey, do you guys want red or white?
- Asshole. What are you doing?
- Asshole?
Elizabeth, that's not a very nice word
for you to use.
I wanted to ask you...
...why the fuck did you send
that package?
What makes you think I did that?
It's because you think you're so much
better than the rest of us, don't you?
Elizabeth, we went out for, what,
two years, right?
And we slept together... Never.
Not once.
You know you just think you're as pure
as the Virgin Mary, don't you?
That's not true.
I was wondering if you and Christian
were playing hide the sausage.
Wrong again. I'm waiting
till I get married and you know that.
- I'm going to scream.
- Yeah, I know, you said that.
But you know what? I think that
probably would be the best idea.
Because, I mean, after all,
I am the "rapist."
Help!
- Try it again. Do it again.
- Christian!
Listen, Elizabeth, there's two
reasons why that's stupid.
One, it hurts my ears
when you scream that loud...
...and two, these walls, Elizabeth,
they're soundproof.
So no one can hear anything
that you're saying.
Oh, by the way, do you know
what "statutory rape" is?
Last year, after we left this house,
I got caught with an underage girl.
She was 14 going on, like, 24.
Lt just seemed fine. She was a hell
of a lot more mature than I was.
We only had sex once.
And, really, it wasn't even that good.
- Why are you telling me?
- Because the girl blackmailed me.
One week later I received a videotape
in the mail...
...of us screwing at her apartment.
Or, actually, her parents' apartment.
There was also an address to a P.O. box
for me to send my monthly check.
- I'm sorry.
- You're sorry?
I'm sorry no one ever told me
I had such a hairy ass.
Christian?
- No vino?
- Where's Christian?
Don't worry about that.
I decided to make margaritas.
- Where is everybody?
- Drinking, smoking and fucking, I hope.
Why do you always have to be so crass?
My manner isn't pleasing.
Do you want me to change it? I will.
I can be just as prim and proper as you.
I'll feel guilty for anything bad
and resent anyone having a good time.
It's called growing up, right?
Have you seen Christian?
I was telling Elizabeth how we're happy
we got the group together. You okay?
You bitches are killing me.
Margaritas in the wintertime?
What's wrong with you people?
What? I like them.
Piper, a margarita is a summer drink.
This is totally inappropriate.
Tropical drink.
- Mexico is fun. I love para-sailing.
- Have any of you seen Christian?
- No.
- What's wrong?
- She doesn't like margaritas.
No, it's Adam. He attacked me
down in the wine cellar.
- What did...? He touched you?
- No, he insulted and threatened me.
Did he insult you or attack you?
There's a big difference.
Unless, of course,
he attacks your character.
Elizabeth. What did he do?
Adam?
Hello?
- Nobody's down here. This is stupid.
- This is stupid.
I never wanted to have this
reunion weekend in the first place.
This house is for entertaining.
Tomorrow night, it's just
gonna be me and you.
We'll have a nice big steak
and a bottle of Lafitte Rothschild.
Our favorite.
Oh, my God.
Jesus.
- Is he dead?
- You should know! Jesus!
What are you talking about?
When you said he attacked you,
Elizabeth...
...I guess you were telling the truth,
only you had it backwards.
Except for the note-card and the fact
that he has a hole in his stomach.
Okay. Take this.
- Who goes first?
- Question:
"Would you have sex with a minor?"
Answer: "Yes."
We begin our slide into the moral abyss.
Oh, naughty, naughty.
Shit, I had sex before I was 14.
I don't see what the big deal is.
All right. What are you gonna do?
What am I gonna do?
What are we gonna do?
I did not do this. I swear.
- Who did?
- I don't know.
Did you have something to do
with those cards? Tell me.
No! lt doesn't...
Why does that matter?
Adam's dead.
Somebody in this house killed him.
And the only one that wasn't
in the bar was you.
All right. Just, don't worry, okay?
Don't worry? Somebody in this house
is a murderer. And we're stuck here.
Listen to me.
We're gonna go upstairs and you're
gonna pretend like nothing is wrong.
- How am I supposed to do that?
- However you can.
Obviously, Adam did something
to deserve this.
Unless there's something
you're not telling me...
...I cannot think of a reason why
someone would want to do this to us.
- But what about the others?
- What about them?
All right, just stay close to me.
All right, as soon as this storm
breaks, we are leaving. Okay?
Here. Wipe your hands.
Okay, Benji. Why don't you show me
how you hold yours?
Like this.
That's good. You can show me
on the table now.
Did you find your rapist?
- What?
- Didn't you say Adam tried to rape you?
No, I didn't. I said he attacked me.
I think he found some porno mags
in the basement.
- Party pooper.
- Lt doesn't mean the fun is over.
- What do you propose?
- Naked Twister.
There are consequences for acting foolish.
Immortal... Imm...
Immorality doesn't pay.
Okay. Fine, Piper. Spin the bottle?
I really don't feel like
playing any games.
I didn't ask you.
Truth or dare, Benjamin?
- Truth.
- Okay, let me think.
I got it. Are you...
...or are you not...
...a raging, full-blown, butt-humper?
Excuse me?
Faggot. Honey, she wants to know
if you are one.
I mean, I don't know...
...but do Republican senators
with openly gay children...
...ever get reelected?
I mean, not that anybody would
want to leak that information.
Me and Kate have been going out
for three years. Okay?
- That really isn't an answer.
- No, it's not.
- Silence equals death.
- "Silence equals death."
You know what? Fuck you.
- That's my man.
- You guys are disgusting.
Bye.
- Want to play, Christian?
- Sure.
- Sorry about that in the game room.
- I'm sure you are.
She looks very happy, huh?
"Virtue, honesty and justice."
Christian's family motto.
Words to live by.
Yeah, yeah.
Or to die by. You know,
at least if the story's true.
Come on, Elizabeth. Don't pretend
you never heard the story.
Lt was such a big scandal.
Christian's polo-playing father.
Vanished after the family found out
that he was romping a prostitute.
Lt was a rumor.
The case never even went to trial.
You are so fucking naive.
Hey, wake up. They probably
bought the fucking judge.
My father's a politician. Believe me,
I know how the system works.
Supposedly, he banged that cheap whore
in this house and got her pregnant.
This isn't the time or place
to talk about this.
- I wonder which bedroom they used?
- Stop it.
The thing about old-money families is,
they can clean up any mess.
How dare you?
How dare I? Let me tell you
something, Elizabeth, okay?
I know the lengths people will go to
to protect their reputations.
You can take that as a threat.
Do you hear that thudding?
I think someone...
...is having sex
in the next room.
- Sounds like fun, doesn't it?
- No.
You don't think sex is fun?
I don't know.
You don't know?
Do you think Christian...
...would ever cheat on you?
No.
Do you think that he would have
a threesome with you and me?
No, he learned his lesson
last time with Kate and you.
I remember.
You know, like the note-card
and the mystery package.
Infidel.
You drink too much.
No. I just get tipsy,
every now and then.
Now and then, every day.
You're a lush.
That's what you told Christian
to make him break up with me.
You're paranoid.
You told Christian that I was a slut.
That only a slut would have a threesome.
- Or a drunk.
- So now I'm a drunk slut? Great.
Great. Wonderful. You know what?
I know what you've done.
I'm not as stupid as I look.
No, I think you have it backwards.
I think you don't look as stupid
as you really are.
God, you're just, like,
a fucking piece of work.
Ditto.
Stupid, I'm not stupid.
Christian, what are you doing?
- Okay, Piper. Your turn.
- Question:
"Would you sleep with a person
of the same sex?" Answer: "Yes."
Now it's getting fun.
- Where's Kate?
- I don't know. Why?
- She was the last one to see Benjamin.
- No, I was the last to see Benjamin.
Okay. Once again, another fact
that does not work in your favor.
Here's a little tip, honey.
Stay away from people that don't
like you and end up dead.
I'm gonna go look for Kate.
Elizabeth.
You've got this all wrong. I'm not
the person you need to be afraid of.
- Who should I be afraid of?
- Don't leave this room.
- Why?
- Because I said so, Elizabeth.
Don't answer the bedroom door
until you hear this knock.
What's going on?
- Nothing.
- Where's Benjamin?
He's taking a bubble bath.
Yeah? What are you guys
doing in here?
Where's Kate?
She's downstairs playing
with some of your daddy's old rifles.
- What do you think of my nightie?
- I don't.
Really? What about you, Elizabeth?
I think you should sit down.
Okay.
I'm going downstairs. Only open
the door if you hear me knock.
Hello.
The two of you are having fun, aren't you?
Just two sorority sisters
talking about the good old times.
- Christian was looking for you.
- You look nervous.
Why is Benjamin taking so long?
Would you mind leaving us alone
for a minute? Piper?
Oh, you're right.
- Time for a refill.
- We should go downstairs together.
We should stay here. Have
a little chat. Just the two of us.
- Bye, Piper.
- Bye.
You can put an end to all of this,
Elizabeth. It's all up to you.
What are you talking about?
We're all guilty as sin, okay?
Remember the little game we played?
I just don't think that we really
deserve what we got.
Sexual preference and frequency...
...shouldn't be a matter
of life and death, should it?
- What's your point?
- The note-cards?
Don't.
I know what you did, Elizabeth.
I know about you.
I know about you too. I know how you
can afford to live so extravagantly...
...even though you're broke
and officially unemployed.
You mean the money Benjamin
pays me to play his girlfriend...
...because he's scared his parents
will take away his inheritance...
...if they find out he's gay?
That money?
Whatever he pays you doesn't even
come close to covering your budget.
Is Prada a crime?
I mean, I hope not. Because good taste
is so damn expensive, Elizabeth.
But you know all about that, don't
you? You spend way more than I do.
But now you've gone and done it.
You've married money.
Congratulations...
Elizabeth!
No.
Damn it.
Oh, my God.
Oh, my God!
Shit!
Your turn, Adam.
All right, the question is,
"Would you have a threesome?"
The answer is yes.
- Two girls, one guy?
- Does it matter?
Mr. Right-Wing Conservative there...
...looks like he might think
two girls would be fun.
Elizabeth.
Elizabeth!
Elizabeth, open up.
Elizabeth, hurry!
Elizabeth!
Don't shoot your eye out.
- What are you doing?
- Having a smoke.
Do you want one?
Oh, that's right, you don't smoke.
Good girls and vices
just don't mix, do they?
Where's Christian?
I heard a gunshot. What happened?
- Hair trigger, could've been killed.
- You still might.
I'll give you 10 seconds to tell me
where he is before I shoot you.
- Ten, nine, eight, seven...
- Don't pretend like you don't know.
- ...six, five...
- You know where he is.
- ...four, three, two, one.
- You guys murdered Adam and Benjamin!
I'd have told you it wasn't loaded
if you'd have asked.
Now, let's play a new game, okay?
You're not the one with the loaded gun,
so you're not calling the shots now.
Oh, I made a pun. I am feeling
very charitable at the moment...
...so I'll help you find Christian
if you play this game with me, okay?
- Then you won't find Christian.
- You've already killed him too.
Christian is alive and well.
But I'm gonna tell you some
information. I haven't killed anyone.
Yet.
Let's play the game.
Put this on.
Elizabeth, this is how the game
is played. Put it on.
You'll try and find Christian.
As you're getting closer...
...I'm gonna say
"warm, " "warmer, " "hot."
When you go in the wrong direction,
I'll give a "cold, " "colder, " "dead."
You got it?
I'm gonna get you for this.
You already have, Elizabeth.
- You already have.
- What are you talking about?
You'll find out soon enough.
Okay, let's play.
Cold. Cold. Cold.
I'm losing my patience.
Okay, why don't I cheat for you.
Turn to the right.
There you go. Step to the side.
Another one. Go forward.
Forward.
Open the door.
There you go.
Forward.
- Hurry. Hurry, hurry.
- I can't go any faster.
You afraid you might fall and go boom?
That would be awful.
Lt would also be a fucking accident.
Elizabeth, relax.
If I wanted to kill
you, I'd have done it much earlier.
Have you thought more about
the mystery package?
- No.
- Really? Because, you see, I have.
Benjamin turned out to be gay, Adam's
the rapist and Piper's the infidel.
That leaves us and Christian to fight
over the prostitute and the hypocrite.
- Warm. Warmer. Colder!
- Sorry.
- What was that? "Sorry"? Wow.
That's a whole new word for you.
A new emotion. Way to go.
Very proud of you. Hurry.
Very warm.
- Christian?
- I didn't say "hot." I said "warm."
Why are you doing this?
What did they ever do to you?
That's a good question.
Ever asked yourself that?
What have they ever done
to you, Elizabeth?
But then, this is all just a big,
fun, happy game, isn't it?
Warmer.
I think you've done it. Hot.
Oh, my God!
- What are you doing?
- Taking her body downstairs.
We have to do something with her.
She killed everyone. Everyone's dead.
Yeah. I guess you might want this.
Question:
"Would you have sex for money?"
Answer: "Yes."
I like sex. Okay?
That does not make me a hooker.
Lt also doesn't make me a bitch.
What's going on, Christian?
We have to do something
about these bodies.
- Why?
- Why do you think?
You can't have dead bodies
littering about the living room.
What would the neighbors think?
- Why can't we just wait for the police?
- It's not their problem.
It's not our problem.
In a roundabout, kind of complicated...
...for-richer-or-poorer way,
it is, Elizabeth, our problem.
I did this, Elizabeth, for you.
- No. Christian, no.
- They knew.
Elizabeth, they knew about what you did.
You were smart...
...but you were also sloppy.
Next time...
...send someone else to pick up
the checks from the P.O. box.
- Whatever they told you, it's not true.
- It's over.
They knew about you.
They planned on getting
their revenge this weekend.
But I wasn't gonna let
that happen, now was I?
- But why...?
- Taboo. They found out about Taboo.
That's why we all came up here.
That's why they were confronting you
with their sexual sins...
- ...to try and scare you to confess.
- Confess what?
Exactly. They knew you'd say that.
That's why they planned on tormenting
you, tricking you into admitting it.
You blackmailed them, Elizabeth.
They found out. Okay?
You don't need to lie to me anymore.
All right? It's over.
- You won. Game is over.
- No, we won.
I'm supposed to think you did this for us?
- Yes.
- Don't patronize me.
But that is why I did it.
Okay. You know what, convince me.
I stacked the note-cards
in an order so that...
...each person would draw the question
they'd answer "yes" to, their vice.
And?
And then I set up a situation
over the past year where they had...
...a golden opportunity
to pursue that vice.
When they did...
- ...you were there to document it.
- Yes.
So you tapped
into their sexual fantasies...
- ...and you blackmailed them.
- That was an afterthought.
You are evil.
No, just poor and desperate.
All I ever wanted was to win your love.
At their expense!
They're degenerates.
An infidel, a prostitute,
a homosexual and a rapist?
You were always the good one,
the strong one, the moral one.
- They didn't deserve you.
- Yes, I know that...
...but did you have
to punish them so severely?
No. lt seems you did that.
You don't think blackmailing people who
considered you a friend was punishment?
Exposing their private lives without
their consent, that's not punishment?
Okay, that's the "why." Tell me how.
Adam was a horny little bastard.
You should know that.
You went out with him after all.
I paid a 14-year-old girl
to hit on him at a bar...
...and have sex with him.
- And what?
- And videotape it.
How poetic. Next victim.
Benjamin. I'd bet he'd pay a lot to
keep his sexual identity in the closet.
There's this bar he liked
to go to where...
...nobody knew your name as long
as you were a guy and good-looking.
And Kate?
Nothing to tell, she was a prostitute.
Come on, she wasn't a streetwalker.
She had a few select European clients.
- How do you know so much?
- I know everything.
I doubt it.
Shouldn't you have given Kate a little
leeway for her humble upbringing?
Just kidding.
And my dear little Piper,
how did you fuck her life up?
Hold on.
You set up that three-way between her,
me and Kate, didn't you?
You knew me.
You knew I'd break up with her...
...that I'd never look at her
the same.
Same with Adam, or Benjamin,
and anybody else.
And speak of the devil, what about me?
Question:
"Would you sleep
with your partner's best friend?"
Answer:
A very disappointing no.
I said one thing, I did another.
I'm a hypocrite.
- But I forgive you.
- Why?
Why not blackmail me, ruin my life?
Because I wanted you more
than anything else in the whole world.
And it was always about you, Christian.
I wanted my family.
Our family. A new beginning.
Yeah.
Well, you know,
I think we're pretty much done.
Talking about this.
There is just one more little thing.
- I know you're not going to shoot me.
- How are you so sure?
We're family, remember?
I just have one surprise for you.
I promise you, you're gonna like this.
Everything is gonna
make sense in a moment.
Christian?
Morning, sunshine.
Christian, are you okay?
- Where is she?
- She ran upstairs.
- I'm gonna go get her.
- I say let's kill her.
- I'd like her dead.
- Not in the plan.
- Change the plan.
- If we change it...
Nobody touches her.
I will go up there alone.
Go up alone? That's a great way
to think on your feet. Very smart.
She's still my fiancée.
I'll deal with it.
Is this guy fucking serious?
Here, you never know.
Is he okay?
Yeah, he's okay. He's just uptight...
...anal-retentive, conservative,
and he's got a very tweaked...
...and twisted moral imperative.
Go get 'em, big guy!
Elizabeth.
It's time for Elizabeth's greatest hits.
- I'm going to enjoy this.
- Nice.
Champagne, anyone?
Good job, actually.
- Here's to living in sin.
- And to good girls gone bad.
We're here, we're queer
and we're not going shopping.
- Kate?
- Fuck it, I'm thirsty.
- Something doesn't feel right.
- Lt feels very right.
- Come here, you little bitch.
- I thought you'd never ask.
I don't ask. I am a rapist.
- What was the sixth question?
- To what?
The game, Benjamin.
What was the sixth question?
I've got a new question. Yeah.
Would you get naked
with your sexiest friends?
- Listen to me.
- You want a piece of this, Benji?
Listen to me,
what was Elizabeth's question?
You want a piece? Go ahead.
What was she trying to do with this game?
She wanted to expose all of our moral
weaknesses. There were six cards.
Kate, do you really think
that bitch would expose herself?
- Why not?
- Because then, Mr. Virtue, Honesty...
...and Justice would find out
she wasn't perfect and dump her.
He wouldn't because she forgave him
for his transgressions...
...which means he'd have
to forgive her.
I know how Christian thinks. Where do
they keep the games in this place?
Maybe in the game room!
Thanks.
Elizabeth?
It's over.
House is locked tight.
There's nowhere else to go.
You had your chance to confess
and come clean.
I realized they were right. You were
the one who blackmailed them...
...ruined their lives. I had no choice.
You understand, don't you?
Oh, my God.
Let me out!
Jesus Christ!
Oh, my God.
I paid a 14-year-old girl to hit
on him at a bar and have sex with him.
- And what?
- And videotape it.
How poetic. Next victim.
Benjamin. I'd bet he'd pay a lot to
keep his sexual identity in the closet.
There's this bar he liked
to go to where...
...nobody knew your name as long
as you were a guy and good-looking.
Looking for me?
Elizabeth.
- I don't think so.
- "You don't think so, " what?
- Keep your blouse on.
- Why?
I'm not really in the mood, so to speak.
You don't find me attractive now?
Not particularly.
But you've wanted me ever since we met...
...the whole year we dated,
and this is your chance.
- No, it's over.
- Lt doesn't have to be.
Elizabeth.
I'm sorry.
If it's over, then why not have one
last hurrah? The first and the last.
Is it bad or immoral?
Not now.
Moral absolutism's
a tricky proposition, isn't it?
Do you like that?
Yes.
You want to kiss me?
Then, kiss me.
Hello? Let me in.
Guys, it's Benjamin. Let me in.
Can't be much of a threesome
with just the two of you.
All talk and no Benjamin.
You're playing with my emotions!
I said one thing and did another.
- I'm a hypocrite.
- But I forgive you.
Why? Why not blackmail me,
ruin my life?
Because I wanted you more
than anything in the whole world.
- Wait. Wait.
- I can't.
I need you to tell me that you love me.
I hope you can forgive me for this.
Not right now, please. I want more.
This means everything to me.
Oh, my God.
All I ever wanted was your love.
But as my brother.
- Now you...
- What?
Well, now you know why I never
let you sleep with me.
What?
Now you know why I did it.
And what...?
What were you just talking about?
Now you know why I never slept with you.
Question:
If your father and the woman he was
having an affair with had a daughter...
...what would her name be?
Answer:
Elizabeth.
What?
That's disgusting. I don't find
those jokes funny at all.
They killed my mother and our father...
...but they didn't kill me.
Stop it, you're fucking sick in the head.
You got everything and I got nothing.
It's not fair.
I wanted you, but never like this.
Now I just want what
I think is rightfully mine.
- Half sister means half of everything.
- Elizabeth, shut up. Okay?
It's fucking psycho. It's not funny.
It's gonna be fun telling
the newspapers and the TV stations.
Everyone's gonna know
about you and your family.
I waited years to find out
who my family was.
When I found out, I had no choice
but to go in for the kill.
I'm really sorry your mom had to die,
but an eye for an eye.
And, now, we pretend here...
I swear she's fucking psycho.
You're fucking crazy, you know that?
To think, you, of all people, will
have their reputation destroyed.
- Tell me you're fucking lying to me.
- I can't.
Fucking say it!
You're lying to me. Tell me!
Elizabeth?
- It's the truth, Christian.
- No, it's not.
I've got the proof inside me.
I should just kill you right now.
That would make an even
better story, if you killed me.
You can't get away with this, Christian.
But, on the other hand, I could
keep my mouth shut and we could...
...live happily ever after.
We're the only ones
that need to know about this.
Just you and me.
Knock, knock.
People, you're supposed
to say, "Who's there?"
Who's there?
Homo.
Christian, work with me.
You're supposed to say, "Homo, who?"
What is it? Fag season?
- You go look.
- I'm in the shower.
You know, if Christian shot him, good.
I'm gonna stay right here.
- Well, what if she shot him?
- Even better.
- Fuck them both.
- You're just a pussy.
Okay, I'm a pussy. Fine.
Get some wine while you take a look.
You know, generally, Pipes, you ask
for favors before you put out.
That was a warm-up, an hors d'oeuvre,
a snack, a nibble.
All right, I get the point.
But listen...
...don't you fuck anybody else
while I'm gone.
You'd better hurry.
- And Kate?
- Nothing to tell, she's a prostitute.
She wasn't a streetwalker.
She had a few select Eu...
Hey, Christian. Hello.
Jesus Christ.
Hey, buddy, she got you good, huh?
You might need some stitches...
...you fucking idiot.
Oh, God.
Hi, Benji.
Jesus.
I know what you've been
wanting, you fruitcake.
Hey.
Jesus, did you hear that
gunshot a few minutes ago?
- I dropped the gun.
- All right, okay, great.
Did you take care of Elizabeth?
- You could say that.
- No, you could say that.
I'd hate for our scheme to fall
apart because the psycho got away.
- She's not going anywhere.
- All right.
Perfect, but...
Now, if you'll excuse me, I've got some
important business to take care of.
Oh, I got soap in my eyes.
Adam, baby, can you give me a towel?
Is that you?
Adam, I really need a towel.
I can't see a damn thing
and it really hurts.
Adam.
Sorry.
Christian, is that you?
In the flesh.
- Where's Adam?
- I think it's called a "fuck and run."
Like all the others.
- What do you want?
- What do you think?
Why don't you reach out and touch someone?
You're cold.
You know what they say,
"Warm heart, cold gun."
- Why do you have a gun?
- I use it for killing people.
- Well, put it away.
- Aren't we bossy.
What's wrong? What do you need?
Huh?
- You, you're scaring me.
- I'm sorry.
You want me to take you out
for dinner and make up for it?
- Just hand me a towel, okay?
- Okay.
Hold your horses. Don't get
your panties in a bunch.
Think you're so great because you're
rich. You were lucky to have me.
And judging from your attitude, you'd
be lucky to get a little pleasure.
God knows this little choir boy
bullshit's gonna make you blow one day.
You'll never do better than me.
I mean, look at Elizabeth...
...you picked a real winner there.
Fucking perfect.
Kate.
- Stay there, Elizabeth.
- No, it's not me that's doing this.
- It's Christian.
- Shut up!
I found Adam and Benjamin.
I saw the old note-cards.
I know, and I'm sorry, but I'm not
the one that's doing this.
Would you sleep
with a relative, Elizabeth?
So now you're just gonna kill all of us?
No.
- Elizabeth!
- No, Kate, stop it. No!
Do you want to break, honey, or should I?
I'll do it.
How's your steak?
Delicious.
And the polenta?
It's good.
And the wine.
It's Lafitte Rothschild, 1954.
The year that our father was born.
- The wine's perfect.
- It's your favorite, isn't it?
Yes.
- To my incestuous sister.
- Don't say that.
Oh, God, it's delightful.
Have another sip.
Savor a wine like this, because you
never know when you're gonna have it.
Do you remember last year
when you said that...
...I believed in principles,
but I didn't have them?
- Yes.
- Well, do you still think that?
- Why?
- Because...
...I want to do the right thing.
I would hate to think that our family
has lost what we most cherish:
- Virtue, honesty and justice.
- Then do the right thing.
- Well, what would that be, exactly?
- Giving me half of everything you have.
I would, but you're illegitimate...
...and you know how
I feel about such things.
Then marry me.
Both of us are guilty, Christian.
Yes, we are.
We are both guilty.
Guilty as charged.
To both of us.
Cheers.
It's agreed...
...we're both guilty.
And the guilty must pay.
We don't have to.
That would make me a hypocrite.
You are a hypocrite, Christian.
No, I'm not!
I'm a man of my word.
You poisoned me?
How could you kill me?
I thought you'd be honored.
Being murdered is one of our family's
oldest traditions, after all.
You can ask our father when you see him.
We're no better than him, Elizabeth.
We failed our family.
What's gonna happen?
Well...
...in a few more seconds, you won't
be able to get a breath at all...
...then you'll lose consciousness and
you'll float away to never-never land.
It's the best way to go.
Trust me.
No, I mean, what's gonna happen to you?
Good night.