25.000
Evans!
Don't come!
LONDON, June 13, 1923
Those ruffians dead Gods
shan't have it all their own way.
Those gods who never lose
a chance of hurting, foughting ...
and spoiling human lives ...
are seriously put out
if all the same, you behave like a lady.
Of course, now I think there are no
Gods and there's no one to blame.
It's so very dangerous to live
for only one day.
I buy the flowers myself, Lucy.
Yes, ma'am.
And Mrs Walker
said not to forget that
Rumplemayers's men
will be here at eleven.
I won't forget.
Oh, what a day, Lucy!
What a day for my party.
What a luck!
What a plunge!
Good morning to you, Clarissa.
Hugh!
And where are you off to?
To buy flowers for my party.
I love walking in London on a day
like this. It's better that in the country.
Evelyn wouldn't agree with you there.
She can't bear coming out to town.
I had to get her to come up to see W. Bud.
He's putting her in a nursing home,
for a few days.
Nothing serious?
No, nothing serious. She's just a good deal
out of salts.
The war may be over,
but there is still the echoe of it.
The Boxborough boy
was killed, you know ...
and she is very close
to Lady Boxborough.
And Evelyn takes things badly.
Yes, one does still hear dreadful stories.
I must get on. The'll be waiting for this,
at the palace.
Will you still come to my party tonight?
Oh, yes! Evelyn absolutly insists I go.
Hugh Whitbread. I can forgive you
liking him, Clarissa.
He's a buffon. Even when he plays tennis,
his hair doesn't move.
He's a barbers block. An imbecil.
He thinks of nothing but his clothes.
I like him.
How can you? He's never read anything.
Never thought anything.
Never felt anything!
Stabel boys are more likeable than
Hugh.
Sally says
he tried to kiss her in the smoking-room.
Oh!
She didn't let him? She rather die first.
Good for Sally. She sees through that
public school nonsense.
Old manners and breeding.
No country but England
could have produced Hugh.
He is sweet and unselfish
and he's very good to his mother.
You're so sentimental, Clarissa!
And you're impossible!
Oh, what beautiful flowers!
That's absolutly wonderful, Sally.
Oh, I thought Sally could be trusted
to do the flowers.
That's wicked. To cut off the heads
of those flowers. Really...
I think they're beautiful.
Peter, look at the flowers.
Yes.
Roses for the hall, I think.
And sweet peas for the table,
perhaps?
Yes! Sweet pea to the table.
It will be perfect!
Those awful motorcars.
Yes
Of course, it was a car.
- I'm loose it here.
- Septimus, please. We must go on.
I'm loose it here,
and I don't know with what purpose.
Septimus, please, poeple are looking at us.
Am I blocking the way?
Allright, then.
Bye, Mrs. Dalloway.
Mrs. Dalloway, Mrs. Dalloway.
I'm not even Clarissa anymore.
No more marrying, no more having children.
Just Mrs. Dalloway.
Mrs.  Richard Dalloway,
who's to give a party.
You'll marry
a prime minister ...
and stand
at the top of the staircase.
Who'll give parties.
You'll be the perfect hostess.
You have the makings
of a perfect hostess.
You could do so much,
be so much.
What you want me to be?
Life seems to me to be very dangerous.
But one must live life
dangerously!
Look! Look, Septimus!
Is no crime.
There is no death.
The birds are singing in Greek.
The whole world is clamouring.
"Kill yourself!" "Kill yourself!"
Septimus, I'm going to walk to the lake and back.
"Kreemo". It says "Kreemo".
-So revigorating.
- I know what you meen.
The bushies, the flowers.
So well kept.
Yes, this is a wonderful garden.
Beautiful.
You should see the Milan gardens!
What a strange person.
She's a foreigner.
Make it now ...  Make it now ...
But there is a God!
No one kills from hatred!
Evans!
For God sake! Don't come!
T. .. O. ..
F. .. F. ..
E. .. And!
It says "toffee"!
I know it's "toffee".
Look, Lucy.
It sayed "Kreemo toffee".
There was a phone message, ma'am. Mr. Dalloway
sayed to tell you he would not be home for lunch.
He would be lunching at lady Bruton's.
He did!
Lady Bruton. Well...
Clarissa, my darling. Parliament
sits so late ...
and the doctor said
you must get your rest.
You must sleep undisturbed.
Fear no more the heat of the sun ...
nor the furious winter's rages.
It's all over for me.
The sheets stretched and
the bed narrow.
What we need to do is abolish
private property ...
because that really is what
causes all the problems.
Let's write
a letter to the Times about it.
Then, we should found
a society ...
to abolish private property
and do away with it forever and ever.
This house as well?
You always
look so virginal, Clarissa!
I am virginal.
Are you in love with Peter?
Oh, love...
I don't know.
But you love me?
Damn and blust! I left my sponge
in the bathroom.
Tell me to go and get it, like this!
You wouldn't!
I would!
Is it all over for me?
I've come up to the tower and left them all
blackberrying in the sun.
Don't run, Clarissa!
Young ladies don't run.
Leipzig is good, but I think
Heidelberg is beautiful...
especially this time of year.
The "Philosopher's Walk".
It reminds me very much of here,
with the gardens.
You are most fortunate the way
your gardens are done.
And you have many trees. The colors and
the way it's all been orchestrated.
It's tremendously fine. I think this is a great
achievement of the English garden.
"Love in her sunny eyes,
just basking play.
Love walks the pleasant
mazes of her hair. "
"Love does both on her lips,
forever stray...
and saws and reaps
a thousand kisses there."
"N'or all her outfought parts
love's always seen ...
but, oh, he never went within."
Clarissa.
What?
The men leed such
exciting lives ...
but their poor wives
don't seems to do so well.
Marriage is a catastrophe
for women.
But it is inevitable, isn't it?
Sally ...
Will we always be together?
Always! Always!
We'll do everything together.
We'll change the world! Come on.
Oh, Lucy!
Silver does look nice.
The doors are of the hangers in
the dining room, ma'am.
And Rumplemayers's men
will be here soon.
Can I help you with that, ma'am?
No, Lucy.
You've got enough to do.
Star gazing, are we?
Yes.
Come on, Joseph. You know the stars,
you can tell us which is which.
You see that star,
just above the horizon?
Yes.
That's Antares.
Heart of the Scorpio
constellation.
He's name means
"rival of Mars."
And that one?
Ask Libra, we have Alpha.
There goes bright star.
And see how Altair, the
brightest star of equality Eagle...
shines in the east for us today.
Ms. Kilman and I are going out.
Is there anything we can get for you, Mother?
Where are you going, Elisabeth dear?
Ms. Kilman is taking me
to meet the Rev. Whitacker.
Reverend Whitacker. Ah, yes.
Wasn't he the very instrument
in your conversion, Ms. Kilman?
Yes, he helped bring me
to our Lord.
And is today's visit part of
the history lesson?
The reverend Whitacker is also
a historian, Mother.
He can put this true religion
in a proper perspective.
I wonder what that is.
I've never wanted to convert anyone, I hope.
I just want everyone to be themselves.
I've often thought that religious fanaticism
can make a person ...
rather careless.
Mother! We just going to talk to him.
You won't forget about my party
tonight, Elizabeth!
I was going to help Mrs. Kilman
sort the clothes for the mission.
Well, I dare say Ms. Kilman could
spare you for one evening.
I'll see, Mother. We must go,
or we'll be late.
It all seems useless. Going on being in love.
Going on quarreling.
Going on making out.
But Peter, you want so much from me!
You leave me nothing to myself.
You want every little bit of me!
Well, I do! I want us
to be everything to each other.
But that's all so suffocating!
God! God! God!
Peter Walsh!
Clarissa.
Peter!
But you're in India.
No, didn't you get my last letter?
I said I'd be here in June.
No. Your last letter said
that you might be back ...
But I never suspected it.
It's extraordinary how Peter
can put me in this state, just by coming here.
He looks awfully well.
It's heavenly to see you again, Peter.
I arrived last night.
Playing with his knife.
How is everything? How are you?
Oh, so like him.
How is Richard?
Richard's with some committee.
Something to do with his constituents.
What's this? What's all this here?
I'm mending my dress.
It's for my party tonight.
Which I shan't invite you to,
my dear Peter.
Why?
Why won't you ask me?
It is extraordinary that
you shown up this morning.
I've been thinking
about Bordon all day.
I heard about your father.
I should've written to you, of course.
Although I never really got on with him.
He never liked anyone who...
who wanted to marry you.
Herbert has Bordon now.
I never go there.
And what happened to you?
Millions of things.
Should I tell you?
Should I make a clean brast of it?
I'm in love, I'm in love with a girl
in India.
And who is she?
A younger woman, of course.
Well, I'm not old, you know?
My life isn't over not by any means.
Well, you of course ...
think me as a failure,
wich I suppose I am compared to all that.
But who is she? Tell me.
A married woman.
Unfortunately.
She's the wife of a major
in the Indian Army.
She has two young children,
a boy and a girl.
And it's a bit of a mess.
I'm here to see the lawyers
about a divorce.
Just called Daisy.
Yes?
Yes
But what should you do?
The lawyers and the solicitors
they can judge...
For heaven's sake,
leave that knife alone!
I know what I'm up against.
All is all up! And am I behaving like a fool,
weepping, being emotional!
Probably annoyed you,
turning up at this hour ...
and told you everything,
as usual?
Are you happy, Clarissa?
Does Richard ...
Excuse me, ma'am. The gentlemen
are here from Rumplemayers.
Oh, thank you, Lucy.
Good bye, Clarissa.
My party tonight
Please come to my party,
tonight.
Come on! Let's get out of this.
I want to do another!
Come on.
Is this what you want?
Staying here and go to parties?
But I like parties!
Oh, Clarissa!
You always tie me up
with your queen standard, Breitl.
It's my turn to shuffle,
Herbert.
Hugh, do you
ever stop eating?
Did you know
Wingate's married again?
Yes, they came to call
last week.
The woman use to be his housemaid.
He had a nerve.
Bringing a housemaid to Cork.
Yes! She was absurdly overdressed.
She looked like a cockatoo.
And she never stopped talking!
She probably thought
you all knew.
Knew what?
That she had a baby
before she was married.
- I don't think I should ever be up to speak to her again!
- Don't be ridiculous, Clarissa.
If this is true we should certainly
not receive her again.
I should think not. If we start receiving
women like that, you don't know where it'll end?
Oh, you snob! You represent all that's
detestable in british middle class life.
It's men like you who's responsible
for prostitutes around Piccadilly.
Me!
Yes, men like you.
That's enough, Sally. We'll have no more
of this conversation.
I'm glad I walked out. They're all
such snobs and Hugh is a fraud.
Clarissa is so prudish
and arrogant.
Not really.
It's just what she's been brought up to.
Wish she would see things more clearly.
Clearly enough to marry you,
you mean?
I see.
This is Mr. Wickham, Peter.
My name is Dalloway.
Richard Dalloway.
But I've introduced you
to everyone as Mr. Wickham.
Still Dalloway.
My name is Dalloway.
Dalloway.
So definitly you're going
to go to politics?
Yes, I think so.
What is with your friend, Mr. ..?
"My name is Dalloway".
What's the matter?
Somebody's just walking
on my grave.
I took another friend.
She's gonna marry that man!
I went into the sea.
I have been dead.
But now I'm alive.
I must rest, I must rest.
Septimus, I'm going to ask
someone the time.
I think we have to go now.
It's nowhere to go,
nowhere to hide.
Septimus, you know we are going to see
a doctor who will help you.
No more doctors!
No more lies!
Septimus, please!
Irvin!
Thank you.
Evans?
Evans!
For God's sake, don't come!
Septimus, it isn't Evans, allright?
It isn't Evans.
There is nothing to worry about.
The man is not Evans.
Really, he isn't.
Come on.
Let's go for a walk.
Clarissa! It's such a lovely evening.
Let's go to the lake.
Yes! We can go boating.
Let's get our shoulds.
It might be cold.
Peter! We're going boating
on the lake. Aren't you coming?
I think Mr. Dalloway
likes you.
Oh, aren't we being
the perfect hostess?
Oh, don't come than if you're going
to be beastly in the wood.
"Dalloway. It's still Dalloway."
Come on.
They're all waiting.
Poor old woman.
Septimus, you won't tell
the doctor, will you?
You mustn't.
They will take you away from me.
Sir William BRADSHAW
M.D.
I've looked at Dr. Holmes's notes.
He's been seeing your husband for some six weeks?
Yes.
He is our landlady's doctor.
She send for him because
I told her I was worried about Septimus.
He threatened to kill himself?
He didn't mean it.
No. Of course not.
And Dr. Holmes prescribed ...
bromine?
Yes
He said that there was nothing really wrong.
But Septimus keeps talking to the dead man, Evans,
his friend who was killed in the war.
And Septimus wasn't like this
when I met him.
It's happened in just the last few months.
He says people are talking
behind bedroom walls...
and he saw a woman's head
in the middle of a fern.
He says he's on trial
for some terrible crime ...
but, of course, he's done nothing.
And then he seems to forget
it all and seems happy again, as he used to be.
We went to Hampton Court,
on top of a bus, the other day...
and told of red and yellow flowers. He said
they looked like floating lamps.
And he was fun, as he used to be
and made me laugh. I was so happy.
And suddenly, as we
were standing by the river, he said ...
"We will kill ourselves."
Then, he held my hand ...
and said he was falling
into the flames. And he cried and cried.
Ms. Warrensmith, your husband is
very seriously ill.
From everything you told me
and from Dr. Holmes's report ...
I believe that his suffering
from delayed shell shock.
But he's not mad, is he?
I never use that word.
I prefer to say ...
lacking the sense of proportion.
But Dr. Holmes said that there
was nothing what so ever the matter!
Your husband needs rest.
Complete rest.
But not away from me!
My dear Ms. Warrensmith sometimes
we have to separate such people...
from their loved ones,
for their own good.
Dalloway! I met Clarissa
this morning.
So, she's giving another of her
famous parties tonight?
Right as usual, Hugh.
And Lady Bruton summond you as well.
Wonder what she wants from us?
Nothing we can't accomplish
ever at a good lunch, I'm sure.
Ah, good day, Miss Brasher.
Good day, sir.
How's your brother,
in South Africa?
I got you here under false pretenses.
I actually need your help.
But we'll have lunch first.
And how is Clarissa?
Quite well recovered, thank you.
The doctor told her he must take things easy ...
But she does so want to
give her party tonight.
I trust we'll should have the pleasure
of your company tonight.
Of course, Richard. I wouldn't miss
one of your parties.
I met Clarissa in the park
this morning.
She was wearing
a yellow feathered hat.
Oh, yes! I like that hat.
We'll you come in now, please?
Good.
Do sit down.
I see that you served with great distinction
in the war, Mr. Warrensmith.
At the war?
The European war.
A little shindy of schoolboys
with gunpowder.
Did I serve with distinction?
I'd forgotten.
In the war, itself, I failed.
No, he served with the greatest distinction.
He was promoted.
I. ..
I have committed a crime.
He's done nothing wrong whatever.
What did Dr. Holmes advised
you to do?
To my wife he said
to make me porridge.
Headache, dreams,
fears are just nerves.
Health is largely a
matter of our control.
I should take up some hobby.
Dr. Holmes ...
throws himself into outside interests.
And throwing himself, he is able ...
to switch off from his patients
on to old furniture.
Dr. Holmes is interested
in antique furniture.
Yes
So, when the damn fool came again,
I refused to see him.
Impulsive brute...
Blood red nostrils...
Once you stumble, human nature
is on you. Holmes is on you.
Our only chance is to escape
without letting Holmes know.
Anywhere,
away from Dr. Holmes.
There is no excuse.
Nothing whatever is the matter.
Except sin.
For which ...
human nature has condemned me
to death.
I can not feel.
I did not care,
when  Evans was killed.
That was the worst ...
but all the other crimes ...
raised their heads,
shaked their fingers ...
and they cheer and they sneer.
And the verdict of human nature
on such a beast ...
is death!
We all have our moments
of depression.
He has impulses, sometimes?
That is my own affair!
There you are mistaken, sir. We are all
responsible one for another.
I am responsible
to Dr. Holmes?
Another humbug.
We ...
have been arranging
that you should go into a home.
One of Holmes's homes?
No, one of my homes,
Mr. Warrensmith.
And there we will teach you to rest
and to regain a sense of proportion.
But I've confessed!
I confessed my crimes!
Why won't you had me off?
He's done nothing. Nothing!
He will be perfectly looked after.
I will visit once a week.
But my husband does not like
doctors. He will refuse to go.
Your husband has threatened to kill himself.
There is no alternative, it is a question of the law.
It's a very beautiful home in the country.
Nurses are admirable.
Now, if you have no further questions to ask...
I will arrange everything with Dr. Holmes.
He will send somebody around this evening ...
between five and six.
It's the law, Ms. Warrensmith,
and it is for the best.
It won't be Dr. Holmes who comes, will it?
Trust everything to me.
I do not like that man.
He's a humbug.
We are deserted.
Do you know who's in town?
Our old friend, Peter Walsh.
Back from India.
Peter Walsh back?
In trouble with some woman,
evidently.
Some woman in India.
Peter Walsh was always in trouble
of some sort.
Didn't he marry someone on the boat
going out?
I don't believe that lasted long.
I imagine that was all what...
I believe is known as "the rebound".
I suppose he'll try
to settle here now.
I'd say it will be difficult to help him.
He'll be quite a misfit.
I'm sure Clarissa will know
that he's here.
And I no doubt he'll be at her the party
tonight and all will be revealed.
Yes, if Peter Walsh is in town,
Clarissa will know.
This is better.
Come on, Peter.
We'll race you
to the top.
Well ..
my idea is this.
We all agree, do we not,
that Britain is overpopulated.
Yes, indeed.
And you agree ...
that many of these men,
back from the war ...
are finding it difficult
to find employment.
Indeed, in some cases,
their work ...
has been commandered by women.
However ...
We all know the rot
that's set in there.
Unfortunately!
Well ..
my idea is a simple one.
All the best ideas are simple,
as we know.
My project is to incourage ...
by making it financialy easy
young people of both sexes ...
to emigrate to Canada.
They will be set up with the fair chance
of doing well in Canada.
And Britain will gain financialy,
in the long run.
It's only so much that I can do,
being a woman.
But Richard, I ask you ...
to make this suggestion
in the House. And Hugh ...
I want you to help me start the ball rolling
with a letter to the Times.
I know, my dear Hugh,
that you will know, exactly ...
how to phrase it for me.
I think someone is already typing
a motion against some kind of emigration plan going.
But I suppose a letter to the Times
will do no harm.
I take it further.
Make emigration obligatory ...
if you couldn't get work
after a certain period of time.
I wouldn't go that far.
These things are never quite that simple.
There is a new chef at the Cafe Royal ...
does marvellous things
with mollusces.
You'll just have time
to catch the three o'clock post, Mildred.
I think we can say if you say it,
that was a job well done.
I should take my rest now.
Go!
I wonder if Peter Walsh has
got in touch with Clarissa?
I think I might buy
something for Evelyn. She is very low.
And jewelry never
loses its price.
I think I buy Clarissa
some flowers.
Yes, I'll pop in to see her on my way
back to the House with some flowers.
Fresh flowers!
I wanted them to be red.
I know.
They're the red ones left.
Richard!
Red roses!
I put them somewhere
very special.
How was lunch? Amusing?
Hugh was there.
He's "rely" is getting quite intolerable.
She wants him to write
a letter to The Times.
One of her schemes
to put in the world in order.
What's all this?
Richard, you couldn't have forgotten!
It's for my party!
And now, it will all be spoiled.
Come here.
Let's sit down for five minutes.
Why would it all be spoiled?
Ms. Marsham has just
sent me this note to say ...
that she's quite sure
I wouldn't mind ...
she's invited Ellie Henderson.
What's so dreadful about that?
Richard! She's one of the dullest
women in the world.
She'll bore everyone. And than Elizabeth said
she isn't coming to the party tonight.
She's gone off to pray
with that dreadful Mrs. Kilman.
You worry too much
about your parties, Clarissa.
Richard, it's all that I can do.
Give people one night
in which everything seems enchanted ...
when all the women seem beautiful,
all the men are handsome ...
and everyone's made to feel
they're amusing ...
Yes, liked.
And go home thinking:
"Ah, what fun it was!"
"What a wonderful evening!"
"How good it is to be alive!"
I don't think poor old Ellie Henderson
could put a stop to that.
You're laughing at me.
Not in the least.
Richard!
You're so much nicer than I am.
You should never have
married me.
Then what would you've done?
Married Peter Walsh, I suppose.
Would you believe that
he was here this morning?
Yes, Minnie Bruton
tell me he was in town.
He's in love with some
woman in India.
He's here to see about
the divorce.
He's just the same.
He hasn't changed the slightest.
You choose a cake, sir.
Thank you.
Did you understand what
the Reverend was saying this morning ...
about knowidge
coming out from suffering?
Not really, no.
But than ...
I suppose I haven't really suffered
yet.
Maybe you'll never will.
Not that I wish that one.
But as he says, real
knowledge is only gained thru suffering.
What was you wanted to buy here?
A petticoat. Mine is in shreds,
I hung on to it as long as I could.
They have some pretty striped ones.
I couldn't possibly afford the striped ones.
I might have to go to the party tonight.
I've forgotten all about it when I
said I'll help with the mission.
Mommy will be upset
if I don't go.
It's a great pity that women like your mother
have nothing better to do ...
with their time than get parties.
Oh, I know it's not her fault.
Women like your mother can't help it
if they'll been spoiled.
She likes giving parties.
I never go to parties.
Why should they ask me?
I'm plain ...
I'm unhappy. But I don't pity
myself. I pity other people more.
Your bill, madam.
You finish your tea.
I pay to set the desk.
I'll help another night at the mission.
I'm sorry. I have to go.
Fear not.
Fear no more.
Who you making that hat for?
Mrs. Filmore's married daughter.
And what's the name of Mrs. Filmore's
married daughter? Mrs. Peters.
I don't like it, but Mrs. Filmore
has been so good to us.
That's too small for Mrs. Peters.
She's enormous.
That's an organ grinding
monkey's hat.
There.
Now, the poor woman looks
like a pig at the fair.
Come on, let's see what else you
have in your workbox.
She shall have a beautiful hat.
There. Now, stitch that together
very, very carefully.
Evans?
Mrs. Filmore, I shall be to busy
looking after Septimus.
It will take a long time.
We thank you for the paper.
Evans?
It was only the evening paper.
Mrs Filmore with the evening paper.
They going to take me away, Rezia.
Sir William Bradshaw said that
you must learn to rest.
It's "must". "Must".
Why "must"? What right has he
to say "must" to me?
It is because you talk
of killing yourself.
So ...
I'm in their power.
Where are my writings, Rezia?
Burn them!
Some are very beautiful!
I'm going with you, Septimus. They can't
separate us against our will.
You're a flowering tree.
You're a sanctuary.
You fear no more!
Not Holmes, not Bradshaw.
You've triumphed.
I'm going to pack our things,
Septimus.
I shall tie this with silk
and hide them away.
Good afternoon, Mrs. Filmore.
Good afternoon, dr.
They send Holmes.
I won't let him come in here.
Ms. Warrensmith, Sir William Bradshaw
is a physician of up most integrity.
He promised not to send you.
Is your husband upstairs?
Look! I will not allow.
It is the law.
Please, go away.
I can not allow you.
Leave my husband alone,
I beg you.
Mr. Warrensmith!
You want my life?
I'll give it to you.
God
God!
Why the devil did he do it?
One of the triumphs
of modern civilization.
Good afternoon.
I'm 12, please.
Thank you.
This came for you, Mr. Walsh.
" Peter, it was heavenly to see you,
I must tell you that. Clarissa. "
We could play tennis.
No. It's too hot
and scorchy for tennis.
Beside,
we need a fourth person to play doubles.
Hugh's gone to visit his mother.
And Herbert won't play.
Maybe "My name is Dalloway" will turn up.
In his perfect whites
matching his perfect teeth.
"My name is Dalloway".
I think we've had enough of
that feeble joke.
She can't be
serious about him!
I'm gonna have this out.
You've come to an understanding
with Dalloway, haven't you?
Haven't you?
It's so difficult, Peter.
Just tell me the truth.
Tell me the truth.
Tell me the truth!
He makes me feel safe.
Safe? Is that what you want?
You want so much of me, Peter.
I just can't do it!
Throw everything away
and go across the world with you.
I'm just not brave in that way.
And Richard ...
and Richard will pamper you
and keep you in a perfectly
beautiful safe prison...
filled with flowers and stuffed
with elegant antique furniture.
He'll make all the decisions for you
and you'll  never have to think again.
You demand so much from me!
Because I love you, for God's sake!
Richard will leave me room,
room to breath.
Clarissa, he is a fool!
And unimaginative,
dull fool!
You want to much of me, Peter.
I can't give it.
So, it's no use.
This is the end.
I'm sorry, Peter.
Clarissa!
Clarissa! Clarissa!
Lord Lexham.
How delightful to see you.
I'm so sorry, but my dear wife
has a cold.
Oh, dear!
She simply would not wear her furs to
the garden party at Buckhurst.
And it was bitterly cold.
Richard!
Oh, dear! It's going to be a failure.
A complete failure.
How delightful of you to come.
Lovely to see you.
We're delighted to see you.
I'm glad you could come.
Why do I do it?
How lovely of you to come.
It was nice of you to invite me.
Mr. Peter Walsh.
Peter, you came!
How delightful to see you.
Peter! Back from India, right?
Yes, back from India.
Must be years since we've seen you.
It was a mistake to invite him.
You'll all know
when he's sorry to come.
And he's criticizing me.
I know he is.
Accusing me of being insincere.
Why do I do this things?
Why seek pinnacles
and stand drenched in fire?
I feel burned to a cinder.
Miss Henderson.
Better that...than
to brindle away like Ellie Henderson.
Ellie! I'm so glad you've come.
It's so grand!
Oh, dear! Why can she at least
stand up properly!
Well, well, I suppose
it's her weaponless state.
Wonderful to see you again.
Richard, how lovely.
Their graces, the Duke
and Duchess of Marlborough.
A duke?
Oh, why did the Marlboroughs
have to follow Ellie Henderson?
They must wonder what kind
of people I invite to our parties.
Clarissa, how lovely to see you.
Thank you so much for inviting us.
Bertie, how lovely of you to come.
It's a disaster! The party is
a disaster! I'm humiliated!
And now there's Peter wondering off.
I'm speak to him!
I know I get the chance, I know it.
Why's he like dirt? He thinks I'm absurd.
Oh, it's too much of an effort!
I'm not enjoying it at all.
I feel like a stake
driven in on the top of this stairs.
Clarissa.
Delighted to see you.
Mr. Hugh Whitbread.
How did you find Evelyn today?
Bearing up, bearing up.
I shall visit her tomorrow.
I do hope she doesn't read
Lady Azquez's memories.
Oh, I doubt it.
Not Evelyn, she's not a great reader.
Lady Bruton.
Lady Bruton? So she came...
My dear Clarissa.
Maybe she doesn't dislike me as much
as I thought she did.
The essential condition
for a study of Milton ...
an  in depth study of Milton ...
A momentary sensation
of an embrace!
It's not a failure, after all!
It's going to be allright.
It's still touch and go,
but it's begun. My party has begun!
Lady Rosseter.
Lady Rosseter? Who I ask can that be?
Clarissa!
Sally
That voice!
Sally Seaton.
Goodness! She didn't look like that
when she kissed me by the fountain.
How wonderful to see you!
How extraordinary to see her again!
She's older, she's happier,
but less lovely.
But, oh, how wonderful that
she's come to my party.
Sally, I've been thinking about
Bordon all day.
Have you? Have you?
The Prime Minister.
Oh, my goodness, Sally, I must go.
Where's Richard?
Sorry, Ellie.
Duty calls.
How delightful to see you.
Unfortunately, my
wife could not come.
The Prime Minister!
It is the Prime Minister.
Clarissa is looking well,
considering how ill she's been.
I know that Richard was very
worried about her.
M.P.'s wives
really shouldn't get ill.
I believe it was her heart.
I think you can always pull yourself together.
Mind of a matter.
Harry Audle.
You painted your wife. Lovely picture.
Peter!
Peter Walsh!
Good Lord! Sally Seaton.
Lady Rosseter now.
Don't be absurd.
It's true. Lady Rosseter.
We live in Manchester
and I have five ennormous boys.
Either my eyes are deceiving me,
or that's Ellie Henderson?
It's our old vicar's daughter.
She's gaping at the Prime Minister.
Oh, do bring her over,
before she disgraces herself ...
and faints with astonishment.
Mr. Prime Minister, how nice to see you.
What would you like?
She's always looked delicate to me.
But such charm.
Richard would've done a great deal better,
if he'd married a woman ...
with less charm and more backbone.
It would've helped him in his work.
He's lost his chance in the Cabinet.
Lady Bruton and Lady Beckford.
What a pleasure to see you.
Lord, what snobbs the english are!
How they love dressing up
and doing homage. Listen to them!
I'd better have baboons chattering
and coolies beat their wives.
Still the same old Peter.
Still playing with your pocket knife.
It is delicious, isn't it?
We are not all the same, Peter.
My husband may have his own cotton mill now,
but he was a miner's son
and when he...
Oh, look! Look!
Isn't that Hugh Whitbread?
What a toady!
What an obsequious toady!
He's not changed at all.
How can she bear him?
It still makes you angry!
Look at her. Intoxicated,
while they all're thinking she's brilliant.
Don't be too hard on her.
After all, parties are a kind of performance.
She has to give a performance.
It isn't the real Clarissa.
The real Clarissa was lost
years ago.
Mr. Prime Minister, can I
introduce our daughter.
I'm sure, if you were alone
with her, you'll find the old Clarissa again.
Fat chance of that this evening!
Richard so enjoyed your lunch and party.
Richard was most encouraging.
And he's promised to drop my little idea ...
into the right ear.
He and the Prime Minister
are having a quiet word now before he leaves.
My plan will save
the government a fortune.
Maybe Richard is sowing
the seeds this very minute.
Isn't that Peter Walsh
talking to old Mrs. Perry?
Yes, that's Peter.
Dear Peter.
So very sharp and clever...
sure had made a name for himself. But
he's allways in some trouble with women.
Do come and say hello to him!
Now, Peter, we can get it straight
from the horse's mouth.
What is going on in India?
Well, great deal, Lady Bruton.
Is a very complex issue.
It is a tragedy.
If my father, the general,
would be alive, he'll sort it out.
Hay, Mrs. Perry.
Clarissa, I must speak with you, please ...
Peter, I must go and deal
with Sir William and Lady Bradshaw.
Will talk later.
I promise.
Awfully good of you to come.
We are shockingly late.
We hardly dared to come in.
We couldn't resist the temptation.
But a rather sad occurrence held us up.
A young patient of mine killed himself.
Really, Richard, there must be
some provision ...
in the government's bill for
this cases of delayed shell shock.
Yes, poor young man.
Awarded for bravery during the war.
And than this evening he just throws himself
out of the window. Impaled on the railings.
It's quite upset William.
She looks like a sea lion
barking at me.
Dear William. He does so hate
losing a patient.
When a young man's body is blown appart,
he loses an arm or a leg ...
or half of face,
as we've seen so often it.
It's immediate.
Stop it! Stop it! Don't talk of death
in the middle of my party!
I don't like you.
I've never liked you.
You're obscurely evil.
And the poor creature will either survive or he won't,
but we all know ...
and we do our best for him.
A young man came to you
on the edge of  insanity...
and you forced his soul ...
made his life intolerable
and he killed himself.
Stucked there with lobs... It's frightful...
Every single mother does everything ...
If you'll excuse me,
lady Bradshaw ...
I have to ...
Alice!
The problem is that politicians
are not really ...
very interested in shell shock.
This is it. This is exactly it.
Hello, Henry, Eleonore.
Delightful to see you.
I see that sir William Bradshaw
is just arrived.
I think it would be most useful to bring him in
on your emigration scheme.
I know he's treating many of this fellows
from shell shock or whatever.
I'm sure, he'll think it's a good idea
to get some of them to Canada.
Open air life and all that...
excellent for mental disturbance.
What a good idea, Hugh.
She's disappeared.
Do you think she went upstairs?
She can't have gone to bed, can't she?
No. She couldn't leave
her own party.
I don't know. I don't know.
I didn't know she'd been ill.
Stop worrying, Peter.
He threw himself out of the window
and impaled himself on the railings.
Up flashed the ground
and through him ...
blundering and bruising
went the rusty spikes ...
and there he lay with a tut... tut! tut!
in his brain.
and then
a suffocation of blackness.
Why? Why did he do it?
Why did the Bradshaws talked
of it at my party?
He's thrown it all away. His life.
Just like that.
I once throw a shelling
into the serpentine.
But his thrown his life away.
You were going to write,
I remember.
Have you written anything?
Not a word.
Not a solitary word.
But then he will
always stay young.
All day long I've been thinking
of Bordon, of Peter and Sally.
We've grown old.
We'll grow older.
Have I lost the thing
that mattered?
Let it get obscured,
gradually...
every day in corruption,
lies and chatter?
Do you remember the night
we went boating on the lake?
Yes, I remember thinking:
"She's abandoned me."
And then, all of the sudden, she was there,
with her hand stretched out ...
looking utterly beautiful, saying:
"Come on, come on.
They're all waiting. "
Why wouldn't she marry me,
Sally?
She was afraid.
Your parents just handed to you,
LIFE...
to be lived right through to the end.
We must walk it
serenely.
But in the depths of my heart,
there's been an awful fear ...
sometimes that
I couldn't go on ...
without Richard, sitting there
calmly reading the Times ...
while I crouched like a bird
and gradually revived.
I might have perished.
I looked across the room
and wondered - "Who's that lovely girl?"
And then I realized:
"That's my daughter."
Maybe she needed someone
who found life simple.
She certainly cared for you,
more than she cared for Richard.
Oh, my life isn't simple.
My relationship with her
wasn't simple.
She broke my heart.
And you can't love like that
twice.
What makes us go on?
What sends roaring
up in us ...
that immeasurable delight
to surprise us?
Than nothing can be
slow enough...
nothing lasts to long.
You want to say to each moment:
"Stay!" "Stay!"
"Stay!"
I cherrish the friendship
I had with Clarissa.
There was something pure about her.
She had such charm,
such generosity.
I can see her to this day, going
bye the house all in white.
She always seemed to be in white
and her arms were full of flowers.
And I wondered ...
does absence really matter?
Does distance?
You'll think me sentimental
and so I am ...
but I've come to believe that the only
thing worth saying is what you really feel.
But I don't know what I feel.
I know that I loved her once
and that it stayed with me all my life ...
and colored everything.
I must go back to my party.
To Sally and Peter.
That young man killed himself,
but I don't pity him.
I'm somehow glad he could do it,
throw it away.
It's made me feel the beauty,
somehow feel ...
very like him, less afraid.
I have to go.
Do you think he's made her happy?
Who can tell, Peter?
All our relationships are
just scratches on the surface.
We tought he wasn't
very bright.
But what does the brain matter?
Compared to the heart.
There you are.
Peter and Sally haven't left, have they?
Don't know.
Clarissa!
I couldn't leave without
saying goodbye.
And you can't leave,
until you danced with me.
Peter's in the library.
Here I am, at last.