ALFRED:
Legend tells of a caped crusader...
...Batman, guardian of New Gotham...
...and his one true love...
...Catwoman,
the queen of the criminal underworld.
Their passion left behind
something extraordinary:
a daughter, Huntress.
Half-metahuman,
she has taken up her father's mantle...
...and under cover of the night,
fights to protect the innocent and helpless.
Joining her in this struggle, Oracle...
...who was once Batman's protégée,
Batgirl.
She was caught in the crossfire
of the war between Batman and Joker.
[GUNSHOT]
Now she fights crime a different way:
a master of the cyberrealms
and mentor and trainer to heroes.
Together, they have taken in
a young runaway, Dinah.
A metahuman herself...
...with powers to open hidden doors
to the mind...
...powers that she
is only beginning to explore.
Together, these three
are the protectors of New Gotham...
...the Birds of Prey.
[HAWK CRIES]
My name is Alfred Pennyworth,
and this is their story.
HELENA: It's hard for me to come here.
-Why is that, Helena?
I don't trust people.
Luckily for you,
this is your last court-mandated session.
Then I must be officially sane.
What a relief.
You don't have to come back,
unless you want to.
I know you think
you can't trust anyone...
...but I'd like to help you, if you'd let me.
Why is it so difficult for you
to let people in, Helena?
After Mom was killed...
...I found out about my dad,
who he was.
Well, most people
would be excited to discover...
...that a billionaire philanthropist
like Bruce Wayne was their father.
I only wanted one thing from him:
That he find the man
that killed my mother.
And then?
And then I wanted that man dead.
We can't just go around killing people,
Helena.
[SCOFFS]
Yeah, that's-- That's what I hear.
All I wanted from him was revenge.
If it had been the other way,
Mom would've done it.
They hadn't been together in years.
She would've killed for him.
And that's when I learned
what my mom always knew:
Rely on no one but yourself.
SLICK:
What's wrong with you people?
I'm talking about real money here.
Ooh! Real money, guys.
What's real money to you, Slick?
More than your pension cash,
I'll tell you that.
I've got some years in,
my pension's looking pretty sweet.
-How about you, Reese?
-I need money, I hit the casino.
-Oh, that ever work for you?
-Mm, not yet.
I'm not talking jackpot cash here, okay?
I'm talking lottery cash, 25 million.
GRACE: Mm-hm, okay.
-Split it however you want.
Okay, okay.
Thirty, okay?
Come on.
Tell you what, Slick.
I'm a simple guy...
...so I'm gonna do you a favor.
I'm gonna leave this thing at robbery,
and I'm gonna forget all about...
...the generous, although misguided,
attempt to bribe three good cops.
Okay?
So...
...why don't you sit tight
while we get you processed, huh?
GRACE: If I had a nickel for every time
a perp offered me a bribe....
REESE:
We'd all make real money.
If you're looking for your paycheck,
forget it.
I don't reward failure.
Excuse me, beautiful, I did my job.
I got in the truck.
You didn't say anything about cops.
I asked you to hijack one armored truck,
a job you assured me...
...you could do in your sleep,
and you got caught.
Heh, people who work for Harley Quinn
don't get caught.
Oh, calm down, baby.
Nobody has to lose any body parts here.
Hee-hee, don't be so sure.
I know, I've only been in New Gotham
for a few months...
...and maybe this kind of pathetic screwup
passes for crime in this town?
Things are gonna change.
New Gotham
ran the Joker out on a rail.
Now he's locked up in a prison
far away from here.
This city is gonna pay
for what they did to my sweet Mr. J.
I'll have a vengeance...
...that will be spoken of in terrified whispers
for generations to come.
Do you understand?
Not exactly, no.
Ah, I'm gonna take over New Gotham,
you idiot.
You really ought to see someone
about those mood swings.
I've decided to give you
one more chance, Slick.
And I know you won't let me down.
We only have a week
before you start classes.
We need to finish filling these--
[WHIRRING NEARBY]
-Out.
-Oh, sorry.
Quite a nice throw, actually.
Excellent velocity.
[BARBARA SIGHS]
Uh, this isn't the Batarang
I gave you for practice.
I know, but this one has
three times the range of the regular ones...
...plus all the automated stuff.
It's way cooler.
BARBARA:
I know, I designed it.
Look, Dinah, your training
is meant to prepare you in stages.
You need to learn one step
before moving on to the next.
[DOOR OPENS]
Which means mastering
the basic weapons...
...before you use the ones
with bells and whistles.
And, uh, target-seeking capabilities.
-Greetings, super-friends.
-Hi, good morning.
DINAH:
How was your sweep?
Slow night: two muggers, store robbery.
Hardly worth the effort.
How can they need...
...this much information
to let one girl into school?
DINAH:
I wanna show you something.
What do you think of this
for my first-day-of-school outfit?
What?
Kind of a draft-me-for-the-chess-club
thing going on.
I'll need to get your basic information:
birth certificate, social security,
that sort of thing.
There isn't any.
Sorry?
Um, information.
There isn't any.
There was a fire at the county courthouse
and all the records burned.
Well, I'll at least
need to get your transcripts.
Uh, they burned too.
Your transcripts would be at the school,
not the courthouse.
Well, it was a really big fire.
[BARBARA SIGHS]
Well, what about your parents?
They're dead. Um, I'm gonna go practice
in the training room, okay?
[SIGHS]
[BARBARA SIGHS]
Poor kid.
You can't mean to tell me
you actually bought that.
Have a heart, Helena.
I took you in at the same age.
Yeah, and I used to lie to you all the time,
only I was better at it.
Uh, not that much better.
Okay, fine.
I'll do a background check on her, okay?
But I'm telling you,
there's no reason to panic.
Something panic-worthy always happens
right after you say that.
Okay, look, she's not just a runaway,
she's a metahuman like you.
Now, you know better than I do
how hard the world is for kids like that.
Okay....
[KNOCKS ON DOOR]
Hey.
-Wade, hi.
-Hi.
-How are the lesson plans coming?
Oh, you know....
School is always so much more peaceful
before the kids get here.
They do kind of clutter the place up.
[BOTH CHUCKLE]
BARBARA: Maybe we should-- Ha, ha.
WADE: So about-- Ha, ha.
-Go ahead, I'm sorry.
-It's um-- No, please.
Well, I was just gonna say...
...should we make plans?
-I thought you forgot.
-Well, actually, I thought you forgot. Heh.
Oh, no, no, no.
Um, the other day,
I was just in the midst of, well...
...kind of an emergency.
-Is everything all right?
-Yeah. Yeah, yeah, everything's fine.
Yeah, it's just, um, this business I have
with my friend Helena.
-What kind of business?
-Gourmet baking.
Uh, custom fudge and muffin tops.
We sell them online.
It's sort of a moonlighting,
hobby sort of thing.
Emergencies in the baking world?
We take our culinary responsibilities
very seriously.
Well, you're just gonna have to trust me
with the plans.
Ah. I promise they will be silly
and absolutely mindless.
So I said yes.
HELENA:
Good. It's about damn time.
All this crime-fighting without a social life
is making you grouchy.
I'm not grouchy, I'm just realistic.
All my relationships come
with an expiration date.
I mean, the moment he asks:
"So hey. Hey, why can't you just blow off
this late-night baking gig?"
[GIGGLES]
The muffin-top cover story?
Possibly the lamest thing
you've ever come up with.
You just get to a point
where you can't lie anymore.
Never been there.
You'll have to tell me what it's like.
Speaking of lying, about Dinah?
-Oh, I ran a background check.
-You did? What'd you find?
-Nothing.
-So I guess I should be relieved...
...she's not an ax murderer.
No, I mean nothing. No records at all.
I mean, as if she didn't exist.
She gave us a false name.
You're just getting around
to mentioning this now?
-I thought you might overreact.
-I'm not overreacting.
I'm very calmly pointing out
that we have no idea who this girl is.
Actually, we do.
I ran a facial-recognition autosearch...
...on yearbook photos
from Missouri going back five years.
[COMPUTER BEEPS]
Meet Dinah Redmond of Opal, Missouri.
Population, 2541 .
Some truancy, she's run away a few times.
She'd been living with her foster family.
Her parents gave her up.
Anyway, the point is,
now we know that she really is a runaway...
...and not some criminal mastermind.
Known by other aliases as,
oh, "The Truth."
-She'll tell us when she's ready.
-And until then you're just gonna trust her?
With all this top-secret,
super-classified intel around here?
-She could get into anything.
DINAH: Hey, guys.
That's my sweater!
-Well, you said I should dress better.
-Not in my clothes.
BARBARA:
Hey, time out.
There will be
absolutely no use of super-powers...
...to settle domestic disagreements.
You, get changed. You, come with me.
HELENA:
That was my favorite sweater.
I think she's evil.
You think she could be evil?
If you would just take your clothes home
once in a while...
...instead of leaving them
all over the Clocktower...
...she wouldn't have found
your sweater to begin with.
You know what,
this is not about clothing and you know it.
Easy for you to say,
she's not poaching your daywear.
Her parents
didn't even report her missing.
Sounds like she had a reason
to run away.
-Still don't know what that was.
-She's got incredible potential.
I just have this gut feeling that--
So do I.
Like I'm about to get sucker-punched.
Helena, think about how we learned.
How we all learned.
Dick Grayson, Tim Drake,
Jason Todd, even you.
It's more than a tradition, it's a legacy.
Take in those like us,
mentor and train them.
Never turn away someone
with the hunger to become what we are.
That's what your father
would have done.
Batman was your role model, not mine.
Yeah, you keep saying that.
[ALARM BLARING]
Barbara?
Helena? Hello? Are you guys there?
BARBARA [O VER RADIO] : What is it, Dinah?
-Oh, okay.
There's a big red light
flashing on the Delphi monitor system.
What do I do?
Oh, there's the download button.
BARBARA [O VER RADIO] :
Don't touch anything.
We're on our way back.
Okay.
CORONER:
Deceased is male, mid-30s.
He's 36, and the deceased has a name.
Jack Barnstone. He's a cop.
Cause of death is consistent
with asphyxiation...
...but there are no ligature marks,
no external abrasions or bruising.
And no sign of anything lodged internally
that could have caused the blockage.
-But that's not the weird thing.
-Great, a weird thing.
Look at this: skin discoloration,
pink foam around the lips.
These are all signs
consistent with drowning...
...but there was no water found
near the victim...
...and no signs that the body's been moved,
so drowning is pretty much impossible.
No, it's not impossible.
BARBARA: The Delphi Protocol
is a database program I created.
It automatically tracks and sorts
crimes reported in New Gotham...
...and then alerts us to anything unusual.
-The freakedelic stuff.
-Yep.
I'm piggybacked on
to the New Gotham P.D. computer...
...so we get information
simultaneously with the police.
-Is that legal?
-No.
The coroner finished the autopsy.
They're listing cause of death
as heart failure.
So?
So of course his heart stopped.
The question is, why?
I need some lung tissue.
Come on, it's Friday night.
What's a weekend without lung tissue?
It's late, Grace.
-Are you gonna be okay to get home?
-Yeah, fine.
I'll see you guys in the morning.
Grace, we're all gonna miss Jack.
Yeah.
Damn it.
[WATER RUSHING]
You.
-What the hell are you doing here?
-Miss me?
So how's the lung tissue?
Alveolar distention
clearly indicates drowning.
And yet...
...there's no excess of fluid in the cells.
-Do I look all right?
-Beautiful. Go on your date, relax.
-I'll mind the fort.
-Okay.
You see what I'm saying
about the lung-cell distortions, right?
Really, how do I look?
Like you need to leave.
Right, leaving.
Okay, there's pizza in the freezer...
...and Alfred's number is on the fridge.
Okay, you know what? I've gotta ask.
Even though it risks delaying
your long-overdue departure even further...
-...but how are you doing that?
-Doing what?
That thing with your chair?
That steering-with-no-hands thing?
Ah. It's pretty cool, huh?
Yeah, I've been, uh, tinkering.
It's a transponder strapped to my spine.
Uh, a subneural-response net...
...that interfaces directly with
the chair's computerized motor controls.
You're techno-babbling.
I think, therefore the chair moves.
Hey, but if it's plugged into your spine,
could you, um--?
Use the technology
to get out of the chair sometime?
Anything is possible.
Do you think it's possible
that you might leave for your date?
Okay, okay. I'm going, I'm going.
-Be good.
-Mm, I'll try.
[SIGHS]
BARBARA:
I don't usually let people push me, heh.
WADE:
Since this requires you to close your eyes...
...you're gonna have to let me drive.
You can look...
...now.
BARBARA:
Oh, wow.
It's beautiful.
Well, I thought it might beat out
dinner and a movie.
-How did you get in here?
-I said I was your sister.
Great. Just what I need...
...another relative
with a creative relationship with the truth.
Well, I thought this way,
I might actually get you to talk to me.
So talk.
[DINAH SIGHS]
You don't want me here, do you?
BARBARA: It seems like all I ever look at
is the skyline of New Gotham.
Never the sky.
Ah, so I'm broadening your horizons.
Day job, night job.
It sounds to me
like you spend way too much time on work.
What about your heart?
I think it's still in there somewhere.
Sure it is.
[PAGER BEEPING]
WADE:
Who is it?
It's just an automated system. Ignore it.
[BOTH CHUCKLE]
[PAGER BEEPING]
[SIGHS]
Wade, I'm sorry, I have to go.
I'll make it up to you.
I promise.
[SCOFFS]
What we do is dangerous.
Been out on the field on my own
for a very long time...
...and that's the way I like it.
I came here to be like you.
I want this more
than I've ever wanted anything.
[SCOFFS]
I thought if I told you how important
this was to me, that you'd understand.
-So why can't you just tell me the truth?
-That is the truth.
Your parents aren't dead, are they?
It's not that easy. It's complicated.
You're 1 6, how complicated can it be?
Heh. Yeah, and when you were 1 6,
life was really simple and straightforward.
Okay, that's totally different
and completely besides the point.
Trust isn't something that you
can just be given, it has to be earned.
Then let me earn it.
If you would just give me a chance,
I know I can prove it to you.
When? When we're out on the field
and it's full-on kill-or-be-killed combat?
Heh. I need to be completely sure
that someone's got my back.
And there's only one person
I can count on for that.
BARBARA [O VER RADIO] :
It's me. Have you seen Dinah?
Yeah, she's here.
BARBARA: Good, I was worried.
But if she's with you, then l--
I'm suddenly realizing I'm still worried.
Why are you home? It's not even 1 1 yet.
[O VER RADIO]
How was your date?
Interrupted.
Another cop is dead.
Same circumstance as Barnstone:
Drowned on dry land.
[WATER TRICKLING THEN RUSHING]
Catching up on current events?
"Man kills ex-girlfriend then himself."
Nice.
I have a professional interest.
George was a patient.
Guess the therapy didn't take, ha.
Oh? I wouldn't say that.
I was the one who told him
the key to his mental well-being...
...was to express his rage.
That's not bad work, for an amateur.
Why do you waste your time?
I mean, a day job for a supervillain?
It's so...
...bourgeois.
George and my other patients aren't work,
they're hobbies.
You know, like golf? Recreational.
You ever heard
of the Greek goddess Eris?
The Romans called her Discord,
the sower of strife.
She started everything
from petty arguments to cataclysmic wars...
...while she just sat back and watched.
Untouched.
Now there was a girl
who knew how to delegate.
You lost me, babe.
Yeah, well, that's what happens
when you regularly turn your brain to water.
Aren't you late for your appointment
with the good detective?
I do need all three cops
out of the picture this time.
I just can't bear the idea of you
screwing up my little hijacking plan again.
Don't worry. It's as good as done.
Take care of the cop...
...and go get my truck...
...Slick.
Don't fail me again.
BARBARA:
We've got a link.
The cops who died were connected
by a case a few weeks ago.
They stopped the hijacking of a truck
by a guy named Silas Waters, a.k.a. Slick.
The truck was carrying
military ordnance...
...and we're talking major-league,
major-league weaponry.
-Missiles, launchers, grenades, C4.
-All the fun toys.
Let me guess, Slick's out on bail.
Uh, not exactly.
The police booked him and locked him up.
The next time somebody looked for him,
he'd vanished.
-A metahuman?
-Someone who could transform...
...into some kind of fluid
thin enough to go down a drain.
We could call him Liquid Guy.
Uh, I'm just trying to contribute.
Police report said
Slick tried to bribe them with a cut.
The weapons
had a black-market value of $30 million.
-Cops said no.
-No to $30 million?
What kind of idiot
says no to $30 million?
You again.
-Can I help you?
-Actually, I'm here to help you.
There's not a lot of time though,
somebody's trying to kill you.
You mind if I get my clothes?
And by the way, who are you?
-Grace Tanner's dead.
-What?
-When?
-About an hour ago.
-Slick Waters.
-Has to be.
So now you think
the guy's coming after me, huh?
Well, listen, I appreciate the heads up,
but I can take care of myself.
Heh, look. You don't understand
what you're dealing with.
Waters is no ordinary criminal.
He can liquefy.
Wherever water can go, he can too.
Liquefy?
[REESE SCOFFS]
Like-- Like a liquid guy.
Is this a joke?
Your friends drowned on dry land.
Waters escaped through a drain.
-Do you have a better explanation?
-Is there actually a worse one?
Congratulations. You've managed
to convince him you're totally insane.
Do you mind?
I am trying to have a conversation here.
Oh, right, right, the invisible friend.
I almost forgot about that part.
Look, I am just trying to help you.
Lady, you look.
I know a lot of strange things
may happen here in New Gotham...
...but a guy made out of water?
Come on, that's just ridiculous.
-Oracle, he's here.
-Huntress?
BARBARA [O VER RADIO] :
Huntress, can you read me?
Huntress?
Huntress!
Huntress, is there a fire extinguisher
near you?
Listen to me,
get the fire extinguisher and spray him.
[HELENA GRUNTS]
[BOTH GRUNTING]
Huntress, can you hear me?
Are you all right?
Once I had an actual ass to kick,
I was fine.
How'd you know
the extinguisher would work?
I figured Slick had to reach
a certain active molecular state...
...to be able to shift phases
from solid to liquid.
HELENA [O VER RADIO] :
Speak English, please.
Uh, cool him down, he's Solid Guy.
It's a temperature thing.
That-- That was....
I mean, he was....
-Is he still in there?
-I don't know.
-Just get out of there.
-We gotta go.
Now wait a minute,
there's a murder suspect in there, um...
-...uh, possibly.
-You gonna arrest him?
With what, a bucket?
Assuming he hasn't already
gone down the drain.
HELENA:
Go.
Huntress, talk to me.
I'm busy right now. Keep it closed.
[BANGING ON DOOR]
REESE:
Oh, my--
[HISSING]
What the...?
It's a temperature thing.
HELENA: It's hot. How long are we
gonna have to stay in here?
I need to come up with a way
to disable this guy.
-It won't be long.
-Better not be or I'm gonna melt.
Okay, so what?
What, we're trapped in here now?
And when we go out there and he--?
What, he gets us?
On the positive side,
he comes in, he's air freshener.
Ha, ha. All right, um,
what the hell is going on?
I mean, for all I know, you had something
to do with Jack and Grace's deaths.
You don't believe that.
I don't know what to believe right now.
Not about you, about any of this.
What I just saw at that pool,
that's not possible.
Funny, you strike me as the kind of guy
that believes in the impossible.
Well, it's a little hard not to,
when you're standing here talking to it.
Aren't you worried
that I might tell somebody?
I mean, why are you letting me see you?
Because it was the only way
I could save your life.
BARBARA: Stay put. You can't go out there
until we know where this guy is.
-I'm working on a way to neutralize....
-She's really worried.
Is Helena okay?
Oh, Miss Helena is remarkably capable.
She can take care of herself.
-Alfred?
-Mm-hm?
My whole life, I grew up thinking...
...that there was no one like me.
You know, that I was all alone.
Then I come here...
...and I finally meet someone
who's like me.
You know, someone who I can admire
and look up to.
Seems like all I can do is piss her off.
If I were you, I would be more concerned
if Miss Helena weren't upset with you.
Why?
I've always found
that how much someone cares about you...
...is directly proportional to how much
you can piss them off, as it were.
[CHUCKLES]
This Slick guy...
...what if Barbara can't find a way
for Helena to fight him?
They're superheroes, Miss Dinah.
They're familiar with tight situations.
Why is it so important to you to know...
...what goes on in New Gotham
after nightfall?
Most people would do anything
to convince themselves...
...the world is a safe, sane,
and normal place.
But not you.
You're actually chasing the madness.
I've got my reasons.
I'm wondering what they are.
Heh. You know, you're not exactly
the poster girl for full disclosure.
And what's that supposed to mean?
It means you're gonna have to keep
right on wondering.
Look, I gotta get out of here.
I'm on assignment tonight.
[CHUCKLES SOFTLY]
I don't think Slick gives a damn
about our work schedule.
Someone can replace you.
You can't be the only honest cop
in New Gotham.
No, I'm the only one left on tonight's detail.
The other two are dead.
Wait a minute, Barnstone and Tanner
were on tonight's detail with you?
Yeah.
Where are you supposed to be?
Reese was on a detail
scheduled to escort...
...another transport
of military weapons tonight.
It's the same deal as
that attempted hijacking a few weeks ago.
The cargo is hardcore stuff:
surface-to-air missiles,
flamethrowers, plastic explosives.
Enough firepower
to start your own little war.
Looks like Slick wasn't in it for revenge.
HELENA: If at first you don't succeed....
BARBARA: This time...
...they're killing the cops
that can't be bought.
We have to assume whoever's taking
Barnstone, Tanner and Reese's place...
-...is in Slick's pocket.
HELENA: Cops. What's the going rate?
BARBARA:
The cruiser assigned to guard the truck...
...has a standard-issue
Gotham P.D. GPS locator.
It's been stationary the last five minutes.
Looks like that's our location.
Look, we still don't know
how to stop Slick, Helena.
Be careful.
Well, I know one thing.
If he's off robbing a truck,
he's not outside this door.
-That would stand to reason.
-It's stuck.
He must have wedged it shut
from the outside.
MAN: All right, guys, let's get
these weapons out of the truck. Let's move.
Bulletproof, bombproof, fireproof...
...but not waterproof.
Huntress, what's your status?
HELENA: We're in position,
and we got here just in time...
-...to crash the party.
-Crash?
Hi, boys, can I play?
[ALL GRUNTING]
[BOTH GRUNTING]
[MAN GRUNTING]
[REESE GRUNTS]
Was it good for you?
Because it sure is for me.
[GAGGING NEARBY]
[REESE GAGGING]
[BOTH GRUNT]
[SLICK SCREECHING]
[THUD]
[PANTING]
[REESE COUGHING]
[SIGHS]
You okay, kid?
Yeah, yeah.
Um, I found Dinah.
What, there? Is she okay?
She's fine. She's...
...really great.
[SIGHS]
Then tell her she's grounded.
I guess this means I'm grounded.
Take the car back. I'll catch up.
Okay.
[COUGHING]
HELENA:
You all right?
With which part, hmm?
Getting drowned by Liquid Guy?
Not knowing what's real anymore?
Or getting dehydrated
from five hours in a sauna?
This was a slow night.
What the hell am I supposed to do
with what I've just seen?
What, just forget about it?
If you talk, nobody's gonna believe you.
They will if you come with me.
Can't do that, Reese.
That's your world, not mine.
So then, we're right back
where we started.
-You don't trust me?
-You won't tell me who you are.
Or why you do what you do.
Right now, you're asking for more
than I can give.
You saved my life and I'm grateful.
But gratitude is not the same as trust.
Can't you just tell me, who are you?
It's...
...complicated.
Look, Reese.
Sometimes you just have
to make the leap...
...let go...
...and believe.
I wish I could.
Well?
-Dinah, l-- Heh.
-Helena--
Let me go first.
I told you trust had to be earned
and I was wrong.
Trust is a gift.
You were there for me
when it mattered...
...for both of us.
And as for the rest of it,
it's an act of faith believing in someone.
I believe in you.
Whatever your name is.
Redmond.
My name is Dinah Redmond...
...and I have been lying to you
about everything.
My mother left me with foster parents
when I was 6.
And they taught me to be ashamed
of what I was...
...never to tell anyone...
...to hide it.
Then when I couldn't hide it anymore,
they were gonna take me somewhere.
Somewhere to make my powers stop.
And I thought if I told you
my real name...
...that you'd call them
and they'd take me away.
Dinah, don't you ever wanna go home?
Being here with you...
...it is the only place I have ever,
ever felt at home in my entire life.
Come on, kid, let's see
what Alfred left us for dinner.
[CHUCKLES SOFTLY]
-You're still grounded.
-Absolutely.
Barbara, what--?
I promised I'd make it up to you.
Heh, I....
I mean, I know it's not nearly
as romantic...
...but I thought it might do
as an apology.
Definitely.
[BOTH CHUCKLE]
It was weird,
fighting side by side with Reese.
What was it like?
Kind of like...
...a first date.
Mm, yeah, I'd buy that.
Considering every time you get next to him
you can't shut up.
Invisible friend.
[BOTH CHUCKLE]
He's really gotten under your skin,
hasn't he?
You know guys don't get to me.
Besides, who has time
for a real relationship anyway?
Yeah.
You know, I still can't figure it out.
What did Slick want with that firepower?
You said it yourself.
It's worth a fortune on the black market.
Yeah, but so are a lot of things...
...and for a guy like Slick,
most of them are easier to steal.
So you think Slick was just a front man.
For who?
[KNOCKING ON DOOR]
Helena, what can I do for you?
I've been rethinking
this whole do-everything-by-myself thing...
...and I've decided
I want to continue therapy...
...even though I don't have to.
Maybe a little help
sometimes isn't so bad.
Please, come in.
HELENA:
I met a guy.
Why don't you tell me about him.
[ENGLISH SDH]