I remember when Roy brought Irma home.
He took me aside and said,
"Mama, I think this is the one."
I wanted him to stay and run the farm.
But he said no, he'd rather be dead.
- Dad, time for the toast.
- I'm telling a story.
I got so mad,
I hauled off and popped him one.
Gave him a shiner on his wedding day.
Let's get Roy and Irma up here!
Where are they?
Come on, let's go,
before they enter their 26th!
- Are we all here?
- Yeah, we are!
I remember when Roy and Irma
first joined our congregation.
What was it, 21 years ago?
They had more energy
and more goodwill toward each other...
than any couple I ever knew.
The goodwill is still there.
I don't know about the energy.
I remember their first
pancake breakfast.
Roy at the griddle,
Irma right behind him with the batter.
As soon as he'd scoop up one pancake,
she'd plop down another one.
Never a cross word between them.
In fact, the more pressure
that was on them...
the more they seemed
to enjoy each other.
I don't know of any other couple
in our congregation...
or in this town, for that matter...
more devoted to each other...
more in love than Roy and Irma.
I'm grateful to have them with us...
because we're all beneficiaries
of that partnership.
Happy anniversary.
Get an ambulance.
Is he drunk?
Dear God...
help this couple find the wisdom
to work out their differences...
and rekindle the joy of their marriage.
Shed your light upon them, so that they
may continue to grow and flourish...
in the love that they have for you
and for each other.
Amen.
Roy, I heard what
happened the other night.
Are you all right?
- I'm fine. It was nothing.
- Scared me half to death.
We took him to the hospital,
but everything turned out okay.
Thank goodness.
I think it has something to do
with the headaches.
I mean, he's been getting terrible,
terrible headaches.
- Have you seen a doctor about this?
- Every one in the phone book.
- He's had a CAT scan.
- Insurance will cut me loose.
- Did they find anything?
- No.
I think it's...
His doctor seems to think it's stress.
Has your work been stressful?
There's some pressure on me.
Honey, there's a lot
of pressure on you.
No more than usual.
He used to have to handle
just the tractors.
But now, he has to take
care of everything...
from the cultivators to the combines...
Yikes!
So you could say that maybe
these headaches are work-related.
They could be.
Is there anything else in your life
that's been bothering you?
You can always find something.
Honey, I think there's been some...
strain between us lately.
Sure, there's been some strain.
Are you having any problems with...
intimacy?
Not really.
We haven't had much intimacy lately.
Because of the headaches?
Yes.
Would you like to talk to me alone?
Whatever it is, just get it out, honey.
I don't even have to know what it is.
I mean, just talk it out with him, okay?
Please?
Irma, if you want,
you can wait in the chapel.
No, I'd like Irma to stay.
Better still.
Tell us what's on your mind, Roy.
I've been...
struggling with something
for a long time.
I prayed for years for it to go away.
But it won't.
Go on.
I was born in the wrong body.
I'm a woman. I've known it all my life.
Oh, my gosh, Roy.
Good grief, Roy...
I don't know what to say.
I don't either, except...
I love Irma very much.
The last thing I want to do
is cause her any pain.
- Roy, are you having an affair?
- No, Irma.
But this doesn't make any sense.
Roy, I have to agree.
I mean, you've been married to Irma
for 25 years.
You have two wonderful children,
and suddenly, out of nowhere...
you make this strange declaration?
It's not out of nowhere.
I've been hiding it for years.
It's been an agony.
I can't go on living my life like this.
I'd rather die.
Oh, my God, do you mean that?
Yes.
Before you jump to any more conclusions
about yourself...
what exactly appeals to you
about being a woman?
What appeals to you about being a man?
Many things.
Beginning with the fact
that this is the form God chose for me.
But I believe that God meant for me
to be something else.
- Meaning?
- Meaning I'd like to...
have the operation...
to change my sex.
Oh, my God, Roy.
Obviously, this is a lot
for us to comprehend, Roy.
You know, I'd like to go home.
I think this would be
a good point to stop.
Obviously, I wasn't prepared for this.
If you two could give me a few days
to do some research, think this over...
Roy, I'm not exactly sure...
how I'm going to counsel you at this
point, but I promise I'm not giving up.
I just want to be sure that...
you'll still accept me
as a member of the congregation.
Heck, you're the only
fellow I can get...
to nail together the
nativity every year.
You think I'll let you go that easy?
What?
What did I do?
Nothing, honey.
Then someone talk.
How was school?
Don't talk to me, talk to each other.
Your dad and I both had a long day...
and we just don't feel like talking.
Talk anyway.
Finish your peas.
Irma, we couldn't go on
the way things were.
Look at how unhappy I've made you.
I'm not unhappy.
There's been a strain
between us for years.
- This is supposed to make it better?
- I'm hoping so. Yes.
Did you feel this way when you met me?
I suspected it, yes.
Then what in heaven's name
were you thinking of on our wedding day?
- That you were the one for me.
- Meaning what?
Meaning that I loved you, I love you.
When we're in bed...
are you a man or are you a woman?
- I make love to you as myself.
- But are you a man, or are you a woman?
Sometimes, I imagine
I have a different body. Not always.
Sometimes, the female part takes over.
I have some books you could read.
Books?
About my condition.
About the operation.
You mean, you expect us to go on
living together after you do this thing?
If you'll have me.
Frankly, honey,
there's no way you're a woman.
Only a man could be this selfish.
- Mom?
- What is it, Patty?
- Could you come out here for a minute?
- Is it something important?
Yes.
What is it?
Mom, it happened.
Just a minute.
- You all right, Patty?
- It's nothing.
- You want me to show you how to...
- No!
Is she all right?
She got her period.
Poor kid. She sounded so scared.
You are not to breathe a word to her
about any of this. Do you understand?
She has to know about
me at some point.
No, I won't allow you to do this.
- There's a way to handle it properly.
- No!
- Absolutely not!
- Irma, it's not going to go away.
Get out! Get out of my bedroom!
- I'll sleep on the couch.
- No, I don't want you in this house.
All right.
If this is only a separation, why are
you throwing out all of Dad's stuff?
Is that what you're wearing to school?
Go change your clothes.
Why?
Don't argue, just do it.
How you doing, Roy?
- Morning, Roy.
- Morning, Bob.
Another goddamn day.
Not a damn thing we can
do about it, either.
See you later.
So, I talked to a pastor in Akron.
He was counselling a married couple...
and the husband said that
he was a homosexual.
He was able to persuade the husband
not to act on his inclinations...
and he saved the marriage.
- Sounds hopeful.
- I'm feeling very hopeful about this.
Now, what this pastor did...
he referred this couple
to a chapter in the Bible...
which I think
very elegantly supports our case.
Did you bring your Bible?
No, I'm sorry.
No problem. You can look on with me.
Ephesians, Chapter 5, Verse 28.
"So ought men to love their wives
as their own bodies.
"He that loveth his
wife loveth himself.
"For no man ever yet
hated his own flesh."
Bingo!
In other words, men
couple with women to
bring out the female
side of their nature.
And the mistake that Roy's making...
is he's looking to himself for
that balance, instead of to you.
I see.
We need to just make Roy realize
that you're all the woman he needs.
He doesn't have to make himself
into a woman...
parade around in dresses and such.
Heck, that's just plain egotistical of
him, to think that he can do it all.
Men need women for completion.
Why do you think we call our wives
our better halves?
Roy has always felt
overly responsible for things.
He used to come home from work...
do a couple of hours of chores, and then
stay up till midnight paying bills.
No wonder he gets these
terrible headaches.
That's why I decided
to take over doing the taxes.
Irma, let me ask you something.
And this may just be a stab in the dark.
Do you think you might have unknowingly
added to his confusion?
I don't know what you mean.
Please understand, I'm not questioning
your love for Roy in any way.
It's just that you're
a very strong-willed person...
and I'm just wondering if you often take
the upper hand with Roy.
Do you mean...
have I emasculated him?
I haven't made myself clear. Forgive me.
Gosh!
I think it's a problem that
every modern couple is having right now.
Who's the head of the household?
Is it the one who brings home
the biggest pay check?
Heck, I'm not going to
win on that one. Not
with what I make on a pastor's salary.
But I don't work.
I know that.
From what I've observed,
you've been a very good wife.
I don't know what I'm doing wrong.
I don't know either, Irma,
but we'll figure it out.
I keep smelling this goddamn perfume.
Where the hell is it coming from?
I think it's Roy over there.
Roy, you dog, have you been stepping out
on your wife?
- No.
- Hey, I'm not saying a word.
I love Irma dearly, I'd
never do that to her.
If you say so.
- I do say so.
- Buddy, there's no judgment here.
Whoever the new lady is, I say enjoy it.
- I wish I could trade my wife in.
- You want mine?
She still has a few good miles left.
I'm looking for a newer model.
So what year's your new model, Roy?
- I'm not stepping out on Irma.
- If you say so.
The perfume's mine.
- I put it on this morning.
- What on earth for?
I like it.
I'd never cheat on Irma.
Never in a million years.
Don't ever say that to me again.
What the hell?
- Did you find an apartment?
- Yes.
What's it like?
It's small. One room, kitchenette.
Does it get any sun?
No, but there are things I can do
to cheer it up.
What kind of life
is this going to be for you, Roy?
I don't know.
But I hope you'll still be part of it.
- Are these ready to sign?
- Yeah.
You won't be able to claim...
Patty Ann as a dependent.
I don't see why not,
if I'm paying support.
But you won't be her father.
I'll be her parent,
who still loves her and cares for her.
I sent a letter to Wayne.
Are you out of your mind?
He's my son,
and he has a right to know what's what.
Not this!
It had to be done, whether
you like it or not.
And it's been done.
What if I told you I wouldn't allow you
to see Patty Ann anymore?
What if?
It would break my heart...
more than you could know.
But you'd still do it?
The postage is all there.
Just drop it in the mailbox, okay?
Let's hear it.
It might seem a little
funny, but it hurts.
I got one. I just got this from my dad.
Get ready to be fucked up.
"Dear Wayne, I'm writing to you
at a frightening...
"and also very exciting crossroads
in my life."
You guys have to understand the person
who wrote this. This man...
Remember "man." My pop.
He's from the corn belt, okay?
Self-expression and communication,
it's not part of his wiring.
He can't even talk to me on the phone
without a conversational cue sheet.
"Hey, Wayne, how's your van doing?
Is the clutch still jamming?
"What's that band
you're working for, Wayne?
"No, I've never heard of them."
Everybody's heard of them.
Then I read this letter...
and I'm wondering if it's some bizarre
joke someone's playing on me.
But no, I know for a fact
that this is from my pop.
He's the only person I know
that would write a personal letter...
on his fucking business stationery.
And then listen:
"I don't know how to express this
other than in a letter.
"I'm having a surgery
next year to correct
a condition known as gender dysphoria.
"In other words,
I'm a woman born in a man's body.
"I'll be getting a sex change.
"I hope you understand...
"that I'd like to find
some peace and happiness in my life.
"I'm still your parent, no matter what.
"I will care deeply about you
until the end of my days.
"I love you. Dad."
What kind of shit is that?
Hi, guys.
There she goes.
Hey, Roy.
- Come on in.
- Thanks for seeing me, Frank.
- Sure, have a seat.
- Thank you.
I know word has gotten to you
about the perfume.
If I believed
half of what got said around here...
Don't give it another thought.
Well, the fact is, it's true.
And I apologize.
I meant to organize things better.
- I should have talked to you...
- I'm not sure I'm catching your drift.
Well, I have this condition.
I'm a female born in a man's body...
and I have to do something about it.
Which is why I'm starting
to take hormones in a couple of weeks...
and sometime next year,
I'm going to have the surgery.
Just so as you know, I'm going
to start dressing as a woman...
bit by bit, and I'll do it gradually...
so as not to disrupt the work here.
I know this is a lot to take in...
so I brought you this.
It's useful, I think.
It explains my condition...
and how to talk about it...
with the other workers...
and how to handle
when I change my name...
and restroom reassignments,
and so forth.
That's good.
Does Irma know about this?
Yeah.
What did she say?
She asked me to leave,
which I understand.
- She's got a lot to figure out.
- I can imagine.
I know you're going to have to decide
whether to keep me on.
I won't deny that you've put
an awful lot on my plate here.
I just want to say that
whatever you decide...
I understand.
Thank you, Roy.
Thanks for being so forthright with me.
Thank you for letting me get this out.
- Hi, Irma. How are you?
- Frank! Oh, my God.
- Come in.
- Thanks.
I guess Roy told you.
Yeah, he sure did.
Is he getting help, Irma?
We've been to counselling...
but nothing will change his mind.
You see, he's determined
to go through with this.
We both know Roy is not the type
to act on a whim.
No, he isn't.
Are you going to fire him?
Well, this is the thing.
Roy works with a pretty
meat-and-potatoes kind of crew.
I'd be happy to keep an eye on him.
The truth is, as soon as I turn my back,
they'll take him...
and beat the crap out of him.
I'm sorry, Irma,
I really don't know what else to do.
No, I understand.
How are you fixed for money?
The insurance won't
cover his treatment...
so it's going to take out a big bite.
I've started looking for work myself.
You know, who knows what Roy
is going to get once he...
switches permanently.
I hear you.
Here's what.
Roy is due for a promotion
in another year.
What if I just hurried him up the ladder
a little bit...
if I found a desk job for him?
You think?
You're a good man, Frank.
Tell that to my wife.
Oh, no, she didn't leave you again?
We were getting along just fine there
for a while.
She goes off her medication.
Not much I can do about that.
I'm sorry, you don't deserve that.
Well, that's the way it goes.
It didn't do it for me. You?
No.
Well, it was something to try.
Thanks for the coffee, Irma.
Thank you, Frank, for
standing behind Roy.
- He's the best we have.
- Yes, he is.
All right, you take
care of yourself now.
I'll take these, too.
Take those goddamn things off.
Mind your own goddamn business.
Give them to me.
Hey, what's going on?
Give me them. Give them to me.
Get him off!
Let go of him!
Christ! It's just a
shitty pair of earrings.
Freak.
You were asking for that.
- Just be glad he's not dancing.
- Move!
To hear the lark as he's taking flight
As he soars into the sky
If you listen close,
you can hear him now
And he soars across the valleys
And he lives in open plains
And he lives right
here inside your heart
As he lives in everything
And he lives right
here inside your heart
As he lives in everything
As he soars into the sky
If you listen close
You will hear him there
As he lives in everything
As he lives in open valleys
Stop. Guys, sit down.
Girls, I don't like what I'm hearing.
Please. Pay attention to the dynamics.
As he lives in open valleys
As he soars across the plains
And he lives right here
inside your heart
As he lives in
everything
I've brought your mail.
Thanks.
What happened to your forehead?
I wore some earrings to work.
That wasn't too smart.
Made me feel pretty.
Do you want an aspirin?
Yeah, I could use one.
- You want to get in the truck?
- No. I'm fine here.
There's a letter from your mother.
I'm out of the choir, by the way.
Sorry to hear that, Roy.
You would've made a fine soprano.
What does it say?
"Dear Roy, I got your letter today.
"As you know...
"your father has been
on a long, slow decline.
"He's had a hard life,
and I want him...
"to be able to spend the
time he has left in peace.
"So I've decided not to
show him your letter.
"By the way, we're having your father's
birthday celebration on Saturday.
"I'm serving supper at 3:00.
Tell Irma to bring her beans."
I forgot all about it.
Do you want to go?
It's probably the last time
you're going to see him.
Hello, folks!
Glad to see you two talking.
Listen, not to disturb you,
I just wanted to give you these.
I went online and found an
excellent site on gender issues.
It's Baptist-based, but the general
principles are still the same.
Here you go. I made
copies for each of you.
And I just want to say
again how sorry I am
about this whole
business with the choir.
Irma, as I told Roy, if
it was just up to me...
But...
I'm still in the ring with you two.
Roy, we need to make an appointment.
- We'll see.
- Well, good night, folks.
Here.
Irma, it's cold. You want
to get in the truck?
- Roy.
- Yeah?
I keep trying to figure out...
what I've done wrong.
You haven't done anything wrong.
Then don't do this.
Oh, honey.
I have been sharing a bed with you...
for 25 years.
I know your body.
I know your smell.
You're a man.
That's what you are.
Don't try telling me
that you're something else.
But I am.
No!
There you are.
Why won't you let me touch you?
Because it doesn't
feel like part of me.
I'm just trying to explain
what it's like for me.
I have to get home to Patty.
- We have to sit down and talk to her.
- Let's get through the weekend.
We'll see you on Saturday.
Clean up them plugs.
- You got a brand-new tractor.
- Needs a tune-up.
- Hey, Roy.
- Hey, Don.
- Hey, Irma.
- Hi, Don.
Hi, Aunt Becky.
- Hello, Gary. Hi, Mike.
- Hello.
- Here they are. How are you?
- Hi.
- Hi, sweetie.
- Here she is.
Come on in, honey.
Let me take those things.
There you go. Here, I'll take those.
Happy birthday to you
Happy birthday, dear Dad
Blow out the candles, Roy.
It's chocolate. I
didn't want chocolate.
That's what you asked for.
- No, I didn't.
- Honey, you did.
- I did not, godammit it!
- Yes, you did, Dad. I heard you say it.
What do you know about cakes?
Never seen you bake one before.
- Roy, leave Becky alone.
- She needs to leave me alone.
She can't wait till I die,
so she can have the farm.
My son hasn't got the spine
to fight her for it.
Dad, I don't want the farm.
Don't get me started on you.
I had to go through all these girls
to get you...
and you turn out to be a hopeless case,
moping around like a sissy.
I didn't mope around.
You didn't give me time to mope around.
That's right.
If I hadn't straightened you out,
you'd still be a big cry-baby.
Did I ever tell you about the time
I caught him in his sister's clothes?
I made him strip down
and spend the night in the barn, naked.
- Blow out the candles!
- Come on, make a wish for yourself.
Good Christ, is he crying?
Roy, the candles are about to melt
all over the cake.
Come over and help your grandpa
blow out the candles.
See, the cake looks delicious.
Did you make it yourself?
No, it's from a mix, but I added
an extra egg to make it moist.
I always add another egg.
Where's she going?
I'm thinking about switching over
to narrow-row corn.
Yeah, I think it's a good idea.
- Where the hell is he going?
- Leave him be.
Irma, do you want some cake?
No.
I think I'll wait a while.
I'm going to start on the dishes.
Patty Ann, why don't you
come in the kitchen and help me?
- Mom, it just looks fabulous.
- Thanks.
You both better be ready.
I'm ready to kill some fishes.
Got my name on them.
- You seen Roy?
- No, haven't seen him.
I haven't seen him, Irma.
Honey, just wait here, okay?
I'll see if I can find your dad.
Come here, sweetie.
Tell your uncle some lies.
You got more food in there for me?
- It's empty.
- Empty? Go get me some take-home.
Put the gun down, Roy.
Please.
I think for now you should come home.
Are you going to grow your hair out?
Yes.
- Will you be just as tall?
- Yes.
- Is your voice going to change?
- No.
So what will you do?
Will you speak higher?
I suppose so.
Do it.
How big are your boobs supposed to get?
Well, my doctor says
they're going to be...
one or two cups smaller
than my mother's, your grandma Em's.
My God! Her breasts are huge.
Are you going to shave your legs?
And under your arms?
- What about your bikini line?
- My bikini line?
So your pubes don't show
when you wear a swimsuit.
What about your beard?
Will that go away, too?
No, I've got to have that removed
with electrolysis.
- That's supposed to be really painful.
- That's what I hear.
- Does it scare you?
- No.
Does the operation scare you?
What about Wayne?
Does he know about this?
Well, I wrote him a letter.
- Did he write back?
- No, not yet.
You know, Patty, whatever
you're feeling...
I mean, if you're angry
at your father or at me...
it's completely understandable.
I'm not angry.
I think it's cool.
The kids at school might start saying
some real cruel things to you.
So? They do anyway.
- So does this let me off the hook?
- What do you mean?
Of having to be the girl of the family.
Patty, you are a girl.
See? She's always on my case about it.
I can't do it. I'm just not that type.
It sucks being a woman.
You'll spend the rest of
your life getting shafted.
You'll be out of the club.
Why do you want to give that all up?
It's easier being a man.
It isn't easier being a man.
Men die first.
That should give you a clue.
And you'll probably
start getting zits.
Oh, I see.
What should I do about it?
There's nothing you can do.
It's hopeless.
Sorry, Dad, but it's hopeless.
- Patty Ann, you want some eggs?
- No, they make me nauseous.
- Then have some cornflakes.
- I don't like the texture.
You're just too precious to live.
This cream is bad.
- It's fine.
- No, it isn't.
- I just got it yesterday.
- Smell it.
- It smells fine.
- It's sour.
- Did you check the date?
- Yes, Roy, I checked the date.
Mom, quit making that
noise with the toast.
- I want you to eat something.
- I'm not hungry.
You can't go to school
on an empty stomach.
- Patty, want some oatmeal?
- No.
- I'm making some.
- So?
- What are you doing?
- I'm making oatmeal.
- Let me do it. You'll burn the pot.
- I'm just boiling water.
Let me do it. It'll take a minute.
- Why are you being so snippy?
- I'm not being snippy.
Yes, you are.
I'm not. You're the one
that's being snippy.
- Can I get another ear piercing?
- You're pretty enough as it is.
I wasn't talking to you,
I was talking to Mom.
I was talking to you. You need to learn
some manners, young lady.
- You need to learn to leave me alone.
- All right, that's it. Get out. Go on.
Walk away. I'm making you oatmeal.
- I don't want any.
- That's too bad.
- What are you looking for?
- Grapefruit.
I thought you were having oatmeal.
I'm having a grapefruit with my oatmeal.
Is there anything wrong with that?
- Let me find it.
- Just tell me where it is.
Roy, if you'd please just sit down,
I'd have everything ready in...
Why don't I do the grapefruit?
And you can do the...
Don't get annoyed. I'm
just trying to help.
I don't want help.
It would be so much easier
if you just sat down and let me do it.
In the time we discussed this...
I could have made my breakfast
and gone to work already.
Here, Dad. Eat the freaking grapefruit.
That was pleasant.
Your oatmeal, Roy.
Irma, you still there?
Yes.
I'm going to come out now.
All right.
What do you think?
What can I say?
You look like my aunt Norma
after her stroke.
- Do I look that awful?
- Yeah.
Yes, honey, you do.
I've been going to thrift stores...
and grabbing whatever looks right
and hope it fits.
This dress is so musty,
it makes me itch.
Poor Roy.
I need your help to order
some decent stuff.
I folded down the page
with things I liked.
All right.
You gave yourself boobs.
What did you use, Kleenex?
Bubble wrap.
You got the shape all wrong.
So, what am I supposed
to be looking at here?
The blouse.
- Oh, no. It's not right for you.
- Why not?
Well, it's too ruffly. I mean, it
will accentuate your shoulders.
You need something more tailored
that'll slim you down.
I don't want to wear anything tailored.
I've been wearing tailored...
You know, you'll look top heavy.
You've got to work with what you've got.
We all do. You know...
I wish I had the legs
so I could wear short skirts, but...
- Your legs are beautiful.
- No, they're not.
- I love your legs.
- Don't.
Mom.
Wait a minute, Patty Ann.
Don't come in.
What are you doing?
Never mind.
- Is Daddy in drag?
- No.
- Can I see?
- No. Now, what do you want?
Tell me if I can wear
this shirt without a bra.
Patty Ann, you can't go without a bra.
You're too developed.
Nothing shows.
Where'd you get that?
- It's Dad's. He said I could have it.
- It's too big.
No, it's not. It's the look.
Well, go take it off, please.
And put your bra back on.
I hate wearing a bra.
- It makes marks on my skin.
- Then go live in a jungle, honey.
Why did you give her your shirt?
I thought she could use it.
I don't think it's appropriate.
She's boyish enough as it is.
- What if she is?
- Roy, she's going to get hurt.
The kids will tear her apart.
For now, please,
just don't encourage it, okay?
- Just let her try to blend in.
- All right.
So what else did you want me to look at?
- Never mind. I know what I'm getting.
- What?
I think you should run it by me first.
We're on a budget.
I'm very aware we're on a budget.
Yeah, well, I don't think you should...
go order a bunch of things
that don't look good on you.
Thank you, but I don't need you to
tell me what I can and can't wear.
Oh, yes, I think you do.
You don't have a clue.
I'm not in love with
everything I've seen you in.
I try not to say anything.
Excuse me, you come out here
with that horrible wig and make-up...
looking like some aging hooker...
I've been sneaking to thrift shops,
for God's sake.
What should I look like?
Like I came from a garden club?
Look, Roy...
you give me a catalogue,
you ask for my opinion...
and then get angry
when I give it to you.
You weren't just giving an opinion.
- You were setting down rules.
- Stop.
I don't appreciate these mean,
nasty comments you're making.
Just stop.
I had a reaction. I'm human.
What do you want from me?
I just want some respect.
I have given you my youth.
I have given you your children.
I have given you my full
and undivided attention...
for 25 years.
And now, I'm giving up everything...
that I believe in...
so you can feel complete.
So tell me...
what more could you
possibly want from me?
Is that how it feels?
Yes.
How awful.
No, it's not awful, Roy.
It's what it is.
And if I look at it hard enough...
you've done the same for me.
So now...
give me the catalogues, because I'm
going to pick out your clothes.
In jubilation
Sing to the Lord
Come rejoice
Sing hallelujah
Come add your voice
and sing hallelujah
Praise his name
Sing for the Lord
Sing hallelujah
For He lights the way
Rejoice today
Let your heart sing his love
Come rejoice
Sing hallelujah
Come add your voice
and sing hallelujah
Praise His name
Sing for the Lord
Sing hallelujah
For He lights the way
Rejoice today
Let your heart sing his love
Come rejoice
Sing hallelujah
Come add your voice
and sing hallelujah
We're having problems with Roy.
You have to talk to him, Irma.
- Why? What's going on?
- He's getting bitchy.
It's the hormones.
I understand that, but
that's still no excuse.
No, of course not.
The thing about Roy is,
he was always such an easy-going guy...
I mean, now he's just so super-sensitive
about everything.
Yeah, I'll talk to him.
Janeane's the same way.
She's always backing me into corners.
I say something, she twists it
and turns it into something else.
What am I supposed to do about that?
- Just walk away.
- But then she says I'm ignoring her.
My mom's the same way. So is my sister.
Seems like every woman I know is nuts.
And then I get to know
you a little better...
and I see there's hope.
I know that Roy and I have a great
deal of respect for each other.
And I figure that once he goes
through his change, he'll be...
moving on to other pastures, I suppose.
Just want to put the idea out there.
Thanks for dropping by.
No, I will have that talk with Roy.
- I'd appreciate that.
- Okay.
- Thanks for the coffee.
- You bet, anytime.
Frank came by today.
He's concerned about
your attitude at work.
He says you've gotten bitchy.
- He used that word?
- Yes, he did.
That's just Frank.
He thinks that all the women in
the office are out to get him.
Don't push it with him, Roy.
You're lucky you still have a job.
Do you hear me?
What are you doing?
Well, there they are.
I had no idea they were so sensitive.
Now you know.
And it's not just
there, it's everywhere.
I feel like whole...
armies of nerve endings
are budding up all over my skin.
Did I ever kiss you
in the crook of your elbow?
I don't believe so.
I think...
I finally realized what it would take...
to be a proper lover to you.
I'm glad to hear that, Roy.
But it might have been easier for both
of us if you had just read a book.
- Can I ask you something?
- Yeah.
Are you going to want to be with men?
No, honey. You know I don't.
Then, if you're not
planning on having intercourse...
what do you need a vagina for?
- That's a ridiculous question.
- No, it isn't.
I mean, I had babies with mine.
I used it to make love to you.
What on earth
are you going to do with yours?
It's not a matter of
what I'm going to do with it.
I'm doing this to make myself complete.
It's a sexual organ, honey.
That's what it's made for.
And as a long-time female,
let me tell you...
I haven't used mine for anything
but to take in a penis, okay?
There are certainly other things
you can do with it.
Like what?
You ever masturbated?
- Well, haven't you?
- Good grief, Roy.
What?
If you need to have an
affair, I understand.
Don't be ridiculous, Roy.
I wouldn't mind.
Really, Irma, I wouldn't mind.
Hello, Frank.
I just want you to know that I have
nothing but the greatest
respect for you.
Thank you.
I respect you, too.
That means a lot to me.
Okay, then.
- That's something.
- Yeah.
Right.
I like the feel of your hand.
- Roy's are going so soft.
- Yeah, I noticed that.
He used to have such strong hands.
That was one of the things
I first loved about him.
I liked the feel of his calluses
when we held hands.
Janeane makes me buff mine down.
She prefers a smoother hand.
I like a man to have a few rough edges.
Well, that's me.
For a fair-haired guy,
my stubble grows in pretty thick.
Yeah, feel.
- Roy can grow a pretty good beard.
- Really?
He grew one, one winter.
But then he shaved it off.
Have you figured out
what your new name is going to be yet?
It's going to be Ruth.
Like the Ruth in the Bible,
that followed Naomi.
- That's a boring name.
- Not at all.
Ruth is pure love.
Will Mom have to call you Ruth?
Once she gets comfortable with it.
Where did she go tonight?
To the movies, with a friend.
Why was she so dressed up?
I'm sure she just wanted
to make sure she looked nice.
- What movie was she going to see?
- I don't know. I didn't ask.
- Why not?
- I just didn't.
Now leave it alone.
I bought you a toothbrush just in
case you wanted to spend the night.
Thanks.
You should know...
that in my last check-up,
I had my blood gone over...
- and I'm clean as a whistle.
- Thanks for telling me.
And I brought my own protection.
Janeane can't have kids.
But when we were trying,
I had my sperm count tested.
It's pretty high.
But if you brought something,
that's fine with me.
I'm going through menopause, Frank.
That's okay.
One less thing to worry about.
Would you like me to undress you?
Not just yet.
Would you like to undress me?
I mean, it might help us
get into the mood a little more.
Yeah, okay.
Just got back to exercising.
I'll be a lot more fit in a
couple of months, I'm sure.
You look fine. I'm not much to look at.
Yes, you are, Irma.
You're a great-looking gal.
You think maybe
that we could turn the lights out first?
Sure.
Were you able to sleep at all, Roy?
I didn't really expect to.
I want you to be happy, Irma.
So do I, honey.
This is a cute look. What do you think?
- What, for you?
- No, for you.
I can't wear pants like that.
They make my butt look big.
- Stop, you got nothing there.
- Yes, I do.
- Honey, can I help you?
- No.
Mom, I'm getting my hair dyed black.
- No, you're not.
- Why not?
- You'll look like a drug addict.
- You could get a streak.
She's not dyeing her hair anything.
- You colour your hair.
- To cover the gray.
Your hair is fine,
you don't need to do anything.
Ruth says she wants to be a redhead.
Patty Ann, you do not call us
by our first names ever.
- Why not?
- Because it's disrespectful.
- Dad, you don't mind, do you?
- Your mother's right, Patty.
Fine.
- Mom.
- What?
Dad and I have the same breast size now.
Patty Ann, would you excuse us
for a minute?
Roy, do you think I could talk to you?
- Am I in trouble?
- No, honey.
Were you showing her your breasts?
She saw them
while I was shaving under my arms.
They're just breasts, Irma.
She's seen yours, she's seen her own.
I won't cover up
something perfectly natural.
"Natural" is not a word
I would use in your case.
- What kind of dig is that?
- It wasn't a dig.
It was a fact.
Excuse me, I'm not the only one
taking hormones in this house.
You bastard!
You have no idea what I'm going through!
If I've been insensitive...
Insensitive doesn't even
begin to describe it, it's grotesque!
- I'm sorry, what more can I say?
- I don't want an apology!
- I want my husband back!
- You can't have him back!
Why are you doing this to us?
I'm still here, Irma.
No, God.
It's me.
Look at me. It's me, I'm still here.
Here we go.
We sure do miss you at church, Irma.
Well, I miss church, too.
Everyone's been asking after you.
The tremendous sympathy people are
feeling for you and Patty Ann.
Everyone keeps coming up to me, saying,
"Can I bring them over a pie?
"Is there anything around the house
that needs fixing?"
Well, I am not a widow, Pastor.
Of course not. It's just...
that you're one of our most...
cherished members.
Everyone keeps talking about
all the great things...
you've done for us over the years.
Thank you,
but Roy has put in a lot more time.
You should be paying him a call
instead of me.
Irma, I know in my effort
to turn over every stone...
I had suggested
that you might have had a hand in this.
- Yes, you did.
- I took a wrong turn.
Forgive me.
Let me assure you, you did not cause...
or enable this problem
of Roy's in any way.
- This is not your fault.
- I know it isn't.
Now I am going to tell
you one more thing.
As your pastor...
and as your friend...
I give you permission
to separate your life from his...
without guilt or regret.
I give you permission to walk away.
To walk away?
Yes.
But he's my heart.
My heart.
It's a beautiful morning
in De Kalb County.
Clear skies, highs in the mid 30s.
Balmy enough to leave your parkas
in the closet during the day.
But plan to bundle up tonight.
We have a cold front coming in
that'll take us down to the teens.
A storm is expected
on Monday, but should
let up in time for
the holiday weekend.
And speaking of the holiday weekend...
it's not too late to order your turkeys.
They have been raising high-quality
corn-fed turkeys...
Patty Ann! Honey, come on.
I can't be late.
- Bye.
- I love you.
You've reached
the home of the Applewoods.
We can't come to the phone right now,
so please leave a message. Bye.
Hi, this is Wayne.
Mom, I got your letter
about coming down for Thanksgiving.
I am really...
busy right now.
But maybe I can come down
for a couple of days.
Maybe one day.
You know what? I'll be there for dinner.
I'll have to see.
Okay, I'll see you then.
All right, bye-bye.
Shit.
I think it's done.
Wayne's here!
Hey, kiddo.
You grew a beard. It's cool.
- Hey, Mom.
- Hello, Wayne.
Mom, look. Wayne has a beard!
I see. Patty Ann, get off his back.
We were worried about you.
Did you run into traffic?
There was a storm on 7th,
so I took a different route.
Honey, I am so glad to see you.
- You feel skinny. Did you lose weight?
- No.
Here, I brought you these.
They are so beautiful. Thank you.
Don't you want to bring your bags in?
No, we can get them later.
Well, if you have any laundry
that you want me to do...
you just bring it in, okay?
Come on in, you must be so hungry.
This is so beautiful.
Wayne, I can make a muscle.
Yeah. I see.
You know what, honey? I like your beard.
- Yeah?
- Yes, I do.
- I got tired of shaving.
- Of course.
The turkey is all set...
so you showed up just
in the nick of time.
- Want something to drink?
- Do you have beer?
- I got it.
- Okay.
Wayne, I got my ear pierced again.
Yeah. You look like a pin cushion.
Who's ahead?
- Chicago.
- All right.
How is work, honey?
The band is on a break right now.
They'll start again in January.
They want me to work their sound.
Really? That's a big step, isn't it?
- What kind of glass do you want?
- The can's fine.
Does that mean that
they will pay you more?
I should be making pretty good money.
This is turning into a
real career, isn't it?
- Do you do a lot of stuff backstage?
- What do you mean?
- You know...
- No.
So, honey, does that mean that you
are going to have to travel a lot?
Yeah. We might go to Europe next year.
- Europe? Isn't that wonderful?
- Can I go with you in the summer?
- I'll work in the crew.
- No.
Wayne, did you know
I'm working at your old high school now?
Yeah? Great.
The secretary retired,
so I've taken on her job.
- Who cuts your hair?
- Will you stop interrupting?
- I wasn't. I thought you were done.
- I wasn't.
Can you finish the
relish tray, please?
Where's Dad?
Well, he's still getting dressed.
You know, Wayne,
I'd love, if you have a moment...
if you could look at the basement,
because...
we seem to have a leak.
- Sure. You want me to do it now?
- No.
I want you to sit and just relax
for a little while, okay?
I don't mind.
Do it after supper,
there's a lot of time.
Hey, Pop.
- How was your trip?
- It was good.
Is the van running all right?
I heard a knock in the engine...
when you pulled up to the house.
Want me to take a look at it?
Yeah, great.
So, you grew a beard?
- Got tired of shaving.
- So did I.
- You want to sit down?
- Yeah.
- What are you having?
- A beer.
I think I'll join you.
Irma, can I have a beer?
All right.
- How's work?
- Work is going good.
Good.
Thank you.
Who's ahead?
- Chicago.
- All right.
Could you turn the sound up on the TV?
We're ready to eat now.
- We just want to hear the game.
- Well...
Patty Ann, would you get
the olives, please?
You know, Wayne, I think that I am going
to have you carve the turkey this year.
- I've never done it before, Mom.
- I'll do it, Irma.
No, I want Wayne to do it.
It's easy, sweetheart.
We have an electric knife.
- Wayne, can you open this?
- Yeah, sure.
- Give it to me.
- I got it.
Come on.
- Just run it under hot water.
- I got it.
Here you go.
- Dad, look at your hand, gross.
- What happened?
A little bit of skin,
that's all, scraped skin.
Honey, you hurt yourself.
No, it's all right. It's okay.
Quit it, all right?
Don't worry.
Dad's hormones are making him soft.
Mom, do you want me to do anything?
No, we're all set.
If you want, you can open that bottle
of wine that's on the dining room table.
And, Patty Ann...
honey, we are ready
to take out the side dishes.
And don't forget to use the trivets.
- Want some help?
- No, I have it.
- Wayne looks good.
- Yes, he does.
I like the beard.
- Are you mad at me?
- We don't have to talk about it now.
- Yes, we do.
- No.
What did I do?
- Roy, you know what you did.
- No, I don't. Tell me.
"Irma, can you get me a beer?"
"Turn up the TV."
What kind of macho crap was that?
I can't relax with my
son and have a beer?
Come on, Roy. You
were putting it on.
- You don't have to show off for him.
- I was not.
What was that crap about carving
the turkey? It was uncalled for...
I just wanted to give
him something to do.
No, you weren't.
You were making him
the head of the table.
No.
- I can't help you in my own kitchen.
- Why don't you toss the salad?
- You're making me an outcast.
- Mom, the cork broke.
- Shoot.
- Sorry.
That's no problem. We can fix that.
- We need an awl.
- An awl?
Got one in my workbench.
We're in the basement.
Right. Okay.
You need some power tools?
I'm giving my extra ones away.
- No, I'm good.
- Look around. Take anything you need.
You know, I think I'll go up and see
if there's anything else Mom needs.
Wayne, I know...
this is hard for you.
But I really appreciate you coming.
It means a lot to me.
- Sure, well...
- So is there anything you want...
to talk to me about?
Anything you want to ask?
No. Not right now.
We never have had much to say
to each other, have we?
No, I guess we never really have.
No. I couldn't talk
to my father, either.
I don't know anyone who really
gets along with their dad.
You know, it shouldn't
have to be that way.
No, it shouldn't.
- We're ready to eat.
- Yeah, we're just coming.
I'm fixing the cork.
She still calls you Roy?
Yeah, until the surgery.
Did Mom decide...
Are you and she
going to keep living together?
Yeah.
So does that mean that...
Do you still sleep in the same bed?
Sexually, you're still into women,
you're into Mom?
Correct.
So as a man you're straight,
but as a woman you're gay?
Your mother happens to be the person
I fell in love with.
- Doesn't that make Mom a lesbian?
- Not necessarily.
Come on, Pop.
Honey, your mother's sexuality
hasn't changed.
We're staying together
because we love each other.
In other words...
if the two of you ever split up,
she'd go back to men.
Probably.
- So she's straight.
- Yes, Wayne.
But she'll sleep with you
when you become a woman.
- Maybe. Maybe not.
- No, if she did...
Women with women. I can understand that.
If I was a chick,
I wouldn't want to be with a guy.
I'd much rather be with chicks.
I love chicks.
- Maybe I'm a lesbian, too.
- That's enough, Wayne.
- What?
- You're being sarcastic.
I'm just trying to figure all this out.
I'm glad you are.
Calling me sarcastic?
I'm too fucking confused
to be sarcastic.
Let's not fight.
You know what? Let's just not talk.
I'm sorry.
Honey, I think you've
carved enough turkey.
It's time to start thinking about
finding those...
special gifts for family and friends.
Well, I think we could make...
a nice soup out of this tomorrow.
Yeah, good idea.
Ma, what do you want me to do
with my laundry?
Just leave it on the landing.
Honey, can you come in here a minute?
Please?
I just wanted you
to go through your Dad's clothes...
before I gave them all away.
- You need a tie?
- I don't wear ties.
Yeah, but you never know.
You might need one for a wedding...
or if you go to a nice restaurant.
Look, this one feels like you.
I think I gave him this one for his birthday, or Father's Day...
or one of those Dad events.
- Can you use an electric razor?
- No.
Here's a brand-new
package of undershirts.
No, thanks.
Look...
this is a lovely jacket.
It's way too nice.
I don't wear that kind of thing.
It's very sporty, too.
You could wear it with a pair of jeans.
Here, come on. Just try it.
Slip it on once.
It should fit.
Well, no, it's too big in the shoulder.
But you could always have it altered.
Lift that there...
and lengthen the sleeves a little bit.
What are you doing?
It still has some of his aftershave
on the collar.
- But it'll come out...
- I don't want it.
I don't want any of his stuff.
Jesus Christ!
Look, Wayne, I'm sorry.
I know this is hard on you.
Forget about me. What about you?
Aren't you revolted? Aren't you pissed?
- No, not anymore.
- Come on, Ma, there must...
Jesus! Do you actually like him
as a woman?
I like having him alive.
- And I like having him with me.
- What do you get out of him?
I get his love, Wayne.
- Is Wayne taking any of Daddy's stuff?
- No.
- Can I have this jacket?
- No, honey.
- Put it down.
- Why?
Just leave it alone!
Wayne, did you find anything
you could use?
My taste is probably a
little square for you.
But this is a sharp jacket.
- Did you try it on?
- Yeah. It doesn't really fit.
Just give it to me, Roy.
- I'll take it to the church.
- I can use the jacket.
No, honey.
Wayne, I'm going to give you my watch.
I had the jeweller clean it.
Put in a new battery.
It should work perfect.
Explain to me why I
can't have the jacket!
Cool it!
- What's this about?
- What do you mean?
What am I supposed to
do with your watch?
Wear it with pride,
and pass it on to the next generation?
"Here, son, this is your granddad's.
"He gave it to me
when he switched to a Lady Timex."
Fuck your watch, your watch is bogus.
I don't want it near my fucking wrist.
Don't use that language
with your father.
Are you actually
trying to defend him?
This freak who kept you going for what,
25, 26 years?
Shared your bed. Got you pregnant.
Don't you feel scammed?
- You're way out of line.
- No, you are.
We can't even have Thanksgiving
with Gran and Grandpa because of you.
- Get out now!
- You half-baked cunt.
You can't tell me what to do.
Don't you ever use that word again.
Cunt.
Stop it!
God!
Wayne, you all right?
- You okay?
- Get off me. Come on.
I'm okay, Ma.
I didn't mean that.
Irma, will you go get some ice?
Patty, go with your mom. Come on.
- Just let me see.
- I'm fine.
Wayne, please let me help you.
- Okay, can you feel anything?
- It's numb.
It's swelling, but I
don't think it's...
I don't think it's broken. Here.
Come on. Sit down with me.
Come on, sit down.
I wouldn't hurt you for the world.
Wayne, my precious boy.
It's all right.
Hello, Mother.
Hello, Dad.
Who are you?
I'm your daughter Ruth.
I had some other daughters
visit me yesterday.
That woman over there,
she can tell you their names.
Margie and Beth drove up from Toledo.
Did you have a nice visit with them?
They brought a pie.
I didn't like it, it was too sweet.
It was a cake. He ate three pieces.
- What's your name? Ruth?
- Yes.
- So I have four daughters?
- Five.
I thought I had a son.
Ask that woman back
there if I have a son.
No, you don't.
Who am I going to leave
the farm to, then?
You're leaving it to Becky.
- Who's Becky? The nurse?
- She's your oldest daughter.
- I can't leave the farm to her.
- Well, you are.
- Where is she?
- She's out fixing the barn.
I better get out there,
or I'll get my butt whipped.
Who by? Becky?
No, my daddy.
We're putting in lima beans.
- I hate lima beans. Don't you?
- I can't stand them.
I told that woman over there
I'm not going to eat them.
That woman over there is your wife.
She's been married
to you for 50 years.
I don't care.
You tell her I'm not going to eat
any more lima beans.
Her name is Em.
She's borne your children and cooked
your food and stood behind you...
in everything you did, no matter how
misguided or stupid or cruel.
She's old and she's tired.
And she still bathes
you and feeds you...
and changes your soiled pants.
The least you can do
is call her by her name.
I don't want her.
I want my mama.
- She's not here.
- Why?
Daddy...
you're an old man.
Your mother's not alive anymore.
Roy, you ready for your sandwich?
I can't eat now.
I wet my pants.
I want my mama.
I'll change you.
- I want my mama.
- You want help, honey?
No, I can handle it.
You get some rest, Mother.
Get some rest.
This is the penis.
And this represents the skin
around the penis.
And these are the testicles.
First, you take out the testes...
leaving the scrotal sac.
Then you take out the
inside of the penis...
and pull it inside out,
making what was once an outie an innie.
Then you take the scrotal sac, and you
cut it in half to make the labia.
Like this.
And voil! You have a vagina.
Thank you.
You've reached
the home of the Applewoods.
Neither Irma, Ruth, or Patty Ann
can come to the phone right now.
Please leave a message.
Hi, Mom, Dad.
I wanted to wish you guys
a happy anniversary.
Is it today? I think it's today.
Anyway, happy whatever.
I just wanted to call to wish Pop
good luck with his surgery tomorrow.
Let me know how it goes.
Hey, Patty Ann.
I love you guys. Take care.
This is Wayne.
Bye.
What do you think?
You're so pretty.
Here.
- Happy anniversary.
- Thank you.
They're so beautiful.
- What do you think?
- They look lovely.
I'd like to look at you one last time.
What?
Thank you.
Sweet Roy.
Sweet soul.
What we do for love.