"Shadows of Love"
Paris...
Will you really come back?
If it goes on like this,
I'm afraid I won't stay faithful to you
This is a breaking news report:
An avalanche
hit eastern Korea this morning
The number of casualties is still unknown
This is Korea's worst avalanche in 30 years
Since the ski resort Dragon Gate is nearby,
tourists might be buried in the snow
A rescue operation is underway
Mr Kwon, any news about Paris?
We're all so worried!
I called her many times
but no one's answered yet
I'm Kwon Jung-hoon
Today is the worst day of my life
Come back as soon as possible
The office is a mess
Everyone's discussing the avalanche
I can't
I booked her the hotel hit by the avalanche
Don't tell me...
What should we do?
Book me a flight to Daegu.
I must find her
What? The road is snow-blocked
I heard it's 8m deep
Go book me the flight right away
Sure, I'll book you the flight right now
I'm already on my way to the airport
Tell me right now
Do you support Dong or me?
Why must I choose?
I just don't want the company to split up
Come with me to Korea, or we break up
Be more mature! Don't be so stubborn
Listen up! It's either Dong or me!
Either him or me!
That's not good for the company
OK then. You stay here
I'm off to Korea to pitch other shareholders
Don't come with me
Regarding my trip to Korea,
I dare to you tell Dong!
Paris... Let go!
Paris...
Hello Beautiful! Qin Xin
You brought me flowers again! Please sit
Oh, and you bought so many things
Are you on leave today?
This is Granny
She and Grandpa had a legendary romance
Granny is very fond of me
She says I'm very like her
Come
It's clean
Have some tea
What program are you watching?
Japanese drama
That's a hit!
It's fabulous. I watch it every day
Paris
What's with you? Aren't you in Korea?
Why didn't you answer my calls?
You got the wrong person, sir
What's the matter with him?
Is he a looney?
But he's quite cute for a looney
I don't mind you playing with me
You know there's an avalanche in Korea today?
I was worried you had an accident!
I don't even know you. Why should I care?
The probability of 2 people looking identical
is 49 out of 1 million
Who said that?
Ridiculous!
Sorry, you look exactly like my friend
I'm so eager to find her I mistook you for her
This is my name card
I'm lucky I resemble someone you're tracking
If I resembled someone you want to beat up,
I could be doomed!
Hello
What should we do, Mr Kwon?
Mr Dong is looking for Paris
You haven't boarded yet?
Ask Derek to greet him
as if nothing happened
I'm off to Korea now
Don't go. The company needs you
Or Mr Dong will do whatever he pleases
OK, I'll come back right away
I like east meets west
This is Dong
An old fox
Since he founded KNC with Paris's father,
he's been plotting to buy it out
with foreign capital
so he can become the major shareholder
Only Paris can overpower him
Mr Kwon, any news about Paris yet?
Mr Kwon Mr Kwon
Excuse me
He's a pain in the ass, you take care of him
How's Paris?
The Korean HQ has deferred the board meeting
I wasn't told
Many matters in the office are being deferred
How can the takeover be deferred?
I heard you proposed the deferment
I better discuss this with Paris in person
She's in the US. Not sure when she'll be back
Takeover and restructuring are big issues
It's good to think it out a bit more
Think it out? Do you have second thoughts?
Don't be silly
You're so competent. I'm always your fan
Let's wait for Paris's return
for further discussion
After restructuring,
KNC will be quite different
Let me remind you, don't ever...
join the wrong team
If Paris still doesn't show up,
according to the bylaws, the Board
shall be chaired by me
Anyhow,
let's decide at the end of the month
OK!
Only you and I are familiar with Korea here
Do me a favor
If you have any news,
contact me immediately
You better take off immediately
Yes, Mr Kwon. I got it
So pretty! How are you today?
Happy? Wait...
Let me take a close-up first
I'm Qin Xin. I help my cousin sell flowers
This is my other cousin
He's inherited the "Romantic DNA"
in the family
Basically, his IQ is zero
Only when his girlfriend needed chemo
for her cancer
did he know it's hard to earn money
for the wedding
Top 50
Any discount?
Look at this one
It came in yesterday. Only $7,888
Yes, discount for you
My cousin is also a sentimental soul
After her husband died in a car accident,
she decided never to marry again
Hurry UP!
What time is it? Still moving one pot at a time
Deliver the flowers before they've wilted!
You're not in top form today
Sorry, no pictures
So pretty! How are you today?
Guess what I heard, Sis?
This cousin is even more moonstruck
His IQ is less than zero
His girlfriend often maxes out his credit card
I'll buy you
a limited edition bag next month
He once gave his girlfriend a pot of flowers
She thought
there's a wedding ring inside
They almost broke up
On my way here,
I heard a Korean company
would develop our area
We've hit a jackpot!
Is it KNC?
I got a letter early in the morning today
YEAH !
Why are you so happy?
If I'm really lucky,
Julian could become an international florist,
with branches in Hong Kong,
Beijing, Seoul...!
And I...
...have inherited Granny's DNA,
namely a hunch for bad things,
especially about people I love
No...
You think you can act willfully
because you're rich?
I've been living here for more than ten years
What are you building?
A science research center?
I won't leave even
if you're building a nuclear plant
Even if I die, I must die here
You can't do anything about me!
Money isn't everything!
When I saw the way Xin looked,
I knew it's over
Sorry!
It's not your fault
It's just me being unlucky
Mr Kwon, Mr Ke is getting much worse
He's worried about KNC and his daughter
If you find Miss Ke,
please ask her to see him immediately
We've done all we could medically
If Paris still doesn't show up,
according to the bylaws,
the Board shall be chaired by me
"Julian Florist"
Let's have breakfast!
Why are you so skinny? Eat more
It's my turn
Good morning
Welcome
Are you kidding?
He came to the florist for me?
Feel free to browse around
It's the looney!
You think I want another lecture?
For the sake of KNC and Paris,
I'll be the looney!
Let me
Who are you looking for?
Excuse me, can I talk to her?
You can talk to me
Call the police
Please don't
Hear me out...
A friend of mine is a spitting image of her
I'm Kwun Jong-hoon of KNC. My name card
I have her pictures in my phone
Look
Look I'm far-sighted
I'm short-sighted
I'm astigmatic
Let me see
Her father is dying in sick bed
Maybe I shouldn't go. Let's go back
Take this as an audition
If your disguise is discovered in the company,
you won't need to see your dad in the hospital
Paris' dad
My dad is very healthy!
Welcome back!
Thank you!
Lovely!
The heels are so high. I must hang in there
I cannot sprain my ankle in front of them
What do you think?
I was thinking about my acting just now
Very good!
Give me five!
Yeah!
Yes!
Thanks. We'll visit your dad later...
Paris' dad!
Oh yes!
Can you play Paris for one more week?
Why?
To stabilize the morale in the company
so I have time to find Paris
Forget it! It's already too nerve-racking
I can't handle it. Let's forget it
I'm serious. Just give me your terms
OK, I have one condition
But no bargaining
No matter what buildings KNC will erect,
you must spare our florist
OK, I promise!
Daddy, I'm OK
Don't worry about me
You'll be fine also
Brother!
Mr Dong
Paris?
Paris...
Uncle Dong is here Hello!
Oh my God! I miss you so much!
Paris was ill in the States
She hasn't completely recovered
She'll pay you a visit in a couple of days
Let me see him
He's still not feeling well
If anything bad happens,
KNC will be seriously affected, right?
Paris, what's the matter?
Paris...
Nurse How is she?
What's the matter?
Mr Dong, please go back first
Is she all right?
I'll take care of her. Thanks!
Paris...
Please wait here. I'll fetch the doctor
Paris!
Yeah!
Daddy, you'll be OK...
Fortunately, your dad is OK
Paris' dad!
Yes, you're right
Hurry!
Baby, not that I don't want to buy it for you,
but my credit card is maxed out this month
Next month
I'll buy
a limited edition bag for you
What frigging bag is it?
How can you cling to such a bimbo?
You crazy?
You don't get it.
When a man loves a woman,
even if she wants you to buy her 100 bags,
you won't think she wants too much;
you'll only blame yourself for being useless
No wonder I won't have a man in my life
I'd rather stay a woman
in my next life
I'll bring you there
You can help me
I got nothing you want?
Let's work hard together!
You know why I do that? Why?
I want the Woman I love
to keep telling me
"I want!"
Whatever
I'm really worried about her
She's simply too nice to people
That's true
I'm taking off!
Let me help you I'll help you
Come
You're really following him
against my advice?
There're all sorts of people in the world
I tell you,
CEOs are not that uncommon!
He gave you his name card and you follow him?
Don't worry
Just let me help her father
Her father is quite miserable
I'll tell you a secret
Whoever lies to me shall come to misfortune!
OK, bye
Bye See you
Bye!
Write me a letter no matter what,
or how would I know
you can save our florist?
To be honest, I think...
Paris is worth much more than a florist
She finally spoke. Good! Very direct
I understand
Besides the florist,
I'll give you $1 million in cash
No bargaining
I'll take you to buy some clothes
You better not take your suitcase
into the house
I'll fetch it for you later
All right?
Just a random comment is worth $1 million?
I won't earn as much
if I sold flowers for ten years!
Mr Kwon
Hello, Uncle Zhou
No suitcase, Uncle Zhou
Uncle Zhou has seen Paris grow up
Hello, Uncle Zhou!
Miss, you're back?
Be indifferent
It's my home. Where else would I go?
Mr Kwon says if you can fool Uncle Zhou,
you're halfway there
So Uncle Zhou is worth half a million.
So where's your luggage?
We left the luggage at KNC
before coming here
This way, please!
You're such a liar
You need to be slicker
Or you won't be able to fool the butler
I'll succeed under the tutelage of King of Lies
What a huge mansion!
Can you give me a map?
I'm afraid I might lose my way
Miss, afternoon tea is ready
Uncle Zhou...
Mr Kwon, an invitation card
When was it delivered?
This morning
Hello, Mr Dong
Jong-hoon, is Paris all right?
She's much better. Thank you
It's great she's OK
She agreed to host
the Charity Ball next week
I got the invite, but Paris
might not be well enough to attend
She didn't come to see me,
Meaning she agrees to the takeover
She only needs to show up at the ball
and everyone at KNC will be happy
Besides, we all know Paris loves to dance
She must come!
I understand. I'll tell her
Why should there be a ball?
Paris, come here
Now you know how shrewd Dong is?
He's been suspicious all along
If he's as shrewd as you say,
shouldn't I skip
the ball altogether?
No way
You promised to play Paris
You must show up wherever she does
Dong has seen Paris grow up
He must be thinking of
testing and exposing you at the ball
So what should we do?
I don't know Paris' history?
Can you dance?
Come on!
Come on...
I barely learned how to wear high heels,
and now I have to dance?
Sit down, Uncle Zhou
Pardon?
Sit down
I sit down?
Sit down please
Paris, come here
Uncle Zhou,
Paris is going to publish a memoir
She must've had so many childhood anecdotes
Why don't you refresh her memory?
Yes, tell us as much as you can...
Tell us as much as you can remember
All right!
I'm not as old as I look.
I'm only approaching 70
My memory is still great
When should I start?
Start from the very beginning?
Her eyes were big and round at birth
Her eyeballs rolled around. So smart!
As if she was already several months old
She got off the bed
and checked out of the hospital.
How amazing!
This is Johnny.
I asked him to fly over to help out
Who knows he did fly over here!
This is Xu Yuan
She and Johnny met for the first time like this
I only found out later
Where's Ke's Mansion on Golden Peak Road?
I know
Take the road behind me
all the way till the end
Thanks
May I have your name?
Johnny said he had set a record
He could find out the name
and phone number
of any new girl he met within 5 sentences
How about this time?
Just call me Goddess
Nice to meet you, Goddess
You had a French boyfriend
when you studied in the UK
Didn't you say I studied in the US? Now the UK?
So did I study in the US
or the UK?
Right, it's different
That's not bad already
He has Alzheimer's!
I'm almost 80,
but I still have a good memory
What else?
We need to change the lighting.
Please take a break
Janet, inform Mr Kwon and other managers
to attend a meeting at the office at 3 pm
Put all the documents in the car
I'll read them in the car. Go!
She's not only a princess
but obviously a queen!
Memorize Paris' activities in recent years
Paris!
Quick, hide it! Don't let anybody know
Go!
Paris!
It's your cousin Xu Yuan! Paris
Hi Hi! Take a seat
Paris, I heard that you're back
So I rushed here to see you
You miss her?
Paris!
What's the matter?
Nothing?
She cannot be Paris
Paris never not wears perfume
My God!
I can help you
as I know everything about Paris
But I'll be very strict,
as you don't look like her at all right now
Mr Kwon, there's someone for you
Shit, who's that?
You're Paris
Paris, you are Paris, okay?
There he is
"'8 you!
Hi! You're way too late!
I met a goddess
who showed me the wrong way
Come
Paris, he's here to teach you dancing
How are you? I'm Johnny
Hi
She cannot be Paris!
You just came from abroad. How do you know?
Come on!
Paris is a great dancer.
She doesn't need lesson
You better do some homework!
OK, listen up
Everyone here must keep this secret for me
OK?
It hasn't been so lively here for a while!
Uncle Zhou...
Uncle Zhou, OK?
OK!
Sorry
One more spin
Two steps back. One, two
Left or right?
Right
Remember it
No, you're way too off
Paris could dance better than you at 8
OK, you tell that Mr Dong
I sprained my ankle and can't dance
No, if I say that...
Dong will pretend to be concerned
and ask the best specialist
to check on you
You know what? Paris' forte
is her unwavering determination
to do whatever she wants to do
In fact, I quite pity Paris
So what if you own everything?
Since the first day I played her,
I've never felt she's happy
Paris and I share the same forte
Are you ill?
I'm sure you can dance as well as Paris
You just let her steal your limelight
Who says so?
I do
I don't know how to dance
Xu Yuan, you're such a great dancer!
Remember, Paris never gives compliments
Good dancers like you
can only be a Libra or a Gemini
These signs suit best for Sagittarius like me
I'm a Capricorn, the nemesis for Sagittarius
Have some water
Yes, I tell you what,
Paris never offers water to anyone
I know, Paris never offers anything to anyone
She won't offer help to anyone
She's the Queen
Can I secretly be Qin Xin here?
OK
Thanks
Any news from Paris?
The people I sent to Korea haven't found her
The only consolation is that
her name is not on the casualty list
It would be ideal
If Paris could come back before the ball
That would be perfect
Do you have a plan B?
To have Qin Xin continue to play Paris,
so Dong cannot be her proxy
in the takeover case
But Qin Xin would have to sign in the meeting
That will be trouble
We can only focus on the ball then
Xu Yuan will go to the ball, right?
Tell me more about Xu Yuan
Tell me, please
Tell me!
OK, I'll tell you
Xu Yuan's favorite is the dolphin. Go figure
Qin Xin, remember
Paris knows how to dress
and she loves to dance
She also pays attention to social etiquettes
She even wears heels at home
She can tell if vegetables
are organic by taste
But few people have seen her eat
Paris needs coffee in every meal,
with neither sugar nor milk
Also, Paris doesn't like flowers
as they remind her of funerals
She only trusts one person in the company,
and that person is Kwon Jong-hoon
Dear Paris,
Who knows how to translate Korean love letters?
Paris
I know Paris won't eat like me
But I've danced for 8 hours
and watched videos for 4
I also learnt to drink red and white wines
Even 10 of Paris' diet meals
won't fill me up
Aren't you hungry?
I don't eat much in the evening
You're suddenly swamped with work
Several shrimps are not enough
Fill your stomach and go to sleep early
I'll taste one too
Don't put so much wasabi next time
If Paris comes back, all hell will break loose
I really want to see
how alike they look
Actually, not at all
That's good then
That is to say, we finally have a consensus
What?
The fake isn't that bad
Frivolous!
I know you're actually an Aries,
the perfect match for Sagittarius
How do you know?
Kwon must have told you
Dolphins!
Real dolphins!
It's really beautiful here
But I think my flowers are more beautiful
Look how beautiful my flowers are!
I designed that
It's me, not you
It's mine, mine, mine!
Mr Kwon
Come, I've something to show you
Smell the flower
Isn't it aromatic and soothing?
Paris will be happy when she comes back
Paris is mysophobic
She doesn't like to put flowers
in her rooms
Sorry
Before Paris comes back,
I'll restore the room to how it was
That's true!
If my room is messed up
without my consent,
I would be unhappy too
I didn't mean that
Anyway,
before Paris comes back,
can you let these flowers keep me company?
I'm afraid of loneliness
OK
If you can let the flowers keep me company,
can I have another request?
Can I be myself again once in a while?
Because if I stay in my role all the time,
I will go crazy!
Can I?
So how much time do you need?
Besides your sleep,
OK,
when there's nobody around,
I can grant you 2 hours
to be yourself again
OK
OK!
Yes, yes!
Sorry
That's the best I can do
OK
Yes!
I was only gone for a few days
What is it?
Who dared to put stuff in my room?
What right do you have? Throw them all out!
Every single shred!
You dared to sleep in my bedroom
and mess with my stuff?
Who do you think you are?
You really think you deserve to be Paris?
Tell her that her dream is over
Nothing here
ever belonged to her
From this minute on, I have 2 hours
to be myself, to be Qin Xin again
2 hours of my own time, Qin Xin's time!
Hello, is that Paris?
You think he's still around?
Sometimes, there are things
you really cannot believe
It happened to us before
When you think of someone,
that someone will really appear!
Had it not been for your Grandpa,
I would have died in the war
In those days, almost all men were conscripted
Grandpa escaped
He wandered all alone in the war,
surviving on tree barks and river water
Most men could not hold up,
dying of illness or hunger,
or being eaten by wolves
Grandpa was lucky
Wake up!
Thanks
Thank you
My father is a doctor
This herb is very good for you
Are you Japanese?
No, I'm Chinese
After my parents died,
a Japanese doctor adopted me
This girl is quite pretty
It's a shame she can't speak
It's OK as long as that man accepts her
We're out of firewood. I'll go chop some
How is she?
Let's go find out
Bi Da, be careful of mines!
She's not a mute. She's Japanese
Bi Da, be careful!
She only pretended to be a mute.
She's Japanese!
Go!
What are you laughing at?
He walked very fast. I was always behind him
I liked to look at his back, his shadow
I felt safe walking behind him
I had a hunch I would see him again
But why do I always have the hunch
that everything will vanish?
You cherish them,
so you're scared of losing them
In fact, there's still a lot in your life
to be experienced gradually
Miss Ke,
the order you made last week has arrived
There are still a few items
on the way from the US
I'm sorry Thanks
I've chosen an evening gown for you
It will be ready soon
Miss Ke
you're keeping your figure so well
That's it, thanks Thanks
Thank you
When Paris wears her evening gown,
she likes to put her hair up
Sorry...
Sorry
Let me
Paris, will you really come back?
If it goes on like this...
I'm afraid...I won't stay faithful to you!
Where did you spend summer 2 years ago?
Brisbane
With whom?
You,
Daddy,
and also Dong
Remember, you always call him Uncle Dong
Yes, Uncle Dong
Who else?
Kwon Jong-hoon
Yes, right
Does Paris have
to remember everybody's name?
But wherever she is,
Paris needs to know first thing
where Kwon is and with whom
24/7 surveillance.
Must be hard to date like that!
How does Kwon take it?
He...
Whatever you want to know, just ask me
Speak of the devil!
Here he is now!
Sorry,
but Dong won't ask such questions
No need to apologize, Guardian Angel
Guardian Angel! (Korean)
You think it's fun to pry?
Pry?
How did I pry?
You asked me to read Paris' materials
You asked me to play Paris seriously
so no one will know I'm a fake
You made me stay in Paris' room
You made me think I'm Paris
So when I see things in the room,
that's called prying?
They are two different matters
OK, please explain to me
What can I see?
What can't I see?
What should I know?
What shouldn't I know?
What should I say?
What shouldn't I say?
So is what happens between you and Paris
absolutely off limits to me?
You know this has nothing
to do with your mission
Understand?
Thanks,Boss
I almost forgot
True, after the ball,
everything here is no longer mine
I don't know what you mean by that?
I'm rehearsing my dance
and you're distracting me
At least I'm Paris now
Out of my room!
Now!
Par... Qin Xin!
Please go. I don't want to rehearse. Thanks
Hey!
Stop the car! Be careful!
Sorry!
Don't say sorry
Let's not fight any more
Anymore?
I'll split after the ball
Don't say that again
I'm not the real Paris you love
How's Kwon in the last couple of days?
I've convinced the Korean shareholders
not to support the takeover
You haven't answered me yet
Paris, I really don't know how to tell you
The less you say, the more I suspect
Thanks for that
Hi! I-li!
Welcome to Julian
ls there a Miss Qin here?
I saw the pictures she posted on the web
They are flowers. So beautiful!
I want to learn more
She's on vacation abroad
I'm her cousin
Hello
How can I help you?
We have a delivery for you
Sis!
What are you here for?
We have a delivery from Miss Qin
Where should I put it?
Put them all here
Put this one over there. Yes
So many?
All brand names!
You know when a man
feels most like a man?
When he can satisfy the woman he loves
Tian Fang will look pretty in this wedding gown
Too bad she cannot wear it and stand up
to take a picture with us!
Silly boy!
Your Miss Qin really knows how to shop
I wish she were here
I could ask her to pick some flowers for me
Flowers, go
This is her favorite flower
It looks like a collection of hearts
Qin Xin is very kind-hearted
Look how much she's given us
What happened?
I...
I was about to give you your wages
when I discovered a new deposit of...
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6 zeros...
One million bucks!
This is for you
Thank you
They are so pretty, don't you think?
Paris called and said...
she's coming back
She asked me not to tell anyone
But after much deliberation,
I feel obliged to tell you
Does Kwon know?
I think, in comparison,
you deserve to know more
Thanks
I'll leave here tomorrow
Don't worry
I've promised you
I'd take you back to the florist
to care for you
I have a present for you
Why are you giving me a present?
These earrings look beautiful on you
They're specially designed for you
1,2,3,1,2,3
I thought you really bought me a present
Paris!
OK, let me try how fun these earrings are
Paris...
We don't have much time left
After the ball,
I'll take a trip to Korea
Aren't you supposed to go anyway?
And I will go back to the florist
During the days at KNC
and in Ke's mansion,
I know...
it's been hard for you
It's not really that hard
Qin Xin, thank you
I will never forget you
I hope you'll remember Kwon Jong-hoon too
Yes...
Had you not reminded me, I almost forgot
What's your name?
I really can't remember
It's like when you have a dream
and can't remember a thing when you wake up
It's like nothing has ever happened
Qin Xin, I love you
I think I've fallen in love with you
Qin Xin,
why did you come see me so late at night?
Look! Your eyes are swollen with tears
What made you so sad?
After tomorrow,
my mission for him will be accomplished
As for my 3 cousins,
I've helped them
But...
you have your rewards too
If you call these my rewards,
I'd rather not have them
From the get-go.
We're from two different Worlds
Say, how can a bird
end up together with a fish?
Grandpa and I spoke different languages
but we managed to stay together, no?
I know you still miss him, right?
I'm absolutely sure he'll be missing me too
Bi Da!
Don't speak!
Stop talking!
Sorry
I need to join the war
I feel that my life is without regret,
having met a man worthy my love
Isn't that the same for you?
It's OK if your heart is overstuffed,
as long as it's filled with things you like
Having loved and lost
is better than not having loved at all
This way, please Thanks
Thanks
Cheers!
Can you hear me?
Loud and clear
This is Xu Yuan. Clear for me too
Good. Have you got off the car yet?
Miss Ke...
Heard you were caught in the avalanche in Korea
Thanks for your concern
So what was that all about?
This is your first appearance.
A few words, please
Wonderful evening!
Thank you. Thank you, everyone
Paris, you're back? You OK?
Annie, thank you. I'm good. Don't worry
You really OK?
Paris is standing right in front of you!
Excuse me.
I need to bring Paris to see Mr Dong
Paris wasn't in Korea...
Paris actually was in the US
She wanted a break. She was back last week
You look gorgeous tonight
Are you praising me or Paris?
I can't even tell the difference
You've surpassed my expectations
Paris
Uncle Dong
Thanks for
inviting me to the Charity Ball
I'm so happy to see you
You know I was so worried about you!
You must promise me the first dance
I have so much to tell you
Of course
You are as pretty as you are competent
All 5,000 of the staff
at KNC worship you
KNC already has a staff of 8,400
KNC has developed rapidly
We have a staff of 8,400 already
Oh that's right
Seeing how ill your dad is
reminds me of the days when he
and I would share a bowl of noodles
They met when they studied in Japan
Dad told me
you were studying in Japan then
They both launched their careers in Tokyo
Time flies
Paris left Japan at the age of 6
I was 5 or 6 years old then
And now, I'm dancing with Uncle Dong
You look more and more like your mom
Hurry! Give her the cue!
I never met Auntie
It's a shame
I was so little when Mom had a plane crash
I simply don't recall how she looked
Sorry
I shouldn't have brought that up. Sorry
Bravo! Bravo!
It's OK. Thanks for your concern, Uncle Dong
I'm going back to the US the day after tomorrow
Want to come with me?
Let me think about it
You are wonderful!
I'm actually enjoying it
Now everyone believes Paris is back
Dong can do nothing about it
What's wrong? Paris!
Paris...
What's wrong? What's wrong?
Let me go check
So you are Qin Xin?
You can go now
Let me remind you,
you have nothing to do with KNC
or the Ke's any more
I understand
Actually, I really have to leave right now
You're not needed here any more,
not even as my shadow
Ladies and gentlemen
We have received a total donation of
at the Charity Ball this evening $ 20 million
We've arranged a big cheque
for the signature of our Chairman, Paris
Miss Ke, this way please
This way, Miss Ke Thank you
Over here, thank you
A picture of you together
OK
This way, to the left. Thank you
Please stand closer Yes, thank you
Thanks This way, thank you
Another one, another one
The chairman of KNC
Thank you, Uncle Dong
Paris bumped into Qin Xin at the entrance
Where's Qin Xin?
She left
Qin Xin, where are you?
Qin Xin
May we have the CEO of KNC,
Mr Kwon Jong-hoon
Paris
Uncle Zhou, throw everything away
that doesn't belong to me
Yes, Miss
Restore my room to its original condition
Paris
We'll pack and return them to her
Are you returning them...
or are you?
She came here to help us
She's a good person
Miss, that lady...
I better shut up
Paris,
we actually didn't mean to offend you
OK, no need to pack
I'm never coming back
Paris...
Paris!
Get in
back to my villa
What?
I'm not going with you
She's in such a rush.
Something must have happened
Get into the car Paris
You can't ask everyone
to listen to you 24/7
I'm not asking
This is an order
Can't you be nicer to others?
You should change a bit
Nicer to others?
Who's ever nice to me?
I'm Paris
I've been running KNC since I was little
After my dad has fallen ill,
I still have to support the Ke family
Who can I rely on?
OK, you want me to be nicer?
I'd have been killed a long time ago!
The fact that Dong cannot prevail today
is because I've been relentless
I can win
I can lose
But I cannot tolerate a draw
I'm giving you 2 choices:
1) you leave with me now;
2) you go back to her
I'm telling you
I won't mistreat someone who loves me
But I'll never forgive a man who betrays me
Today, you've chosen to leave me
I'll strip you of everything you have
Paris, I'm sorry
It's my fault to find a substitute for you
Let me apologize to you
Sorry! (Korean)
You always told me
you had a hunch you'd see him again
I believe
you're already with him happily
You spent your whole life waiting for him
You've finally made it!
I asked you
why my hunches had to do with losses
You told me
because I cherished what I liked so much
I was scared of losing them
I've fallen in love with a man
I'm scared of losing him
Now that we've split up, I still cherish him
I finally understand
Qin Xin
I'm clear about my choice
You are irreplaceable
Even if I have to sacrifice everything,
I'd still rather be with you
and never come apart!
I hope you know
in the depth of my heart,
you were never
someone else's shadow!
How beautiful!
I, Yang Lin, take thee, Tian Fang, as my wife,
my lifetime companion
and my only love
I, Yang Lin, take thee, Tian Fang, as my wife,
my lifetime companion
and my only love
I, Tian Fang, take thee,
Yang Lin, as my husband,
my lifetime companion
and my only love
I vow never to leave you
but will always follow you
because wherever you go, I will go too
Don't cast it yet...
Her! Give it to her!
Xu Yuan!
Marry me!
So this is our story
Some might find it unrealistic
Some might find it ordinary
But I think Granny was right
I am really like her