[ SILENCE ]
[ ALARM CLOCK BEEPING ]
[ BEEPING CONTINUES ]
>> [ SIGHS ]
TURN IT OFF. GOD.
[ BEEPING STOPS ]
[ KEYBOARD CLICKING ]
[ TELEPHONE RINGS ]
>> MICHELLE AND SAM ARE A GREAT
COUPLE.
>> WELL, THEY'VE ONLY BEEN
DATING A FEW MONTHS.
>> THEY MET AT NEW YEAR'S LAST
YEAR.
>> [ SIGHS ]
WHERE'D YOU GUYS GO FOR DINNER?
>> I THINK I SHOULD MOVE OUT.
>> OKAY.
>> I'M GOING TO.
>> MAYBE THAT'S A GOOD IDEA.
IS THAT WHAT YOU WANT?
>> YEAH. I'M ECSTATIC.
>> WELL, WHAT DO YOU WANT?
>> WHAT DO YOU WANT?
>> MAYBE IT'S A GOOD IDEA.
>> THAT'S WHAT I THOUGHT.
[ MID-TEMPO MUSIC PLAYS ]
[ COMPUTER RINGING ]
>> HEY.
>> HEY! WE CAUGHT YOU!
>> HEY, DOUG.
>> HEY, DAD.
FIGURED OUT HOW TO USE THIS
THING?
>> [ LAUGHS ] VERY FUNNY.
WE WENT UP TO SAN FELIPE ISLAND
THIS WEEKEND WITH KEITH AND
KELLY AND DYLAN.
>> OH, YEAH.
DYLAN WAS PLAYING IN THE WATER
FOR HOURS.
HE, UH -- NO, HE'S NOT AFRAID OF
THE WAVES AT ALL.
>> THAT'S GREAT.
>> SO, WHEN WE CAME BACK, UH, WE
STOPPED AT SEAVIEW AND VISITED
YOUR GRANDFATHER, AND HE'S
LOOKING PRETTY GOOD.
>> OH, THAT'S GOOD TO HEAR.
>> HE HAS SOMETHING THAT HE
WANTS YOU TO GIVE CLARE.
SHE'S NOT LISTENING, IS SHE?
>> UH, NO. SHE'S NOT HERE.
>> YEP. ALL RIGHT.
IT'S A RING THAT, UH, BELONGED
TO YOUR GRANDMOTHER.
>> HE THOUGHT IT WOULD MAKE A
NICE BIRTHDAY PRESENT.
>> UH, CLARE AND I HAVE DECIDED
TO TAKE A BREAK.
>> WOW.
HAS SHE MOVED OUT?
>> YEAH.
>> OH, HONEY.
>> WELL, WE WERE STRUGGLING FOR
A WHILE, AND IT'S REALLY BETTER
THIS WAY.
>> WHAT WERE YOU STRUGGLING
ABOUT?
>> WELL...
>> I MEAN, NO, IT'S OKAY, DOUG.
YOU DON'T HAVE TO TALK ABOUT IT.
>> I KNOW YOU'RE BOTH
DISAPPOINTED.
>> NO, WE'RE NOT.
>> WELL, OF COURSE WE'RE
DISAPPOINTED.
I'M NOT SURPRISED.
I THINK CLARE'S GETTING OLDER,
YOU GUYS HAVEN'T BEEN
PROGRESSING OR ADVANCING, AND
WOMEN NEED TO THINK ABOUT THOSE
THINGS, OKAY?
CLARE -- SHE NEEDS SOMEONE --
>> WELL, YOU KNOW, CLARE'S A
VERY NICE GIRL, BUT IF SHE'S NOT
THE ONE, SHE'S NOT.
IT'S BETTER NOT TO SETTLE FOR
SOMETHING THAT YOU KNOW ISN'T
RIGHT.
>> YEAH, EXACTLY. THANKS, MOM.
>> TWO AGAINST ONE.
SO, WHEN DID SHE MOVE OUT?
>> OVER THE WEEKEND.
I HELPED HER TAKE MOST OF HER
STUFF TO HER FRIEND CARA'S.
SHE'S LEAVING A FEW THINGS HERE
FOR NOW TILL SHE FINDS A PLACE,
BUT IT'LL BE OKA--
HELLO?
>> WE'RE LISTENING.
WE'RE JUST OPENING ANOTHER
BOTTLE.
>> WE ARE NOT DISAPPOINTED,
DOUG.
>> YOU'RE NOT DISAPPOINTED.
>> SHH.
>> WANT A LITTLE WHITE WINE?
>> I LOVE THE MERLOT.
>> ALL RIGHT. YEAH.
>> ALL RIGHT. DOUG, YOU'RE NOT
TRYING TO HIT A BULL'S-EYE.
LET'S GO.
"E." BEAUTIFUL.
LISTEN, DOUG, YOU'RE GONNA WANT
TO KEEP YOUR DISTANCE NOW, MAN.
I'M SERIOUS -- LIKE RADIO
SILENCE.
SHE'S GONNA WANT BACK TOGETHER.
>> NO, I THINK WE'RE BOTH
REALIZING HOW UNHAPPY WE WERE.
>> OH, PLEASE. COME ON, DOUG.
SHE'S GONNA GO OUT WITH SOME
SLUTTY LITTLE GIRLFRIENDS AND
THEN SHE'S GONNA FUCK SOME AWFUL
GUY AND THEN SHE'S GONNA START
THINKING HOW SHE'S WORTHLESS AND
SHE'S GONNA COME RUNNING TO YOU
SO YOU CAN CONVINCE HER THAT
SHE'S NOT WORTHLESS, AND THEN
YOU'RE GONNA GET BACK TOGETHER.
GUARANTEED.
>> I DON'T THINK YOU'RE GIVING
EITHER OF US ENOUGH CREDIT.
>> OH, COME ON.
LET ME HIT ONE, THEN. MOVE.
HOLD THAT.
>> NO, YOU'RE WRONG.
THERE'S NO GOING BACK.
I FEEL LIKE I'VE BEEN GIVEN A
NEW LIFE.
I FEEL LIKE NOW I CAN --
>> [ LAUGHS ]
>> ALL RIGHT, I'M GONNA HIT THIS
ONE.
>> [ Laughing ] OH, MY GOD.
YOU REALLY NEED TO WORK ON YOUR
SWING, MAN.
>> YEAH, WELL, I'M OUT OF
PRACTICE.
>> NO, YOU KNOW WHAT?
YOU SHOULD TAKE LESSONS FROM ME.
WATCH THIS.
>> [ Laughing ] YEAH.
MAYBE I WILL.
SEE, THAT'S WHAT I'M TALKING
ABOUT.
I FEEL LIKE NOW I CAN DO THAT.
LIKE, NOW I CAN TAKE LESSONS.
NOW I CAN DO WHATEVER I WANT.
NICE.
>> HEAR THAT ONE?
>> I AM GONNA TAKE LESSONS.
>> [ SPEAKING INDISTINCTLY ]
>> ACCESS. ACTIVATE.
>> ♪ AND SHE LOOKED LIKE
>> CUT THEM INTO QUARTER-INCH
SLICES.
>> DURING THE DAYS, THE AFRICAN
SUN CAN RAISE THE MERCURY TO
23 DEGREES CENTIGRADE OR MORE.
THE MOUNTAIN IS, IN FACT, A
STRATOVOLCANO CONSISTING OF
THREE DISTINCT CONES.
HIKERS ASCEND THROUGH SEVEN
MICROCLIMATES TO REACH ITS
SUMMIT, THE UHURU, OR KIBO,
PEAK, WHICH STANDS AT NEARLY
6,000 METERS ABOVE SEA LEVEL.
[ CELLPHONE VIBRATING ]
>> SORRY I MISSED YOUR CALL.
PLEASE LEAVE --
>> CALLED "EVERY MAN'S EVEREST,"
THE MOUNTAIN LURES OVER
10,000 MOUNTAINEERS EVERY YEAR
TO ATTEMPT SCALING ITS HEIGHTS.
LESS THAN HALF SUCCEED.
THE FAMED SNOWS OF
KILIMANJARO -- IN ACTUALITY, ICE
GLACIERS -- HAVE RECEDED
MARKEDLY IN RECENT DECADES.
BUT THE WEATHER ON THESE SLOPES
REMAINS VARIED AND OFTEN
INHOSPITABLE.
TO THE WEST, THE BORDER OF
TANZANIA BISECTS LAKE VICTORIA.
THE CITY OF KAMPALA STANDS ON
THE LAKE'S NORTHERN SHORE, HOME
TO OVER A MILLION AND A HALF
PEOPLE.
[ CELLPHONE VIBRATING ]
>> HEY, DAD.
>> HI, DOUG.
THE NURSING HOME...JUST CALLED.
YOUR GRANDFATHER HAS BEEN TAKEN
TO THE HOSPITAL, AND I DON'T
KNOW HOW SEVERE IT IS, BUT MOM
AND I ARE GONNA GO THERE RIGHT
NOW, AND I WILL CALL YOU LATER.
I JUST -- I WANTED TO LET YOU
KNOW.
I THINK IT WOULD BE A GOOD IDEA
TO FLY OUT HERE FOR THE NEXT FEW
DAYS AND SPEND SOME TIME WITH
HIM.
>> HEY, ERNIE!
HEY, BUDDY!
HEY! COME HERE.
WHERE IS EVERYONE?
HELLO?!
>> SEEING THIS WHAT SEEMS TO
BE...
>> GRANDDAD?
>> HELLO, DOUG!
COME ON IN HERE.
>> HEY!
>> WAIT A MINUTE.
LET ME TURN THIS THING DOWN.
OH-HO.
>> YOU COULD NEVER GET CLOSE
ENOUGH TO SEE WHAT 95...
>> OHH. HEY.
>> OH, GOOD TO SEE YOU.
>> YOU LOOK GOOD.
>> THANKS. HOW ARE YOU?
HOW YOU FEELING?
>> OH, I'M GREAT.
UH, I -- UH, OH, SORRY. HERE.
PULL UP A CHAIR.
>> [ SIGHS ]
>> I GUESS I'M NOT MUCH OF A
HOST THESE DAYS.
>> OH, NONSENSE.
>> [ CLEARS THROAT ]
NOW, I WANT TO KNOW ALL ABOUT
EVERYTHING THAT YOU'RE DOING,
BUT FIRST, I WANT TO -- I WANT
TO TELL YOU.
NOW, YOUR FATHER KNOWS THAT I'M
GOING TO DO THIS.
OPEN THAT DRAWER THERE.
YOU SEE THAT RED BOX?
I WANT YOU TO HAVE THAT.
I WANT YOU TO GIVE IT TO YOUR --
YOUR FRIEND.
THAT WAS YOUR GRANDMOTHER'S.
YOUR BROTHER, KEITH'S, ALREADY
MARRIED.
ANYWAY, I THINK SHE WOULD WANT
YOU TO HAVE IT.
>> I APPRECIATE IT.
>> NO, NO, NO, NO, NO.
I KNOW A THING OR TWO ABOUT
WOMEN.
[ CHUCKLES ]
YOU'VE GOT TO SPOIL THEM JUST A
LITTLE BIT.
[ CHUCKLES ]
CLARE -- OH.
SHE'S A RARE GIRL.
WELL, ENOUGH ABOUT THAT.
I WANT TO HEAR ABOUT LIFE IN THE
BIG CITY.
>> WELL, THERE'S NOT TOO MUCH TO
TELL.
WHERE'D YOU GET THESE?
>> YOUR MOTHER MADE THOSE FOR
ME, BLESS HER HEART.
>> IS THIS WHEN YOU WENT TO
MEXICO?
>> YES, THAT WAS THE FIRST
TRIP -- 1948.
THAT'S A PICTURE OF MY FRIEND
JAMES McKENZIE AND ME.
>> DOING A HEADSTAND?
>> YEAH, THAT'S RIGHT.
HE'D DO A HEADSTAND, AND HE'D DO
ABOUT ANYTHING YOU'D ASK HIM TO
DO.
HE WAS A CRAZY MAN.
WE WERE GONNA TAKE ANOTHER TRIP
DOWN THERE.
HE HAD A WHOLE ITINERARY LAID
OUT.
WE WERE GONNA GO ALL THE WAY TO
PANAMA CITY.
YEAH.
BUT THEN THE KIDS WERE GETTING
OLDER, AND...WE -- WE STAYED
CLOSER TO HOME.
THERE'S A PICTURE OF YOUR FATHER
AND ME ON OUR TRIP UP TO THE
CASCADES.
[ CELLPHONE RINGS ]
>> HEY, MAN.
>> HEY! WHAT'S UP, SURVIVORMAN?
FUCKING AFRICA? REALLY?
>> DID YOU LOOK AT THE PICTURES?
>> YOU KNOW WHERE WE SHOULD GO?
>> WHERE?
>> BANGKOK.
>> YEAH, I'M NOT GOING TO
BANGKOK WITH YOU.
>> WHY WOULD WE GO HALFWAY
AROUND THE WORLD TO GO ON A
HIKE?
>> LET'S MEET UP IN AN HOUR.
YOU WANT TO GET SOME LUNCH?
>> NAH.
>> DO YOU HAVE TIME TODAY?
I CAN COME BY ON MY LUNCH BREAK.
>> UH, YEAH, SURE.
YEAH, IF YOU WANT TO.
>> KEN?! KEN!
>> CALL YOU WHEN I'M DOWNSTAIRS.
>> KEN!
WHERE'S KEN?
>> UH, SORRY. HE'S NOT HERE.
>> WHERE IS HE?
>> I GUESS HE STEPPED OUT.
I DON'T KNOW.
>> HOW COULD YOU NOT KNOW?
YOU SIT RIGHT ACROSS FROM THE
GUY.
>> YEAH. I WAS ON THE PHONE.
>> ALL RIGHT.
>> IS THERE SOMETHING I COULD
HELP YOU WITH?
>> NO, IT'S ALL RIGHT.
WHEN HE GETS BACK, TELL HIM TO
BRING IN THE LAYOUTS FROM ANNE.
>> FOR THE COOKBOOK?
>> YEP.
>> HEY!
>> HEY.
>> YOU TAKE LUNCH AT 3:30?
>> YEAH, SORRY.
I COULDN'T GET AWAY AS QUICKLY
AS I THOUGHT.
CHECK IT OUT.
>> WHAT? WHAT IS THIS?
>> IT'S ONE OF THE ROUTES WE CAN
DO.
LISTEN, WE FLY IN TO NAIROBI.
>> I SIT ON MY ASS FOR NINE
HOURS A DAY.
I'M NOT -- WE'RE NOT ATHLETES.
>> I RAN TRACK.
>> YOU SUCKED SO BAD.
>> ALL THE MORE REASON TO DO IT.
LOOK, WE GOT MONTHS TO GET IN
SHAPE.
MITCH, THIS IS A TRIP OF A
LIFETIME, MAN, AND WHEN PEOPLE
ASK YOU WHAT YOU'RE DOING THIS
SUMMER, YOU CAN SAY, "I DON'T
KNOW.
I'M CLIMBING THE HIGHEST PEAK IN
AFRICA."
>> ARE YOU TRYING TO IMPRESS
CLARE?
>> NO, NOT AT ALL.
>> I TALKED TO HER, YOU KNOW.
>> OKAY.
LOOK, MAN, THIS IS A SAFARI WE
CAN DO.
THIS IS A TWO-DAY TRIP IN MOSHI,
THIS TOWN AT THE BASE -- ALL
RIGHT? -- SO WE GET A LITTLE
ACCLIMATED BEFORE WE START.
AND AFTER WE SUMMIT AND DESCEND,
WE GO TO TANGA, MAN.
IT'S A BEACH TOWN ON THE
INDIAN OCEAN.
>> ARE THERE ANY TOPLESS BEACHES
THERE?
>> I DON'T KNOW. MAYBE.
>> WHATEVER. I'M IN.
>> YOU'RE IN?
REALLY? ARE YOU SERIOUS?
>> YES, I'M SERIOUS. YES.
>> GREAT, MAN.
THIS IS -- THIS IS GONNA BE
GREAT, MAN.
LOOK AT THIS.
THIS IS A PICTURE OF THE
SHERPAS, AND THEY'RE THE GUY
THAT CARRY OUR BAG.
>> THAT'S GREAT.
LOOK, I GOT TO GO.
WE GOT TO TALK ABOUT THIS LATER,
HONESTLY.
CALL ME LATER.
>> CAN I GET A SMOKE?
>> REALLY?
>> YEAH.
>> HERE. ENJOY. KEEP IT.
>> THANKS.
[ MID-TEMPO MUSIC PLAYS ]
>> [ CHUCKLES ]
>> ARE YOU LOOKING FOR
SOMETHING?
>> YEAH, MY KEYS.
I HAD THEM ON MY SHOE.
>> OH. DID YOU HAVE A KEYCHAIN
OR SOMETHING?
>> YEAH, A BOTTLE OPENER.
IT'S BLUE.
>> I'M SORRY.
LOSING YOUR KEYS IS THE WORST.
>> IT SUCKS BALLS.
>> I'M DOUG.
>> YVONNE.
>> WELL, DO YOU REMEMBER WHEN
YOU HAD THEM LAST?
>> YEAH -- WHEN I GOT HERE.
>> WAS THERE ANYTHING ON THE
BOTTLE OPENER, LIKE A SPECIAL
SHAPE OR SOMETHING?
>> NO.
YOU KNOW WHAT?
MY ROOMMATE WILL LET ME IN.
IT'S FINE.
>> I DON'T MIND LOOKING.
>> NO, I-I GOT TO GO.
BUT THANKS ANYWAY.
>> I'M SORRY WE DIDN'T FIND
THEM.
I HOPE THE REST OF YOUR DAY
DOESN'T SUCK BALLS.
>> [ LAUGHS ]
UH, IT WAS DAVE, RIGHT?
>> UH, DOUG.
>> DOUG. OKAY.
GOT IT. GOT IT NOW.
[ CHUCKLES ]
>> WELL, IT'S GOOD TO MEET YOU.
>> YEAH, YOU, TOO. OKAY.
>> YVONNE.
>> YEAH, YVONNE.
SO, I'LL -- I'LL SEE YOU AROUND.
>> HI.
IT'S NICE TO SEE YOU, TOO.
>> I'M SORRY.
I'M JUST SURPRISED YOU'RE HERE.
>> I LEFT YOU A MESSAGE ON MY
WAY OVER.
>> I DIDN'T GET IT.
>> I JUST CAME TO GET THE REST
OF MY STUFF.
>> UH, THERE'S SOME MAIL FOR YOU
OVER HERE.
>> I SAW IT. THANKS.
>> I'M SORRY.
I'M HEADED BACK OUT.
>> IT'S FINE.
>> I MEAN I'M SORRY WE CAN'T
CATCH UP.
>> I THINK IF YOU WANTED TO
CATCH UP, YOU WOULD ANSWER YOUR
PHONE.
>> I KNOW I DIDN'T GET BACK TO
YOU LAST WEEK.
I WAS IN CALIFORNIA.
MY GRANDFATHER HAD A STROKE.
>> OH, MY GOD.
IS HE OKAY?
>> UH, HE -- HE'S NOT, LIKE, UP
AND ABOUT YET, BUT HE SEEMS
FINE.
>> I'M SO SORRY.
>> HE ASKED ABOUT YOU.
>> REALLY?
IS HE SEEING ANYBODY THESE DAYS?
TELL HIM I SAID HELLO.
>> I WILL.
>> HEY, UM, ANY CHANCE YOU CAN
HELP ME GET THESE DOWN TO THE
STREET?
>> I'M SORRY.
I'M RUNNING LATE ALREADY.
I'M MEETING UP WITH MITCH.
WE'RE LOOKING AT CLIMBING
MOUNT KILIMANJARO.
>> REALLY? WOW.
WHEN DID ALL THIS HAPPEN?
>> OH, I JUST, UH -- I JUST GOT
THE IDEA.
>> WELL, THAT'S -- THAT'S COOL.
THAT'S REALL-- THAT'S REALLY
GREAT.
>> WELL, IT'S NOT LIKE IT'S
MOUNT EVEREST.
>> NO, NO. IT'S REALLY --
THAT'S REALLY GREAT, DOUG.
>> YEAH. I'M LOOKING FORWARD TO
IT, YOU KNOW -- SOMETHING NEW.
UM...
WELL, IF YOU CAN'T GET IT ALL
TONIGHT, DON'T WORRY ABOUT IT.
I CAN HELP YOU TOMORROW NIGHT OR
THIS WEEKEND OR SOMETHING.
>> I'LL BE FINE.
>> WELL, I'LL SEE YOU SOON?
>> WILL YOU?
I DIDN'T KNOW WE HAD ANY PLANS.
IT WOULD BE NICE TO SEE YOU AT
SOME POINT.
>> YEAH. WE SHOULD GET A DRINK.
HOW 'BOUT TOMORROW?
>> I CAN'T TOMORROW.
>> OKAY. UH, THURSDAY?
>> YOU WANT TO DO DINNER?
>> DINNER, UH -- DINNER SOUNDS
GREAT.
I'LL SEE YOU THEN.
OKAY.
>> BYE.
[ DOOR OPENS, CLOSES ]
>> ALLEGEDLY, I'M HERE TO, UH,
TELL EVERYBODY IN THE ROOM TO
GIVE YOU THEIR MONEY.
THAT'S HOW THE COMPANY PROFITS.
THAT'S HOW I GET PAID.
BUT THAT'S NOT HOW I OPERATE.
SEE, I CAN'T KNOWINGLY TAKE
THOUSANDS OF DOLLARS FROM
SOMEBODY THAT I CAN TELL
IMMEDIATELY WON'T MAKE IT TO THE
TOP.
AND LOOKING AROUND THIS ROOM
RIGHT NOW, I CAN SEE SOME PEOPLE
WHO WON'T MAKE IT.
SO, I'M GONNA MEET WITH EACH OF
YOU, ONE ON ONE, AND WE'RE GONNA
TALK ABOUT YOUR BACKGROUND --
YOUR EXERCISE REGIMEN, YOUR
HEALTH CONDITIONING -- AND I'M
GONNA BE BRUTALLY HONEST WITH
YOU ABOUT WHAT I THINK.
AFTER THAT...
IT'S UP TO YOU, FOLKS.
LIKE THEY SAY, A FOOL AND HIS
MONEY.
>> WHAT A FUCKING RETARD.
WHAT A COCKSUCKER.
>> WHY? WHAT DID HE TELL YOU?
>> THE SAME THING HE TOLD
EVERYBODY.
IT'S JUST HIS SPIEL.
>> HE SAID YOU WOULDN'T MAKE IT?
>> HE SAID I NEEDED TO BE
EXERCISING MORE.
IT IS SUCH BULLSHIT.
>> THAT'S WHAT HE SAID TO ME.
>> YEAH, I KNOW.
HE TOLD THAT TO EVERYBODY, I
BET.
YOU KNOW WHAT I TOLD HIM?
I TOLD HIM I'M ALREADY RUNNING
5 MILES A DAY.
>> [ Laughing ] YOU LIED TO HIM?
>> [ Laughing ] IT DOESN'T
MATTER.
HE'S NOT GONNA BE ON OUR TREK.
HE'S JUST A SALES REP.
>> YEAH, "KILI" KURT, THE GUY
WHOSE BLOG I READ -- HE SAID
THAT ALTITUDE'S THE ONLY THING
TO REALLY WORRY ABOUT.
>> YEAH, SEE?
IT'S ALL MENTAL, OKAY?
DON'T LET YOURSELF GET PSYCHED
OUT BY THAT FUCKING DIPSHIT.
>> DID YOU KNOW ABOUT THE TRAVEL
INSURANCE AND GUIDE FEES?
>> IT'S, WHAT, LIKE A GRAND,
RIGHT?
>> $1,200.
>> YEAH.
>> WE SHOULD DO
THE SEPTEMBER TREK.
THAT GIVES US THE MOST TIME TO
GET IN SHAPE.
>> NO, NO. I CAN'T DO SEPTEMBER.
I GOT TO TAKE MY TIME OFF BEFORE
AUGUST 31st OR I LOSE IT.
>> WELL, I MIGHT NOT BE ABLE TO
GET THE TIME OFF IN AUGUST.
WE HAVE THE HUDSON BOOK FAIR.
>> YOU CAN'T TAKE TWO WEEKS OFF?
>> NOT DURING THAT TIME, NO.
>> THEN QUIT.
YOU HATE IT THERE ANYWAY.
>> YEAH. HOW WOULD I PAY FOR THE
TRIP?
>> NOT NOW.
QUIT RIGHT BEFORE YOU GO.
>> I CAN'T DO THAT TO THEM.
I'M THE ONLY GUY THAT KNOWS HOW
TO RUN IT.
>> THAT IS NOT YOUR PROBLEM,
DOUG.
>> WELL, I CAN'T JUST QUIT.
>> NO, YOU KNOW WHAT?
LOOK -- YOU GO INTO HIS OFFICE,
AND YOU TELL HIM YOU'RE LEAVING
UNLESS HE GIVES YOU THE TIME
OFF.
HE'LL GIVE YOU THE TIME OFF.
I'M SERIOUS.
THERE'S NO WAY HE'S LETTING HIS
MOST EXPERIENCED GUY JUST WALK
OUT THE DOOR.
>> YEAH.
>> HE'LL PROBABLY EVEN GIVE YOU
A RAISE.
>> YEAH, A RAISE WOULD BE NICE.
>> WHAT, YOU NEED SOME MONEY?
I-I-I CAN LEND YOU SOME.
>> NO, NO, NO.
>> NO, I KNOW YOU'D PAY ME BACK.
IT'S NOT A BIG DEAL.
>> NO, WHAT -- SERIOUSLY, MITCH,
I APPRECIATE THE OFFER.
IT'S NICE. BUT I'LL BE FINE.
I MADE A BUDGET.
>> ARE YOU PAYING ALL THE RENT
NOW?
>> NO, SHE'S GIVING ME SOME OF
HER SHARE UNTIL JULY.
THAT'S WHEN OUR LEASE IS UP.
THAT WAS PART OF OUR AGREEMENT.
>> OH, OH, THE AGREEMENT.
PBBT! HEY, THAT'LL STICK.
>> BILL.
UH, IS THIS AN OKAY TIME?
>> WHAT'S UP?
>> DID YOU GET MY E-MAIL?
>> UH...
I HA-- I DIDN'T SEE IT.
WH-WHAT'S UP?
>> WELL, I'M PLANNING WITH A
FRIEND OF MINE TO CLIMB
MOUNT KILIMANJARO THIS SUMMER,
AND I WANT TO SCHEDULE A TIME
THAT'S CONVENIENT TO TAKE OFF IN
EITHER JULY OR AUGUST.
I HAVE SOME EXACT DATES I
COULD --
>> HOW 'BOUT SEPTEMBER?
>> UH, SORRY.
MY FRIEND CAN'T DO SEPTEMBER.
>> WELL, I CAN'T HAVE YOU OUT IN
AUGUST, AND KEN'S ALREADY TAKING
TIME IN JULY.
>> NO, I SPOKE TO KEN, AND OUR
DATES WOULDN'T OVERLAP.
>> BUT YOU'D BE OUT
BACK-TO-BACK.
WHY DOESN'T YOUR FRIEND JUST DO
SEPTEMBER?
>> WELL, HIS JOB -- HE HAS TO
TAKE HIS VACATION BEFORE THEN.
>> WELL...
I-I DON'T KNOW WHAT YOU'RE
SUPPOSED TO DO.
UM...
MAYBE TALK TO KEN ABOUT CHANGING
HIS TRIP?
I DON'T KNOW, DOUG.
>> BILL...
I HAVEN'T ASKED FOR AN EXTENDED
VACATION IN OVER THREE YEARS,
AND I'LL WORK OVERTIME TO MAKE
SURE KEN HAS EVERYTHING HE NEEDS
WHILE I'M AWAY.
>> STOP.
>> [ SIGHS ]
>> DOUG, YOU CAN'T TURN KEN INTO
YOU.
YOU'RE THE LEAD GUY HERE.
YOU'RE THE ONE I DEPEND ON.
>> WELL, THANK YOU.
I APPRECIATE THAT.
>> I NEED YOU TO BE THE POINT
PERSON ON THE JAVITS THING,
OKAY?
I DON'T EVEN WANT KEN TALKING TO
THOSE PEOPLE.
>> WELL, I UNDERSTAND THAT, BUT
THIS TRIP IS VERY IMPORTANT TO
ME.
>> I DON'T KNOW HOW IT COULD
WORK.
>> WELL, I-I WAS THINKING
MAYBE --
[ TELEPHONE RINGS ]
>> YEAH?
[ LAUGHS ]
NO, I'M NOT DOING ANYTHING.
CAN YOU SHUT THE DOOR?
YEAH.
WELL, THAT'S A LOT OF MONEY.
>> AY, YI, YI.
[ SIGHS ] SORRY.
>> MM, FINE.
>> [ SIGHS ]
MY MOM KEEPS ASKING ME IF I'VE
SEEN YOU.
WE'RE DISCUSSING OUR
DIFFERENCES.
>> HMM.
>> I TOLD HER WE WERE HAVING
DINNER TONIGHT.
ACTUALLY, I SAID YOU WERE MAKING
DINNER, AND SHE JOKED THAT MY
DAD HASN'T MADE HER DINNER IN
LIKE 30 YEARS.
>> WELL, I'M ON A BUDGET.
>> WELL, ANYWAY, SHE'S CONVINCED
THAT I'VE LET THE BEST THING
THAT EVER HAPPENED TO ME SLIP
THROUGH MY FINGERS.
>> MY PARENTS SAY THE SAME
THING.
>> BUT IN YOUR CASE, THEY'RE
RIGHT.
>> HA.
[ CELLPHONE VIBRATING ]
OH. MITCH.
>> TAKE IT.
>> NO. WE'RE HAVING DINNER.
I'LL CALL HIM LATER.
OH, I JUST WANT TO MAKE SURE
IT'S STILL OKAY FOR YOU TO COVER
PART OF THE RENT.
>> UM, WELL, I FEEL LIKE I NEED
TO HELP OUT CARA A LITTLE BIT.
I MEAN, I'M LIVING ON HER COUCH,
AND, UM, I'M SORRY.
I JUST -- I NEED TO GIVE HER
SOMETHING.
>> WELL, IF YOU CAN'T, YOU
CAN'T.
>> THANKS. I-I KNOW IT'S NOT
WHAT WE AGREED.
HOW'S WORK? HOW'S BILL?
>> BILL'S, UM, BILL.
>> [ CHUCKLES ]
>> HOW'S SCHOOL?
>> IT'S OKAY.
>> DID YOU GET YOUR CLASSROOM
PLACEMENT?
>> YEAH, STATEN ISLAND.
>> MM.
>> YEAH. IT'S NOT THAT BAD.
>> YEAH, IT'S A BOROUGH.
>> [ Laughing ] YEAH.
[ CELLPHONE CHIMES ]
>> OH.
OH. UM...I'LL BE RIGHT BACK,
OKAY?
>> OKAY.
>> HI.
[ CHUCKLES ]
[ RINGING ]
>> HEY.
>> HEY, MAN.
>> YOU GET MY MESSAGE?
>> NO.
>> I FOUND TICKETS IN AUGUST FOR
$1,680.
BOOM!
>> AWESOME.
YOU KNOW, I'LL TALK TO BILL
TOMORROW.
>> WHAT DO YOU MEAN, TOMORROW?
I ORDERED THEM.
I COULDN'T LET THAT PRICE GO.
WHY DIDN'T YOU TALK TO HIM
TODAY?
>> IT JUST WASN'T A GOOD TIME.
>> WHATEVER.
I MEAN, YOU'RE QUITTING THERE
ANYWAY, RIGHT?
>> NO, I'M NOT QUITTING.
>> YOU SAID YOU WERE GOING TO.
ALL RIGHT.
AT LEAST WE GOT THE TICKETS.
>> WELL, I WAS GONNA PUT THEM ON
MY CREDIT CARD.
>> ALL RIGHT.
WELL, NOW YOU CAN PAY ME.
>> O-OKAY. WELL...
>> DO YOU NOT HAVE $1,600 IN
YOUR CHECKING ACCOUNT?
>> I HAVE THE MONEY.
I'LL JUST WRITE YOU A CHECK.
>> THERE'S NO HURRY, SO YOU CAN
JUST PAY ME AFTER.
>> ALL RIGHT. WELL, THANKS.
I APPRECIATE THAT.
>> I CAN'T BELIEVE I FOUND THEM
SO CHEAP.
>> THAT'S AWESOME.
ALL RIGHT. UM, I GOT TO GO.
>> OH, YOU'RE BUSY?
TELL HER I SAID HELLO.
>> MM. MITCH?
>> YEAH.
>> I TALKED TO HIM A COUPLE
WEEKS AGO.
>> I HEARD. YEAH.
>> YEAH. MM-HMM.
HE TOLD ME THAT YOU WERE SEEING
A 19-YEAR-OLD, A MODEL -- THAT
HE SET YOU GUYS UP.
>> SHE WAS 20.
>> VERY FUNNY.
>> YEAH. WE DIDN'T HAVE THAT
MUCH IN COMMON.
IT WASN'T REALLY WORKING OUT.
YOU KNOW, SHE DIDN'T LIKE TO
READ.
>> DID SHE KNOW HOW TO READ?
[ BOTH LAUGH ]
IT REALLY WOULDN'T SURPRISE ME.
I MEAN, WE BREAK UP, AND THEN,
SUDDENLY, YOU'RE LIKE A
MOUNTAIN-CLIMBING STUD.
>> WELL, I HAVEN'T CLIMBED ANY
MOUNTAINS YET.
>> SO, TECHNICALLY, YOU'RE STILL
JUST A STUD?
>> YEAH, EXACTLY.
>> I'M REALLY GLAD THAT WE'RE
HAVING DINNER.
IT'S WEIRD, RIGHT?
>> WEIRD WHY?
>> NOT HAVING DINNER EVERY
NIGHT.
[ CHUCKLES ]
NOT TALKING ALL THE TIME, AND,
UM, YOU KNOW, I JUST -- THERE
ARE NICE THINGS ABOUT IT.
I'M SURE YOU THINK SO, TOO.
IT'S JUST A BIG CHANGE.
I MEAN, UH, AT LEAST YOU HAVE
THE APARTMENT.
ARE YOU MAD AT ME?
>> NO.
>> REALLY?
>> WHY WOULD I BE MAD AT YOU?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
I MEAN, FOR BREAKING UP
WITH YOU.
[ CHUCKLES ]
[ LAUGHS ]
WE BROKE UP.
FOR NOT GIVING YOU MORE MONEY
FOR THE RENT AND --
>> I'M NOT MAD.
I'M NOT.
>> OKAY.
>> HERE. YOU HAVE SOMETHING IN
YOUR HAIR.
>> OH, THANK YOU.
>> [ SIGHS ]
[ MID-TEMPO MUSIC PLAYS ]
[ GROANS SOFTLY ]
>> WHAT HAPPENED?
>> I WAS JUST SAYING YOU BETTER
SHOW UP ON CRUTCHES.
>> [ LAUGHS ]
>> I PUT THE REVISED PAGES FROM
GENE CHRISTOPHER ON YOUR DESK.
>> THANKS.
>> I NEED YOU TO PROOF THEM AND
GET THEM BACK TO HIM TODAY IF
THAT'S STILL POSSIBLE.
>> NO PROBLEM.
UH...
>> ARE YOU OKAY?
>> YEAH.
I HAVE AN APPOINTMENT WITH A
SPECIALIST THIS AFTERNOON.
>> GENE REALLY NEEDS THOSE
TODAY.
I TOLD HIM YOU'D BE ALL OVER IT.
>> GOT IT.
YEAH.
>> KEN, CAN YOU COME IN HERE?
>> YEAH.
>> YEAH. HE'S REALLY BOOKED.
YEAH, I DON'T -- I DON'T KNOW.
WHY DON'T I HAVE THE DOCTOR CALL
YOU BACK?
>> UH, HI.
I'M HERE TO SEE DR. PATEL.
>> HI!
>> HI. YOU WORK HERE.
>> I DO.
[ LAUGHS ]
>> HOW ARE YOU?
>> UH, I'M -- I'M GOOD.
HOW ARE -- HOW ARE YOU?
>> WELL, I'VE BEEN BETTER.
>> OH, MY GOSH.
[ Laughing ] YEAH, I'LL BET.
UM, I DON'T MEAN TO LAUGH AT
YOUR AILMENT.
>> NO, IT'S FINE.
>> WHY DON'T YOU TAKE A SEAT AND
I'LL GET YOU THE FORMS?
>> OKAY.
>> I'M PLANNING -- I'M HOPING --
TO CLIMB KILIMANJARO THIS SUMMER
WITH A FRIEND OF MINE, SO...
>> COOL. KILIMANJARO? K2?
DAMN.
[ TELEPHONE RINGING ]
SHIT. I HAVE TO ANSWER THAT.
UH, JUST -- AAH.
I JUST CAN'T BELIEVE HOW CRAZY!
I MEAN, IT'S SO FUCKING FUNNY
RUNNING INTO YOU AGAIN, RIGHT?
AHH.
[ RINGING CONTINUES ]
DR. PATEL'S OFFICE.
>> ALL RIGHT.
LIFT YOUR LEG A LITTLE BIT UP --
A LITTLE BIT UP.
I KNOW IT'S GOING TO HURT.
IT'S GONNA HURT. OKAY.
YEAH, I SEE THE SWELLING THERE.
>> WELL, I'M HOPING TO CLIMB
MOUNT KILIMANJARO THIS SUMMER,
AND...
IS THAT OUT OF THE QUESTION?
>> WHEN IS YOUR TRIP?
>> MY TRIP'S IN AUGUST.
[ SIGHS ]
>> ARE YOU STILL GONNA BE --
WAIT.
OKAY. OKAY, GREAT.
TUESDAY AT 3:30.
OKAY, BYE.
OKAY.
WHAT DID HE SAY?
>> HE SAID I'M SUPPOSED TO TAKE
IT EASY FOR TWO WEEKS AND SEE
HOW I START TO RECOVER, SO...
>> YOU'LL BE FINE.
JUST STICK TO LOW-IMPACT
TRAINING, LIKE SWIMMING.
>> YEAH, THAT'S A GOOD IDEA.
>> DOES YOUR GYM HAVE A POOL?
>> NO.
>> UM, THERE'S THIS PLACE IN MY
OLD NEIGHBORHOOD THAT I ACTUALLY
STILL BELONG TO, AND THEY HAVE A
REALLY NICE POOL.
I COULD GET YOU IN AS A GUEST IF
YOU WANTED TO CHECK IT OUT.
>> UH, THAT'D BE GREAT.
>> YEAH.
[ TELEPHONE RINGING ]
I MEAN, I CAN'T TONIGHT, BUT
WHAT ARE YOU DOING TOMORROW?
>> NOTHING.
>> OH, OKAY.
[ RINGING CONTINUES ]
YEAH? OKAY. OKAY.
>> DR. PATEL'S OFFICE.
YES. CAN YOU HOLD, PLEASE?
UM, WHY DON'T YOU JUST, UH,
WRITE YOUR INFORMATION DOWN
THERE AND WE'LL MAKE A PLAN,
OKAY?
YES.
>> PHASE 2 BEGINS, OKAY?
GOOD TO SEE YOU.
HEY.
WHERE'S DOUGLAS?
>> UH, DOUG -- DOUGLAS -- IS
RUNNING A LITTLE LATE.
HE'LL BE HERE LIKE FIVE MINUTES,
TOPS.
HE -- HE SAW A DOCTOR TODAY.
SAID THERE WAS NO QUESTION THAT
HE SHOULD BE ABLE TO DO THE
TREK, SO...
>> THAT'S NOT EXACTLY WHAT HE
SAID.
>> WELL, YEAH.
I DON'T KNOW THE EXACT MEDICAL
TERMINOLOGY, OBVIOUSLY, BUT THAT
WAS THE GIST OF IT.
>> UH, DOUGLAS, WE HAVE A REFUND
POLICY.
LET ME GET YOU THE INFO, OKAY?
>> OKAY.
>> ARE YOU SERIOUS?
>> LET'S JUST SEE WHAT HE HAS TO
SAY.
>> YOU TWISTED YOUR ANKLE.
YOU'LL BE FINE.
>> THE DOCTOR SAID TO TAKE IT
EASY FOR TWO WEEKS, SEE HOW I
START TO RECOVER.
>> THE DOCTOR DOESN'T KNOW SHIT.
>> HE'S A FOOT SPECIALIST.
>> DOCTORS ALWAYS GIVE YOU THE
WORST-CASE SCENARIO, AND
EVERYTHING'S --
>> THANKS.
I THINK I'LL BE OKAY FOR NOW.
>> IT'S YOUR MONEY.
>> I FUCKING HATE THAT GUY.
>> DUDE, I HATE HIM, TOO.
>> I KNOW, SO CAN WE JUST NOT
SPEND ANY MORE TIME THINKING
ABOUT HIM THAN WE ALREADY HAVE?
>> HE'S JUST SO CONDESCENDING.
>> I KNOW. HE DOESN'T KNOW SHIT.
LET'S NOT TALK ABOUT IT.
WHY ARE WE TALKING ABOUT TROY?
TALK ABOUT TROY IN THE
AFTERNOON, NOW YOU'RE GONNA GO
OUT AT NIGHT AND TALK
ABOUT TROY?
>> I DON'T WANT TO TALK ABOUT --
HOLD ON.
[ CELLPHONE VIBRATES ]
>> CLARE?
>> YEAH.
>> WHAT DOES SHE WANT?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
SEE IF SHE LEAVES A MESSAGE.
>> SO, YOU GUYS ARE BACK
TOGETHER NOW?
>> NO, WE'RE NOT BACK TOGETHER
NOW.
>> "NO, WE'RE NOT BACK TOGETHER
NOW."
NO, OF COURSE NOT. WHATEVER.
>> ACTUALLY, I'M GOING OUT WITH
SOMEONE ELSE TOMORROW NIGHT.
>> THAT'S IT?
THAT'S ALL YOU'RE GONNA GIVE ME?
>> WHAT?
>> WHY DON'T YOU TELL ME ABOUT
HER?
OH, SHE'S BUSTED, THEN, HUH?
ARE YOU EMBARRASSED?
YOU'RE EMBARRASSED, AREN'T YOU?
YEAH, SHE'S GOT A FUCKED-UP
FACE, DOESN'T SHE?
>> NO.
>> WHERE ARE YOU GOING?
>> I'M GOING TO THE BATHROOM.
>> WELL, WHERE'D YOU MEET HER?
>> I MET HER AT THE TRACK.
>> WELL, TELL ME MORE.
COME ON.
IF I WAS DATING SOMEBODY, I'D
TELL YOU ABOUT IT.
>> YEAH, IF. IF.
>> RETARDED.
YOU WANT ANOTHER BEER?
>> NO.
>> I WASN'T GONNA BUY IT FOR YOU
ANYWAY.
HI. YOU TWO, HI.
I'LL BUY YOU GUYS BEERS IF YOU
WANT ONE.
WHATEVER.
[ CELLPHONE VIBRATES ]
>> ♪ WHERE IS THE ONE TRUE LOVE
WITH EYES THAT DANCE FOR ME? ♪
♪ I'M GOIN' HOME TODAY
♪ WHEN WILL THE STARS ALIGN FOR
ME? ♪
>> HOPE YOU HAVE FUN TONIGHT.
>> YEAH. WE'LL SEE IF SHE SHOWS.
>> YOU WANT ME TO HELP YOU WITH
SOME OF THOSE?
>> UH, NO. I'LL BE FINE. THANKS.
>> I DON'T WANT YOU TO BE LATE.
>> I'M NOT MEETING HER TILL LIKE
6:30.
REALLY, IT'S OKAY.
>> OH, ALL RIGHT.
I WANT A FULL REPORT.
>> DOUG! HI!
OH, MY GOSH.
I AM SO SORRY THAT I AM SO LATE.
HAVE YOU BEEN WAITING FOREVER?
>> NO, I JUST GOT HERE.
>> HONESTLY?
>> YEAH.
>> OH, GOD.
OKAY, GOOD, BECAUSE I JUST HAVE
HAD, LIKE, THE CRAZIEST DAY.
I'M GOING THROUGH ALL THIS SHIT
WITH MY FRIEND HALEY AND HER --
>> I'M SORRY.
>> NO, YOU KNOW WHAT?
IT'S -- IT'S NOT YOUR PROBLEM,
IS IT?
>> IF YOU WANT TO TALK ABOUT
IT...
>> UM, NO. ACTUALLY, I DON'T.
>> OKAY.
>> OKAY. SHOULD WE --
YOU'RE STILL -- OKAY.
OH, I'LL GET IT.
[ CHUCKLES ]
[ CHUCKLES NERVOUSLY ]
UM...
YEP. JUST FEELING AROUND FOR IT.
[ CELLPHONE VIBRATING ]
UM...YOU KNOW WHAT?
CAN WE JUST GO IN FOR, LIKE, A
MINUTE?
>> I'M SORRY.
>> WHY NOT?
IT'S NOT LIKE WE'RE TERRORISTS.
I MEAN, THEY CAUGHT BIN LADEN.
NO MORE TERRORISM.
[ CHUCKLES ]
>> I CAN SEE THE POOL FROM HERE.
>> NO, I JUST WANT HER TO LOOK
IN THE COMPUTER AND SEE THAT MY
NAME IS IN THE COMPUTER.
>> WE CAN COME BACK SOME OTHER
TIME.
>> NO, IT'S FINE.
THIS IS JUST RIDICULOUS.
OKAY, LOOK...ARE YOU THE
MANAGER?
>> NO.
>> WELL, CAN I SPEAK TO THE
MANAGER?
>> SORRY. SHE'S NOT HERE.
>> OH, OF COURSE NOT.
>> REALLY, IT'S FINE.
>> NO, IT'S NOT FINE.
IT BLOWS.
OH. OKAY.
[ CHUCKLES ]
I'M SORRY. I'M SORRY.
THIS IS JUST NOT MY DAY.
>> HEY, DON'T WORRY ABOUT IT.
YOU WANT TO GO GET A DRINK?
>> YEAH, I DO.
THAT SOUNDS REALLY GOOD.
[ CHUCKLES ]
>> I DON'T EVEN THINK I NEED
THIS CANE.
>> REALLY?
>> YEAH.
>> NO, I THINK YOU NEED IT.
>> NO, I NEED IT. YEAH.
>> [ LAUGHS ]
>> OH, COOL.
>> [ CLEARS THROAT ]
YEAH, NOPE. YEP, NOPE.
MNH-MNH.
>> WHAT? WHAT'S UP?
>> YEAH, THAT IS HALEY'S
BOYFRIEND, AND I JUST -- I
REALLY CAN'T DO SETH RIGHT NOW.
[ SIGHS ]
>> DO YOU WANT TO GO SOMEPLACE
ELSE?
>> YOU KNOW, I JUST FEEL LIKE
HAVING A BOTTLE OF WINE AND
WATCHING TELEVISION.
IS THAT TERRIBLE?
>> OH, OKAY.
>> BUT MY PLACE IS A -- IT'S A
BIT OF A HIKE, SO...
>> WE COULD GO TO MY PLACE IF
YOU WANT.
I MEAN, IT'S NOT TOO FAR.
I MEAN, OR WE CAN GO TO ANOTHER
BAR.
>> NO, NO, NO. OKAY.
YEAH, LET'S GO TO YOUR PLACE.
>> OKAY.
>> OKAY. LEAD THE WAY.
>> UM...I THINK WE SHOULD GO
THIS WAY, OKAY?
>> OKAY. [ LAUGHS ]
I'M KIND OF HAVING, LIKE, A
MOMENT IN MY LIFE.
LIKE, I REALLY DON'T KNOW WHAT I
WANT TO DO WITH MY LIFE, YOU
KNOW?
I FEEL LIKE SUCH A LOSER, BUT I
DON'T KNOW.
OH, NICE.
>> I KNOW.
>> YOU SURE YOU GONNA BE OKAY?
>> YEAH, I GOT IT.
>> OKAY.
>> OH, THAT FIRST DOOR OPENS
WITHOUT A KEY.
>> OH, IT DOES? OH, OKAY.
HERE. I'LL OPEN IT FOR YOU.
OH, MY GOSH.
I WAS TALKING TO THIS GUY LAST
NIGHT WHO SAID HE WAS GONNA GO
ROCK CLIMBING OR SOMETHING, AND
I WAS LIKE, "I KNOW SOMEONE
WHO'S CLIMBING K2."
THAT SHUT HIM THE FUCK UP.
[ CHUCKLES ]
>> THIS IS IT.
>> COOL.
>> LET ME JUST GET MY KEYS.
I'VE BEEN HERE LIKE --
>> OH, I GOT IT.
>> NO.
>> I GOT IT.
[ CHUCKLES ]
>> THANKS.
>> YOU'RE WELCOME.
>> AFTER YOU.
[ CHUCKLES ]
>> OH. UH...HI.
>> WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?
>> WHAT AM I DOING HERE?
WE HAD PLANS.
>> NO, WE DIDN'T.
>> I'M SORRY.
ARE -- ARE -- ARE YOU HIS
GIRLFRIEND?
>> NO.
CLARE, WE NEVER MADE PLANS.
>> YOU TEXTED ME LAST NIGHT.
>> WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
>> OKAY, YOU KNOW WHAT?
I'M JUST GONNA LET YOU GUYS WORK
IT OUT.
>> NO, NO, NO.
NO, I'M -- NO, I'M LEAVING.
>> NO, CLARE, I SWEAR TO GOD, I
NEVER TEXTED YOU.
>> OKAY.
EXCUSE ME.
>> PLEASE, JUST --
>> EXCUSE ME.
>> CLARE.
MY EX. I'M SORRY.
CAN YOU JUST HANG OUT?
>> UH...
>> I'M REALLY -- I'M REALLY
SORRY.
>> IT'S -- YEAH.
>> CLARE!
CLARE!
CLARE, PLEASE, JUST WAIT A
SECOND.
I'M NOT WITH HER, OKAY?
SHE'S JUST A FRIEND.
>> WHY DID YOU DO THIS?
>> I DIDN'T DO ANYTHING.
>> YOU TEXTED ME LAST NIGHT.
>> NO, I DIDN'T.
MITCH TEXTED YOU.
>> FROM YOUR PHONE?
>> WE WERE OUT DRINKING.
HE PROBABLY TOOK IT AT SOME
POINT.
>> WELL, WHY WOULD HE DO THAT?
>> WHY WOULD I DO THAT?
>> TO PUNISH ME.
>> PUNISH YOU?
>> I'M SORRY.
HAVE A GOOD NIGHT.
>> CLARE, PLEASE.
I'M NOT WITH HER.
SHE'S JUST A FRIEND.
WE WERE IN THE NEIGHBORHOOD, SO
WE CAME HERE.
THAT'S IT.
>> OKAY.
>> OKAY?
>> WHAT HAPPENED?
>> I WAS RUNNING, AND I FELL.
>> [ LAUGHS ]
>> I SHOULD GO.
I'LL CALL YOU, OKAY?
I'D BE SURPRISED IF SHE EVER
WANTS TO SPEAK TO ME AT THIS
POINT.
>> WELL, YOU CAN THANK ME LATER.
>> THANK YOU?
>> YOU'RE WELCOME.
>> YOU READ A TEXT FROM MY PHONE
AND RESPONDED FROM MY PHONE.
>> YEAH. YEAH.
THAT'S PROBABLY A FELONY...IN
GEORGIA.
>> SHE DIDN'T NEED THAT, MITCH.
SHE DIDN'T NEED TO COME TO MY
APARTMENT THINKING THAT I
INVITED HER AND HAVE ME WALK IN
WITH SOME GIRL.
>> AND WHAT?
WHAT? YOU GUYS AREN'T TOGETHER,
ALL RIGHT?
SHE'S GOT NO RIGHT TO BE UPSET.
>> SHE'S A HUMAN BEING.
>> [ SIGHS ]
WELL, DO YOU WANT ME TO SAY,
"I'M SORRY"?
>> NO, I DON'T.
I JUST WANT YOU TO STOP PULLING
SHIT LIKE THIS.
>> WHY DOES CLARE STILL HAVE
KEYS?
YOU NEED TO CUT THE CORD, MAN.
>> WHAT DID YOU WANT TO HAPPEN?
I MEAN, WHAT WERE YOU HOPING FOR
WHEN YOU SENT THE TEXT?
>> WHAT?! I WAS FUCKING AROUND.
IT WAS A FUCKING JOKE.
>> YEAH, WELL, IT WASN'T FUNNY.
>> I FIGURED THAT YOU'D SEE THE
TEXT OR SHE'D CALL BEFORE SHE
JUST SHOWED UP AND LET HERSELF
INTO THE APARTMENT WITH THE KEYS
THAT, APPARENTLY, YOU WON'T TAKE
BACK.
>> YOU KNOW, IF YOU'RE SO
CONCERNED WITH ME GETTING RID OF
HER, YOU'RE DOING A REALLY
SHITTY JOB HELPING ME FIND
SOMEONE ELSE.
>> LIKE THAT'S MY JOB.
>> OKAY. IS IT YOUR JOB TO
SABOTAGE WHAT I HAVE GOING ON
FOR ME?
>> WHAT DO YOU HAVE GOING ON FOR
YOU?
WHAT, YOU AND THIS OTHER CHICK?
>> SHE CAME TO MY APARTMENT.
>> [ SIGHS ]
ALL RIGHT, I'M SORRY THAT I
SCREWED THINGS UP FOR YOU AND
THIS OTHER CHICK.
>> YVONNE.
>> I OWE YOU.
OKAY?
>> THANK YOU.
>> SO, ARE YOU GONNA CALL THIS
YVONNE?
>> I DON'T THINK THAT'S REALLY
AN OPTION AT THIS POINT.
>> YOU GUYS GOT A LOT TO TALK
ABOUT.
THAT'S FOR SURE.
I'LL MAKE IT UP TO YOU.
I SAID, "I'M SORRY."
>> I COULD ACTUALLY USE SOME
HELP FINANCIALLY.
>> CLARE'S NOT HELPING WITH THE
RENT?
>> NO, IT'S MY ANKLE.
THE DEDUCTIBLE FOR THE X-RAYS
AND THE MRI WAS LIKE
1,000 BUCKS.
THINK MAYBE I COULD BORROW LIKE
$700?
>> DOUG, YOU STILL HAVEN'T PAID
ME FOR THE TICKETS.
>> BUT YOU SAID I COULD PAY YOU
AFTER.
>> WHEN? WHEN ARE YOU GONNA PAY
ME -- NEXT YEAR?
YOU'RE QUITTING YOUR JOB.
>> NO, I'M NOT.
>> YOU GOT THE TIME OFF?
>> I'M WORKING ON IT.
>> [ SCOFFS ] OKAY.
>> I'M GONNA -- I'M GONNA TAKE
OFF.
>> YOU'RE LEAVING?
>> YEAH.
>> WH-- 'CAUSE I WON'T GIVE YOU
THE MONEY?
>> NO, BECAUSE YOU'RE AN
ASSHOLE.
BILL.
>> CAN IT WAIT?
I HAVE LIKE TWO MINUTES HERE.
>> I'D PREFER IF WE COULD JUST
TALK FOR A MINUTE...
>> ALL RIGHT.
>> ...ABOUT ME TAKING TIME OFF
IN AUGUST.
>> I THOUGHT WE ALREADY
DISCUSSED THAT.
>> I UNDERSTAND, BUT I-I CAN'T
CHANGE THE DATES TO MY TRIP, AND
I'M PREPARED TO LEAVE IF
NECESSARY.
>> LEAVE?
[ CHUCKLES ]
YOU'RE GONNA QUIT?
>> I HAVEN'T ASKED FOR A
VACATION IN OVER THREE YEARS.
>> YOU CAN HAVE THE VACATION.
YOU CAN HAVE THREE WEEKS IN
SEPTEMBER.
BUT I CAN'T HAVE YOU OUT IN
AUGUST.
>> I-I'VE MADE A DECISION.
>> WHAT IS THAT SUPPOSED TO
MEAN?
>> IT MEANS THAT I'M PREPARED TO
LEAVE.
>> BECAUSE YOU CAN'T GO IN
AUGUST?
>> IT'S JUST 11 BUSINESS DAYS IN
TOTAL.
>> NO.
NO.
CAN I MAKE IT ANY CLEARER?
>> OKAY.
>> SO, YOU'RE GONNA QUIT?
>> I'LL STAY UNTIL THE END OF
JULY.
>> DOUG, THAT IS THE WORST
DECISION YOU COULD MAKE.
I TRIED TO MAKE IT CLEAR HOW
MUCH I DEPENDED ON YOU.
I GUESS THAT DIDN'T MATTER.
>> [ SIGHS ]
I THINK YOU WERE IN A HURRY WHEN
I KNOCKED.
>> MY BUS?
OH, I MISSED IT NOW -- BY A LONG
SHOT.
>> I'M SORRY.
I DIDN'T MEAN TO INCONVENIENCE
YOU.
>> YOU SAY THAT ALL THE TIME.
"I'M SORRY."
HOW SORRY ARE YOU, ANYWAY?
>> IN THIS CASE, I'M NOT THAT
SORRY, I GUESS.
>> I DIDN'T THINK SO.
>> YOU CAN FIND SOMEONE STARTING
TOMORROW.
>> SO, YOU'RE QUITTING NOW?
>> CAN I MAKE IT ANY CLEARER?
[ INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS ]
"YIN."
[ CELLPHONE VIBRATING ]
HEY.
>> HEY. I SAW YOUR UPDATE.
>> YEAH, I'M STILL PROCESSING
IT.
>> UM, ARE YOU CELEBRATING?
>> YEAH, I'M AT ESPLANADE.
>> I THINK YOU'RE GONNA BE A LOT
HAPPIER.
>> AW, THANKS.
I APPRECIATE YOU CALLING.
>> WELL, YEAH.
UM...
ARE YOU UP TO ANYTHING SATURDAY?
>> UH...TH-THIS SATURDAY?
>> I FOUND A NEW PLACE, AND I,
UM -- IF YOU DON'T MIND, I'D
REALLY APPRECIATE THE HELP
MOVING IN.
IT WON'T TAKE VERY LONG.
I DON'T HAVE THAT MUCH STUFF,
OBVIOUSLY.
>> WELL, CLARE, I DON'T KNOW HOW
MUCH HELP I CAN REALLY BE WITH
MY ANKLE.
>> YOU KNOW WHAT?
EVEN IF YOU COULD JUST WATCH THE
VAN, I'M SURE THERE'LL BE OTHER
PEOPLE HELPING WITH BOXES AND
STUFF.
I'D REALLY APPRECIATE IT.
>> OH, ALL -- WHAT TIME?
>> HOW'S 10:00?
>> OKAY.
GREAT. I'LL SEE YOU THEN --
10:00.
>> YOU WANT ANOTHER ONE?
>> UH, NO, THANKS.
>> THERE'S JUST 10 MINUTES LEFT
TO HAPPY HOUR.
>> I'M OKAY.
>> YOU SURE?
>> YEAH.
>> ALL RIGHT.
>> THANKS.
>> THANKS, DUDE.
>> ALL RIGHT, HOLD ON.
I'M -- I'M FINDING IT.
NOW IT WENT AWAY.
WHY DOES IT DO THAT?
DON'T DO THAT! WHAT?
OH, HERE IT IS.
ALL RIGHT. HOLD ON.
IT'S AT A LITTLE OVER $6,000,
AND IT MATURES NEXT, UH -- NEXT
JANUARY.
>> DOES THAT MEAN I'D HAVE TO
PAY A FINE OR SOMETHING IF I
WITHDRAW IT NOW?
>> WELL, Y-YES, DOUG.
I MEAN, IT'S A 5- YEAR CD.
>> WELL, HOW MUCH IS THE FINE?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
WHY WOULD YOU WANT TO DO THAT?
>> WELL, MITCH AND I ARE GONNA
CLIMB KILIMANJARO THIS SUMMER.
>> RIGHT, BUT YOU'RE NOT GONNA
SPEND YOUR SAVINGS TO GO CLIMB
SOME MOUNTAIN.
>> I WOULDN'T NEED ALL OF IT.
THE AIRFARE WAS AROUND $1,600 OR
SO.
>> YOU ALREADY BOUGHT THE
TICKETS?
>> YEAH.
>> YEAH, BUT YOU DON'T HAVE THE
MONEY.
>> WELL, I PREPARED A BUDGET,
BUT I WAS THROWN OFF WHEN CLARE
BACKED OUT OF HER END
OF THE RENT.
>> NO, NO, NO, NO, NO.
YOU'RE NOT GOING TO TAP INTO
THIS MONEY TO COVER
IRRESPONSIBLE PURCHASES THAT YOU
MADE, RIGHT?
BECAUSE YOUR MOTHER AND I HAVE
SET THIS MONEY ASIDE SO THAT
WHEN YOU WANT TO BUY A HOUSE,
YOU'LL HAVE HELP WITH THE DOWN
PAYMENT.
THAT'S WHAT WE DID WITH KEITH
AND KELLY, RIGHT?
THAT'S HOW THEY GOT THE HOUSE
THAT THEY'RE IN.
>> ALL RIGHT, I UNDERSTAND THAT.
>> NO, YOU DON'T UNDERSTAND.
LET ME MAKE THIS SIMPLE FOR YOU.
I'M A COSIGNER, AND I AM NOT
GOING TO LET YOU CASH THE CD.
>> HEY, MAN.
>> YO.
>> THANKS FOR HELPING OUT
WITH THIS.
>> YEAH, MAN.
YOU KNOW, THAT'S WHAT ASSHOLES
DO FOR EACH OTHER.
>> HEY, I GOT THE RING IN THE
BAG HERE.
I WANT YOU TO TAKE A LOOK AT IT
FIRST.
>> I'M GOING INTO THE NEXT ONE
ALONE, YOU UNDERSTAND?
>> YEAH. WE'RE NOT GONNA SELL IT
FOR LESS THAN $1,000.
>> I KNOW -- I KNOW THAT.
THE GUY'S JUST -- HE'S
LOWBALLING US.
YOU JUST -- YOU LEAVE IT TO ME.
>> ALL RIGHT. I'M JUST SAYING.
MITCH, COME HERE.
LOOK AT THIS.
>> NO, NO, NO.
WE'RE NOT GOING IN A PLACE LIKE
THIS, I'M TELLING YOU.
YOU FIND A SMALL LITTLE HOLE IN
THE WALL.
>> YOU SURE ABOUT THIS?
>> I'M POSITIVE.
>> ALL RIGHT.
I'M -- I'M LISTENING TO YOU.
WHAT? WHAT DID HE SAY?
>> YOU READY FOR THIS?
$2,200 CASH.
>> HOLY SHIT.
>> I TALKED HIM UP FROM $1,500.
>> [ SIGHS ]
WELL, LET'S GET SOME LUNCH AND
TALK ABOUT IT.
>> DOUG, DOUG, $2,200 CASH.
LET'S GO.
>> WHERE'S THE RING?
>> IT'S UPSTAIRS.
>> YOU LEFT THE RING UPSTAIRS
WITH THIS GUY?
[ SIGHS ]
YOU SHOULD LEAVE THE REST OF
THIS STUFF IN THE HALLWAY FOR
NOW.
>> [ SIGHS ]
>> WHAT?
>> WELL, IT'S JUST THAT SHE TOLD
ME I COULDN'T GET IN TILL TODAY,
AND NOW SHE'S SAYING I CAN'T PUT
MY STUFF IN THE HALLWAY SO I CAN
PAINT.
>> PAINT'S NOT THAT BAD.
I'M NOT MOVING ANYTHING BACK
INTO THE VAN.
>> OBVIOUSLY.
ALL RIGHT, LET'S JUST GET OUT OF
HERE.
I FEEL LIKE I CAN'T BREATHE.
>> OH, YEAH.
COULD YOU DROP ME OFF AT THE
SUBWAY?
>> I'M GOING TO RETURN THE VAN,
AND THEN I'M TAKING YOU TO
DINNER.
>> AW, IT'S FINE.
>> NO, NO.
YOU SPEND YOUR WHOLE DAY
HELPING ME.
>> NO, REALLY.
I APPRECIATE IT, BUT IT'S ALL
RIGHT.
>> LOOK, I THINK I MIGHT HAVE
JUST MOVED IN WITH, LIKE, A
TOTAL BITCH, AND I JUST WANT TO
GO TO DINNER.
>> WELL, YOU SHOULD.
>> OKAY.
I'LL DROP YOU AT THE TRAIN.
>> I'M JUST TIRED.
LET'S HAVE DINNER SOME NIGHT
THIS WEEK, MAYBE.
>> PLEASE DON'T.
>> WHAT?
>> YOU KNOW, IF YOU DON'T WANT
TO SPEND TIME WITH ME, THAT'S
FINE.
>> CLARE, I SPENT ALL DAY WITH
YOU.
>> I'M SORRY IT WAS SUCH A
TORTURE.
>> I WANTED TO HELP YOU.
I DON'T UNDERSTAND WHY YOU'RE
FIGHTING WITH ME.
>> I KNOW. I'M SORRY.
I DON'T KNOW.
I'LL TAKE YOU TO THE TRAIN.
>> I MEAN, NOW YOU'RE PISSED AT
ME.
>> WELL, YEAH, 'CAUSE I DON'T
KNOW WHAT IT IS YOU WANT.
I DON'T KNOW IF YOU THINK WE'RE
JUST FRIENDS.
BUT MORE THAN THAT SOMETIMES?
I'M FEELING A LITTLE LOST HERE.
>> I WANT TO STAY FRIENDS.
I WANT TO SEE YOU.
I JUST DON'T WANT TO GET BACK
TOGETHER.
I DON'T THINK THAT WILL EVER
WORK.
>> YEAH.
THANK YOU FOR MAKING THAT CLEAR.
>> I'M SORRY. I SHOULD GO.
>> I'LL TAKE YOU TO THE TRAIN.
>> I WANT TO WALK.
>> OH, YEAH.
AW, THIS IS SOME REALLY GOOD
SHIT.
ALL RIGHT?
SO, WE'LL HAVE A LITTLE BIT OF
THIS, AND THEN, UH, WE'LL GO
OVER TO SOME NYU BARS.
YEAH?
>> UH, NO.
>> NO, COME ON, MAN.
NO. NO, NO, NO.
WE'LL GO TO FIT. DONE.
YEAH, WE'LL GO DOWN THERE, MEET
SOME FIT GIRLS.
>> NOT TONIGHT, MAN.
>> REALLY?
ARE YOU SHITTING ME?
ALL RIGHT, FINE.
>> WHERE'D YOU GET THIS?
>> I, UH -- OH, ONE OF OUR
LONDON V.P.s GAVE A BOTTLE TO
EACH ONE OF THE GUYS AT THE
DESK.
IT'S LIKE $300 SCOTCH.
TO FUCKING THE PAIN AWAY.
>> TO KILI.
>> OKAY, TO KILI. ALL RIGHT.
UGH!
>> DAMN.
>> AW, YEAH! FEEL THAT?
>> HEY, DO YOU HAVE ANY CIGARS?
>> YES! I HAVE -- YES, I --
DOUG, THAT IS A FANTASTIC IDEA,
DOUG!
[ MID-TEMPO MUSIC PLAYS ]
>> TELL ME SOMETHING ABOUT
YOURSELF THAT THIS RESUME
DOESN'T TELL ME.
>> INTEGRITY IS VERY IMPORTANT
TO OUR CULTURE.
TELL ME ABOUT A TIME THAT YOU
EMBRACED INTEGRITY.
>> THANKS FOR COMING IN.
SOMEONE FROM OUR OFFICE WILL BE
IN TOUCH.
>> GREAT. UH, THANK YOU.
[ CELLPHONE VIBRATING ]
HEY, MAN.
>> HEY, BIG NEWS.
>> WHAT'S UP?
>> I'M MOVING TO HONG KONG.
>> WHAT?
>> YEAH. I FOUND THERE WAS AN
OPENING AT OUR HONG KONG DESK,
AND -- BOOM -- I'M GOING.
BEST NEWS IS THEY'RE GONNA GIVE
ME THIS BIG, FAT-ASS BONUS CHECK
FOR GOING OVERSEAS AND THEY'RE
GONNA PUT ME UP RENT-FREE FOR
SIX MONTHS.
>> THAT'S GREAT, MAN.
CONGRATULATIONS.
>> THANKS, MAN. THANK YOU.
UH, THERE'S ONLY ONE DOWNSIDE,
THOUGH.
UM...OBVIOUSLY, I GOT TO BAIL ON
KILI.
BUT, YOU KNOW, I GOT TO DO THIS,
MAN.
>> YEAH.
WELL, IT SOUNDS LIKE AN AMAZING
OPPORTUNITY.
>> YEAH, THANK YOU.
IT IS. IT IS. I'M PSYCHED.
I'M SO PSYCHED.
>> THAT'S AWESOME.
>> YEAH. I NEED SOME, LIKE,
SAMURAI-WARRIOR GEAR, PRONTO.
>> YEAH, MAYBE I CAN COME VISIT
YOU.
>> YEAH.
I'M GONNA CHOP SOME PEOPLE UP.
>> YEAH, IT'S -- THAT'S AWESOME.
I'M HAPPY FOR YOU.
>> CHONG CHING CHOCA-CHAW-CHAW!
[ LAUGHS ]
>> [ SIGHS ]
>> [ LAUGHS ]
DOUG!
HI.
>> HI.
>> [ CHUCKLES ]
ARE YOU COMING HERE?
>> I'M, UH -- YEAH.
I'M MEETING SOMEONE HERE FOR A
DRINK IN A BIT.
>> OH, COOL.
>> HEY, MAN.
>> HEY. I'M -- I'M DOUG.
>> SETH.
>> [ CHUCKLES ]
>> SO, YOU DIDN'T SAY ANYTHING?
>> NO, BABE. I WAS --
>> OH, IT WAS NICE TO MEET YOU.
>> YEAH.
>> OKAY, BYE.
>> SHE SAID...
[ UP-TEMPO ROCK MUSIC PLAYING ]
[ CELLPHONE RINGS ]
>> HEY.
>> HI, DOUG.
HEY, LISTEN, I'M GONNA PUT YOU
ON THE SPEAKERPHONE -- OKAY? --
'CAUSE I'M HERE WITH MOM.
HOLD ON.
CAN YOU HEAR ME?
>> YEAH.
>> HI, HONEY.
>> HEY, MOM.
>> SO, UH, YOU KNOW, WE HAVEN'T
HEARD FROM YOU IN A WHILE.
>> I KNOW. I'M SORRY.
I'VE BEEN A LITTLE BUSY LATELY.
>> THAT'S GOOD.
>> KEITH SAID HE SAW ON YOUTUBE
THAT YOU QUIT YOUR JOB.
>> UH, FACEBOOK, DAD.
>> UH-HUH.
SO, IT -- IT'S TRUE?
>> YEAH. IT IS.
>> THAT'S...BIG NEWS.
>> YEAH.
>> WHAT BROUGHT THIS ON?
>> AN ARGUMENT WITH BILL.
>> AN ARGUMENT? ABOUT WHAT?
>> ABOUT ME TAKING TIME OFF THIS
SUMMER.
>> TO GO TO AFRICA?
>> YEAH, THAT WAS PART OF IT.
>> WELL, WHAT DID HE SAY?
>> A LOT OF THINGS.
LISTEN, CAN I JUST CALL YOU GUYS
LATER?
>> WELL, NO, NO.
WHAT ARE YOU GONNA DO?
>> WELL, I'M GONNA FIND ANOTHER
JOB, DAD.
>> YOU KNOW THAT'S GONNA BE KIND
OF ROUGH WHEN YOUR PAST EMPLOYER
OF SEVEN YEARS WON'T WRITE YOU A
RECOMMENDATION.
>> I REALIZE THAT, DAD.
>> HOW ARE YOU GONNA PAY FOR
YOUR TRIP?
>> WELL, THIS WILL UPSET YOU
GUYS, PROBABLY...
BUT I S-SOLD THE RING THAT
GRANDFATHER GAVE ME, AND I'M
USING THAT MONEY TO PAY FOR THE
TRIP.
>> THAT WAS A STUPID THING TO
DO, DOUG!
OKAY? THAT WAS A STUPID,
SELFISH, SELFISH THING TO DO.
>> THE RING WAS A GIFT TO ME.
>> IT WAS NOT A GIFT.
IT WASN'T A GIFT!
IT'S YOUR GRANDMOTHER'S RING!
OKAY?
THAT WAS GIVEN TO YOU WITH THE
UNDERSTANDING THAT YOU WOULD
GIVE IT TO SOMEONE SPECIAL,
SOMEBODY YOU CARED ABOUT THAT
YOU WANTED TO MAKE PART OF THIS
FAMILY.
YOU KNOW, THAT'S WHY YOU WERE
GIVEN SOMETHING THAT WAS PART OF
THIS FAMILY!
>> OKAY, DOUG, WE'RE GONNA CALL
YOU BACK LATER.
>> NO, WE'RE NOT.
YOU FUCKED UP, DOUG.
YOU FUCKED UP.
>> DAD, I UNDERSTAND
WHY YOU'RE UPSET --
>> NO, NO.
THIS IS THE WORST THING YOU
COULD HAVE DONE.
[ INTERCOM RINGS ]
>> HELLO?
>> HI. I NEED TO COME IN.
>> OKAY.
[ DOOR BUZZES ]
WHAT'S WRONG?
MUST BE PRETTY SERIOUS IF YOU'RE
WILLING TO COME TO ME ABOUT IT.
>> I HAVE TO COME TO YOU.
CONGRATULATIONS.
>> REALLY?
>> NO. I'M FUCKING JOKING.
>> WHEN DID YOU FIND OUT?
>> FOR SURE YESTERDAY.
YOU LOOK EVEN MORE DISAPPOINTED
THAN MY MOM.
>> I'M -- I'M SORRY.
I'M JUST SURPRISED.
WHAT DID YOUR MOM SAY?
>> THAT I WAS A FUCK-UP,
BASICALLY.
>> DID SHE ACTUALLY SAY THAT TO
YOU?
>> WHAT ELSE WOULD SHE SAY --
"GOOD JOB?"
>> HAVE YOU TOLD ANYONE ELSE?
HAVE YOU THOUGHT ABOUT WHAT YOU
WANT TO DO?
>> OF COURSE.
I CAN'T.
[ SIGHS ]
YOU HAVE NOTHING TO SAY?
>> THIS IS A BIG SURPRISE,
OBVIOUSLY.
I CAN'T SAY THAT I'M NOT SCARED,
IN A WAY.
BUT IF THIS IS HOW IT'S GONNA
BE, THEN THIS IS HOW IT'S GONNA
BE.
YOU'RE NOT A FUCK-UP.
YOUR MOM'S A BITCH.
>> NO, SHE'S RIGHT.
>> NO, SHE'S NOT RIGHT.
[ SIGHS ]
HERE.
>> THANK YOU.
>> IS IT JUST ONE OF THOSE
THINGS WITH YOU BEING ON BIRTH
CONTROL?
DID THE DOCTOR SAY ANYTHING?
>> I HAD MISSED A FEW DAYS.
I DIDN'T GET IT REFILLED BECAUSE
WE HAD BROKEN UP AND I DIDN'T
WANT TO KEEP TAKING IT, YOU
KNOW?
I ALSO DIDN'T THINK THAT
ANYTHING WOULD HAPPEN THAT
NIGHT.
IT WAS LIKE TWO DAYS.
>> YOU THINK SHE'S LYING?
>> NO.
>> HERE.
>> THANKS, MAN.
>> YEAH.
>> AND YOU REALLY BELIEVE THAT
SHE DIDN'T DO THIS SHIT ON
PURPOSE?
>> YEAH. I DO.
>> THEN SHE -- SHE'S COMPLETELY
IRRESPONSIBLE.
THAT IS SO FUCKED.
>> WELL, I PLAYED A PART, AS
WELL.
>> NO, NO.
YOU [CLICKS TONGUE] BUT UNDER
THE IMPRESSION THAT SHE'S ON
BIRTH CONTROL.
>> THIS ISN'T SOMETHING SHE
WANTED.
>> SHE WANTS IT ENOUGH TO KEEP
IT.
WHERE ARE MY SMOKES?
YEAH, ALL RIGHT.
DOUG, JUST BECAUSE SHE'S
PREGNANT DOESN'T MEAN THAT YOU
HAVE TO GIVE UP EVERYTHING ELSE
IN YOUR LIFE.
>> NO, I UNDERSTAND.
>> AND IT DOESN'T MEAN THAT YOU
GUYS HAVE TO GET BACK TOGETHER,
EITHER.
>> NO, I KNOW.
>> THIS IS THE 21st CENTURY,
MAN.
THIS IS HOW IT WORKS NOW.
>> YEAH, WELL, WHAT DO YOU
SUGGEST?
YOU'RE AN EXPERT ON
RELATIONSHIPS.
>> [ CHUCKLES ]
WELL...GO TO TANZANIA.
YOU DISAPPEAR INTO THE JUNGLE.
FUCK IT, RIGHT?
LEARN HOW TO HUNT BOAR.
I DON'T KNOW.
I REALLY DON'T KNOW.
>> IT DOES CHANGE THINGS.
OTHER STUFF SEEMS LESS IMPORTANT
NOW.
>> LISTEN, MAN...
WHAT IF THERE WAS NO BABY?
TAKE THE BABY OUT OF THE
EQUATION.
THIS IS THE REST OF YOUR LIFE.
IS THIS WHAT YOU WANT?
[ CELLPHONE VIBRATING ]
IS THAT HER?
DON'T ANSWER IT.
DON'T ANSWER THE PHONE.
>> NO.
>> YOU'RE HOPELESS, MAN.
>> IT'S MY PARENTS.
>> OH. I'M GOING OUTSIDE.
I'M GONNA GO SMOKE.
>> HEY.
>> DOUG, HONEY...
UM...I'M AFRAID WE'VE HAD SOME
BAD NEWS.
THE NURSING HOME CALLED.
>> IN OUR CONVERSATIONS, I
LEARNED SO MUCH ABOUT THE
COMMUNITY THAT I HAD JUST COME
TO CALL HOME BUT WHICH HE HAD
KNOWN ALL HIS LIFE.
I SAW THE SELFLESSNESS OF A MAN
WHO HAD LEFT COLLEGE WHEN HIS
FATHER'S ACCIDENT MEANT THAT HE
WAS NEEDED TO RUN THE STORE, WHO
LEFT HOME WHEN HIS NATION CALLED
HIM TO FACE ITS ENEMIES ACROSS
THE PACIFIC.
HE WAS A MAN WHO ALWAYS PUT THE
NEEDS OF HIS FAMILY FIRST.
THAT WAS THE MILTON SR. THAT I
MET, THE MAN SO MANY OF YOU CALL
"FRIEND," "FATHER,
"GRANDFATHER."
>> [ CHUCKLES ]
GOOD BOY.
[ SIGHS ]
>> HEY.
>> WERE YOU JUST, UH, GETTING
SOME AIR?
>> YEAH.
>> I, UH -- I THOUGHT IT WAS A
GOOD SERVICE.
>> YEAH, IT WAS.
>> SO...HOW ARE THINGS IN
NEW YORK?
>> GOOD, YOU KNOW?
YEAH.
>> ANYTHING HAPPENING ON THE JOB
FRONT OR, UH...
>> I HAVE A SECOND INTERVIEW
NEXT WEEK.
>> REALLY?
>> GETTING SHOTS ON TUESDAY FOR
MY TRIP.
>> YEAH.
SO, WHAT'S YOUR, UH -- WHAT'S
YOUR SECOND INTERVIEW?
>> WITH A SMALL IMPRINT.
THEY PUT OUT FOREIGN-POLICY
TITLES.
>> THAT SOUNDS INTERESTING.
>> YEAH, WE'LL SEE.
>> GIVEN THE POSSIBILITIES, WE
NEED TO ENLARGE OUR TEAM.
>> IT'S NOT A TEMPORARY
INCREASE.
>> NO. IT WOULD BE A PERMANENT
POSITION.
>> GREAT.
>> RIGHT.
WELL, UM...SO, IF WE WERE TO
OFFER YOU THE JOB, COULD YOU --
COULD YOU START IN TWO WEEKS?
>> TWO WEEKS?
>> YEAH.
>> UM...I BELIEVE I MENTIONED
BEFORE IN MY FIRST INTERVIEW
THAT, UNFORTUNATELY, I HAVE
TRAVEL PLANS NEXT MONTH.
BUT I COULD START SEPTEMBER 1st
OR MAYBE A FEW DAYS BEFORE.
I RETURN ON THE 28th.
>> DOUG, YOU KNOW THE
PARTICULARS OF YOUR TRIP, OF
COURSE.
WE DON'T.
BUT I THINK THE SALARY IS
COMPETITIVE, AND IT WOULD BE A
PROMOTION.
>> PLUS YOU'D HAVE FOUR WEEKS'
PAID VACATION THAT YOU COULD
START CLAIMING IN SIX MONTHS.
>> WE HAVE SEVERAL TITLES GOING
TO PRESS IN LATE AUGUST, AND
WE'D LOVE TO BRING YOU INTO THE
PROCESS AS SOON AS POSSIBLE.
>> THANK YOU.
I APPRECIATE THE OFFER, BUT I
CAN'T ACCEPT.
>> OKAY, WELL --
[ CHUCKLES ]
ALL RIGHT.
UM, WELL, YOU TELL US, DOUG.
WHAT WOULD MAKE IT WORTH IT FOR
YOU?
>> WELL, I'M NOT TRYING TO ASK
FOR MORE MONEY.
THIS TRIP IS VERY IMPORTANT TO
ME.
IT MAY BE THE LAST TIME I GET TO
DO SOMETHING LIKE THIS FOR A
WHILE.
>> PAID VACATION, SIX MONTHS.
JUST PUSH YOUR TRIP BACK A
LITTLE.
WE REALLY WANT YOU TO JOIN US
HERE, DOUG.
SO...
[ CELLPHONE VIBRATES ]
[ INDISTINCT CONVERSATIONS ]
>> [ SIGHS ]
>> OH, MY GOODNESS.
>> YEP. THIS IS THE LIVING ROOM
AND THE KITCHEN.
>> WOW.
>> THAT IS -- THAT'S AN
INCREDIBLE VIEW.
>> SO, THIS IS THE BEDROOM, OF
COURSE.
>> COMPARED TO YOUR LAST PLACE,
THIS IS LIKE NIGHT AND DAY.
>> OH, YOU HAVE A MASTER BATH,
TOO.
THAT'S GREAT.
>> YEAH.
>> I'M GONNA GO CHECK ON THE
GRILL.
>> IT'S REALLY NICE.
>> YEAH.
>> THANKS.
>> ARE YOU GONNA PAINT?
>> HEY.
MAN, THIS IS GREAT.
I MEAN, YOU FOUND A GREAT PLACE.
>> YEAH, WE'RE RENTING IT FROM
MITCH.
>> WHERE IS HE?
>> HONG KONG.
>> OH, RIGHT. RIGHT.
ANYWAY, CHEERS.
>> CHEERS.
>> YOU KNOW, DOUG, I-I, UM...
I'M REALLY PROUD OF YOU.
YOU KNOW, YOUR MOTHER IS, TOO.
WE'RE BOTH REALLY HAPPY FOR THE
WAY THINGS ARE GOING FOR YOU.
IT'S A BEAUTIFUL VIEW.
>> ♪ OH, BE NOT AFRAID
♪ OH, BE NOT AFRAID
♪ TROUBLE CAME, THERE'S NO
SURPRISE ♪
♪ FALLING DOWN FROM UP HIGH
♪ OH, BE NOT AFRAID
♪ A DREAM TO FOLLOW, A BECKONING
STAR ♪
♪ WALKED SO LONG
♪ OH, BE NOT AFRAID
♪ I HEARD THUNDER AND RAIN COME
DOWN ♪
♪ AND I SAW THE DEVIL IN EVERY
CLOUD ♪
♪ I DREAMED I WAS SLEEPING, IT
FIT ME SO WELL ♪
♪ I DREAMED I WAS GOD, AND IT
WORRIED ME STILL ♪
♪ OH, BE NOT AFRAID
[ SONG ENDS ]
[ MID-TEMPO MUSIC PLAYING ]
>> [ WHISTLING ]
[ MUSIC CONTINUES ]
[ MUSIC STOPS ]