GUY: When we see
a God-like face or form,
we are amazed.
"When we see a God-like
face or form, we are amazed."
When we see a God-like
face or form, we are amazed.
Amazed.
Because it reminds us
of our own God-like nature!
DOUG:
Anyone sitting here?
Uh, what?
Oh, no.
No, no. Be my guest.
Aah.
Oh, oh, oh.
[ Burps ]
Oh.
Hot.
What?
It's hot.
A hot day.
[ Burps ]
Nothing like a good burp.
Yes. Yes -- yes, it's hot.
What do you think?
What?
Oh, the new condos?
Nice. Expensive.
Ah.
Only half a mill each,
give or take a few hundred thou.
You want a swig?
No. Thank you.
Donut?
Donut. Uh, no.
Cold cut?
No.
Thank you.
Mm-mm-mm.
Ick.
Now, that's a big sucker, huh?
How'd you like to get your mouth
around something like--?
No.
Thank you.
You know,
donuts aren't good for you.
And that sandwich isn't either.
Cold cuts? Do you realize
how dead that food is?
Does your wife fix your lunch?
She's gone vegetarian.
You know -- "ommm."
All that New Age crap.
I say, "A man -- a man eats meat."
She says, "Real men
don't need to eat at all."
And I say, "Oh, see,
now they got you brainwashed
into thinking we're angels
instead of people."
I mean, who can fly after eating
something like this, right?
It's like a rock in your gut.
But in my line of work,
I need something to...
...hold me down.
You know,
meat's not good for you.
And consuming it
sure isn't good for the animals.
Your wife's right.
Gita? Not my wife.
That's not even her real name.
It's her "spiritual" name.
We're so different.
Plato would call that
the law of attraction.
Well, that figures.
She's very attractive.
No, it's not that simple.
Once we were all
this perfect being.
Then we broke up into pieces,
like a jigsaw puzzle.
Life is about those pieces
fitting themselves back together.
Cool.
I fit with Gita because she's great.
We're having a baby. A boy.
-We checked with the... radar thing.
-Yeah.
I've just never been able
to figure out
why she was attracted to me
in the first place.
We are attracted to things
that remind us of when we were
the one perfect being.
There's no explaining it.
Some people love sushi.
It makes me gag.
You got a special guy you fit with?
What?
It's cool. A lot of gays
live around here.
Oh.
I mean, this -- this part of town.
At least that's what some
of the guys at work told me.
That's what all you macho guys
talk about?
No, hey, it's cool.
It's not like it used to be.
Everybody talks about it.
It's on television. You know.
The male body's
the "in" thing, right?
I hear a guy can get a blow job
real easy around here.
I wouldn't know.
You wouldn't ?
No.
What?
I just figured.
You were gay.
Ohh.
Oh, and I suppose you figured
if you walked into those bushes
over there,
I'd follow you
with my tongue hanging out.
Actually....
Then go. See what happens.
The best you'll get is
a tick on your dick.
Of all the arrogant....
Well, what can we expect
from a meat-eating,
animal-killing, impregnator?
You're no doubt a Republican?
I'm sorry. I just figured....
And why, pray tell,
did you figure that?
Here it is,
the hottest day of the year.
Everything's melting,
and you're sitting here all... cool,
like you come
from another world.
Got your white sneakers on.
Not a scuff on them.
T-shirt that says, "Plant a Tree."
"I reserve the right to..."
What?
Oh, "arm bears."
That's good.
I bet your place is like
a cool green valley, isn't it?
Green curtains, green rugs,
green bedspreads,
toilet paper, poodle dogs --
all dyed to match.
No dogs.
You've got some nerve.
Hey, when a guy looks at a guy
the way you looked at me--
Oh, as if you weren't posing?
A beer in your crotch.
[ Sighs ]
Plato would not be happy with me.
"Just say love" is not working.
What?
The theory is that
what we are is love.
But we forget that,
and wind up looking around
for something we already have.
So to avoid getting hung up
on whatever attracts us,
we just say "love."
It's a mnemonic device.
Something that helps us remember.
Life is like a photograph,
and "Just say love" helps us
keep it in focus.
That sounds like something
Gita's learning in her yoga.
So, she's not your wife?
She said she won't marry me
till I'm free of my addiction.
What?
Me. I'm ... horny all the time.
Yeah. She says some people
high up in her yoga
only have sex to have a baby.
She says we shouldn't
spend energy on pleasures
that have to be repeated all the time
in order to get the pleasure.
I say, that's the whole point, right?
Get it as often as you can.
Gita tells me I'm stuck.
I tell her she's crazy.
I think I'm like you.
Maybe it's because
we both have the penis.
What? You think gay guys
don't have penises?
I never thought about that part.
-What part do you think of?
-Head.
Ohh, head.
So this is one of those
very serendipitous meetings.
Two people who are exactly
what the other is looking for.
Perfect fit.
I don't think that's the kind of fit
Plato's talking about.
Would make
the perfect fantasy though.
What?
Really!
This? Really?
I'm filthy. I'm all sweaty.
I probably don't smell too good.
My jeans are all worn out...
...in certain places.
-How can this be?
-I...
...haven't a clue.
I bet your hair is all curly ringlets
with perspiration.
Really? Is it?
Your other hair.
My other hair?
Your "other" hair.
My "other" hair.
I could blow on it.
Make it cool.
Blow on it? You want to...
...dry my hair?
I live just a couple of--
[ Whispering ]
Just say love. Just say love.
Look, I see this for what it is --
a fleeting infatuation.
It was interesting.
Thanks.
He's wrong, you know.
Wrong?
Plato.
[ Scoffs ]
Are you trying to rationalize Plato?
He says we must see the attraction
for what it is
and go beyond consummation.
Sublimate the physical desire
to the more noble and sublime.
That's when you discover
other pleasures.
I bet that's what your friend Gita
is trying to tell you.
The yogis teach
the same thing as Plato --
you abstain from expelling energy
on the lower level
and channel it upwards
to the higher.
Yeah, I still think he's wrong.
So is she.
Do you remember
"Snow White and the Seven Dwarfs" ?
Yeah, I thought
that was Walt Disney.
All right.
The witch gives Snow White....
An apple.
And she makes it all nice and red.
Delicious.
"Attractive." But....
But it put Snow White to sleep.
Plato says we're asleep right now
because of the things
we're attracted to --
we get caught up in them.
But sometimes another piece
of the puzzle comes along.
-The prince!
-Yes!
And we wake up,
and we're all happy and excited.
-And horny.
-Yes!
No.
No, I don't think Plato
is talking about "horny."
Look. Okay, it says right here.
Um... okay.
"When we see something
that reminds us of our true self,
we are amazed,
and a shudder runs through us."
Shudder.
[ Shudders ]
Horny.
[ Whispering ]
Just say love.
Just say love. Just say love.
You see, that's --
that doesn't work.
Just say love
doesn't work if -- if....
If?
If ya gotta take a leak,
ya gotta take a leak!
-That's a biological necessity.
-So is this.
Us meeting.
There's no love, just need.
A purely physical act
with no emotion attached.
A doctor curing a patient.
One human being helping another.
It's a duty, really.
Well....
If we've gotta go, we've gotta go.
-Oh, listen, listen.
-What?
Ah, I know you have this... fantasy.
A gourmet would say,
"It's not the portion,
it's the presentation."
That -- I'm not --
that's not what I'm talking about.
Then what?
I have a....
-I have a tattoo.
-Yeah, I know.
No, I have -- I have "another" tattoo.
Oh?
Where?
Just above that "other" hairline.
[ Gasps ]
DOUG:
No AlDS, right, or nothing?
I mean, it's just me and Gita,
and now with the baby coming....
GUY:
Then why are you doing this?
DOUG:
I don't know.
I saw you sitting there,
and you reminded me of when....
I don't know, like we've met before.
How about some iced tea ?
It's green iced tea.
Actually I'm --
I'm kinda on a time schedule.
Yeah, right.
You got a nice place.
Thanks.
What is it, a museum?
Look at all these paintings.
They're mine.
I figured. Your apartment.
No, I mean, I painted them.
Really?
An artist. Cool.
You make a living?
Oh, no, no. Not with these.
No, um....
I do mostly freelance work
for lawyers, small businesses --
stuff like that.
Well, they're nice.
All those swirly colors.
Gita would like them a lot.
Me -- It's sorta like, you know,
someone talking to me
with words I gotta look up
in a dictionary.
I like things I know --
people, animals.
But these are -- these are very nice.
You really think so?
How you gonna sell them if you
don't believe in them yourself?
All right.
Well, look at this one.
It's a tornado, right, with the sun
in the middle shining through?
It's called "Falling in Love."
Really?
Yeah.
Yeah, I guess that's ...
...how it is.
Just go for it, man.
Just bring 'em into a store,
and they'll start selling.
-I'm not sure.
-Well, your call.
-Can I use your john?
-Yeah.
You know, I've -- I've never done
people and animals.
-Where's the cat?
-Huh?
Kitty litter box in here.
Ahh.
You know, she died
a few days ago.
I just had her cremated.
She was old. I expected it.
I just can't bring myself
to get rid of her things.
Her turds?
Those have a special meaning
for you, do they?
Yeah, I know, um....
Trash collection's tomorrow.
Ahh, it's cool.
Cinderella.
Yeah, she was given to me
when I was a kid.
We-- Oh!
We kinda grew up together.
You gonna get another one?
I don't know.
So....
Look, um....
Maybe this wasn't such a good idea.
It just -- it felt more natural
out there in the park, ya know?
-Is it money?
-What?
Money?
You want to be paid?
[ Laughs ]
No.
You?
Well, it's your call.
I got a few minutes,
then it's back to pounding nails.
[ Thud ]
It's heavy.
You should try lugging it up ladders
50 feet in the air.
I-I really don't know.
Your move.
I've never let a guy
touch me like this before.
It's okay.
My God!
I've been working... hard.
I must look raunchy.
You look okay.
Okay?
-Shall we go?
-Your place or mine?
Yeah.
Uh, listen. If you ever do
come to my place,
remember to knock
'cause the bell doesn't work.
Why don't we just, you know,
if we're here, we're here?
We'll keep it loose, okay?
Yeah, okay.
So, guy, what's your name anyway?
Uh, that's it.
"Anyway?"
Guy. My name is Guy.
Oh, okay. Guy what?
Okay, it's really Quido.
Quido Salvatore.
Italian?
Mom's Irish.
-Yeah.
Well, do you want to know mine?
I -- I-I can read it on your belt.
Doug Carpenter.
Oh.
That's Doug is a carpenter.
My name is English.
Oh? What is it?
English. Doug English.
Oh. Oh, I get it.
Shall we go?
It's your picnic.
-So, Sal.
-No, don't , okay?
Never Quido and no Sal.
That's what the kids
all through high school called me --
Sal, short for Sally.
It's cool.
Okay, no Sal.
Actually, uh....
They were envious.
See, nobody, could
jump-rope "peppers"
faster or longer than I could --
even the older kids.
Oh, no, no. There was this one girl.
My best friend actually.
We thought we were soulmates
till her parents moved away.
She could jump just as good.
Look, don't call me Sal,
and I won't call you...
...muffin.
Muffin?
English... muffin.
-That's good. Good.
-Yeah.
-Shall we?
-Like I said, it's your--
I know. It's my picnic.
Mmm! This is good!
Lentil. No dairy, no animal.
Three above-ground vegetables
for each one below.
You know what's gross?
Ever since I've been eating
your cookin'
I go to the bathroom better.
Like, clean.
Yes.
Gita says my skin looks healthier,
and she's been wondering why
I'm eating her food all of a sudden.
I told her I'm picking up vibes
from when she meditates.
Well, when your eliminations
are healthy,
you are more pure and receptive
because your cleaning out
your colon.
This is a shitty conversation.
[ Laughs ]
No.
Improper eating,
like those sandwiches you buy,
load the colon with toxins.
Eating that dead food is like
not putting out your garbage.
It rots -- stench, putrefaction.
No, imagine.
Pounds of toxic waste in your gut.
Then the intestines pick that up,
and they absorb it
into your system --
into your blood -- your brain!
Now, imagine your brain
swimming around in all that crap,
trying to what, remember the good
so we can remind each other
of who we really are?
It's like putting a TV antenna
in the closet --
the reception's lousy.
We're the antennas,
and we're always receiving signals
from the universal wisdom station.
But the blocked up colon
makes us deaf -- spiritually.
Hey, that's why churches have
tall steeples. God's antenna.
Hm.
You want more?
Yeah.
So, like having wax in our ears,
we got shit built up in our systems?
Exactly.
This is so good.
You looking at me?
Why not?
Why?
You know why.
All right, tell me honest....
Was I a disappointment?
First time you, you know,
saw... "it" ?
You are preoccupied with how
you measure up to other guys.
What other guys?
Guys.
You're not seeing other guys.
Oh?
This is supposed to be clean.
It's just me and Gita
and a baby coming.
-I thought you were clean.
-I am clean.
And besides,
you're not doing anything risky.
You do other guys?
Yeah, and they do me.
Gay guys?
-That's worse!
-Worse?
Yeah. At least with straight guys,
they're not doing
a lot of messing around,
taking chances.
Whoa. And who's straight?
Me! Me!
Honest. I'm just trying
to be level here.
I believe you are.
So, uh... what if Gita
is fooling around?
She wouldn't .
Pieces of the puzzle
attracting each other.
Naw. She....
No.
She'd say the same thing about you.
And I'm not fooling around.
This is just sex!
Look, you're not a woman
I could get involved with,
and I'm not a gay guy
you could get involved with.
It's simple as pie.
I'm just gettin' done by a gay guy.
That's funny.
Gay "Guy" .
There were others.
There aren't now.
So....
I wasn't a disappointment, then?
You were not a disappointment.
Prove it?
No.
What's wrong?
Baby's due soon.
Yeah, so?
So....
I gotta go, okay?
No!
What?
No, it's not okay.
No strings.
I know.
See ya.
Will l?
Just say love. Just say love.
Just say love.
Why do I feel like a fish on a hook?
Damn you.
I don't need you.
I'm never waiting for you again.
Never.
Hello?
Hey.
Doug.
Yeah.
Are you okay?
Yeah. You?
Yeah.
Did you have the baby?
A boy, right?
Yeah.
So, uh, what's his name?
Charlie.
Just Charlie?
What's wrong with Charlie?
With all the exotic names?
Was Charlie your father's name?
You're as bad as Gita.
She wanted....
What?
Never mind.
Maximilian.
That's a name.
So is Charlie.
I suppose.
So, uh, everything all right?
Healthy mother and baby?
Yeah, yeah. Yeah.
It's been a while.
Us.
Yes.
Tomorrow?
Well....
Uh....
Okay.
Wear something warm.
It's cold as two witches' tits.
Come to the apartment.
Ohh.
What?
Okay.
Don't forget to knock.
The bell doesn't work.
[ Doorbell rings ]
It works! You did it! Yeah!
Hmm?
[ Laughs ]
[ Scoffs ]
My hero?
Mm-hmm.
I'm gonna go outside and ring it
so you can hear it.
[ Doorbell rings ]
Who is it?
The... big bad wolf?
I hope he's hungry.
[ Knocking ]
The, uh, big bad wolf
locked himself out.
The landlord kept promising,
promising....
-You don't want to?
-Just like that?
Do you know how long it's been
since you called?
[ Sighs ]
No strings.
A simple question.
Yeah, a married couple's question.
Look, I felt funny. Gita's so....
She was so big, ready to deliver --
here I was doing this.
-I'm doing the doing.
-What?
You don't do anything.
You don't even know what I look like
without my clothes on.
And I don't want to!
I thought our arrangement was cool.
If not, then, hey.
What do mean you felt funny?
Do you mean you felt guilty?
No, l....
Just knowing I was
about to be a father.
Yeah, maybe because
it was all so easy.
All you did was unzip,
drop your load, and go.
Yeah, well, it seemed to me
where I was dropping my load
wanted it pretty bad.
Doug, do you even know
what I look like?
I mean, if you were asked
to describe me.
This is shit.
Yeah, I know how you look.
Yeah? Turn around
and tell me how I look.
This is bullshit!
What are we talking here,
a relationship?
There is no relationship!
-Then why are you here?
-For you.
Me?
Look, you don't even know
what you want.
If I made this a relationship,
you wouldn't want me anymore.
You want me like this -- straight.
Ha.
You know I'm straight.
I wouldn't be attractive to you
if I wasn't .
And I want you the way you were
when we first met.
And we agreed -- no strings.
If one of us
wasn't on the corner, hey.
When was I not there?
You know what I mean.
It was simple, pure. It was just....
-Sex.
-Yes.
But that's what
makes you feel guilty.
You don't feel guilty
about the good food you eat now
or the bell you just fixed for me.
So why don't we just do things
for each other and forget the sex?
What happened to you?
I want you the way you were.
When we met,
you made me remember,
when I was... free, like....
Like a God.
-I gotta go.
-Thanks for the bell.
I really was looking forward to this.
I....
Just say love, just say love,
just say love....
What?
Say love.
Just say....
Just go.
Why are you fighting
what we both want?
Just say love. Just say love.
Just say love.
Will I see you?
No strings.
If we're on the corner,
we're on the corner.
No.
Just say love. Just....
Just say love.
-Hey.
Cold as two witches' tits
out here, huh?
Hey, what is that?
Is that the two tits on one witch
or the tits of two witches?
Which ever is coldest.
-You want to come home with me?
-Shit, yeah.
Not for that, okay?
Then why?
I put up a tree.
I have friends
hang the decorations.
I wondered if you'd hang a few.
Yeah, sure.
All right. Come on.
It's nice.
It's small.
It's a nice tree.
Yeah? Well, I get to plant it
after the new year.
Thanks for helping me decorate it.
Five decorations?
Well, they were Cinderella's .
Oh!
Merry Christmas.
Ay-yai-yai.
Very pretty.
Did you wrap this yourself?
Aah.
Oh, hey, can you save the paper?
Thank you.
Wow, beautiful.
Gloves.
Thank you.
Aah.
I didn't get you anything.
No, that's okay.
Hey. You know what this is?
[ Laughs ]
Yeah.
You and Gita.
She has that stuff all over the place,
secret-like,
so she's standing under it,
or I'm standing under it,
and then we gotta kiss.
Oh, you mean like this?
Hey, come on.
I-I was just kidding.
I gotta go.
Hey, um....
Do you want to...?
Oh, no, no. It's -- it's okay.
I'm glad you wanted me to put
Cinderella's things on the tree.
-Yeah?
-It's nice.
Thanks for the gloves.
[ Door closes ]
Just say love, just say love,
just say love, just say love,
just say love, just say love.
Just say love, just say....
Just say love, just....
[ Sobbing ]
I hadn't planned on going home
for Christmas.
My father had made it clear
he didn't like having a "queer" son.
But you gave me the courage
to be who I am, even to him.
My -- my mom looked at me,
her eyes quietly saying, "I love you."
My father walked out of the room.
I'd taken Cinderella's ashes with me.
I planned to scatter them
in a nearby field
where she and I used to play
when I was a kid.
I remember her, only a kitten,
chasing the butterflies
through the wild flowers.
The grass was dry and brittle now,
but in the spring,
the flowers would bloom,
and Cinderella
would be there again.
It started to snow,
so I opened the urn, and I ran,
letting her ashes fly
in this wide arc,
and Cinderella fell down
with the snow.
The finality of my loss
of Cinderella crushed me.
So, I knelt on the ground,
just sobbing.
Then I heard a voice say, "Quido."
I looked up.
My father was there,
reaching down for me.
I stood up, and I fell into his arms.
He said,
"You made me remember."
And he looked at me.
And he smiled.
And he kissed me,
and I felt my tears on his lips.
The snow came down
thicker and thicker,
and with it came
this wonderful peace.
After I left your apartment
that night, I felt strange.
Like people on the street,
especially the guys,
were all staring at me.
But then I began to look at them.
And I felt...
...powerful.
In total control.
Free.
Whereas before I had dreaded
seeing Gita, now I couldn't wait.
She looked at me,
and I could see right off
she knew something was different.
She put her arms around me.
She started to kiss me, slowly,
and then she'd hold her face back
so she could get a better look,
like she was....
Like she was recognizing me.
And she kept saying,
"God! Oh, God!"
She led me upstairs.
I felt like the North Pole,
attracting the whole world to me,
you know.
Later, when Gita was asleep,
I went to Charlie in his crib.
Now, don't get me wrong,
but I felt horny looking down
at this pure little guy.
Not horny in the usual way.
It was everything,
even my little toes.
He was awake, quiet,
just looking up at me.
I picked him up,
held him against my body.
He's like a feather,
compared to the things
I carry at work, you know.
I took him to the window,
and I could see in the streetlight
snow coming down.
"Charlie," I said. "It's snowing."
I looked into his eyes,
and he looked right back at me.
I had seen that look before --
that quiet, trusting, loving look.
What was he thinking?
Was he thinking how the snow
was coming down on us in our home,
and on Guy,
and how we're all connected?
I don't know.
As he reached his little fingers up
with those tiny little nails,
and he grabbed my lower lip
and pulled down.
And then...
...he burped.
[ Laughs ]
What a little shit, huh?
I kissed him,
and I realized his skin and Guy's
felt the same on my lips.
And then I remembered
where I had seen that look.
It was the same look Guy had
the first time I touched him.
He came without effort,
like he was melting
into my pores and into my blood.
The Bible talks about God
using spit to create Adam.
It wasn't spit.
"Gita, I knew I had to tell you,
but I didn't know how.
Would you believe
I drove to church?
[ Laughs ]
As I walked toward the front doors,
I looked up -- way up at the steeple.
And then it came to me.
And I knew how to tell you. "
GUY: We all have
the same problem --
loneliness.
We're not really alone, of course --
but most of the time we forget that.
Every now and then, though,
something or someone comes along
and reminds us.
That's attraction.
The problem occurs when
that attraction is misunderstood.
It takes on a power
it doesn't deserve,
and we spend our lives trying
to cure the symptoms of loneliness,
not the disease.
Plato has a lot to say on this,
not the least of which
is that most of the world's problems
could be solved
if we could just remember
we are more than body.
We are soul.
Remember that our desires
are just a longing
to feel that connection
we already have but have forgotten.
I think what he and other great
philosophers are trying to say
is that our real purpose in life
is to remind each other, by example,
of who we really are.
[ Cell phone ringing ]
Hello?
Hey.
Hey, Doug!
I'm coming over. I want
to bring you out to the house.
-What?
-On Saturday.
Gita's going on a weekend retreat,
and I want you to meet Charlie.
Are you sure?
And... I got you a cat.
He's a stray. He's been hanging
around the construction site.
His name is Spikey.
[ Laughs ]
Spikey?
Yeah, you know,
hammer, nail, spike... Spikey.
Oh, so you can arrange a weekend
for a cat but not for me.
-It is for you. He wants you.
-How do you know?
Everyone wants "good."
I'll be there at 6:00.
-Why so late?
-a.m. !
What?!
Then we'll have the whole weekend
together, just the four of us.
Be ready. I'll ring the bell.
Mr. Spike is usually right over there
in those woods.
Where in those woods?
Just bang the can, he'll come out.
Of course that's not his usual tuna,
so I don't know.
What? It sounds different
if it's tuna?
This is good.
This is vegetarian cat food.
Vegetarian?
Well, now I know he won't come.
He's not stupid.
Just bang the can.
Bang the can.
Spikey!
Come here, guy!
Come on, guy.
That's funny -- calling him "guy."
Yeah.
Just as long as he comes.
Tsk-tsk-tsk.
Do that again.
That's why you're
such a good lover.
We make sex, not love.
No, no, no.
Yeah?
What if I didn't give you head?
What if I didn't have a cock?
What?
Would we still get together?
Why would we want to?
Because it's not just the sex.
You let me breathe.
Here.
I'm gonna go call the sitter,
check on Charlie.
See if you can get Spikey
to come out.
I think the problem is that food.
Here, Spikey.
Look, look, it's all organic.
With chick peas.
Come on, Spikey.
Aah.
So?
What?
You wouldn't want me
if I didn't have a cock?
I didn't say that.
Besides, letting you breathe
isn't an answer.
Yes, it is.
Before I met you,
I didn't know how to breathe.
I had this friend in high school.
We could read each other's minds.
I mean, he knew where I was
going to throw the football
before it was even in the air.
We played our last game.
We got drunk together,
hired a hooker.
We really just wanted
to be alone together,
but that's what guys did, you know.
We were afraid to breathe.
He was dead two days later.
And his name was Charlie.
Yeah.
Hey, that's him.
That's Spikey.
Do you see him?
No, only moving bushes.
He's not sure what to do yet.
Yeah, it's because of that tuna.
We should have gotten real tuna.
Oh, my God.
He's a yellow tabby, just like....
What's he doin'
He's smelling
that food you brought.
No, he's not.
He's eating that food I brought.
Spikey!
He likes it! He likes it!
Come here, buddy.
[ Meowing ]
Spikey, I want you to meet Guy.
-Hi, Spikey.
-He needs a home.
Here, let me hold him.
Oh.
Wow, you're big.
Ooh, but skinny.
I'll fatten you up.
[ Purring ]
Doug.
No matter what,
I'd like you to be my friend.
So, you're saying yes, you would
want me even if I didn't have--
Yes.
Because I love you.
Isn't that what you wanted
to tell your friend Charlie?
Yeah.
But you never did.
No.
Tell him now.
Just say, "I--"
Say it.
Uh....
I love you, Charlie.
I love you.
GUY: # The clothes you are wearing
are the clothes you wore #
# The smile you are smiling #
# You were smiling then #
# But I can't remember
where or when #
s
I see you found
where everything was.
Oh, a kitchen's a kitchen.
I'm surprised there was spelt bread.
I thought you were making
French toast.
Oui.
With that?
Banana is an egg substitute.
Oh.
Why do you have that smile
on your face?
It's Spikey.
I've never seen a cat go poop
with his tail so straight in the air.
He thinks he's royalty bestowing
a gift on the universe.
Is it like having Cinderella back?
-Oh, and such a surprise.
-Why?
You'll see when you get your gift.
What was that?
Vanilla soy milk.
Hey, why don't you get dressed?
Why?
Just because.
[ Growls ]
[ Laughing ]
You're nuts.
What about them?
Hey, you ever seen
"Gone with the Wind" ?
Yeah.
Do you remember that scene where
Rhett and Scarlett are fighting,
but he's horny, so he grabs her
and carries her up the stairs,
and she's going, "No, no, no, no" ,
and he kicks the door
and throws her on the bed?
The next morning she's sitting up
with this grin on her face
and singing.
Well, I don't hear you singing.
# Oh, what a beautiful morning #
# Oh, what a beautiful day #
That's it.
That's probably enough.
[ Laughs ]
You know, it was a beautiful night.
Yeah, it was.
But nothing happened.
Yes, it did.
Yes.
Yeah.
Plato was right.
What do they call it?
Plato-nic love.
Real Platonic love.
Well, it's great. It's like, having
your cake and eating it, too.
Oh, that was a terrible pun.
No.
No. This -- this'll last forever.
For me, anyway.
You know what I liked?
Lying there, naked,
you pressed up against my back...
...breathing right up
against my shoulder blades.
You'd be my wings if I had them.
I love just feeling your presence.
You know what else I loved?
Hmm?
Your snoring.
I do not snore!
Oh, yeah. Yeah.
And I didn't think gay guys snored.
You didn't think we had penises.
How very wrong I was.
I'll take that as a compliment.
Oh, there were some papers
on the table.
I put them over on the counter.
Oh, it's just some legal stuff.
Legal?
You know that contractor who's
building the 23-house subdivision?
Yeah, well... asked me
to be his partner.
Congratulations!
I have some good news, too.
I took your advice.
I showed some of my paintings
to the gallery on Newbury Street.
They took 'em?
I mean, how could they not?
One.
But it's in the window.
I sit on the sidewalk,
and I just stare.
"Falling in Love."
Oh, and I told Gita about us.
Oh. What?!
It was the right thing to do.
So she knew I was coming here.
Yes.
So that's why there was
spelt bread and soymilk?
No. No, she uses that stuff, too.
God, I knew l'd like her.
She liked the name Maximilian.
Ugh!
So?
So....
She says we're ready.
Oh.
Oh, okay. Um....
Uh, I guess we shouldn't
see each other anymore, then.
Are you saying no?
What?
What, the -- the two of us?
Well, well, what about...?
Gita?
She's been awake for a long time.
She's just been waiting for us
to catch up.
Uh....
If you're not ready...?
No addictions. Just...
...love.
Together?
All of us?
Perfect fit.
Oh, my God.
Oh, my God!
[ Laughing ]
Plato would approve.
Yes.
I love you.
Mmm.
Close your eyes.
[ Humming ]
I can guess what this is.
It's a long-playing CD.
Huh.
Oh, my God!
Yeah, it's Spikey.
I did it before I ever saw him.
Yeah. Yeah, it's Spikey,
and that's you,
and that's me, and....
That's Sue.
Sue, that friend I told you about --
the one who jumped peppers.
Yeah, I took a stab
at what she'd look like today.
-Sue?
-Well, Susanne.
Gita's real name is Susanne.
Collins?
Collins.
["Your Eyes Tell The Truth" plays ]