A tornado warning remains
in effect
for northeastern Johnson County
In east central Kansas
and southwestern Jackson County
in west central
Missouri until 9:45 PM
National Weather Service
Doppler radar indicated this danger
Storm was located
seven miles...
Ah! No!
God, help! God!
So is your mom home?
No, she's at her weekly
hair appointment.
You want to fool around?
Do you ever think
I'm gonna say yes?
Patience is a virtue
Mmm.
Well, you got one
Seriously though, you want me
to wait till she gets home?
No, I want you to wait
until I finish this cigarette
Remind me again
why I hang out with you
Cause you want to sleep with me
Oh yeah
Thanks again for helping me
cut geometry today.
Hey, I was leaving anyway
Besides,
I'm going to be a porn star
The fuck do I need geometry for?
Thank you
Hey, cheer up.
Your dad's coming home soon
Yeah, maybe he'll buy me
a GTO just like your daddy
Hey, I mowed a lot of yards
to get this car, okay?
My dad's yard
a lot of times.
All right, see you Saturday
So it's a date then?
Bye, Sean
I'm six-months sober as of tomorrow,
as a matter of fact
My wife's coming back to me
Hmm.
I get to see my kids again
I got you guys to all thank for that.
Thank you
Okay, I guess I'll go next
Uh, my name is Janet
I'm an alcoholic
and I've been sober
for four months.
Hi, Janet
Well, I should be happy right now
because my husband's coming home tonight.
He's in the military. He's been fighting
overseas for the last year and a half.
But to be totally honest,
I don't feel happy
I feel-- I feel really scared
Like I've been thinking about
all the things that he's seen over there
and everything
that he's lived through
And then he's gonna
come home to...
me.
I just thought that sobriety
was going to make things better
You know? I thought that
if I could just stop drinking
that things would improve
But it hasn't been like that at all
In fact I feel like every day
everything's getting worse
at home, you know?
I don't know, it's--
I've just been really selfish
I guess that's why
I'm here, you know?
I just-- I want to do better
I want to-- I want to be better
As these trained
weather spotters are continuing
to feed us and give us
the new information,
we'll make sure
to give you the updates
Stay tuned.
We will keep you advised
to this rapidly changing situation
Good afternoon.The National Weather Service
issued a tornado watch
earlier this morning
and things are going
from showers to thunderstorms
and getting a little more dangerous
across eastern Kansas.
You can see over the last few hours,
starting to see those colors
brighten up--
a lot more red on the screen
That is indicative
of the storm strengthening.
And really they're all converging
on eastern Kansas.
Several warnings have been posted
At this point, it is only
for hail and high winds.
But certainly,
as the National Weather Service
has issued that tornado warning
there is the potential
for some tornadic activity
as we progress throughout the day,
as all of this travels across
the state and to the east.
Areas west of l-35 look to be okay
But areas east of l-35
Girls, are you ready?
I thought you quit smoking
Watch your face
...a serious situation to a slightly
more dangerous situation as...
You ready?
No, I'm running away.
That's why I've packed a bag
Why are we staying
in Kansas City tonight?
Weather Channel says
there's going to be a storm
If your father's flight is delayed,
we might have to stay in a hotel
Then why don't we just stay here
tonight and go in the morning?
Because I want us to be
the first people your dad sees,
- not some hotel desk clerk
- Whatever.
County off to the east in Linn County
the situation is turning a little worse
We're going from the thunderstorms now,
severe weather.
Quite a bit of hail
reported down in Linn County
and that is indicative
of these storms strengthening
Once you see the purple, the bright
mobile homes and vehicles
should be abandoned
for sturdier shelter.
Otherwise go to an interior room
on the lowest level
of your home or place of business.
Make sure there are as many floors
and walls between you
from the outside as possible.
Repeating: A tornado warning
remains in effect...
Please, I've lived in Kansas
my whole life.
I've never once seen a tornado
You know you were born
during a tornado.
Yeah, I never heard that before
I can't say I remember much about it.
Ditto
Hey, Mom?
Can I change my name?
Why would you want to do that?
Sally is just so unprofessional
What do you mean?
Well, can I at least go by Sarah?
But your name's not Sarah
it's Sally.
Your father named you
Yeah, you were named
after Charlie Brown's sister
I was not, Jennifer!
Hey, Alice, how's your book?
It's fine
What's it about?
A lot of things
Like?
- It's a bunch of short stories
- They any good?
Haven't you read them?
Yes, but I want to know
what you think.
Magma?
- A tornado warning remains in effect
- They're fine.
...until 5:15 PM
Central Daylight Time
in Linn County in Kansas.
The National Weather Service
in Topeka, Kansas,
has issued a tornado warning
for northeastern Linn County
near Blue Mound, Kansas...
Mom, I have to pee
-Weather Service Doppler radar... Peachy.
sturdier shelter
Otherwise, go to an interior room
on the lowest level of your home
or place of business.
Make sure there are as many
walls and floors betw--
A tornado warning remains in effect
until 5:15 PM Central Daylight Time
in Linn County in Kansas.
The National Weather Serv--
Sally, I told you to go before we left.
Hurry, gotta pee!
- Sorry.
- It's okay
You-- you all right there, ma'am?
Yeah. We're heading
to Kansas City tonight
Oh, I really don't think
that's a very good idea
There's a tornado ripping
thought Blue Mound right now
- It's headed this way
- Oh, really?
My husband's flight gets in
in a couple of hours.
He's in the military.
He's coming home from overseas tonight.
Well, I reckon he could
wait a few more hours
as opposed to his wife
and daughters having an accident
Where would we go?
I'm the wrong guy to ask.
I'm new here myself as of last week
But I'd be willing to bet
any of these old farmers
would let you hole up in their cellar
Looks like the townspeople are
really taking this storm seriously
You folks best get some shelter
Thanks
Need any help
closing up, Mrs. Shurman?
No, thank you, Barney
Carr, get those people out of here
Now you all be damned careful
out there.
Thanks
I can't believe
his name is Barney
A tornado warning remains in effect
until 5:15 PM Central Daylight Time
in Linn County.
At 3:41 Central Day--
What is that?
A tornado siren
- Hey, Mom?
- Yeah?
12 miles west of Mound City
I'm sorry I didn't pee at the house
It's okay, sweetie
other locations in the warning
include Anderson County...
this storm is visible
...straight-line wind gusts
of up to 60 miles per hour.
...or place of business.
Make sure there are as many floors..
A tornado warning remains in effect
until 5:15 PM Central Daylight Time
in Linn County in Kansas.
The National Weather Service
in Topeka, Kansas,
has issued a tornado warning
for northeastern Linn County
...Blue Mound, Kansas,
until 5:30 PM Central Daylight Time
At 4:50 PM Central Daylight Time
Mom,what's wrong?
Doppler radar indicated
a severe...
Everybody out of the car now!
In addition to the tornado,
large hail the size of quarters
Don't look!
Run, run!
...vehicles should be
abandoned for sturdier cover
Otherwise, go to
Hello?!Hello?!
Help! Help!
Mom?
Go, Mom, go!
Mom, hurry! Go, go!
Come on, come on!
Go go go go!
I'm scared
I think we're safe.
I think we're okay
Okay.
Jen, are you okay?
Yeah. Are you?
Yeah
Everybody
I'm fine
Honey, you're always fine
Okay, come here
Wow
That was intense
Don't tell Dad I cried
Oh, honey
It's okay.
Where are we?
You think the storm's over?
I think it's over enough
for us to leave.
Damn it.
There's a tree across the door
Shit, ow
Jennifer, can you help?
Oh, Shit-
Push, hard
Okay
Now what?
Come on.
Well, at least there's booze
sorry
Let's see if somebody's home?
Hey! Anybody up there?!
Help! Help!
- Hey!
- Hello?!
Shh, wait a minute.
] yam [mag
cellphone?
Oh, duh-
- You got a signal?
- Yeah, three bars.
It's roaming though
Is that okay?
Yeah, I think
the extra charge is okay
Nothing.
Nothing?
Are you connected?
Yeah, it connects.
It just connects to static
- Who are you trying to call?
- 911.
Keep trying
If you push me up there,
I bet I could fit through.
Oh, honey.
Are you sure?
No, but if you break out
the rest of the glass, I'll try
Any luck, Jen?
No.
- Try texting someone
- Yeah.
Good idea.
Wow, you're fast at that
Who are you texting?
- His name's Sean.
- Yeah? Who's that?
He's a guy that would travel
through a storm to get laid.
Jen, please, the girls
Mom, please, I think we have
bigger fish to catch right now
Damn!
What is it?
Unable to send text message
Well, maybe it'll send
after the storm clears
Hey, will you send
a message to your dad?
- Okay, you ready to try this?
- Mm-hmm.
I'm gonna knock
the rest of the glass out
Dad, stuck in a cellar
halfway to KC.
Running late
Be there soon, Jen
Okay,"message pending".
Hopefully he'll get it soon
It's "fry," by the way
What?
You just said we had
bigger fish to catch,
but really it's bigger fish to fry
Oh, thanks
Sure.
You should talk more
Why?
Because you're smart
Are you ready?
Yes.
Is that--
Do you think they heard us?
I don't know how
they couldn't have
What the hell?
Why would they do that?
I don't know
What was that?
I'm willing to give
that window thing a try
Yeah. Come on
It's throbbing,
it's throbbing inside!
Go get something
to wrap her arm! Go now!
- Oh my--
- Help me!
Help me!
What is all this shit?
Rope
rope-
Okay, let me see, let me look
This is soft
Come on.
Here here
- Ow, don't! No!
- Shh shh, oh baby
It's okay.
Hold still, hold still
Shh, there
It's okay, sweetheart
I won't tell Daddy
you cried, I promise
What did that to her?
I don't know
- Is she gonna be okay?
- Yeah.
We just-- we just need
to get her to a hospital
- right away.
- What happened to her?
I don't know
I think maybe--
I think maybe she got bit by a dog
Mom, did you see her arm?
I know
What?
It didn't look like a dog
Of course it was a dog.
What else would it have been?
It just looked--
it just looked too clean--
Jennifer, please
We need to-- we need to get her
to a hospital right away.
Shh, Mom-
Ah, come here
It's okay. Here, I want you
to stay with Sally.
Come here.
Here, I'll help
- Push.
- Oh, it's giving-- okay
- Yes.
- Come on
The windows!
Get through the windows!
What the fuck is wrong
with you people?
Let us out!
Where the hell are we?
What now?
I don't know
Sally is passed out
Someone is...
keeping us here.
Please help.
We are
in Wellsville."
Hey, Jen, we need
to clean Sally's wound
- There's water
- Where?
On the shelf in the corner
Okay, let's go get some
Another storm?
Yeah
The radio said
it's going to storm all night
I'll go get that water
Come on.
- Oh my God.
- I wish your dad was here
- What is that smell?
- It's not water.
Wow
Definitely not water
- What is it?
- I think it's moonshine
What? Why?
That's alcohol
I'm gonna use it to clean her wound
and it's gonna hurt like hell.
Help me hold her down
Okay, sweetie. Here we go
Ahh!
- Ow, Mommy!
- Mom, stop it. You're hurting her
- Mom!
- It's okay, Alice
I'm sorry.
- Mom!
- I'm sorry
I'm sorry.
That's it.
That's it. Stay still
It's gonna be okay
I promise.
Promise.
Jennifer?
Stay with me
I will, Sally
I wont let anything happen to you,okay?
in
I love you, Jennifer
I love you too, Sally
Just go to sleep now
and rest, okay?
We're gonna find a way
to get you out of here.
You okay?
Mm-hmm.
There's got to be a way
out of this basement.
Maybe a door that leads upstairs?
Is there a flashlight or something?
I don't know. Maybe
Hey, Jen, do you have your lighter?
Oh.
Uh, no-
It's in the car
Jennifer?
Check Sally's pockets
What?
Promise not to be mad at Sally
course.
When we were in the car, she took
your lighter out of your backpack.
- Really?
- Yeah, she thought maybe if you didn't
have your lighter,
you wouldn't smoke
Are you serious?
Yeah, check her pockets?
- I don't believe it.
- Sally saves the day
I promise, Sally
no more cigarettes, okay?
Jen?
- Hello, Barney.
- Hi, Mrs. Shurman
Well, goodness sake,
get yourself out of this weather
- You'll catch your death
- Thank you, ma'am.
Can I get you a cup of coffee?
It's still warm.
That'd be great. Thank you
Are you baking something?
Cookies before the power went off
- Want one?
- Oh, sure.
Looks like the tornado
went right through.
Lot of trees and power lines down
It'll be a hell of a clean-up effort
around here.
Hell, it isn't even over.
Gonna storm all night
That's what I heard.
Gotta love this time of year
I never get used to it.
- Makes people crazy in this town
- Yeah, I noticed.
I'm surprised you weren't
holed up in your cellar?
Waiting for the storm to pass
Well, I prefer to wait it out up here
- And bake?
- It calms my nerves.
Uh, Mrs. Shurman, real quick
the reason I stopped by...
Yes?
Well, there's a car out front
- Oh really?
- Yes ma'am
It belongs to a couple ladies
on the road up to Kansas City
And I was wondering
if you'd seen them.
You don't say?
Well, no, I sure haven't seen 'em
Mmm.
Mrs. Shurman, their car
is out in the ditch by the road
Mmm, perfect
Well, I sure hope they're all okay
Are you sure they didn't stop by here?
It just seems like this would be
the first place they would check
Well, not unless
they got here before I did
How many of them
did you say there were?
There were four of them actually
There was a mother
and three of her daughters?
Oh my.
And you say they were
on their way to Kansas City?
Yes, ma'am, to pick up
her husband at the airport
Hello, Barney.
Out checking the roads, I see.
Hey, Sheriff!
I didn't know you were here.
I just stopped by to help her
board up her cellar.
Oh, yeah, I was going
to ask about that.
Looked like you got it
boarded up pretty good
Don't want a flood down there
Lots of valuables
in that old storm cellar
Yeah
Sure.
Well, I'd better get back
out on the road.
Horseshit. Stay inside here
and have another cup of coffee?
You know, Albert, I would love to,
but those travelers
really got me worried
They probably just went down
to Jacob's farm up the road.
Yeah, I'll check there
You sure I can't talk you
into another cup of coffee?
My, those lights seem
to have a mind of their own?
I'm sure they'll have them
up and running soon enough
Yeah. Thank you
for the coffee, Mrs. Shurman
But I really should
go check on those ladies.
You be careful
out there now, Barney
and don't forget to say hello to that
beautiful new bride of yours.
Will do. Now you folks
get some candles lit.
- No telling how long this will last
- Oh.
Oh my!
You forgot your cookies.
Oh. Wow! What are they?
They're little tornadoes
Cute.
Good night, folks
If something happens,
you're explaining it to his wife
Shouldn't have married him
in the first place,
especially a month into storm season.
Here, let me
Is this for Dad?
Yeah. These storms are harder
on him than they used to be.
Roger?
Settle down
Is he getting a case of cabin fever?
Just a little restless.
I'm surprised that you grew out of it
You used to be a real handful
this time of year.
Storms really don't affect me
the way they used to.
Teeth hurt a little--
that's about it.
Now you get that
from my side of the family
I wish your brothers
were more that way.
If this supercell they keep
talking about gets any closer,
I might not be able to control myself
I'm gonna let Roger and the boys
out for a while tonight
to enjoy the storm
- Hershel's already out.
- Well, you know Hershel--
always was a free spirit
He took a bite out of one
of our visitors earlier.
- And Tommy?
- In the cellar.
The storm got to him early
I was hoping that new
muzzle will help him.
You know they make
those things for kids
and they never work right anyway
I had to chain him up and give him
some extra moonshine to calm him down
Probably won't stay
that way for long though.
It's a shame about
that family down there
They seem real nice
ls there somebody out there?
- Hello?
- Hello?!
Hello?
This is Deputy Carr
from the Wellsville Sheriff's Department
- Oh, thank God. Help us!
- We're trapped.
Well, hold on, I'll see
if I can get you out.
What the hell
are you doing down there?
- Get us out of here
- Are you okay?
My daughter needs help
Hold on, I'll get the woman
who lives upstairs.
- No!
- What?
She's the one that
locked us down here
All right. Let's get you
the hell out of there.
Take my hand. I'll pull you out
Alice, you first
Ahhh!
Hello?
Hershel, calm down!
Creepy
Oswald triplets
Where are you
Sally is hurt bad
A cop tried to help
Help
Struck by lightning
Hey, I think I found
a hallway or something
I'm gonna check it out
Okay, I'll go with you
- No.
- What?
I said no
Then let Alice go with you
- I want you both to stay with Sally
- No, that's stupid.
You're not going down
a dark hallway by yourself
Jennifer
I can stay with Sally.
It's not that big a deal
- I don't want to leave you alone
- I'll be fine.
Is it just me or does that
sound like a terrible idea?
Yeah.
You're right.
We all stay or we all go
Then we all go
How long is this tunnel?
Must be 100 yards
What is it?
I think it's a still
Jen, careful with your lantern
Why?
If that's a still
and this is a propane tank
it could explode
Alice, I need you to stay with Sally
We'll be right down the hallway
so if you nee something,
-just yell,okay?-Okay
Mom?
Yeah?
What do I tell Sally
when she wakes up?
Tell her everything's
going to be okay.
Is that true?
Alice, with every other
beat of my heart,
I believe we're going to be okay
Okay
It's not so bad
No, it's just-- it's just awkward
Really
Okay, do you want to go
forwards or backwards?
I'll go backwards.
Can you get the lantern?
Mm.'
Ready?
- Wait wait.
- What what?
I need to change my grip
This could be a process
- Ready?
- Yeah.
Okay, back up
- All right.
- Okay, you go first
Okay
Mom?
Going too fast. Okay
Yeah?
You okay?
Can you see now?
That's good
Here comes the door
How's the ramp on your side?
It's good.
- Are you okay?
- Mm-hmm.
All right, it's good
- Don't go too fast
- Sorry.
Wait, do you hear something?
What is that?
I don't know
Keep going.
That's it. All right
Mom, where's Alice?
Alice?
Put the still there
- Alice? Alice?
- Where is she?
Where is she?
Alice?
What the hell is this?
Oh God, no!
Oh no!
I'm sorry. Oh, my baby
Oh God, oh
Oh God, no!
Mom?
We have to get out of here.
Mom, we can't give up
Jennifer
we're gonna die here
No, we're not
You still have daughters
who need you right now.
I won't give up
Jennifer?
What was that thing?
I don't know.
But next time we'll be ready for it
Mom?
Give me a minute
Never mind
Mom, are you okay?
No, Jennifer
I'm not fine
Mom, I need you
to pull it together
Pull it together?
Your little sister just--
Mom, I'm thinking
about right now, okay?
And right now we need to put
that contraption in front of the door
and blow it off the hinges.
And I need your help
Do you hear that?
Uh-huh
Mom!
- Jennifer?
- Mom!
Oh God
Can you stand?
You gotta get Sally out of here
We're all getting out of here
Look at how happy Dad is
I haven't seen him
with this much energy in years
Should we let Roger out?
Give your dad a little while
Looks like that second storm
is coming after all.
It's gonna be strong
Then I guess that explains
all their energy.
They're gonna sleep
for a month after this
Where am I?
- It's okay, Sally.
- Jennifer, it hurts
I know, Sally
- Where's Mom?
- Right here, sweetie
Mom, are you okay?
Sally, Mom got hurt real bad
I'm fine
- Where's Alice?
- Sally, we have to get out of here
- What's going on?
- We need to leave.
I need you to cover
yourself, okay?
I-- what do you mean?
Where's Alice?
Alice is gone
She-- she's dead?
Yes. Now, Sally,
we have to get out of here
Can you walk?
Bleeding.
It's okay, honey.
I need you to be strong
and we're gonna
get out of here, okay?
We're gonna get Dad too, okay?
Come on.
I need you to get behind me
and cover your heads.
- What are you going to do?
- I'm gonna throw this,
you're gonna hide, okay?
Can you run?
- I don't think--
- If I help you?
- I'll try
- Okay.
Mom!
Mom?
Mom, please wake up
Mommy, please!
Thank you, Mommy
Are you ready?
Okay
Are you okay?
Behind you!
Shit!
Jennifer!
Why didn't you just listen
to the weatherman for once?
Relax, all right? We're not
the only ones with trees down
It's gonna be fine
I told you to cut down
that branch last year.
What if it would
have hit the nursery?
It wasn't going to hit the nursery
Honey, come here
What the--
You girls okay?
She's cut up pretty badly
Let's get you guys inside
Come on.
All right, let's take a look
Oh, sweetie
We gotta get her out of here
or call the cops--
Shh.
It's gonna be all right
It does look pretty infected though.
- You poor thing.
- You don't understand
- There were things out there that--
- Just calm down.
I'm gonna go call for help
Let's get you some new bandages
Bathroom's this way.
Come on.
Ahhh!
Ah, hee hee hee!
Poor kid's teething
in the other room.
There's disinfectant
and bandages in the top drawer
- Just take whatever you need
- Thanks.
This baby's just
kicking up a storm
I hate when this happens
Excuse me.
Jennifer! Jennifer!
Sally! Sally, no!
Get away from me!
Please get away from me!
Jennifer, help me!
Jennifer, please help me!
- Sally!
- Ahh! Jennifer!
Jennifer!
I'm so sorry, Sally
There's no need to run, sweetie
We just want to have
a word with you.
Get the fuck back
You're lucky that the storm affects
each one of us a bit differently.
Otherwise you'd be dead already
Shit
This is where we
part company, dear
Shit!
No no no no!
No dead. But there's still a lot
of us unaccounted for--
mostly youngsters
But you know
how these storms go
Some of them just don't know
how to recover yet.
They'll find their way home
this afternoon.
Any signs of the girl?
No.
You think she's still alive?
No, she's gone with the storm
With this much damage,
there'll be news teams
heading this way.
We'll see
I'm sorry about your mother
More storms coming
in a few hours.
Could be worse than last night