Astronaut Forrest...
you give us hope.
And your great accomplishment...
will be edged
in the history of mankind.
You're not alone.
People from all over the world
are keeping their eyes on you.
So please, don't lose
your hope and faith.
We'll be praying for you...
and your safe journey home.
What is it that inspires
mankind to take great risk?
Why is it that throughout
history...
humans have been driven
to explore distant uncharted
places...
despite the possibility
of no return?
In the case of Europa, the icy,
mysterious moon of Jupiter...
that inspiration came
in the form of photographs.
Photographs that revealed life.
These ghostly images gave the
entire human race unrepentant
knowledge...
that life as we know it
is not an isolated event...
reserved merely for Earth.
But rather a miracle that
is pervasive throughout
the cosmos.
And for the first time
since the 1970's...
humankind, once again, sought
to set foot on a distant world.
Hey, kids.
Um, I want to know, how do you
go to the bathroom in space?
I'll answer this one. Check
this out. We have a small--
Actually, there is a little bit
of gravity on the ship...
so, so going to the bathroom...
in space is a lot like going
to the bathroom on Earth.
Well, I think the kids would
enjoy how number one works.
Next question.
In the days after NASA retired
the space shuttle program...
and since the abandonment
of the International Space
Station...
the world has had to turn
to private enterprise...
when it comes to getting man
back into space.
The most influential name in
space exploration has been...
without a doubt,
Walter Moffitt.
Whales on Europa.
Yes... every time I see these
latest pictures...
man, it gives chills
down my spine.
Which brings me to my next
question... of pictures.
Mm-hm.
We have dozens
and dozens of pictures.
Lots of pictures.
NASA is preparing a submersible
rover to dive under the ice.
NASA and its rover...
My name is Gavin Hayden.
Why aren't you wearing
any spacesuits?
The space suits, or EVAs...
are used for extra-vehicular
activities...
so, that would be outside
the ship.
But I suppose they could be
used in an emergency.
About two hours worth
of life support.
Charlie, it takes NASA
a year just to pass gas.
They have quadruple redundancy
in everything they do...
in their engineering chain,
and you name it.
I have respect for NASA,
but by the time their rover...
gets there, our boys
will be on their way home.
To accomplish
the 13-year mission to explore
the distant world...
astronauts Nathan Miller and
Michael Forrest are placed into
a deep sleep for six years...
as their space craft races
from planet to planet...
before speeding off to Europa.
There they will spend one year
in a state-of-the-art
facility...
studying the newly discovered
species of alien giants...
before finally returning home.
My name's Emily. Um, aren't
you going to Venus, 'cause
that's the wrong way?
That is actually
a very astute question.
Um, it has to do with the
orbital ellipses of the
planets...
and a very concerted effort
on the part of the scientists,
as well as ourselves...
to increase the speed of the
ship using not only the earth's
gravitational pull...
but Venus as well.
Yeah, so what I think my
colleague is trying to say...
it's all about going fast.
So what we're gonna do is spin
around Venus to pick up speed...
then slingshot
from Venus to Earth.
As we get even more speedage,
we're off to Jupiter.
Faster than ever.
Sounds cool, huh?
Isn't the redundancy exactly
what is needed here for safety?
There are those who criticize
you who say that you rushed
this mission.
This is not meant to be
a disclaimer...
but everybody knows how I feel,
you know, that I'm very
protective of my men.
Columbus went around the world.
Magellan sailed around the whole
planet.
We got guys going to the moon.
They rushed them to the moon.
And that was for a reason.
We need somebody there.
We need somebody to put their
foot in the dust of the moon.
Like many brave explorers
before them...
the two-men crew of Life One...
entrust their lives to their
tiny vessel and to each
other...
for a chance to witness
the extraordinary.
It has been called the most
dangerous whale watching
expedition in history.
When you see the planet...
what does it look like
outside the window?
It looks like stars.
We have heard that this mission
has cost you personally...
50 billion dollars.
It cost me a lot.
But look, that's what
we're here for.
That's what we're working,
that's the whole deal.
Think about this for a minute.
These boys are travelling
at the speed of a .45 bullet.
They're sound asleep.
They're gonna go around Venus,
past Earth, and then start
orbiting Jupiter.
What a miracle.
They'll see the whales
of Europa.
But they'll be seeing it
with their eyes.
It won't be photographs
from NASA.
Your a man who's wealthy enough
to do anything he wants to do.
Why aren't you up there
with those men right now?
Charlie, I've done everything
I've wanted to do... just about.
I'm a bit long in the tooth.
I would'a, could'a, should'a...
but it really isn't about me.
It's about future generations.
Can I ask a question?
How is it that you plan
to spend your free time?
Space pong.
We actually won't have
a lot of free time.
Now ping pong in space--
We're gonna be doing
experiments 24/7.
Not to mention
a lifetime of study.
Having to cram that
into just one year, so--
Yeah, but in our free time,
I will be in my space suit...
sitting on my porch, reading
from my pocket Shakespeare...
by the light of Jupiter
on the horizon.
Um, that sounds beautiful.
Thank you.
Well, I guess it's time
for us to go.
We have a lot of work to do
before we go to sleep.
Thank you for your
wonderful question.
Bye-bye.
Thank you, kids.
We'll see you guys in six years.
Nathan!
OMS thrusters check?
OMS thrusters... check.
Hey, pal, how we doing?
I am doing just fine.
This is Life One
to Mission Control.
There is a leak in the main
habitation chamber.
I sealed the capsule
and I'm suiting up.
I'll be out of communications
for-- until further notice.
Nathan Miller is dead.
Life One out.
Life One,
this is Mission Control.
We received
your emergency beacon.
We're analyzing all of the data
pouring in right now.
As soon as we have some answers
for you, we'll get back to you.
Acknowledge receipt of this
message. Mission Control out.
Life One, this is Mission
Control. We have multiple
failures of the hull...
in both the capsule
and the habitation module.
We recommend suiting up--
This is Life One to Mission
Control.
There is a leak in the main
habitation chamber.
I've sealed the capsule
and am suiting up.
I'll be out of communications
for 12 hours.
That's great, you're on it.
We'll keep sending more
information as it comes in.
Mission Control out.
Life One out.
This is Life One.
The main habitation
chamber is secure.
The hibernation
and reentry capsule... is--
I'm sorry, I don't know
who you are, um...
Can you find me Ben Elliot
or... Bob Jansen?
Would be great.
This is Life One out.
Space travel is inherently
dangerous.
There could always be a problem.
Let's say on the first leg,
heading towards Venus...
or on the second leg, going
from Venus back to Earth...
aborting the mission
would be relatively simple.
We'd just come home.
We'd actually be asleep at the
time, so we probably wouldn't
know that there was a problem.
Of course, after we make that
last push around Earth and head
towards Jupiter...
well, there's really
no going back.
Life One,
this is Mission Control.
We have Robert Jansen
to come in and talk to you
face-to-face.
All right, great, thanks.
Michael?
It's Life One.
No, it's Michael,
and you're Adam and I'm Bob...
so let's cut the jargon.
Michael, hi, it looks like
the space craft...
was more than likely hit
by a micro-meteorite.
Information is coming in and
we're doing our best to process
it as quickly as possible.
Just know that I am here...
and as I know anything,
I will transmit back to you.
Bob out.
This is Life One.
It's good to see you, Bob.
Damage report.
Life support is solid.
And oxygen is holding,
for now.
The habitation module
is stabilized and we're at 1.0
of earth gravity.
So whatever hit us, must have
not been big enough to knock
us off our spin.
The central fuel tank
and booster engine are
in the numbers.
Nuclear reactor remains
unbreached...
and all radiation shielding
is functioning well.
Europa habitation ballast array
and all contents including ice
drill platform.
Inflatable habitat
and mini submersible
are reading 1 00 percent.
Looks like the only thing
that we lost, actually...
was the hibernation
and reentry capsule.
I'll do another diagnostic check
and I'll be in touch.
Thanks, Bob.
Life One out.
Life One,
this is Mission Control.
We have an update
on the situation...
but Mr. Moffitt would like
to deliver this message himself.
Thank you.
Michael... Walter Moffit.
Listen, first of all...
we deeply regret
the loss of Nathaniel.
And there's not much you can say
about a thing like this...
but Mr. Jeffs has taking over
for Mr. Elliot...
who passed away about two years
ago in a heart attack.
A lot's changed since
you've been gone.
And on that note, we've decided
to abort the mission.
I'm looking forward
to talking to you.
Mission out.
Hi, Mike, my name is Irwin
and this is my family...
Mila and Drew.
We'd just like to thank you for
being our eyes in another world.
Bye!
Bye.
This is Life One.
I have received your message
and am aborting the mission
to Europa.
Given our current position,
we will continue our present
course...
past Venus as scheduled and
toward Earth as scheduled.
At which point,
we will execute a Leg 3 abort...
scrapping the slingshot maneuver
to Europa... from Earth.
I'll make the changes necessary
for our break in procedure...
and preparation for reentry...
and thereby an end
to the mission.
This is Life One out.
Okay, this is all very exciting.
Hey, ease up, man.
Smile!
It's for the kids.
It's good PR, hit the button.
This is Life One.
It's been 24 hours
since the accident.
My hibernation sickness
is starting to wear off.
The food recycling system
is up and running.
We're at 1 00 percent.
Obviously most of the comforts
of home are locked away
in the Europa.
Habitation ballast array.
So I won't get
my comfortable chair.
But I am gonna miss my bed,
and the window for that matter.
We're only supposed to spend
a week to two weeks
in this chamber...
but we're just gonna
have to make it work.
We're just gonna
This is Life One... out.
Michael? It's Bob... obviously.
It was important for me, right
now, to tell you that I need you
to get on a routine.
I need you to sleep. I need you
to eat three meals a day.
I need you to exercise.
It will be very, very important
for you and for me...
for you to do all of the work
that you can to stay sane up
there...
and to know that I am here
to talk to you...
or at least send you periodic
messages that at some point
in the future you'll respond to.
I'm here for you, buddy.
All right?
Bob out.
Niobium, Nb.
Bromine, Br.
Krypton, Kr.
Rubidium, Rb.
Strontium, Sr.
Hi, Michael, Bob here.
Just checking in.
You've got a lot of people
around here watching you.
In fact, you're pretty much
the biggest story in the world
right now.
Um, so I need to ask you...
can I have the exclusive rights
to your book?
But also, I was asked today
to ask you how you're feeling.
Seemed an odd question.
But then I realized
I hadn't asked you...
so... how are you?
How are you feeling?
Bob out.
This is Life One.
Diagnostics seem
to be going smoothly.
As of right now...
it'll probably take me
another three days to fully
check the entire ship.
At least this part of it anyway.
I've taken in
about 2,100 calories.
I have 600 to go.
I'm gonna try to keep it
at that level for the duration.
Done about 1 6 minutes
of exercise.
I think that's too much.
I'm gonna try to dial it
back for tomorrow.
Otherwise, we're just trying
to conserve our energy.
I'll get in a daily log tomorrow
about this same time.
Other than that,
we should be fine.
This is Life One... out.
Okay, Michael,
here's the situation.
You have a lot
on your plate right now...
but every single bit of it
is extremely important.
You've got a post-Venus engine
burn that needs to happen...
otherwise, you're going to spend
the rest of your life as Venus'
only real moon.
Unfortunately, from my end,
I am looking at an electrical
system that is completely fried.
And it needs to be rebuilt
from the ground up.
So you're going to have
to perform that engine burn
manually...
which obviously wasn't the way
things were meant to be.
The system's primary generator
is unstable, at best...
and you have got to keep the
power running.
You lose power and you will
freeze to death in a manner
of hours.
So be very careful.
Michael, what we have here
is a classic, old-school
Christmas light situation.
Remember at Christmas when you
were trying to get your
Christmas tree lights to work?
And they weren't, inexplicably.
So you had to go through every
single bulb and test it...
to get proper connection
in order for the lights
to light up?
Well that's what you're going
to have to do, alone...
with a 25 gazillion dollar
spaceship.
What I'm gonna need you to do is
I'm gonna need you to take all
of the control systems...
from the capsule and reroute
them to the habitation module.
The monitor that you're
looking at right now.
So let's take all of the systems
and let's reroute it there.
Now I hate to tell you this,
but this means that...
Michael, you're gonna need
to go back in the capsule...
and get your hands dirty.
It's gonna take you
a lot of time...
but, just like Christmas,
it'll be worth it in the end.
Bob out.
This is Life One,
received your message.
I understand
what you're saying, Bob...
but I think I can get to
everything I need to get to...
in the main habitation chamber.
If I go into that capsule,
I'm gonna have to get fully
suited up.
It's gonna be hard to work.
It may take extra time coming
from this way, but...
hell, I got plenty of time.
Frankly, I don't want to go in
that capsule if I don't have to.
So let's see what we can do
from this side.
This is Life One, out.
Life One,
this is Mission Control.
Um, it's me, Adam.
Um, I know you lost all your
music and entertainment data
with the death of the capsule.
So I put together some music
that I'm going to send up
to you now...
and I think you'll enjoy it.
No, no... uh--
No! No!
Surf's up
We're surfing every day now
The summer's here to stay now
Surfing till the sun's gone
away
This is Life One.
Turn it off and keep it off.
Life One out.
Surf's up
We're surfing every day now
The summer's here to stay
We'll be spending all our time
Surfing till the sun's gone
away
I started work on rerouting
the control panel today.
And happened to find
two ping pong paddles.
Ping pong ball and a book
of light reading.
Compliments of Nathan Miller.
Life One out.
It's in the toilet.
Astronaut Forrest...
On behalf of my family and with
love from all of our country...
we wish you a safe return and
you've been a really big
inspiration for all of us.
Please come back safely, okay?
Thank you, Kadru.
See you guys in six years!
And thanks again
for your great questions.
You did good.
Finished Mary Shelley's
Frankenstein... again.
Don't really care
for her poetry.
I'll move on
to Shakespeare tomorrow.
This is Life One out.
Jackson, Lincoln, Johnson,
Grant, Reagan, Bush...
Clinton, Bush, Obama, Raton.
Okay, first names... George--
Hi, Michael, it might be time
now to start thinking about...
performing some no-fire
engine burn test.
Just to check the connectivity
on the primary generator.
Let me know when you might be
ready to start testing and we'll
get ready on our end down here.
Bob out.
I've rerouted
the circuits from S-23.
I think we're about,
let's say ten days out...
before we'll be able to do
some kind of engine-burn test
on the new control panel.
This is Life One out.
This is Life One, daily log.
Did another ten minutes
of exercise.
That seemed to go pretty well.
2,400 calories consumed today.
I guess we'll call it a
late-night snack to finish up.
I've been eating...
candy corn-flavored paste
for the last 14 days.
I think we'll switch
to cheeseburger.
Life One out.
Sleepy, Sneezy, Happy, Grumpy...
Dopey... Doc. No--
Dopey, Angry and Doc.
Gray-6, pull wire.
They're all gray, Bob.
Have eaten what
I'm supposed to eat today.
I have exercised as much
as I'm supposed to exercise.
I have been working on rerouting
this damn panel for I don't
know how long...
and I would love to have
just a little room to work.
Next time you build
one of these things...
maybe-- maybe...
a little elbow room.
Just a thought.
Sleepy, Sneezy, Happy...
Was one drunk?
Daily log 42.
Calisthenics, ten minutes.
Caloric intake, 2,700,
right on the money.
And happy to say that
Panel 17-OHG is finished.
So, put a big check mark
by that one.
We'll get to work
on 1 8-01HG tomorrow.
But today, I do believe
I am putting my feet up.
Sleepy, Sneezy, Happy, Grumpy.
Sleepy, Sneezy, Happy, Grumpy...
Dopey, Bashful and Doc.
We're about 24 hours from our
first engine-burn test.
I wouldn't get too excited,
I think we have a long way
to go.
Fortunately,
we got plenty of time.
Talk to you tomorrow.
This is Life One out.
This is test number one for an
engine burn after reconnection.
We are going in three,
two, one.
It's about what I expected.
This is Life One.
Test number one has failed.
We startin' over.
Hi, Michael, it's--
My name is Eric Hainen,
I'm from Haifa, Israel...
and in behalf of my family,
my town, my country...
I wish you best of luck
and a safe journey back home
from space.
Thank you.
Michael, standby.
I have an important message
to you from Mr. Moffitt.
I will be sending it
to you now.
Michael, this is Mr. M.
I got something
that might cheer you up.
We've compiled a short video
of well-wishers
from around the world.
I'd like to ask your permission
to transmit this up.
This is Life One
with an answer to your request.
No.
No, no, thank you.
Life One out.
Read a little Hamlet today.
He says there is nothing
either good or bad...
but thinking makes it so.
Question is, do you you change
your thinking or just try to
stop thinking all together?
This is Life One out.
Um, I want to know, how do you
go to the bathroom in space?
I don't know why you let
something like that bother
you so much.
It was a personal question
about my personal business.
Kid asked the question.
What do you want me
to tell them?
That every time we defecate,
our stool is reconstituted into
a paste that we eat for dinner?
It's flavored paste.
And you get to choose
your own flavor.
This is Life One, Day 1 82.
Six months.
I don't know, Bob.
Should we be celebrating?
Okay, Michael,
everything appears to be 100
percent on track...
and you're getting
everything done, famously...
except that my data is showing
that there are issues
and problems...
that I don't understand...
so, let me do some more work...
and let me get back to you,
but stay the course,
things are improving.
Bob out.
Toronto...
Stockholm.
New York City.
Burlington...
Vermont.
Vermont...
Santiago, Chile...
Hollywood.
Hi, Michael, uh,
we've been quiet down here.
Just not wanting to put any
unnecessary pressure on--
on you.
We have some people
down here who...
want to know how close you
think you are to a second
engine-burn test.
So if you could, please kindly
confirm receipt of this message.
Bob out.
Uh... I'd say we are...
three weeks--
Three weeks out from our next
engine-burn test, so...
nobody get excited.
I'll check in again tomorrow.
That looks like that's
gonna take forever.
Bob, I need to talk
to you about something.
I, uh--
I know there's a vacuum
in that capsule.
I know that there's no sound
in that capsule. I know that
Nathan is dead...
but I hear something in there.
I can't figure out what it is.
And I'm starting to think
that it's me.
Life One out.
Astronaut Forrest...
what is it you plan to do
with your free time?
Michael? Bob here.
Listen, buddy, could you
do me a favor and just get
a little rest?
I know that you are working
very, very hard on this
repatch...
but there's no reason to push
yourself to do another
engine-burn test tomorrow.
Between you and me,
you have got plenty of time...
so let's just put it off
for a day or two.
Go to the beach,
drink a Mai Tai.
Just take a day off, okay?
Bob out.
I got about six more hours
on this repatch...
but we are doing this
engine-burn test tomorrow
come hell or high water.
That's all I got.
Life One out.
This is engine-burn
connection test number two.
Arming... in three, two, one.
Fuck!
This fucking--
Bob, I'm becoming concerned
about the failure of these
engine-burn tests.
I'm worried about the
ramifications.
We've got, uh...
about 2,500 calories...
taken in today and about
1 1 minutes calisthenics.
There's a sound coming from the
hibernation and reentry capsule.
I don't know what it is.
Could you... take a look
at that for me?
Or give me some ideas
about what that could be?
Thanks.
Life One out.
Michael, this is Bob.
There is no reason that there
should be any sound coming
from the capsule.
The capsule is dead.
Now, listen to me.
You are not sleeping.
One friend to another,
you look like hell, bro.
So, get some rest, continue
eating, continue exercising.
You have to exercise not just
your body, Michael, but your
mind and get some rest.
That's my advice to you today.
Bob out.
Shut up, Nathan!
Shut up!
Goddamn it!
God--!
This is engine-burn test
number seven, three, two, one.
number eight...
in three, two, one.
Test number 1 1
Number 1 4... in three, two, one.
Three, two, one.
In three, two, one.
This is engine-burn test
number 25...
in three, two, one.
Oh, baby.
Come on, come on, come on.
God--
No, no, no, no, no!
No, no.
1 632, 1 634...
no, that's all right.
Goddamn it, come on!
Wasn't a-- wasn't
a frayed wire, was it?
S-20, S-26, 27.
Ugh, it's not here.
Fuck, it's cold.
No, no, no, that's fine.
It's fine.
This isn't it.
Come on.
Guidance systems, check.
Guidance system, check.
Hey, look, pal...
there's nobody else I'd rather
do this mission with.
I mean that.
Let's do this.
What are you doing?
This ain't the man I know.
Get the fuck up... Michael!
Michael, get up!
Michael, you--
you son of a bitch.
I-- I cannot believe
that you made it.
Uh, I lost a lot of money.
Um, be well, we'll do
the work we need to here...
and, uh, send us a message
when you can.
Bob out.
Yeah, I made it.
I'm alive anyway.
So what's next?
I still have a post-Venus
engine burn ahead...
and have yet to perform
a successful test.
And if I do get all the way
back to Earth...
I have to crawl back
into that capsule...
and hope that whatever
rudimentary interior repair
I do...
won't rupture on reentry.
And before that can happen...
I have years of this.
For what?
To say... I survived?
Sometimes I think...
if I could get these
engines fired up at all.
Maybe I shouldn't stop at Earth.
Maybe I should...
ride this thing...
all the way to Europa.
In a lot of ways...
I'm dead already.
Otherwise... yeah...
I made it...
but what's the point?
Astronaut Forrest, I just
want to thank you so much...
for being a tremendous
influence to me and my family.
We're so proud of you.
We wish you the very best...
and please,
have a safe journey home.
You're my hero.
Michael, Bob here.
Listen, buddy,
you are now nearing Venus...
and your ship is sending
back the most...
beautiful pictures
that I've ever seen.
Buddy, Venus is right outside
your ship right now...
and I-- I wanted
to implore you...
to-- to let me send you
the images.
It's amazing...
Bob out.
This is Michael Forrest
of Life One.
I have just seen Venus.
It's so close,
I feel like I can--
It's so close, I feel like
I can reach out and touch it.
I'm millions of miles
from home.
My only companion is dead.
And I can't help but think...
that I'm the luckiest man alive.
I wish... that you
could see what I see.
This is Life One out.
This is Life One.
Standby for a post-Venus
engine burn.
Arming... in three...
two...
one.
That's the stuff.
Michael? It is official.
The Broncos have won
the Super Bowl.
No, not really.
Uh, you're on
your way home, buddy.
Two more years to go.
Maybe by the time you're home,
you'll be old enough to have
a beer with me.
Sleep well,
'cause I am going to bed.
Bob out.
Life One to Mission Control.
You remember that video
that Moffitt made for me?
Think you could track
that down?
I think I'd like
to see it now.
Thanks.
This message is for
Astronaut Michael Forrest.
My name is Avery Grey.
I'm from Omaha, Nebraska.
Good luck, Michael,
in Chinese.
Hi, Michael...
Astronaut Forrest, I just want
to thank you so much...
for being a tremendous
influence to me and my family.
We're so proud of you.
We wish you a safe return and
you've been a really big
inspiration for all of us.
Please come back safely.
One-- one time, in school...
I was watching
one of your videos...
for a long time,
like, we're talking hours.
Um, and then
this teacher came in...
and she said,
""You're missing science class.""
And then I told her,
""I ain't missing nothing.
""I'm watching Astronaut Michael
Forrest going to search for
space worlds.""
That sounds like science to me.
You're my hero.
Astronaut Forrest,
you are a great hero to the
Japanese people.
You give us hope.
And your great accomplishment
will be edged in the history
of mankind.
Sometimes I wonder
if you're scared.
You don't ever look scared...
but you might get stuck
up there...
and I just wanted to tell you,
don't be scared.
'Cause I'm gonna be
just like you.
And, if you get stuck,
I'll come and get you.
All right,
cross checks are complete.
We've run ten pressure-test
simulations and it appears
that your patch is solid.
The inflatable aero-shell
is 1 00 percent,
was never compromised...
so you've got yourself
a heat shield.
You can start warming up the
capsule for the ride home.
Really, at any time,
all systems are go...
with power generator running
at 99.6 percent.
Truly, a hell of a job, you've
got her purring like a kitten.
So this is it.
Time to say goodbye
to the HAB MOD.
to Life One.
Listen, Michael, um...
I'm proud to have been
here with you.
Thanks, Bob.
I couldn't have done
it without you.
That is so true.
It's been my pleasure.
Okay, standby.
All that's left to do is fire
the engines for the breaking
procedure.
We'll see you after splashdown.
Bob out.
Life One to Mission Control.
Mission Control, over.
Jeffs, how you doing, buddy?
Listen, I need to speak
to Mr. Moffitt.
Can you find him for me?
Thanks.
This is Life One out.
What can I do for you,
Michael?
How's the countdown going?
Funny you should ask.
That's actually what I wanted
to talk to you about.
Shoot.
I've decided to abort
the countdown.
What are you saying?
What do you mean abort?
I'm rebooting the mission.
I'm going to Europa.
Wait a minute.
I got a ton of reasons
why that's not gonna work.
Besides, everybody here is
working to get you down safely.
Just listen to me for a second.
There's a reason
I came up here.
Someone's supposed to go.
Someone's supposed to see this.
Michael, I have no button
to bring you down.
You got me.
There's nothing I can do.
I thought my life was over
when that accident happened.
The truth is,
I've been living life up here.
I'm gonna continue to live.
Michael...
what was this all for?
See the whales on Europa?
Mr. Moffitt...
you got to learn
to trust me again.
Michael, listen to me.
I don't know how else to put
this, but we gotta lay
Nathan to rest.
We have to.
I just want you home.
You hear me? Michael?
I can't have another death
on my conscience.
Michael? Michael?
This is Michael Forrest
of Life One.
You'll have to forgive me.
I'm not normally a man
of many words...
but I'm doing the best I can.
I wanted to thank all of you...
for your support.
Thought I was alone up here.
I was wrong.
It was about three years ago...
from now that Astronaut
Nathan Miller lost his life.
I lost a colleague,
a fellow astronaut, friend.
But just like all of you,
his spirit never abandoned me.
In a book he brought onboard,
a collection of poems.
He speaks to me.
One passage in particular,
I still hear him loud and clear.
It's by T.S. Eliot.
It says, ""We shall not cease
from exploration.
""And the end of all our
exploring will be to arrive
where we started.
""And know the place
for the first time.
""Through the unknown,
unremembered gate...
""when the last of Earth left to
discover was that which was the
beginning.
""Quick now, here, now.
Always.
""A condition of complete
simplicity costing not less
than everything.
""And all shall be well.
""And all manner of things
shall be well.
""When the tongues of flame
are enfolded into the crowned
knot of fire.
""And the fire
and the rose are one.""
We're just getting started.
This is Life One... out.