In the name of Jesus Christ!
Jesus!
Jesus! Jesus!
A dream?
Yes.
I was dreaming
of your mother's bread...
still warm from the oven.
Keep dreaming
if you want to eat today.
Nothing to eat
and sleeping on stones.
I'm getting too old forthis.
We must find work.
Let me be the first
to welcome you, Governor Pilate.
You appear to be
the only one to welcome me.
Please make note of that,
Governor.
I am the only one
to welcome you.
A conqueror doesn't expect
a warm welcome.
These people don't accept that
they've been conquered.
Well, they will.
Judea is the most troublesome
province in the empire.
So I've been told.
And who are you?
I am Livio, Roman citizen.
And why are you here?
Well, a kind man would say
I am Caesar's historian.
An unkind man would say
that I am Caesar's...
spy.
( laughs )
- Good morning, Mary.
- It's a beautiful morning.
Have Joseph
and your son returned?
No.
I'm sure they must have
found carpentry work in Jerusalem.
God willing.
Pontius Pilate!
Most honored citizen of Rome!
I, Herod Antipas,
Tetrarch of Galilee, welcome you.
( applauding )
I accept your welcome,
Herod Antipas.
And Caesar sends
his blessings on your land,
and his kingdom.
May I present my wife,
Herodias,
my stepdaughter, Salome,
and your fellow
Roman citizen, Livio.
We've met.
Please, come sit beside me.
I must say,
this city surprises me.
In what way, Governor?
The structures,
they are most impressive.
Built by my father,
Herod the Great,
beloved of his people.
They hated him.
A vicious man, I'm told.
How distasteful of you
to speak of my father this way.
As his son,
I am a hero to the people.
The butt of all of their jokes.
You misunderstand.
In Rome, we call yourfather's
way of ruling, "statesmanship."
Perhaps Pontius Pilate
would like to see
the grandest of all structures
in lsrael, the Temple,
built by my father,
a personal friend of Augustus,
as I am a personal
friend of Tiberius.
How strange.
I've never
heard him mention you.
I thank you
for your welcome.
And I will visit the Temple,
as you suggest.
Make sure you take your troops!
And show their insignia proudly!
Livio,
whatdoes he mean,
"show their insignia"?
Well, I could tell you,
but it would spoil all the fun.
The High Priest of the Temple
is Caiaphas, appointed by Rome,
which puts him in
a very interesting position
on the one hand he has to appear
to be on the side of his own people,
but on the other hand
he owes his position to Rome...
a very narrow path to tread.
Welcome, Pontius Pilate.
I am Caiaphas,
High Priest of this Temple.
We come to wish you well,
as you undertake the post
of Governor of Judea.
I thank you, priest.
Allow me
to get right to the point.
Rome is displeased
with the number of legions
it has to keep in this barren land
in orderto maintain peace.
Your taxes don't begin
to pay back the costs.
You speak of the past.
This disorder erupts directly
from your corrupt religion,
which erupts directly
from this Temple.
That ends today.
My soldiers will be posted here
every minute of every day
from now on.
This order defiles the Temple!
Our religion forbids graven images
in the Temple!
Your soldiers are an abomination
to the Temple.
Even their flags break our laws.
We allow no graven images,
and your banners carrying
the carvings of Caesar,
these shields are symbols
of Roman dominion!
No building in Judea,
not even the Temple,
is exempt from the display
of these symbols.
What your religion forbids,
Rome demands!
We submit to yours words.
Here is my bare neck!
Let Rome cut it!
We will die before we allow
the Temple to be defiled.
Governor...
an awful lot of blood
for your first day.
Are you sure
Rome would be happy...
if you were to murder
every priest in the Temple?
Mary, stop staring
at Jesus like that.
He will never finish that door.
We do love when the carpenters
arrive, don't we, Mary?
Because there is nothing worse
than a door that squeaks.
Is there anything else that squeaks?
There is one thing that's broken,
but it's beyond repair.
I can repair most things.
A broken heart?
Martha,
you've embarrassed Mary.
And you've enchanted her.
She's a beautiful girl.
Woman. She's a woman, Jesus.
And she needs a husband.
Poverty, debt, hunger.
The Romans say
they bring us their world.
All they bring us is misery.
It's misery, Lazarus.
At leastthey let us worship.
The Temple still stands.
For now.
But the day may come when they
decide to destroy it too...
destroy us all.
But enough gloom.
Let's see if my son
has done any work
with your sisters
distracting him.
So, are we finished?
Yes, "we" are almost finished,
not that you had much to do with it.
I'm the aging supervisor.
It's my job
to sit back and watch.
Yes, well,
you do it very well.
Lazarus tells me that we will be
paid highly for these repairs.
Lazarus has never paid anyone
"highly" for anything.
I heard that snide remark
from my sister.
Joseph and Jesus
are our blood relatives.
Do you really think that I would
let them work without pay?
The truth, Lazarus?
You will pay them nothing!
Mary and l
have worked all day
to pay them
in food and wine at dinner.
And so,
they shall be paid-- highly.
No, no...
It is enough.
Don't be proud. You worked,
I pay my debts.
Thank you,
thank you so much.
Thank you again, Lazarus.
-Jesus?
- Yes?
Mary's had an offer of marriage
from a boy here in Bethany.
I thought you'd like to know.
She loves you.
Surely you must know this.
Why do you treat her as if
her feelings mean nothing to you?
- Lazarus, of course they do.
- Then tell her!
Mary!
Lazarus just told me.
It's not my idea.
You know that--
Mary...
please.
I wish that...
I wish you could understand.
I feel that-- I feel that l...
Have a safe journey, Jesus.
( knocking )
Open the door!
Get out of the way!
Where is your husband?
He's working in Judea.
He's in the hills hiding,
Like the other men,
to escape paying their taxes.
Right, you owe one third
of your income for two years.
You were deferred last year...
but no longer.
Take the goat.
Oh, please no!
We won't have milk!
The rest is due
when I come back
through this stinking village
next month.
If I had been here,
I would have thrown
that traitor out into the street.
Joseph,
no one could have done better.
A Jew,
working for the Romans!
He should be ashamed.
Ashamed!
Come and eat.
Please, come and eat.
To think I've lived all this time,
and itonly gets worse.
When?
When will there be an end
to the suffering of our people?
Are you asking me?
Are you telling me that I can
end the suffering?
When will he act?
He will know when it is time.
How will he know?
Joseph, stop talking like this.
Two days ago, we saw
a farmer leaving his house,
losing everything he's worked for.
We're not going to lose everything.
God will provide for us.
For him, too.
Mother,
I know what Father wants.
- I know he thinks I should--
- He thinks...
you should do
what your heart tells you.
Come back inside, please.
Joseph! Joseph!
Come, come, Jesus! Come!
Father, are you all right?
What happened?
Jesus...
Yes, I'm here.
What is it?
I've loved you.
I've loved you... as my own.
...as my...
Joseph, no!
( wailing )
Father, this is too heavy.
Now, when I am in the most need,
you take him from me?
You want me to step out,
but you leave me alone.
How can you ask this of me?
Alone? I have never been
without him.
You can give him back to me.
You can do it now.
Give him back to me!
Now!
Give him to me!
I am in need!
I cannot walk
this road alone!
Raise him,
raise him up into my arms.
Let it be your will, Father.
I cannot do this alone!
Raise him.
Raise him!
It's all in the hands.
Mine are not as talented as his.
Jesus, he loved you.
I disappointed him.
He thought he disappointed you.
How?
He knew you had
a Father in Heaven.
Joseph is my father.
Thirty-one years ago
I had to tell Joseph something
that just broke his heart.
An angel?
An... angel?
I am a religious man, Mary.
Don't blaspheme.
It is the truth, Joseph.
Out of all the places in the world...
all the women in the world,
God found you,
in this little village?
Just...
just an angel.
Just an angel...
I think he thought I was crazy.
He did not think you were crazy.
He used to tell me
that story all the time.
He thought he was crazy when
an angel appeared to him in his dream.
No.
He loved you with all his heart.
And he loved you
as if you were his own.
I was his own.
Now it's time for you to go
and find the answers you need.
And leave you alone?
It is what your Father asks of you.
You've given me so much joy.
We heard about Joseph.
How was the journey?
It was long.
A loss to us all.
Yes, thank you, Martha.
Could I have a moment with Mary?
Certainly. Come, brother.
- Mary.
- Jesus.
There's something I must tell you.
You see, my father's death
has ended my life as I knew it.
And it's time now
that I find my way.
Where is your way?
I can't be with you.
- What have I done?
- My life is not my own.
What have I done
to turn you away?
It is not you.
- You love someone else.
- No, no.
I am not who you think I am.
I know who you are.
And I know you love me
as I love you.
Mary, listen to me.
You must live your life...
without me.
Jesus!
Whatever it is...
you have to do...
safe journey.
( Man shouting )
We stand here.
on the banks of the Jordan River
where the people of lsrael
once crossed so triumphantly
in their God driven
wanderings toward freedom!
( laughs )
Look at us today!
Our leaders are weak and sinful.
They fail to keep the spirit of
the Covenant
of the letter of the law.
The prophet lsaiah said,
"Wash yourselves...
make yourself clean...
remove the evil of your doings,
learn to do good."
Who will be baptized here today,
to show the world that he is cleansed?
Baptist, cleanse me.
Come. All who wish to
be baptized will be cleansed.
Forthe Baptism signifies
that your commitment
has already been made...
to hate injustice,
and fight the battle
of the righteous ones.
I baptize you with
water for repentance.
( laughing )
What's the matter, John?
Don't you recognize
your own relatives?
Jesus?
You are unrecognizable.
I am?
Look at yourself.
I'm a prophet,
crying out in the wilderness!
Yes, and properly dressed for it!
- Come, sit.
-Thank you.
Eat with us.
This man is my blood,
my family--Jesus, of Nazareth.
Thank you, John.
How long has it been?
Twenty years?
How are you?
What are
you doing now?
How are Joseph and Mary?
Joseph has recently died.
I'm sorry.
Mother is well.
I am a carpenter.
Joseph would be proud.
Actually, Joseph
wanted me to move on,
to serve my God,
as you are, John.
You are welcome here, Jesus.
Thank you.
Joseph was a good man.
He taught us both a lot.
Remember our first trip to Jerusalem?
Of course. Passover.
This is the Holy Temple,
and tomorrow we will go inside.
But tonight, tonight help me
make our camp, maybe there.
Come.
Look, isn't it beautiful?
Through those doors is the Sanctuary.
If you look closely maybe you'll
see the golden menorah.
At the back of the Sanctuary,
is the inner most chamber,
the Holy of Holies.
( praying )
Mary! We must go...
if we are to reach home
before dark tomorrow.
I can't find Jesus.
He's probably gone ahead with John.
So we're leaving now.
- Come, Mary.
- I'm coming. I'm coming.
Let's go, then.
- Mary!
- I'm coming, Joseph!
He's not there.
No one has seen him.
- John?
- He's asleep.
They haven't seen
Jesus since Jerusalem.
You said he was with them.
- Yes, I thought he was.
- Well, he's not.
Look here!
I'll start on the streets.
If you find him, wait here!
- "lf"?
- When! Jesus!
Jesus!
Excuse me,
did you see a little boy...?
The prophets tell us that this city
and this place
will be a light to all
the people of the earth,
because everyone
will keep the Torah.
The Messiah will
be the prince of peace.
The prophet lsaiah says,
"They shall beat their
swords into plowshares,
and their spears
into pruning tools.
Nation shall not lift
up sword against nation,
neither shall they
learn war anymore."
Your mother and I have been
looking for you for three days!
Three days!
Child, why have
you treated us like this?
Why were you searching for me?
Didn't you know I would be
in my Father's house?
Your Father's house, yes.
Did you see the men hanging
from the crosses on the way back?
Terrible memory.
The Romans got so bored
at crucifying men,
they started doing it upside down,
justto entertain themselves.
John...
will you baptize me?
If you confess your sins...
and dedicate your life to God.
Of course.
Jesus of Nazareth, I baptize
you with water for repentance.
( thunderclap )
Behold...
the Lamb of God.
Jesus...
Jesus.
The Spirit has
brought you to me.
Do you know why?
To be tested.
The Spirit has led you here
and has allowed you
to know what men feel
when they are being
tested by me.
But to do this you
must give up every privilege.
You must be like them
in every way,
as fragile, alone
and little as they are.
Give up your shield.
Abandon the protection
of the power that abides in you.
Empty yourself of your divinity.
Empty yourself of
the Father, Jesus.
Without the protection
of the Father?
You know it is necessary.
The Spirit tells you, not me.
Only in this way
can we challenge each other.
I am willing.
( screaming )
Welcome to life, Jesus.
You don't look so good, Jesus.
- Are you hungry?
- Yes.
Command these stones
to become loaves of bread.
You mean call upon
my Father's power?
You have the power to
command these stones, don't you?
I am only his Son.
But you have the power!
( laughs )
And if I use it in this
way I will fail his mission.
He has asked me to bring his
word to man,
not to crush them with his power.
I'm jus tasking for bread
to relieve your hunger, Jesus.
Men have hungers.
Feed your starving people, Jesus.
Man does not live by bread alone,
but by every word that
comes from the mouth of God.
You're missing the point, Jesus.
You have the power
to solve mankind's problems.
Feed these people.
Many are starving.
- You can feed them.
- I was sent to feed them the truth.
- They hunger for bread, Jesus.
- No, they die of hunger,
because of hearts of stone of
other men, not because God wills it.
And you can change all that.
And so they are to listen to you, hmm?
A peasant from Nazareth?
You and only you have
the truth... sent from God?
Others have spoken the truth.
And men have destroyed
all of them for a thousand years.
Butyou... you, they will
listen to, hmm? Why?
They will.
And just how
will you do that, Jesus?
How will you get them
to listen to you?
So, I'm going to help you.
There is but one way
to make them notice you, Jesus.
You must convince them
that you are sent by God.
Throw yourself down and he
will command his angels to catch you.
Then they will see that
you are someone to listen to.
They would listen then,
wouldn't they?
They would listen to
someone who could do that.
That's not my Father's will.
If he wanted me simply to test
his laws, nature's laws,
he would not have sent me.
Don't test God
for your own purposes.
Jesus of Nazareth,
Jesus of Jerusalem,
Jesus of Egypt, Jesus of Bethany,
Jesus of Bethlehem.
- Where else have you been, Jesus?
- Nowhere.
No.
So, you cannot understand
the stakes!
Let me show you.
Power, Jesus, power!
Not second in command,
but number one.
You have never felt that power.
I have.
You've never been able to
until now.
Now you can be number one.
Do you know what
that means, Jesus?
No.
Power is what every man wants
more than anything else
in the world.
They kill for it.
There is nothing more precious,
and it is yours to have.
How?
Bow down to me, Jesus, just once.
In all of existence,
before and aftertime,
just once, Jesus.
It's a small price.
Consider the reward.
Away with you, Satan!
For it is written,
"Worship the Lord, your God,
and serve only Him."
I will not create a human kingdom
by becoming the most powerful,
but by being the poorest.
For I am the Lamb of God.
See you again, Jesus.
It's only just begun.
Do you think he's coming?
Hmm?
If he's been out there
all this time he hasn't survived.
If he hasn't survived,
he isn't who we thought he was.
Go home if that's
what you want.
Do you think he really is the one?
It's him!
Rabbi!
Why do you call me this?
We were there, Rabbi,
when you were baptized.
And John the Baptist
called you the Lamb of God.
You are the Messiah.
Are you sure?
- Yes!
- No.
( laughing )
How did you find me?
John the Baptist told
us where your mother lives.
What do you want?
To be your followers.
Rabbi, where are you staying?
Come and see.
Oh, Jesus...!
How long have I been sleeping?
Two nights and one full day.
I was dreaming of this bed,
this house.
Joseph was here.
Those two young men
waiting for you...
what do they want?
( chuckles )
To be my followers.
Good.
Maybe I'm not ready, Mother.
In Bethlehem,
in that stable behind the inn,
kings came to bow down to you,
carrying precious gifts--
frankincense, myrrh, and gold.
Those men did not travel all that way,
following that star,
without the will of God guiding them.
What's this?
This is beautiful.
Did you make this?
It is a wedding present
for your cousin, Benjamin.
Little Benjamin is getting married?
Yes.
Let's go!
And your followers?
Friends!
We're going to a wedding.
- The Baptist said he is the one.
- That's not enough.
If you do not approve
of my son,
why do you follow him?
Our people are slaves to Rome.
Our freedom fighters are being killed
and this is how he spends his time?
- He is a man.
- Yes...
and I fear, nothing more.
We are fishermen.
Our brothers are working right now
on the Lake of Galilee.
We should be there
working with them.
What for?
To make money?
Life has gotto be
more than that.
We went looking for answers,
and we met him.
And you follow him?
- Should we?
- Yes.
Why?
I am so thirsty.
I shall fetch you wine.
What's the matter, Andrew?
You don't dance?
I'll dance...
when lsrael is free
and men are honest.
That will be
a very slow dance.
( laughing )
It will not come a tall
if we wait for you.
I thought when I found
John the Baptist that--
Andrew!
But he said
you were the one.
And you spend your time
drinking wine and dancing!
There is no wine left.
Andrew, I'm sorry
I have disappointed you.
- I was only--
-Jesus?
There is no wine left.
Yes, Mother,
what concern is that to me?
Perhaps you could provide...?
My hour has not yet come.
It is time.
Jesus will help you
with the wine.
There is no wine left.
Just do exactly
what Jesus says.
Andrew needs to know.
The world needs to know.
Could you please fill those jugs
over there with water?
- With water?
- Yes, with water.
- Yes.
- Thank you.
Jesus, the jars are filled.
Draw some out and
take it to the bride groom.
Impossible.
Drink, Andrew.
The cup you desired is here.
He is the one, Andrew.
Have no fear
in following him.
Anyone who has two coats...
must share with those
who have none!
Anyone with food,
must do likewise!
Tax collector!
Collect no more taxes
than those prescribed for you!
Herod! Antipas!
Come out!
Herod Antipas!
Ruler of these people,
come out!
I have heard from the corners
of lsrael of you, John,
son of Zachariah.
And I've come
to hear your message.
You must repent,
Herod Antipas,
for the sins that you have
committed to your people!
I come in peace, John.
What "sins" do you speak of
You live in sin
with this woman, Herodias!
Hold your tongue, "prophet"!
You are married to his brother,
and yet you lay with him!
You're a liar!
He's a filthy liar!
I want to hear
your words, John,
but I cannot allow you
to insult my wife.
You are a sinner! Put away this woman!
Confess your sins!
Arrest this liar!
We're leaving.
- No...
- Salome!
You can turn your back on me,
Herod Antipas,
but not on God's judgement!
Go.
Beware, one who comes after me
will cleanse with fire!
James!
Simon!
We're back!
You go off
without saying anything,
leave me to do
all the fishing.
It's a good thing
James was here.
We've found him!
Now you return,
grinning like an idiot.
- Can't you feel it?
- All I feel is wet.
Can't you feel his presence?
Are you possessed?
What are you talking about, Andrew?
Look... there.
The Messiah!
Have you gone mad, too?
The quiet one is James.
The loud one
at the stern is Simon.
Have you been telling my brother
that you're the Messiah?
- Are you a rabbi?
- He's a carpenter.
Where are you from?
Nazareth.
- Nazareth?
- Yes, Nazareth.
Can anything good
come from Nazareth?
( laughing )
Your boat is empty.
We've been working all night
while these two followed you around,
searching for...
Whatexactly was it
you were searching for?
If you took me out
I could fill your nets.
Climb aboard, "Messiah."
The "Messiah" is going
to fill our boat.
Where are the fish, "Messiah"?
Further out, where it's deep.
- Ha, that's original!
- Simon, he's the one.
I've seen him
change water into wine.
Really?
Andrew,
scoop up some lake water,
I could use a cup of wine.
Scoop up one for me, too.
Cast your nets here.
Now.
James...
I'm only going to do this
so you won't waste your life
following this jackal.
What do you think, James?
Should we drag the net,
or just let it sink?
I don't know.
Ask the carpenter,
he knows everything about fish!
Pull it in.
Pull it in?
It's only been in the water--
Pull it in.
Of course.
James, pull it in.
Stop laughing and help us!
What kind of man are you,
that you can command
the fish in the water?
Come with me, Peter...
I'll make you a fisher of men.
My name is Simon.
Wait, wait, wait!
Is it all right if we drink
from your well?
-Thanks.
- Yes.
You are from Nazareth, yes?
I saw you at the wedding
in Canaan.
They said you made
the wine from water.
Is that true?
Did you do that?
Yes, he did that.
He changed the water into wine.
- I saw it.
This is the one.
Jesus of Nazareth.
He changed the water into wine!
Sir...
man of Nazareth.
If you can do that,
can you heal my son?
Come.
Please, I beg of you.
Wait!
This man is a fraud
and a false Messiah!
Believe.
He is the chosen one!
He comes here
to steal your money!
Yes!
Every week the same thing!
( angry clamor )
Quiet! Quiet!
Listen to the Master.
Do you believe I can help you?
Yes.
( outcry )
Rise up and walk!
( weeping )
He's the Messiah.
- Did he really do that?
- You saw it!
Yes, I saw it,
but I don't believe it.
Believe it! Believe it!
- What's your name?
-Thomas.
Come with us, Thomas.
Follow the Messiah.
Come!
I have given you
your wish.
He can speak
against you no more.
You fill your palace
with graven images,
and you forget your God!
Cut out his tongue
and feed it to the dogs!
Live by the Word of God!
Oh! Roman pig!
Open the door.
Caesar comes
to collect his taxes.
"Caesar" comes?
My, how the mighty have fallen.
- Your taxes are due.
- Have you no shame?
You, a Jew,
doing Rome's dirty work?
Your taxes are at work,
building and repairing roads,
aqueducts--
And they are lining
your pockets!
Do you wish to pay,
or do you wish to have
these men take you away?
( laughing )
Zealots.
Zealots!
Zealots! They're coming!
Stop! Stop!
Who says this?
- Jesus of Nazareth!
- Oh, yes...
the latest "Messiah."
I've heard of you.
Will you save
your people, "Messiah"?
Spilling blood
won't save them.
Spilling enough
Roman blood will.
The stones of Israel
are covered with blood,
still we are enslaved.
You will change nothing
until you remove the blood
from your hands.
I am Barabbas.
Maybe you need
a bit of blood on you.
No! No!
Do you love me now,
"Messiah"?
This is what Rome does
to your people, every day.
Strike me again.
And when you have
exhausted yourself--
When I have exhausted myself
there will be
legions more to strike.
- Exactly! When does it stop?
- When we are free.
You will be free
when you learn to love.
Clever words.
Nothing more.
Don't fill my people with your
empty promises, "Messiah."
I'll be the one to
free the people of lsrael,
Jesus of Nazareth!
And I'll do it with a sword.
You cry over Roman blood?
Human life!
Romans are not human.
Your hate will only
harm you, friend.
Hate can be a useful weapon,
used correctly...
and I'm not your friend.
Wait...
Is your lsrael free
now that these men are dead?
No.
Then follow me.
I will show you
how to be free.
I am the way.
You!
Tax collector!
What is your name?
Levi, son of Alphaeus.
Well, now your name
is now Matthew.
Do you wish to kill
this collector of Caesar's taxes?
Follow me, Matthew.
Where?
To your home.
Come Judas,
son of Simon lscariot.
Your fate is with me.
How did he know my name?
Follow him,
and find out.
( chattering )
This food...
it was bought
with stolen money.
I told him that!
Bless you.
Matthew, thank you
for your hospitality.
Rabbi, why do you do this?
Do what?
Eat with me...
a tax collector.
Don't you see
how they hate me?
And they are right.
I despise myself.
Why?
I steal from them...
from all of them.
Then stop.
Give back everything,
and come with me.
It's simple.
James, Peter,
you're not eating.
It's very good.
I'm trying to love him, Rabbi.
I really am.
Keep trying, Peter.
Keep trying.
( drums and cymbals )
Happy birthday, my King.
( cheering )
Wonderful, Salome!
Delightful!
A gift, worthy of a gift.
Give her
whatever she wants!
I hope it's me!
( laughing )
Whatever you want.
I pledge it
to you tonight, Salome.
Anything?
Anything.
( cheering )
Come now,
that's not fair, Salome.
Your mother's desires
are far too expensive.
( laughter )
Anything?
Now, my dear,
it's just a dance.
You promised!
"Anything", you said!
Pay up, Herod Antipas!
Anything.
I want the head
of John the Baptist.
But, my dear--
Will you not rid me
of this vermin?!
Bring me the head
of John the Baptist.
On a platter!
I forgive you.
I will live again
in the kingdom of heaven.
( drumming and clapping )
Water!
Andrew, friends, come.
Andrew...!
( laughter )
( screaming and shouting )
Adulteress!
Shame on you, adulteress!
Caiaphas!
All right, all right.
Jared...
I've heard this Joseph of Nazareth,
has just entered the city.
"Jesus" of Nazareth.
Only moments ago.
Is this the one who claims
to be the Messiah?
He is one of the ones
who claims this, my lord.
Good.
Take the girl to him,
and ask this "Messiah"
to judge her.
Test him in front of the people.
Show him to be a charlatan,
and they will lose interest.
We have to expose these fakes.
They are dangerous men.
Bring her.
The kingdom of heaven
is like a treasure,
buried in a field.
And when you find this treasure--
( angry voices )
Stone the adulteress!
Adulteress!
She's an adulteress!
Teacher!
This woman was caught in the act
of committing adultery.
In the law, Moses commands us
to stone such women.
What do you say, Teacher?
They are baiting him.
It's a trap.
I was told you preach
according to the law of Moses.
Do you have an answer,
Nazarene?
Let anyone among you
who is without sin...
be the first to cast their stone.
( crowd murmurs )
There is no man here
who condemns you?
No one, my lord.
Neither do l.
Go your way.
And from now on,
do not sin again.
I want to see the Temple.
I'll tell you more tomorrow.
Do you want to come with us?
Where?
Does it matter?
Yes.
I go where I want.
I'm free.
You're not free.
But you could be.
Why don't you come with us?
You treated her like...
Iike she was worth something.
So are you.
( chattering )
Change your coin
to temple currency!
Purest gold!
Pure gold!
I have the best price--
This is my Father's house!
My Father's house
is a house of prayer,
not a house of trade!
We pay tithes,
butthey care more
about Caesar than about God!
They have forgotten
the Word of God!
Do you say that we should not
pay taxes to Rome?
Stop!
That's my money!
Who's image is on this coin?
Caesar!
Then give to Caesar
what is Caesar's,
and give to God
what is God's!
I will make this
the house of God again!
( yelling and protesting )
( cracking )
Get out!
Get out of here!
This is the renewal
of lsrael!
Take these things
out of here!
Stop making my Father's house
a mocked place!