Subtitles By Sub-VidzClipz
www.sub-vidzclipz.com
Do you ever feel
like a plastic bag
Drifting throught the wind
wanting to start again
Do you ever feel,
feel so paper thin
Like a house of cards,
one blow from caving in
Do you ever feel
already buried deep
Six feet under scream
But no one seems
to hear a thing
Do you know that
there's still a chance for you
Cause
there's a spark in you
You just gotta
ignite the light
And let it shine
Just own
the night
Like the Fourth of July
Cause baby
you're a firework
Come on show 'em
what your worth
Make 'em go
"Oh, oh, oh!"
As you shoot
across the sky
Baby
you're a firework
Come on,
let your colors burst
Make 'em go
"Oh, oh, oh!"
You're gonna leave
'em fallin' down
You don't have to feel
like a waste of space
You're original,
cannot be replaced
If you only knew
what the future holds
After a hurricane
comes a rainbow
Maybe you're reason
why all the doors are closed
So you can open one that leads
you to the perfect road
Like a lightning bolt,
your heart will blow
And when it's time,
you'll know
You just gotta
ignite the light
And let it shine
Just own the night
Like the Fourth of July
Cause baby,
you're a firework
Come on show 'em
what your worth
Make 'em go
"Oh, oh, oh!"
As you shoot
across the sky
Baby
you're a firework
Come on,
slet your colors burst
Make 'em go
"Oh, oh, oh!
You're gonna
leave 'em fallin' down
Boom,
boom, boom
Even brighter
than the moon,
It's always been
inside of you,
And now it's time
to let it through
Cause baby,
you're a firework
Come on show 'em
what your worth
Make 'em go
"Oh, oh, oh!"
As you shoot
across the sky
Baby,
you're a firework
Come on,
slet your colors burst
Make 'em go
"Oh, oh, oh!"
You're gonna leave 'em
goin "Oh, oh, oh!"
Boom,
boom, boom
Even brighter
than the moon,
Boom,
boom, boom
Even brighter
than the moon,