[No sound]
[brakes screeching,
cars crashing, glass breaking]
[sirens blaring]
[indistinct radio
transmissions]
?
Woman: we've yet to find
a working number
for his father.
We've called friends.
She never
talked about him,
or even mentioned
any brothers or sisters.
There's no relatives
on file.
If we find
a working number
for his father,
and he doesn't answer,
we'll leave a message.
The state will handle
funeral arrangements.
Man: check the file again.
The boy has
a grandmother
in moorpark, colorado
on his mother's side.
I've been trying to call her,
but she hasn't been
answering the phone.
I'll look again--
just prepare
the foster care paperwork,
in case she chooses
not to return our calls,
or decides not to
take him in.
With him turning 18
next summer, who knows
where he'll end up.
[Truck horn honking]
? I can feel you
in the distance?
? I saw you glimmer
in the sun?
? But I can't stand
looking right at you?
? Wish you'd tell me
what I've done?
? Like a fire
that keeps on burning?
? And I keep trying
to blow it out?
? I don't wanna
keep on watching?
? It burns each time
I drink it down?
? I'm lost in
my weakness?
? I'm breaking
into pieces?
? Is anyone
waiting for me?
? On the other side
of the street??
? I need a lift
to take me home?
? I saw you standing
in the shadows?
? Watching over me
at night?
? I'm gonna swim
across this ocean?
? But I can't do it
on my own?
? I'm lost in
my weakness?
? I'm breaking
into pieces?
? Is anyone
waiting for me?
? On the other side
of the street??
? I need a lift
to take me home?
? How do I keep
moving on?
? If all that I love
is gone??
? I need a sign
to give me hope?
[Knocks loudly]
can I help you?
Are you, uh,
wallace russo?
That would be mrs. Wallace
to you, young man. And you are?
Your problem for
the next nine months.
I will not be disrespected
in my own home.
I don't care who you are
or what you want from me.
I'm only gonna ask
your name one more time.
You can stay out here
until you find out.
[Knocking on door]
[knocking louder]
my name is aldo russo.
You do speak.
Well, come in.
You're not what
I expected.
Sorry to be
a disappointment.
I didn't mean it
like that.
Why don't you
go eat your food
before it gets
any more cold
than it is.
Can I just
go to bed?
I thought there was
supposed to be
a social worker with you.
I didn't expect you
to be alone.
Well, I am.
Your room
is upstairs.
[Sobbing]
[dialing]
hi, you reached emilia.
sorry i...
- mom!
- aldo, I'm on the phone.
aldo!
[laughing]
[answering machine beeps]
i, um...
Stupid.
This is so stupid.
I know
you won't get this.
I just needed
to hear your voice.
I just wanted to...
[Dial tone droning]
[dialing]
you hungry?
Well, if you
get hungry...
Can I sit down?
I was just getting up.
Go ahead. Finish.
Hi. I'm lorri mcglocklin.
I'm aldo's
social worker.
I am so sorry I'm late.
I fully intended to--
- come in.
- Okay.
You know, miss scott
from the d.H.S in jersey,
she wasn't able to
forward me all of
the information
in time for
aldo's arrival.
Doesn't help that
we are so understaffed.
- Please sit down.
- Oh, thank you.
Hi. Well, at any rate,
we're all
caught up now,
and I apologize
on our behalf.
We'll work together
to make this a smooth
transition, okay?
Well, uh, why don't
we start with you.
- How did it happen?
- I'm sorry?
- The accident.
- That information
wasn't released to you?
I didn't get
all the details.
You know what? Mrs. Wallace,
if you don't mind,
- we can start
someplace else--
- why do you care?!
I am trying to understand.
It doesn't matter!
I'm here and she's dead!
- She's dead!
- I just wanna
understand what happened.
Look...
Mrs. Wallace,
it's very important that
this is something you wanna do,
in order to make
this relationship work.
Well, at the end of the day,
I don't really think I have
anything to offer him.
You do, you do.
You can offer
him comfort.
Comfort's a pretty hard
thing to come by
for a kid in
his position.
Don't you think so?
It's not about
what I think or what I feel.
Emilia is still dead.
He will never let that go.
Does he remind you
of emilia?
Yes. Sometimes.
I've made good
by not letting him know.
My past has been
very confusing.
I've done a lot of things
I'm not proud of
that I wish I could've
done differently.
Listen, mrs. Wallace,
whatever happened
in your past,
it just doesn't matter,
because I think there
might be something
good in there
for both of you.
Why don't you let me
go through this whole
program with you.
Okay? I'm gonna take you
through it step by step,
and I'm gonna give you
all the information,
and we'll talk
about your options.
Is that okay?
Yeah.
Okay.
[Water running]
[knocking on door]
[knocking continues]
[knocking louder]
oh, uh...
[Giggles]
sorry.
- Hi.
Um, is mrs. Wallace here?
I don't know.
You can look around
if you want.
I've never
seen you before.
- You live here now?
- Just passing through.
Temporary.
Well... I'm sure
you'll find it
very warm at
mrs. Wallace's.
What's your relation?
Still trying to
figure that out.
Not much of
a conversationalist, are you?
Not much conversation
to be had.
- Well...
I'm gonna go.
- Yeah.
I come here on saturdays
to help mrs. Wallace
out around the house,
but since she's not here,
can you tell her that
madalyn stopped by?
- Sure.
- Thanks.
Perfect.
[Engine sputters]
- what are you doing?
- I didn't mean to--
to what, touch things
you're not supposed to
be touching in the first place?
- I didn't think
that you'd mind.
- Well, I do mind,
and why is
no concern of yours.
[Sound of brakes screeching,
metal colliding]
[sobbing]
[container clatters
on floor]
- hi, mrs. Wallace.
- Hey.
- Nice day, isn't it?
- Mm-hmm.
Let me help you
with this.
Thank you, sweetheart.
You never came by
last week.
Something special happen?
I did, but
you weren't home.
I left a message
with that boy
who's staying here.
- Oh, well,
he never talks much.
- Yeah, I got that impression.
I'm sure there's
some good in him.
It's just getting
it out that's hard.
- What's his name?
- Aldo. He's my grandson.
Mrs. Wallace,
you never told me
you had a grandson.
I didn't know
I had one.
Is emilia all right?
- She died.
- Oh, my god.
Mrs. Wallace,
I am so sorry.
- I shouldn't even
be prying into--
- oh, honey.
You know
there's no secrets here.
Maybe see if
he'll come help us.
You sure?
It doesn't seem like
he wants to be bothered.
That's his natural look.
Go on.
We never formally met.
I'm madalyn.
Wanna come down here
and give us a hand?
We could really use
the extra pair of hands.
I promise you it's not
as girly as you might think.
So what are you
writing about?
You're persistent.
You look like
you can use a friend.
A matter of opinion.
An opinion I'm sure
I didn't really ask you for.
I just thought,
since you're new
in town and all...
Do us both a favor.
Go back to gardening, okay?
Go ahead.
Run along. Shoo.
I'm sorry for your loss.
Could you please
just leave?
I'm sorry. I didn't
mean to...
Look, I don't know you,
and I don't wanna
fucking know you.
- Hey, aldo.
- I'm sorry,
mrs. Wallace.
I was just
trying to help.
Will you both
just leave me alone?
I'm gonna go,
mrs. Wallace.
No, no, stay.
Don't let him
bother you.
Come on.
I brought you some food.
I know you must be hungry.
You haven't been
downstairs all day.
- I'll just leave it here.
- Don't bother.
What did you say?
I said don't bother!
I'm not gonna
eat that.
- And you can stop being
so fake while you're at it.
- How dare you?
I've tried the best I can
to make this work.
You are not gonna make me
seem like the bad guy here.
You are the one with
the problem, not me.
I'm sure that's what
my mother was to you, right?
Something to get over.
Aldo.
Aldo!
- Aldo.
- What do you--
- what the fuck?!
You old bitch!
- It's gotta stop.
What do you want from me?
- You are not the only
one living here.
- I don't wanna live here.
You can have your tantrums,
be all depressed if you want to.
I refuse to be,
and I refuse to let you
walk all over that place
like you don't care,
like no one cares.
Listen, I'm only your problem
until next summer,
so you won't have to
worry about it anymore.
Until then, I'm gonna
get some respect from you.
I don't have to
listen to this.
You're not my mother.
Right. I'm not your mother.
I do not deserve
to be treated like this.
I know emilia raised you
better than that.
- What did you say?
- You're gonna hit
an old woman?
I dare you. I dare you!
[Frustrated yell]
- you don't know me.
- That's right,
I don't know you.
I don't pretend
to know you.
I don't consider you
a child, but you sure
are acting like one.
Consider me gone.
You're not going anywhere.
Get back in the house.
You have school tomorrow, aldo.
Aldo! Aldo!
Aldo!
Well, lord, where have
you been hidin'?
Hiding. Wish I could.
Madalyn came by.
She told you?
Oh, shirley, I don't
know what I'm doing.
I'm too old for this.
Oh, wallace, you just old
when it's convenient for you.
So...
He's your daughter's son.
Shirley, he's so beautiful.
He looks just like her.
Well, I believe it.
The sun envied that girl.
- He is so angry.
- As well he should be.
And he's disrespectful,
and he's rude, not to
mention, his name is aldo.
Oh, he's an aldo junior.
He doesn't even know
his grandfather's name
was aldo.
Every time I look at him,
I see emilia and aldo.
He looks more like her,
but he's hard-headed like
the old man was.
Well, he's probably
in pain, hurt.
He's just young
and needs somebody
to guide him.
Plus, he's livin'
with a stranger.
Stranger?! Stranger?
- Is that what I am?
- That's exactly what you
are, wallace, a stranger.
That boy doesn't know you.
He's never even met you.
What did you
expect him to do,
just come in and instantly
run into your arms?
- Well?
- You know you ran
your daughter off.
How many times you
gonna tell me that?
- Until you get it
through your head.
- Well, it is through.
In one ear
and right out the other.
What happened between
you and her is what
put that man in his grave.
I'll never understand it.
That girl dreamt of
being anywhere but here.
She never cared about
nobody but herself.
Wallace, how can you
go and say somethin'
like that?
Care. Care!
She loved you, wallace.
She wanted more
for her life.
for her life than
just livin' in a house
that's been here
hundreds of years,
and I don't blame her.
That girl wanted
to see the world.
And I remember.
She waited, and she
waited for your approval.
You never gave it to her,
so what did she do?
She left,
and when she did,
aldo was never the same.
Mm-mm. He was not
right after that.
Now listen to me, sister.
You get a second chance
now with this boy.
Most people don't
get a second chance, wallace,
but god gave that to you.
Don't you run this boy off
like you did her.
You hear me?
Now come on.
Let's go get us some tea.
[Knocking on door]
time for school.
Get up.
- I'm not going.
- That's what you think.
What the hell?!
- Time for school.
- Are you crazy?
Get dressed.
The bus is coming
in an hour.
And I'm sure
I won't be there.
you will. Ha ha!
[Angry yell]
oh, god!
- Aldo.
- I went to
school, okay?
- How was it?
- School.
I know, but did
you meet anyone?
Really, come on,
let's not do
this right now.
- I'm gonna go to my room
if that's okay with you.
- Aldo, i--
look, I'll go to
school and back
because you're forcing me.
We don't have to
talk about it.
We don't have to be
friends or anything,
okay?
- Okay?
- [Thunder rumbling]
so you just
leave me alone,
I'll leave you alone.
It'll be like
I was never here.
? I'm so tired
of the myth that goes?
? That nice guys come first
and bad ones come last?
? I should know by now
? Things are not
what they seem?
? And if I do,
then I must be crazy?
? 'Cause time has taught me
that in order to play the game?
? You must be willing to
throw away your self?
? If I can't be
part of the game?
? I'll end up losing
every ounce I have left?
?
[Phone rings]
- [ringing continues]
- hello.
Yes.
What are you saying?
I thought being
waited up for
- stopped when you were
12 years old.
- Stop it!
Just stop. I've let you
walk all over me
these past months.
I'm not gonna let you
stand there and lie
to my face.
[Derisive laugh]
lie about what?
You know what
I'm talking about.
Your principal
called this morning.
You haven't been in school.
I'm sitting there on the phone
feeling like a fool,
feeling like
a goddamn fool,
because it never
occurred to me
that you could be
so deceptive, so manipulative.
Aldo, I'm at a loss
for words.
There's nothing
left to say.
You can't stay here.
This just isn't gonna work.
Pack your things and leave.
You're in god's hands now.
Now you wanna bring
god into this.
When he's ready,
I'll be here waiting.
I'm sure he's already
figured out...
Aldo. Aldo, stop.
Who are you
trying to fool?
Look around. There's
no one here for you
to be tough in front of.
If you're in pain,
be in pain.
If you're in mourning,
mourn. Why don't you cry?
I am in pain!
I am angry!
I've lost all feeling!
I'm numb to everything.
Numb to everyone.
Can't you see
that I'm suffering?
[Crying]
I'm not this person.
I don't know
how I got like this.
My life, it's so...
I just want it to end.
Aldo, stop.
Do you know what it's like
to sit at home
and wait for someone
who you know is never,
ever gonna come back?
Still, you sit there
and you wait.
You think to yourself,
what was the last thing
I said to 'em?
Did I say anything at all?
Do you know what that's like?
I do.
- Yeah.
- I do.
I drove your mother away
and sat by that door for months,
waiting for her
to walk through it.
Waited by the phone
for a phone call.
Mail couldn't get here
fast enough.
Anything so I'd know
she was fine.
It's my fault that
I wasn't in your life.
I don't know you.
I wake up with that
every morning.
sense of lost time every day.
But I refused to let it
do to me what it did before,
what it did to
your grandfather,
what it did to us.
[Sighs]
I know what
you're going through.
[Rueful chuckle]
believe me.
I know very well.
Emilia was taken from you.
You had no choice.
I had every choice.
And I made the wrong choice.
I'll never forgive
myself for that.
I live with that
every day.
I'll live with that
till the day I die.
I'd like to stay...
If you'd let me.
I'm sorry.
You didn't do
anything wrong.
Look at the way I've been,
the way I've treated you.
- I've been such an ass.
- How could you have known?
I was wondering if
you wouldn't mind
me taking a look
in the shed at the car.
I know you don't like
people messin' with it and--
go ahead. Nothing you can do
to it that hasn't already
been done.
- Really?
- Sure.
Madalyn: aldo?
Mrs. Wallace told me
you'd be in here.
Said you might
be thirsty.
Peace offering?
Is that freshly squeezed?
I don't think so.
Well, then,
the war must go on.
This car's been
broken for a while.
Not broken.
Sleeping.
So you're trying
to wake it up or something?
- Trying.
- Maybe it wants to sleep.
If you never try,
you'll never know.
Can I help?
Are you a girl
that likes to get dirty?
Excuse me?
Gloves.
So I haven't
seen you at
school yet.
- Yeah, I haven't
been going.
- Why?
I guess I wasn't
quite ready for
the world yet.
Is everything okay?
I don't know.
Like that car out there?
Yeah, it's pretty cool.
Where'd you learn
how to fix cars?
My mom's car would break down
all the time,
and she didn't have money
to pay someone to fix it,
so someone had
to learn how to.
What?
Can I show you something?
Look at this.
Who's this?
- Hey, that's the car.
- That's your grandfather.
He looks just like me.
I think it's you
that looks just like him.
I'm named after him.
I never knew that.
There's a lot you and i
don't know about each other.
Your grandfather
loved that car.
I think that's why
you love it.
I want you
to have it.
- The picture?
- The car.
- Really?
- On one condition.
That you go back to school
and catch up on your studies.
Okay.
Can I keep this, too?
Sure.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
I'm gonna try
to be better.
I wanna be better.
I know.
?
So things gettin'
better now?
Well, I'm glad that
it happened,
but now that
it has happened,
sometimes I feel
more hopeless than
when it hadn't.
Am I really all he needs,
is he what I need?
You know, you've been
so set in your ways,
livin' your life,
this boy comes along,
you don't know what to do.
I want it to be
better for him.
I see him starting
to be better, it makes
me wanna be better.
I haven't felt
so alive in years.
I just can't help
but wonder where
it's going from here.
So hard to live
in the moment.
- Is it too late?
- For what?
As long as you got
life in you.
- I've made so many mistakes.
- No, now, wallace,
you made one big mistake,
and you've let it run
your life ever since.
I was so wrong
about emilia,
but I loved her so much,
I couldn't let her go.
But there's nothing
wrong with that, honey.
Oh, shirley, I wish
I could believe you.
You know what?
That boy's gonna change you
in ways you don't even know.
I think he
already has.
Can I tell you something?
You deserve
to be happy.
Wallace, it has just broken
my heart to watch what
you've put yourself through.
But now, I know
what it was for.
It was for this moment
right here.
This moment right here.
Thank you.
[Shirley laughing]
oh, I'm sorry.
I didn't know
you were here.
Um, I shouldn't have...
I shouldn't have done
anything.
I'm really sorry.
Could you do
something for me?
- What?
- Come here.
Okay.
Could you tell me
about her?
- About mom?
- Yeah.
What was she like?
I don't know...
She used to always dream
about going to new york
and seeing
the statue of liberty.
Please do not remind me
of that trip.
- She went?
- Yeah, we both went.
We stayed at her friend's
studio for a week.
All four of us...
It wasn't the best
of experiences.
But me and mom
were really close.
We told each other
everything.
She was one of
my best friends.
My only best friend;
we moved around a lot.
I even tried to set her up
with a few of my friends'
single dads.
She started dating
one of them, and I realized
it wasn't
such a good idea.
Let me show you something.
This is a picture
your grandfather
took of me in paris.
Wow.
Your mother used to love
to look through these pictures.
She'd always say she was
gonna visit all these places.
Really?
All of her favorite stories
were of me and your grandfather.
She couldn't sleep at night
without a story.
Why'd she leave?
Well, your mother
was very ambitious.
She had a long list
of things she wanted
to do in her life.
Like what?
Like ride something
bigger than a horse.
Travel around the world,
write a book.
After graduation,
she wanted to
go to college,
and god bless her,
she got in.
She wanted to
study abroad.
What did she
wanna study?
She didn't know.
She just wanted
to get outta here.
Out of colorado.
That was at the top
of her list, to get
as far away
as she could from here.
You know,
she never finished school.
- She didn't?
- No.
Because of me, she didn't
do half the things that
you just said.
- It's not your fault.
- Then whose is it?
Aldo.
I'm just tired.
Hey.
Hi.
Writing your book?
More like thoughts
rather than a book.
Whatcha thinkin' about?
If I told you,
they wouldn't be thoughts,
but something I said,
which would make it
a quote,
and I'm not
writing quotes, so...
But you're writing it down.
But I'm the only one
readin"em,
so they still stay
my thoughts.
You write about me?
- Wouldn't you
like to know?
- I would.
I would.
Okay, but if I read
you something,
you gotta promise
not to laugh.
- What if it's funny?
- No, you gotta promise.
- No laughing.
- Scout's honor.
Isn't that only valid
if you're actually a scout?
I was for,
like, 15 days,
but who's counting?
Okay.
"In jersey,
I'd never find this."
See, I first wrote this
because...
I so badly wanted
to take back how
I treated you.
"Be nice to her.
"Because to wake up
and see her
there's nothing better."
I'm sorry.
I shouldn't
have done that.
Wait.
Well, can I hear
some more?
No.
But can i
see you again?
No.
You're glowing.
- I am?
- She's a nice girl.
- Who?
- Madalyn.
- Yeah, she's pretty cool.
- Just cool?
Come on, grandma, what--
ooh, grandma.
I like it.
Yeah. Me, too.
What's the rush?
Gotta get some sleep.
Madalyn wants to go
horseback riding tomorrow.
Do you know how
to ride a horse?
No, but how hard
can it be?
- Hey, aldo?
- Yeah?
You okay now?
No, but for once,
I know I will be.
First time really?
There's more to this city boy
than you think.
Yeah, I'm beginning
to see that.
Hey, you hungry?
- Yeah.
- Let's go.
This is actually
pretty good.
Good to know, 'cause
it's about the only
thing I make good.
I'll have you know I'm actually
a wolfgang puck in the making.
He's a famous chef.
Yeah, I knew that.
Yeah.
What's the city like?
You've never left
this place?
No.
Everyone who lives here
is practically born
and raised here,
just like their parents.
Well, it's loud,
for one.
Unlike this place.
And it's definitely
not like this
when you're sittin' behind
a red light in traffic.
- Where are you from?
- Trenton.
It's in new joisey.
I know a trenton.
- Oh, yeah?
- Yeah.
I'm sure there's
no relation.
My dad lives
in california.
Your dad lives
in california?
Mm-hmm.
Him and my mom
got a divorce
about three years ago.
I mean, they fought
all the time.
You never told me that.
Aldo, it's not a big deal.
That's everyone's story.
Who cares? You just...
Have to deal with it
the best way you can.
There are no victims
in life.
Life happens to us all.
When your father left,
how did it feel?
Good.
[Chuckles]
seriously.
I hated him so much.
I hated him so much
for taking the easy way out.
And I hated my mom
for letting him.
You asked me
why I was here.
I'm here because
I was in a car
accident with my mom.
I wish god had
taken me, but he didn't.
It gets better.
- When?
- I don't know,
but it does.
Come on.
Day's not over yet.
This is beautiful.
Nothin' like this
in the city?
One can only wish.
I used to come here a lot.
Not anymore.
Not for a long time now.
Why?
This is my dad's
favorite spot.
I used to come here
after he left.
It sucks losing someone
that you can't replace.
You still have
the memory, though.
And when I think about it,
I feel it.
And it's as though
the memory was
never lost at all.
So it's okay to be happy.
You'll never forget her.
It's like breathing.
Hey.
Hi. Always writing, huh?
Got a lot to say.
I, uh,
I wanted to give you this.
What is it?
It's a letter that
I never mailed.
- It's to mom.
- Open it.
What does it say?
[Laughs]
I wish my memory
were that good.
Why didn't
you send it?
Oh, I don't know.
So many reasons.
I'm sure they were
all stupid.
- You read it.
- Okay.
Okay.
"Dear emilia,
"I've spent the past months
looking around this empty house,
"and staring back at me
is nothing but an empty feeling.
"And now I fear
there's no changing that.
"How did we get here?
"I ask myself that
so many times.
"I love you, honey,
"and I was afraid for you.
"The world is not
what pictures
paint it to be.
"I never wanted you to
miss out on everything
you were made for.
"But I realize now
what you were made for
"is more than what
was around you.
"I'm sorry, emilia.
"If I could have
another chance
"to tell you
what I should've said
"when you asked to leave,
I would say,
"'don't miss out on
everything that's out there.
"'Until you spread your wings,
you'll have no idea...'"
[Laughs]
"how far you can fly.'
"Love, mom."
She would've
loved that.
You should have
sent it.
Oh, there's a lot of
things I should've done.
If you could,
would you take
everything and change it?
Of course I would.
Then that's
all that matters.
I guess we both
have to learn that.
And just live
a little more,
bit by bit each day.
I would do anything
to bring her back,
but I can't.
And neither can you.
When did you get so wise?
I don't know.
I guess I'm just
ready to start
living again.
But I want you
to live with me.
- Me?
- Yes.
Okay?
Okay.
- Okay?
- Okay. Okay.
?
Give it gas,
give it gas.
Keep pushing.
I got this.
Go, go, go!
Yes!
Wait!
- Where are we going?
- You'll see.
Wow.
No way.
- Is that you?
- Yeah.
I was something
to marvel at, wasn't ' i?
That was
back in the day.
I used to dance
and be wild and free.
That was a long time ago.
Things have changed a bit.
- Did you hear that?
- What?
- The music.
- What music?
Take my hand.
- May I have
this dance?
- Yes.
One, two, one, two.
One, two.
Oh, wow!
All right, all right.
?
Uh-oh.
Still got it.
? I found my face
in a photograph?
? I lost my words
in a paper bag?
? I caught my tears
the last time it rained?
? Sometimes I think
we're all the same?
? I heard your laugh
from across the room?
? I've held your hand
underneath the moon?
? I felt your love
when you looked at me?
? Seein' myself...
- No peeking.
- What is all this?
All right,
my eyes are closed.
- Really?
- I promise.
What is going on?
- All right.
- Okay?
Surprise!
Yeah!
- Make a wish.
Blah, blah, blah,
make a wish.
- Should we all
make a wish?
- Should we?
Thank you guys so much.
- Thank you so much.
- You're welcome.
Do you want a piece?
- Yes.
- Yeah, really,
you want a piece?
Oh, my god.
Are you serious? Okay.
?
Wow!
Is it too much?
No. Not at all.
Come on.
[Door squeaks loudly]
[car radio playing
mid-tempo hip-hop]
[turns volume up]
[laughing]
come on.
- [Groans]
- come on.
[Static, music changes
to romantic ballad]
?
Do you love me?
- Yes.
- Yeah.
?
Aldo, hurry up.
We're gonna be late.
- Do you have
everything?
- Yeah.
All right, mom,
let's go, go, go.
Been thinkin'.
About what?
About us.
Life after summer.
College.
Do you wanna go?
- Where?
- To college.
Do you? I think I wanna
stay here, ya know?
You're here,
grandma's here.
I just finally feel
like I'm gettin'
my head on straight.
- Is that bad?
- No. Not at all.
We could take
a year off,
and then apply
to colleges.
Colleges? Isn't there
only like, one
college in the state?
First of all, no.
And who says
we have to stay here?
You'd leave here?
Yeah.
I mean, maybe.
I don't know.
I've never had
to think about it.
If someone would've
told me a year ago
- that life
could be so--
- unexpected?
- I told you.
- How it wouldn't
hurt so much.
I'm sorry. I didn't
mean to bring up
any kind of memories.
No, no, no.
I'm just so happy
for once.
Good.
She would've
loved you.
I love you.
Wait.
Um...
I... I might
be bad at it.
How was it?
Perfect.
Really?
- Was it for you?
- Yeah.
Yeah, yeah, of course.
I just wasn't sure
if it was what you
were expecting.
- I just expected it
to be with you.
- That's great.
- I was just expecting you
to say something else.
- Like what?
I don't know.
Maybe you'd say
it wasn't what
you were expecting.
Then I'd say I didn't
have that much experience,
and that it was,
like, my first time.
- It was your first time?
- No, no--
- I'm kidding.
I'm kidding.
- Shut up.
I love you.
I can't get
enough of you.
You make me feel like...
Like everything's
gonna be okay.
As long as
we're together.
Everything will just
be good, ya know?
Just good?
Great.
I love your eyes.
What's so special
about my eyes?
You have no idea
how they say so much
about you.
Like what?
How you feel broken.
As if...
You're never
gonna heal.
But something in
your eyes shows hope.
So it's that obvious.
To me, it is,
because I see you now.
More than I think
others do.
I love you so much.
It's late.
I should
head home.
Right now?
Oh, come on.
Don't you wanna stay
just for a little longer?
Please?
- What's that for?
- I don't know.
That boy.
Can I help you
find something?
Aldo! Can I help you?
- Mrs. Russo?
- Yes. Can I help you?
Mrs. Russo, can i
speak with you for
just a minute?
About what?
- Just with you, ma'am.
- Aldo, go inside.
- Why?
- Just go inside.
What happened?
- What happened?
- Sit down.
Come on,
someone say something!
- Sit down.
- I don't wanna sit down.
Aldo, sit down!
Grandma, you okay?
Tell me. What is it?
What happened?
Hey. Hey.
I wanted to
talk to you.
My name is david warwick,
and, uh...
How do I even say it?
You're my son.
I just thought that
if I could see you
and explain...
Explain what?
- Did you know
about this?
- No.
Son...
Don't you dare call me that,
don't you dare call me that.
Hey, I know you must
think that I'm--
that you're a lowlife?
- A good-for-nothing
piece of shit?
- Aldo!
- You do not understand.
- Oh, please, help me.
I don't expect
anything from you.
I won't let you
do this to me.
I can't stand
the sight of you.
You left me and my mom.
And now... And now,
you wanna come back?
You're right not to
expect anything from me.
I grew up just fine!
You are not missed,
so you can leave!
Leave!!
Listen, if you just
let me explain, I swear,
I will leave.
- Fine. I'll leave!
- No, aldo. Aldo!
Aldo. Aldo!
I'm sorry.
I, uh, just thought
if I could see him,
I'd be okay again.
I didn't think about
how he'd be, or what
he's been through.
I'll be staying
here for the next
couple of days.
If he comes around,
I'd love to
talk to him.
Sorry, ma'am.
I wish I could
just be someone else,
someone better off than me.
- Different person,
different problems.
- But still problems.
What'd she tell you?
Enough.
- You didn't go home
last night.
- I couldn't.
You know, out here,
everything in itself
is so simple and perfect
and I just thought
that maybe--
why are you doing
this to yourself?
Doing what?
Letting it
affect you like this.
It was all right before.
It'll be all right again.
- Talk to him.
- About what?
Something. Say anything
until you say what
you need to say.
I have nothing
I need to say to him.
You will relive this
for the rest of your life
wishing you had said
too much instead of
nothing at all.
You'll find that
it's easier said than done.
Didn't you tell me that
I needed to move on from this?
Well, I moved on
from this years ago.
This is different.
I've already
made up my mind.
I'm leaving
after the summer.
Leaving?
College.
T.C.N.J. In jersey.
What?
You applied to college?
It's not like that.
I wasn't gonna go.
I just wanted to see
if I could get in.
I thought we agreed
to take a year off.
Apply together.
Madalyn, I wasn't
going to go.
Were you gonna tell me
when your bags were packed?
No.
No, i...
I just think that now,
it might be best,
so I don't find myself needing
to rely on anyone but myself.
Myself.
It is so sad to see
how easy it is
for you to think
about yourself.
You can run
as much as you want,
you... You coward!
- Madalyn, it--
- no, I can't...
Unfeel the way I feel
for you just because
you don't need me to.
But, one day,
you are gonna wake up.
You are going
to wake up!
And realize you could've
been something better.
Look, every word
I said, I meant.
I meant every word.
Oh, god.
I let you get
the best of me.
But...
It is obvious that
what we have is not
the real thing.
Hey. Hey, hey.
- How can you
say that?
- Oh...
How can you say that?!
Would you come with me?
Oh, and do what?
We'll figure it out.
Oh, that's
a great idea, aldo.
Look, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry!
Stop saying that!
Please.
- I'm sorry.
- Stop.
I still feel like
this is where I need to be.
Even if you don't.
You can leave here
just the way you came.
Madalyn!
You should talk to
your father
before you have nobody
but yourself left to lie to.
Aldo?
Where have you been?
I'm sorry if
I scared you.
I just needed
some time to think.
It felt like everything
was just crashing down
around me.
Talk to me.
- About what?
- About your father.
My father?
I don't even
know the guy.
Don't you wanna
know why?
- Aren't you pissed?
- Why?
He just shows up
out of nowhere.
No warning,
no phone call.
That makes him and you
more alike than you think.
You should talk to him.
I'm here for you,
whatever you decide.
You want anything to drink?
Yeah, I could use
something to drink. Thanks.
It's a little warm.
It's from earlier.
It's fine.
Thanks.
I didn't think
you'd come.
To think all I could say,
all I would say...
You know, I never knew.
Knew what?
About you.
Yeah. I, uh...
I dated your mom...
When she was a freshman
at perdue,
and I was a senior
in high school,
till one day,
she just up and left.
Now I know why.
Why now?
I don't know.
They called
over a year ago.
Left a voicemail.
By the time I got
the courage to call back,
months had already passed.
To find out
you have a son, overnight...
I can't tell you
how that felt.
Why didn't she tell me?
Did she think I wouldn't
be a good father?
I would've loved you
the best I could.
I deserve that.
That was just
taken away from me.
You have a family now?
Yeah.
Three girls.
Six, ten, and, uh... 14.
- No mom?
- No.
She left me and the girls
a short time after
emily was born.
I was never the best man
for her,
but she always seemed to
give me another try.
Emily.
Yeah, emily's the youngest,
and sasha's the middle,
and then, savannah...
God, I tell you,
you look exactly how
I thought you'd look.
What did you expect?
You look like her.
Emilia.
I'm sorry.
Sorry.
Ya know...
I really could've
used a father after
what happened.
You know, I just...
I wondered if I'd
make things worse.
Hell, you'd just
lost your mother.
Would you have even
wanted me around?
Person you didn't
even know?
But when you find out
you have a son,
or just a child
in general,
it's, like,
nothing is the same.
I started
to search for you,
but you had already
turned 18; c.P.S.
Had closed your file,
wouldn't tell me
a damn thing.
But I felt like
if I never tried,
I would never know.
- I always say that.
- Say what?
If you never try,
you'll never know.
I promise you...
If I'd have known
she was pregnant...
I'd have been
a good father to you.
Yeah, you seem like it.
Thank you.
It's just, my life...
It's been so difficult
lately.
Every time I take
a couple of steps forward,
it's like something
sends me four steps back.
Then there's this girl,
and I didn't wanna hurt her,
and I just...
I really messed things up.
Now I don't even...
- Sorry, never mind.
- No, no. Tell me.
Tell me.
Well, I love her.
I think.
You never been in love?
I don't know.
How do you know?
Hoo!
Well...
When you wake up
in the morning,
it's the first thing
that comes to mind.
And when they're hurting,
you somehow feel it.
And when they're not around,
time does move slower.
Yeah, I'm definitely in love.
What happened?
Me...
Just me, running my mouth
before thinking about
what I'm saying.
Sometimes I build myself up,
and I tear myself down
all at the same time.
I don't know
what to do.
how to deal with things.
Yes, you do.
Hey, you know how to
deal with things just fine.
You're here, aren't you?
You're dealing with this.
Hell, if we were all
so well-put together,
what would we
experience
in life?
You're gonna
be okay.
But how do you deal
with being alone?
Well, you're never
really alone.
There's always someone there
to keep you hangin' on,
make life good.
Yeah.
You know, i...
It's crazy...
How something can just
change your life
and wake you up.
I mean, like really
wake you up.
I laid in that hospital bed
for days,
thinking the same thing
over and over again.
What?
If you don't create change,
change will create you.
To think
it took me so long
to really understand
what that meant.
Look, um, it's getting late.
I should go.
Grandma likes to
wait up for some
stupid reason,
- and the couch is really
not that comfortable.
- Aldo...
My flight leaves tomorrow.
I can get you a ticket.
You know...
Only if you want.
Come by before you leave.
I will.
Hey.
Come on, you should've
went to bed by now.
- Let's get you to bed.
- I got it.
I got it.
Did you go?
Yeah.
Good. I'm glad.
Me, too.
- Hey.
- Aldo.
- I can't...
- I know.
But maybe you can call me
from time to time,
just to
check up on me
if you want.
Yeah, I'd like that.
Here's my cell.
Thanks.
[Glass shattering]
mrs. Wallace?
[Siren wailing]
she received
a head trauma,
we're assuming
when she fell.
Your grandmother
suffered a heart attack,
and quite frankly,
the head trauma
is just not helping us.
She's alert,
but her vitals
continue to drop.
I wanna prepare you.
She may not make it
through the night.
We're gonna keep her
comfortable, continue
to monitor her,
[voice echoing]
but we've done
all we can.
She's down the hall.
This would probably be
a good time to see her.
Madalyn: I called
ms. Shirley doyle.
I'm so sorry.
You should go in there.
[Moaning]
aldo?
Grandma.
Is your father
out there?
Yeah. Everyone's here.
How are you feelin'?
Not good,
but I know
I will be soon.
I love you so much.
[Monitor beeping steadily]
I got into college.
You got in.
Yeah. I'm gonna go, too.
Oh, I'm so glad.
Will you do something
for me?
Anything.
Will you read to me?
Sure.
Do you have a book
you want me to read?
Your book.
Okay.
"You look around,
"and staring back at you
is all you know--
"doubt, fear of failing,
"falling, life unexpected.
"But just because
it's all you know,
"it doesn't mean
it's all you could.
"The refusal to let
fear control you
"will let you experience
the beauty of what inspires us.
"Even when you feel
like giving up,
"and you don't know
where you're going,
"the whole point
of being alive
"is to become the person
you were meant to be.
"You don't
have to be afraid.
I'm not afraid.
Not anymore."
[Flatline sounding
on monitor]
doctor!
- [Voices echoing]
- nurse: get
the crash cart now!
Doctor: she's flatlining.
I need to start
headin' out for
the airport, so...
You remember the way?
Yeah, it's my third time
flying out here.
I oughta know by now.
[Both chuckling]
- you leavin' tomorrow?
- Yeah.
I'll call you
before then.
You call me if
you need anything.
- All right?
- Thanks.
Okay.
? Purple mountains fall on
chimneys made of gold?
? To keep you warm inside
but tingling for more?
? I see you rockin' by
the fire of your home?
? But you keep on fadin'
? The bottle's deep enough
for heaven to unfold?
? But from this alley hell,
it's definitely cold?
? Mmm, do with
what you're told?
? To keep from fadin'
hi.
Hi.
Looks like
you're going somewhere.
Finally moving forward.
I just want to say
I'm so sorry.
Me, too.
Promise me one thing.
You won't forget
to remember me.
Never.
Come with me.
Is there room for one more?
Yeah.
What will you
do out there?
We'll figure it out.
- [Door squeaks loudly]
- I like the sound of that.
? So shine on, little light
? Shine on from heaven
? Show me it's all right
? Oooooooh
? You keep your balance
as you reach out from the dark?
? To touch a light that's
barely bright enough for talk?
? And everybody knows
that tickin's just for clocks?
? But you keep on fadin'
? Yeah, you keep on
fadin'?
? So shine on,
little light?
? Shine on from heaven
? Show me it's all right
? Stay strong,
my little girl?
? Look up to heaven
? They tell you
it's all right?
? That everything's
all right?
?
? Just lay down
? Little girl
? Eyes up to heaven
? They tell you
it's all right?
? Everything's all right