Lightfoot:
This is Black Ice, on team
syncing at Level Five security.
Base: Roger that,
we're locked.
Base: Your next contact
is at 0430 at Melbourne Station
- then you're home.
- Lightfoot: Roger that.
Going full stealth.
Mean and extreme.
Base:
Mean and extreme, Captain.
(beeping)
Lightfoot: I have a bogie
at heading 176,
in pursuit.
(rapid beeping)
(metallic clanking)
(groans)
(groan)
(shrieking)
(gunshots)
(sizzling)
(screams)
Woman:
...Dr. Leon?
Doctor: Can I help you
with something?
Woman: Yeah, what's wrong
with that man?
May I ask who you are?
I'm Loren Mercer.
I'm here to meet
Dr. Leon from World Health.
I'm Samuel Leon.
My associate, Susana Gabriel.
The man is suffering
from necrotic paralysis.
Thus far, we have been
unable to treat it.
Man:
Doctor, sorry, I'm late.
You must be Mercer?
Lev Valentine,
nice to finally meet you.
So you need a pilot
to fly you somewhere in the Celebes?
That's right.
Some of that area
is disputed territory,
I've led expeditions
in the South Pacific.
I'm concerned about the landing.
There's a runway from World War II.
No plane has landed there for years.
It's out of the way.
So how'd the sick man get out?
By boat. Think you can make a beach
landing if the strip's no good?
I do it all the time,
but if you're worried...
Worried?
No, not at all.
What sort of expedition
is this exactly?
Medical. The native
was brought in by a missionary.
He told us that
Toe Boy's people are dying.
- Toe Boy?
- He'll be our guide.
And along with the medical mission,
we'd also like to identify
and isolate the vector
as soon as we can
to determine the threat it presents.
In English?
Find out exactly what bit him, dear.
Bit him?
Bit him.
A spider, we think.
Toe Boy's not being clear about it.
Second thoughts?
No. Get your gear to the airport,
we'll take off tomorrow at 8:00.
Dr. Leon:
Excellent.
(plane engine hums)
(humming stops)
Mercer: Hey, are you
looking for something?
Man: I found this magnificent
specimen of Nephila Edulis...
That could be poisonous.
Put that down!
All spiders have venom.
Arachnids eat by injecting
their prey with either
a necrotic factor,
a neurotoxin, or both.
When the prey is paralyzed
they cover it with digestive enzymes
and suck a syrupy biomass
into their stomachs.
That's more than I needed
to know. Now, put it down.
My book on arachnids.
Oh, Henri Capri.
You can keep it.
I hate spiders.
Everyone does.
My theory is that we recognize them
as perfect predators
and fear them.
She's harmless.
You really like them, don't you?
- I understand them.
- I just step on them.
They want the same things we do...
food, shelter, and a mate
to propagate the species.
- Leon: Hi, Mercer.
- Good morning, Doctor.
- I see you've met Dr. Capri.
- Oh yes.
He's our entomologist.
- Capri: Look what I found.
- No more spiders!
That spider is not coming.
- It won't bother anybody.
- Please, Capri, no.
Capri: How's your patient,
Dr. Leon?
He died this morning
of massive pulmonary edema.
Literally drowned in his own plasma.
- Doctor.
- Thanks.
I had tissue samples
forwarded to the CDC...
Good morning, everyone.
Doctors, Mercer.
Hi.
I'd like you to meet my adjunct,
Bear, and Pablo Reyes.
- Nice to meet you.
- Where's our...
That's the one over there.
Okay, Bear, load it up.
(Bear whistles)
Tell me, if you're
not worried about anything,
then why are we carrying enough
firepower to overthrow a small country?
Simple equation.
The more guns I have,
the safer I feel.
Insects are notorious
for carrying viruses and microbes.
However, I doubt very much
that spiders are capable...
to carry or transmit a virus.
Capri: My thinking
is that first of all...
Plane's in good shape.
Huh?
Valentine: I said the plane
is in good shape.
I learned on an old Piper.
My dad flew a crop duster
out of Fresno.
So you flew in the Marines, huh?
How did you know I was Corps?
You and Bear are cut that way.
"Semper fi, me and mine,
Marines until
the day we die."
Hooray!
So how come didn't
pilot them in yourself?
You knew the South Pacific.
I figured you'd bring us back.
That's odd, considering
we've never met,
and I'm fairly new to this area.
A fighter pilot
the Navy was fast-tracking
until you abruptly resigned
your commission.
Now you fly charters.
I did a background check.
Why'd you resign?
Let's just say
I'm looking for something.
Yeah?
Aren't we all?
(Valentine giggles)
Look, I'm not interested
in companionship,
relationship or even a hump buddy.
- Let's keep it professional.
- What?
Sorry to be blunt.
Just want to be clear.
Mercer, get over yourself.
Yeah. Like you weren't
bird-dogging around, jarhead.
Two girls are sitting there,
butt-fucking-naked...
Really?
Mercer: Guys,
this is our island.
I'm going to circle and try
to find the landing strip.
(plane engine sputters)
Shit!
- What happened to the power?
- I lost it.
- Restart the plane.
- I can't.
Everyone strap in and hold on.
Go manual on the hydraulics.
Manual?
Okay, pump up flaps 10%
and increase by 10%
every five seconds and call it out.
Buckle up, everybody,
we're in for a rough ride.
- Valentine: Flaps at 10%.
- Hang on, we're gliding in.
- Valentine: Flaps at 20%.
- You know any prayers?
Flaps at 30%.
Flaps at 40%.
Full flaps!
Whoa, whoa... whoa!
(crashing)
Nice flying, Mercer.
Nice praying.
Bear: This is Alpha 6,
come in, please. I repeat,
I repeat, come in, please.
This is Alpha 6.
This is Alpha 6, over.
- Bear: I repeat...
- Okay.
Well, how's it looking, Mercer?
There's absolutely nothing
wrong with the engine.
Then what caused the power failure?
No idea, but no one
is going anywhere soon.
That's quite obvious.
Bear's been trying the radio system.
The satellite phone's not working.
There seems to be some sort
of natural magnetic interference.
I just thank God we're not dead.
God wasn't flying
the plane, Susie, I was.
This entire expedition
is in serious jeopardy
because of you, Miss Mercer.
I'd appreciate it
if you'd at least show
some respect to my colleague.
Okay.
As soon as we finish here
we want to have a strategy meeting.
See what we can salvage
from this disaster.
Okay.
Capri?
Reyes, you seen Capri?
- I haven't, sir.
- Would you look for him?
Reyes: Okay.
You better put on some Deet.
Mosquito-borne encephalitis
is serious business out here.
- Oh yeah?
- Yeah.
I'm mega dosing vitamin B.
It keeps insects away naturally.
I don't do
artificial anything, Güerita.
Dios mío.
(whirring)
(sizzling)
Dr. Capri?
(rustling)
¡Puta Madre!
Capri: Stop!
Stop!
- Stop!
- Valentine: What's going on?
We're okay!
Coming back in.
Doc, what the hell was that thing?
Now we won't know, will we?
Come on, Doc, come on.
I am not a little child.
Sorry, Doc. Big meeting,
you're invited.
- I have to collect my equipment.
- Go.
- Be careful.
Come on!
Valentine: Okay, here's
my recommendation.
We sit tight and try
to establish radio contact.
Mercer's checked the plane.
She thinks the engines are functional
and with any luck
we can probably attempt
a beach take-off.
I'm afraid we haven't had much luck
with the plane
or with Miss Mercer so far.
Yeah? If I don't get this plane
out of here then...
No, excuse me. We are here to give
medical aid to these people,
and learn what's killing them.
That's exactly what
we're going to do.
After we reach Toe Boy's village
we can discuss how best to proceed.
I don't think that's a good idea.
Mr. Valentine, I believe I'm still
in charge of this mission.
I'd rather take
my chances in the forest.
Every piece of electrical equipment
we had went out, including the plane.
I was in the cockpit. She's
the only reason that you're alive.
We break camp in the morning,
first light.
Bear, take the first watch.
Reyes, you spot him in four hours.
Yes sir.
That's liquid nitrogen,
Mr. Reyes.
If you accidentally drink it
it will freeze your esophagus.
Then the gas will expand inside you,
and you will blow up
like a balloon and explode.
(laughter)
Mercer:
Hey, hey, hey.
Where did you get this?
Do you understand me?
(Toe Boy speaking native language)
Here on the island?
(speaking native language)
- Valentine: Mercer.
- What?
I want you to reconsider.
- You should stay...
- Give me a brake. I'm not a baby.
Okay.
Good. Then I'll
see you tomorrow.
Good night.
Bear: This is Alpha 6.
Come in, please.
- Over. I repeat, this is Alpha 6.
- Any luck, Bear?
No, sir.
Mercer, I wouldn't take
what Leon says too seriously.
He's under a lot of stress.
What's Susie's story anyway?
Valentine: She was one
of his graduate students.
Became his assistant.
Wonder what she did
to earn her Masters?
Actually, Miss Mercer...
I spent three years
in the Brazilian rain-forest
classifying level III viral agents.
I was five months in Kikwit, Zaire,
tracking the source
of the Ebola virus.
That is where I met Samuel.
I can survive with just a knife,
shoot anything you put in my hands,
and I have a brown belt
in tae kwon do.
Impressive.
I just fly planes.
Apparently not well.
Anything else?
Yeah. I make
a great dehydrated stew,
and I can suggest something
for those unsightly blackheads
around your nose.
Quite a resume.
(laughs)
Okay, let's roll.
Get your gear, let's go.
Uhh...!
¡Chingado!
Stay away from there.
Puta madre.
¿Qué chingado es esto?
Aggh!!
Leon: Oye, Reyes,
¿qué pasó?
- Este chingado brazo.
- Déjame ver.
Wait!
These are ticks.
If you don't remove them correctly,
their venom
will remain under the skin
- and release neurotoxins.
- Fuck that! Get them off now!
You should have used
the insect spray, sir.
- (Reyes yells)
- Leon: Oh my God, look at that!
Yes, extraordinarily large.
Actually, this could be
a new species.
If you don't shut up, I'll kill you.
Okay?
Okay, cabrón?
Whoa!
Put the gun down.
Easy, buddy.
Easy. Breathe.
Put it down!
Look at me, God damn it!
Come on now, put the gun down.
Bear: That's it,
- Bear's got you.
- (Reyes groans)
I'll get them out.
Come on!
Susana, be careful.
We need to preserve
a sample of those ticks.
¡Vaya mierda!
- How you feeling, Doctor?
- I'm fine, it's just the heat.
Okay, everybody,
let's take a break here.
Take your packs off and take a rest.
Mercer?
Bear, do a reckon, five by five.
Yes, sir.
Susana, be careful with the water.
I need to wash him off.
Try to use as little as possible.
Mercer?
Mercer, are you okay?
Er... Mercer, there's ticks
out here. Be careful.
Look, I appreciate the heads up,
but I've been in the jungle before.
I can take care
of myself... Shit!
Mercer!
You okay?
Yeah.
Just stuck.
Huh.
It's not funny.
No, it's not.
Let's get you out of there.
Come on, you're stuck.
Aggh.
Oh God, look at this.
What?
It's all over
the inside of that hole.
I think there's something in here.
Well, don't piss it off.
Aggh!
Something's got my foot.
- Valentine: Hang on.
- Get me out of here.
Get me the fuck out of here, now!
- Bear!
- Get me out of here!
Get me the fuck out of here!
Shit!
Whew.
You okay?
Been better.
Stuck.
- Oh, shit.
- We're stuck.
(soft chuckle)
Okay. All right.
Ahem...
Okay.
Looks like spider silk.
- Your boot's still down there.
- Yeah, I know.
- Just leave it.
- You can't walk with one boot.
(grunts)
(hisses)
Look at this.
What could have done that?
(Reyes screams)
What's going on?
What the hell happened?!
Susana:
Help me!
(screaming)
(Reyes pants and screams)
Help me, I need to sedate him!
Easy partner, easy.
Easy, easy.
What's happening with him?
Shh!
Quieto, quieto.
Susana, what happened?
We were trying to get the ticks out.
As soon as we touched them
they buried deeper.
That's impossible.
Ticks don't move like that.
Okay, all right, this man's
in a lot of trouble.
Let's remove these ticks.
Is he going to be okay?
A field surgery would carry
a high risk of sepsis.
And if we try again to remove
them forcibly,
they could conceivably damage
something internally.
Will they harm him
if we leave them in?
The ixodides should simply disengage
once they're gorged with blood.
How are they gonna disengage?
They're under his skin,
for God's sake.
I don't know.
Come on, Capri.
You are the arachnologist.
Stiffen up, coño!
I... I don't know.
I've never seen or heard
of anything of the kind.
I don't know.
Doctor...
Your bedside manner
basically sucks, Doctor.
Can't you see the man is upset?
(Leon groans)
- (Reyes groans)
- Shh.
He's going to be all right.
Let's all get some Deet on.
Bear, let's get him up.
Where the hell did Capri go now?
That man's becoming a liability.
I'll get him.
Are you okay?
Sometimes I don't know
all the answers.
None of us do, Henri, all the time.
They look like ticks.
Something's not quite right here.
Yeah, I know.
I've been reading about ticks
in your book.
These days I never go anywhere
without it.
Come on, I need to spray you.
Cover your face.
I remember the first time
I soloed in an F-14 Tomcat.
I was so scared, I almost
planted it nose first into the deck.
They wanted to ground me.
I'm still flying.
We need you to take
a look at something.
Capri:
Um-hmm.
Mercer:
So what's the verdict?
Do you think it's spider webbing?
It would seem so.
Ridiculous.
The hole is much too large.
Agreed. A spider that large
couldn't exist.
Its internal organs would crush
under the force of gravity.
Maybe there's a simpler explanation.
Such as?
The Japanese occupied the islands,
dug tunnels everywhere.
Maybe this is one of those tunnels
that some spiders covered in silk.
That's certainly a plausible theory.
So what grabbed my boot?
(native language)
What is this, Capri?
These are normally found in caves.
I mean, it is an aganpofinus,
but it appears to be a mutation.
Mutated how?
Valentine: Dr. Leon
better come this way.
Where are they?
Maybe they're headed for the coast.
It smells like death here.
(in native language)
(thump)
(flapping)
What the hell do they
put on those darts?
Damn.
Normally that would be spider venom.
What kind of spider?
Most likely they use
the venom from a widow.
The neurotoxin can stop
a bird's heart in seconds.
Its even deadly to other spiders.
Now where was I?
Absolutely amazing.
Have a look, Doctor.
Ahh!
This specimen has no caeca.
I can't imagine
how it digests its prey.
Leon: What is
this structure?
It looks skeletal.
Capri: And that should
also be impossible.
Nothing with an external skeleton
has an internal one as well.
Nature would never be
so blatantly redundant.
Such a peculiar mutation
has never been on record.
(Reyes coughs)
Susana, can't you do
something about that man?
Yes, Doctor.
Is the sick man
bothering you, Doctor?
You bother me.
I'm tired of your attitude
and insults.
As you can see there's no one here.
This mission is over.
Why don't you go fix your plane
so we can get the hell out of here?
I'll talk to you later.
Mercer.
Hey Mercer!
I'm fine. I'm going...
- to do a little...
- Take it easy, will ya?
What are you looking for
out there? Huh?
I know.
I know it's not a relationship
or a hump buddy.
Just stay here, please.
Right here.
Wait.
I'm sorry I was a bitch on the plane.
Huh?
Look...
I found this on one of the natives.
Yeah, they've all got this.
It looks like parachute silk.
Yeah, well...
I think it belonged to my brother.
Your brother, what...?
(retching)
- It's okay. Breathe.
- (Reyes coughs)
It's okay.
(Reyes vomits)
Ahh!
(grunts)
No, please don't shoot it.
(coughing)
Samuel, do something!
- (grunting)
- (Rattling)
(rattling)
(grunting)
(crackling)
(heavy breathing)
(Reyes screams)
(hissing)
(footsteps)
Shit!
(in native language)
We're coming in.
Shit!
Mercer, what is it?
There's something in the jungle.
What did I tell you
about going in the jungle?
It's big...
(scream)
(in native language)
Go to the camp!
Everybody by the fire.
Mercer stay here!
(scream)
(growling)
(squealing)
- (thud)
- (Loud squeal)
(rustling)
(slithering)
(rattling)
(squeal)
(animal whistling)
Is everyone all right?
- Susana: Yes.
- Mercer?
Mercer?
My brother Joli was a Navy Pilot.
The plane he was testing,
a stealth craft,
disappeared 10 months ago.
The Navy stopped looking
after two months.
I didn't.
They never came to a real
conclusion about what happened.
Some bullshit about...
pilot error, presumed dead.
Too good a pilot.
Too good a man.
(Toe Boy, in native language)
(in native language)
My God!
What did this?
(in native language)
Capri: Apart from
the extraordinary size,
this is
inter-species mutation.
Like the small spider?
Yeah, but far
more biologically advanced.
These creature seem to be evolving
at lightning speed towards
becoming the ultimate predators.
I thought that was us.
If spiders were as big as cats
the human race would be finished.
Dr. Leon, we've got
to take it back with us.
We've got to get
ourselves back first.
You were hired to take us in
and bring us out, with the specimens.
Do you have a problem?
I got one man dead,
I got another man dying.
Your expedition's over, Doctor.
We head back
at first light, with specimens,
if there's anyone left to carry them.
I'm sorry, sir, I can't possibly go.
I'm going to send Bear
up into those hills tomorrow
to try to send a signal back to Guam.
The rest of us
are heading to the beach.
Doctor, please.
You can't stay here alone.
We're going to wait for help
or until that plane is airworthy.
- Valentine, I'm staying.
- Can't let you do that.
I'm not leaving without my brother.
- You can come back for him.
- No.
You were hired as our pilot.
Do yourjob.
We'll meet you
back at the plane tomorrow.
Yes sir.
Bear...
be careful, huh?
You bet your ass.
Mercer.
Mercer, I'll help you
find your brother.
You're right.
He's here somewhere.
Just help me get
these people out of here
and I'll come back with you.
- Okay.
- Leon: Where cojones is Capri?
Damn.
(soft buzzing)
I swear, when I find
that gilipollas entomologist...
? When I get home
I'm going to see my baby ?
? It's been long,
she's feeling kind of shady ?
? But I love her, oh I love her ?
? Yes I do, yes I do. ?
- (laughing)
- (Rustling)
Yeah. That's how we do it
back home, baby.
- (whoosh)
- (Screams)
Ahh!
Get behind me!
(rustling)
Ahh!
Don't worry about Bear,
he can take care.
Let's keep moving.
Let's go. Let's go.
Oh, fuck!
(Capri groans)
This is it.
Dying ecosystem.
A mutant...
a mutant, prominent,
arachnoid and reptilian features.
A predator of enormous potential,
and correctly
adapted for the environment.
However, it seems to be
destroying its own habitat.
Why? Huh?
(wheezing)
(squealing)
(sniffing and coughing)
Massive organic decay.
That's what we're smelling.
Yeah, but from where?
From what is the more
salient question.
Mercer.
What?
You better take a look at this.
My God!
Valentine: Your brother?
I'm so sorry for you.
What did this?
(in native language)
A spider.
Fuck the sonofabitch
that did this to you!
(wheeze)
Capri:
Web spiders produce
seven different types of silk,
sticky silk, web frame silk,
egg sack silk,
dragline...
cocoon silk.
(in native language)
(Capri groans)
Capri: It's injected
some kind of nerve toxin
into my spinal column.
Now so I don't feel much.
Although my nose,
does twitch occasionally.
This is truly astounding.
(Capri laughs)
Okay, I'm going to cut him loose.
No, stop! I beg you.
This stuff is stronger than
steel, and besides
you can't cut me
from the cocoon anymore.
My insides are feeding the eggs.
Whose eggs?
What is this thing?
Capri: I don't know.
It's spider-like.
It's massive.
If it breeds successfully...
So all the other spiders
are his offspring?
Yes, but they are not viable yet.
It hasn't found the right
genetic combination.
Leon: You're saying a giant
spider evolved in this island
and it's trying
to further adapt by evolution?
No. Nothing so large
and so alien
could have evolved in our gravity.
Alien?
(rumbling)
(in native language)
What? What did you say?
My God, is it here?
Out here somewhere.
(grunting)
Capri: Oh please.
What?
Kill me now.
No!
Susana, get my kit.
But he's pumped with spider toxins,
- he doesn't know what he's saying!
- Miss Mercer, Capri is dying!
(Capri groans)
Can't you give him something?
To cure him?
Leon: No.
To help him.
He's right, Loren.
It'll take a few moments, okay?
(Capri groans)
(Capri sighs and whimpers)
All spiders go to heaven.
Didn't I read that in your book?
Please take my samples back with you.
I would like this species
to be named after me.
Henri Capri.
I'll make sure.
(squelching)
For God's sake, let's go!
Leon: Let's go, now!
(squealing)
- For God's sake, let's go!
- Step back, now!
(Toe Boy in Native Language)
Leon: Susana, run!
(squealing)
(in native language)
(squelching)
(squealing)
(gunshots)
Let's go!
(squeals)
(gunshots)
Enough!
No! This thing's not killing
any more people!
Come on!
(growling)
Valentine: Susana!
Wait! Wait!
Shit!
- Susana: Get me out of here!
- Hey! Hey!
Get me out of here!
(Toe Boy in native language)
Shit! Help!
- (squealing)
- Leon: Ahhh!
(in native language)
(squeals)
Get me out of here!
(Leon screams)
(squealing)
Susana: Help me, please.
Mercer, I need some help.
I got an idea.
Okay, break it.
- There. Come on.
- Okay, retreat.
Where's Leon?
Leon?
(growl)
Susana: What is this place?
Valentine: Must be left over
from the war.
Okay. Check all the doors and
windows.
(rattling)
There's a storage room or
something back there
but it's locked.
We can't get in.
Mercer: Where's Toe Boy?
I was just thinking,
I've never faced anything
that I could not kill
with a loaded gun and now,
I don't even have that,
I've got a 45 and a half a clip.
Valentine: What about you?
About the same.
I still have four rounds.
(clanging)
(growling)
(groaning)
(clang)
Aww!
(loud squealing)
Ahh!
(squeals)
(groaning)
(heaving)
(loud grunting)
(groaning)
Ahh!
(squeals)
Aww!
(growls)
Uggh!
Susana: Where is it?
I don't know.
It didn't penetrate much
but I'm not sure about the venom.
I'll be okay.
Just sit down and rest!
I'll barricade the windows
and the doors.
Can you work an M-16?
You better believe it, sugar.
Good.
(Valentine shivers)
How are you feeling?
I'm cold.
I've got a fever.
Thanks for asking.
Anything interesting?
I don't know.
Let me see.
Spiders are susceptible
to drugs and toxins.
Maybe there's something
in the med kit?
You think you want
to get close enough
to that thing to give it a shot?
I don't know.
If you come across anything
interesting let me know.
(crackling)
(thwak)
Mercer: Quick Susana,
get off your butt!
Now! Go!
Go!
(groaning)
(squeals)
What's it doing?
I don't know...
(squealing)
Mercer: But we can't
stay here.
What about the back room?
(squealing)
Shit!
Ahh!
- Are you okay?
- I'm fine.
You're the female
equivalent of Tarzan.
Jungles, I do fine.
Small rooms and big spiders
are a problem.
(heaving outside)
What? I'm not dead yet?
No, but you will
if we don't get you out.
(panting)
I don't hear it.
Mercer, do you think it's gone?
I doubt it.
I don't see it.
Take it easy, Susana.
Take it easy.
It's not out there.
Great, now take it easy.
For God's sake, I can't stay in here.
Yes we can, Susana.
- It's gone. Look!
- For God's sake!
(squealing)
Susana!
Ahh!
(screams)
(squealing)
- (thud)
- (Screaming)
Fuck you!
(spider squeals)
(blast)
(loud squeal)
Aggh!
- (bang)
- Christ!
Shit!
(bang)
Look, look!
- Mercer: What?
- Valentine: It must be a way out
for the war. Open it!
(bang)
Mercer:
Ahh! Are you coming?
(spider squeals)
Ahh!
Come on.
Aggh!
Mercer: This way.
We're clear.
Okay. Okay.
I got to rest.
Just for a minute.
Awww!
Oh my...
Man's voice: Loren...
Mean and extreme, Loren.
I've been waiting for you.
What took you so long?
Joli...
Uhh!
What's wrong, Loren?
Don't you like the new mother nature?
(screams)
Oh, shit.
What happened to you?
Ran into my man back at his village.
He picked up your trail.
Did you get anywhere on the radio?
No such luck,
interference everywhere.
Mercer: He's got a fever.
Where's the rest?
Something back in the jungle...
killed my brother too.
I want it, Bear.
(gun clicks)
I want it dead.
That's why me and my man are here.
Aww!
Hey... hey.
Okay, I'm going to leave you this.
- No.
- Just take it.
I'll be okay.
Don't worry.
I've got her covered.
Hey, the next time you need a pilot,
don't call me.
We'll be back for you.
Hooray!
Semper fi, me and mine.
(Mercer laughs)
- Go, let's go.
- Yep.
(snap)
Bear: What in the hell?
No, That's it.
That's the cocoon.
Mercer: It's in molt.
Bear: Molt?
When they come out of those things
they're usually soft.
God, it's breeding.
Look at all those eggs.
I'm going up.
Hey, hey, going where?
I got to take a closer look.
Cover me, okay?
Shit!
Okay, it's in here.
I am going to try and get it down.
Mercer: When I do,
give it all you got.
Shit.
It's not working.
Oh no, Bear!
Bear, it's waking up!
Oh my God, Bear!
Bear, get out!
Bear, get out of here!
Ahh!
No Bear!
Oh my God, Bear!
Ahh!
(groaning)
(spider screams)
Bear, no!
(spider hisses)
Ahhh!
No!
(spider groans)
(in native language)
Shit!
(spider squeals)
(spider crackling)
(squealing)
(in native language)
(clank)
(spider screams)
(sighs)
Fuck!
(Mercer whimpers)
(heaving)
(spider squeals)
(snipping)
(Mercer whimpers)
(groaning)
(loud squeal)
(grunting)
(spider squeals)
(whimpers)
(spider roaring)
Shit!
No fucking way!
Aggh!
(ripping)
(crackles)
(spider heaves)
Fuck!
I hate spiders.
Take it easy.
- Is it dead?
- Yeah, it's dead.
Okay. Let's get
the hell out of here!
Come on.
(heavy breathing)