Which of the bikes should we load up?
Actually none of the bikes. Just the boxes, thanks.
Alright guys, I'll be downstairs if you want to grab a drink later.
You're already in L.A.
You never came back.
I try to think about tomorrow.
Does it hurt?
You tell me.
-Hey. -Hey.
-I see you're all done upstairs. -Yeah. Off for the day.
No way.
-Jung? -You...you know this?
I do know it. Self-help or school?
Come on. Jung isn't exactly a recreational reading.
Individuality, consciousness, the dissolving into the crowd.
Yeah, yeah. Sounds like you're a fan.
I am a fan.
Self-help or school?
Recreation.
-So what are you drinking? -Pale Ale.
Pale Ale? Ok.
So...
I know. This is gonna sound weird
but, uh...
What are your thoughts on dancing?
-Are you ask...asking me to dance? -Well, it depends.
Are you looking to dance?
You're asking me.
Yeah. I'm asking you. Is that a yes?
"I would be a warrior."
Do you always ask strangers to dance with you?
Do you always lead?
I'm Jordan.
Spencer.
"and you would be a thief"
"but you would be a good thief"
"and what kind of warrior would I be?"
I'm afraid I'll forget.
I feel like I've already lost.
What is there to win?
If you're always afraid, how will you live?